<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mvbeckstrom @WhiteHouse And what gun control do you want? Most of these deaths are by Illegal guns!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolecimbura “The company worked over the weekend, and in about five or six days, Sarepta was able to synthesize… https://t.co/Xf5gfvg38N]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this season of the @BacheloretteABC ...@aaveni15 https://t.co/koKpBulNrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dutch impressionist, Willem de Zwart Medium: Oil on panel Framed: 10 1/2 x  13" Art: 5 x 8 Farm, barnyard scene, si… https://t.co/OTWj5Ue0XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know that feeling when your trying to finish homework and your eyes get blurry and your brain starts melting? I hate that lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the many tweets of folks sharing the harmful things said and done to them under the guise of “counseling” -t… https://t.co/KE1626SPKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family doesn’t like it when I talk about what I want in a funeral so @Alicia20M and I are just planning the littest funeral ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoapJenn That’s what I’m gathering based on posts I’ve seen on Facebook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the destruction of Pittman Wash - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/Td1woyXNpA via @Change #pittmanwash… https://t.co/kd6wlUKB0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys,  #StarWars is awesome and identifiable but it is a fantasy series. Some fans seem to fight about SW subjects… https://t.co/r2KKO78QUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scothawkins @washingtonpost And something to celebrate the birth oh Jesus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zamboni_bodoni If you came to visit me you wouldn’t have that problem 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Rebirthday , Kennedy!  And 11 years late, Welcome home, Brother!  Welcome home!  #XONR8Rs #blackbehindbars… https://t.co/jyJWS3S88e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diegopaulav Pero si de entrada planteo el ekipo a la defensiva,q mas se puede esperar de este mediocre..q hasta al… https://t.co/RnTDqNowcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest I'm from Alabama and I take it as being respectful ,but however these bots that be in your dm like hey ba… https://t.co/8gNMV2nCZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sillywithsad I also put the leg over the hip of everything lol. Cuddles at allllll times]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a match! Wawrinka🇨🇭 vs. Fucsovics🇭🇺 — 3.5 hours of fight. 💪🏻🎾👈🏻🌴👏🏻 #awesome #BNPPO19 #Stanimal https://t.co/l2OfBqWeAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @allinwithchris Really enjoyed tonight’s show on the US Mexico border. It was so interesting that my h… https://t.co/8RudBnxtua]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s great to be an Auburn Tiger but even better to be your friend. Wishing you the happiest of birthdays, flower c… https://t.co/GTs8Q1PSAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get really testy when people whisper amongst themselves about a fellow co-worker. They then leave the room to gos… https://t.co/PCaOR7Uwzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“An address by your favorite president, me!”   The irony is just too damn funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts u broke and stingy as fuck if u don’t tip at least 20% everywhere you go. Bad service or not have some manner… https://t.co/adN25LARyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erniebjorkmantv -A “juvenile “ delinquent “mountain lion” https://t.co/trfczjBy5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wavy lone wolf beats 🛸🐋⛓. #darkbeats #darkbeat  #instrumental #producerlife #untaggedbeats #losangelestrap… https://t.co/xzcmy94oKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bihhh she’s does it again @iamcardib “Please Me”video out today y’all go peep it that hoe is 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm good to see you inherited your fucking lying gene from your father 🤔asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[How topgolf shifts boutta be when they dont close till 2am then our asses gotta be back there at 8am]]></document><document><![CDATA[the nhl: who gonna check me boo? gritty:               🖤🖤           🧡🧡🧡        🧡🧡🧡🧡            🧡        🧡  👁 👁  🧡… https://t.co/C0b8RTsbnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@club4growth @ClubForGrowth @RepMcClintock @RepMcClintock sold us out in #CA04 for his special interests  Cap on SA… https://t.co/74PKSLGLoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I drop something I mumble to myself “nice Katelyn good one” and it really be like that sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I am trying my best. To be social, to be kind, to be a friend, to give myself excuses to do things outside. But… https://t.co/eKyr5dBMlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be here at the CAS Awards, and so proud of our mixers who are nominees tonight! @ InterContinental Los Ang… https://t.co/NGcfm862W5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody will ever get that kinda  love from again &amp; that’s on me. Only apologizing for if you thought i gaf .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Ruby is a force ! Every meeting or chance encounter with her always leaves an imprint. I feel thankful to learn… https://t.co/zSPoZNm0I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FanSidedDDT My Reaction When I See Kofi Kingston Is The # 1 Trending Topic. This Is #BlackExcellence At Its Finest… https://t.co/vV4qYSnpUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilminmeow @LaloElizondoTV Mi punto es, que se están enojado por algo a lo que no le deberían de tomar importancia… https://t.co/GB8j5yVwUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 He’s always had diarrhea. But, it’s been diarrhea of the mouth and constipation of the brain. I said… https://t.co/5DYeaFRUFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntDior Hi Buddha, we specialize in Design and Developing excellent Mobile Apps (iOS and Android)!   Please take a… https://t.co/FjO3lgOVav]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love doing everything when I’m drunk so I can blame it on the alcohol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Shreveport, LA, check out this job: https://t.co/MYko0EdE9p #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkieSpaceQueen Furry little genius-monster-scientists... they are the best (and the worst, esp when food-motivated… https://t.co/mLQ4SHhaiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally me especially cause I’m talking all these psychology classes. I’m the family shrink now]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have ourselves a game in the AA Finals, BK Girls lead @mvogtpenfield 26-23 at the half. Highlights tonight from… https://t.co/rEfyyLs4rY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 29th birthday might have been the best! Thanks @BrettJackson21 for making it special! 🎈🎉🎂 https://t.co/I9CH4pKkn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xogiselleeee igual con usted.. pero también muy pendeja.. you’ll get there one day 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THETimHaynes @JamesCraigmyle @GreeneCountySO @PhatScoot https://t.co/hKI2ZATQA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @talvarez2 on your Pillar of the Profession Award!! You represent @NASPA4W so well!! #NASPA19 https://t.co/BNkgLLIJ2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my #thinman movie marathon Saturday! The wind which knocked out the power has died down and power is finall… https://t.co/HVG6NHXlIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexieYORK_ Thx lex . I just hate green tea 🤪 wbu coffee? U have a fav ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulwasher I don’t know why I need assurance everyday, but thank you brother Paul! God Bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro Tuesday with Flooring Associate Angel and Flooring Specialist Kci teaching the class on measures at… https://t.co/7rrVoPgQFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceymeis @RealKyleMorris Neither does a signature but I still cherish the person who signed their name!! You Rea… https://t.co/usqFZyH2Dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the helicopter if do we need to have like the blades on the top like I mean we have planes flying without blad… https://t.co/ptV5ZQm3st]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJustinFabus @DonnieWahlberg @JennyMcCarthy @GenRescue It was wonderful meeting you last night. Safe travels and… https://t.co/xUOqv3qnfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brabul @ladyrasta Tbm. Mas ainda assim achei válido compartilhar pra quem ainda tem estômago pra acompanhar aquilo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9thWardNuawlins 🤣 It’s the hardest part of this cancellation for me! Gotta change my whole vocab!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corey_Feldman @jojoclap_1 Corey you have helped me so much over the years. I fully believe n support you. Brook Sh… https://t.co/57XDdFiinU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah! Let’s go Tone!!!! Congrats!!!! @aahunter29 @DurangoHSHoops @LV_Knicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harp &amp; gear are packed for travel; 🐱 is standing guard. https://t.co/oVnoreDGxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosgilman It’s Been Difficult.I’ve Become More Tired Each Day.Having All My Little Furry Best Friends Helps I Neve… https://t.co/sz7dFSNM0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW Rodan + Fields SPOTLESS Regimen Fights Teen &amp; Young Adult Acne | SPO... https://t.co/yoJSNYwNIe via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femlorepod I’m listening backwards and just got to Kakuarshuk, and I figured I should point out that there’s actua… https://t.co/dXyXvViiZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like your fitness goals, your meditation and daily affirmations only work if you make them yourself and put th… https://t.co/5KCXGLRp3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im trynna figure out why a nigga beefing with another nigga bout some pussy but got ME on his page.. like nigga del… https://t.co/ev6MO2bi2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I just saw Aziz Ansari at Hewing Hotel but i could be wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump That was beyond disgusting of you to side with a man who kills his on family.   If you… https://t.co/QTWK7JKd3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughing at one FB comment on GMA’s post about ArMaine.. “Aldub left the Earth, Move to Uranus.” 😂 but fans there a… https://t.co/WIjBXZKoIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illegal immigration cost the country one hundred and fifty billion dollars a year, the Wall in its entirety will co… https://t.co/AOZfWIXk4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[of the aristocracy to extract peasant surpluses encouraged them to try better methods; and the tenants also had inc… https://t.co/jMy2ZOI1LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight Baby 🎶💃🍻 At mstheater #funknla with @smith90008  #cameo #zapp #sosband #thedazzband #maryjanegirls… https://t.co/HzoJU92fET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special day special person and special celebration  Happy Birthday  Ccto  @mainedcm  / MaineTurns24 #Maine24th https://t.co/nTTarGJe5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJonCryer John &amp;Ken on kfi said today that the crime was way down in these countries an they come only for the money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[R4: I do-We do-You do slow release. I love showcasing what I can do FOR your students BUT also love getting others… https://t.co/yJBWmlXGR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SloppyYellow @jimmywaggs3 @Umatter_Waverly @TooToughToTame But you still need to come out West.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge THANK YOU to @codeorg @TeachCode @adafruit  @mymindSpark @DHLUS @Microsoft  @InfyFoundation and all the othe… https://t.co/jRRsI13VHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tourism in South Carolina is a $22.6 billion industry now. That's a lot of zeros ($22,600,000,000,000!). This is th… https://t.co/Qn7A6QzA2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this team... even if they’re crowding my shot. 😉❤️🎥 #dreamteam #working4you https://t.co/BVFuJyUA6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holler_lori Thanks Lori...Make it a great one. https://t.co/gycUCQdKhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall gotta separate Galaxy phones from androids lol cause when yall talking down on android phones I know yall mean… https://t.co/dAVFuVG1H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStoryShorey Is 146 going to be a nightmare this morning heading into Providence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stella is the sweetest creature I have ever known. #Caturday https://t.co/ZfWNh8aSu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t keep up with all my friends travels so travel safe everyone 🤪🥰 luv y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[i could only watch The Dark Knight for the rest of my life and i’d never bet tired of it because Heath Ledger’s per… https://t.co/5es7idhKbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Communist-Socialist Operated #WMUM, #WABE, #WJGA, #WSBRadio Won't  Although Mother #MaryGreer a #WSBTV and #AJC… https://t.co/1HpqV6SKJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“School administrators said they found small amounts of #blackmold at Sullivan North Middle and High Schools.”… https://t.co/6uf93axM3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts are a problem for liberals. @SpeakerPelosi @senchuckschumer @SenTedCruz @KamalaHarris @BetoORourke… https://t.co/PzHw9KMe6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[As in the overthrow of Sodom and Gomorrah and the neighbour cities thereof, saith the LORD, no man shall abide ther… https://t.co/eUT7PK2Xaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This description makes me think that Eastbound and Down didn't live up to its full potential...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get it our belly 🤤🤤 Says the #doubletrouble 👿👦🏻🐷👿👶🏻🐷 #BoBo #bobothemaltese #spoiledbobo  #DoDo #dodothemaltese… https://t.co/oEeynxqOm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJonAbramson @MattWalshBlog I agree some people probably shouldn't say some words.  But, that they can't? 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHenkelman @LinusTech Thank you for listening!! Linus makes it very easy 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe some of you will actually recognize this caption now 😂 #SoFarGone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really love both, but I just can’t get over the fact that Canes doesn’t have barbecue sause. Its blasphemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The committee has voted to move forward with the hearing. #MichaelCohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many people are in the news for endangering people or killing people by driving on dope. Why isn’t ruining your… https://t.co/IRgQvEOt2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: can i not feel like shit after working out Lactic acid:  https://t.co/A93yMUgyOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amos8125 @ZioKlint @EntropicBazaar E cmq dire che il processo di difesa dello stato è parte del processo rivoluzio… https://t.co/ItMPwYLjT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mah boos.. . . . #gettingtogetheratthebird @TimBlackmon @ The Dirty Bird https://t.co/89sZvQ6CxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolakPotrafi333 @SuzanneLepage1 @BleuAnnRN @lisiabrahao @dazerac @MMP__Dreams2 @LovelynHild @angelaa318… https://t.co/Z4PZil1yY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought 'Gel Adhesive for Nail Caps' on Purrdy Paws https://t.co/prWfufu9F7]]></document></documents></author>