<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Thats hilarious that reading and the White House in one sentence.. https://t.co/CkJNpsHe8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPloran Not out of the question for the union to have a bowling league— if they have time to ‘spare’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun end to a fun-filled day with friends from @stregismb #elitetravel #capturecaliforniaconnections… https://t.co/wtx6JtPsWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The republicans in the Cohen hearing clearly have the script from their propaganda machine, we can clearly see the… https://t.co/6LdXRfEmpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna stop complaining about the weather, Texas knows what it’s doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me a while to make #meditation a habit @kevinwgrossman but now I am hooked. I even use it at night when I w… https://t.co/0bm5bVKNka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClinicalPearl I have thoughts about this opinion of cheesecake.  And now I'm really thinking about the definition of pie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The party of hate defending the anti Semitic #WalkAwayFromDemocrats 🇺🇸❤️🇺🇸❤️Liz Warren Defends Omar: Calling Critic… https://t.co/rto81jOXAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY We are here and We stay! NoChill @SYFY @IDWPublishing Put our FAMILY back on the screen!!… https://t.co/6gVPCEJqEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farmer_Tom_UK Sharing a lovely walk with you and your sheep. So lovely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine ingraining the “build the wall” mantra into an innocent 7-year old like this. God these parents are gross..… https://t.co/CSmhojO8VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pouring in San Diego! A Flash Flood Warning is in effect for much of the north country. Widespread rain, heavy… https://t.co/HWu9YSy42f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concerts on snowy nights... I'm going to play this even if only two people brave the weather... Even if no one show… https://t.co/iLgUbSk0tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so quick on buying other people shit but hesitate the minute it comes to me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[E. Marie's Southern Style Spicy 🌶 Fried Cabbage🔥🔥🔥👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 #MyPotsAlwaysClickin DM for private dining / special event… https://t.co/LwWaQVLVbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeMama59870 @brianstelter Which is why I only referred to my last bowel movement..... Who knows what wonders and… https://t.co/YYhyi7mRWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garfep @SuckerPunchProd Welcome to the most beautiful state!! Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[***Work in progress*** when your friend agrees to design your dress for ainttooproudmusical opening and sends you f… https://t.co/3ruMnZ2hTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileyMariee_ did you get those stats from a follower app? i think theyre lowkey not true because some people deact… https://t.co/lMesasn9cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Applicant meeting tomorrow morning at 7:15am! In the CRC. See you there sophomores and juniors 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @CNN They've lost me. Cuomo always trying to curve reality into Trump being innocent coupled with th… https://t.co/qWCypI0zaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisPower1 @AOC And the baby killing. How fecking ignorant are these sub human stains?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregBoll Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE A VO… https://t.co/S5wToROAoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't see it and playing Fred Hampton ain't no easy task. I hope he gets the accent and mannerisms down pat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tah-Dah! Again, thank you so much, Lorena 💖😉😎 navarroelvia74 💋💋💋 -besthairstylistbarberwhomakes #housecalls… https://t.co/a9RyjPbgj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don’t understand how people don’t get what I’m talking about when I say this shit🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you just plan on seeing the Grizzlies, but you get an added bonus of seeing Peyton Manning’s interview, the ba… https://t.co/ufHoqGPeBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's executive order to bring back free speech on college campuses is bold and necessary move https://t.co/AzSLrTN6HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to the talking to some of the officers who helped save this man’s life.  Such powerful body camera video.… https://t.co/Xd0doS4eUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshZampich @RepDanCrenshaw @SecNielsen Trump was left with no choice but to declare a national emergency. Dems sh… https://t.co/8Hz15Ldvty]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ERA, I was obsessed with Orton,  Jeff Hardy &amp; Shawn Michaels 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelface927 @goale35 @CBSEveningNews @Jerickaduncan With that line of reasoning, there's no need to put him in p… https://t.co/MtBobgpXer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ianncaab chileeeeee ion even know you could look at him and tell he gay but had a whole girlfriend 😭 sis you just… https://t.co/Se9UMYRpAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m taking my niece and nephew to school tomorrow. And the funny thing is I can see the school outside my window. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I’m hoping that our new compatriots will settle for a moderate VP pick. That said, I don’t want Berni… https://t.co/zDeIwieZd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macasu Thanks for the follow Your profile statement is intriguing I followed you back, to see if your POV, is as intriguing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quien hizo esta playlist, posiblemente era fan de La Oreja. https://t.co/YadNWNuLO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a really good day and I thank GOD for his blessings. It’s been a rough year but I’m finally starting to s… https://t.co/5ZfZ6Dlrf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re having a long week and your local slice joint comes through with a record breaking 19 minute delivery 🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fã da banda the maine que não parece fã da banda the maine pq não tem coragem de se passar na internet desse jeito, entenda o caso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowtoronto Wish we could declare open season on him but we don't shoot dictators here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food stamps don't reload until the 6th. Can anyone help? https://t.co/RB4Ykd7v4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to light rain Saturday morning and storms roll through after lunch #inwx #storms #indiana #indy… https://t.co/GN46QWGGbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinwada I think he looked at Namors wardrobe and thought “hmmmmm Emma might like this”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob Playing around with polls this early doesn’t even make sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macdaddie415 @cnnbrk You mean you didn t believe a liar. Really. Trump isn’t on the stand. Cohen did. Trump didn’t… https://t.co/zHnRFm98kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenfry I'm reading this right now and had to jump on Twitter to see if anyone else thought the same thing. Wha… https://t.co/tJYnr2TPWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love children but if this little girl doesn’t stop kicking my seat I’m going to love children a lot less]]></document><document><![CDATA[i has the most perfect thursday: went to mod for a veggie supreme pizza, the went to Roseville for @lushcosmetics a… https://t.co/fVwneoTCPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many good shows in April, I guess I’m celebrating my birthday all month long 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Hulu,  It is 3am and I live alone. Please stop playing trailers for @UsMovie. I need to sleep at some point.  Thank you, Natalie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch The real trouble that I have with @sliccardo's efforts come down to audio recording in FFLs. That is ridic… https://t.co/ejCFB2vAka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debrakay23 In my house, this is known as "parrot could have red juice" expressed at every opportunity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LWLOttawa @JimWatsonOttawa @ottawacity @Foodthought Yes I am on it - talked to Korey yesterday directly and again this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be SO AWESOME if we could stop using WOC to shore up the deep deficits of white men. No more white men for… https://t.co/UN5UZiLm6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CristianFMendez Hahahahahaha I’m crying! I wanted to tag you you’re specially featured 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get off til 5 so these 10 hour days 5 times a week is gonna blow]]></document><document><![CDATA[#layla #artist #11yearsold #dietcoke #amazing #mygranddaughter @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/c6CA54a4G0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donnielover6 @DonnieWahlberg He surprised me I thought he was Cee Lo Green, congratulations on your win T pain 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnChardRE @w_terrence @JussieSmollett Where’s the DOJ????? And for that matter Where’s Ruth? https://t.co/YuR72vTWVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[FaceTiming with my bebe is always going to be the highlight of my day :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JerryFalwellJr just a bunch of haters with fake news sources in your mentions. They have no idea what they’re eve… https://t.co/FuInGnRPOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Golden Corral team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/MLkVCUlTVp #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish I was celebrating Vee Day by going to the movies to watch #FamilywithMyFamily I can’t wait to come ba… https://t.co/x8pdodAfCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 6 ARCs tomorrow and inciting campus is currently down.🙃  If you know what the means, please pray really REAL… https://t.co/leqeVbw7lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have to leave in 15 minutes for work and i’m still laying down. i’ve been telling myself “5 more minutes” for 20 minutes lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between the politics of the day and the horror of last night’s LIRR accident, I needed a moment of joy. Got it this… https://t.co/SEWl9HhBwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[People at Trader Joe’s don’t say excuse me they just slowly start getting too close, I don’t move anymore until they say it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2casey451 @mattbc @downhiller1976 Fifteen years working for a mid-sized international pharmaceutical company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato Congress can close down the emergency. So can the courts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el #DiaMundialdaRadio agradezco ese invento que me acompaña todos los días unas 15 horas. 🙌🏻 y mis favoritos, los de @WRadioColombia]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm designing a lingerie line finally... hope y'all like it &amp; support. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeanine_new @Valac666 @JeannaMarie32 @SharonG40210896 @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep… https://t.co/k2Sh7hkNHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second stop in our Showcase Tour! @DominionLcps #LCPS19 Thank you, Dr. Brewer and staff for hosting us! #LCPS19… https://t.co/3wAWpo9oNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS PHS F.F.A. AWARD RECIPIENTS!!!🤲🙏🙌 MAY ALMIGHTY GOD CONTINUE BLESSING YOU IN ALL YOUR FUTURE FFA AND… https://t.co/u8kXI7TjHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And in this administration, all the crises that we’ve had so far have been self-inflicted. We haven’t had one from… https://t.co/WHypWCO5ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation I have shared a purse with my girlfriends when we have gone out for a day of shopping, lunch and a mo… https://t.co/3wHnxDxpiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 🙌🏼 stop going back to the guy who doesn’t choose you every. single. time.   You deserve to be valued and loved… https://t.co/MNQiSIBQf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[some good ol bestie throwbacks, bc it’s been 4 months since the band was together. 🍒 https://t.co/yvg4EUIXia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gummies on the go! I’ve never been good about taking my vitamins (good thing I like veggies, right?) so before the… https://t.co/6ILx311s6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado It'll end past my bedtime. And I live in the Mountain Time Zone. Watching basketball or hockey instea… https://t.co/nCbRdpkhAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tRKNYGVevc I Love You Baby- @franksinatra enjoy... I have several times this morning this one!! WOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol niggas always wait until it’s too late to fix something they’ve destroyed. Go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrho_jrho Isn't it time to break your finals appearance streak? https://t.co/Q2Ul2hMhQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[And people wonder why catholics are leaving the church in record numbers!....this is outrageous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The toast strips called soldiers is such an English cultural thing! I have never cracked open a soft boiled egg to… https://t.co/zWtw5kAPsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathleenLights1 I’m a little behind on your vids, watching the full face of MILK makeup now 💗 @TheEverygirl_ has b… https://t.co/LVCpka0fCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizaNgufor @hipcated @thvgcess @khloekardashian the fact that Khloe kept forgiving him and his “community dick” i… https://t.co/KBYf5dJY4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[well you’re a stripper.. there’s a difference between shaking your ass and having to serve and attend to a group of… https://t.co/jmF90eltYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Caiturday night Eo1 💖  Credit to @Camilla68521063 #LoveForCait #caitrionabalfe @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/MPKOrNgmVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you get the feeling this is exactly what Trump wants? To be impeached or to resign. He’s messing up like craz… https://t.co/f5X7Bbjj0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTube Now y’all are demonizing vlogs of my favorite vloggers because their kids are in bathing suits?  I tell yo… https://t.co/d1JhjfEjeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetMaslin That said nobody does it better than @sonyclassics but that’s not the business @netfkux is in. And Rom… https://t.co/YnHroJENGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just going to put this out to the universe. I frickin' hate VeriCite. I get heart palpitations each time I subm… https://t.co/4ERZtvfhA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp #RenewWynonna @WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing @emtothea @MelanieScrofano… https://t.co/xplDLlijX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudeDarkmoney It is not a direct correlation because the feed value is not lost it is just turned into high protei… https://t.co/iiWIJPZnEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night dinner 🥘 yummy 😋 Beef smothered Oxtails w/sting beans, black eye peas and broccoli and cheese @ Los Ange… https://t.co/4h2q8eysVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msgicebaby Me too ! I can't imagine standing there in front of 20,000 people looking at you . He's so amazing and… https://t.co/8PuC3TZoRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgWriterArk Oh yes — but it got fixed and all is well (except my wallet) Live and learn &amp; check the basement when it it rains]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hop Rocket by @octopibrew @ Ruby Owl Tap Room — https://t.co/bIjPo3LfeR]]></document></documents></author>