<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WillingBlam working on a fjord....see you Saturday and Sunday. https://t.co/lLoopYWDvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part about waking up on the weekend is watching supercar highlights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our March Special! Trial program valued at $250 for just $59.  Call or visit today!… https://t.co/s5L2Tn2c69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb @sambassartist Very nice Jeff  He was the kindest Caring man I ever met.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky holds a 12-11 lead at the under 12 minute timeout. The Tigers are starting to catch their stride as they’r… https://t.co/YHJCEpDClr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are we doing to protect the children?  What are we doing to provide them justice?   In the new era of #MeToo a… https://t.co/Fm9ic0NQSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colorme_quin I do not understand you. I think farts are funny and I don’t know what being white has to do with any of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Charlton Not the first time he’s hit the floor because of Willie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSparrow3 @manny_ottawa @Puglaas Let's not forget that Philpot tried to stiff taxpayers for campaign work by ove… https://t.co/ZwGRBEIZoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxavierfilho Entendo. Eu só vejo de uma forma que a própria punição em si, talvez nem seja a palavra mais adequada… https://t.co/zCFKMmOj3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah ha! There’s my capecodtimes! #capecodproblems #snowmageddon @ Cotuit, Massachusetts https://t.co/lTPAaP0odO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl But, I thought the Orange Ass Clown ran on ending 'stupid wars'? Why increase military spending then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/kySsAok0bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong!! I fucking hate Cocaine. Hate it!! It's just I love the smell of it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job again Jerkoff Ohio Gm closing 1400 jobs lost on top of over 1000in 17 keep it up goof you’ll start taking… https://t.co/hdzOjAKFlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NobleSpencer Learning to get in touch with, and be honest about, your feelings and needs. And being with someone w… https://t.co/mwYfdT3RaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMessyCar @jimbro83 @CatherineSalo20 @grati2d @charliekirk11 @POTUS I don’t know what you think because you don’t even know what you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseysas826 @TrishelleC What was your point of telling her that or taking the time to find that out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coogs strand 2 runners, trail 9-1 after 5.   Battery also dying so that may be my last baseball update today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC To demonstrate that you truly understand, please explain what was antisemitic about @IlhanMN's remarks.  Be specific.  We are waiting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayInslee Better yet ask how many Americans are ready to give up their SUV’s ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/l834hfy5Yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezraklein Maybe if we avoid identity politics altogether especially the minority groups the majority groups wouldn… https://t.co/qezHmTVIOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could totally see having maybe 2 extra people visit at the hospital but 6?! Y’all are wild. This is not la marina… https://t.co/Tbf6GDMjOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamborghini Huracan Evo Spyder revealed ahead of Geneva Motor Show - Roadshow https://t.co/Y9P9fmW4MP @cnet-roadshow https://t.co/xnAOBFxOt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is fine, I guess, but at some point you'd like to see a guy show some significant improvement]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will forever love this clip and will always need more. From every sport.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_landale I think we win comfortably. They dont have the defensive tenacity of LMU or USD. And they certainly c… https://t.co/Kq0J2dAbrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobProvince @JamesAALongman @ABCWorldNews She made that bed and can sleep in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theamandaread Here's the number one reason and number two reason Kim won't give up the nukes… https://t.co/q7ZvJUFYxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#junktx #rockband #dirtydeer #dirtyfest #dirtydogrockbar #sxsw2019 @ Dirty Dog Bar https://t.co/TrXxw7yMnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kylep0wers Lol someone posted this pic the other day. Meant to share with you. https://t.co/XqJFp9sl13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenacupcake @topshelftyson Pee and coach k counting the money they are making off of Solos not answering https://t.co/uhmzlU5jkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGalt_Dagny @Paul27560022 @JoesGuy @minniefirst @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/2CnOM5muvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobileHelp No wonder why Tmobile wont support eSIMs they make $25 bucks from SIM cards. Just had order one from amazon for $9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtobis @GretaThunberg It is far too weak, but complying with it is still progress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristenrudd I guess that's better than Starbucks, but I'm a coffee-should-be-hot advocate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah nirvana ⭐  #tomnedreb #mustang   #kurtcobain #nirvana @ Youtube https://t.co/8lOf23LsAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Russian Cultural Reference by @oneworldbrewing @ One World Brewing — https://t.co/24IqdrDCfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence You sure it was an accident. You did puss off a lot of democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenny__i Haha thank you my love!!! ☺️💖🥰 Excited to share the others, which only you’ve already heard! 😎🙌🕺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drodostudio Big fan of Autochess! I want to make a website to display MMRs / Rankings - Do you guys have any APIs… https://t.co/jmJ66kWIld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtreze_poker @Ikagoryk @mafia_summers Moro na Praia, Complicado, ainda mais aonde o Estado Vivo é cheio de Lagos e… https://t.co/4EfzMH1xNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyQuick @SquawkCNBC @CEOMikeJackson @elonmusk Thanks for the great discussion with Mike Jackson this morning.… https://t.co/8ZKvEVXJsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PromoKitchen A1 - I never fail.  No, srsly tho.. one time (not at band camp) I spent a lot of money doin specs for… https://t.co/0GFikzaDrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gonzalezboxing #Tempe #boxingtraining #tempeboxing #boxeo #boxinglife #ASU @ https://t.co/dnRVncc6Zo (John Gonzale… https://t.co/fgBJ5JkXfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[61:54 back to L&amp;LD. Was just a jam in the middle. 64:34 end song. End set.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some, not all, of the worst U.S. presidents were Andrew Johnson, Nixon, Lyndon Johnson, George W. Bush, and tRump.… https://t.co/Fg0QaHnanr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning @ATLHawks fans. Please let this sink in. Trae-mendous. @TheTraeYoung]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertJohnDavi 🇺🇸 The reason we are in this position of the left being in existance, is solely on the hands of all… https://t.co/SFr3ZhtZPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISPEvansville Watch out for the kiddos. Have a great Monday Sarge. https://t.co/7zZYlMmUeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeBasner @ecq023 @ronwade Ausmus played for Detroit when they still played in Tiger Stadium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP While y’all applaud the ramblings vomited from your dictator’s mouth. What would Ronald Ragain say about @GOP,… https://t.co/iE0m5tgqaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save the date for our ACM Gala!  . Interested in supporting the museum through a Gala sponsorship? There is one wee… https://t.co/pKPu4jcnf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 in Colorado has past and I’m already feeling like I’m living my best life. I haven’t even got to the slopes yet.💜🏂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes a lot of effort to be this stupid.   And judging by the comments, there are loads of folks more stupid tha… https://t.co/bMeoMkyoc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prensagrafica En tiempo de elecciones,  aumentan los asesinatos en el país. Ya sabemos ahora quienes dan las órdenes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And of course I discover this after I buy tix...and the price goes down!! 🙄😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray my future kids come into the world healthy, it’s so much that can go wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redhead4645 @Jali_Cat @POTUS Did we get the results from the Mueller investigation? If not how do you know that th… https://t.co/r1kWalxPIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pimp_CSGO You and @seangares need to be featured during more matches! Great speaking voices, even better knowledge… https://t.co/2BYpA3LvUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuggetpalooza I was lucky enough to ... I’m stunned at this news. Sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seazoo jaunty Welsh band. Very cool. @ Dirty Dog Bar https://t.co/94IiR2ZIQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s outstanding that @FoxNews gave @realDonaldTrump debate questions before the presidential debates.   The commit… https://t.co/8GhgmonZdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can barely beat my girlfriend in Tetris now I gotta lose to 99 people I don't know? Sounds good to me! Shut up an… https://t.co/CTBZYIN79w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone drew this portrait of me in a course today as part of an exercise. It was draw the person next to you in 60… https://t.co/ISdChwFh4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reprobate79_ @Colteastwood @JezCorden @JamesWa82830654 @kidsmoove @Rand_al_Thor_19 @Dealer_Gaming A troll with 1 f… https://t.co/e6oVcjed7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evan_P_Grant @ChrisCBlake Ha, i think it’s a good practice to ask Skip Bayless not to say what he thinks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact y’all be having the time AND energy to be hating on somebody amazes me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @pugnaciouskvz1 @realDonaldTrump Damn Donald you don't go to a gunfight without bullets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mirror mirror on the wall who’s the racist of them all / you are Harris you are/time to put your walking shoes on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kemji @AskTrillAC It's both sided but the topic is mens preference. And yes a grown ass real woman wouldn't be mad… https://t.co/4ykUypD4B8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Berlin, a city with just double the population of metro #Richmond, will spend 45 times more on its annual transit b… https://t.co/GnO4TBBzC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz  just looked up the word reprehensible in the dictionary and look what came up? People in glasshouses sh… https://t.co/iJG4PGbhFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind fuck when ur tricked into a cult.. socialist business of other logical idoits forcing ur gender other bullying behavior..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRN3 @BrianPaulStuart @HillaryClinton Trump can’t get his feet out of his mouth to wear those shoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was out running 4.02 miles with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/YsyTM9kLRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porfin lists para un short stream 😑 #devilmaycry5 #twitch   Link in bio @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/XYOvJJoYjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Hollywood, Florida https://t.co/vjcn7C1RJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[From my own Seattle scene to The Orwells, Swans, up to Chris Brown, the sad indie boys and the confident party boys… https://t.co/JqUVwAGbqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@lukeburbank manages to summarize the whole of Twitter in 50 characters. Impressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJohnson_Jr Setting up a Venmo to find Jack and Frank’s art school degrees]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to the gym on Valentine’s Day, all the single ladies will be in there instead of at dinner https://t.co/XV4B0El1k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a Great Day. #gracelinette #jeremiahandres @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/9scEHluHPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveSchreiber3 @RL9631 @AsiaTater @Wblscott1 @AnnThacker2 @cheriseguilfoil @grannyanon1969 @Aug1405 @Lathenerd… https://t.co/ozIcIC94cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSHunter71 I’ve had the privilege to meet David two times now and he’s everything you see here.  I eagerly await our next get together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhurtissPerry @ParkCrossingFB @TFootballGeek @Madhousefit @CoachJonesRB @DatDude70 @ChadSimmons_ @JohnGarcia_Jr… https://t.co/HSluDq08yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just beat DMC5, that shit was a fucking jackpot. Good job @DevilMayCry for giving me the game I've been waiting so long for 👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhettRamsey That’s what I use to do but I watch now just to hear the stupid things he says to get a good laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RugbyCanada @USARugby Sad for the home side. We seem to be losing now, at the end of the game. Better than getting blown out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-Bush ethics chief: @GOP lawmaker @mattgaetz 'should be arrested' for witness tampering https://t.co/5HPcJvY43D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBeatonBulldogs @mrs_degraw @mssavoni @MrsStewart3 @meganseal1 @LjuljS @MrPolitis @mruttley1 @MrStLouis1… https://t.co/3yRsMasYc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgoold @stltoday I'm afraid that this will just complicate things, and we just don't need that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg Other than seeing his name on tweets that young William post I have no idea who he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet my new friend Leo. Leo lives in Phoenix now by way of Michigan, Chicago, and Baghdad, Iraq. Welcome to the… https://t.co/K1k3ycSD1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago So toni is a Lesbians as well she can't hide it is written all over her face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieSims13 True, but not the point (there are, as of now, no women in USAF Special Forces)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howaboutafresca @SwollenDome  Following Kareem Abdul Jabbar's lead, Robert Kraft is also selling four of his rings… https://t.co/mZg1JUR7tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partymuscles @realDailyWire @KassyDillon Yeah? How many votes did he get in the South?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Watertown Brewing Company T-Shirt! #giveaway #win https://t.co/7SxSzfKp4h]]></document></documents></author>