<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I really don’t be trying to snap but damn sometimes i just wanna be left alone yo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @RatlSecurity! Aussie listener here. Thanks for featuring my origin country in the pod today. FYI the news in A… https://t.co/IbCPgh2RL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYT reporter responds to Trump's tweet: That's a lie  https://t.co/gGezStWuNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to start the @ACOGAction Legislative Forum with @mpcohenmd!! @ACOGAction #2019CLC #AccessIs https://t.co/noWL7Y0xRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Kris Kuksi’s bday party with Iveta @ Merchants Pub &amp; Plate https://t.co/P2WfpdenWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO HITTER ALERT in district play vs Plano East. Pay attention to McKinney Boyd Bronco Softball Team. A special shou… https://t.co/il76AUPhwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has it ever occurred to you that that's how she feels whenever you come home and tell her all about the dangerous t… https://t.co/Enaxerahol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBtruthteller Man!! Folks cant take care of their stuff but want to compete and travel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an Instagram crush. When I met him in real life I asked for his IG. (You didn’t follow back so f*ck you. 💀)… https://t.co/5lGozc6hkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caller to 911 says his toenail hurts and needs it removed....  ummmm, ok....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost 3) Which is strange in this modern time, we have good translators. Some American medias really got… https://t.co/LqhUYR0Yod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissa_marr I had a heart attack in 2014. Meds helped me survive. But I haven't written that much in a week. Mayb… https://t.co/jvVRJVpVNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skull6394 @AKrell_media Nope. And I heard Giants gave long term offer too but CA taxes are insane and would make t… https://t.co/Z3P1JE1INP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheleChabin1 @SamHeughan The Coaches did the Stratosphere Sky Jump! Ad video below!  In SkyJump 2018 YouTube… https://t.co/0qUupmWoyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was special. Thank you to everyone who came out to our #secretsessions at @techniquerecords to vibe and… https://t.co/AWSgUjOPx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize how much I wanted to go Australia until like 15% of my Instagram feed became photos of Australia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterhermannnet @laura_navins @ASHD159 I’m game for that because it means we’ll have more Cheryl Sussman/Martha Pl… https://t.co/lBwasncffR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cereal I eat every night at midnight is technically my breakfast for the next day]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone needs me I’ll be freaking out for the next hour bc @Keeiraaaa is prego!!!!!!! https://t.co/8DCf1wYDqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you not know that your bodies are temples of the Holy Spirit, who is in you, whom you ha… https://t.co/KlDURsIjN3 https://t.co/hYRA4ufaGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online @RueNahcMohr @iMikla @devoopes I want to try it with a reverb tank.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gearing up for the WIAC SWIMMING FINALS tonight by wearing my @JJWatt training shoes! https://t.co/34oWEtIBHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pediatrics Staff Claps Back at Anti-Vaxxers With Brilliant Custom-Made T-Shirts https://t.co/IE24Cff1sy #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video two ft. Taika, Jemaine &amp; my new fav vampire at the WHAT WE DO IN THE SHADOWS tv series premiere https://t.co/r1BoVebQWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2016 at the @crossfitgames, I won the most improved award. There were a few different reasons for this but one b… https://t.co/88TLChcMbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Hope somebody out there will take a pic of her using plastic straws, utensils and cup while out eating… https://t.co/twJwhH29UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a year I hope to be living in the best place on earth with the greatest person in earth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZombieTrev5k Wrapped a late-night Facebook live stream of snow. 1 hour drive took 2.25hrs to get home. Rewarding myself with pizza 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WILLOWOOD2 @PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @glammalg11… https://t.co/pt7PTARtEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTKarNa1 @SirPareshRawal Chacha go read the conventions first n then come argue.. ur problem is u r spoon fed prop… https://t.co/gKv2i7Afli]]></document><document><![CDATA[You: “I’m sorry I didn’t mean to hurt you. I love you so much babe. I promise I won’t do it again you’re not my sec… https://t.co/wb4c7YjqRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[On to the next one! Well done, Mavs!! 💛🏀🖤 @ Maize South High School https://t.co/lWJuWZqM2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top ten languages for successful business leaders. https://t.co/AzWRtcpKo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@engrJehanullah This is not a dating site and I’m offended by the question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaieye @ianoland I have a few others to add....ahem #bmarch although his tweets lately are on point...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delegateguzman @SpeakerCox @cToddGilbert @VAratifyERA @HalaAyala Women’s Rights are MORE important than any kind o… https://t.co/1QX5o3dFij]]></document><document><![CDATA[so late but @LittleSimz grey area is incredible. I'm blown away. Can't judge an artist by their name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruby slipper lips, ‘cause “there’s no place like home”😘   #KN #1920 #DaBaddestBearZ #finerzetas #FeelsGoodToBeHome… https://t.co/TNyzRb3H5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philquinn1 is Finding Neverland on Netflix? Because I can’t find it 🤦🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halcyonsparkles @BetoORourke Thank you for saying her name. Like Jim Lawson (only more so, as she's a woman), she'… https://t.co/aeW0gEtp8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out Luke Perry (52) and Keith Flint (49) passed away today  What the fuck this is so sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foxtrot44 And the flying Valentine’s Day cookies 💕... I window shopped hard that day lol https://t.co/yY6rkxGH1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s really asleep on my shoulder, i’m so 🤧 my heart https://t.co/J1hzdXAWqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siubhan_H @AcampbelTeacher @Zigmund_Fraud @Rosewind2007 @badzoot7 @KimPaddockASD @djt10 @JuliaHadley15 @SueQuez… https://t.co/IXnzC22L0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again this is me!!!!🤷‍♀️🏽 @ El Segundo, California https://t.co/lrpy9UpFsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá: "Nicole, ten cuidado por favor." Yo: "Mamá, voy a patinar no a saltar en moto." https://t.co/q1X0OmNYWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joellehyman that’s not the tiny finger size but the best color of the acceptable chiquito. also notable mention, the hoops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a friend that takes cute pics and videos of you at the bar lol https://t.co/TvC2ih1EcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/db90RoeNKT  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 644-33  What happens in Vegas stays… https://t.co/3EWfvQcJuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silentrunning12 @Krissy_Caster @scifiotica @MsAvaArmstrong @Sk8Gidget @Skadi649631 @VOCRadioRobDoc @drawandstrike… https://t.co/qrBy3mTp5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcalasanssuecia @romulusmaya @PatVauquier @camilagove @RedYorkshireTea @Cesare74486345 Muita extravasao pouca sabe… https://t.co/c7Oq99oj96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian She was drunk and he kissed her, that sounds like assault sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang cute. parents-01 #mirth #laugh #smile #comic https://t.co/IQhHeUTsSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday nights going to be so cold 😩😩😩😩🤦🏻‍♀️ gotta get my whining out now... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg We’re behind you Fred.  We mourn your loss and are fighting everywhere across the U.S. to get this job done. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadManBear_ @KermitDoesTweet @bayharding11 @MAJORsince92 All shots he might have you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe it’s that time again! Come hear about this awesome opportunity to see Democracy at work🇺🇸… https://t.co/z0Id7PdJQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran the stats and these are the results of my study  Crushes I’ve had: 10.35 mil People I’ve actually been into: like, 4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @booklover1226 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews-just… https://t.co/lfxuqBBLEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could @MargaretHoover be anymore gaga over @ericswalwell ... ish. Be a journalist not a fan. Can you say swoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost my motivation to do cardio workouts. Turned out I needed to do the workouts along with the video to get the… https://t.co/37sGkK4Max]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryIsFunny Just maybe making sure you're not "stuck in the mud"!?! 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing our #CobbLMS supervisor @hollyfrilot reading!! Our LMSs should read across the district together in the… https://t.co/clzGXbYV6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain Do[ooooooooooooo it no decision  why u be such bad boy make me sad I don't  want non discipline  man who do… https://t.co/U6b2aANGc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julian, Brad is keeping more than a secret about Wiley's birth mother. He keeping a secret about stealing Wiley fro… https://t.co/76F7Y4PUyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meredith, you're Alex's best friend. And he's mine. The fumes are measuring with my eyes. #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you realize you lost the 131 pages of crim pro notes because your PDF handout doesn't let you save the… https://t.co/G9w3IlULeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoelPaine You got it! Especially since you asked so nicely 🤗 Thanks for being a man who supports us women. The 🌍 i… https://t.co/wd5JNTkL5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raine_Thomas @andrewpyper Thank you so much for taking the time to share my post. Wishing you a wonderful day/evening!☺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally home. Had to get a bus pass downtown. Then stopped at Smith's. Got a ride from Louisiana and Lomas. Silly m… https://t.co/rP3glwZfth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UUWorld Big fail, y’all. There better be an even bigger mea culpa and doing things DIFFERENTLY in the near future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @MargaretJosephs say “Your husband is in the pool” or “Keep your stupid friend” is the highlight of my… https://t.co/UniwpGsPKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palaeofail @gwylock1 I have a great deal of admiration for Empress Matilda, but considering she couldn't even land… https://t.co/fARCNv57XM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_palazzolo @NJ_2_FL @Acosta @realDonaldTrump Acosta should NOT be allowed within a hundred miles of President Tr… https://t.co/GGntdSDqcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the workout 🏋️‍♀️ #gymrat #fridayfitness #lovingmyself #healthylifestyle @ River Oaks Gym https://t.co/Ccn4C214Mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fyibri1 @PattyArquette I lost my mom on Saturday too.  I still don’t want to believe it.  She was 88, but I was no… https://t.co/prjNzGICsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será q si viene @mbachelet y quieren tener para esa visita todo como q no pasa nada, y la señora si creerá eso o le… https://t.co/zrVz3pAPWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He is the brother-in-law of Nancy Pelosi,former minority leader of the U.S. House of Reps and its… https://t.co/8FI5tDOzLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit Deja Vu Boutique (@Shop_DejaVu) in Mount Airy, MD to snatch this red getup 💋 —— gown: @Shop_DejaVu  photog:… https://t.co/KaHXjelbV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fasten your seatbelts, it’s going to be a bumpy ride!! #thelmaandlouise @ Dallas Love Field https://t.co/KHwgzXdYUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last #lotd for #bsbvegas #ootd #fotd #vegas #lasvegas #backstreetboys #bsbfan #bsbfanforlife #backstreetsback… https://t.co/s1IQOP5GA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am living proof  #dreamscometrue I was in #Hollywood #BeverlyHills #BeverlyHillsHotel #SanDiego I was guided to g… https://t.co/WTEeHBqNkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @dbongino Never look toward evil - - to find justice.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who don't know, Amberly was an 11 year old who's precious little life was taken Friday night/Saturday mor… https://t.co/QAP1yT0VOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniellin AHAHAHAHAAHA honestly I sound like that to my sister sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytpolitics @ddale8 ⏩Perhaps #Trump inspired b/c DJT wants libel laws to be more favorable to him, so he can destroy the hated media. #ETTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you work in K-12 education in the Raleigh, NC area?  We would love to have your anonymous feedback!  6 questions… https://t.co/KbOE3LTZDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpioli64 Sorry, that came off kind of smug. There's a really big difference between being popular on dating apps a… https://t.co/GtxwItmDbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are working together with hundreds of school teachers, nurses, and administrators at our #ProjectHere Summit tod… https://t.co/ar6yHaqhgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi @tarapalmeri It’s funny to read the comments from earlier yesterday, BEFORE it was shown that the vide… https://t.co/wI1FZOwpf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essa #WinterStorm flopada é só para acabar com o estoque de TUDO no super. É o Cléo Kuhn dizendo que vai nevar em G… https://t.co/hfykcyip4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st birthday @shannonmayw 🎉💞😻 Have a fun day!!! #swooshbday #cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Likewise, it's fascinating to watch people pick and choose which atrocities make one an "enemy of the US."  China i… https://t.co/PGcdvXMmn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My my my, look what showed up in the front yard @ Northeast Tampa, Tampa, Florida https://t.co/lnuJTffGAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrgil77 @AustinTXSteph @gilstem Did someone say Queso?!?! I’m thinking of going to the Valentina’s event on Friday  Cc: @RoseMc99]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am loving the design of the space here at the @WomenTechmakers #WTM19 event. Psyched to be volunteering at the wo… https://t.co/1NPW8iYBvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's train is going out. Who's boarding? DM for a ticket to ride 🇺🇸MAGA KAG 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @gabryluce @SimySemsem @carolina_smal @TereOrt51687394 @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @Alcioni5… https://t.co/gJocCslPad]]></document><document><![CDATA[so a guy spent 50$ on food &amp; drinks today and gave me a 50 tip 😭😭 so fucking kind !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be invite to southern university’s junior day #GOJAGS https://t.co/Je6iBhj10R]]></document></documents></author>