<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just a bit of clouds but mostly clear skies.... So excited to have some sun even though it is still cold....… https://t.co/PFCzHYPDOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sweet 16” for Lady Bears 🏀 on the road to Avery Co 6:00; hear “live” https://t.co/n6lIk4QUWG AM 740 WPAQ; good luc… https://t.co/IDSNvaRbhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD #internationalwomensday International Women's Day is a worldwide event with a human rights theme, highlighting… https://t.co/tZDxGJS7zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my Emotes and Badges if you come and join Emerald's Green Frog Crew. https://t.co/LevdmfB4dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrBobbyBones ...but isn’t so NICE  to find that it’s still light out—at 7pm?? 🤩 More daylight=more playtime! (Well… https://t.co/YDbBmO2ukA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 Does anyone have any ideas or understanding if these drops? I’m headed to China on Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oklahoma gun bill to remove permit and training requirements clears House vote https://t.co/LbNWxBc4CP #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy it’s Balto’s 100th birthday. Also his story is really sad and he and his mates were wronged but he ended with a… https://t.co/Tv3EDl60cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to the point where I spend majority of my days gettin high, sleepin &amp; playing the game 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DougJones do you agree with your fellow Democrats that mothers should have the option of killing the infant once… https://t.co/gKUSXOxZ6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get a ride to the vet... and don't have to go in! #win #windinmyface❤️ #tresperrosatx #healthydogs @ Griff… https://t.co/d8nbFnDGf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBates @seanhannity Why would an attorney discuss one client with another one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 12:3 King James Version (KJV) 3 And I will bless them that bless thee, and curse him that curseth thee: and… https://t.co/mtVdAS0zpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5. I have no issue with that. There are usually aspects of a job that are mundane or boring. I like to know what p… https://t.co/ubKmXERrlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 weeks until photos🔥📸 3 weeks until Ireland🇨🇮 7.5 weeks until tryouts🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: @CCPS_LibertyHS 37, @CCPS_WHS_OWLS 11. @Connorjstew leads the Lions with 12 points and @lilgiles_ has six for the Owls. #CVHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[mar 5- Sweeney Todd 5.5/10 i dont have anything against this show i honestly think it would be super fun to do/see… https://t.co/I7Jo3oGDVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solidarity and Shabbat Service Orange County #marchforourlives @ Costa Mesa, California https://t.co/KmATmzVy8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe this is me being a mom, but I think play should stop when someone loses their helmet. They wear those for a reason. Not optional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a “mutually obsessed with each other but in a healthy way” kind of relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSopranosClub @immatureAMRCN When Tony killed Chris...His eyes looked like the devil...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You CAN’T live RIGHT if you don’t think RIGHT. #guardyourthoughts #youareyourthoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacque_shepherd Meanest people I’ve ever worked with! Not a single person talked to me. I got there at 1:45 and co… https://t.co/WFS9VLuhCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[back 2 back for the ppl who didn’t get the memo 💍🤣❤️🤞🏼 https://t.co/60wfuMsuAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson Please leave her alone. Her mouth will make the Dems look so bad. The more they let her go, the better, Republicans are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@That_Guy_Stone you can be whatever you into fam and I’m not mad at ya but it’s annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaseyBoes I mean, what if it happened a few times? They run together 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trebienbeauty @AriesLaVey @commutergrl @for_pacific @BernieSanders Uh, sorry he was too busy saving a state and th… https://t.co/giFNiznAaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you say you can’t live without me then why aren’t you dead yet? @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/vS9ieOSMuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting parents and they wanted to show me the hard copy photo album from their trip to Italy. Pgs 1-3 start with… https://t.co/PXIU0VykOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not going to lie I haven’t started studying for my tests I have tomorrow because I’m really praying that school gets cancelled 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we date and you don’t love movie theater popcorn...that’s fine because that means more for me. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder The Back Starts to hurt oh wait I have scoliosis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binuhat lang talaga tayo ng filter 😂 Happy birthday my lil gorgeous friend. Happy 16th 🤘🎊🎉 gandahan ulit natin sa s… https://t.co/ytvCVLbyl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day, I couldn’t remember the word ‘mustache’ so I referred to it as ‘upper beard.’  That’s where I’m at these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna singgggg to my hearts content but I can already hear my brothers “shut the fuck up for once in your life” l… https://t.co/JwfbBppyNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJBHenderson Had a tough conversation last week with someone I greatly respect who believes that businesses are a… https://t.co/4vG8lrzuee]]></document><document><![CDATA[The consequences of ingesting too many prunes. #SignsYouNeedANewHobby https://t.co/pVyuRcZPYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraotaDigital En que libro o diccionario encontraría  esa definicion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I smile at you while walking and you don’t smile back I’m fr never gonna smile at you again and expect my rbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, YOU are!!✨✨ #selflove #loveyourself @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/TIlxnTnzlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me a v long time to fall asleep on the plane and some bitch in the row ahead of me woke me up to help her look for her AirPod?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever get tired enough to sleep but stay up anyways then get past the point of tired and can’t sleep anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jays 1st experience in the pool! He did some good kicking! Thank you photographer Elle. She’s a natural. Amazing to… https://t.co/BFtg3Y1ygv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jealous of all you lucky fuckers that got to see Metallica... you’ve been blessed by their presence😭💔 I hope all of… https://t.co/vrE1NMa5kP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needing to get my head back in  the game! I was doing wonderful, then M.G.B happened, then shit just went downhill… https://t.co/wR8crcPxGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vergas. Ya mero famosa pero ni cita para esto. lmao lmao just kidding asi no https://t.co/sIKPPlmGpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCMO311 @OneEyedz I hope you aren't replying to this clear photo of a car parked in the bike lane, suggesting that… https://t.co/mbl950Sqjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EloolyM @JT_Springston @Jim_Jordan There you have the words of JT, a person who really shouldn’t be allowed to have weapons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find out @TomHansensports finished off all the press box Mountain Dew  Bonus: when @zschneider218 finishes… https://t.co/bMi1YAxTP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made pasta with meatballs from scratch and I couldn't help myself before I took a picture https://t.co/UvDle4NbQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are Real Women Supporting Women in the Fight Against Heart Disease ❤  Learn more about our Mission here:… https://t.co/HI1wSN4JXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieRickert I've seen it done in coffee shops and it's not big enough to give people the space they need to hear. Yes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last lynching was in 1981  From 1882 to 1968, "...Seven presidents between 1890 and 1952 asked Congress to pass… https://t.co/RIpcU4DJTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandyknauer @BettieRose100 @thefishermon @gracie_e2016 @coffee_minion @Flashbakx @10MinutesaDay4U @dillman_diana… https://t.co/3gHO16pnOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PTnoSenado O carro da GLOBO passando no RJ🤣 #showdavida  #FUDERJ_BOQUETE_PINTO   NO RJ JÁ É CARNAVAL! #showdavida https://t.co/NYC4z2sxFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCUTCH22 Remmington 19...trying to be like his hero andrew mccutchen. https://t.co/m9gZFzQESg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure @_JazminA1_ this is you and my kids 🤣🤣 https://t.co/vM9x7SqfDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but I can't stand when girls cakeeee on their makeup. Like I don't know, I just don't find that shit cute 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warning: NEVER buy a “swappable” Pop socket unless you want to drop your phone every time you use it!!!!!!!!! HIGHL… https://t.co/t0k2q2cLqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov. Janet Mills today directed United States and State of Maine flags be flown at half-staff statewide from sunris… https://t.co/2yYgvWSwhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raytheon It’s not an https://t.co/bG8FXZ38On and update voter rolls,eliminate practices that lead to fraud such as… https://t.co/u7whWZHpaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[double tap if u think Sav shouldn’t graduate and leave me unsupervised @ Greenwood, South Carolina https://t.co/hW9fwTygsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niagarasays wow‼️ And, I just sent you a hug on Nancy Pelosi’s Twitter of her hugging Mexico’s President .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Facebook interview @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert. So glad I got to see it after I got home from my appoin… https://t.co/bICoiYVdrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayla_lela In a weird way I'm kind of the opposite. I like math but it's a little harder for me to understand. But… https://t.co/BkyLd7XpH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will really pull out their phones and record someone struggling instead of helping them. We are not the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump 300,000 die each year from obesity on drugs like Coca Cola, Twinkies, chocolate, candy, McDon… https://t.co/8oS0JEMJ3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cleanh2oaction Worst. Valentine. Ever.            Unless of course you are a fossil fuel company, real estate deve… https://t.co/04tUsjyQ2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the brills Douglas Kearney emitting, singing, shouting-- "shhhhhhhhhhh." 🌟 #thelouisvilleconference https://t.co/QWdMwjUaYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAZ0RFIST @tajjackson3 What was the civil suit for then? I believe MJ all the way, I just don't know as much about… https://t.co/EInFtRhEao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsSamG Yeah... I thought everyone knew your not supposed to do that 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny to me when other providers have automated emails so I know you recieved my reference email but several d… https://t.co/IEsTsOXgrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rkellymemes #rkelly 😂😂😂 #worklife #worklifebalance #random #randompost @ Anaheim, California https://t.co/cOiADMChYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to tee-hee. This "newborn baby" shoot is just too funny! https://t.co/Gn7XFPwg5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USABlanket I like to spend stormy days snuggled up on the couch reading a good book. @poisonsix9 @Smile7891 @joannaonthelake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissLizz Swear to God:  I sent “ I think someone just tried the front door. Not sure.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care who opens for fomo tour. I’m going to see the boys. That’s all I care about 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @robbieknox34 ! @BisonBaseball - Baseball Victorious in Pitching Duel Vs W Kentucky https://t.co/wPdWuyEbsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't prioritize your life, someone else will. — @GregoryMcKeown this episode arrived at a time where ever… https://t.co/MJz3ky6ELl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Greenberg, you are trash. To say “he’s a rock star, he doesn’t need to force women to have sex” is disgusting… https://t.co/tK3waZjE1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett Looks like someone didn’t get breast fed as a child. Just stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianMSweis Maybe an abstract version of this? https://t.co/UvTY6AlZsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@posivibeman I happen to have this old one as well which I inherited from my mother. His key to success- PMA, “posi… https://t.co/zeB478PYFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[butt tattoo and nose piercing both on my 18th birthday. starting off adulthood right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stone Tropic of Thunder Lager by @StoneBrewing @ BB's Pub N Grill — https://t.co/Xie8AfHaW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much @JohnathanJ_713 !!!!!  I appreciate it soooooo much!!! Great to FINALLY meet you:-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how there’s a whole ass kitchen and sink in this building, yet some of y’all are still disgustin… https://t.co/TDRbkhhYxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[صادرات نفت ایران در ژانویه افزایش یافت؛ ۱.۱ تا ۱.۳ میلیون بشکه در روز / رویترز: میزان صادرات ایران بالاتر از حد انت… https://t.co/s3o2xiiJPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already missing this magical place.  What is your favorite thing about Disney? . . . . . . . #magickingdom #disney… https://t.co/VLMtrkokVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coastal Beauty. #ArtOfNature #BeautifulBritishColumbia https://t.co/aPneKJKKEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great thread about algorithmic violence, and the reinforcement of privilege via the savage capitalist combo of sc… https://t.co/cYUs153gLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayouwilson Thank you for this, @bayouwilson ! My son started BCT 2/11/19. MOS is 68W. I don't have words to tell… https://t.co/DdDEDsFaye]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAYNE AGREED TO GET MATCHING SWIMSUITS WITH ME FOR OUR VACATIONS THIS YEAR 🤩🤩🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we stop using the word ‘self made’ when describing Kylie’s wealth? She grew up wealthy with a recognizable last… https://t.co/FNXYSWEZCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are places to surrender an animal, leaving them somewhere/dumping them is a crime and puts them in danger!  S… https://t.co/AGZCDrJEF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbycrianna Thanks beautiful 💘💘 lol we’re both still young af I was just on one😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of myself for planning Avriana’s party completely on my own]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! Luisa, #kindergarten #DualLanguage Teacher and #play advocate! So excited for tonight’s chat! #ECEChat https://t.co/ei7TMBytEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will always be a time where Into The Woods jokes are appropriate 🙌🏼]]></document></documents></author>