<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FrankFigliuzzi1 @YouTube @MSNBC @DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace Thanks Frank !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlmeyer1980 Should find an engineer/producer who can teach you what your "train of thought" really means in terms… https://t.co/SFWQQalxT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdavid_04 @jonsmithmusic_ @Jackie_flash We all better have City MD on speed dial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSAliciaD @ProSoccerUSAcom Good stuff @OSAliciaD ... Really enjoyed reading this this morning and also… https://t.co/B7K79JmKka]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would make people feel better about self-driving cars. You can see that the car does notice obstacles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC Mueller is who we care about only an idiot wouldn't  understand the Russians and Trump are the same… https://t.co/tpCc38XHA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerHageman in divisive times like this, at least we can unite on this issue https://t.co/V7h5s2gcR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaGalbra19 For sure, but there's also a lot of stuff that people should clear off of the internet. If someone… https://t.co/WVYfj2zuur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the article in detail..shoutout to whoever wrote. The internet thanks you. https://t.co/QrMGv1ttuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeTedSmith Great with soda, if on a budget even the Svedka is good...Cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferocious_snail @Ryzen_Studios The family would have also received the message.  It could not relay any tragic upd… https://t.co/oeX0s9pQBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HIVAIDSupdates @pozmagazine Really? Still, have not acknowledged my story and how it has been the leadership of th… https://t.co/Hbizq2UHHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day... Zander didn't get me anything, except snuggles lol. #catdadproblems #catsofinstagram #cat… https://t.co/VyzPaY1XKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyandreasen Most of the design of K-12 education as-we-know-it was built on horrific beliefs. As we try to reco… https://t.co/wAwrn9FzN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemoon_mua @PhiPhiOhara Simple unless you've fucked with me or someone i love tgen i dont care what you do or how or to whom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please close GITMO and bring those there to trial! Also, try those who went and fought with ISIS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After two periods, Dow is down 2-3. One period to go versus Big Rapids. Go Dow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayBlackDesert I’m having an issue where it is disconnected me from BDO servers. Before I can even log in!! HELP!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @LegionofHonor in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/3buVO98JOp https://t.co/H49s8ZbrdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dude I just got enchilada taste in my mouth!” Words from @TheBuckFuffalo this morning as he sparks up a cig!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gal ready for St Patrick’s Day - r u? Going live tonight around 8:30pm w/ ur SPD outfits - don’t miss (on my f… https://t.co/L89cM1i7kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well we've crossed the Rubicon here at my house! My little girl isn't little anymore. Proud holder of a Driving Per… https://t.co/0h2EA0OOnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc what anyone has to say I’m gonna figure out a way to get this Twitter, YouTube, and Twitch big one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad that our dedicated and vigilant media only focuses on the most important of issues. https://t.co/DFE9d42yr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronWrestling You gotta be good to pull off that pink singlet.  Thank God the coaches didn't wear theirs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought several hundred cards on an online auction for $2. Literally delivered in a paper bag. Had no idea what I wo… https://t.co/x732IOhwuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilJohnston @CaltransHQ @CHP_HQ @napsgfoundation Yep out of the box web app builder isn’t great on mobile, your s… https://t.co/vQk7bkisQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoePlenzler @EyeOnVeterans @kate_germano @KellySKennedy @RambaKy @JeannetteHaynie @coffeeshopjihad @kwilliams101… https://t.co/CXn9DTLiEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Am Happy To Announce That @expensiveglobal has officially secured our first Publishing Deal. I want to thank God… https://t.co/o8mKPkBFhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU MOVED THE GOAL POSTS FROM The price of weed to  THE EFFECTS OF CARCINOGENS ON THE VOICE BECAUSE YOU HAVE LUNG C… https://t.co/HPwqgy1ioV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElCipayo Y hay algunos de cambiemos que tienen mas... Es un problema de la casta politica  Todos impresionanteme te vagos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something nonpolitical to brighten your day: https://t.co/OamtFl2SVl (via @LaughingSquid https://t.co/o7HxOa7qKX)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaberuski Two hour head start but I’m basically single you have wife kids and new baby. You got balls like church bells]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raiders4life3 @AdamSerwer @texacojr1212 You can swallow his rhetoric all you want. I have seen amd heard enough to… https://t.co/fwsflNz5gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mission Arrr-ange IIPA With Tangerine by @missionbrewery at @missionbrewery — https://t.co/A41o88OZnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haircut + Photoshoot Bookings Open on my Website   💥Link N Bio 2 Book💥     #Barber #barberlife #barbershop… https://t.co/urVwJwvn4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSILN Contrary to what the radar says, no precipitation of any kind has fallen in Dublin, Ohio. I am a trained sp… https://t.co/d3Lh3ffE1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fry's Electronics in Woodland Hills, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/7IAYcQur6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't give three shits about either. Both are rigged and disproportionately biased.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner bells ringing in spring ball.... let’s get it #cakesareup #2for1 #stanggang https://t.co/iMogVsiMMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[75% chance my boss’ road rage is gonna get me killed. He pissed off this straight truck and they shot from the left… https://t.co/qqmJOXBe25]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I end up giving up on everything I just want everyone to know that @Phamino_ is probably one of the best “friend… https://t.co/STcV1hhHCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife of White House communications director pushes false anti-vaccination claims - CNNPolitics https://t.co/dR8dES88Rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano So it’s fine that people can just walk into our country.   What would do you tear down all walls????… https://t.co/reXvgEA3Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 6 episode 2... it’s like I just witnessed the first Easter Sunday, plus giants are so underutilized]]></document><document><![CDATA[@State_Champs Thanks for one of the best nights of my life you guys absolutely killed it! https://t.co/f00pNbQ0qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mets #SpringTraining #photosphere @ First Data Field https://t.co/TsDVGPvd3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was the last good dunk contest. But I think vc had the best ever!! He the best dunker the nba has ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim McGraw - The Cowboy In Me (Official Music Video) https://t.co/GARcMyGei3 via @YouTube HAPPY MONDAY EVERYONE‼️ t… https://t.co/OZCfdSuwqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox @Antoinotabot @IlhanMN Imagine MARRYING YOUR OWN BROTHER in order to stay here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[\MANAFORT  AND THE RED NECK JUDGE\ING THE JAIL SYSTEM ARE BROWNS\BLACKS \NOT FOR WHITE MEN \SAY YOU @NBCNews \@BBCNews \@BBCWorld\@cnnbrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna sit around and wait and be SOL because the university took their time. I’m gonna find myself  some ho… https://t.co/hIHb93PlCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hckwilli @thehill 3/3: Extreme example. However, a rural Pediatrician has already refused to care for the child of… https://t.co/Vj2FJG6fvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they use a four man outfield on Harper, a good bunt down third could be a DOUBLE if he hustles...⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tacos 🌮 time @ El Progreso Carniceria Y Tiendas https://t.co/XpEnWja7zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hooray! Paid for with the blood of American citi— wait... wait a minute! WHY ARE YOU LIKE THIS!? #ElChapo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And now these three remain: Faith, Hope, and Love. But the greatest of these is Love.” Corinthians 13:13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWBunch @BrianHartleyKC There are no independent polls in this race. All that I’m aware of were funded by campa… https://t.co/Kc14yMJ8pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @SenFeinstein Shameful for you to post this snippet of the video. Shameful for you to think it’s oka… https://t.co/euoBdKUg5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMightyPen @pithypacky @drewgetbusy @joffiecakes @FiredupBethy @3parenthesescat @sherrillsj @prageru @CHSommers I… https://t.co/RJ8br9YxmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must be in active war to charge treason.  They don’t accept muller report showing potus did nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmoores2 @moesgametable @Volko26 @josephnschmidt https://t.co/k2iryWAbBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all... she was with ricky last month... and guess what..????? she won’t dating him shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[No doubt in my mind the goat is, @ColinCowher For the worst takes in sports. I can’t imagine what they pay you to s… https://t.co/Uj7YsKeRGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love a rainy day adventure! #goldenretriever #rottweiler #bordercollie #germanshepherd #labrador #puppy #puppies… https://t.co/M5SYnFtp81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating gluten with Pain au Gruyère. @ Grand Rapids, Michigan https://t.co/k3czHukzMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liamwalliams @davisbe @thistallawkgirl @TomiLahren Billy Graham bestowed godly blessings on every war our country… https://t.co/220ZK0YJhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megarian87 @aureaux We’re not that useful beyond reaching things from high shelves, honestly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit has levels bro...just watch and watch carefully 😂🤣 https://t.co/0fOKLofn7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveOnSports @RFRSH @drdisrespect @FalleNCS @dev1ce I wish.  I almost died when I read it in the treatment🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaspluck @victorlavalle Nabokov was a slippery writer. It's one of my favorite things about him. He laid traps… https://t.co/PnCygbkJHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just turning into a sloppy coup attempt, with the help of Mueller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepGrothman  https://t.co/aXndymbYjf #impeachTheMotherFcker #MuellerIsComing https://t.co/chnksCpgfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXXcalibar Definitely beautiful! The both of you defiantly are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are what is characterized as 22 hot wars in the world. 21 of them Have Muslim combatants on one side or the o… https://t.co/i42arn3TKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The association between statin treatment and antidepressant use: unproven.  https://t.co/eFW1fhaCwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq Simple answer is that Trump lies,  about everything,  all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joseph661847561 @israelsanchez99 @Gravity_Ferb @hburton375 @LeniLoud6 @LynnLoudTLH @LucyLoudTLH @LanaLoudTLH… https://t.co/GSbUzjWhxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know its NEVER A DULL MOMENT when the #GetFreshCrew is in the HOUSE 16 X AWARD WINNING EDDIE KAYNE SHOW EVERY S… https://t.co/MsaixRh7HK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfLRE If you need more, let me know. I “owned” that city for 5 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @Lindseyschup !!🎉🎉🎉 Hope you have a great one Linds!❤️🤙🏼🤙🏼 #1309 https://t.co/q2DuhAZuvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t be an American and think the church should be involved with government 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle The least that should be done to Shrewd Lawyers that hide the Truth is remove them from a Job that Leads Pe… https://t.co/VkafUQ0tiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston, Houston Houston I am exhausted you hear me but damn y’all showed up and showed out for the @TheQCDocket wi… https://t.co/p2rcaxPAyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teenagers Say Depression and Anxiety Are Major Issues Among Their Peers https://t.co/ZNv6e4jzhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny Well there you go. You knew enough to correct me on the germline thing..even though I believe future scien… https://t.co/xMZfRlGhmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Victor_Asal @smotus YES. It’s totally a thing. Dish washing + dry Utah air means I can’t use Touch ID all winter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliciaAtout So Randy Orton perfected the RKO so I pick Orton. #OutofNowhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[If funny how people on Twitter say "what I post isn't really me or how I am in person" ......so then why post it you dumbass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To people receiving responses from PHD programs, if I may:  I submitted many applications: ‘08/09: 13 applications… https://t.co/IXbtjhxhWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Yes.  A friend and classmate from junior high who had a deep affection for Judy Garland.  The jocks… https://t.co/T6N7DNEGiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU I WAS THINK ABOUT THE BROWN WOMAN SAY PRESIDENT TRUMP TRYING SEXUAL CONTACT WAS MADE ON HER=KELLYANNE CONWAY  N… https://t.co/3sXcgFgaJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my fellow comics creators, be realistic with your limitations in creating art for publishers. I’m lucky that my… https://t.co/uuIpewwJAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr That’s s freaking tuff one ☝️ @DonaldJTrumpJr but in THE SCHEME of it all - it’s a TIE… https://t.co/gFO1ooBjOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grady missed two open layups earlier in the half or this game would be really close]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @Lakers Best thing about you and Skip ( not same show any more) your always strong and always wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog @maddow Wait, does the Whitaker thing today relate to the smaller story you did time back about Trump’s… https://t.co/FibBQXWF17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFL Real talk, good for her...but going to the NFL?!?! Come on now, she would get destroyed trying to tackle anyon… https://t.co/l3qsAz08td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open house is ready and we will be here till 3pm!  995 Stuart Dr, Pottstown. 4 bedroom 2 1/2 bath dedicated office,… https://t.co/3J8URG04ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus man our PG has killed us last 2 plays. That's 4 points we should've had n up 8. Come on man gotta do better than that!]]></document></documents></author>