<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wow just happened to put on #CallTheMidwife for the first time in awhile and it’s Nurse Crane’s first appearance ❤️… https://t.co/rToMCloyDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChubbyFishInc Ok . Well see.  Since we're dealing in hypotheticals let me ask you this if they beat Xavier and win… https://t.co/vzNijADKhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepBodalia @Joseph_Duhaime @TSNHockey https://t.co/IdaYLY1ftf  Also, an article from STLtoday on the day he got t… https://t.co/soDInAW4dG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeRudd12 Especially considering the cap limitations that resulted in offensive line and receiver issues (not to… https://t.co/ERZ14j8QZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoganknows @NotVandyOC They practice but are told how great they are and they never make mistakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey what’s up just checking in with everyone by posting a quick selfie in some clothes I didn’t end up purchasing.… https://t.co/LAHxHn8Cg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wow, you’ve gone the entire hour without going on Netflix.” “It’s called growth.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetalMeepleBeer Back at you cuz nothing goes better with board games than metal and beer! We can be friends fo sho!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smb #entrepreneurs #friends #family ##mom #dad #neighbor #wife #husband #divorced #Girlfriend #BOYFRIEND #dating… https://t.co/u8FSc137qC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevecheckoway congrats!  here’s a style pointer: lose the indefinite article.  sounds cooler!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I ran 5 miles in 39 minutes (not Hein’s speed, but good for me) and yes, as soon as I got off treadmill I star… https://t.co/1COkM3wleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This white girl comes up to me  Like “let me sing u a hook” “nah” Music shuts off she sings  “I’m a slave in the ho… https://t.co/gYMWil9nRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonalowe @johnalucas @fbcpikeville @whosyour1_ Substance AND Style 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Person next to me on the plane currently reading an article entitled - “When does binge drinking become a problem?”… https://t.co/9GY9JxMktE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow you people who hate him so much legit just have nothin betta to do then trash on @aaroncarter my good friend !!… https://t.co/0xmqyQcr02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly, this was warned and with all the ongoing scandals... Appears, like much, it was lost in the wind.… https://t.co/725FLwYlVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwinCharles We are almost cavemen as it is. We can't go back much further]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re either lonely or bored.” -@scottwernerd   If you’re working on something new and novel, few people will get… https://t.co/3sc0u99ABK]]></document><document><![CDATA[That kid from Liberty sells better than most of the current WWE roster. Sign him up, HHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The black BMW with passenger side windows blown out by @NYPDnews gunfire. After driver tries to run down officers e… https://t.co/WE4uqsnSoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#oregonvideolottery #videolottery #wilds #winning #gamble #cashout @ Joe's Cellar https://t.co/azGaE7Gedn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylereifert #GoIrish! #GoCowboys!  @thejaylonsmith @thegob70 @dallascowboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOTICE; Trump has abandoned press briefings where a free press can question or challenge his claims. He communicate… https://t.co/ywDehMSEQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to his world, Kristine #MarriedAtFirstSight https://t.co/KXvUBkkPXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ I’m inviting you to join Drop, the free app that’s giving away millions in cash rewards every day! Use my code 0o… https://t.co/725CuHaX5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know y'all niggas ain't sleep y'all better be peeping my boy @2chainz  new album cause you know that shit bangs… https://t.co/YSzuPt9Bbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatGermain76 When does fangraphs come out with their playoff percentages]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Friday I had the honor of appearing with the incredible string quartet ETHEL for a special performance at Deniso… https://t.co/zFr8SEk9rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fourth: 195 Evan Lykins Fifth: 145 D'artagnan Spitler and  CBC Sportsmanship Award for Graham: Tanner Jordan and  M… https://t.co/PGggC5fooR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governments are instituted among Men, deriving their just powers from the consent of the governed, — That whenever… https://t.co/agqezqpA9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 - 5 years ago we bought 3 49 cent #goldfish for #thing2.  Last one standing.  Seemed lonely a couple weeks ago af… https://t.co/IYgahf3lnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpathianMts @MarshaHenck Great list. Based on the movies in your top 10, I’m suprised to see “Cold War” missing.… https://t.co/9wr5p7F96f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbqbaseball62 @YankeeSource I thought the opposite. I was shocked they didn’t sign Manny. Didn’t need to move Andu… https://t.co/CQvtrCXfOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BTSxRoseBowl 2-HOUR COUNTDOWN!!! Tickets for added Rose Bowl show go on sale at 4pm! How long will it take to sell… https://t.co/JovE1mMsvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn bitches are leaving , left and right on the bachelor https://t.co/d4YNW5P6lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MuscleBeachVenice #FitModel @musclebeach1 #Model @bodybuildingcom #Fitness #MuscleBeach #Bodybuilding #FitnessShow… https://t.co/tPA7lvIdnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[•Have an offer/serious interest?  -Maximize your exposure with PRO to provide more opportunities  •Under the Radar… https://t.co/dGOp2qdlWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastGMen Like Cruz or Joe said you can go out getting your head sqeezed. Robbie went out/limp from the choke an… https://t.co/14AsrnlKjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyCrandall I got the get away car on stand by https://t.co/MwIz6ttakP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man in uber pool: John how ya doin? We up man. Almighty God woke us up, and he...  Me: https://t.co/ILRSALNrDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look at other folks kids and just think damn my parents did a great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump With all due respect, Mr. President, grow up. If your skin were any thinner, you'd be translucent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miggiesmalls Oh, I’m familiar with that most unfortunate episode. Still liked watching him blow up offensive linem… https://t.co/FV6aEfDZF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs are in! If you need one for your yard please inbox me.  . . . . . . . #WorkSpeaksForItself #PortArthurTexas @… https://t.co/wTBTbLXcVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Wow liked to watch you on Fox...but feelings care About facts...when well expressed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @gearhart44 Maybe Kamala Harris is looking to substitute her income illegally now or it could simp… https://t.co/ovAXG5DvIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 8 year old wanted @Nikki_Gio autograph, Then she said, “I liked it when you talked about Jesus, I’m a big fan of… https://t.co/9nF78l7T8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand why people mistaken my name for “Tyler” ?? How many girls do you know with the name Tyler]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this meme after the #SamsungEvent and felt bad for the old school Motorola RAZR 😂 https://t.co/0XMBvSxZdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FacultyofHorror Found the show thanks to @Danielleri, and it’s so good! Started listening to your discussion of Th… https://t.co/KI1qHC71Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyes tell the story.  Model: @alyssajoycrane  Captured on: #sonya7iii Location: Venice, CA  . . . #sony… https://t.co/YoVK27oBXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenshawkins @benshapiro Well then we will have to rise up against them too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new animated Reign of The Supermen cracks me up. @rainnwilson is awesome as Lex Luthor, but nothing’s as hyster… https://t.co/tVruZ2p1tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omgmaryannnn You Soft then. Franko should start being mean to you so that when people talk shift to you it don’t hurt lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días amantes de la ciudad de la furia, para desayunar va mi columna  https://t.co/sWcE73lQMR https://t.co/6zw843vZ0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Street subway.  #nyc #nycsubway #subway #Manhattan #NewYorkCity https://t.co/oJEaeLJHi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NmoRocio @NicolasMaduro Gracias por compartir tu estimada opinión. En efecto, estoy considerando cerrar la cuenta.… https://t.co/8Wv5wPGdeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Britain Herald - CCSU president, banker and doctor join Community Foundation board: https://t.co/qrsXods1rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarawellman Sure.  As long as you like t-ravs, Imos, White Castle, pork steaks, Red Hot Ripplets, and Vess Soda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Hoffman on the ice for #FlaPanthers morning skate in Denver...Troy Brouwer dressed but not out there yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MSU UM rematch. Saturday night espn. The world will watch: Duke NC MSU UM. Basketball or technology development, ei… https://t.co/GbKGPO6Jgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanebacon @Titleist I’d have or should I say, we will have Sauvignon Blanc from Naples, Fried Oysters appetizer,… https://t.co/BFSTNgJBSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_selby723 @goldendoekd @EricJoh37288055 @Kellie2727Paula @MikeFender5 @hotblondtrouble @EmzdadRunToWork… https://t.co/2M6Kpsu6QE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. But not with you.  • • • • @dollskill #dollskill @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/9N4S4UNEfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww, one of our neighbors left this by our front door today!  The bag has 4 pieces of Lindt truffles in it! What a… https://t.co/WHBuHYQgLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You not cancelled, just stop saying stupid things. No one wants to hate u lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisCrazyTrain This sucks CJ.  Praying for your Mom, Jennifer and you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cdean0508 @CamDR14 @MattWeaverAW @joeylogano It pisses me off too! I like  @Twitter, but damn I hate it after a ra… https://t.co/yFZ8CeS5A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC ...decent people everywhere recognize anti-Semitism when they see it. @Ilhan is blatantly an anti-Semite and s… https://t.co/u5m3pr39od]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @GreggJarrett @FoxNews Absolutely, 100% on the mark..which is why the outrage machine is so spun up.. #SocialismKills]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may be a self important narcissist, but you are a self important narcissist who is making the world a better pl… https://t.co/iI9wa3gEYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that tuberculosis claims more lives every year than HIV and malaria combined? This video from… https://t.co/ED0oswiSma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s just me, but I’m getting pretty tired of the Sullivan/GMJR era in Pittsburgh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallJenner big win today!well, the good luck charm was back boo-yah! Ur bf's boss hooked it up. Props]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson Maybe she should be required to go to the @Reagan_Library where I went to yesterday.  At least she will… https://t.co/h1cGjAXCx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Embroidered Top!!  #embrodery #embroideredtop #embroiderydesign #shopping #womensboutique #womensapparel… https://t.co/NiCpGYniza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDonBeyer Where's your answer to the sexual harassment fund Americans want to know a lot more than they want to… https://t.co/MEIw5Uvpf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonWeichsel @PCBushi I read that book in high school. Freakin’ amazing. I should dig it out and read it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Music Label Spotlight March 5, 2019 Celebrating 15 Years of Cosmicleaf Records  Various Artists -… https://t.co/0BgmcbvR6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncanYB Better late than never. We all know it’s about priorities and resource constraints. At least the engineer… https://t.co/g7UibZUste]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Mercedes Benz AMG 63 S is all about top down performance. Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Rai… https://t.co/L8qYVuM71a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickygervais I must say #AfterLife may have helped heal my heart. Thank you for making a real show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cogecohelps Hi.  Trying to watch TV tonight and video and audio are glitchy.  Any complaints?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People react as the first sign goes up officially renaming The Paseo to Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Blvd. #fox4kc… https://t.co/7IbfC4qJtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo he can get 1 check? Most guys who get drafted don’t even play their first year or even second year? The game i… https://t.co/VeyRhLmixJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Fun fact, everything he said could apply to the President he loves so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me this morning: I’m happy that Trump is visiting Lee County  vs.  Me this evening: Get out of my state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @BoxingFA Geezus 😳 note taken don’t mess with anyone with a face tat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmeriRoughneck @GMA He used both. Glock for the first shooting and Walther for the other two shootings. Police believe his Glock jammed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkelly1956 @twoodchosen1 Look out for the latest @DGF101ESPN pro wrestling edition this afternoon. My guest migh… https://t.co/r4Lrqyswkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaDowdy3 @scswcoach @bridg_alexander @afish1 @UKLarsJorgensen @bobbygunt Pasta, salad, and as much water as I can drink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna make it. Gbye everyone. Please have my funeral at jeds https://t.co/cTu4091PKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to #monstersofrock #morc #xyztheband #terryilousandthevagabonds #music #80s @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/cfMZKtuCSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is "playoff Bron" activated yet?..cuz the window is closing.. #NBATwitter #LALvsMEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful stuff from Michael Cohen in the hearings and testimony. #MichaelCohen #MichaelCohenBreaksTheInternet @CNN https://t.co/bTBPQp3v4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s stop letting juice wrld say he’s gonna kill his girlfriend if she leaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; moderate rain temperature down 56°F -&gt; 51°F humidity up 67% -&gt; 87% wind 3mph -&gt; 16mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boulder field on Sea Street Beach Cape Cod Bay is a popular Summer Striper spot in Dennis.… https://t.co/JCh26U0sI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two deer in the parking lot at City Market tonight. #deer #steamboatsprings #steamboatskiarea #skisteamboat… https://t.co/bOmIGMKogT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol nothing he can do on this play. Click bait at its finest https://t.co/VSOokUdFrT]]></document></documents></author>