<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[City moose selfie! #selfie #selfies #us #itsus #me #itsme #girlswithcurls #moose #mooseselfie… https://t.co/yJqAsQSldn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great story on @allsaintstyler  ases_broadcast_network mikecobbtx in the @tylerpaper Great job Mike in such a short… https://t.co/Z8vH6rrH7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[The marching band music 🎼 🎶 @LGHSOfficial @PolkSchoolsNews in Lakeland!! Home of the Braves! @10NewsWTSP School of… https://t.co/IWvyVv106p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast How did her father, who I didn't always agree with but who always seemed like a decent solid intelli… https://t.co/bVG7xCFaAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone is speaking in the 3rd person and yelling, crying, creating a scene....that’s GUILT and narcissism. #MuteRKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is shattered. My nephew seen a pic of my sister on the fridge, took it down, kissed it and held it to his… https://t.co/QvEOKmgdZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenEmmel Delta math is the light side and ixl is the dark side. See also:khan academy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaCLinder @AppStore @littlenuggetco @gBETAstartups https://t.co/mQC9ct82Cr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGPVAN @lisa4progress @parkinsandrec @washdems Gotta start the chants somehow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kotagreek Bro I heard the people who’s making that wedding is from North Carolina eck 🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are some more amazing products. Find my Web page to order https://t.co/NiJeW3ZIRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lameravioli ...inputs. So Then when they would be on the floor and doing things incorrectly, it would be my fault… https://t.co/H3SUlIhTpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauriceBenard Looking foward to see just hrre our writers for Gh take us...great job maurice on My fathers daughte… https://t.co/nSGuwB9Oep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh baby  how I love you  #funkonew #funkohunting #funkocommunity #collectives #toys #exclusiveoftheday #vinly… https://t.co/1YaDoTMMSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @rookie_usa celebrity kids fashion show and red carpet was 🔥🔥  Stay tuned for our official #runwayrecap and hea… https://t.co/cImjpIngFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker just told me it’s National Margarita Day.... you know what that means????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to michael jackson who is it by pinhead1984 #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/cKYAPN4bCH 😒😇✝️😷😴🛍️😒✝️🌍📱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt So sad that I barely missed you when you left the Majestic tonight.  I brought this picture for you t… https://t.co/JcIUYLi2qO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkisynfunbe Estoy contigo. https://t.co/NRjriOVlAl Ahora si viene, a muerte con el.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmeloanthony What a beautiful picture happy birthday little Melo it's good to see you Carmelo I miss seeing you… https://t.co/ChIzfVvXFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to share this info with my colleagues. What an important documentary! #BlackHistoryIsAmericanHistory… https://t.co/yKcZPjGXKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[*has bad day *picks fight with Heinz company on Twitter  *feels slightly better]]></document><document><![CDATA[makes me laugh 😂 every time I see a tweet about SNL — I probably should take it seriously, but it’s way too funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Everyone needs to travel. It's good for the mind to just get away for a bit. I need a vacation. #iFlyAlaska #alaskahappyhour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me just say, not the slightest part of me is surprised that this girls name is kendall Liegh]]></document><document><![CDATA[repeat after me: one day, everything i’m stressing about right now will not matter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OSWALT EAGLES 🦅  Way to play with heart, determination, and defense!  🏀☀️@OswaltAcademy @MrsDuldulao #WeAreRusd https://t.co/1VD8d6gAPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InThePastLane @99piorg Well than I am happy the Red Sox beat them. Hawkeye however was a bigot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charles_S_Viar You obviously are not aware of the truth - https://t.co/9O64dwCLN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got my dads card on my phone SOOO should i just pay $2.99 to get rid of the ads on this game bc its my favorite &amp; i hate ads. 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskLyft what's the point of scheduling a pickup if the driver drops you??  Stranded in Minneapolis trying to get t… https://t.co/n63NzZ3sgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea how i was able to drink 3+ days in a row during college. I can barely function after 1 night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your low back pain isn’t always because you’re injured. You might be lifting incorrectly. 🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/mcY7Ho1ws0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought 34 slim Jim’s last night so that means slim Jim’s for breakfast today 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryan &amp; Katie Torwalt - Prophesy Your Promise (Acoustic Video) https://t.co/pnsXmyuI6f via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am an aries and that’s why y’all are so excited to see me... lmfao basically]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RenewODAAT cause we need latina twilight back as Elena’s best friend @Isabella_Gomez  @ArielaBarer]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW you run into @calvinarsenia and @ramyessam rehearsing a new collaboration @folkalliance @ Fairmont Le Reine Eli… https://t.co/TyWjbEBgCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re off! First annual Parent University @SouthridgeES @noexcusesu #SREPride #LISDculture. @3rdtimesachArM_ ki… https://t.co/WdOEcZZf6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should investigate Nancy Pelosi and Chuck Schumer and the rest of the democrats and liberal's who are waiting ou… https://t.co/K4LtlIy64k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff 10 hours you dems met with Cohen before he testified you shady bastard I say as a taxpayer I’m sick… https://t.co/SlbrJ1SptH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no vine a poner ninguna valla, las vallas las van a poner los candidatos después de la veda. No vaya a confundir… https://t.co/1OS5y5oSwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman @connielipnick It just never ends. If they did anything legal it was a mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincipalKafele Amazing! I have been trying to figure out how to do something like this. Inspiring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I told them I wasn’t gonna clean anything until it got done bc it wasn’t going to get cleaned up if it wasn’t… https://t.co/BaCPj3fDy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glowing Big Red here in the @unlcba Business Career Center!! #GBR #Huskers @ Nebraska College of Business https://t.co/TrOw2mlgyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting @CycloneWBB at our Girls on the Run practice tonight! Gonna try to recruit a few little Iowa State fans… https://t.co/h0QdSu3zXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will look back on tonight and remember this as the night i decided architecture was my calling. Thank you https://t.co/T2l0WtW318]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Ellis is a Article III fed judge appointed for life.The point of life tenure is to keep justices insulated fr… https://t.co/ZXSmGcICMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let Light In🌹 3x4feet  #internationalwomensday #strongwomen #believe  (shinning in the sun) #rosegold  #art #artist… https://t.co/TNy0smXtwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alright i’m drunk enough, fuck marry kill xerneas groupon lunala” @Linkyoshimario]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would a Monday morning be without an email to kdp/amazon? https://t.co/YtYYr1NoXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full story arc! With the conclusion being “Yaas Qween, I approve!” #GlennClose #BillyPorter #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane Happy happy anniversary! God Bless you and keep you  always! https://t.co/IQdd670cQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwiibi I have that too!!! I’m afraid to take it out of its package cause i think the red will just chip... we are keyblade twins!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My housing is confirmed for living in Downtown Orlando!!! 🙌🏽😁 can’t wait to move]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never seen the movie Grease and everyone always gives me shit for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is perfect!  Let’s believe the best about our students.  They navigate sooo much on any given day. Compassiona… https://t.co/xsTZqaUC9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating 36 years of dedicated service @amfam and a well deserved retirement. Thank you Managing Attorney Pete F… https://t.co/WgMD3tQROQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hotel I am at is fully booked. People are enjoying the indoor pool and outside this very moment at a bonfire ma… https://t.co/zKOGt8VU4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Portage County deputy serving a warrant was severely burned Valentines Day by a man who threw gas or some other f… https://t.co/fm5Ulplqac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabes que te tienes que ir de ese bar cuando ponen @taylorswift13 y la gente empieza a gritar de la emoción]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way to end a Monday is outside. #OptOutside #UpperPeninsula #hikingnorthernmichigan #girlswhohike… https://t.co/kGnETzFUeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to self: Watch out and don’t get run over while touring the @pwpmproducemkt  — even as today’s biz winds down.… https://t.co/bFDTzI57oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirPowerUnicorn What’s not to understand? it is literally a movie made to be understandable to children...  Like,… https://t.co/B0O1NMOyJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Magic Kingdom looks so lovely this morning! Keep up the awesome work, Princesses! 🏃🏻‍♀️✨🏰 . . .  #runDisney… https://t.co/Y0klpS51Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriaSteinem u r one of the most important things that’s ever happened. thank you for your work in the sixties, I… https://t.co/yqssIsQrcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kebrik So appreciate you taking the time to comment. The more you know the better decisions you make.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC AMEN !! No !! SOCIALISM In This UNITED STATES Of AMERICA !!!! https://t.co/gME53sKN9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yellow or blue for #Fjord ?  Yay for more #strawberryShortcake #mightynein  #criticalrolefanart #critters https://t.co/PUyECIJgC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mobinfiltrator I mean he certainly wasn’t trying to hide himself looking right at the camera was he? Any chance he… https://t.co/GZQqYoizMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When that thing you ordered is backordered on top of the backorder... https://t.co/h3giU349PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennafischer insta stories on her bread making is giving me life!!! I don’t have the patience to make bread, so I’… https://t.co/kO0yDVXUHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriterRAS I’m so sorry! Broke my heart too. He definitely will be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Firefly518 @StormIsUponUs Btw: the young minister went astray. After I asked, "You're a minister, aren't you?" He… https://t.co/ff09wO94Qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @jaketapper Yes to @jaketapper speaking truth to power! Good to see broadcast journalism upping their gam… https://t.co/CjO5sYsvCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[you @ChrisCuomo are showing your ignorance.🤣🤣🤣🤣. Let’s all believe a convicted liar and go down the garden path wit… https://t.co/OmfDYyGgwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk who needs to hear this so ill just leave it here https://t.co/EOzKIINWK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time hearing @stdennard and @BrigidKemmerer talk about their books at @AndersonsBkshp https://t.co/AaENd1npRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got out of an incredible production by @UPittStages. Major congratulations to the amazing cast and crew of Flyin’ West!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghanmakinley @smithkira6600 This can’t be a one sided relationship anymore. I need more effort]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mex_Libertario @lopezobrador_ @econokafka @memobarba @CartonCalderon @isabellemexico @OSWALDORIOSM… https://t.co/6vKcd5ArxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nutterlie @hansonmusic Oh wow!! 😬 hopefully when the madness is over it’s back to normal]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u lay down in bed and u turn on the tv and it says “morning news” .........]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go back to work tomorrow😭Tonight was such a needed mind clearing type of night]]></document><document><![CDATA[hier on a mangé de la poutine, alors jsp trop quoi en penser mais je crois que ct bon https://t.co/RuTauIsRJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkeithhatfield @Aaron_Torres Then, you should see the other POs security guy shoving a Nevada coach from behind in the tunnel. Clown show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSwiftPR   this person that’s stalking you is some sick and demented person. It must be frightening to even think… https://t.co/cFdM25JGbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold your man to the same standards you hold your friends. Drop both. But don’t dare make excuses for him and be li… https://t.co/qHNsdiycWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montelll13 @netflix I do and yet there is no way I’m watching it no matter how fantastic it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler So the Clintons stealing millions from Haiti doesnt ring a bell?  Trump works free!  He gives his c… https://t.co/IQMnn2WZX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You probably really wanted to say ALL republican women]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, to these women below, #RetweetWomen and just adding today... @womensrrhumanr  @reshmasaujani  @bevneufeld… https://t.co/DRbn58d43U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for those @MIWband &amp; @atreyuofficial tour dates to drop like https://t.co/nrAa91giDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there such a thing as an ethical aquarium? Like a fish sanctuary? I just love fishies]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Bellator fight looks like it could have broken out in the JCMO Walmart parking lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He goes "I hit it too hard and too fast" ....and I go "something else you're probably used to".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplyemjhaee @iammahninmundah Hahahaha close kami tlga. Di nyo lang alam 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @NOW1SOLAR @hey_butter @poppij @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @Itridpm @delgeo1 @Msgargoyle13 @agavecorn… https://t.co/VkMPgy3y93]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to see Michael Buble this Sunday.  Tix were given to me by dear friends. Adrian has been fighting to stay ali… https://t.co/kNThRtNHoY]]></document></documents></author>