<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I know it is the biggest race of the year for these drivers, but that doesn't mean they have to go all stupid in th… https://t.co/OJ3403TD1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Pod 🚨🚨🚨  We’re pumped for tonight. Pregame with us now. 🙏🏻💙  #LeafsForever #TMLTalk #HockeyTwitter #Coyotes… https://t.co/lAqdTcZcKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should hang out at @thesanddollarlv bc #imrickjamesbitch   Also I have to follow #rickjames on bass… https://t.co/MNYJIK0y5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WordPress 5.1 is GA, released, out, go upgrade!  https://t.co/9wexcaWQ8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dragonslayer951 take me with u for all those times i helped you close deli😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryGeren @TheSCEA Junior is a pathetic sound bit waiting to happen. Bless his heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes @AdamSchiff when are you going to jail. Leaking, lying schiffhole. https://t.co/R7k8slEHoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faithandfury @AlternatFacts @RepKevinBrady @HouseGOP All the RepubliCONS know is the perversion of christianity fo… https://t.co/ibHVZVyUDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @AlaniNutrition is going to get here today I’m so excited I’m gonna get home from school to so many presents!!! https://t.co/kiANXkR3ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments What a joke.... once a cheater always a cheater, once a dumb ass, always a dumbass. #Drama https://t.co/Oor96V9DzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and fly (@ St. Louis Lambert International Airport - @flystl in Saint Louis, MO) https://t.co/VCm2qdjW3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting down to a great cup of coffee, a blank #moleskine and exploring a question that I’m always asking myself...… https://t.co/GMwLBHf1ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cern_lXXl @Captainswoop1 @sygarte The apostles would have known the gospels were false in your scenario. That mean… https://t.co/NMSNpHcfZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hope is for development projects in underserved areas to move forward as quickly as possible. My fear is that so… https://t.co/Tt6s548GH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianagrandebr I did a little loop guitar cover of Needy! Check it out! https://t.co/yyx3HtEcWd #ArianaGrande… https://t.co/0Hpf9Jtdnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I don’t Really  believe we should just celebrate Black History In just 1 month. However, why  not end the month… https://t.co/NaRpDwJHWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nike should give me a deal I would put the money in trust fund for kids and at end of year make kids donate clothes… https://t.co/i6M2PBRYeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re on a roll today. Let’s keep it going. Concrete Canoe 9% - Pecan Porter. CC is the latest release in our tapro… https://t.co/5CxOIeY6SR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dustinyoho @Jordan_Lopez13 Yeah they’re all ugly now lol even Nissan looks better]]></document><document><![CDATA[U16 Boy's Major Midget - Pool H - @MississaugaBall def. @EBAThunder 65-53 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kay_Petey Yeah I tweeted about it like a week or so ago :/ she died the day after her bday like 2 weeks ago now. It was awful]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when the guitarist finds the photographer in the pit! MAREK ‘ASHOK’ SMERDA of CRADLE OF FILTH in Sacram… https://t.co/BKT7qva35V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@relyt2000 @jase1129 @BillShanks Because they had $50-60M come off the books, two clear lineup spots available, and… https://t.co/tLLfNrPA7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Velvety smooth, fat-burning zucchini soup. Extra delicious because my hubby made it with homemade chicken stock fro… https://t.co/4oKhFFLG91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gTubbyschmidt @ReddHead_13 @PumpkinNation @SportsBoyTony It truly is! Guess I forgot to use #SarcasmFont 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realeyes2c @noclue72 @OnWithLogic @outlawjw I wonder if the older demographic, if they are on social media at all,… https://t.co/xN0X2KaZMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JordanWoodsAppreciationPost kardashian drama aside #JordynWoods is gorgeous https://t.co/jXBSiG3QpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dont tell me that you love if you not gon die fuh me-“ RUN. THAT. SHIT. BAACCKKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisgiles01 @Athletics @RFWill149 You will, Chris. Hopefully, Will has proven himself to you and @DaveKaval. He h… https://t.co/EdOHrEq6U6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out to @Pokemon too! I got it a couple days earlier then when I was supposed to get it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriciaSydney @BoldBebo Explaining math always makes it seem more complex. https://t.co/pWRjBmxhFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why so serious 🃏  Put some jokers in your deck. Life’s too short to be so damn serious all of the time.  Healthy te… https://t.co/Tg7qlwrnGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fuckingmanny @rosettastone I’m holding out for the lifetime download and 24m app for $120 I saw late it was sold out that was 2 weeks ago 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting @GEOjobeGIS’s own @nicklawalin as a walk-on for the “Oregon Homies” #dodgeball team. Good luck in the to… https://t.co/vRJVjq2BVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittanyZima @bumble @Tinder Tinder will give you more matches, but you have to be wary of scammers far more often… https://t.co/Ti7K99Zquf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@43feetPodcast Peruvian Pullman.  Plastic is a huge issue in Peru that won’t be cleaned up.  Solution - make the co… https://t.co/wbQo59lhle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow @andylassner @MaryConnelly @EdGlavin @iamjeanniek Please Make My Dream Come True, Help my fiance and… https://t.co/qO4LvauIDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutOfStepXXX Wow, that sucks. I'd head to my Facebook then. All the stuff is also posted on my page and Marketplace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariayo6 @wsferries @komonews @KIRO7Seattle @KING5Seattle That would be awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakdownUSA @MNHockeyMag @nuhsboyshockey @mnhockeytv @LetsPlay_Hockey @FollowThePuck @YouthHockeyHub… https://t.co/UEMUQC5xkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working at the @the_phoenician today. Better then being in the office. #schwablife https://t.co/m3W9p7jTHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ednanatina @Here4it4 Dawww! I love you both! I Try my best! I have so many flaws! But knowing I at least got you a… https://t.co/AJBnvVrce2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moment of silence for all the dudes who got gifts for their wcws that get their guts rearranged by the guys who d… https://t.co/muT4yGTtQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScienceNews Okay, maybe so, but why promote its use? Why add anything to food except natural herbs and spices?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_wentz @SportsRadioWIP @DeSeanJackson11 What a loser he never won anything.  How many games you think you both will be on the field for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhh What people don't realize is that when they say "in the wealthiest country in the world" they are actually sig… https://t.co/Z8F7DTUZxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always see IU as an opportunity to compete well! Sophomore Andy Stohr with a PR in the 3200 with a 10:27.  Will… https://t.co/N2U55x3YUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guys phone blowing up and he’s not even cute and my shit dry like the desert 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday To My Mentor/Therapist @madflavor Wish You The Best, Health And Manny More Years Of Blessings For Me… https://t.co/RKm4xf4cYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are in my mentoring academy, you never know when I may pop up at your school just to make sure your doing… https://t.co/GFNdX1EGlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My write in candidate never had a chance...  #chicago https://t.co/pXVGwbrkUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captainafrica91 Yes lol Unless we talking 2k I’m picking up Paul pierce before melo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSimmons Davis only gives a fuck about his brand, how much money he can make &amp; worshipping his eyebrow(s)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OZCRYPTO2 “Re hypothecation” it’s so crazy to think we should trust any bank after 2008?!?!?! So what stops the ba… https://t.co/pPMMVTf1Gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the greatest experiences I’ve ever had. Got to rub shoulders with the Colombian political elite🇨🇴 https://t.co/ZGl9mLYGfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MEN IN BLACK: Alien Attack - @universalorl in Orlando, FL https://t.co/vszza8naTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some more great pics from this weekend !    @AHSBaseballKTA    https://t.co/w0KT0Hf4SL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucienGreaves And, what kind of dressing was served with this word salad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@An_Wr3n @cueinc @alicekeeler @whoisalexmitts @EdTechBrennan @Monica_M_Daniel That’s the worst thing about presenti… https://t.co/mhYrRJzobN]]></document><document><![CDATA[first person that had their leg fall asleep for sure thought they were full of bees]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KansasEDMFam @Jennifer_Fox10 @ZooWildlife @FOX10Phoenix That’s honestly the only reason I clicked was to make sure of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This maybe over stated. I read the same headlines with BitCoin futures trading on the CME which when launched was t… https://t.co/GJ05Kg17K4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEMIvik G☕️☕️d Morning Viktoria!! Happy Thursday my amazing friend. ♥️☕️♥️☕️🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@maxwillens uncovered whatever happened to The Atlantic’s paywall, announced in Dec 2017 https://t.co/r4uE99oyEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iceman525 @I_Am_MFR I've felt that for the past few years as well. Seemed so perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Elephant Bar for making me look stupid!, ( could never be my fault)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEChrisMack do u think ab is turning into a pariah in pgh like rich rod has in WV. even now if u mention rich rod… https://t.co/2mZ3u6PJDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Instead of just watching and recording...why didn't y'all do something!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[everybody posting their valentine photos and I’m over here like... #marshallmathers #mykittynottherapper @ Des Moin… https://t.co/YifokxZ5p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very excited about having these guys around for a free more years. Polemic was great when he returned and Keple… https://t.co/ZZuL2iY0OY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithDecorum @RealTimBlack We should be demanding our money back from 2016. The DNC cheated, leading us to believe… https://t.co/mkS0b8wwp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m MIGHTY POSSESSIVE @AlderLaneeggs could not have found himself a better successor  Every shot you see them t… https://t.co/tEGYgL3LK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best duo Russ has played with since KD/Harden. PG13 is showing that he can play alongside the best of t… https://t.co/FojNAOsE7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJwhoknew888 I was going to ask a question, this means I don't need to. Thanks for saving me from looking very foolish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peabodypress @burkanuck Even if a libertarian runs, I might write her in just for shits and giggles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fort Kent’s stunning loss to Calais means GSA would play the Blue Devils at the Cross Center with a win over Centra… https://t.co/w4S2PGvaGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toben41 @nypost How dare he knelt ! How dare hahahaha such disrespect! https://t.co/Mtrsdtkxxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wyBR06IHu5   “Lit “🔥🤘🏾  ..available now YouTube  (shot by @Treydhagreat ) https://t.co/iRAoYnkMBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Dozen Things I have Learned About Business from Rza (the founder of Wu-Tang Clan) – 25iq https://t.co/zndeOCetZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally:  Because of the cost of college we will begin to see this much more.  And it will be a good thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon-St. Johns! #plaidaboutiQ #WAnderers #explORers #creditunion https://t.co/m4U3uUQKFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReflectorVideo It is disgusting that President Trump would falsely claim the Democratic party is anti-Jewish.  He… https://t.co/aNIc2u8PMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonNBC @KurtBusch @NHLonNBCSports @NBCSN @GoldenKnights @UfoJoe11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Sure he did after colluding with you for 10 hours, I hope you committed a crime, you are a liar you… https://t.co/Q5jBxGCb6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s declare a national emergency because I can’t get my way. Not a spoiled spoon fed brat at all...@realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewfromJersey It’s fine. Allows other team to set his market in worst case. And that team is going to factor losi… https://t.co/pn8D7tSoo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneritchie Hi Rene…are you aware there’s an issue with the amore web site and 1Blocker? The site is white listed… https://t.co/GNXBsQJeMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ajdekanur look what surprised me in my mailbox this morning!  So cool to hear from former students serving the… https://t.co/hEn5QOUHwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesley_jordan Sorry for your loss. My dad passed away in August from ALS. It sucks but it will get better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Fox News to is obsessed with Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.  Understandably so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought she was referring to the printing more money portion of the Green Deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#todaysstudio #crimescene #dexterwashere? @ College Heights, Pennsylvania https://t.co/p2QLd6hkI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting my Saturday with some learning at @orlandomayor’s annual Neighborhood &amp; Community Summit. https://t.co/nUj95Fj3p9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Yeah well Democrats don't even get charged for crimes, spend no time in court or in jail. Yet they are still s… https://t.co/HWEjAx8MuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nichole_sara I'm so Happy for You Sara, You deserve it!!❤❤❤😁😁😁🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your annual #DaylightSavingsTime PSA from @ThomasGroupKW #RealEstate Keller Williams Louisville East - https://t.co/EVn5jximOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Stop Asking Me Dumbass Questions This Early In The Morning Susan,  Put Your Head Back In Your Damn Cubicle...… https://t.co/obTMEsodXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HellaPalattella Good story. Senderoff has got to play him. First, because the Flashes need him. But secondly, beca… https://t.co/FOB1Ktv9Ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very humbled and honored to be a part of this amazing team. This is @JonnyBones’ 13th UFC title. We appreciate… https://t.co/gtnV7BrV7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[she tells him to calm down and that i’m only the uber driver . his dumb ass tips me $20 for getting his girl home s… https://t.co/rVYnfQSPyp]]></document></documents></author>