<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking an One Four Three by @Oraclebeer @ The Michigan Tap Room — https://t.co/pS3euJE0AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meridithmcgraw @RadioFreeTom Maybe I'm naive, but it sure seems to me that DoD should be the first coordination po… https://t.co/EwiWE17xp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LewisBrinson don’t forget who had faith in you ! Second one was an absolute hanger but that’s what you’re supposed… https://t.co/ti44CQlHUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[182 - Dawson Brandt | ✌️10-2 @LakeSunSports @LakeNewsOnline https://t.co/iEt86dsWfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I’ve felt about the Kings every season for the last decade #kangz https://t.co/mjIx2gZGnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Tierney Aldredge and @denveragency for taking the journey with me to support the Adopt The Arts Founda… https://t.co/CWaFUcaLf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Can’t we all agree we don’t need any more immigrants from Yemen or Somalia?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for patterns today in #SpencerScience about why some things float while others sink. Something interesting… https://t.co/pgkUukiKy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew Hey, Jared.  Are you still in Mohammed Bin Salman's pocket?  https://t.co/rQkBjtnCK5    MBS has told peop… https://t.co/iBvDMw5Rwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @sobeys @MichaelTibollo @ToddSmithPC Guess we all know what the luxury Van is for when it's done. Skip… https://t.co/9hIsqFJVOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sZPjMxx44S Verizon Customer Service Phone Number can help resolve the Verizon issues 1-855-431-6111… https://t.co/E2YnRLi16E]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the kind of political platform I would like to see more of. #EndTheClockChange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris We are waiting for an apology for the Jussie non attack you ripped trump supporters for no reason at… https://t.co/iOYf4k03dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jabbathasIut I do think it’s funny you the first person to clock me for that 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flat_Molar @LionelMedia We’re all gone in 12 when you think about the matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What in the world could @swiftkaratechop have me reviewing this time... https://t.co/LfCOTgFRCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tired of these lying, disingenuous #Democrats misleading their districts about their taxes.  When your taxes wen… https://t.co/fXG7GaEtRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thespiderpup I YouTube 'whose line is it anyway' compilations. That's always a go to for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 The comment would be... this problem is only 2 meters high at 6,000 yards.  #SemperFi https://t.co/rCugO1rB8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people still need to learn when it’s okay to be prideful and when it’s not necessary]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for some intermiamicf soccer? ➖ I think we should be the 1st squad to rock custom boots all season. How… https://t.co/FKCfS1YsGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[TURNUP W/ @liljon FOR THE ROWDIEST PARTY @hakkasanlv TONIGHT 📲 440.487.5000 4 FREE ENTRY ON MY GUESTLIST OR TABLE I… https://t.co/8x48AM7dPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve done floors through the whole house, counter tops, back splash, plumbing, electrical etc but you know what I s… https://t.co/3gfDhXRXta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riopedre31 @chance4gardener @JonAnthony7 @woodywood1999 @FrankBenXXXOOO @KingPeachDP @someone_1958 @TaggartRehnn… https://t.co/YFTW9x5UMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey fellas!!  Come on down to the CIBC theater and we can all duel it out together!!!  😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN: Facing an aggressive Beijing, Taiwan's president issues a warning to the world. https://t.co/EICMThIeOk  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maroonsista @Porsha4real Congratulations my dear on the bady and the wedding I'm a big gay fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotoNutJob @tommytickover @maja_kenney @GL650_LynneG @biker_Ian @highwaylass Just takes a bit of getting used to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Lyons Sings Sinatra And More https://t.co/vWYXwjC4pq via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me puse a rallar queso parmesano y acaba de venir el vecino a decirme que me lave las patas.. https://t.co/stH8GA4Mvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CA_Marie13 I need you to do this next time he shows up... https://t.co/HgOAyQx2N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERose1324 So, it’s probably smart to wait until after the reverse split to go long]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga choji really married a strong black woman https://t.co/F0anb6qvor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo Algún negro le ha hecho un daño irreversible a este weon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_SKG_1983 @CarlyJA22 @bubbagump324 He also could no longer borrow money in the US.That's why eh borrowed from Duechebank]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous 185th Birthday Toronto! I love you Toronto but you are too cold to me now!  Here's a magnificent bird's-ey… https://t.co/YiMOyYR8YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL Although I was amazed at the women who praised their film about "menstrual equality"  As a man, I don't… https://t.co/DuPrZWBWkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[54-46 South County over Patriot with 7:23 left in 4th.  Back to back huge 3’s by Van Dever  to get the crowd into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a positive masculinity standpoint, point of view and perspective, only the sweet and sour and SWEET compliment… https://t.co/F7Tpf7nONu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go4itbas @Maryfis90730348 @heyitsCarolyn @DoingRight1 @JulieReichwein1 @AnnThacker2 @nancy_hamm1 @mymynags… https://t.co/4YLO6yHPS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assuming this was an unfortunate editorial oversight, not an intentional reference to Michel Trudeau.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing more relaxing than a scortching hot bubble bath and scrolling through Pinterest finding things to spend my money on]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can u be so childish when your over 50yRs old  "seriously grow the fuck up" #idiots #disgusting #]]></document><document><![CDATA[this old guy at halo asked me last night if he knew me from like 10 years ago   ... man since i was 11 i really really hope not]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hawthorne's New York Pizza &amp; Bar - @hawthornespizza in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/OMw9zbQ7Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haikus2You @PattyMurray So Obama’s 6 National Emergency’s were just fine for you ...let me guess you voted for the… https://t.co/f2nyEXAbwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow (3.10.19) - St. John Fisher Catholic Church ⛪️ - 2:30pm - Rancho Palos Verdes, CA - IT’S GOIN DOWN!!🔥🙌🏼🙏🏼… https://t.co/xReHNY9b7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my forever life-long❤️ i love you &amp; hope you have an amazing day🎉  since '06  @breauna_stott https://t.co/zpPusKzsQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knew a turn was coming, figured it would be the other way around. Glad I was wrong! #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carey Price tied a record with his 314 career wins 🏒  https://t.co/MMHXtwbxaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gimpmaker @dmshaw85 @JordanFlorio1 @jmittleman25 @davidhogg111 The Dickey amendment has not been lifted. Obama ord… https://t.co/p75Cxbifbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[if these hate full demorats are that heartless that they can just kill a baby whats to stop them from just killing anyone they don't like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steelers ruined potential dynasty by blindly supporting Ben Roethlisberger https://t.co/YnCEoHrelx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Divababie @AnnieIlonzeh @karakillmer @msmayoalldayo @randyflagler @ChristianStolte @squad2tony @DaMinoshow… https://t.co/iSAqC958d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[instead of benefiting an individual, the pooled funds address the needs of all the members of the organization. For… https://t.co/kjxEiEhs4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first 15 centuries of the church, no one had personally own books. No personal libraries! Oh the humanity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBrownSwag @Jeff_Radcliffe Make bumper stickers with this on them !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeSnyder @GabbyFerro01 @readandgeek And the reason he had 6 weeks was because the movie was being released in… https://t.co/IZr1lgZ8W7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierre_lemieux I think Friedman views it simply as 'something else' gets produced. But I see it as something, but… https://t.co/AD6fi32E5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ya right. Again how many falsely testified and are under indictment or already in jail? How many m… https://t.co/PLfQhOAqoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sendo que já fui acordado varias vezes de manhã com essa criança chorando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makscrazed @kellyelliottmcm Just helps me determine who’s a troll, or possibly a bot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianehake @Steel_Curtain4 @JasonLaCanfora Looks like you got your wish!  Brown to the Bills!  I read their 9th for… https://t.co/840gPkRFRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter is a loser, and I think the American people have no interest in what he has to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Union Square, San Francisco https://t.co/FHccQrojYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @Brooke_trout__ , @Sea_of_Cortes and @Cottus_rex, recipients of this year’s Oregon Chapter of the… https://t.co/mLANA3qR7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/vYvsrXN5D5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinetr33ecogang @EducatedLefty @VIEJOARMY @CNN Medical technology, IT, water and farming technology and the list g… https://t.co/KK39jxpb5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @DeepMindAI released a learning environment for Hanabi, and I will start to do some experiments on it this w… https://t.co/9AIGPYxuRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 @SueGlashauser There is no, I mean no comparison to white collar crime punishment and meaningless smal… https://t.co/VgERIIAXyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[React + Redux + Coffee Time #devlife #coffetime #reactjs #LambdaSchool https://t.co/ZewFwCyJkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been trying to grow my hair out.   Not sure if I like it.   What do you think?? (Don't mind the scruffy face) lol.… https://t.co/vpskf8xwyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upsguest @_ISTA_1501 Там не может быть встречных машин, потому, что там нет дороги, там сугробы.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanDav23194167 @CanesWBB Yesssss Yesssss Yesssss. Best Team in Miami. 1st place in the ACC. Keep Balling Ladies s… https://t.co/nHzUF39zly]]></document><document><![CDATA[One person followed me //  Automatically checked by HOW THE FUCK DO WE GET RID OF THIS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Carolina today at a swap-meet.  Looking around. These folks look way worse off than last year. Selling stuff… https://t.co/kk2FvUNQJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gourmet lunch #Vegan @ Midhurst, near Barrie, ON https://t.co/D0Tw2ojDTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy, there's a lot of folks from #PiratesNation in a good mood today!  #rcnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying my day off with a hike on this perfect Arizona day! Hope you are all having a great Thursday! #azhiking… https://t.co/OO0K4xc1fE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz You can’t offend an incorporeal thing. Businesses are not people. Neoliberals need to get this throu… https://t.co/YBWueG6ArH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesSuer Yes, since that’s the whole reason they are there... unfortunately too many orgs look upon them as free/cheap labor only]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLoulouC @haldol @Ski_Bromont Loulou y ´a sait pas combien de maisons dans la montagne des fois me dis qu’on doit… https://t.co/1zDDxEgzBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ObiMon_ This is how I consumed Harry Potter from start to finish while driving tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember that weird time in Basketball where Shawn Marion and Jermaine O'Neal were members of the Miami Heat and… https://t.co/ZD9pA1wxmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of folks gonna say Tyler Herro has an “off” game.   He’s got 12 boards with 5 minutes to go in the game. All around player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Don, @AOC will draw it out for you as soon as she is done sharpening her crayons! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_monicakeee Nobody ever does 🤷🏻‍♂️! I was just a lil kid tryna walk home in my America jersey and here comes this guy.. 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s game day for my fats.. #MiniMe #SheGetBucketsToo https://t.co/WmTpYnBUdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobMargolis Rest well Oppy. One day we’ll come up there and get you. I hope it’s soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They really do check on Dems and others. But it must seem to you unfair because you lie and exagge… https://t.co/MnMWnGEpxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t like beer? You should still visit @ExNovoBrew in Beaverton because the food is great. The ham and mortadella… https://t.co/uuHIO7tjYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders My wife and I have a small business and pay for our own insurance. One typo on one form caused our i… https://t.co/OlxH3Lmrfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HobeyBaker candidate @priskie4 goes end to end for an incredible goal vs Clarkson. Rumor has it that @croesler21 t… https://t.co/cSbTXiIzAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ravi88545166 @blackyngdave1 @Lisa19576 @_dopedaneille @Shaun12361257 @crazyjane125 @Pastabowl2 @FreddyBryan801… https://t.co/bnfR39zYSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I said I wasn’t nervous for the next 90 minutes I’d be lying.  Not sure why I bothered with sleep, a 440am alarm seems stupid.  #COYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justin_hicken they’re as capable as anyone. they’re a really good team. maybe the best in the country. but they do… https://t.co/BljSZMLKn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SicilianSpeed @RealAlpha_2 @phonedrone64 @Happy19111 @gonefishing178 @Lucille77316971 @TinaDeplorable… https://t.co/kh3KVIqk4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodby #vslive! The @KLASresearch Web development team now begins our 6 hour adventure drive home. https://t.co/k9t4Eii17G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veredes I would call that a very successful long awaited solution integrating to conclusive strength the ideal dri… https://t.co/NxKlZUUISC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for #system96 #fusibleglass from #spectrumglass #oceansideglasstile #uroborosglass and #youghioghenyglass?… https://t.co/yK6QlWPBay]]></document></documents></author>