<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Well I guess it was a fairly short ceremony. Might have been cool if there was actually some stuff that celebrated… https://t.co/zJcScABpQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yvonnejsmit @FernMajestic I reread the previous chapter to get back into the flow, edit, and then write the new ch… https://t.co/9GwXmkqJRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoArquette @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Another corporate loyalist voting for trafficking, teen prostitution, c… https://t.co/cxaCn5R7zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dig deep. I'm worth every penny. https://t.co/lt0cyksjOI https://t.co/SO4y22Di0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always think of these people as just football players and not solely people. Case Keenum has carried himself his… https://t.co/lkyLhB9IEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeBroTrill @peter_king Yeah wait your Mom just let him out the window, she didn’t want to hurt your feelings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I make a bet against my boss on this Duke/UNC game and Zion gets hurt the first play. My luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know, Melanie. [sic] My dad always said a cross in the ground doesnt look right unless it's on fire. https://t.co/hvlZpFbqe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aside from academic excellence and integrity, John Jay College is constantly striving to keep students, faculty, an… https://t.co/QNo2A6YIgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton is leading the disinformation campaign. Just like she led the seditionist campaign that brought us… https://t.co/HaZ4ANM8ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what @Bharper3407 is going to see when he wakes for his morning coffee. JM still waiting in his house for a… https://t.co/LB4sGtK6g8]]></document><document><![CDATA[NACADA Conference Bay Bay! #RoadTrip #WeekendFun #SATX #Leadership #FridayFeeling https://t.co/Brqg1rqECH]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Jean-Michel Basquiat’ at the Brant Shows His Bifurcated Life https://t.co/xYl72BYcaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kausmickey I know you're pretty well decided on this, so I don't know if you'll consider this with an open mind, b… https://t.co/wQu7AeDHrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch was on her phone in the coffee line parked 3  cars from the window, I went around her, and she looked su… https://t.co/rviP8SEHlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acoyne I had thought Sheila Copps had ridden off into the sunset. Sheila get back on that horse and keep riding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s talk about SEX!!  • In leadership, if we are going to protect and cover the identity of this generation why w… https://t.co/lxqVza8LtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Can You Recognize A Mature Disciple? Look For These 5 Character Traits https://t.co/NUDFrn0VzB. Great read on d… https://t.co/w7YqAkI20R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett I hope you enjoy your time in prison! #Jussie #JussieSmollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Union_Sports_ @biffy7 @TheRyanBaker @alexblagg @JordanUhl @pattymo Highway offramps are actually fun w the IRS. Wo… https://t.co/fC6v619EWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AM34 really earning that new contract ehh! Your effort is absolutely disgusting! You look non existent out there!… https://t.co/0uKmZp7yLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF the Demokkkratic National KKKommittee (DNK) have already decided that Senator Kamala Harris (@KamalaHarris,… https://t.co/dyS9fE0WBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I will be happy with Ed Sheeran sitting on the fucking throne so long as I finally get #CleganeBowl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhh shit!!!! My edges just got snatched.. emmet is not playing!  #HTGAWM https://t.co/iv98q1ouwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We may be old and broken down, but we can still #getbuckets. #uncledrew #oldparklandcrew @thechinzilla dgoldsticker… https://t.co/oeOcPdmmMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[New AOC doll. At the grownup table.  @ffweekend https://t.co/aqyAP6KJ7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[If somebody had a gun to my head and said “recite something word for word or you die” this would be it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricFPhillips Contrasts greatly w/ his salesmanship of the Amazon HQ2 plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @NightlyPolitics It's because Trump is likely on mind control pills]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wife @goddessjuless and I took a little walk this morning around the #island of #monterio ... #flooded… https://t.co/5wBYExINJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleigh40466485 @JonasAfrend @alllibertynews @OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1… https://t.co/Y5F5ehLGBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techcoachjuarez That's so awesome! Congrats to you and those educators!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the new replacement for Facebook which is badly needed? I have not used it but I will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day One: I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @mmorrisBHS. I’ll post covers of 7 books I love—no expla… https://t.co/enBOnWqLpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can always tell a person that doesn’t know much about the dynamics of youth soccer. When you ask what’s the probl… https://t.co/C7gKqKhaUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaBRobbins No report available for the 2 minutes BEFORE that when we had that 7 point lead. Refs stole the gam… https://t.co/hY8tXiVwVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melissa lleva dos semanas en ingles y ahorita me levanto con esta pregunta.. Any plan for the weekend? Vaia vaia lo… https://t.co/vqaVfiYok5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Kaczyński jesteś pedałem czy nie, przyznaj się! W teczkach akcji "Hiacynt" sporo było o tobie. Co za różnica z res… https://t.co/iIjSNprZZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are those maggiemckethan ? @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/HjdBBD6yA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super late night thought but I hope one day i can redeem myself in the FGC in terms of the spectators watching. Onl… https://t.co/NAPy3qM99h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdwachter Should have gone with apple fritters, get your fruit servings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve recently accepted a challenge from @edocarroll to post the cover of 7 professional books, no explanations or r… https://t.co/mywJeb3xpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cabron no recuerdo eso de le pelicula... pero me interesa jaaja #hp #HarryPotter #MiercolesDeGanarSeguidores… https://t.co/SxD4MyUkrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sinjin1 @britainelects @Panelbase @UKLabour Also I just saw scotlab spent more money raising funds last year than they raised...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine going through life thinking that humans will never act right unless the government puts a gun to their head… https://t.co/EDggJguIjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maximizing the benefits of today's sophisticated arsenal of FDA-approved medical products requires an equally advan… https://t.co/dSG8siixQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Roat Ok well if you offer no explanation you're trolling.   I guess you were the only one who knew otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy coffee shop with some Sinatra in the background in SF feels very movie like for some reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class 4A Boys Regional Sem-final:  FINAL West Limestone 51 Curry 26  Christian Clemmons led the way for the Wildcat… https://t.co/N5snU3Q6U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is embarrassing if this is how the leafs are going to play playoff style games come April #Leafs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been to a concert in like a whole month so uhhhhh I think I need to buy some concert tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be another fun game #downtown @Coatman1 @JeffGriesch @gussowilliams5 @HuskersWBB keep it up don't let up #YouBetcha]]></document><document><![CDATA[The San Jose Sharks just got screwed big time!  A gift win for the Boston Bruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proof that you don't need to be #CaptainMarvel to be a boss. When elected, I'll continue advocating for inclusivity… https://t.co/XFHjxFvbOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp WTF schlapp! Why is not okay to call the worlds biggest liar a liar?? You on the right accept lying as th… https://t.co/7X4vlZBCWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doorsandcorners Is it acceptable to blame you? You were in attendance today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_kevsl @RegalCourtier7 That's true but he gotta say that. On the other hand, homies gotta abide by the code.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distinct_Words @Phishie_Philly Comments on what he would be called PPH was the cause. #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKAY BUT DELL LAPTOPS ARE BASICALLY JUST AS MUCH AS MACS AND HPS AND EVERY OTHER BRAND NOW!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remove Rep. Ilhan Omar from the House Foreign Affairs Committee - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/ta9ZLQRA3C via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting with my very own Congresswoman’s office @RepMaloney @CarolynBMaloney with members from @CenterForArch… https://t.co/Vpj1S0q1I7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotCoachJohnson @georgiapburdell Russell displeases the Queen https://t.co/Pmhj7AYcx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great point. Yesterday, I understand but today is a much different story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @RepAdamSchiff Does Schiffy know that the presidential power of pardon is in the Constitution and that… https://t.co/9ECUUQHkh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobby_riggins11 @MrMasonOBrien @WTAMUPOLICE Never really experienced that one, bud! But hey good try with that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flixology101 @MooseheadLager It’s a great combo, better than Oreos and milk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @TavianBorseth hope you have a great one g🙏🏽 big things coming in your future my man 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFPhq @sendavidperdue So David Perdue @SenatorIsakson @RepLoudermilk pass Trump's MASSIVE VICIOUS RICH REPUBLICAN… https://t.co/OIRnaoRWRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats and happy #ValentinesDay to all the happy couples 💑. And to the rest of us, happy Thursday. 🍻🍸🍷cheers. #singleawarenessday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I call that market macro efficiency. Did the same trading OEX options and Brent in the 90s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos Kevin McCarthy @kevinomccarthy is a @realDonaldTrump puppet! (Look close...you can see the strings!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te sientes cansado magnus rico suplemento q te da energía asta 8 horas para más información asclik en el enlace 👉💪👊… https://t.co/BvDgqe5pWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[De La Salle 95 Golder 61 Final #IHSA  @NBCSPreps @mikeclarkpreps @michaelsobrien @Tim_OBrien10 @disabato @HSBBALLjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I believe this dip shitt doesn't even look at his comments! I respect the presidency but you are a fuktard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighheelsDes @TimRunsHisMouth Any updates on the Virginia Gov, Virginia Lt Gov and Virginia Atty General?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broadcity I regret being so late to the party. This show is pure gold. #BroadCityDelivered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMundi13 @FrankLaic @torontofc I think when a player wants to leave, their heart won’t be in it and naturally not… https://t.co/YpvG4W3f1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir her meds are in her bag any why am I on hold when nobody is there?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GotToMyExerciseClassLate ☹️ If you are motivated, you can get your stretch in in my IG story @ Museum Mile, New Yo… https://t.co/ggy73FgJKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanDavies84 It’s funny seeing women in short and flip flops saying it’s snowing omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, @discordapp. Why in the world can I not turn of people's screen shares in Voice Chat. I have my friends watchin… https://t.co/GDoWrvZqBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are being played for a fool. It’s the coordinated exercises with South Korea that keeps North… https://t.co/8p6yJRKt2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickerySec @tedcruz Senator Cruise, I also demand an answer to this question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is probably not that unusual, but I haven’t seen it before. Stanford student section has heckling cheat sheets… https://t.co/Lab8HbFGKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh and find some new words.Big and great are getting old]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamUpRGC we, have a position.. I like my odds... the impressions are a  all time high... and, climbing https://t.co/eOql3TaEad]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Coast Christian Preschool at CDEA Conference #ignitethepassion2019 @ First Baptist Church of Orange Park - Fi… https://t.co/4oTnTmFy9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the desirable jobs are spending other people's money, reporting on  spending other people's money and lobbying… https://t.co/E4nWbcdkfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much like the #WWEHOF was a joke until Randy Savage's induction in 2015, so too was the Hollywood Walk of Fame unti… https://t.co/o4HF7mCA3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nSaSADb0xn @SeanRMoorhead I wouldn't say they are not as engaged but they are the targets of propaganda and they r… https://t.co/1auTv82AMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dc8bit Agreed.  If you're cordial with the bar owners I'd give them a friendly "heads up."  In today's litigious w… https://t.co/R8LtqU6uEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pops is still undecided... Any suggestions? #NHLJets #WPGvsTBL #GoJetsGo #Bolts #Tampa #Florida #YearSix… https://t.co/lFdKF8PteE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Velvet Merkin by @FirestoneWalker at @easytigeratx — https://t.co/wvy1bGwwj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewGalanty You’re right. But when a MAGA hat wearing person does commit violence we never hear any apology fro… https://t.co/QoXUuJm2vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thugmajesty The cost of living in Massachusetts in general sucks. Best of luck finding somethin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moparmann76 @HurdOnTheHill If one state makes it hard to own a gun, criminals will just get their guns from states… https://t.co/sr6ojjS3yC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malemalefica I love this. I could tell you some things about Diamond Head on Hi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrison__weber Your a sad strange little man, and you have my pitty. (PS. It autocorected to kitty, I almost kept it)]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: There are about as many Sanders-to-Sanders Democrats as Clinton-to-Biden ones: At least for now.… https://t.co/F1i3dXyIfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you've ever wondered what kind of person defends @realDonaldTrump even after knowing all we know at this point i… https://t.co/PLStDBUytz]]></document></documents></author>