<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1 #MAGA… https://t.co/Q8DOmaWRRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTS of our shoot yesterday. I love my face,I’m very excited about what is happening behind the camera. 😂 . . . .… https://t.co/TTgfCMQBUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another example how you touch people through what you do and who you are.   Thank you.....God bless and #lgm https://t.co/JttjNt7muz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn that first dude that dig up some dinosaur bones was probably confused as shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County Airport - @dtweetin in Romulus, MI https://t.co/pUbYg4P2Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKaetz @TheReber007 @ESPNCleveland Injuries happen to hitters just like pitching injuries but that being said it i… https://t.co/TWlW805mYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@true_pundit I wonder?  Has this Blowhard race-baiting mouthpiece ever done anything for our Republic or has she ju… https://t.co/BLcLojIpLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean like Marshon Lattimore does on the regular vs Julio Jones?   He literally tackled Julio Jones on a 9 route… https://t.co/fjyZm8qlNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @politico In order to say there is actually disinformation you have to have this weird little thing called proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddyxlonglegs1 @NXOnNetflix Stardust Crusaders might be added later this year at the earliest but DIU will be added on late 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️FIRST ALERT❄️: Cold weather fans rejoice! Winter is far from over for the ArkLaTex.   Find out when our next ARCT… https://t.co/Ix6JJ4t2e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 weeks in just doing main sets of 10x10 and 8x8 we have guys hitting 280-405 on squat already here’s sophomore def… https://t.co/S1tvT8BVl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paul_eastside @Bowler1961 @DetroitRedWings I don’t have Netflix I’ll search when I get home on direct tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I have to keep seeing things like this. I had already put to bed the idea of Harper coming to the #Cubs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My thanks to @createartcenter for hosting me in concert and workshop yesterday. Had a great time and hope to be bac… https://t.co/zNIJBxFouQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yanks vs Blue Jays (@ Dunedin Stadium - @dunedinbluejays for @Yankees vs @BlueJays in Dunedin, FL)… https://t.co/auLQ4qAyHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Sayer I mean Snell and Verlander are gonna regress too but they’re still elite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I have learned: When everyone in the room tells you you're drunk, it's time to fall down. There are times… https://t.co/Ya8Geqdn32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still not a single pic? Shouldn’t be hard for someone to get one when she leaves today]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy for them but who puts butter and oil in coffee? I’m missing something here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @PeteButtigieg @CNN I'm definitely intrigued. Impressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was an exit interview to find out info on how Tomlin is running the locker room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unlimited Open Training Sessions Monday - Thursday. * Meal plans * 3 additional Fitness Boot Camps per week * Inter… https://t.co/eZScXQsgvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LostFelicia @RobotThomas My dad did the same thing. And the good ol’ days of sitting around the dinner table after… https://t.co/9S4lgh7yuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felix_Sicard That's what happens when your skate speed is half of everyone else and can't hold onto the puck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radkat I think that pattern extends quite a ways... Though Twitter may be a problem, soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX10Phoenix Sending my prayers to the Jaguar 🙏🏽nobody better touch him or her. 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SconnieSports Dude I opened Twitter and half my feed is people obsessed with fant because of a 40 time. Like sure!… https://t.co/2tGoPSsaw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock Bridge leads Belton 17-0 with 3:55 left in the first quarter. https://t.co/hiofBHY1ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reagancolyer @rcsanchez93 Oh Seattle is rad, I just don’t know if I’d ever qualify it as a college town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicklovekicks Hope things are ok at home Lagerald. You &amp; your family are in my thoughts and prayers. https://t.co/VwqmhwOvSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmall I don’t believe there is a right or wrong way but for me, I think it’s better to keep all the type aligned… https://t.co/qeuPEFK8B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesillybuddha @Tacky_Nerd @G0nFreaks @Demthagod @Oh_Watup Ours won’t be a failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is now a jonas brothers stan account so get ready for me freaking out over joe, mildly freaking out over nick… https://t.co/GphlmGbiOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viccccccc7 @ashaleyjanell @MarinaNuckles You two know each other?? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alelopezp_ @kleeomg Pues al final donde manda capitán no gobierna marinero y pues me bañe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Gosh Wally wouldn’t it be neat if everyone whistled show tunes and rode bikes to work?”  “Oh Beev don’t you know… https://t.co/uSbfXzZPQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human freedom is the enemy of the conceit that resources are limited. The conceit that resources are limited is the enemy of human freedom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasChance @sportsmediaLM That’s how I read it. And if so, $100k please. But it’s obvious the penny somehow should be the answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯… https://t.co/PNlKDrxSfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @TPUSA @LeadershipInst He must get the maximum sentence for that crime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[white chicks in porn get fucked in the ass like it aint shit.....asshole be looking like a chimpanzee booty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm three hours into this day and I've already reached my maximum amount of stupidity I can tolerate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@portupielsalee2 @lauriadaleplay @LMXLM @MiguelAlemanM @ALEXBASTERI Un placer!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitting the town with the Muzzys. @ Tannin Wine Bar &amp; Kitchen https://t.co/L8OC9TWL5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Paddleton they talk about and watch a Kung Fu movie called Death Punch. Is that a real movie???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was wondering who, if any, of the 17 candidates for Public Advocate supported the Amazon deal and, of course, the… https://t.co/H1sADwpxZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Budget to demolish Georgia State space doubles to nearly $10 million https://t.co/fPsEBSjE4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Temedaio_ @JasFly It would have stemmed from this https://t.co/n3DXARmxG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Done for the day (@ somewhere between here and there in TX) https://t.co/x6vrToRUjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democratic Harrassment of President. GOP must muster their forces and stand up for President Trump. It’s a travesty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some vitamin B(ike) #tbt to low altitude flying at #imwaco703   #bebetter #gohard #freshstart #mojoracing… https://t.co/hnO0502hCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Reagan Knew the value of Mexican labor, there hard work familly values contribution to U.S. economy,… https://t.co/gjv0DKAjiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BbHorror great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my latest horror film review CREEP https://t.co/DSOrEgTONa https://t.co/tfWuWO5PwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing right now in Las Vegas... and it’s staying on the ground too. Looks like we brought down the snow...… https://t.co/DRLq6BKG1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedrogomezESPN @SPChrisHatfield How do you envision the Sox playing out Devers, Chavis and Dalbec? Devers stays pu… https://t.co/rvemz8jEtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deadletterpoets @talkingrobins The movie hasn’t even come out yet. See it then make your judgment. It’s ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanCovay I believe the reaction to the video tells us more about society than it does about Larry and Pam Baer.... pretty sad....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williedinardo “oh you’ve never been to Tigers Den? Yeah you’re not from around here” LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump - "I didn't need to do this. I'd just like to do it faster." … so … how is this a… https://t.co/O11ApqTLrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeyesposito That's funny, because mine would be titled Mario Kart: The Fuck is that Shit!?:A Memoir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VT was good. Cheers! propigbrewery alchemist foambrewersvt hillfarmstead @lawsonsfinest @alvinnebeer @ Carlisle, P… https://t.co/rCyVQ1ZXdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilsonp911 @benshapiro I’m sure you still believe everything you did 17 years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡JUST SOLD🏡 Upgrade season is in full effect. The journey of contacting me on thinking about a change, to cashing i… https://t.co/ywwtfrtrqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTAIntro2Soci how come African Americans that are a part of the lower class have a higher number of members that g… https://t.co/rHscfqCCOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The priests and the captain of the temple guard and the Sadducees came up to Peter and John while… https://t.co/83QAXRRhW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy247 @MrSmith9ja @LundyLunds23 @BIGPartyOne ... and a very good example of the intersection between historica… https://t.co/dMlOKEHEAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistacabbage Yeah, a check to separate from the puck is part of the game.   But skating in full speed to drive the… https://t.co/CDYH3uoEw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my new listing in #Murray! Come be my neighbor!🏡  OPEN HOUSE: Saturday, March 9th 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM 6576… https://t.co/2kXDUojpgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ Are Baby Boomers who watch Fox also aware it broadcasts Russian Propaganda?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvvheartxcx @OfficialEmail THERES MORE OMG SOMEONE GIVE ME HER @ PLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really getting tired of this nigga tell me to turn my music down 🙄🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm He is rather annoying. We are letting him do whatever he pleases.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brodostthoucode @marti4667 @redsteeze But we can be pissed at MSM for pushing this obviously fake story, I think T… https://t.co/nPhQTZXFW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Newport Beach Boardwalk in Newport Beach, CA https://t.co/VdysCL2Rox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotThatMelB @kwicke3 @patrickhealynyt @maggieNYT I’ve got a stat for you.. 92.63% of ecology majors, don’t find jo… https://t.co/c2IFoKV2BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerMahanCoe Dude, I totally agree. This goes back to the authenticity thing completely. I think for those of us… https://t.co/NmoGrxJ8E2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFuhriman @SaltyTyrman @WestsidePizza To each their own. Some folks insist that pineapple has no place on pizza. I… https://t.co/gvy95kY52n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerveyRoads13 @MLBStats @AROD @PujolsFive @Rockies @Yankees Blocked —&gt; Reported.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kieraAshley7 @JacobAWohl @ShyLilMermaid @realDonaldTrump Actually not true, in 1994 she claimed not to know who he… https://t.co/VAEFFSqX5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[#backstreetboys @ Planet Hollywood Resort &amp; Casino https://t.co/Icm4klEPqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NHLPlayerSafety announces #Flyers defenseman Radko Gudas has been suspended two games for his high sticking/slash… https://t.co/RvrI4KN992]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigPitt25 @yayaajp She about to beat everyone’s ass in that room until she gets her answer haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtTheBuzz_ Basketball only sport where the fans can actually put paws on the players]]></document><document><![CDATA[A salt truck on Taylor Mill Rd dropping salt, but not having any problem navigating the road. https://t.co/TPGbgP308b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarvardDivinity @Harvard Aren't we in one? I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770… https://t.co/vRugXIW2F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:27.6°F WchillLow:7.1°F Wind:7 mph Dir:WSW Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.02in Hum:71% UV:0.0 @ 16:00 02/13/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LondonFire @FDNYWomen @MayorofLondon @LFBCommissioner Congratulations @LFBCommissioner!  I have been privileged to… https://t.co/2ENsTV2r2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myldwill77 @MBTA_CR @MBTA Update - it’s 10AM; 3hrs into my commute and I’m now on my 3rd train of the day (4th if… https://t.co/WpSSTX15Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the lighting on this photo! #kiss #kissband #anaheim #hondacenter #rock #rockmusic #rockband #hardrock… https://t.co/NHnxWfYnAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[White House is barring all but 1 print reporter from the Trump-Kim dinner. This is not how this country operates,… https://t.co/4JIA0bwYGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geoffkeighley @thegameawards I guarantee he will always have a spot...but will you always be host?. My vote is for… https://t.co/24d6LBAhKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icp Whoop whoop; fresh! Can't wait to pick up cd! Fearless Fred Fury &amp; Flip The Rat both 🔥🔥🔥🔥!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY Rohan! Mr. Smith better have that information for you and me😅! #mhsbdayselfies https://t.co/qhbIX986ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@protoz0ha @Achibo0 But the tradition requires entire pizza... https://t.co/hXePu2T20p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Briggs1 @kristphr 6 years of dealing with well done steak chats. My lord props to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting in the mood for tennis, I got my tickets for the first weekend in Indian Wells open! #poptennis… https://t.co/Oep3en2k1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman Why not public option to set the conversion in motion? People would convert voluntarily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalazsSimonBalu Yeah but it's not like I'm shoving snow in. I keep it to a minimum. I don't really want a repeat o… https://t.co/73C7vwqOMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know what it’s like to lack motivation  I know what’s it’s like to have extreme pressure to perform I know what it’s like to be HUMAN]]></document></documents></author>