<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Best Valentine’s Day text I’ve gotten all day 🥰 https://t.co/7PqLdb0ZZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lady at the check out at my local grocery store looked at me and said, “This is totally random but what is that… https://t.co/NbcQb7lsxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m never posting anything on marketplace on Facebook again, it literally makes me hate people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 COACHING UPDATE 🚨  Please join us in congratulating @coach_ham on his well-deserved promotion to safeties coach!… https://t.co/GjUIgfD1Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pgeerkens  So you "liked" a willfully ignorant soul-poisoned hateful reply to me.  I'm so not impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wacky hair and even wackier faces! @BelleViewES #spiritdays https://t.co/keF2WtqdvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET ME SOME SUN, TEXAS. It's been so grey so long, I feel like I need a SAD lamp... #BroadCity… https://t.co/ateoQ1U9ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwyerAlys I talked2 you a couple months ago I a very English Ani am 50far from fat and we were having a nice time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @LJR1106 Cohen destroyed his career &amp; his credibility.  The  sharks will tear him to shreds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX23BradCarl #okwx 4:33 AM Saturday- Kendall Whittier Neighborhood 47* feels like 44* Drizzling 🌧 wind SE 6 mph,… https://t.co/WeRN3aWQW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RvGomez02 Ah yes, gargoyle gray is my favorite. It matches the stonework around my home. Color would be out of pla… https://t.co/tQ8qD4KvSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope. They're voting to uphold the US Constitution. The most important document in any Presidency. At the top of th… https://t.co/R9v66ik30j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhetrick @JonVigliotti @GayleKing @CBSThisMorning You can see someone standing behind him. You see feet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcmuffinman Ok this actually wasn’t about you but now apparently it’s applicable. I DIDNT EVEN KNOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me feel older thank knowing So Far Gone came out 10 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i want to be remembered for is... having the genuine heart.❤️ all the good vibes always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Не знаю, интересно ли это читать, но мне интересно это писать. Поэтому через некоторое время продолжу.😆🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOBGeez @MDAndersonNews @ShahNyma @znjamal So great to see you today! Thank you for coming out to support!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wrote a @theactionnet letter: TELL YOUR REPRESENTATIVE: PASS THE “RAISE THE WAGE ACT OF 2019.”. Write one he… https://t.co/z7eZD9HuUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to see you tomorrow morning.  🌞 Where else can a family (up to 6) eat breakfast for $20? Thank you to the wond… https://t.co/livKEDi9wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day on the Strip 🎲💎💸🇺🇸 still trying to find Mike Tyson’s tiger, plenty of time yet 🐅 #vivalasvegas #lasvegas… https://t.co/UY937OmsrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Check the Miami Herald in-depth  coverage of the Alex Acosta situation. Nothing but a nest of perverts a… https://t.co/e98qLKLygg]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOHN BENNETT 195 1A STATE CHAMPION!!!!!!! 😭😭🐻🥇🙌🏻🤼‍♂️  MAMA BEAR IS CRYING AND IS CRYING HAPPY TEARS https://t.co/RHdx0WA22b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler This is an antisemitic conspiracy theory about 2 Jews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Mercer Langston was the first African-American to pass the bar in 1854. The next year, he was elected town cle… https://t.co/ClNgB8nDT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not about the size of your circle, it’s about the loyalty that’s in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It baffles me that a one hour change on the clock can make such a difference yet here I am, wide awake at 2am. I LO… https://t.co/a2oxu7voNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinSalo3 @TheOfficerTatum @alex_spagnuolo @realDonaldTrump Really I am not a socialist but I don't believe that… https://t.co/xx3R0SKdkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[But our love was stronger by far than the love  Of those who were older than we   ~Edgar Allen Poe🖤  #twithaca… https://t.co/339pWPe8Ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KSpringsLions K Ss in .@BencinasKinders class are learning with .@SMART_Tech #CobbInTech #CobbDLDay #DLDay https://t.co/dDJLW6XyWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[😆 are we trying to get her recruited?! ... because if so, I have  another one in the class of 2036...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil_Lewis_ In my entire 24 years, 3 months, and 2 days of life on this planet, I have never once used or felt the… https://t.co/hDUkpo6PBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doritkemsley1 Don’t you get it?  People see what is going on with LVP and how you have ganged up on her like junio… https://t.co/vNIcU1qMl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlkSantaX @MrsblksantaX @CIAnderson3 @1helpamerica @PoliGal @Toni_Bostone @ungemarg @SuzyQuest @MasonPampinella… https://t.co/WfGdErCsrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkharris2002 @CounselorJMT @GSCSAware @GriffinSpalding You know we love our safe place, works at the secondary level too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is happening 🥰😭 💒 #jrbridesmaid #bridesmaiddress #my #baby #is #so #grownup @ The Wedding Shoppe https://t.co/6cno00X9gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Received a junk email from a "recruiter" about how my experience as a Commissioner is desirable to many companies l… https://t.co/vIkximxjfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVE TO MISS THE 21ST BIRTHDAY OF @ClaireNeville OR I WILL FAIL A CLASS I AM THE WORST]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️Happy Valentine  birthday to my sister @ETSU90 Alice Crowley!   Have a great day!❤️❤️🎁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep down you know what is in your best interest. Put yourself first and follow your intuition. Create healthy boun… https://t.co/qOOqYkQpiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim and Joey! You always make @NJAHPERD more fun, enjoyable, inclusive, and meaningful! Thanks for sharing your lov… https://t.co/eXd8uSxEyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets start! #readingtime #momtobe #tracyhoog #babywhisperer https://t.co/bAN4EsVydF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penelope has always been such an independent child. Never wanted to be held, always wanted to explore. Sebastian is… https://t.co/IcT9vBndGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quand Normand Auclair se déguise en Cyrano dans ses temps libres ❣️... @OvidePlouffe Merci pour cette magnifique so… https://t.co/E6YGO1zqlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[i say this all the time but this world is toooooooo small! I know wayyyyy tooooo many people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't realize how long my hair got until I saw this. Kind of sad that the pink is basically gone ☹️ how was your… https://t.co/3wt6ydh1kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Optionality is the greatest currency of life.” - @ClarkValberg #InVisionIRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol. My friend turned out to be right. Ya Mexicans are too loud. Hahaha. Literally my mom yells too much. Even when… https://t.co/7x37rc3NKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow She Needs to Go NOW !! Especially With her Boyfriend With PERSONAL Info. On CONGRESS Email !! Your Above the Law !! Newbie]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one iconic moment when @Miguel and I made eye contact https://t.co/xh7XC4biEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place just screams brunch. Halfway to the weekend! ☀️⁣ ⁣ ⁣ #visitarizona #absolutelyscottsdale #scottsdale… https://t.co/sb0PKayi2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaetantguevara Main stream “media” is the empire’s tool of colonization, it make things seem real.  #VenezuelaCoup… https://t.co/KX6bWVfoij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBarrie I am glad that someone is calling out LeBron. LeBron knew what he was getting into. He is not a good te… https://t.co/m1UOTw6eh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[[More] for “them” doesn’t mean [less] for “you” it’s a whole bunch of [get you some too] out here. 💯 💰👜🎒😼🚗🛩🏘📍📈💡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 12th Birthday, Elizabeth Fisher!!! Have an amazing day!!! @Bryantprin @RachelMarieMom https://t.co/qXfSyh4clH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ve fulfilled my cross-cultural requirements in one meal! In Grand Rapids, MI- notorious Dutch background-… https://t.co/824VbWlLTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[why did my boyfriend make this meme and send it to me at 2am https://t.co/YvWvAs8TrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#swipeleft for #purejoy travelswithallie #snow #oregon #whitedog #traveldog #myheart #doodlesofinstagram @ Bend, Or… https://t.co/Z89GlbW4Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/V8HXRpcHTN #reciperemake #glutenfree #blueberrybiscuits 💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a nose job but I’ve never found a before photo online that looked at all similar to my nose and so I have no idea how it’ll turn out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being friends with a girl just because you like her is the sleaziest thing ever, and honestly if they had kept that… https://t.co/yNGVmV1PSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJMack @SenFeinstein If they’re born then they weren’t aborted, duh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have 6M followers. Can you please stop promoting yourself and blowing up my TL with stupid tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[National #RandomActsOfKindnessDay !! Imagine if everyone in the @CityOfMountAiry did one single random act of kindn… https://t.co/RahKuV4GZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 Free speech is going to be a thing of the past. Praying for you to remain safe Laura ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOD that has a Son.. who's name is above EVERY NAME... JESUS IS HIS NAME.. not allah..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got sunburnt protesting... #NotesFromNationalEmergency #PresidentsDay https://t.co/LClYU9ST11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwwww..those eyes!  They get us every time!  Life is better with a dog or two in the house 🐾🐾🐕🐾🐾💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Don't give this girl any airplay.  She went off the rails years ago.  It is just sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if people are trying to purposely lower #CaptainMarvel score with reviews? I haven't seen it yet, but I th… https://t.co/lkTQDnRCPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[the whole time I was on my trip I was just pretending I was on CA time so I wouldn’t be confused when I got back an… https://t.co/XuoypnWLnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have absolutely no use for people like you Harris who stands for Killing Baby's.  And your family the SLAVE OWNER… https://t.co/T38HJ1AeSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredMichaelis2 @Lrihendry @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Your President is the one spewing hate. You must have your he… https://t.co/g7U9WtjUI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are all my great bowlers out there? Here's your chance to show off those skills.  Sunday, Feb 17, 9p-1a, @AMF… https://t.co/bf3dS9d9hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmfao i remember in middle school i used to role play gg characters on myspace with my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please show @colton how to open a freakin’ bottle of champagne! 🍾 @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iveyjanette_207 @Lupus_Chat @CaringForLupus @Xtel007 @SynceNerd_Carli @TiffanyAndLupus The surgery further weaknes… https://t.co/AWxeqIrJEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like doc said.. Somethins gotta give.. Probably at someone elses bar,  not his. A musical meltdown.. Afterall,… https://t.co/PSsx4rB5If]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets for the aces show tonight in DC is $6..... someone call me an Uber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck. Yes.   @DonCheadle, you’re a god damn saint and I love you forever.   - Signed, someone who wishes she had pe… https://t.co/n3UUSr0a9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case youre wondering. Hes gone through half the loaf of bread already. Thats like 5/6 sandwichs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @KonstantineMit2 She convinced young children that they are going to die in 12 years! Congratulations for… https://t.co/YJp8SXIOqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some great music and tasty micro-brew beverages! #SmokedMarcyMild #Sláinte! (@ Woodland Farm Brewery -… https://t.co/MazusV27YC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fighting with @SickKids to combat childhood #Cancer. What’s your VS? #SickKidsVS https://t.co/wPNfnXPWed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Who are the blue collared guys behind her I wonder!?Someones financing this dingbat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[coming to the unforuntate conclusion that I’m equal parts jean ralphio and schmidt so please send Ts and Ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AverageGamerTVO @Hanabishi8918 @R3almTh3 @Phantomdragon31 @SammysDaddyo712 @SpRiNgStR3Am @Amberbubblez1… https://t.co/kvl1ETvZ7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who do you GET to do life with? These are my people! Asher has a school field trip 3 hours north at a historic Russ… https://t.co/0rfVK7OdRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timberwolves @SteveHelwagen @NBA @KBD_33 Great work with the THEEEE here, friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 AM. I just watched the last eipsode of the season for Shameless and I can’t tell if I want to cry or if i’m tired or both]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m taking some advice and trying something new - I did a thing and am starting a beauty blog ! Feel free to che… https://t.co/H5nRWpOHaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you @AshleyAlese for writing this verrry necessary take https://t.co/61C9DFHpBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's laughter. #funniness #snicker #smirk #comic https://t.co/PEmUThqFX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been saying I’d go visit Reagan for the past month or so but I STILL haven’t gone ihms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey Of course! They are your voters. 🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of everyone in East Alabama and West Georgia. Be careful and weather aware!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin We as a nation need to never normalize what this administration is doing to our DEMOCRACY and continu… https://t.co/r72BVmAYP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaycemick @CNN @BernieSanders Are you freaking kidding me? Norway too foreign? It shoukd be the ticket fir these w… https://t.co/cLez5u8YcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobKellyFOX29 @FOX29philly Corn flakes w/honey, strawberry frosted mini wheats, Honey Nut Cheerios Raisin Bran, an… https://t.co/EOVqU8merZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Joe Biden give an endless hug to Hillary Clinton https://t.co/lug2HCO8G9 via @YouTube]]></document></documents></author>