<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's gonna be on seeing Shayna Baszler on a match against Mia Yim LET'S GET IT! #WWENXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that Adam Schiff  represents the Hollywood and Hollywood Hills district in CA? Now I know why he is so kooky and rabid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LodurZJ That’s a silly name for a mountain side dungeon protected by trolls and fire-throwers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randfish I had a client that refused to listen to advice about cleaning up their email list and were marked as spa… https://t.co/mIIvz2VMFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did i say all off season ??  Thank god @IndyCar is back next week . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the best year but still a great beer - Drinking a Pliny the Younger (2019) by Russian River Brewing Company at… https://t.co/prxw1yT404]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why were we the only gays at the rockabilly chili event today? Rockabilly is cool. Gays are cool. Chili is delicious. 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone even fooled me by using “Keezy” as their name and they rolled with my Harry Potter references trying to pre… https://t.co/uG8H4iNksH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyhudginsdc @EggerDC @NFL @MLB @NCAA @PhRMA So I replied, “So you’d prefer a socialist system like the NFL’s to… https://t.co/YuU3bumewf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? UNLOAD ASSOCIATE (Part-Time) - https://t.co/DAh6TRFCpa #SupplyChain #Westminster, CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaBestiaNegra16 For me it shows a more deep seated negative opinions he has of FCB to go from a footy match to mor… https://t.co/cxdO9TXJi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrooperBob_SC @MegMRivers I think a log went thru his windshield....ouch!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LSU replaces Vanderbilt as No 1 team in National Collegiate Baseball Writers rankings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_fibs Bad that such an important piece of artwork couldn’t attract a legitimate hugely excessively appreciative b… https://t.co/WDe1ZkV4A5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeirdreS I will definitely do Berlin, probably not Milan unless @alex_casalboni needs an emergency fill in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/4xMEmXHboJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travelnpack @paulsperry_ @RealMattCouch Can't expect anything less from a pro crime, corruption and anti American values]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moonspinner55 Dean is awesome until they put that unconvincing aging makeup on him, and then had him do that awful drunk scene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hifiman36 @tastyporkchop @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump I'm not trying to insult you. Your Qanon-filled Twitter feed does that well enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 Really you need to have a discussion with your AntiFa cousins. Tell them it’s time to smoke peace pipes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out! https://t.co/GZ5BEdgHAY #ThirtySecondsToMars #BalloonDrop #Encore #live in #Concert 2018… https://t.co/XGdhuEmPMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_MJF @LWMaine Congrats, @The_MJF -- now keep it warm for @IamTheDangerKid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@confessions_cup @magee333 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @suziday123 @cazij @CaraMiaSG @ja2cook @JackConnie… https://t.co/lGge3ALZhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotBryanRay Woo hoo!! Great analysis!! I do want to make clear when I said this article was, 'well written.' I mea… https://t.co/naZ1lRBCDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TakeALoveSongToTheBathroom Dancing with myself..oh oh oh https://t.co/7PA3QS10Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you soon beautiful #Seattle ! Sun the whole weekend! 🤩 https://t.co/jP9QS1JfoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beINSPORTSes @DonBisca @Jaimefmacias gracias por su buen trabajo saludos a mi hijo Albert sermeno y mi sobrino Aid… https://t.co/1bxPZB3dBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kick! Block! It’s all in your mind...  Yessssssssss!!! #ParappaTheRappaRulez!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does @edhelms do voiceover work? Announcements at IAH sound a lot like Andy. I'm just waiting for rit-dit-dit-di-do… https://t.co/6pvy5LqCad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iBreezy6 Find me an example of jstreet criticizing inn the way it criticizes birthright, aipac etc. many JStreet J… https://t.co/qamXzfZ9rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSUTurf students took the afternoon break at @APinv to check out Isleworth across the lake. Big thanks for Sean Du… https://t.co/syPza2A9KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexrosstweets @MontanaCOPP Sausage making at its finest! Looking forward to seeing the finished product #nmleg Co… https://t.co/ubm24GwC15]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIP Actor #LukePerry , known for roles in “ #BeverlyHills90210 and #Riverdale has died after suffering a stroke on… https://t.co/LBgqlQ0Usf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, singing under my breath to myself:   "wake me up...when September ends..."  My girlfriend, from behind: "That's… https://t.co/nbnBmiDWEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art 🎨 &amp; the  #law ⚖️ #grayrobinson 🚶🏻‍♀️🎈 #miamijudges 👩🏻‍⚖️⚖️👨🏼‍⚖️ @GRLobby @grayrobinsonlaw @originaIbanksy… https://t.co/9hHQaVrydN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBKPLO @MozzyThaMotive @yg bigrut415 united_playaz @ Bill Graham Civic Auditorium https://t.co/5nXprhQgMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If all goes well, I’m exporting and rendering and doing all that stuff to the FINAL versions of MISGUIDED Season 3!… https://t.co/Cjdg3qkgS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nickelodeon @TheNickBox I’d pay my weight in blue tornado bars to get to be any kid in #Wellsville.   #PeteandPete https://t.co/kxfYk1QLnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayYoungBR Cowboys - talent everywhere, starters on the bench.  Redskins - let’s count ‘em.  Yep, that’s ‘zero’ d… https://t.co/LatphezZF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalligShadow @YellowFlashGuy Yeah im pretty pissed he shouldn't be saying people who have religion are weak on a l… https://t.co/8v0PHOruiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hope Barca shows no mercy and slaps 3-5 goals in this game. Madrid have nothing this season. #ElClásico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintsHappyHour Maybe they learned their lesson about jumping in before the market sets itself *cough cough* kurt coleman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFordFANatic @MapleLeafs #FansGoFurther I don’t even remember choosing the leafs! It was already set in stone wh… https://t.co/YYI1V64d8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Wow! Wow! Congratulations to the @BC_Bearettes for winning the State Championship! You girls have represented… https://t.co/VVz1GnwCAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Problems Juan states are real - solution he is offering seems like it will only create worse problems in trying to… https://t.co/oFKAel3vwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tuff_Overlord @T31974 He has been losing velo since his mid 20s  that's a bad sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielHouseNFL Keys:  Coffey shoots at least 40%           Score 70 points or more           Curry supports Oturo… https://t.co/3dY17Hcnco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdb_jody @TimothyColman @billmckibben @Jawbonefnass It’s a beautiful poem by a beautiful man who knew how to live… https://t.co/kWyTcK39H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurawTheRealest @KellyJ_Mena @BklynCollege411 @KingsCountyPols Vermont's black leaders: we were invisible to Berni… https://t.co/QZJfLccQzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Th3Franchise @chadholland13 @TreyJohnsonnn @Zay_Conner https://t.co/Yq0JgxffcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo if you are heading to #vegas anytime soon you have to get to @ontherecordlv it’s the newest night spot in Vegas!… https://t.co/II8qh5mtjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted.  https://t.co/C4gfUAomdR  https://t.co/XMKWPDtknp   @HotMaleStuds @ns4wxxx @TLAgay @porn_actors… https://t.co/vyr0aTV2Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know is this Nevada team is good enough to make a final four when they play their best. When they play like t… https://t.co/UuaGJuBlqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saltair on the shores of The Great Salt Lake.  . . . . . . . #shore #shoreline #shotfromabove #castle #saltair… https://t.co/ul1AJBhZX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope reasonable people will start looking for real facts and stop giving in to gossip, smears, and projection of… https://t.co/8FVMOOM1CR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globaltimesnews Chinese tourists? Let me help you with that, you mean Chinese illegal overstays in the E.U. There, fixed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an English Golden Ale by @MadFoxBrewing at @MadFoxBrewing — https://t.co/253fsAOQLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck!! Dije hoy duermo temprano!!! Llego a casa a las 2 y el horario cambiooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, 0 point something. We have to account for Diamond &amp; Silk. 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngieSullivan0 @tsegerblom Rent rises too. We’ll have affordability issues but we can’t have it all ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerrettFarmer @JaladandDarmok @RolandelliDsign @ddmfhsuk @ausomedivergent @WilliamShatner Hi! I understand it's di… https://t.co/KQKiezuP4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and Gentleman!  I want to introduce to you  Mr and Mrs Lamont and Melvisha Davis!  #immarriednow  #Warren… https://t.co/392cxiVkJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMezzera @PWTorch @AEWrestling It would take a non-zero amount of money to get me to watch Raw like I would need… https://t.co/c4uya8nL6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0xmchow I guess what’s disappointing is that people who write about (or comment on) j-schools don’t bother to talk… https://t.co/kUNVg1iUMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your ability to influence and persuade others will account for more of your success than any other skill.… https://t.co/HPdTvF7Sni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn4amber @TJCarpenterShow @thenation To much education makes a liberal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachPhilLongo me and my @WvilleFootball staff enjoyed your sessions at Nashville @GlazierClinics. Good luck to yo… https://t.co/QH4xWcqgZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDMRMCMLXXXV @Lauren_Steiner @JDoza1 @mtracey The dissolution of American society, I suppose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Time for the U.S. to Lead on Data Privacy Law | Opinion https://t.co/ipfqDMpBmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DanielleVenton what is the typical compensation for a trade magazine article of 3-4000 words?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Margaux_mew @CoreyHirsch @dmmckey @DanRiccio650 @NHLCanes Yes, shouldn’t get too mad on the ice. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cougs4Iife That is a great example of how bad officiating has an impact.  If they had called the hook and hold, th… https://t.co/XscMK2jACW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethFratesMD @Havenlust Reminds me of the farm I owned. Worked at Atlanta International Airport. Massive Stress Jo… https://t.co/GFfpTakW4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to https://t.co/vIiiplnbyt @ Chozen Martial Arts Academy https://t.co/PJ7nvnzl3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there's one thing I can't stand, is grown ass adults who drag their feet when they walk. Unless you have somethi… https://t.co/3Hs9IEsTiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @Boothe08887997 AS I'm enjoying my steak/bacon/cheese on a bun breakfast LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamVTV @realDonaldTrump Watched, that is a lie. Unless of course the suggestion of not choosing hate is taken by a… https://t.co/X47UDF75LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhhhhh Michelle..... Come get her! We don't want n9 problems. https://t.co/9uG3TBU61h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start the week off strong. Make attempts today! @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/AE06CnkQsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SdDawg8 @xshs03g @nancy_hamm1 @JoanneTirado09 @cindy_nurse @AsiaTater @Lathenerd @kidgolferman @GodFirstGina… https://t.co/nUN5ZPaban]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueMystery No... ZERO DAY back door society...  And  A CONSCIOUS RESISTANCE. Rather than the GOVT generated THOU… https://t.co/CE7yJ6wSem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is everyone hating on this? I personally like it. https://t.co/8SSi0eYRu8 via @vice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter With a nobody throwing to him, that streak ends. They need @NickFoles..just sayiiinnnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker You're a freaking  FAG?? Dude! Really ? No wonder you were all uptight about the kid in Chicago.  https://t.co/mX0nWCPgaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simply going to post this short thread on a fwiw basis , noting that despite hearing such reports many times in the… https://t.co/pDBOogcTQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #brightwhitekitchen, we sure loved designing and building you...and even on this stormy LA day you are… https://t.co/Do3RJqWiCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericbolling Well she does work for @CNN after all... so I'm thinking she has loads of freetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoganmag It is a crop line so that they could reduce the size to run more strips.  There is an excellent explanati… https://t.co/xD9HgcX9N1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veneficaultrix I wouldn’t be going back there until I see photos of cleanliness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Termina 3er Cuarto @Fuerza_Regia 77-55 @CorrebasketUAT   #EsteEsMiJuego #LNBP #LNBPLaTienesQueVivir @LNBPoficial https://t.co/0co7Lgkphm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlarson32 Heck no! You are such a inspiration to all of us and we are so proud of what you’ve accomplished!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyphylilbitch And it’s always the people who’s parents pay for everything tryna give you constructive criticism lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myLusciousLife Think about it, hopefully save the taxpayer money, less s to Mara Lago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_oneil @art_stapleton Thank you.  That’s all I take his comment as.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotShadowNinja Their like”hmmm what do these both have in common?” Another guy “they both exist” “That’s it! You t… https://t.co/LyXIaNyNNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsilly3 @ElectronComm @Polixenes13 @BertelSchmitt @danahull You don’t know how to cope with people challenging you… https://t.co/Xn4nuyTBuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/hSH3oXDh80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of miles this week- . . . . . #zag1  #ibikekern  #bicycle  #cycling  #activeliving  #healthyliving… https://t.co/2FtjDK4Ewo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC What did you do with the one million dollars you and your staff embezzled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personally I dislike homosexuality and sexual abuse, and would never vote for anyone involved, including the two sh… https://t.co/JEqcNbV7z0]]></document></documents></author>