<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Adulting is ordering your first @grovecollab box and being genuinely excited about new, earth-friendly cleaning supplies 🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Polish Polish shoes. Polish polish in the news. Polish polish polish all day long. Polish Polish Polish, generations strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonigirlrustys That was so random I really don’t know what that was for but I picture him saying that]]></document><document><![CDATA[ig i had my lyft driver before and he mentioned that and he remembered everythinnngg even where i worked aaat and the movie we talked about]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great speakers @DNC meetings.  Inspiring words from Chairman Tom Perez and Rev. Al Sharpton. https://t.co/Jf5Dy42PbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone you could talk about any and everything with and keep em &gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will do! Happily. My guess is that HBO didn't get the ratings they were expecting. People generally don't like lies… https://t.co/sGaHbwBRda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourAlteredEgo @maddow Erik Prince-he and Betsy could share a cell. Sweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the best time playing with my little guy today:) I actually didn't play too bad either🤪😜⛳️💗 * * * * * * *… https://t.co/ElI56KVd83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo why do they wanna use the chapo’s money to build that freaking wall.. I don’t think so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bam6273 Can you go into the building it’s inspired from and get some ideas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandyRed He is!! I'm a lifelong wrestling fan but stopped going to live events years ago. Roman pulled me back in… https://t.co/jxJi21Oh2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great way to support a parent! Aside from the fact that holding a baby allows us to release prolactin and ox… https://t.co/xB7nvQozgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPFK @KPFKRadio this is news not what you're doing now on the radio! Bring back @jerryquickley]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was taking pictures of my Valentine’s Day makeup look that I did with my @jamescharles palette and my cat interru… https://t.co/xi6aIOLoUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night someone said to me “em if you really think about it, look at where you were a year ago and look where yo… https://t.co/oAHww1V177]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher you were talking about white people in dreads. A lot of deadheads wear dreads. It's a hippie thing. And… https://t.co/hK7T73q3JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Night Thoughts While Sick:  It's okay to cry https://t.co/jO95qTOpKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not going to hire me can you atleast send me an email to let me know I’m not getting hired and why 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband Rick got his honor 21 salute as a Marines yesterday at Riverside,CA... Couldn't afford the trip there bu… https://t.co/IOFklFtooE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. He does not age. No fair! Is it special water? What beauty products does he use? Sheesh he’s so pretty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black’s are raking in the cash with victimhood, boy that slavery thing is sure paying off now.😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is it with republicans and young girls?  Donald Trump Roger Stone Tucker Carlson Roy Moore Elliott Broidy Jeff… https://t.co/fh4Vlma28t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flipping tires🖤🏋🏽‍♀️  Let us design your next training 🏋🏽‍♀️ #greatness #trainer #athlete #muscles #fitness #fit… https://t.co/uOCspcAAFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh for frig’s sake. Denying themselves God’s cookie (Samoas) to own the Libs. Rolled my eyes so hard I got dizzy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rather experience a zombie apocalypse than see The Walking Dead continue with more episodes/spinoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitchhhh my paycheck AND tax $ hit my direct deposit at the same time I’m so mf juiced 🤪 this is dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching Flavor of Love, and I'm somehow so blown away by how ugly he is. Oh, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@butterfly019sw @JoDresbach @fabiola_pizana @RobeEmpire_1 @lunalover25 @rockromanfan @kaikaisonic @diamond_shonna… https://t.co/MH4MCoPf8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLoveBel0w @AOC Let’s dig up 15 year old jokes to support a false narrative]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would I go into cardiac arrest if I shotgunned a 16fl oz Red Bull? Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone plz knock some sense into me and tell me to get up and go to class]]></document><document><![CDATA[#safarilive Good Morning/Afternoon everybody! Made it just in time! Ready to bumble!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because: As brothern Elijah Cummings says:  “We’re better than this” “Stronger Than This”  United States of America… https://t.co/hqRCHYBe7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohshesprettytoo I be in the car like 🙄 But then Keith comes with the lil sexy chuckle and the ladies seem so happy… https://t.co/60aGZJ5h0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrayLiotta @Pizzapuff15 @LucyFurTweets The only sneks I hope are ever in my house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grandma_Shelia @DonnieFire @holachola @CapotesClaws @whyknotmeagain2 @Z3RoForksGiven @suzystays @h8Wankmaggot45… https://t.co/xVPZJ6RY0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoveled my driveway, but can’t get into my neighborhood, or down my street, or into my driveway, or in my car, but… https://t.co/fCQPjsBaBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOtherMandela I had a serious discussion with a friend yesterday who said, “I like to help people help themselve… https://t.co/J5UIu8AjuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning thanks to all the emotional OTA/Olicity tweets from when I was sleeping I'm crying again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kanvaz_GeRM If you're not Hindu, wouldn't that be considered appropriation? I'm sure some would find it offensive...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom That's saving $100/month.  Totally doable, even if you're only making $25,000 year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Explain $107,000,000 donation for your inauguration money payed for, and name of persons that donated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlecBaldwin is going to play Donald when we #Vice this presidency right?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to wake up early to take my mom to work. And instead of going back to sleep I’ve just been watching videos of monkeys hugging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking of Random Acts of Kindness week with bookmarks hidden in the library! Be kind...Pass it on!! #3RoxMHS… https://t.co/KDja4JRDGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marathongirlie @PatrickDempsey @MollyRingwald I want to see this movie too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wolf’s arc would not have been improved if Terry Farrell had stayed with the show, even though we were all so, so,… https://t.co/p0TOOA9E9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a wonderful evening hearing from some of Missouri’s female cabinet members.  An inspiring and insightful discu… https://t.co/cgJgbOSR8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b4ph_ Hahah you know me so well. I could just picture you copying me rn lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Office365 She's 8, in 3rd grade. She worked on it again last night. She discovered design ideas 💥 so she had a bla… https://t.co/QUCZHpPpeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day!! Still have only a few openings this weekend.  Text me to reserve your appointment today.  4… https://t.co/vBI7TqEZOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Says the man who bragged about grabbing women by the pussy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyDMVRealtor @LBoogie213 I am a retired high school English teacher, and I  simply believe we all can have a bette… https://t.co/aNbJxPZSyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo I Love Bean so much! I follow her on IG, and she always makes me smile 💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews If he thought he could get away with it, he would do it in a heartbeat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TunafishTiger @BriannaShrum Tbh I was like omg it has been 23 years? It's bound to come around again hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to #PleaseMe lets take a trip to the moon.  😊 https://t.co/dI1rqTYrjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[look at the weather sunday 🙄 i hate ga but pls don’t go back down IM BEGGING i hate the cold so much https://t.co/8D5xQ1C8sQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Karpiak tfw you realize you forgot about this tragic situation &amp; Adam's tweet reminded you it's an hour later now. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein OMG I didn't no he was that sick How sad for him an Trump could not care less!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mean to brag buuuut, I rocked my presentation y’all 💖👊🏻 And did I mention it was at a conference with 4K+ a… https://t.co/SHHFTrTgEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He is mad he didn’t win.  This must be the New Black!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @gator4kb18 @KevinMFerrara @trumpAngel45 @NahBabyNah @bedevilme666 @Libphobic @carlasare_john… https://t.co/luMR46aZox]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to impending weather forecast, there will be a “3 hour delay” (or sleep-in) on Wed Feb 20 for @GraniteBears GO… https://t.co/UQ8MdVT84B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump Ya mean the TREASONOUS asshat , Putin's bitch, stole the election. No we will never accept that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddiew_07 i get stressed when there’s one chip or something and then i have to take them all off 😅😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Trump is the most evil President ever! He does not care about these poor children and neither does hi… https://t.co/xebPWwLxFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITGeekCT Have you spoken to the planning committee about this? Retreats are not the time for politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelleHGRides @bikenewyork @TransAlt The bike was in the Hudson, so it’s outside of our jurisdiction. We have enough waterways of our own!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could someone please help me understand why the world is constantly bending over backwards to help Donald Trump esc… https://t.co/csxoZBisdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald  - any predictions on Tiger this weekend? I have always enjoyed your play-by-play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fentonpompey @fankristopan You’re right!!! It was just Kristopher #imcomingfancy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieAnneMore1 @realDonaldTrump God bless you &amp; Thank you so much for praying for Pres Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shout out to @Starbucks !! This location is super friendly. https://t.co/75ibSYw5R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casey’s Intercept is a must-read always, but if you, like me, understood that today’s Facebook announcement was big… https://t.co/i8GX8iONS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to look for an apartment in a different state next week so that's... terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If some Yankees fans actually thought they were getting Machado, I have some beachfront property in Orlando to sell them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin has to be up at 4 and he’s sleeping so peacefully.... but I just wanna bug him. Miss that little shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I’m deleting all social media apps to focus on myself. If you need me call me or text me? idk bye lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can literally keep your mouth shut instead of saying some unnecessary bitchy shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[i used to be so sad when my parents got deployed but whenever they leave now i be so happy 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christian_x3x3 @_KarlaaBoo Your first??? Omg you’re gonna have a blast. Best festival ever hands down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fox35Danielle @ryanelijah good morning. Can someone tweet out the information about the little girl with cancer wa… https://t.co/4vgFdvO8ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_stephmua L’octianne has a really great line of moisturizers and I love their exfoliate too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalSTP @MartinsvilleSwy Wow , what a Great prize to win tickets to @MartinsvilleSwy !!  🏁 Soooo… https://t.co/MokQ6Q7k4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finally watching Abducted in Plain Sight and I have a lot of thoughts https://t.co/rBKQjI7x05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up not having a good time being stuck in tempe https://t.co/lTm1XwEt2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bndaisies @MunozSusel @CP24 That’s terrible. Hoping and praying she’s found safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertJohnDavi I have two words for you!  “Battlestar Galactica” Brilliant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estaba esperando el bus y en eso llega una señora grande y le cedí mi lugar para que se sentara porque no había asi… https://t.co/LYmVEiRESj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pilot as we taxi for takeoff to Detroit just said “we are Motown bound” and it was everything. @Delta]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cutest valentine message I’ve ever gotten ❤️ https://t.co/qTVe0WTrL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ITaughtMyselfHowToGrow  the song by @TheRyanAdams that I think I relate to the most.I too had to teach myself how… https://t.co/3HgGFtNczU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracy43020084 @ChuckCallesto @richieintx Absolutely no way . Trust me on that! I am not even sure Jussie knew thes… https://t.co/8MX8D7qOMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Raisin? What the hell kinda name is that? Like the fruit??” - Donald President, 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[One in a series of a juvi eagle stealing a fish from an adult eagle on the Hudson river, making him land in the wat… https://t.co/dzwTcG1ObE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamaBethsWorld1 @LadyBoogiee @taraleigh2020 @ReviewsJans @AdiyanuAmari @AvidDiva @ich_angelo @FroggyPush… https://t.co/fTojj0QBcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaO @AdrianaH1130 Jajajajajaja escuela de monjas😂 awwww te mando un abrazo enorme! 😘 yo también te quiero much… https://t.co/WuxLdfkb9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NELLY161076 @joluisgarcia @AnaMafud @MauroMoralesMtz @_LASNOTICIASMTY Igualmente manita. 👏👏👏👏💛💙🐯😘]]></document></documents></author>