<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[For those of you who follow me from the DFW area, drive carefully. My dad was in a car accident...]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BEYUTMdJic #Prince #Funko #Pop Around The World In A Day Raspberry Beret video outfit #Ebay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kireau @TiffanyDavid113 @_murphylisa @tijohnson @OwnTheThroneMov @fitbit @cda0891 @dopamine Ugh that sucks!but you… https://t.co/ev3mo3jWBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @YouTube @FBI @NewYorkFBI @nytimes @AE911Truth @CIA @NSAGov @WhatTheMandela @NISTcyber @Microsoft @intel… https://t.co/JR0dHAN8Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louford1 It looked it.  Hopefully no retakes required for that one 😳 #Ouch #MurdochMysteries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bribrim I watched it too,  but you’re not there to hear conversations or see what’s really going on. Those shows a… https://t.co/0QAgX6Uwi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abualfawarss123 @zahrkh0a @SecStudiesGrp @gnuseibeh @bubasl @MHA_KSA99 @Dr_AlIsmail @Yoorrii9 @a_albander… https://t.co/yKC9UULKHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryamMonsef I prefer gender equality in Canada first.  You may want to invest in your "abroad" agenda soon though… https://t.co/oDWooqtZNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Barrett 82A1 50 BMG Rifle from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $9000! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/Px7ZZr8sOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennQSpoonerSt @WalkWithLyle I remember wanting Turner so bad in that draft.  I was so wrong about him.  I even w… https://t.co/Q0R0ZZucIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterAssEater Too many typos now i feel like this https://t.co/96RYZqksA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterMacKay says Justin Trudeau has already waived any [client confidentiality] privilege...  https://t.co/MQtVYkpbZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Firstly, it’s not your money, it’s ours. Keep it up and we’ll pull the plug and you’ll be working out of your… https://t.co/Lgw0EldZWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#haileesteinfelded#bumbleebeemovie#onset🎥🎬 @ Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk https://t.co/iTabhrFNUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Broken Heels by New Trail Brewing Co @ Hoffman cabin — https://t.co/zmvaXf2tg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sonora Sunrise Sterling Silver Pendant Save 20% Off With Coupon:. FEB20  EXPIRES 2/28/19  See More @… https://t.co/520S09TDZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents charged after toddler's body found in bucket of acid, prosecutors say  https://t.co/CtiEVxuRBG  Download th… https://t.co/Mya4cgzPJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacesam17 @JaredSiegrist @marquisegoodwin If you didn't see it put there, you know nothing. You assume it was put… https://t.co/hdnIKJaQSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @BannonRace Your bullshit is embarrassingly deep, sweetheart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all! It’s time for a #springtimejazzhang ! Hopefully see you Sunday! @DispensaryLV #vegas https://t.co/vUOJou8YG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[here, the sos lists things the us government has inflicted upon Venezuela in its attempt to undermine their democra… https://t.co/K54tzZbxEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats cause ya made it out your momma house, I hope ya make enough to buy your mom a house]]></document><document><![CDATA[It surprises me that anyone wants to play with LeBron anymore. I mean being repeatedly ran over by the bus has to g… https://t.co/mejSvxq0Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thareal_2......Welcome to the Family Little Brother.                               #WeAre... #LinenackerU]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is Canada described as a “full democracy” when it still has first past the post voting? And why is literally no… https://t.co/skm10Hly8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedaMor_ I agree but tRUMP isn't nothing but an idiot to keep us busy waiting on stupid things he says.True proble… https://t.co/JWvhM1DNSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark it in your calendars! #postit on your frigerator, this night is going to be epic! @thehellenbacks @DocEllisWeb… https://t.co/Fajs6Ir1PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Replacement heifers getting fed.  #cattle @JayPalm87431099 https://t.co/f7NKPofB8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCRadio I think it's only the Celtics.  They want Tatum and a first rounder.  Turning down the Lakers boatload… https://t.co/qT1HpS1lQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[First grade students in Mrs. Pabst's class learning about soil and water as part on our STEM Friday. @RootElem… https://t.co/d7l6SgpBfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all of our southwest_mississippi  and @southwestbsu students who were inducted to @phithetakappa today!… https://t.co/u8pi25Ln9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[*bravely endures a tumultuous week w/o bein able to play black ops due to my modem/router shittin on me like it sno… https://t.co/sUoHjVGZrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_favourite So if you liked Mean Girls...this has much better costumes. Otherwise HARD PASS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to Las Fontanas Mexican Kitchen for providing a weekly place for us to perform and share our music. We rea… https://t.co/VNjneCuz0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some live on the inside, some die💗 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/nkvSFeQwSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. @Colin_Hung and @nicolegrubner together. Big brains and collaborative talents. Neat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nascarman_rr I sure do miss the old Atlanta! Better racing and look in the stands at the fans!!! I saw Dale Sr dri… https://t.co/rR6tJPxYKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump O' beautiful, for spacious skies But now those skies are threatening They're beating plowshares in… https://t.co/aDWdFAVdAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phil and Team #Pantano #HomeDepot ready to hell with your #energyefficient #windows and #patiodoors… https://t.co/riV6NH8MqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now everybody watch Kyle Busch running to his trailer because he lost what a sore loser cry baby boys cry baby boys… https://t.co/lKuWKG7DTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_nich @timothyzillion @onethinline Look what I found :)  https://t.co/Qm44GewFfK https://t.co/ZJoayiwyl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMARCA @marca AL QUE DEBE CORRER ES A flor Y AL MUY IMBÉCIL DE solari RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We MUST balance the budget! How? - Entitlement Reform - Cut government waste - Eliminate Federal Agencies - All gro… https://t.co/m58IPwhPwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestleEvents @Ole_Anderson_ Jesus Christ I'm going to look like a monster next to these people today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LikeMike_52 Man. It would be crazy. Now we just need New Mexico to wake up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRC: UNT is down 68-66 and has the ball with 11.5 seconds left. UNT just took a timeout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Acumen Oil. Corporate America wants that oil. Its a tragedy Venezuelaa governing elect failed at investing it'… https://t.co/RXADz9Q8GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Probably for the same reason there is no longer a Democratic Party, it has been hijacked  by Social… https://t.co/OW9S4I5lIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingIsKing @RWAnimal @PaulElleringWWE The rolled up Wall Street Journal.....love it 😀👍🏼 Georgia Championship… https://t.co/3KDC4zyJpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The video of the off-duty denver cop knocking out the handcuffed guy at Jackson's is brutal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I really miss—multicultural week (and assembly). The food!!! Have a great day Saxons!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard Maybe he don't remember the election and he thinks obumber is still in and he's having flashbacks from… https://t.co/yfLJZQteK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpshow I’m concerned about Bernie’s votes, or lack of voting, on Russia related issues since the #ActingPresident… https://t.co/RQ0oostjsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The willingness to break the visual style to show emotional change. Body portions changing when characters yell n s… https://t.co/yVHa7yfwcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAristeguieta Más fácil conseguir un hombre justo en Sodoma y Gomorra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders wouldn't say whether Trump believes Democrats hate Jews, which is what he reportedly told Republican… https://t.co/GlnoLHYuBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @Acosta You are the clown asshat #crookeddonald #LiarInChief]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNewRDurle4 I’m deff a homer when it comes to LSU but can you really name me 5 teams that are flat out better than LSU?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCaminoWTAM Does anyone understand where Bauer is coming from with any comments]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcwright07 That’s what I’m saying. And the looks will be plentiful since they sit in zone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I wanted to say something witty about strawmen but Devin sucked the wit out of the room]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas @krispykreme @krispykreme it's only fair. Flower is ya'lls kryptonite. @GoldenKnights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RajGiri_303 @WrestlingInc Why not just do Charlotte vs Becky winner faces Rhonda at WM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw Mr.  Crenshaw, you need to use this as an example of what will no longer be available should #MedicareForAll become real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byshondaland um I’m sorry is @GiacomoKG’s dad from Krypton? Because this is out there #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe Hi Leese, Your too young to have watched the original - Vietnam: A Television History —————-&gt; Now;  2.0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlodeJo07 @RamirezClaudia_ Y si se cae solo,  Cual es el proposito de contratar golpeadores de tiempo completo como tu?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sscottpga Cool story. I just found out last month that Wilson actually rebuilt a couple greens at the nine hole co… https://t.co/8zsqEs2hvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinnBalor It covers your abs as you rock the Intercontinental championship  Too SWEEEEEET 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carl Icahn says the best way forward for Caesars Entertainment may be a sale https://t.co/ZIIVh1E76E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejand71152542 @RizzoGigirz58 @2018Ria @AKD09 @SusanGilbert @terrinakamura @starseed009 @Fujio0606 @LOYALFAN1… https://t.co/YxEW03xywN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettJoshuaE @splashinmud @TheJaredMonroe @Alyssa_Milano Actually - because of that and this stuff and pretty much… https://t.co/1rghTDm1Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @ChatByCC Why is not @IlhanMN already before the #EthicsCommittee already?  Are the people of… https://t.co/cKtIW6Rld2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PodSaveAmerica somehow I managed to listen to your newest podcast on half-speed. While the podcast is great on its… https://t.co/v6gah6AA4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrath_of_Comm @_Carja @_Delathor_ @_lynnwolf_ @0yogini0 @1Nastygal @1SKERKRO @2018LookOut @5_2blue @5BlessedHarts… https://t.co/0iagqzZXHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@expomick Hertl-Marleau-Burnzie.  Owen Nolan I was there for the call his shot AllStar game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanLittle I would have to say Aria in Las Vegas. I find the room to be super comfortable and always a decent… https://t.co/JA139CJm8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the #NBAAllStarGame with the fam. Watching dad try to follow what Meek Mill is saying has me rolling. https://t.co/lJqF9E6Q4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME Let's not forget America's #1 trading partner - Canada which has been designated by Trump as a threat to the… https://t.co/LMPFb2JJWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[DISTRUST DISORDER COURT JUDGE OR 2.A MERI CAN LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE JURSDICTION AUTHORITY ACTION SECURITY JU… https://t.co/fPO1I4NjAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Heritage Gallery in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/dP6LoCJtMG https://t.co/zaW4HXx9bB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normwilner @KimsConvenience @johnsonbecky Ha ha ha Becky and I spoke at length about this scene a couple of weeks back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[En México la violencia continúa de manera generalizada. Siguen los informes de tortura, desapariciones forzadas, ej… https://t.co/2QIRAXMVHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 Bless y’all,Brian; My best to all concerned my brother...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Flagship CrossFit in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/4l99ghA5mt https://t.co/Xx2ZaiyXH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Otter_News Thought you like my mother’s sketch. https://t.co/avk0UgjNFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlamoOnTheRise @pldLMT #ImpeachtRumpAlready!!!! https://t.co/sCikQ22dH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm disappointed that it took @VTDallas moving literally next door to me before I tried it. I officially live in ar… https://t.co/4vYnZyby34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief?  can you make it illegal for these cheap assed stores to stop buying that crap form China and selling it to… https://t.co/kamW3KzcaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @TheWashington15 although there was never doubt about your future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lacedevenn14 @7 Thanks for letting me know, hopefully I can get it on radio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been all over Mexico but I still need to see Torreón , Toluca , Monterrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnMahon2 On the one hand I suppose it's meant to help if something so terrible would actually happen, but cruel t… https://t.co/3c6tuU9wxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I didn’t get to take a shower until 5pm because I was working straight through from 6am until 5pm. Cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonz970 @Sequencer16 @Razorsmack1 @John_R_Berna @OrenIShiKiddo @ImabitcSumtimes @CaliRN619 @misspunk63… https://t.co/fMY6iEDTj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMac_1326 Being a father of a 5 year old I stopped watching after part 1. #Neverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know we love them as friends, but Daniel and Betty would have been the ultimate couple tbh. The finale is literal… https://t.co/OVwzWDkbiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Kenions...  In case you missed my introduction, meet Sarabi.  This cutie is 1/2 Shetland Sheepdog, 1/2 Shiba In… https://t.co/Lym3qCnUNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My future wife is currently like this with me. She knows I’m struggling bad right now. And I’m happy as shit she le… https://t.co/tjs2NjfWXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helenow04733698 @Wendys I'm doing it! I ran 8 miles yesterday to train.  If you can help these kids click here and… https://t.co/3pkKa3Kyw9]]></document></documents></author>