<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to see again @ananavarro at #NADOHE19. Can't wait for your keynote! #sjsuodei #inclusionmatters… https://t.co/vMUUpENS41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamchronicpain Awesome to hear better news in this madness of inhumane treatment by our government.  God bless you and these Doctors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FamilyGuyonFOX Imagine if Brian knew that Bonnie touched those snacks after she came back from the bathroom ...and didn’t wash her hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nephew's first (American) football game ♥️. There was no food 🙃 @ Preparatoria 16 UANL (sitio Oficial) https://t.co/uvg7hgpOxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped off at the Starbucks off 30 and Winslow because I never see it packed and it’s the nearest to my hood and t… https://t.co/6AmZHYzx5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday the community put on a ski race in Big Sky for the locals, I won best beer chug and this girl not only tr… https://t.co/vUt2LJ5rBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @iamcardib and @BrunoMars just do a joint album so I can live my best life?! Por Favor 🙌🏾😍 https://t.co/2ITJfRjyR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[we r home, drunk, but home. I had an extensive conversation with the uber driver about Jamaica (?) and Denisse is t… https://t.co/jMl3914MDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you don't have to be in your teens or 20s to be a louis Stan https://t.co/bEl7dlmwx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might be badass, but not Paul Newman hanging out with Clint Wastwood badass. https://t.co/O6EdZpzb01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg #wish that I had money to enjoy the things that come my way. #wish that all cancers had a cure so l… https://t.co/MRQ82I0uJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So awhile ago my iPad got stolen from Adrian’s car at a party in Maypearl WELL I GET A TEXT FROM A NUMBER SAYING TH… https://t.co/EEn8fnkXNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scary, inspiring, and motivating all at the same time @FulbrightTeach @ECAatState #Fulbright #TeacherLeaders https://t.co/5LZ4dK3r8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Junior High Night!!! This Friday vs Independence AT INDY! Come out and support us! https://t.co/En4f6olW1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las caras que pongo cuando comienza cada canción en el concierto de los #BackstreetsBoys en #Viña2019 https://t.co/nrdg4SGJLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cydneecimone I’m just renting them now, you can get em for like 40-50 dollars for a day. I’m willing to make that… https://t.co/Gymy3I3CrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I srsly can’t wait to be able to drink with @Viiankkaa &amp; the guys. 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avveerryy_hearn First of many beautiful!! SO excited for you! Keep that 🔥 in your belly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinneappleRyan Oh! You should go. Fresh and fast! It was a little drafty so if you get chilly you’ll want to keep your coat on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs @BernieSanders This is definitely the best way to convince folks that voted for Hillary to vote fo… https://t.co/l5VpJafmfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in the middle of a nervous break down yesterday planning a 1ST BIRTHDAY PARTY and my mom looks at me and says “… https://t.co/joJyw2isTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For this double shift yet to come. #happymonday life is beautiful today✨ https://t.co/ExKLtXMiwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago somebody tweeted that the Red Cross was a mass scam but nobody listened....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why? Kompa is my happy place @fitofarinen @enposib @ Club Cubano https://t.co/g23SHZAKsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk and you'll feel better. #funniness #tee-hee #grin #farcical https://t.co/dHO3bC3XEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what pizza day at work looks like when you are #Keto. https://t.co/OSpdnMNmPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been so long since I've felt anything inside these walls. You can't heal, you can't hurt when you don't feel at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Scrimmage today !!!! At Jefferson Co. When- 4:30 https://t.co/yqcYCwemrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[June 18th I get to hear Andy Samberg sing “terrorize that pussy” in real life 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this moron pulled behind my house and parked his car in my driveway, hopped out of his car through th… https://t.co/mPCISjmRUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz @joneill55… https://t.co/rx3RIzj4Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is the beach ☀️🌴🐚🌊 #SashaInPCB #SaltLife #VisitFlorida #Florida #VisitPCB #travel #PanamaCityBeach https://t.co/uJdyaPxi3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚Genesis 26:1-34 The continuum, be careful what our kids observe in us.  Isaac is receiving the blessings God promi… https://t.co/onaw6EC3bR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodySIO I hate that you’re up “late” but I’m up early to come see u play more songs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should know we're Jewish, God loves us all 😂 this movie makes me laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re at the hearing today to let #mnleg know Minnesota is Ready for #PaidFamilyLeaveMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovsInfo Sean of SGT interviewed Erik of TradCad Knight; still relevant today. Scary truths being exposed 2years later. 🙏🇺🇸💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the #dumbadses trying 2 light my smoke ... I'm #jaded #af and I got my own #lighter #dickwads 😂😂😂😂 #tuesdaymood… https://t.co/9EX6ypjoZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fHpHtN1Tk7  Game Playing AOC Video Big Hit...  If you haven't seen it, you GOTTA watch. Mind-blowing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bencapistrant G and I really want to watch more TV. The only shows I’ve seen in the past 6 years are Broad City an… https://t.co/O30XAGVmq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrerucker51 @landscaperstev1 @DudekLinda @Itridpm @SarahGould_SA @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/dhkKt1kIvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but this bitch is forever talking shit .... like get your life together first 🙄. Pinche pendeja 🙄 one day ima just punch her dumbass .]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an ACV, turmeric and OJ kinda day...  ...too bad it’s also a stay-warm-inside-don’t-grocery-shop kinda day 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismoreira7 @SW_ON_TRAFFIC I did too; both times. No need to be nasty about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saltysixties Good morning dear sweet friend  Have a lovely day  Take care 🕊🐾🌹🏵⚘🌷🌸💐🌼🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbeyMastracco Ugh I can’t stop. And same re: the eye rolling. I don’t know who I am anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That thing when you have so much to do but you don't know where to start so you just lay there doing nothing. https://t.co/E8zhXprru9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyrelates @theurbanplay I would throw some support behind one of these...where to purchase 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelcmcelroy First, you and Griffin make a very adorable couple and this is delightful. Me? Married 28 years and… https://t.co/uVcaEdPf56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrVanHammersly @JoyceWhiteVance Hell, YES, RIGHT NOW ! #ImpeachTreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorPenceNOW… https://t.co/Pfu2gXknoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgtennisnation @darren_cahill @PatrickMcEnroe Looks like my Roger going play @MutuaMadridOpen this year. #clay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannetteMacur1 @dtdstable To be honest I’m not sure ! Does he @dtdstable ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #HockeyDayInAmerica by watching my 4th game of the weekend. #5 later today 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever send someone ur playlist and they say “LMAO ur joking right”....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganDanielleK @bri_anna5 @tayshelt_11 Morgan, send me the pic when you get it lol plz and thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is working all thing for your good...God  has a plan  for your life! You  may not see it all now - But He is ta… https://t.co/CU8JMGjzxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everybody 👋🏼  We’re having a car wash for Izaac today @ the Family Dollar in Colton. Any donations help and are… https://t.co/MCvsKWzGmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite the smile, our little Spiderman isn’t happy he hasn’t gotten to see the real Spider-Man yet!… https://t.co/PK2NXoKhgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBragdon @SlickZillaZilla @luluHru @jdoc_k @LivinJk @ctanner3 @ButchJ9 @ricka057 @Pritzieee @Fifthdidy… https://t.co/zsNoSYqtfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does it feel being so basic and always trying to be like everyone else?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Branches &amp; limbs litter @TowerGrovePark (and at least on downed tree) but enjoying the sunshine #highwinds https://t.co/KGEAgmyROq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will give you the keys of the Kingdom of Heaven; whatever you bind on earth will be bound in heaven, and whatever… https://t.co/jYyHaD9dop]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need every single movie to come with a disclaimer at the beginning to warn me of any animal deaths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just completed Module 1: Introduction to You•ology Skin Care Line! #Younique #you•ologist #training]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone with 8mill followers can command anywhere from 16k to 27k per sponsored post, she gon’ be aiight. She’s onl… https://t.co/uy2ptJQYyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al B. Sure! | Night and Day | Music Video https://t.co/zlatCIn2jI via @YouTube @Andy to think Danielle thought this… https://t.co/SJz7iKdjwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoyngn lmao and bc of that video you know why I loved it so much 😂. the soundtrack was perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready to take that tax return and use it for your down payment on a new home? Let’s discuss your options.… https://t.co/F2sqGKdkDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @Steel_Curtain4 @dlolley_pgh @Dejan_Kovacevic @CarterCritiques @mattsunday @HunterAHomistek… https://t.co/ynDLhNK5CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyDutton16 @Mopor777 @tristrash @KarenHBStanley @MTumarkin @ElkeHansen7 @barb71 @Lynette84649831 @nanafrey7… https://t.co/EI70FLkyHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I received a fun challenge this morning from @karigartextiles  =============== Kanak wanted me to send over a photo… https://t.co/0iTGqETVJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thatbaseballfan @SMBuzzWeed @AJEarley4 I also DO KNOW Manny would have added only a menial number of wins to our t… https://t.co/1RvRvrbQTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxRose We the people For the People shall not perish. Thank you Max.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTcowboy3250 @SpeakerPelosi LIE..  noone is executing babies.. get your FACTS straight or look like an idiot. Your choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacksonsaysso @RealTT2020 @canalzone721 @DebStev80504671 @timhoover @KyleClark @9NEWS @Corp125Vet @battleofever… https://t.co/N9pqJLeQoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Our kinder crew put lots of hard work into their Animal Research projects. To present, we used @ChatterPixIt .… https://t.co/0Q2EbxDIQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how much I weigh... I’ve been eating pretty good lately... maybe 140+ Time to hit the gym and tone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are all right, it’s really Sunday pt.2, seeing as it’s a federal holiday here in the states, and pretty much ev… https://t.co/45fMFIEelB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Patterson Park Pagoda #pattersonpark #pattersonparkpagoda  #thepattersonparkpagoda#pagoda #walkinthepark… https://t.co/2riF6jamzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Keller Williams Realty at the Parks:  ThinkLiveBe Property Team in Orlando, FL https://t.co/0waU1zRS04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Symb10teCat @biancapunkloka @Poppa1973Poppa @Skyhawk1 @InsurgencyNQ @deezel21 @VexingHarlyQ @newotakuman5000… https://t.co/rMs9Dt9Mgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please #CALL 202-224-3121 &amp; tell your Rep to #SupportHR1004 - PROHIBITING Unauthorized #Military Action in… https://t.co/vzivugQyQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gonna put some positivity out and say THANK YOU to the universe. I have a job I work hard at and love. I h… https://t.co/lyoEtiZMvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every night someone smokes weed out in the parking lot and we had our windows open and you can smell it in our room now 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchfaefife No they won't take them without ins or cash ..i have Banfield for our Cat she has a Policy ..i called… https://t.co/KEqzGcAjEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carliewillisss Kissing w your eyes open has got to be the most uncomfortable thing someone can do 😂 but like what… https://t.co/L5jHW86hGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 1 minute. Take it for yourself and give #gratitude for the day and all the experiences it gave you… https://t.co/ZRgXkKpUc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“La forma más sencilla de averiguar qué sientes por una persona es despidiéndote de ella.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCSO_S6 Maybe it's because I'm jealous of anyone who gets to wear winter garb, but I love that hat. It's cool!! 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really convinced that there is almost nothing a little Jesus music can’t fix 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherorourke7 Good morning! Up &amp; getting ready for dentist Again . not liking it butttt https://t.co/sZ21mUv8Ml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBROINTHEAM ayo Fam Kelz gets a BIG #FOH for that rant 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to discussing this quote during my #UCET19 session: It’s the Wizard not the Wand!  “I believe all s… https://t.co/QbEVygu1yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Duval - Smile (Living My Best Life) ft. Snoop Dogg, Ball Greezy (Off... https://t.co/byyzsrHBzA via @YouTube yo… https://t.co/QEG6gZvhqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 18th #dool #days  Marlena is caught in a  tug-of-war for her soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could stand up to my mom. She is the opposite of who I want to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! I love this! Such a simple change, yet it makes so much sense and could really help encourage students to come… https://t.co/CyGHAd170I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@movingpanoramas at @HOTELHOTBURRITO #athvssoto #sxsw2019  #atxmusic #austinmusic @ Hotel Vegas https://t.co/iFaIwFWTsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Become a DoorDash driver! Earn up to $25/hour and get a $100 bonus after 200 deliveries in 60 days for signing up h… https://t.co/aJrd7Wjk4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans have hit a new low. They should not have been allowed to put up this poster, this juvenile poster, duri… https://t.co/NQJlzh9aR0]]></document></documents></author>