<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Cold Rainy days = Loaded Grilled cheese😋  I used: 🥪  Ezekiel 4:9 sprouted bread Miyokos butter (for toasting) Daiya… https://t.co/wXRcf5cXqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because he could have helped lead her in the right direction and this suicide might have been prevented. It was at… https://t.co/wUty5FtqUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freddymederos every song you show me😂😂😂 two months later that my new jam 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[APEX 30 BOMB ON CONSOLE | Stream Highlights Ep. 1 | Prewitt                Subscribe to —-&gt;&gt;&gt;… https://t.co/saaDPPxnKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMura You coulda said this was last week and I would of believed you. Haven’t aged a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zarchasmpgmr At least I’m in first and have a bloody https://t.co/qcaF6UzHmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLPAction @LeoDiCaprio @amylhatcher @Lyricalswordz @JoelRGarza @TimHoffmanPhD @matheeli @ncte @PineLakePride… https://t.co/SACke6us6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Country1025WKLB @jackson... If I can't have an @TheTimMcGraw song in the morning then I'll take @DylanScottCntry a… https://t.co/F6W6vfRveU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@76speedymouse Have you actually taken a look at any of the information that readily labels these accusers habitual… https://t.co/DVCInGeAIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[regard to Mr. Kushner's security clearance.'  They cited an earlier letter seeking information about President Trum… https://t.co/6MiSOvTTjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ODDwayne @kendallybrown @bourgeoisalien @Lollardfish @sadydoyle Give me a break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vito Genovese had Luigi kill Andrew G. Hicks for his body to rape Sara Rothschild who is Jackie Kennedy who is Marg… https://t.co/kk1wYF5ZRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTgalvestontx @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You took the words out of my mouth! Personally I want to see his taxes !… https://t.co/rJlEGs47oI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themarketswork More like priceless - she’s the gift that keeps on giving - Go @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting to increase the minimum wage in CT! Fight for $15! https://t.co/0jFDZjlvZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikRankin @Enterprise Yes!  He totally needs a car and then he can tweet about how awesome your company is and all… https://t.co/NS8GrdU9hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just gotta make it till tomorrow because I get to take a nap then and sleep as long as I want on saturday i’m stoked]]></document><document><![CDATA[William Barr’s Son-in-Law Just Landed a Job Advising Trump on “Legal Issues” https://t.co/51ZBYKcxXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cassavetes #IndieSpirits award goes to a movie under $500k, Jim McKay’s En El Septimo Dia — the filmmaker is shooting in Vancouver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski @nation_myers @NAUSECAR @PaigeKeselowski @amsupdates You have a beautiful family. These are great pictu… https://t.co/WPr5Gkp69W]]></document><document><![CDATA[lady gaga didn’t end her engagement to sit next to brad and his gf. no. she loves him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited and nervous about the UIL Competition today !!! Way to go to the Music Memory students who placed in every… https://t.co/Oz5OSg5PpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a TEXT from the guy I’ve been dating for 3 months at 4 AM “you want commitment and I can’t give it to you sorry” 😤🤪.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I twist into a pretzel in an unsuccessful attempt to pop my back, and sometimes I am laying with my legs… https://t.co/4ixiVoWa3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want to assure you we will do our absolute best to present the state’s position once  #ksleg acts, whenever that may be.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_bbbcb01 Lol! Someone needs to enlighten me? Pretty sure I'm much older than you and have had experiences that… https://t.co/nxVkb65ycC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Sad. Bigly sad.  He has been one of the quieter and less interesting people on Dump’s cabinet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time at a hannah montana concert the jonas brothers opened up for her and kevin winked at me and i’ve been in l… https://t.co/StqyXfWQO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want to hear anything about snow any more!!! The ground hog said Spring was coming not 6 more weeks of wint… https://t.co/7zMnVCZfgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daydreaming about your future is the worst feeling ever when it feels out of grasp and the best when you have hope that it will happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤 2 DAYS 🖤  Love and Chaos by Author S M Soto  Pre-order Now:  https://t.co/cM3iN1nVOY  BLURB:  Hell is rising Peop… https://t.co/cVqsX3Guj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump, is Mitch a Conservative or Rino?? Does he give just enough to make us think he's working for Ameri… https://t.co/IGEw8rhDbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Readyforit18 He moved to New York and Kentucky without telling me. I had to find out on Facebook and that he was serious with another girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMSpeck @nova_road Uhhhhhh that's not Photoshop??? That's the first all-Emilee Mars space crew, obviously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precisely. @FOXTV needs to do the right thing and fire him. His lies incited violence against real victims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Nice try at smoothing it https://t.co/4AsjgXC1c9 could go either way but I’m sure each side will spin it for their own position]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJamesLeary @WizardWorld @MelissaBenoist @tylerl_hoechlin Omg you met Tyler]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest flaw? I always forget my boxed-up leftovers at the restaurant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @jaketapper Only 60 ? Surprising considering it was a weird 2 1/2 hrs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks, enjoy your food - girl at Jimmy John's  "thanks you too!" https://t.co/f1KmIDnrNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I learned that there is nobody with my initials currently playing in the NHL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not good girl affiliated you’re wrong. Membership applications close March 9th 🤷🏾‍♀️   @howardgoodgirls  https://t.co/HRE9gP9obx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandeemusready @JoeNBC I'm all for Republicans pointing out that the ones who followed Trump made a conscious choi… https://t.co/fM8Jahxgxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abhisheka Mudra 🎯 Dharana { One-Pointed Concentration } 👁 Concentration: exclusive attention to one object; close m… https://t.co/8Dm1VU5pk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a over 40 year old man looking for “a great girl”, I’m not the Woman for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I so emotional ?? Robby just sent me a video of his surroundings of where he’s sleeping at his friends house… https://t.co/wF5n1DpmN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[MR. COHEN I WAS PROUD OF YOU TODAY! YOU WERE GREAT! MR. COHEN  YOU REALLY PAINTED US A PICTURE OF TRUMP'S INVOLVEME… https://t.co/jCvPRZgniz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvrilLavigne @FallonTonight Saw performance  when 1st aired, watched again last night. It was amazing   to see you… https://t.co/nfRODxWOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[There a very nice lady came aground the street to help me and called 911. She helped me and comfort me a lot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EXACYNFROMASHES Thank you!!! I hope you're feeling better at least a little bit. Sending huge hugs and love! 🤗🤗🤗🥰🥰🥰💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettysburg - photo by @NikiParanormal for @haunted_images https://t.co/6CYfD5VqSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejandrarrisd @laura_segers @CallisonES @RoundRockISD @KristaRRISD @AshleyRRISD This was an awesome event! Thank… https://t.co/IFj2Gkdczr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The renovated venue where the MN Lakers used to play. This  historic venue stood vacant for decades before re-openi… https://t.co/rj192ZCn9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romanceiscorny I love his first plunked, and then they punk him again on the set of Moses it was so funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[We 💓 everything about the #hgtvdreamhome  #WhitefishMontana. Thank you Sponsors #scrippsnetwoorkLLC… https://t.co/cmBHlhzZEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherrierohde I’m with you. I hate being depressed. I had to Google these examples. Hollywood is awful, for the most part.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m slowly learning how to walk away from situations or people who threaten my peace of mind, self-respect, or self… https://t.co/54fykwTg3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessssicaeden @mrBobbyBones Literally me every time I travel with someone &amp; want to binge the podcasts 🤣🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this Elite Force girls team and how hard they've worked and the hours put in the gym!!! It paid off! Th… https://t.co/CfLu9uZqgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my Alabama peeps, remember when God said he wouldn't flood the earth again? 🤔 #RainRainGoAway @spann https://t.co/jzy6PZwH65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incoming 2019 Shreve Freshmen interested in volleyball this fall-Mark your calendar for mandatory clinic days begin… https://t.co/MRd9Glw06O]]></document><document><![CDATA[when u unleash the memories of form 3 and jimbo https://t.co/5QOd3xJrIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[An artist is also an audience. This is why I always try to explain art as a thing that exists outside of and betwee… https://t.co/9VTb13JosZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to potential karaoke songs for this weekend, and this Carrie Underwood would have been perfect 2-3 years… https://t.co/Up79aaPIHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your couch needs an immediate refresh when @JessicaTarlov can, with a straight face, diminish the progress the POTU… https://t.co/4zoQWnUtwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha 😄 Okay,  so now it has a name! ‘Päntsdrunk’ Is the Wellness Trend You Need Right Now!  #pantsdrunk #relax… https://t.co/rUp1Rr3G7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@gwblazers1 @cafesanchez13 so proud of our singers! Two nights in a row Blazers!!! Back to back… https://t.co/9ar0YcpRrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blondieclub Mi Chompiras 🥰 hoy cumple un mes de que lo adoptamos 😽😽🥰 https://t.co/OfKZrIeoo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xojg25 Bro she is getting sexier and sexier each time I see her posts 😘😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former @HenryFordNews CEO Nancy Schlichting looks for talent outside healthcare https://t.co/2djjmK9fZN via @modrnhealthcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW no wonder @RepAdamSchiff @TheDemocrats are losing it! https://t.co/XhZ9V5NF7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexnazaryan He’s fuckin crazy. So is his bitch wife. That CPAC is an insanity magnet]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support the candidates that support holistic agriculture. #yes2meat #ruminantsrule   #gosavory #meatheals our 🌎 a… https://t.co/szfxuta5od]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katherinehunnah Next time don’t take the dog out and then just put it in her room and then let it piss on her bed.… https://t.co/wxxGCnI3yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When getting Ss to properly create constructed responses, @Miss_C_Steele at TSGC has her Ss RACE to the top! The GR… https://t.co/icUQVwjnJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for me. My least favorite person decided to join my yoga class today... she’s drunk and sat right next to me a… https://t.co/sqGrYRf0cK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessFirstD1 @JalenReeves_10 @IvankaTrump Not you 2 again. Don't listen to Jalen. 😅 You are more than Qualified… https://t.co/5bk9uDONJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo pasándole a todos mis amigos los stikers de familia peluche https://t.co/Eg5ynqpT0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanohaak @GeogWortley @Lit8Sunset @MsSamReid @AWellington83 @holburn_farah Which book?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo #porquenotecallas  aca nadie le ordena nada al presidente. Deje ya ese cuentico que suena rallado. Qu… https://t.co/yAz3OAgicV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLB @Giancarlo818 @TheJudge44 I’m not a Yankees fan but I’m a baseball fan. The sights and sounds of Spring Traini… https://t.co/nVtehp7rq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking And we have the nerve to say Venezuela's election was rigged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RepPaulGosar. Is sneering all ya got?   Do any of your Repugs have any valid questions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn @TheKingCenter @HolocaustMuseum What happened to parental supervision??? This is horrible! Makes me… https://t.co/cXKfuw5cJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been drinking all night but I’ve also been using chicken tenders as a chaser. Am I an adult or am I going through a mid life crisis ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day my Friends #Love #Family #Friends #Sunny #Sun #Beach #New #Luxury #best #Sunrise #paradise… https://t.co/LfwOjWPw7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniel_devito Yes!! Got a problem with that? They are my sorority sisters from college for girls weekend. Get your mind out the gutter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpwenzl Omg. Sending you love, patience, and light. So glad you’re ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at work a 5 year old boy asked me if I have a baby in my tummy.... yea it’s time to start running and drinking green shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't believe I'm turning 23 this year in June. Ima be a old lady before I know it. 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indigenous_Me @ulliowl @VABVOX Why? Why would they do that? As punishment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i updated my bio on tinder about 20 mins ago to “lets do meth together &lt;3” &amp; i keep getting messages :/ i love crack heads]]></document><document><![CDATA[The attorney is saying no amount is appropriate, and Wagstaff shouldn't be sanctioned. The judge is now saying ever… https://t.co/TRDrE0jL8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out that my (almost) husband still keeps the Chipotle receipt from our first date in his wallet. That was 4 years ago. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOHS Robotics Team at the VEX Competition @NOHSRobotics https://t.co/ZguTNyFBl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McShauno @kiki40400470 @reachjulieroys @HarvestBible1 @ExHBCMember @MemberHarvest @JackieAgal220 @BiblicalJustice 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyAssBritt1 We not together. But he dumb. Why he trying to get in another relationship if he just got out one?… https://t.co/PjunNNKtoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Human trafficking!’.. the same human traffickers your “ billionaire friend” is having sex w… https://t.co/pd3Bhs7UCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patytigresa Dejalos se cren pero no al menos los 👦🐧👎👎 chiquitines no lo quieren reconoser pobres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triste porque no quiero que termine Amar a Muerte ,difruto mucho verlos juntos ,espero hagan otro proyecto que este… https://t.co/9MTi7B7zU8]]></document></documents></author>