<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dropping some #WednesdayWisdom from the newsroom today! Couldn’t have agreed more with this! From the bad times to… https://t.co/5VP4XX60PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm trimming my PlayStation friends list dramatically. If you want a re-add,  please reply or dm with your psn name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to bundle up at the bus stop this morning!  https://t.co/kmSDipAkbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MainstreamMedia fears @AOC - end of story.  Her sponsor is very powerful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scattered211 Ok. I put together an IKEA dresser. Got my mind off Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceylnewman @CBCQueensPark @AaronWherry Little green men from Mars with the 128 crayon set from Crayola   They s… https://t.co/HZ3C6F7OFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marksmen_Hockey thank you for a fun Star Wars night and a fun hockey night. See you tomorrow! Let’s get the W!… https://t.co/hUOie3xua3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesEDIT Who have they lost?? Ive been so consumed with all of FSU losses that I haven’t noticed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Bernie really announcing tomorrow? Because I feel like every day, there's 10 new factions of leftists who hate e… https://t.co/fboPkHRNO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @CobosInsCenter Post-Match Interview with @WrestlingElyria freshman Nate Burnett. https://t.co/BLoORGbc8L #LoCoMats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my sweetheart Anne! She shares the day with Total Con!  #birthday #totalcon https://t.co/zvqzdDGj4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I not surprised that call gets confirmed, we get fucked over move than every other team combined]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJF588 @RepMattGaetz Because without bipartisanship the gun laws you want to change won't change. There's nothing,… https://t.co/3natpC77ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[New to Point and Figure charts? Here's an introduction https://t.co/cYFw985Cc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SOS Incomunicados en Venezuela 🇻🇪 Colapso eléctrico desconecta del #Internet a casi toda #Venezuela  #sinluz afect… https://t.co/u2KSwxfz7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[La neta ¿qué onda su chiste de poner stands de "pon la mentira más grande que te hayan dicho" "love sucks" etc, etc… https://t.co/j3kBnGXlQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god. You are a piss pig grandpa. They got R Kelly, they are going to get you too. #maga]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in loooooove w/ the turnout of the pictures that I took with my family in Los Angeles (,: https://t.co/4bigAB4wB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad’s richest friend, haha. Giannis Antetokounmpo named as one of the NBA’s Highest-Paid Players for 2019 https://t.co/EFp8idzBql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad, tragic news. And yet, you have to almost look for it in the news. There's more going on locally, nationally an… https://t.co/JNnFWEzddi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ina_hajek @LadyThriller69 @realDonaldTrump @atpeace101 😂😂😂no politician follow the law. They believe they are above the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol at retard texas fan trying to fight our fans https://t.co/X6UKWreQiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkeduk8er @HowardU @floridastate @SpelmanCollege @EmoryUniversity @UCF @HamptonUniverse @FAMU_1887 @ClarkAtlanta… https://t.co/b9UY4qPXIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WmScottBlair @31BJN @KentSailor @ClarkKe95563197 @DoodlesTrks @janetshoemake @roosterpisces @Marizellell… https://t.co/RyBU9AGC5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember, it's the cover-up that got Nixon caught for his involvement in Watergate.  So too, will Merkel and her ty… https://t.co/Cd3eGyifAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[His right hand doesn't know what his left hand is doing. #resist #unpresidential @ Worcester, Massachusetts https://t.co/Uekt3EOkx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkSpaziani As far as I can tell, there isn’t a good answer right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, NTX-Factor you shared and showed latest trends, performance, and priorities. I promise to drive metrics for… https://t.co/VUKByantbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whosryanneff @rayduker @missmayiband @levibenton @JustinMMI @whosrobertseed @jerodboyd See ya tonight bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speakingabtpain 6/I have no superior wisdom on this. However, what I try to ask myself is (a) is my own anger goin… https://t.co/ra0WOPEeRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AStallings88 This is just an entertaining showcase of the tech.   What gets me excited is the possibility to enhan… https://t.co/47vRiP9Sat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...bye. That’s a 3 run 💣 for @leilua18 and @HailStateSB takes a 4-2 lead into the 7th against Ga. Tech.… https://t.co/CZ4fDnyET6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taodominguez @eochoa_antich @HenriFalconLara @MareaSoc89 @efernandezVE @claudioefermin @felipemujicah ¿Eres el árb… https://t.co/wNtO1jo8i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Around $2000 it’s from a tailor on Seville row 46 regular with an extra long zipper for my massive penis thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamChvatal Mine as well obviously (I’m an American so I’m obliged to say so), wouldn’t have served a single secon… https://t.co/yEwNivskk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Before all that HRC took millions. Russia.   When you doing something about that?  Dumbass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maplewood boys basketball will face Farrell at Slippery Rock University Friday at 6 pm. @maplewoodtigers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ned is a comedic genius hidden in a Midwest idiot. @tystapp11 @Thetimmac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovLikeJesus For by him [Jesus] all things were created: things in heaven and on earth, visible and invisible, whe… https://t.co/7fkV1PtVae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like a F’ing Socialists. Pres Trump re-energizes our Steal Industry by partnering with Capitalist run steal co… https://t.co/yOBFj2Xcl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[First ‘task’ of the day done. Im blowing through a pair of shoes a month. Buy Nike stock folks. #entrepreneur… https://t.co/WycpY2eIG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanleyRoberts @EklecticRose @TitusOneLuv Why would it be considered a public area if the space is owned by a priv… https://t.co/fvCHkBH4Yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stance #FujiXT3 35mm-1/250th@ƒ/1.4-ISO640 #internationalwomensday #rally #woman #unionSquare #Candid… https://t.co/OTY1uTKwtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[wicked snakes inside a place you thought was dignified  let that evil wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive @SkyNewsBreak @AJELive @CBSTopNews… https://t.co/J7xDtBeqiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moulton’s regional championship trophy. The Bobkittens face Dodd City in a Class 1A state semifinal at 8:30 a.m. Th… https://t.co/W1jwodIHKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[so did I miss interweb’s disscusion on @Eminem’s lyrical genius with “Venom” - yes, “lyrical” genius. #imthesuit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MboroSevereWx @Bigunit1865 @RuthSevereWx No argument. It’s called a tweet. And or a response posed to a previous t… https://t.co/CuuC0vLdG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when we factor in performance (velocity) to create an efficiency metric (mph produced per normalized unit of st… https://t.co/a65xeFWhv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @littlesexbuddha @milanamaylove @missjojokiss @AbbyCrossXXX @ScarlettSageX @akaDaniDaniels… https://t.co/pivat4fpUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ECON senses are tingling... Too bad there's no one special to share this with 😂 https://t.co/HmFcb77KhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[my hungover ass just woke up to a detailed video on the subtle difference between Sonic plushies throughout the years   happy v day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vámonos a 🇪🇸! Primer viaje los 4 en familia @Rebe_Julia #luciana y #emiliano @ Seattle-Tacoma International Airport… https://t.co/S4cZaChGVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It wouldn’t have happened if @AB84 and @LeVeonBell weren’t such cry babies]]></document><document><![CDATA[a nigga having his booking info in his bio because he slapped a girl ass on spring break is still the most profound… https://t.co/Bw5AikjsNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[the "nobody: " memes (if you even want to call them that) are so unfunny it actually blows my mind how anybody finds them funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabretoof @ontsabres905 The worst thing Jason has done here and the only flaw to this point is hiring Housley but… https://t.co/3NeIChSKo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WyndhamHotels do points expire? If so, where can I find out when they do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranciscoPoleoR Pero los que robaron el dinero para reparar la infraestructura eléctrica son de tu generación y al… https://t.co/jpLxnOA9cA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just4BeerLovers @JonMontag @ephoustonbill @JohanBBT @zappafaye @cellmavin @beerguypdx @lhtetrick @HermannTLombard… https://t.co/i4cSyBrmvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideEdition Hope she was taken to court and pays to put that baby ALL THE WAY through school. 👏🏼😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without McCabe hooked up to a lie detector it will be meaningless. He has lied so many times. One more will not mat… https://t.co/tZvflr2P8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Métro  feet,04/03/2019 #commute #montreal #ForeverWinter @ Place-d'Armes station https://t.co/Hl8lBVlcb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC traffic...Always moving. #nyc #ny #newyorkcab #yellowcab #traffic #bridge #photography #newyorkcity… https://t.co/jLFZSzkQsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoshWithTyler @amberwelton I thought this was you and Steve for a minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen you know the prestige publisher, little brown? if they spun off a younger, cooler 2nd niche publishe… https://t.co/RF2xSgusOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betrainor @VirtualLukeG @vBrianGraf Yeah, notice how no one is giving him a high five there.  Everyone just left h… https://t.co/CMZStGfphD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_QueenLioness_K how would you figure out mine because my birth month is 6 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Mora: Playoffs??!!  Me: Yupp! Starts tonight, then two  #NWHL semifinals this weekend. #ChasingIzzy🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melva1212 @60Minutes @realDonaldTrump Lying under oath and during questioning is quite a bit different than omitti… https://t.co/D4KihVyRi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsygirl203 @TNtales @housesandme @PressSec She looks and acts like the evil lunch lady from my childhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a planet, we really aren't taxing the rich enough. https://t.co/Wq4Ml8SK4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always read DM as BM and honestly it doesn’t change a thing about either of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a direct quote? Or was it scrubbed of bad language? I can read lips and Little Richie has a potty mouth. Ca… https://t.co/yA7TO9rYoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your friendly reminder that even when things are low, somebody else has it just as bad... or worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyParrillo @RayGun0231 You’re just spinning your wheels now, Tea Party Nietzsche.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YC's latest cohort includes a company that plans to develop and sell... 🧐, quote, "flying motorcycles"... https://t.co/ro6eOYiwoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrispossible @UnivisionNews @Univision @jorgeramosnews @NicolasMaduro Lol i was just being sarcastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should never have to chase love, affection, or attention. If it isn’t given freely by another person, it isn’t worth having.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaning on the Lord... @ St. Mary's County, Maryland https://t.co/19q7hNEC0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time available, let me know if you’d like to set up an appointment. Slide in the dms 🙏🏼🎉🕺🏼 #pinup… https://t.co/5ige0ujVIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garlic Knotts @ Wise Guys Pizzeria Orange, California https://t.co/eSOuw9To7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hijos de puta, lárguense! #Furukawa y pensar que hay gente de a verga que piensa que esto está bien. Emplear a personas y negarles todo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eaglefan3 @joegisondi My daughter was born April 1. And to those uptight about April Fools, i only have this to ad… https://t.co/1ZWSKTpgFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobSheft @KimStrassel @WSJopinion A train don’t deliver to ever grocery store and can’t haul fruit vegetables or m… https://t.co/dm06fFEe5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrickHamilton @andresintheory @JEFordNCTOY @BernieSanders One reason why i follow, ... Never wrong when you fight for social justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro what the fuck. Why did I wake up sore from my shoulders because of LAZER TAG!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gumballfanatic1 @cartoonnetwork @TAWoGWiki @benbocquelet You know what the Fans and the Company said they want to… https://t.co/K1hLsFIBwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Jesus I wild have whooped him if that was my teammate THATS NOT BASKETBALL. So we gon play whatever the hell you… https://t.co/l2TDSGhu1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching @NHL: @PredsNHL at @mnwild live from the @XcelEnergyCtr on @NBCSN on @fuboTV on my @Roku Premiere! #NHL… https://t.co/QRuZIbncYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miamichris1 @latimes WHY U TYPING HERE ON ENEMY PRESS? I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth… https://t.co/56OAs32Fyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pounding the pavement! Windy 8 mile run today! #runtolive #livetorun @ Bremen, Indiana https://t.co/cK6oIKIveK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#orchids #orchidmania @cbgarden #botanyart #flowers #flora #floral #floralart #floralphotography #flowerphotography… https://t.co/r20cDq8jJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onovotny @MakeYourselfNrd @NerdPyle @venzann @CarmenCrincoli @DanSloan @SwiftOnSecurity No. The Feedback Hub. Gets… https://t.co/vHChKBWNas]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know math controls your life when you have to take out your earbuds to hear yourself sing the quadratic formula so you can remember it]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@whatswrongla sometimes God Just uses #Crayola https://t.co/lSbjCsyrtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SackzAllDay Fuck y’all it’s anything cheese and Fritos top 3 regardless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfrase44 @karyssawasko @USArmy Thank you man!! We are stoked about this opportunity!! Hope all is well! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really good #Daytona500 so far. Watch for Chase Elliott in this last stage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dirk4Ray @DJRayRevel @AOC @ltthompso And that is in violation of the law as written. Maybe we need to bring down t… https://t.co/Bgg8nepx7e]]></document></documents></author>