<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#RedWings in warmups: Bertuzzi-Larkin-Nyquist Vanek-de la Rose-Mantha Helm-Glendening-Athanasiou Abdelkader-Ehn-Ras… https://t.co/GnwbgS7BqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find JOY in the JOURNEY ❤️ Let the beauty of what you love be what you do.  #rumi . . . . . . . . . . . . #grateful… https://t.co/1Td1c71YNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir y’all. I’m feeling bamboozled. I’m trying to get ahead of a snow storm headed to STL and get no grace… https://t.co/1LuZOltJH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike6Truth @jill_magnussen @helensmomma @pratoshnivedita @loveGoldenHeart @BabyGo2014 @gerrinnesmac @pkamla1… https://t.co/H0HyJHO4Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Duah  beeatch every person in the USA wants to lower their taxes . What an idiot .!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a lot more to achieve and am nowhere near where I want to be. But if you have a dream never give up on it. N… https://t.co/lbh9kFvYL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first Twilight movie is so cringey but I don’t care what anyone says, this series will always be a guilty pleasure of mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janaethegreat I’m at home. I’m about to order some Rise &amp; Shine but thank you boo 🥰 I’ve been wanting an omelet all weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was both a tough and beautiful day, and @lkx47 is exactly what I need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaiseyDoesIt @Matt_NSR Not much, just glad to see baseball stuff gracing my timeline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pledged to save part of my tax refund with @SaverLifeorg for a chance to instantly win $5! https://t.co/qEZYtUyxbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristin8news @Katie8News @NatalieKalibat @Morgan8news @MattDiNardo @wxmorgan8news @juanconde8News @Talya8news… https://t.co/E9E41iHqWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPWellman @conservmillen These two Aunt Jemima’s are right up there with the other Uncle Tom’s and Steppen’ Fetchi… https://t.co/9Zbr7cjBv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurseOfBeth @MrsBBoarding Oh yeah the famous tim strode stomach pounder I wanna try that😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameekie @ImAaronJ Oh it’s just fighting. Pretty sure they almost never have sex ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just turned night mode on for my Twitter after literally being roasted by everyone about it and I’m v uncomfortable with it 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildoeOn @irish_today @snacks80 @JonRothstein Better on both counts. Check last 5 years academic rankings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessierOnFire Market or canal? Line ups were crazy waited over 20 mins.. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upulie No no. Our eating habits are not to fulfill our needs, they are for others' entertainment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will find yourself in every scripture of the Bible especially if you believe in God. The scriptures may have di… https://t.co/JKj1IYeDzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Processing my renewal today.  Pretty sure I'm the only Massachusetts Electrologist on the membership list!  So ....… https://t.co/jSJffAexhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[She just said she’s getting ready to move on with her life #TheBachelorFinale]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg is GOOD! I would urge everyone to listen to his CNN Townhall.  #PeteTownHall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaTheMost @TobinHeath @ThornsFC Next time you do will you buy me one? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for @SherrodBrown to get some answers at this hearing @SenateFinance #pharma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BugsBunnyInDrag @notcapnamerica By his own admission he didn't bother to vote until he had the chance to vote for… https://t.co/v2Kbcw8jlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCabe’s Troubles Run Much Deeper Than ‘60 Minutes’ Interview Suggests https://t.co/HkQlJJu67s via @epochtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfrutando del fin de semana en familia: deporte y comida saludable!!! en Pasadena, California https://t.co/DASHixzlzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to tag @ThoughtsByJilly @ProNickLow &amp; @JimMudd too but ran put of characters lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad swore I ate chips for breakfast because there was a big of chips on the table (BTW I DIDNT, it was from the… https://t.co/TO1z2yJIH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomainAmiel C’est genre le Dog persons weekly meet-up de Quebec.  Fantastique]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo Gehrig quote ends "luckiest man on the face of the earth." With proper Bronx accent on "earth" BTW t… https://t.co/UntAU3YHhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMeltlingMan1 @pattonoswalt No! If you know a depressed person, YOU reach out! Check on them. Make them and deli… https://t.co/OpXCA1KOw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrSteveyJames @DerbysWildlife @NatureUK @Natures_Voice @WaxwingsUK @BBCSpringwatch @Britnatureguide @iNatureUK… https://t.co/vX1r9lUqzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness, faithfulness,…… https://t.co/FIACMC7m2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary #whoknew https://t.co/M0ZykMw0XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalloquiGreg @ScumBorgSteve @AnthroGirl73 @Benwa99 @TomiLahren @BernieSanders Well Universal healthcare will also… https://t.co/lASHfkThf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FieldsFalcons teachers kicking off Dr. Seuss week!! 🎉📚🎉 IT’S FriYAY!  Enjoy your weekend everyone. ❤️❤️… https://t.co/1Qf28x45Om]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luka Doncic is 19, in the NBA. Cassius Stanley is 19 playing in High School]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericisaac @kim What am i misinformed about... that he has pass bills he wrote naming post offices what else has he… https://t.co/zfRmWm0W58]]></document><document><![CDATA[you have no idea how hard it is not to heart every Sword &amp; Shield meme on twitter right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[FAITH and LOVE in TIBET: Lightning in the Prairie (English Edition)  https://t.co/F1oewrDW6E vía @amazonmex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess now that I’m 25 I should probably learn how to truly adult. How do I do buying a house, getting on my own ins… https://t.co/lQvijmS1UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[showing sis around town 🏔 . . . #grandcanyon #grandcanyonsouthrim #arizona #northernarizona #flagstaff… https://t.co/bVcjDhnjXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud mom moment: when your 11 yr old tells you that she will be doing her 5th grade biography on @mattnathanson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge sharing @usmcocia @univmiami on #SDGs #Sustainability #Partnerships #Innovation between leading speakers… https://t.co/2hOeRZaDsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally can not leave the house without telling my dog I love her at least 5 times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonkapalka @alexiskennedy @tronbevan Oh I most certainly did ask for it 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It pays to not be on time” - my boss, in reference to the fact that depending on when you get to work, good food o… https://t.co/dga3LVLPCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you guys at our next event✨ Thank you for your support once again. Hope your rest of your day goes well! 🧡😊🧡… https://t.co/TGGtILtjhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Look what my sperm can do. “ TIP all them words... https://t.co/e8Fq1wbzeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toastmasters Area Directors for 44 &amp; 42 for contest held on Saturday 02/22/19. #39dtm  #d39tm https://t.co/Tbf8NUBvyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LabrantKen not gonna lie i thought this was @Thesupercole y’all literally look the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisPerkins5 @seanspicer @extratv @SecPompeo @KellyannePolls @SarahHuckabee So Dennis there are doctors who care help your condition!🐸🐸🐸🐸]]></document><document><![CDATA[me ando desvelando como si mañana no tuviera clases en la prepa y mis 3 horas en inglés 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsBonillaTeach @RochellRangers @MrsMorrison_3rd @MsJonesTeach 😘😘😘 Right back at you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun weekend @magnolia with #mybeautifulmom and #mybeautifulsisters. https://t.co/ccFMqoDjPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constant BS, he doesn’t know and doesn’t care what he doesn’t know. #BeLikeBob @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote a new poem ... I might perform it tonight at @UNTxPJ  ...  Which starts at 9pm  .... in Wooten 222  .... in… https://t.co/otvGodWsvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dimms think everyone but them needs to give up their wealth. I got news for you Hollywood and professional athletes… https://t.co/Oe9aFRMsy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[not gonna sit here &amp; have one sided relationships anymore so your either with me or without me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @IAMSUMMERWALKER #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/S6Wrquy1Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lil table set up in the middle of the pizza that shit never served a purpose 🙎🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la__civetta @yrfatfriend @mockumatrix Sugar cane. Just pull it up, peel it and suck it. Tastes delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought my ticket,,,,,buy yourself a nice meal tomorrow @ShawnMendes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just one more reason why #TeamSISD IS the best! Providing #EndlessOpportunities for our students!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is so sweet!! Thank you!! Isn’t Greg incredible, these amazing things were created in his brain! How cool abou… https://t.co/yCYAtZjPOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umm_osman I saw that earlier and was gonna tag you in it lmao you love it don’t lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ladies of Delta Sigma Theta, Inc. are here in Annapolis today to share in their mission of community service. H… https://t.co/WKsPvOaXZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jshelb24 @sethcowan_ @_MichaelRyan_ At least we still got the mAAD city remix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este hombre tan valiente @jguaido. Rezo porque a su regreso no lo apresen. @NicolasMaduro no te expongas, no se te… https://t.co/J0GNlJYBAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually I do a dress or T-shirt + jeans but decided to try jeans + a sweater today. I like it? Also picked up new 🎧 https://t.co/I8kyvD4wPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun at Lego Discovery Center!! @Cruennas https://t.co/KQ07hc328U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyDeraney @DrJenGunter @TheView I’d like their booking info too thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[the day I met you was the best and I hope what we have will last long as I live or I cannot imagine the rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I know I’m an asshole and shit but everyone knows it’s a front and I’m genuinely far too kind for my own good tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Dr. Remy '13' Hadley from "House" which is scarily on target. I should have lied though &amp; said house plant.… https://t.co/HyGeGFsiFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nooo the hot ass host from cheaters (Clark Gable III) died Feb 22 and I bearly opened the link my sis sent me last month...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TChanMD @MGVanstone @MacEmerg oooo - looking forward to reading! as ever @TChanMD, so grateful for your  insight and support]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy Valentine’s Day I went to a restaurant by myself and broke a wine glass wbu @ New York, New York https://t.co/iLYSVsBqqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Super Duper Double Citra by @hookerbeer @ County Route 1 — https://t.co/7E1Ct0lpcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BasedMistress @RajahTavares It’s like how would she even respond? This dumb as hell 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@designsponge @iSmashFizzle I’ve seen them live 13 times. I have many, many, many stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJamesMU This will destroy any thoughts I had of coming back to WV to work someday. Insanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russlee  @newsongonline  #wichitaks #winterjam2019 https://t.co/P1oVGqzu2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Are you saying ALL HATE CRIMES ARE HOAXES????  SERIOUSLY???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keepupwithjen @ToughGuyMankas @EricaGoss @deborah26449389 @sharon_cantley @vroberts9 @LordGraydon @lynda3035… https://t.co/cnLkNic9Z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vroberts9 @MissytheB @lynda3035 @sharon_cantley @GordonHarmony @BloomNight2 @Marina935home @marisbellamy1… https://t.co/Rkt2qLuUQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy the ones you think you can trust the most, you can’t trust at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHOOPS. KYLIEQUINN. https://t.co/2XEFqZ8Qt1  SPREAD THE WORD. RT PLEASE 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twerking 9-close tonight at @kitkatclubpdx! . Wearing: @LainaRauma  . Hair and makeup: me . #doyouwantmetoseduceyou https://t.co/lPqPQAS8Qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I like the notion but won't believe it 'til I see it. If true, however, we could be looking at a flood o… https://t.co/k1REOownWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do what YOU want to do, don’t let others influence that decision, I’m asking myself the same question .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargaretJanz Obviously need a followup survey. Although the tops are closed while on display so you can see the flavour name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe ATM and gave me 100$ I cried my eyeballs out. And then he told me that he wasnt going to let me slee… https://t.co/iLvqkTZIGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LouFest owner alleges vendor tried to sabotage music festival, lawsuit says  Sound and light vendor accused in the… https://t.co/5nSNrEsT3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told my manager I want to go back to school and he said he planned to promote me to general manager and would offer… https://t.co/Gn7rTwqvhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It goes down at @Pluckers 🤓🔥 @ Pluckers Wing Bar https://t.co/Cru5SJ6b6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantaParkerPD Congratulations @ChantaParkerPD ! Reggie would have been beaming from ear to ear I’m sure. Looking… https://t.co/oyu1t4SeVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capnoonan1 @chrislhayes What a despicable, disparaging thing to say about 63M American voters. This is the read HRC lost.]]></document></documents></author>