<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LivinLarge44 @LukaG_55 @GaryDolphin I’ll expect your apology by noon Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_john819 @alegriselle @NombreEsJustin @AnneRN79 @1STROS @KingBobbyWdlnds @TheManimal18 Would it make you happy… https://t.co/r2TlObA7AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[LE DARÁN PALO A SERGIO GOYRI  / En la Shorcha con Mario Luna 24 de febre... https://t.co/I9ry8loOKA vía @YouTube ¡Vista mi nuevo vídeo! 🤣◀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Murray_Brewster Be nice to have a Minister of Veterans Affairs. Must be out of MPs to demote I guess.😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[their bodies down on the edge of the bed, their legs dangling over the edge so we could get a great angle between t… https://t.co/2Pgm7T9OIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Emerson Electric Co team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/bkJpQ4AOsO #IT #Rushville, IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasualEffects Do you mean you want command line access to the version history and the ability to switch to a parti… https://t.co/rcopkasaRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenStabenow.  Further more.. Insulin dependent diabetics are rationing their insulins because of price..some are d… https://t.co/XiKvPi3hd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I retweeted my bsf #pieceofyourlovechallenege for 0.2secs then I realized I knew the nigga in the video 😂🤦🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/eCLcvyCSgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare Sunday morning presentation!! Awesome crowd at The LEP Summit at Western!! #GrateFuel #HoorayForEverything!!… https://t.co/F0cGsJVkM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPGeek @ChantalMachabee J'espère qu'il sera  prêt poir les lancers d'éviers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Another indication of #FoxNews failing credibility that matches their increasingly #Leftist tilt.… https://t.co/XDoyt9Egu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Increase faith,,,,planted it in thou sea of glass,,, my tree,,, https://t.co/A9aKDE5wgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership that improvement requires team development with individuals becoming mature adult athletes]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is from when I opened for Hugo Chavez in Copenhagen in 2009.  https://t.co/fpLLGmHJIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally drawing again... Starting off with some quick gesture work and going in with some heavier lines. First 20 m… https://t.co/3WRUCUCQ7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callmeAdje @anchorgalEDU @Seesaw @PintoBeanz11 GO ADRIENNE GO!! WOOHOOO! KES will soon have a CERTIFIED in-house Specialist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi How about a message to have the racist anti Semitic Omar and Taleb step down from Congress !?’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau's Trained Seal, named CBC #canpoli https://t.co/vUHEnEOub1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loading a bowl of The Devil’s Lotus. 👨🏽‍🚀 Hope you’re redeye for this release 😝 @ Hops and Grain https://t.co/Gc8chvZvaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this playful. #laughter #tee-hee #smile #hilarious https://t.co/qPngGArSHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Go ahead and run, this will make for good fodder for us, who know that your ideas, do not work. And we… https://t.co/obsGR892Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all is said (and truly said) about the divisions of Christendom, there remains, by God's mercy, an enormous common ground.  C S Lewis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Lying liberals got their clown to perform but it won’t help them in the long run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathFournierQc Désolé...Mais plus l'opposition fait obstruction et plus ça prendra du temps.  Ça aussi c'est prévi… https://t.co/tG6g4rWFCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always lose sleep because of this kid 😐 &amp; I’m not talking about Zion]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will be discussing these and related issues in #Hist262MLO on Thursday. Students, make sure you have finished Sa… https://t.co/HOpoPZM2Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dad and his baby out for a ride on Howard Street today, just days after the tragic loss of #TessRothstein .  It’s… https://t.co/sClNavRqh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to have a girlfriend someday and stay at home one night and cuddle on the sofa while we watch 1988’s “Sh… https://t.co/OyEAsUnTQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[LETS MAKE THIS A SUCCESSFUL SEASON WITH LOTS OF PARTICIPATION AND THOUGHTFUL CENTRING OF YOURSELF IN THE UNIVERSE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ew, David!  . . . #schittscreek @ Sony Centre for the Performing Arts https://t.co/0N2143sLZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My happy place. #baseball #photography #sportsphotography #springtraining #canonpro #canonphoto @canonusaimaging @… https://t.co/4WYiucGswM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still going strong here at Casper Events Center. 2A State title game in double OT between Pine Bluffs and Wyoming I… https://t.co/cEas54a5Sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjbowles4 @DoingRight1 @Deplora39336480 @cheriseguilfoil @ChadBush1972 @Autoharper @dontreaddd @Aug1405 @BundyGP… https://t.co/CjyuuysMCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonzaga floor general @JoshPerk13 is 1 of 9 NCAA DI players to have accumulated 200+ assists on the season. Of thos… https://t.co/aVxmX2pbWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic vibe, music and life at Beach Volleyball 2019. #beachvolleyball #miami #usa #sunset #travelblogger… https://t.co/jyGFqaTPQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s good. But they’re not going to be getting any of my money at the Theatre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be thankful for side hustles that end up like this.   #sidehustle @ Ahwatukee, Arizona https://t.co/TAsuH2YV5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Cognizant team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/phxUi8jNUz #FullStack #Dallas, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[a little disappointed in alitamovie #alitabattleangel to be honest @ West Hollywood, California https://t.co/d45QtsHGeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD I had a nap and am definitely ready for action #BringItOn https://t.co/ZZ2tncczLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Twilight Oblivion by @Redhornbrew/@jesterkingbeer at @redhornbrew — https://t.co/zG8iqXOe3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so many fine ass Females like Jesus Christ why y’all so fine for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ofthevalley21 @BadgerMBB Looks like you’re keeping it together today 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UptownReport It was the dolphins who never offered him that deal. https://t.co/4Z20g7lTJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kgriff_run You are awake to live life for today, whatever it brings! And, the world is brighter for having you in it! #LiveLife #LoveLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[And maybe this is where my brain isn’t wired like a fan and quite honestly, I’m truly pleased for that to be the ca… https://t.co/RQ4lqHgObN]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 3, 1991. Motorist Rodney King beaten by LAPD officers after a traffic stop in Lakeview Terrace. Video from ap… https://t.co/ej4PPY3Jgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, on the commute tonight I had several opportunities to yell #ZipperMerge out the window. And yet no one did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPaulGosar Why don't they pass a resolution that says, YOU CAN'T MARRY YOUR OWN BROTHER? It's ridiculous that she… https://t.co/F1Eu6wKIVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belltane57 @Jaymi_723 @KristinHockey7 @AlannahNewell @Wiselatina626 It was the look of you better run and hide!  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh , if Jussie Smollet really staged his own attack, I won’t believe anyone anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already have a nice guy but is it too much to ask for more expansion packs? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watanabe2k Oh and I totally bought my first yoga mat- from @Onnit ...because they make one that is Han Solo encase… https://t.co/kmlU9WMpWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit. These people are truly fucking drooling dribbling morons.   It’s astonishing. I’m wheezing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukeymcgarry @Postmates Danna invented the bendy coffee lid when she was in college. Wasn’t paid beans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there’s one thing I’ve learned so far at the Senate Finance Committee Meeting: @JoshRBuckley has on a helluva red coat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tleehumphrey HOW? does trudeau know so much about pizzagate? His pedophile friends inform him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a fantastic gig at @CafeCodaMadison. Thanks for having out tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful Dead - West L.A. Fadeaway - 12/27/83 - San Francisco Civic Audi... https://t.co/6WewyAhiC3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muirwoodwheeler does Stormglass take place in the same world as Muirwood?  Wondering because of the academy at the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Schien man! Lay it on us! Bring me the clamor on the sports topics, that grease the narrative wheel! https://t.co/jynv5oMWLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhoDat #WhoDatNation #NOLA y’all need to follow and listen to this Saints podcast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @Thomas_Spectrum found four hazardous waste containers on South Campus in areas open to students and the pub… https://t.co/JzdudvVvi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wildwoodfoods Is your soy creamer out of production? Cannot find anywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real training begins when you want to stop. Physical strength will help you compete but mental strength will he… https://t.co/OZa7sntSHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the storm. Col. Carrington @ Princeton, Kentucky https://t.co/zOVBfrr7Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Page__Me @SportsTalkMiss Agreed. I love watching those homecoming videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nectar of the gods ☕️ (@ Starbucks in Beverly Hills, CA) https://t.co/ctS1G1KvwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day, another #sink now only #halffull I could always use a #dish #washa . . . . . . . . . . . . #amateur… https://t.co/Vet5H8VFUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know I taught at a school I was once expelled from. I tell a couple of stories in our latest… https://t.co/pBFigonFRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retr0h No... I was too full from a 15ounce NY strip steak, she-crab soup, and a Caesar salad.  I must be slipping a little...]]></document><document><![CDATA[They probably do not even remember me....after 20 years, people forget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iam_Fouad @Manasseh_Azure I did. What used to be Brong Ahafo, with Sunyani is now Bono Region. And that’s what he sought to point out, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black garlic tonkotsu ramen hits the spot on a dreary day. @ Ichiraku Ramen https://t.co/5XftHbxmCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th @doublebeatdiddle ... today you DO NOT become an adult, because you accepted the role of young man long… https://t.co/k75dYSAQg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listos para conocer los nuevos #GalaxyS10 en el #Unpacked2019 #SamsungEvent https://t.co/Lg2voUvAXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta crush Buy she don’t like me back... it’s my life and it’s tuff 🤷🏽‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_vladeck @YaleLJournal As an aside, in the airborne in the 70s we trained for riot control a lot. I hated it.… https://t.co/nb1ktdBEjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdacosta @Alyssa_Milano In case you’re ignorant, ICE detains illegal immigrants who chose to break our immigration laws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GazetteLawson I'd much rather see a 23-8 Liberty team in the field than a 17-12 Clemson team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tea time. Brought to you by @Teatulia and @RickandMorty. 🍵🙏 https://t.co/teJ5rLF8Lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Not one of us is capable of holding ourselves to Christ, but Christ is ever faithful to hold us unto himself.” - @albertmohler]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm. If you must put puppies in the window for sale, can you not at least put them together with each other rather… https://t.co/QnSZKHRGgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[! El Buenos días! Alguien busca roomie en Monterrey? Sean serios. https://t.co/hJewTczbkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent a dm to Tom Cruise Friday night when I blacked out telling him my Mom was a huge fan and I wanted to be in a… https://t.co/5W9M9tJ0MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop calling what Trump did at #CPAC A speech.  It was a 2+ hour unhinged barely understandable rant @JoeNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mister_CPU @ErikJLarsen I apologize - I incorrectly read your tweet as a defense of Larsen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTBDarin @Struvee406 I have to wonder how well the pilots were trained on those planes.  I mean none have crashed… https://t.co/YLzGirlqMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It only takes a few good people to show the rest it is pretty cool to do something for others]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our last Last Minute #ValentinesDay2019 ideas from the Home Depot https://t.co/RUW405yx4P  @HomeDepot2505]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great morning for a Texas hike with these great San Antonio educators. Thank you for letting me join!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnlyEverHessa YES omfg the love story is amazing but the most heart wrenching part is the girls home life she is s… https://t.co/PCAZR7q6S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoogiePhoenix @RadioPal1580 @RadioRandy777 Hahaha that’s a creative thought...thank you, Boogie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pokemon Attacc and Pokemon Protecc #Pokemonswordshield https://t.co/ny6iHlibZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sanfrancisco #northbeach #alleyway #alley #cloudy #stormclouds #cloudporn #buildings #iphonexr #iphonography @ San… https://t.co/3qFXC5NS1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefensorSp @CONMEBOL Se hará justicia y no se ganarán los puntos en la mesa, equipo mediocre!]]></document><document><![CDATA[........ come on bruh, spread some of that athleticism around for everybody else]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can say without a doubt even without the dlcs Fallout: New Vegas is the goat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @winegirl73 @realDonaldTrump Perhaps but Bernie will pocket millions and probably buy another house and… https://t.co/Qj1Pm6x9Fj]]></document></documents></author>