<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[MOOOOOOOD. Peter was my Monkeeeee. Once at a show, his slide fell off of his finger. Someone tried to pocket it and… https://t.co/Qw98lAlwx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson @SaraGonzalesTX Please bring on-we keep letting then in and they make high ranking positions, then t… https://t.co/Itbl3R0rSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been around babies for the past 2 days straight and let me tell ya, my baby fever is getting so bad 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Listings hitting the market this week! #thebestwearblue #coldwellbanker #realtor #realtorsofinstagram @ Manhatt… https://t.co/CxNTrquUBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite presentation at the #HIMSS19 #NursePitch is from MyRA which is an app for an RN staffing agency #Nurses4HIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The audit’s data reflects poor-performing building principal’s and high teacher turnover  “PPS has faced substantia… https://t.co/AmgsdUHfmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier She will own this school, if she gets a good lawyer. She needs to talk to the girl from… https://t.co/y7o1uxw8tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSchweigert @Roots_Journey @SammiWangsness Freezer jam is quick  Flash freeze them n use on ice cream or in yogurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that everyone else is allowed to be tired from work or want to go to bed early except for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[❗️🚨GAME DAY🚨❗️ ⛹🏽‍♂️REGIONALS GAME 1  🏀BISON 🆚 CHRISTIAN HERITAGE ⏰Varsity Boys 8 PM 📍CHRISTIAN HERITAGE HS  🗣 YOU… https://t.co/AhXfSRJUKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia House panel approves anti-abortion 'heartbeat' bill https://t.co/L7swYh0HDl via @NBCNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went to bed at 10 pm and my body instinctively woke up at 2 am... nice to know my routine sleeping schedule doesn… https://t.co/E4mA4DEjKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith She never ever mentioned anyone's name. Funny how a guilty conscience shows itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019-20 @CulturalTrust #BroadwayinPittsburgh season has @MeanGirlsBway @thebandsvisit and underrated @BXTaleMusical… https://t.co/fGEYEU1tCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening Now: the Oregon Secretary of State Audits Division is holding a town hall to discuss the recent audit of… https://t.co/CXmpwy1DMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AutumnLilyMTG I’m so happy for your win!! You played AMAZINGLY and had the right build and basically you’re GREAT.… https://t.co/k8Uhhw3fW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find Manafort's sentence suspicious. I'm not sure, but can the judges talk to each other? Is it meant to throw Tr… https://t.co/8Gwcx8reR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kale0579 @Marcpski I think she even rolled her eyes at one point, such an emotional moment doesn't phase her at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump I don’t support a crook of a president that bullies people and lies about everything! He isn’t my president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plz excuse me while I watch law and order SVU and try to figure out how Olivia Benson is so smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[took a pic of my cat using one of the snapchat cat filters and i didn’t expect this https://t.co/PYlUk9kBph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @LukePerryIII Praying for a full and fast recovery for Luke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished the General Session about PBS and wellness. Walking away with some great questions to think about as… https://t.co/derkp8ulfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[An agent of the Russian-controlled arm of the Ukraine gov't ....is what you meant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man really made me bring him to a Mexican restaurant even though we’re working at our Mexican restaurant today 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com Funny thing is in the TRAVEL ads they keep mentioning them as a place to go see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianelyssa Jaysusss lighten. The. Fuck. Up.  If laughing at the orange fucking turd in the WH offends you, then so… https://t.co/QYPJg62XOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD had a plan. Great News. Living With the Silent Enemy will be available to order in Ebook or Book online very so… https://t.co/4NoQhLC6fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FL_lewoo @lynnv378 There were women in that Bernie crowd in Brooklyn. Lots of them.   I am a black woman.  I am NO… https://t.co/a4mWGr3pqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/a3o2k5zc7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 ways to make all your friends hate you (cruelest but yet funniest pranks ever) #comedy #giggle #grin #clever https://t.co/iU9x15uvWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What great ideas and innovation!!! And I'm happy to see so many young people inventing these things!!! You know Tru… https://t.co/JZ0jalJnzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulgogi Banh Mi at #NBAAllStar (Cred: @LevyRestaurants) 🏀🏀 https://t.co/7uqAV1sWUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m certain I am the only person in the world freaking out because the @TUWG stream is not working!!  Is it so much… https://t.co/Zt4zkXZzEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came to help them  move but bad ass wanted to attack me on my brake https://t.co/ltTqy2Ml6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiski Lacrosse season is here. Very excited to watch my sons play together! @TheKiskiSchool @JakeRosa21 https://t.co/c3RGN0eXkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two wonderul #CareerDiversity opportunities available at the @UF_Humanities]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE HOW @stassi TALKS WITH HER HANDS. CRACKS ME UP...YOU GO GIRL... https://t.co/s4GGRJLrhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan I don’t think Zabit won that fight. I’m worried about you. I listen to almost all your podcasts, and that… https://t.co/XsKRxRBgCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet peeve when ppl ask how many sets you have left .. just wait your turn!! 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baxterite I'm really grateful because I did need new shoes for work 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaivanShroff Bernie needs to take his senile ass home and shut the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to join some troublemakers! This is going to be fun! #goodreouble #eduleadersri #sxswedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everyone here in twitter land..   Went for a bike ride this morning.  I like riding around the neighborhood,… https://t.co/b55JDGXpig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttoFernandez Reese, in fact, is saving himself for his one true love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc7greg I’m actually crying. Who could treat a poor innocent animal that way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lauryn Hill, India Arie &amp; Erykah Badu kinda night 💞 // my favorite late night music]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this new location for our conference in #Cambridge  . .#eventrepreneur #lifesciences #meetingplannerlife… https://t.co/o7jIlveyJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kaitlin_s Oddly I don’t love the blueberry goat cheese! But the honey one with some sliced pears...oh my. My kids… https://t.co/5V0OX9Rw83]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sad I missed last night😩 fffff a stomach bug dude. SO SAD @masongarcia18 @candaceeenicole @shelbygriffin96… https://t.co/JGu6ShLp0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[being friends with girls because our bitmoji are actually cute even tho we essentially all look the same and for wh… https://t.co/4pdJfi0jxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt NATE saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade in #SouthKorea  Breed: Jindo Mix Gender: Male  To… https://t.co/WF7qoG4N46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our thoughts are the compass to guide us, point us North, get us to where we are going with the least amount of unw… https://t.co/3i1N5MO0WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever see a man with a beard and perfect set of teeth and wanna just sit on his face Ouuuuuh 😍 bc same 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karynsauers I've been thinking the same thing as I watch this...all day lol. I couldn't do it and not yell at them when they make excuses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyLongDog @brooklinen Your Absolutely Deserving Of Dis Delight Miss Sally.  Dat A Girl. 🥓🥞🥓💕🐾💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceemulahgang On me. I seen a Pre-Game Flyer that had to address on it but said “No Locals Allowed”...Fuck y’all lame ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[huge shoutout to @chelsiexbyrum and all the @BadAttitudeMgmt gals for putting on a dope af sxsw showcase today!! so… https://t.co/QdUnB4UaHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Club Misfits - War Cry ft. Tauren Wells (Lyric Video) https://t.co/HeRsjtDN4V via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ivanka would Pay for Family Leave by Raiding Individual Social Security Funds, Impacting Retirement Funds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renevelation @erichovind your horrible book of fairy tales is why I am atheist. None of it makes sense, None of it happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/SUCIae7ylg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Ok a break is good  Deleting it no we need u I take a break when I need to from all social media]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kainahwilliams Talking to one of your old assistant college coach yesterday, she thought Bek was a Junior:) nope j… https://t.co/1LNj5bVscc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck i miss this. You know youre fucked up when you have dreams about your ex bestfriend picking thing s over you l… https://t.co/sPQqFT4Lj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been nonstop with clients and a photo shoot with Hillary of agapephotographyny today. Awesome energy and a lot… https://t.co/xk0jl4nKLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video is live on my channel!!!  https://t.co/jQ32hNw3qF https://t.co/WMN14rDLjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[V. Franklin on Young Males of Color Consortium/CSU-DH. “You treasure what you measure.” You don’t want program for… https://t.co/aGNdmpEG3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN THINK SOMETHING IS WRONG WITHOUT THINKING THE GOVT NEEDS TO BE INVOLVED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Similar college hunger talks in MN. As stated today this is a growing problem that needs to more discussion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boisestatelive I am pro- Steh' kel at the moment. That said, Stoy' kel could be a fun way...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never will I ever drink your keto coffee you crazed pyramid scheme loving human. Leave coffee out of your nonsense. 🙅🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Hall of the Elders tonight and my FIRST thought was "I haven't seen crabcore/heard music like this since Attack… https://t.co/IbC4IxmkGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly No......they sold their souls out to Obama...…...he was their idol!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobalMouthful @catholicdisco Well it's what works for me. I don't understand why I'm being chastised for needing… https://t.co/KZvZjEpMmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melkargi @elamin88 @takarasmall Thanks for the support, Melissa! We'll miss you 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy la única que puede ver que suleta la pelota y cuando camina le sale otra por la boca]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think about this proposal?  New law would protect people who break into hot cars to save pets -… https://t.co/3l3qXxuQkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I need to catch up with the times, but it’s still weird to me when I see people make social media pages for their babies 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sit down...stay humble. 🤷🏻‍♀️💯 #wheeliewednesday #wheelie #sitdownstayhumble #crash #stuntlyfe #honda #grom… https://t.co/TFynxh6HAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  Cl… https://t.co/R8cdg2n6jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[In bed at ten on a Saturday night. Am I 24 or 82? The world may never know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would highly suggest folks read and watch @TheHateUGive by @angiecthomas - this “situation” we’ve been tweeting a… https://t.co/MuO5bvV1Jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 18 I went to the self proclaimed hot dog king of Chicago’s apartment for a party with my then boyfriend… https://t.co/Lv0Zm5rieT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my #dreamteam on a hike to Potato Chip Rock on Mount Woodson. #whoseafraidofheights #sd #beautyallaround @ Pot… https://t.co/p98iP8OjB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simmonssteve @MaryOrmsby @Ewingsports @DLSpencer10 @RDiManno @blatchkiki @cbrennansports @amyrosewater… https://t.co/5vTJniqZn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you know your heart and the person that you are, you won’t settle for people who don’t know you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kuidu @mmpadellan I have had that same premonition to no avail thus far!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillardLCPS ss conversed w diplomats focusing on history, culture and Peruvian/USA relations and the rest of Spani… https://t.co/aj38gsHdGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning drawing before taking Conrad and Homer to the park.  • • • • comer_the_labs  fbairprogram #watercolor… https://t.co/329ifBTNpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Trump Cover-up -- Mueller's report must be public  https://t.co/CbqheTfdwd @moveon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I just sent President Trump $25. Today's donations are being matched and tripled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I expect nothing less from Tribe. The hate that flows from his pen is palatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyLauraRivas Yo siempre doy Rt y Fav #LosCabronesSomosMás  #LosCabronesSomosMás  #LosCabronesSomosMás]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo! It’s walk-the-show-floor day for me at #expowest. What’s a MUST SEE in health and beauty?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob__Janes Not sure why he would not have if he played on this team for a time. I'm sitting on a bus at 6:15 AM in… https://t.co/6NG7sRlwmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaStJohnBoxer @TheArtofJulian @kristoffstjohn1 @TheStJohnFamily Stay strong 💪🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[ummm me &amp; my sister are still up just hoping we get a 2 hour delay 😓😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiomitre y que PAIS DE LOCOS!!!CON LO QUE SE ROBO Y ESTAFO !!!LA SIGUEN PLR TODDOS LADOS U SIGUE LIBRE!!!PAIS DE… https://t.co/yszbDd6PIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good plan! I didn't order it like stroganoff this time 😂😂😂😂😝💞🔥. Sent my favorite delivery guy. Such a sweetheart. @… https://t.co/O80sAeWWq5]]></document></documents></author>