<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A daily text sent to multiple people from me: “sorry I fell asleep!”  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[She work for it tonight at BEACHES WEHO #beachesweho Just say you won’t let go #choreographer #life #create #LA … https://t.co/X5hY2P8aGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Renata_Melo @solosolooo The hair on both of them is so fuckn gorgeous]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet is the greatest Valentine’s Day Birthday gift of all. The only thing better would be a shout out from… https://t.co/y5bzK2q85E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomSimoncini @SeanRicany We’ll pick you up at the airport in 6 hours!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdyplumber @hobadog @deafheaven @onearmmofo @crazybatmanfan @MtManimal @Nostrafartface @samrulestheworl… https://t.co/ECX6yqUpQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brixius77 @wemlet @MsGMDeJesus @MrDerrGrade2 @KenseyCoach @ankoser @Techieteach11 @MsDelaneyWMS @giasjones @MicSle… https://t.co/5txdJ4NCX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I firmly believe @Bharper3407 joined the Phillies ONLY because of that one time I was in an elevator with him when I worked at the stadium]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david2224r1 @ANAGABRIELRL @annysousa_AG La verdad ella es muy muy sexy y sensual.  Lo que se ponga, le queda.  No… https://t.co/g9vibpeqO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love The Ashby Family. Don't phase them out @joshgriffith59.  There is many s/l's to tell about them with willing w… https://t.co/QOMUw3jZ9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once I start drinking liquor straight from the bottle plz take that shit from me 🤕🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranklinFoer Nobody has a blameless life.especially him.everyone has probably done something wrong.not criminally… https://t.co/fXfrfFB6fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_barona @hkiliaan @UN right down to the 'Merkel's Manufactured Migrant Crisis' and the 'Replacement Pope' ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viktria19050233 @Glenda68336051 @RamonaCousins3 @happycagirl1 @NydiaRaquel25 @RobinACollier1 @TarpeoDesiree… https://t.co/BspMcIQJsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[no need to speak on my problems to anybody anymore. I can solve them hoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and if we’re telling the blogs the complete truth... tell them what led me to make a Tinder in the first place.… https://t.co/SFD6ZlYS3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is National Love Your Pet(s) Day around here. #dogmom #rescuedogsofinstagram #dogsnotdiamonds… https://t.co/s53Ebvd6Y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras y’all!⚜️💚💛💜⚜️💚💛💜⚜️ Laissez Les Bon Temps Rouler!!!⚜️ Gonna be a great parade day!!!… https://t.co/2LvL2t7iV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another empowering @hopelatinas Latina History Day on #internationalwomensday ! So many special nuggets of wisdom f… https://t.co/egrMHWq3Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard4127 @nerdyplumber @tripprrr @Richard65049965 @onearmmofo @deafheaven Richard Peeps giving me the Luuuuuv Mmm hmm I Feeling It!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vintage 80s Billy Idol, Vital Idol cassette tape! #mynostalgiclife #vintage #vintagetap #cassette #cassettetape… https://t.co/TSJtxYJD4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctanner3 @BuddyB04863931 @kc6dhi @my3monkees @RobinFredricks1 @Aug1405 @JSOC_DF2 @misspunk63 @1GaryBernstein… https://t.co/O9AQdmW24P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hwmnylx69 What long lives they both lived!  I’m sure they will meet again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrCaliGrit @fablefy @heARTISTatWORK @AbeRiveraEdu This is wonderful! Thank you so much for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad I was in the morning cave when this came in or else the whole newsroom would have see a different side of… https://t.co/Zzfr0cLoxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OverHorizon808 @AllenWest @JDRucker @NoqReport @realDonaldTrump @gophawaii Lots of states have these issues. Citiz… https://t.co/lj52TVIm19]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the coolest thing I’ve seen in cycling clothing for a long time. https://t.co/QoAc8i7vPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPS_Crestridge GATE 4th Graders using critical thinking, problem solving and teamwork to complete a Breakout Box!… https://t.co/C4OdgjIYLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp   Are you deaf dumb and blind? Don’t you know the truth when you see it?  If you think Trump tells the tr… https://t.co/P25zNeJJMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you DR. @RepRobinKelly for your advocacy in #maternalmortality #2019CLC #AccessIs #powerfulwomen #awomensplaceisinthehouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching @SpeakerRyan have bus ancestry shared on #FindingYourRoots. “That’s an immigrant story if there ever w… https://t.co/65IQjv7dhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so glad you are back on board for Thrive NC year 2 to tackle food insecurities Lionel!  @BlueCrossNC is look… https://t.co/746WmFXd8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean chop some wood with his shirt off?  😂🤔🤔not sure Hallmark will give us that! #Hearties @hallmarkchannel… https://t.co/sp5MjPPhew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just delivered a whole block of cheese to me for vday lol some people just get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new cafe supports employees and customers with disabilities https://t.co/qCO8H4zD7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally every single childhood friend of mine has had a baby  and im just hoping to be married by 30 ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny how some people claim to be a Christian but yet they are the biggest hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow THIS from the media outlet that told Americans that it was ILLEGAL TO READ WIKILEAKS when the Podest… https://t.co/p0cwu02wJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all country music is amazing but listening to it reminds me of summer :-( nebraska plz stop snowing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetJoeLocus @laker477 @bluefamilyprays @Ginger4EverMe @mrshhjones @KathyDutton16 @DarleneG64 @lonestarexile… https://t.co/kt06RptDIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SjCattledog @dogcelebration Nothing like a morning woggle...Have a great day. Thanks of the fluffy Silver pic...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaDied @Conservative_VW The Muslims will outlaw Pork. Wonder what India has to say about this? Cows are sacred there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg lady gaga in jimmy kimmel’s new video COULD SHE BE ANY MORE BEAUTIFUL WE-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarism @cubanalaf It didn’t really affect her until she went to kindergarten; it’s rough for a couple of days and then evens out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedHats4Trump @pattyd1001 @DonaldJTrumpJr @TPUSA @EricTrump @TeamTrump @GeekGirl2u @TeamTrumpGA @CRNC 🙋🏼🙋🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @realJeffreyLord @KurtSchlichter            What about hot dogs?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is playful. Funny Sports Ecard: What does a Bears fan do after his team wins the Superbowl? Turns... https://t.co/rDdvFPDbDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[so happy to be in my bed 🙌🏾 idk what made me think i can hang like i used to omg 😭😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Sounds good - they can use his money to take down the trumps.  I don't care if they throw them all in… https://t.co/bWJ7QoouuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[this was something that had happened before, since i was diagnosed with anxiety and depression as a very young chil… https://t.co/sbEEkjWKAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so faded last night ion even remember who won the Skills Challenges]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seaperch with @Grace__Kearney ! They let us be judges!! @GeorgetownISD https://t.co/JAfMKQvdK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delta Trying to deplane the 9:00 from #Boston to Detroit to get the 12:10 to Phoenix - please hold the plane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok this bitch not only stole MY window seat on the plane but her elbow is in my stomach. I hope she has a miserable day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahWaldrop4 Excuse you, I only think about sleeping earlier because I love to sleep https://t.co/ebPqbMvjBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Key Ways Regular Massage Can Impact Your Selfcare  ▪▪▪ https://t.co/oAEK8D9nIp  #health #Happiness #wellness… https://t.co/fIo1dOaSdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonitaRajpal @AOC LOL, yeah cause Democrats know climate science!! LOL https://t.co/mV7SLTWCRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for this great group of coaches that will be coaching planters and spouses for San Diego! #sendnetwork… https://t.co/Wy2HlOwYjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[IndyGo, planning on electric buses for Red Line, skeptical of Albuquerque’s reported woes https://t.co/ACXUtJH3AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHS Dabbing to make a Difference #fcsdab @FCS_SEC @standandria https://t.co/9bW0St5Utk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Disgusting GOP! Debt surpasses $22 trillion for first time https://t.co/aohIGJt3UK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We 😮😮 when we saw AREs of Book 2 in the #snazzycatcapers series “The Fast and the Furriest” on our publisher’s desk… https://t.co/5wdpkhx9EU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the same patients I had yesterday and one lady was so sad I had to leave last night and was super excited I was… https://t.co/o7D3BTRGfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see the #rotunda at nmsanfrancisco 😍 #neimanmarcus 📸: @nireyam @ Neiman Marcus https://t.co/wF8rRPjWgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream once, I have to be so aware that I can hear a tear drop in the ocean! In the mist of disaster! Which is where I was in the dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy about this tide shifting only in the way that @WonderboyMMA can come get this 170lb belt. You’re not just a g… https://t.co/3pTPj4WqGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennis legend @Martina Navratilova doubles down on transphobia: Transgender athletes in women's sports is 'insane'… https://t.co/8cHseFHSiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the weather can stay like this for next weekend, that would be great! ☀️ #sunnyand60 #nca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mte_detroiter They will watch every move we make.... 100% control EVERYTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Numecet @PointEElbo1 @emrazz For every guy that says that I wish they could give birth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtrovertedMuse Also... if we’re ready to consider leaving FB, don’t we have to leave Insta as well? I don’t know.… https://t.co/aFjn9Zg4hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SsssamanthaaMUA @beautylish That’s freaking nasty!! How are they gonna sell you a swatched product?? Unreal!🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Onde acha Kinder Bueno White messed Estados Unidos de meu Deus  Não aguento mais procurar e ficar passando vontadeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aren’t you sick of being called Racist because you support Our President? My husband MIL is straight from El Salvad… https://t.co/fMuXBobKNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir I fly @Alaska because of the world class service #iflyalaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladybay8 @SamHeughan @mary_markssngr @MakkOlga @GHJNancy @pjl24 @Sheugs @LaurelSchuett @sarahjaswim @barbaramills1… https://t.co/G1i3Q203fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the TD Bank US team! See our latest #CustomerService job openings, including "Teller I - Part time", via the l… https://t.co/Y0Pty1BRwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepy_serpent that was me walking around downtown earlier. da windy city baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers says the budget includes a bump for higher ed.   “We announced this week that we’re increasing Technical… https://t.co/21kM84ksZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C3ddyced Bruh just chatting I ain't worried he think cus I'm a girl I'm gone sell 😂 it's all good]]></document><document><![CDATA[The chemistry between @ladygaga and #BradleyCooper was #sizzlinghot at the #Oscars #ladygagaandbradleycooper ftw!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joel_K_Kramer make it seem like this is only for such a small subset of students and a clear waste of money. I who… https://t.co/RVnV9y3oQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl just goes “I thought we were friends” lol last week you charged my mom $280 for half a head of highlights… https://t.co/QSLl78wMlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man who made me realize life can be fun, happy, adventurous, safe and blissful. I love my husband, lover, best… https://t.co/fCWf23gbpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I wonder How many times they bragged to one another who got the youngest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBurrisWESH @AlexvWESH @kengordon @SpaceCoastSkies Hurley's helping me celebrate my birthday weekend.... Happy… https://t.co/OeFt43Bw6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[every item in my postmates order was incorrect so it’s one of ~those~ days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @TuckerCarlson Can’t take it that he is irrelevant! Begging for some camera time. Has absolutely N… https://t.co/aj0eMcCx0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to announce the launch of @CaparisonGuitar  at  @sweetwatersound ! Soo exciting ! #ccshred #caparisonguitars… https://t.co/8OoHIbj23n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepUnderwood @SecNielsen is lying when she says they are not putting children in cages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in the uber last night at 2 am @jonasbrothers https://t.co/sUuNI65bfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland woo woo  extraordinary beliefs for which it is felt there is insufficient extraordinary evidence, and… https://t.co/3iMwN80xUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler prolly messing with us knowing we’d take the ‘next one’ comment out of proportion and over analyze it 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm kind of an asshole and like to walk across the road in the middle of the road just to see if people stop hoping they hit me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NE_Newmans @erianna16 @Niktor_Newman @EBraeden @MelodyThomasSco Well I beg to differ on the abuse. Mental abuse, a… https://t.co/VQvoPshrta]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yeah, well, outside of landing the Hindenburg in a lightning storm that’s about the shittiest idea I’ve ever heard… https://t.co/zztP3oWVK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan How does it feel to have the Speaker of the House tell Americans you are too ignorant to comprehend the most… https://t.co/hZS6fUcJ8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pullin up like Kobe in the fourth on Friday with some girl in my comp class. If y’all don’t see a swish gif know I airballed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chasewicker This is what I just now dealt with lol https://t.co/mNBtXZ905A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitlinCramer2 Thanks for opening up, Kaitlin! You’re right, there’s always perfect timing. Sometimes it’s hard to remember day-to-day 😌]]></document></documents></author>