<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MattTheGamerGod @TMZ @ChynaJoanLaurer Getting in with DX is likely the first step. Next year she probably gets in solo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukeandymusic totally killed it last night in DC @FlashClubDC 🔊 https://t.co/AM52ZxIoYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskerHistory @OWHbigred vs Miami FB at the 1984 Orange Bowl on the failed 2-pt conversion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been making peanut butter banana smoothies lately for breakfast and snacks and just wanted to remind folks the… https://t.co/dZHKYZiBbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renscorona @santiago4kd @Rayados @Concacaf @ATLUTD Pero hay venta libre no? O ya se acabaron?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Too bad you don't know the difference between communism and socialism.   Hint communism is bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sale, Porcello and #RedSox pitchers out to stretch on Day Two of pitchers and catchers workouts. #wbz @wbz https://t.co/l0cQNy0kMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trinidadyelmo Muy buenos días y feliz sábado para ti también saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is clever. Batman! Thought I already pinned this but oh well https://t.co/JmKQ0j3aNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome time with @Habitat_org. Always great to give back to the community! 🙌 #CanesCare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning be encouraged today https://t.co/YMaO6z9BpN https://t.co/aXnOpVf9OC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We think outside the box....because God doesn’t fit in a box. #DoThings]]></document><document><![CDATA[First song I dropped 100+ views   Latest song 3 views  They don’t support you until they can benefit]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 people wanted to hang out today but they weren’t you so I turned em all down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoBranco5 @CrankyClair Problem with the DP rule is that it can get out of hand, and won’t give incentive to the… https://t.co/H5sNVbe6ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ron_Nirenberg I'd take a city that expanded 1604 to 3 lanes between 35N and I10W some time this century.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes it's best to hang w the ogs! #olliebrown RESPECT .@sinbadbad respect x u man!!! https://t.co/uSPtKbrujQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Part I - Rabbit 2 Ways: rabbit, portobello and chive stuffed ravioli, Tuscan fried rabbit leg, spicy ra… https://t.co/aJA065wfuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we play as good in the Fall as we dance in the Spring, @IndianaFootball will shock the @bigten  Gotta love the w… https://t.co/EMvfrv2m2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip One thing of the many reasons a wall is needed. You people only see what you are told to see your like fucking parrots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@An0nymous_GT El problema es que en Guatemala ay gobiernos corruptos y ricos corruptos de riqueza de Guatemala]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mind/Body/Light/Sound by Foreign Objects @ BRU 64 — https://t.co/rLQouYdjkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latrilife @RottenAl Sixers are pissing me off again today with their half ass and what’s up with Ben “#NotCharlieHustle Simmons?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@five9a2 @hpcnotes @exascaleproject @RiceK2I I was actually referring to her assertion that we should be switching… https://t.co/JjYh3ozeaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximaxoo @ConversationUK OK, let me try to get bbavk on track a bit. The Deccan craters and the asteroid event co… https://t.co/LnmrpzXiPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying something a little different. The photo turned out not have bad considering the cape is hard rubber lol.… https://t.co/BWlOknLdpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManMadeMoon Marketing for port o lets is outstanding! Give us your stinking business!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love Funkos @RogerClark41 - check out these custom designs I drew up for @patkiernan @JamieStelter and you!… https://t.co/27CVIi1bmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#home at last, I feel like the Prodigal Son coming home to see his #Geronda #saintnicholas Chapel @… https://t.co/1p2sXLouZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOUTS OUT TO THE @DaBabyDaBaby FOR THIS AWESOME MARKETING PLAN!!! 😂😂😂😂 I SEE YOU!!! PROMOTERS SEND THAT FRONT END… https://t.co/4CnXsPUE0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of me thinks Ronda Rousey and the WWE are working everyone with her newest vlog. But part of me also thinks sh… https://t.co/Gg3Aho8hVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[is br*tman r*ck really being retweeted onto my timeline https://t.co/m0dD6UsWWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN @Espngreeny @Realrclark25 @RealJayWilliams It’s a shame if labron would have stayed in cleveland he woul… https://t.co/xstVI5Vr4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Certainly not purely benevolent motivations at play. But focusing on the oil alone is incredibly reductive. Much of… https://t.co/UO4XJZNORs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Then she should move to Nevada. Leave the rest of us out of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo de @fecode no sólo es en Colombia. @__ayduchis__ @cmbustamante @LuchyB @Lizz_Bennet @vivibarreral @LeszliKalli… https://t.co/NRVHZPLvyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people argue with these facts? And that thing about the parties have changed positions since then is fiction… https://t.co/OCTQkYhN5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taorminalepore Also raised/learned on two but die-hard one spacer now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLoesch They probably don’t get the show live so when he calls no one answers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I not have VIVID dreams and just sleep like a normal person? I genuinely had to reacclimate to my surroundings… https://t.co/1JuZKZMgHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNITED STATES SERVICE ACADEMY NIGHT🇺🇸 Congressman Latta is hosting a United States Service Academy information nigh… https://t.co/tvsS4vZB3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBMatthews Agree 100%. These are not merely covers. They’re total reinterpretations! Bravo, Bettye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather is bad out here make sure yall drive careful to yall destination..message from Sprint Complete @ Okemos, Mi… https://t.co/ZSRi8QbbVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i dont do nothing except for lay in my bed and laugh at my phone screen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex and Ethan are beginning TeenPact today. Praying that they will learn the Biblical role of government and how t… https://t.co/5XBV7ejF3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy came in the museum about a rock It was simply a rock  He has to ask how old it was... I’m over today...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MENAsymbolism @bdaiwi_historia Yes, for the people that modern scholars have called Byzantines, who generally call… https://t.co/hP4KS72xhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMal_Content Every time I drive by this sign I hear it in a “Bulls on Parade” voice https://t.co/riWMEJQLo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murraymaker @russellcrowe @mang0ld I saw for the 1st time last night Bad Lieutenant Harvey Keital. How did I miss… https://t.co/UaQqp5ENZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney The bill is Congress' way to say Trump is a moron. His $11B shutdown was all for nothing. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo.... my wife and I have now had to resort to leaving 30 min before our usual time to get on @NYCTSubway. Even w… https://t.co/cL43QEK6zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT It needs scrapping. It’s pretty simple really you play for the country of your birth unless you have joi… https://t.co/LZrijpNzOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachgraham8 I still think we make a Wild Card spot if we can replace Trump at QB with Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCTigerTracker So you didn’t see anything in Mexico that indicated something was wrong with his neck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salem, Systems, Settle, Spriggs, Spec https://t.co/r1WCcCQSxK https://t.co/WdqJN9zsGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fwabbys I must’ve missed it in that stretch out past Ingles. I gotta pay closer attention. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really good player &amp; even a better kid. Kid’s been well coached. Congrats Garrison!!! @Lilly_Steve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Solo documentary about Alex Honnold who climbed 3,000 ft vertical granite slab El Capitan in Yosemite withou… https://t.co/P0bPtGJoNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joco609 @GGMidnight_ @SaintsNato No wonder they cant pay players when they cant even afford decent branding or designs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Whee...Heavy by Jim-n-I Brewery @ Meece's Martini &amp; Beer Deck — https://t.co/n1xIkjWk0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win an iPad mini from @RightThisMinute and you can too! Details here: https://t.co/u3Z3g7edfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplySylvan It’s decent! Only 6 side buttons but really most MMOs/ games don’t use more than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Public_Citizen @MikeOkuda @AOC You know, on the surface this looks like one of those issues on which liberals and… https://t.co/AWbiQ4ANBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub @Andy Marge thinks it’s cool that she and her mother cheated. Oink Oink 🐷]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s So Cool About Manufacturing? Awards program was held this evening. 1100 people turned out! https://t.co/ObxDXnbDhm @PAManufacturers]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman is a saint for tolerating me, and that's why I'm marrying her https://t.co/YYsJmPBufF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaugauphil @JFLisee Y'a des gens qui se sont fait des carrières sur des gags méchants et gratuit sur Jean Charest,… https://t.co/j7v3DZhue6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a CSO/CISO or VP/Head/Director/Manager serving in a security capacity within your organization, please t… https://t.co/z8IESScdNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKinzinger you need to vote on resolution I am from Illinois and you are my rep, please vote for it. The president is breaking the law!]]></document><document><![CDATA[His League Basketball games and Pictures for Saturday are cancelled. We will make these up. @ New Salem Baptist Chu… https://t.co/S6TW1hGR1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBobb20808476 Trump signed more executive orders than any president. Look it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bedford–Stuyvesant, Brooklyn https://t.co/uPJNpMCPAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell In the words of the great Mr Jefferson (GEORGE Jefferson): "Mighty white of him to say that!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[☺️😶👊🏻👷🏻‍♂️😻😀☠️🤰🏻🥽☂️🦖🐸👨‍👦‍👦💆🏻‍♂️ 💆🏻‍♂️👨‍👦‍👦🐸🦖☂️🥽🤰🏻☠️😀😻👷🏻‍♂️👊🏻😶☺️ 😀😃😄🤫🦷🖕🏻🧙🏻‍♂️🤘🏻👔🤮👄👩🏻‍🔬👊🏻😶 🦷😙🧙🏻‍♂️🧠😱😀🥺🤘🏻🥺😀🥺🦷😢🤣🤘🏻👊🏻… https://t.co/i9AnyUKGIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monsters_Multi @T_HUD_REPPIN @IncorrigiblePar I like your line of thinking ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammy_Goal You Europeans need to get rid of these all powerful bureaucracies that control your sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulljahhh No but,  I say hey if it happens it happens we're adults.  That's between us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarlemPictures @Help_Them_Out @Struthers72 @TheDemCoalition @Quaker1949 That's what I say,they'd do that if it was… https://t.co/3OawBFtoy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewdd214 @SECNetwork @Vol_Hoops @KentuckyMBB Maybe if he stayed on his feet more than his back I’d agree 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Armelgeddon I agree with you in Cali being the worst 😂 I haven’t been to Washington or Arizona yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mud works when you run out of ideas. Ideological driven mindset will crush all under the weight. Canada has come ou… https://t.co/dieXXrzdeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @OklahomaPatrio1 Actually, it is entirely and utterly believable to be coming out of the foul mout… https://t.co/gpskOXgITI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking It’s about time. UK Labour Party sucks big time. It’s Laborious.👎🏻😂 #UK #Labourparty #sucks #EU #Brexit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems Yes because the democrat are doing what you the republicans traitors didn’t do MICHAEL i… https://t.co/A2lvItzwIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby AUNTIE IS MY HERO!!!  #crabby2020 #womentalkandmenopause #enoughwiththehashtags… https://t.co/ovY0n1C91Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @googlecloud (App Engine) &amp; @springboot how come you guys don't wanna play nicely together? #frustrated]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/W0IwvfkKZo #Solarweather #Astrophysics #ClimateChange #Science]]></document><document><![CDATA[it completely owns how someone else is using my @spotify account and neither i nor they have been able to do anything about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[A.I. NO OXYGEN HUMANS NEED OXYGEN  REALLY YOUR BUILDING A LIFE FORM SMARTER THAN HUMANS THAT DOESN'T NEED OXYGEN.… https://t.co/bBzbWvfAq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBegnaud @Politics_NYY Hey,From day of storm  thru 2day PR has been treated worst than a 3rd WORLD? So much fr… https://t.co/izCuTTo7yZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnkdowling @DrShawnQI @IlseZorn @VaillancourtSam Also true ... a full change management program attached to… https://t.co/GUSt9ZW5U4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohiamjanie That’s a YUGE warning sign. I’d tell him not to contact you anymore. https://t.co/YAiy0gY2C8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dodgers need to close the deal and sign Bryce Harper: Close the deal, Dodgers. Bryce Harper is out there, waiting.… https://t.co/eAM4uC0g2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @SlayerMosh @chriswaslight @Truth2Dj @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/6v4q97UhSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the entire @SpaceX and @NASA teams for whom some of the hardest work of data analysis now begins… https://t.co/8j18e1Kkl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn the Arkells put on a good show. I’ve seen them more times than I can count, from a tiny club in the Market to… https://t.co/iBG3sJ8cGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karliebrassclub @pr3ttyinp3arls @wetlike_Raine @My_Tinymonster @yourmusicsucks @CanadianBeave13 @MomO5Tiff… https://t.co/ymLBeUpNlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of people checking out this thread. One like, no replies. The most visible/discernible symptom of the damage d… https://t.co/P3byw6K4M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents have packed the high school cafeteria to learn about a proposal to drug test students. The new policy could… https://t.co/1VisoEuPFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sactownhammer @IamKDiddy I used to go to work at Kennedy Airport at 345 am. If that's the gig, you do it. And I wasn't hoopin.]]></document></documents></author>