<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@robinmarty @LeahNTorres That’s 2nd trimester. Yes. That’s why. Not 1st trimester.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJKoch She kills babies because is a damn multi billion dollar business, CONVINCING WOMEN, that this is their… https://t.co/n5HRbAua5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner is served!! A bit diverse and extra light tonight!! Have a great weekend!! #guacamole #cucumber #celery… https://t.co/R9xG6N718h]]></document><document><![CDATA[...that logic to all the ideas that come to us. Maybe the way we’ve been doing things is actually killing our futur… https://t.co/CI6R26ZBy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BVM @EvanonHB @SeanFromSeabeck @benbbaldwin @bRoundy @CableThanos_ @SeahawkScout @Camorooni @zjwhitman I SAID THE FIRST PART]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naturalwayj @sailormarspimp omg what lipgloss are you wearing it’s so ✨✨✨✨✨✨✨✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcarmody My biggest celebrity crushes when I was younger...  1) @RobLowe  2) @jonbonjovi  3) Patrick Swayze 🙏🙏🙏  I… https://t.co/Ts6dDri98i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC And you realize that most teachers don’t even make this. You disgust me with your ignorant posts. THINK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on, @DallasStars. You just told a family that you’re flying them to LA and giving them tickets to the Magic Ki… https://t.co/CZdRCDG7gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra I don’t think she’s talking to us.  It’s all brainwashing for the young]]></document><document><![CDATA[gave my first official conference presentation today! it was an honor to be a part of the inaugural #IGGAD https://t.co/hhdETgEehv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always wanted super long hair but I actually love shorter hair ! https://t.co/5EJjzfaXFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hope you have unprotected bird sex and get bird AIDS.” - @ArtoDas to the annoying vulture in super Mario 64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackystjames @jackystjames 😍 I wouod absolutely love to be directed by you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Dear Ms. OMAR.. ..I am a democrate from NJ who fights for everything America stands for, is,and should be. B… https://t.co/0ficsFB95x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this how my morning is going OR a new country song I’m working on - you pick: I hit my knee so hard on the dress… https://t.co/ghAQsxpqOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDreamKiller Once, I was in a packed hotel room where someone slept in the bath tub. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WHATABLESSING!💜 @ Raising Our Sons in America - ROSA https://t.co/G7UjMwBAVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOHNNYLAUNONEN @KenCageRepo @Discovery Right? We could do this all day 😉 https://t.co/tCQPIf2z27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johbee44 @RealJamesWoods It amazes me, the haters can't make a statement against any Republican without calling th… https://t.co/7MU3W46o2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[💔💔😭 I have so so much love in my heart for animals,I feel such a strong connection 2 them, literally balled my eyes… https://t.co/x7vDXyjY4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why aren’t u speaking up for us. U say u care about the American people and God. We need u to help us fight for our… https://t.co/8K4QiTl4uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an interesting point. So you are an #AI firm and do not use #AI?  Thanks @MusicComposer1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes This part of the Trump administration war on women. Put dumb girls in charge of something so later when th… https://t.co/paCPauvFYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance I’m not sure Trump even knows what a job description is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time me and zach got stuff for margs (he’s 24 and never had one??) and we had ONE (1) marg each before he drank… https://t.co/w5dnd3NS6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Georgiaecon provided on-time and relevant resources to teachers through the “Economic Decision Making and the U.S.… https://t.co/kjvApzdCmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SOCIALISM in OUR USA !! Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders enters crowded 2020 presidential race  https://t.co/DuPl1tRg5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I'll second that! @RepAOC #AOCStupidestHumanBeingOnThePlanet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schiff needs a gag order and an investigation. He clearly talks like he has gotten insider info he shouldn't and tr… https://t.co/rNV4jp6kT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albee once again refuses to participate in my thirst traps. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/wjDSRfvQG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally forgot about this rainbow from last Sunday. From Little Tokyo. #rainbow @ Little Tokyo https://t.co/8hQ37YM1kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenMacKinlay Oh I recall those days with fondness... but don’t worry, soon they just mix in with the life creas… https://t.co/J33mF2QXtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who doesn’t care about the kardashians or the jonas brothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMNPolitics @BetoORourke @JohnCornyn @gromerjeffers 😂Beto couldn’t win for Dog Catcher!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Sooo true!!! And they want to control our money!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TripsWithTykes Dude I hear ya on scheduling summer camps, they tend to be ‘you snooze, you lose’ around here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two videos @thecherrypicks made. One for female features only and one for all features. This is one with ALL LADIES… https://t.co/6SXYZzpvl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind @cmclymer well clearly they haven't improved the quality of their staff with this one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are my #TeacherStats! Create and share yours here:  https://t.co/4G8RDxphBA #T2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning, early learning. Getting schooled @Cronkite_ASU  with @azlatinomedia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My press release regarding today’s Budget Hearing on Senior Center Food and Kitchen Staff. Throughout the budget se… https://t.co/C2jQiLx9JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeTomCorbett @seanhannity Hey Sean. You liked this tweet. Guess it wasn’t fake?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You perverted ass nigguhs is sexualizing fucking pants that fit 😭😭😂😂😂 not surprised but sir shut up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90daysthefilm made their debute last night on @revolttv.  If you have not seen this film it is a must!  The dialog… https://t.co/TN5r4Z8Rsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toyin81 Idk about AGREEMENT 😅 I would give my child a strange name though 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattypriorfan I would love to be there to cheer you on! Love your attitude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my coworkers are getting emails/meeting invites from me rn and honestly, I hope they complain]]></document><document><![CDATA[This must be unconditional.  How can a governor take away our right to vote.   You all wanted Christie out now we h… https://t.co/0bazONOcG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to try this gonna try this @SnoopDogg come chief with me here in Oxford Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eggs are already jumping up and down just watching him come around that corner...come on big ole Fitz 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinMahone BEST VIDEO IN MY OPINION!!!!  💖💖💖💖💖 I LOVE YOU SOOO MUCH!!!! 🥰🥰🥰🥰 Austin Mahone - Why Don't We (Offic… https://t.co/4mle9ZTnTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for a talented and wellness-loving student to serve as our Marketing and Media Intern this summer qu… https://t.co/o7twdGrfwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe this drunk guy tonight asked me if I was dressed as snookie..... it was an 80’s themed party lmfaoooooo 😂🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineW73414395 @YouTube Only thing I might of done different is have @Wynonna instead of JLo. ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some comedy. 75 Family-Friendly Elf on the Shelf Ideas | Skinny Mom | Tips for Moms | Fitness... https://t.co/5NQ8Dk9HdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deisleynk @EmmaRikas @educationrocks5 I just purchased this. It is next on my reading list 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iivid @mlinewoods If you don't mind sharing...was only a reflector used? You SHOULD be proud 👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smolderInspire @katysimoncm @cmortara77 @khackbusch I got told i won’t have funding for my position next year!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We found the value #SouthernSummit @KimPollishuke https://t.co/UbpKYZMFH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFetterman @JohnFetterman your determination, generosity, and willingness to think outside of the box fills me… https://t.co/v8zT0KQwaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michaelpagejr3 @msmoon61 @keeshond81872 @ClaraMo18952708 @DrJimmyStar Your welcome!!! Make sure to put it thru Facebook and instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing that fux me up more than these melatonin gummies I bought for my trip to Canada last week. I just had 2. Goodnight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meg Ryan, where'd you go? Such a treat to have world's most likable interviewer @david_marchese join @nytmag: https://t.co/YeF2Lc6Lb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was tipsy af this weekend and still didn't eat Ohio pizza that's how dedicated I am to NJ pizza. 🍕#ThePizzaLifeChoseMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[the disagreements that turn into arguments that turn into something worse have GOT to stop and tbh, it’s starts wit… https://t.co/SqLptuSUhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if he has to be miles away, I can finally carry this picture wherever I go 😭🖤 https://t.co/468UdkEpge]]></document><document><![CDATA[mas show do hungria foi mto legal, o cara botou ate gospel p tocar, uma vibe mto boa]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to the kiddo who punched me in the jaw Bc that shit still hurts lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Moreno Valley, California https://t.co/MZzaDI3dWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Really? LIMBAUGH? the drug addicted lying sycophant? #LimbaughSucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question.  Since companies are getting the same tax breaks they got last year are their employees getting the littl… https://t.co/BejeDMPufo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanvickers hey are there going to be more of the autism comedy nights?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been so busy lately, I haven’t had time to do the things I love. Hopefully I find a new pattern to have time f… https://t.co/Se1EsECZy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Please. Making Comfort Dogs an Everyday Part of School https://t.co/McApsptBU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got to visit the winery where my FAVORITE Pinot Noir is produced. 🙌🏻✨ Not only is @PennerAsh one of my fa… https://t.co/6nksgZn5Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR You don’t deserve the disrespect by the scum who are questioning the validity of your story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KensingtonRoyal @queenscomtrust I️ don’t understand WHY KP headline her name before the future Queen of England, s… https://t.co/LNXxt2cXTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next issue of The Valley Star newspaper and website will have my review on the extraordinary Peter Jackson WWI… https://t.co/qw28r7i5RO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KRIS6News digital team, sorry us reporters are the way that we are 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come nobody is boycotting the show 'Empire' and demanding that Jussie Smollett be exiled like   Rosanne Barr?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just dropped my whole container of yogurt on my black scrub pants &amp; freshly shampooed seats... HAPPY FREAKIN WEDNESDAY TO ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helene_wpli @GoImpact_Today @TF_Ecosperity @Temasek @galipeau @sallyeaves @debraruh @DioFavatas @UN_SDG… https://t.co/ma7ozr82PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopChassid @AOC And look how her supporters are now coming and replying to you aggressively. It will take minutes… https://t.co/YZ4AwJ6r0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @katyperry @LionelRichie @LukeBryanOnline They are the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“#SelfCare is a MANDATORY part of maintaining a #traumainformed school program.” @JulieBeemATN #TSS2019ATN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your best friend gets engaged to HER best friend, your character wears a pride ring to celebrate. 💕🌈… https://t.co/4bXRzVcC1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[You met both sides, know the drama, know the craziness and you're still with me @erivas199813]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pristine Mobile Detail - Get Car Detailing from the Professionals https://t.co/BZhBBZezS8 https://t.co/eyzj98gCLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Watershedd @reinventionfail @43a6f0ce5dac4ea Your killing me...I can't stop laughing🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used to be a bit easier, now there’s so much etiquette to unfriending. LOL. https://t.co/dgCLObcdon]]></document><document><![CDATA[🆕 arrival available in white, black and leopard 📷:@lattesandlabcoats https://t.co/l14nn5MTDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johniadarola All of what you said is true except for the parts where faux news or for that matter ANY national new… https://t.co/j9muocHhJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being such a POS that you're threatening to arrest someone that is pretty much dying of cancer. All because… https://t.co/6cFvG1fBpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to donated used/old/new bras they don’t want anymore let me know! My store is donating them and sen… https://t.co/bX5UxTkB0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voguelaurel @JonHewettWWJ @WWJ950 Anybody hate traitors?  Worth taking off work for in my book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godVeveryone @Pontifex "Bad Fog Of Loneliness" I See What You've Become And Put Aside The Rest I Dream Of Everythi… https://t.co/yBwunVDG6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarpad and @realGpad are literal relationship goals. Support, love, kindness, confidence, and a collective goofine… https://t.co/LstMAMV4qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FcknTide It technically is but anyone can go to your profile and switch it to tweets and replies and it’ll be there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow she is sunny and the sky is blue. The east coast schools could not 🤧]]></document></documents></author>