<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[17:54 Temp. 74.3°F, Hum. 73%, Dewp. 63.1°F, Bar. 29.85 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 194° 2.7 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex is great and all but being stuck in Trenton listening to Africa by Toto is next level boys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Buddy Abraham Lincoln once said : It is better to be thought a fool then to speak up and remove all doubt… https://t.co/elTKLzDicH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy mommy how come daddy changed so much after becoming FISA JUDGE.  Dear he had to give up Truthfulness  Loyalty… https://t.co/B1D83CjQnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3hnQLkpW01 can I put you @JewdyGold in the running... Fingers crossed]]></document><document><![CDATA[STEP OUT OF YOUR COMFORT ZONE MOTIVATION https://t.co/NkmDmHejXm via @YouTube wonderful words of wisdom from my fri… https://t.co/mcQlpXpLed]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to play the game, put in the time so that people with other things to do will want to come to your… https://t.co/33dt74CD8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaylaRimpson Crazy huh? We've had freezing temperatures in California also. Climate change is real]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Amell reveals real reason why Arrow is ending after eight seasons https://t.co/gIZo4zQVqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[El primer tour del año me lleva a cantar en los camiones de la bella angelópolis. Si Dios conmigo, ¿quién contra mi… https://t.co/1cADRLVgME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsBreaking @michaelbeatty3 Oklahoma Gov. signed bill this week allowing people without licenses, training to car… https://t.co/F3GtavMitL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleClout @DefiningSports @GPSTPETE He just likes to hang out on the table and be close!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimlittle3388  Happy Hsppy Happy Birthday Kim!!!  🔴⚫️🐾 Hope it’s a great day!! 🍾🥂 https://t.co/lyyUllrqdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got groovy at the Grateful Dead tribute show last night @_thisdummy @stashalaska @McAwesome2012 https://t.co/pNAdqEJFmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ainsleyearhardt nice job getting paid to lie and distort facts.  https://t.co/BFDWYP0eT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tawdrylorde All the shows on HGTV should go back to their past clients and re-remodel the houses. Then in 40 years… https://t.co/pKiZJlYTId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgoodlaw @emzorbit @SenatorRisch is nothing but a embarrassment to the US, the Senate, thoughtful constituents, an… https://t.co/urH4SmqLOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawgsfan34 Whoa....didn’t see that coming: Appreciate the update!.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday, let’s get this week rolling. Good run to get the day started. Steady winds added extra resistance thro… https://t.co/aOwVeBdddH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning sunrise from Waterloo,Ont @Lyndsay_CTV #StormHour @MurphTWN @WeatherNation @ExploreWR @sunset_wx… https://t.co/hLnIDCVHBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've committed to giving that pay raise, and we'll advance those pay raise measures again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece from @alexbaca on sprawl.   IMO, our policy choices in infrastructure are the biggest overlooked input… https://t.co/lJAwTnBOcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenifa_0_Jenny No he gets classified because they take and don't give ,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You know nothing about Our laws.  We The People despise socialism and anyone scum who supports it.  You get wh… https://t.co/JGurnsVrop]]></document><document><![CDATA[L’un des plaisirs de l’hiver à @MTL_Ville @LePMR❄️💪🏻❤️! https://t.co/qiB5cekxzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Football games too besides every white kid doing that goofy Fortnite stuff most look around for acceptance for thei… https://t.co/EKqGMq2wDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job tonight Jazz band!  #jazz #BrahamProud #cheesecake @ KBEK 95.5FM https://t.co/RC9OYO9vMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to #JamesBaldwin! #IfBealeStreetCouldTalk #Oscars #ReginaKing]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The country.  The country is breaking. It may not be long for this world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was INCREDIBLE. Thank you to everyone that came out in the shitty weather, HUGE thank you to all of the… https://t.co/7bqicDph0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane @jodymacman Great offseason would have meant a BIG free agent and Realmuto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeidckol @GobiernoMX @lopezobrador_ Y la seguridad pública para cuando?🤔 https://t.co/LKCEE5lhXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcool629 @Futurist_conf @IOHK_Charles @AlBurgio He really did. He was there to learn about the disruption of blockchain. Exciting times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penny for their thoughts..... @ Baltimore, Maryland https://t.co/11zxHJaMn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAristeguieta Sera probo pero es admirador del Monstruo de Sabaneta y su legado, lo cual lo desacredita para dirig… https://t.co/LcBjoKh4Q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimesLikeThes14 @realDonaldTrump I’m sure you do.  After all, that’s what Faux News tells you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump It's also ignorant to think that Obama had anything to do with it right been over 2… https://t.co/a7X2cnZRZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cody_Mercier8 Padres could be awful or not.. either way Machado will be happy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump supporters are ugly AF. I'm pretty sure like 90% of them are fat too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billyb2009 Thanks Billy. One day, we’re going to meet and do big drone things together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning 🌞 Scripture of the day 📖 Have a blessed day 🙏🏻 #scriptureoftheday #scripture #haveablessedday… https://t.co/wgd9bVJFOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Call Out My Name by The Weeknd, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/fxGb9iMtKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuriousBug @Cmoore704 @michhastings @tresmagnafique @aterkel That's even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 In Washington State, labor unions are supporting efforts to address the housing shortage by ending exclusionary… https://t.co/9L1xq4xElp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting Saturday morning off, as I often do, in @flydogyoga.  One class down; one more to go at the end of a long… https://t.co/3ao7Snkb7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_imonlyb @OfficialFayBla @noobde Hit that 🔎 and punch it in...we all out here wonderin where it's at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith please explain to me why this man didn’t make the futureNBAallstar game??? @NBA @KingJames]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s awesome how one solid workout can improve your whole day for the better! Mindset, attitude, and confidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay. Waffles the dog found safe after 60-hour Erie adventure https://t.co/FNuHH9i7YK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Baystate Health? We're hiring in #Springfield, MA! Click for details: https://t.co/nebQUFk77I #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you say B E A Utiful weather⁉️ It’s going to be a ⛅️ 70 degree day for our partners @ORUBaseball &amp;… https://t.co/P79xh0oJdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lopeezie @girlsreallyrule “Fake news again. It was to pass a silent one- but it was wet. Thus the shaky knees and… https://t.co/N6saWBOx43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day isn’t just for couples, im gonna get fucked up to just for the hell of it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwayslapislove None of them did. Jeremy Irons is English, other dude is French. Gabriel B is Irish, and the only… https://t.co/odMOEpi8NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendys any reason why when I ask for a burger with ketchup and pickles only, not only am I not offered a receipt b… https://t.co/lCuOkpusD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHenderson2000 He didn’t wanna go to a team with a trash QB and then went to a team with a trash QB. Makes no sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benifits of CBD OIL: ANXIETY- EPILEPSY- NAUSEA- SLEEP AID-  . If you deal with any listed above maybe if your time… https://t.co/CBh2qHTpym]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why not name the monsters, so we don’t get them mixed up, general. It’d make things a lot easier.”  “Well... sound… https://t.co/Jps8lsBwq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jandrade @BriannaWu You folks really want to let them out, come up to New England Dragway with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn_DeMore1 @LadyRedWave Were those WALLS keeping all the commoners away from Hollywood and media "royalty"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 Our politicians where not entrenched lobbyist whores .who think they're royalty maybe something will get done]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I will kill a lot of red wing black birds to help out frustration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nitro. Wow. - Drinking a Nugget Nectar by @TroegsBeer at @troegsbeer  — https://t.co/GKQswNx11P]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Future of Homo Sapiens” @XapiensMIT: my thinking as always on expert events, what does an average person, not… https://t.co/gNqBxMD0dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning 🌞 5 Below Zero in West Bolton Vermont 🇺🇸 https://t.co/JeKmzCEPmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No filter. Dear filmmakers, it isn’t the setting or the scope/angle. It’s the wet pavement. Please. #indiefilm… https://t.co/s0ztIx4dSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielamunoz_ @carriebeck114 WOW. Definitely not. You’re the one fan girling over the Jonas brothers instead of Lo… https://t.co/ekMPKCjsYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hip Hop artist and actor Common with his group August Greene at Stubb's BBQ during SXSW 2018. Sxsw is in the air, c… https://t.co/zkKlMyJvL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Charleston Recommendations for Coffee https://t.co/GSLTHAKNb1 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how females only have this energy on social media but imma stay quiet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnWalkerShow @albinokid @Greg_Archer @BrianSimsPA @wcruz73 @DrewSteller @EricShawQuinn @frankdecaroshow @teeco71… https://t.co/GQmqLAPbnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido No preguntes, destituye a los ladrones principales. #noperdon a las ratas ladronas. https://t.co/lYs3u4Y78S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guatemayabyesi @jamesrgoodman @clvtrujillo @DavidHarris707 @NaranjoFdez @1207go @silvamalabet @irene46mx… https://t.co/f5leVp0jh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdenAdore I would love to slide my dick in your pussy and fuck you till you cum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typing out a huge vent post and deleting it because I don't /really/ need everyone to know my business lol. Long st… https://t.co/4iQV87QAfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dal vs Stl. That’s the best 60 minutes of (STARS) hockey I’ve seen all year. Tremendous effort top to bottom. GO STARS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnolan888 @realDonaldTrump Why don’t you use some of that surplus to get some of the homeless off the streets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @SouzaParejo This phony dumbassadry by Lindsey Graham is getting stale. It’s high time that sorry POS… https://t.co/VYrjZwr3YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__GJ2 She’s an AKA and from Columbus that’s worst combination ever bro lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Risked it all tonight, but the main focus is taking care of close friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[a day at the #theatre #marktaperforum #lindavista #traceyletts @ Mark Taper Forum https://t.co/AOIzRrDV5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to go support my brother @devonfranklin at barnesandnoble   Event for his new book “The Truth About Men”. I a… https://t.co/VGzBBP0b1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how he was dragging his feet giving up info now he ready to tell everything as soon a possible .. that e… https://t.co/htaXPnFmhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhAlexandriaa She’s was literally such a bitch about it: “I WON BY A MILLION VOTES” OKAY AND WE’RE ASKING YOU TO H… https://t.co/rZVZTZrshM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BlessUp 🙏  @Nike @KingJames @Kaepernick7 @highsnobiety https://t.co/1ZlMuS4BX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a nice look at former #STLCards CF Tommy Pham by my pal @TBTimes_Rays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyJones23 It was awful down there. I had to drive up at 5 right when it got really really bad. The roads were sliccckkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a living baby outside of its mother.  What points are scored here?  Disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our joshuatreeicehouse is living up to its name this week. Cannot wait to be warm inside under the tin roof when th… https://t.co/yb5fvMaOFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hwy 330 between Coffeeville and Tillitoba,  near the Tillitoba Lake is temporary closed due to water going over the… https://t.co/TgIStLIXu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[De @Chivas para toda la vida y sin duda hoy más que nunca, es necesario empezar a considerar la salida de Cardozo O… https://t.co/BbstnsyLUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walgreens, Walmart ,Rite Aid, CVS , all put their Valentines stuff on 50-75% off 2 hours ago pacific time.   Flower… https://t.co/gIMcokPlII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BracketguyDave I’m curious how the bracket community will treat VCU if Temple becomes a Q1 win. The win at Dayton… https://t.co/IFkmI97zrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which is what they have in Kap, Nylander, Johnnson, Kadri, etc. Giving up draft picks to add size when they’ll just… https://t.co/5xMFC0mlLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrassWisdom @NickSoutter There is no way you actually belive that to be true. You are insulting both our intellige… https://t.co/un5r8FZr6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWeirdTeacher It's my favorite album of the year...so good in every way...Their first one is amazing, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Orange Sickle by @carsonsbrewery @ Carson's Brewery — https://t.co/MLDXVMQZip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @giddy81370604 Republicans are so gullible. They think Trump is conservative when he was a liberal, pro… https://t.co/UpJrkBWSX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ridiculous how much I’m constantly moving at my job lol I’m at 17,000 steps and it’s not even noon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just deleted mine and Karinas messages for the first time and it literally freed up 5 whole gigs on my phone...]]></document></documents></author>