<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Great keynote address by Dr. Gerber at the LCCC Psi Beta Induction ceremony.  Congrats to our inductees! https://t.co/qrK29Jaf7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaricelaAlcan10 That he is in remission!! He is returning to his Yard now but he now calls it our Yard now!!🤗 He i… https://t.co/8LwlX9MGZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Importance of Good Sex as a Black Woman https://t.co/jn0csnIRg2 via @glamourmag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Most would still gladly bend over with their hand extended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least it’s over. He picked a goddamn team. Now if Bryce can just decide already...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Media night for thenakedmagicians  @LeCochonNoir @ Brad Garrett’s Comedy Club at MGM Grand https://t.co/NkXcnKFtaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thing when I reactivated my #Tidal account 👀 #CRWN https://t.co/2KsIqmfKkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insane that Bohemian Rhapsody won sound editing over a Quiet Place bc without sound quiet place wouldn't happen???? #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Inspiration - Humbleness   https://t.co/TcZMBbwTHi @ Enterprise, Nevada https://t.co/ZOmVjzHpAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say “remember Glasgow” as a way to tell them to calm down about working all the time. Here I am, imagining conveeswrionsntobgoo far]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was tagged by @VKHardy to share a favorite book for 7 days, adding a friend each day. I've chosen books that I co… https://t.co/S0RnTePzll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living my best life 😘😍  #MarianasTrench #FirstRow https://t.co/F50QP6YNf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmoe371 @AmackerHDHR @Acworth0156 @TTChapman13 @ChrisBergHD @CoreyL81894800 The stars come out at night, Awesome job Kyle!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I h8 this bitch Maddie and like she just ruined my night again @kmonayyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FastNLoudTV Definitely wishing them both the best... divorce is hard enough for us regular folks. So can’t imagine… https://t.co/ObmNFjjfTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meg_deck Remind me when the season is done and then I’ll do the free trial and binge it lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not having a good morning! My anxiety is through the roof! My back is killing me! I feel as if the walls are closin… https://t.co/hOe8sXLYbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will literally NEVER be able to increase or decrease your value to the universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ash_wednesdayyy  10 Things Only Daughters Of A Football Coach Will Understand via @twitter https://t.co/PrF55FJXHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found voice mails you left me and in glad/needed to hear your voice again 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraB16901827 Good morning Sandra. Thank you and love the picture. I believe the one on the left is Venice, Ital… https://t.co/byIYpflJWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plainview32 @FOX2News I'm not defending or condemning  anyone. Did you watch the story? It's informative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug Ford, the 1st premier in Ontario's history to threaten to use the notwithstanding clause to cut Toronto's city… https://t.co/XujhKyrJiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what she does, Glenn Close will forever be known for Cruela de Vil. #TheOscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regina King!!!! Love the movie, love her, love that she won, love love love!! ❤️ #Oscars @ReginaKing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Perhaps Jussie should have considered his actions b4 trying the victim role.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy does time go by way too fast wish it would just slow down for once!! ⏰😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do you politely tell someone you don’t want to give them your number???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThunderT16 @JeffVeillette If someone says "Fuck off. You should fucking die. I'll stokp you." Or something similar… https://t.co/dam945TNnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NastyGirlsVote2 @DWStweets She backed out because of threats.  In July 2016. I think someone needs to ask Cohen about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such deliciousness... @ca_delbaio @StemWineGroup https://t.co/JFx5cGo38Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misfit9999 @RealMAGASteve How did we let this happen? They're taking our country away by using our laws and Consti… https://t.co/k1ehxjAJHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilanandCo Tbh I expect it at this point. And they’ll swear it’s ados causing the divide. The division was already there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would think it’s so easy to let someone go or stop talking to them but it’s not 💀💀currently missing someone bad rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Communista2 Same back. I have lost my mind for next month. Will be bumbling about during this time 🌷❤️🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitzen in einem Yellow Cab. Aus den Radio-Lautsprechern erklingen sanfte Jazz-Klänge von Cole Porter  untermalt von… https://t.co/RG302e5Xbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m giving up soda starting now , so.. if y’all hear me craving or reaching for soda it’s ok to yell at me or some 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @mslowpaz to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. In honor of Youth Art Mon… https://t.co/kqXY6FyQSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like the AAF teams would be better is they had better names. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Browns cut starting strongside linebacker Jamie Collins https://t.co/5FBqTqFHgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loot boxes are gambling.  Just like slot machines and scratch tickets. I used to make graphics for pull tab games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in science, facts, and equality. I believe in building bridges, not walls. I believe a government's purpo… https://t.co/bKpYFJNoxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[A piece of #sky #lowellma #myview #houses #driveway #morningview #latergram #massachusettsphotographer… https://t.co/jd1oE2KZxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are my text messages not going through? I’ve been left without a response by two different ppl so like what is real… https://t.co/4XGlClgUiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eathbound420 @TeahCartel @HeathFloof @ElleWibble @GOVTWINE @bunnykittenpupp @CunningSq16 @DetroitLove88… https://t.co/SrNL3tvB4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I came to your page to read your tweets and was highly offended you didn’t follow me. Turns out I ca… https://t.co/nyJ7h8IsVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ginger ale is truly medicinal.... and a lifesaver. Cured my carsickness.  I still lost service for 52 minutes though 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look terrible😫 but thanks for the picture❤️ guess I’ll have to come to another show so we can have a pic retake 🤪… https://t.co/f1SEUASIj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacieDufrane @realDonaldTrump @Daddy_Mike Go and do what you do best This... https://t.co/hUclP50vyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iraentis Thank you. You did awesome challenging ideas and opening minds! #AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@iMovers are the lyrics for “So Glad You’re Here” available online anywhere or do I need the physical copy of the… https://t.co/nIRxNaVFjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano #SorryNotSorry Reality Winner needs your help. This young patriot warned us about a threat to our vo… https://t.co/4JrKuVhSw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJoelSchwartz I thought you'd dig this. Whenever we talk shop, I get the impression that you know this well. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of @The_BMC @BUMedicine @BMCSurgery getting out the red and blue carpet for @WiscSurgery Grasberger Professors;… https://t.co/f26tHhB7sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came to see @InquiringJoy and @WhovianFeminism talking about how to rock a convention panel in terms of being res… https://t.co/kGQ4t10kLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOLLLLL my roomate literally has an app that she uses for pics of her and her bf to photoshop a smile on his face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_MichaelT Well.... we all know you have a fetish for the red heads so there is only one explanation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a sad day.. R.I.P. Ted Lindsay 😢#TedLindsay https://t.co/eqzOdAqqM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#acomerseadicho🐷 en Famous Dave's Bar-B-Que of America https://t.co/mdoUx4mfhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my valentine a little extra today❤️@dawson_brooks7 https://t.co/pYHQiOUdK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren @NRA @GOP Russia is funding the NRA! Shout it from the rooftops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[World leaders' response to Pence's greeting from Trump was not the news. The earful he gave them about NATO was gre… https://t.co/BT10M5rfmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[ELECTION-INTEGRITY ADVOCATE ON TWITTER.   Jenny has fought TIRELESSLY to bring this EXCRUCIATINGLY CRITICAL SUBJECT… https://t.co/OPD1YBD4Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cenk, let's put Roger Stone's book sales in prospective. Stone owns 95 out of the 97 sold. #TYTLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@father_rmv Namely from Galatians 1:8. That tells it all. The Catholic Church in Salt Lake City has this in large letters in the sanctuary!]]></document><document><![CDATA[for something to match it and  bought that other thing but now, I don't like it. I'm looking for some chairs that I… https://t.co/kTPszG5Vwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer     Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gift… https://t.co/IXLKmSUqs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to #workingmoms positively impacting their babes futures - sons and daughters #thereisproof #dropthemomguilt]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY SUNDAY! #jadedbodybutter  #healthyskinisin  #estyshop  #ebayshop  #linkinbio📲💻  🐰🌱❤ @ Jaded Body Butter https://t.co/1zSvkmYHe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trngchief11 @PressSec @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Well whatever he's doing,  our country is thriving]]></document><document><![CDATA[#foodprep this week: taco bowls! 🌮 @ Los Gatos, California https://t.co/xw6HdWUoIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favourite salads from @aromaespresso is the Sweet Potato Salad. This is not paid ad. I’m just sharing my… https://t.co/GdYrxvX0bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd night in a row the frogs are singing loudly in the Everglades. They do this a couple of times a year.  They sou… https://t.co/XK10O02NWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RADWomenCode @bethbrains @lmangano @ztugcesirin @codefriar @tami_ell @surfahjoe @Swati_Taunk @krithikaiyer… https://t.co/1LvP7phpIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating our writing piece with a friend. @HicksTigers #wearehickselem https://t.co/5rwXwQpFlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bueller, Bueller..... has anyone tried this stuff?  I’m have read the reviews and there are some really good ones b… https://t.co/RT0jXP3T0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man just violently banged on my window that I thought I was going to get murdered so I got up and stood there lik… https://t.co/vB8ZBRdrxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll create the vibe, you just hop on and ride the wave 🌊 with me. You down? 💨🍃]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally the best thing ever.  Dogs know.  Animals know.  @AOC @RepAOC #AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missbabbeezy @ladygaga I feel attacked. 😂😭 I ♥️ @ladygaga though. She deserves every accolade she receives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never ask a clock (birthday, new year, wedding) to do what YOU are supposed to do.....make a decision to change! @BishopJakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MortalManRaised @bevandeveire What @MortalManRaised ?? Okay ummmmmm wow 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Flashpoint by @house6brewing at @house6brewing — https://t.co/iea92zse31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the night with my valentine, the Saturn V rocket 😍🚀 https://t.co/abODOfVCXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HB1638 #antivax #washingtonstate #evidencebased https://t.co/kdRSziIgng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Principal_EL @stsanchez6739 @Simpsonart78 @JarushaG @mradamwelcome I always get some kind of collateral... a shoe.… https://t.co/7SvQDFIaUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABHcosmetics Dipbrow “Chocolate”  @juviasplace The Festival By Juvia’s #abh Eyeshadow “Noir”  @MACcosmetics Glitte… https://t.co/bEcxDcpkaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @POTUS, I think my cousin beat you to it on your wall thing. https://t.co/xU6bge49UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roxanna told me to get off my phone and I said “hold up let me send this meme” 🤦🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Solange, I wonder if Unity National Bank is accepting new clients #WhenIGetHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your friends are all imaginary, your shrink stopped answering the phone So you decide to make incisions at your hom… https://t.co/1DudQcFaI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arwmd - was just reminded that you’ve been advancing what I’m just waking up to for a long time. Thank you for you… https://t.co/APxbvQtsLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasonGross @WBGO @JazzOn2 @artpridenj @NJArtsCouncil @jerseyarts @RutgersNB @rutgersalumni @RutgersU @RutgersU_News Congratulations!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I saw was engagement. Republiscum like Graham and, McConnell would have dismissed those kids.  At least she en… https://t.co/np3TsSdTvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos los caminos conducen a Roma @estudioparrotta pablofedericozarate en Caesars Palace https://t.co/vGFpZMuZVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeRock401 @artiequitter Ahhh you should subscribe so you can see me on the mornin show lol. Kidding just listen to… https://t.co/Asw0ArTQh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MapleLeafs Marner is public relations sweetheart! He is all heart ❤️ #makemydayMitch #GoLeafsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteelCity_Burg @DetSRBenton She's adorable. How she solves things so easily and her tactics impress me every singl… https://t.co/b89RBfFU4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats want to take another look at the T-Mobile-Sprint merger https://t.co/KwxHa8vbsF via @engadget]]></document><document><![CDATA[COHEN SUPPOSE TO BE IN JAIL TODAY? NOPE HE IS STILL LYING TO THE CONGRESS.....]]></document></documents></author>