<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t ever hesitate to check on someone. If you think you need to check on someone, there’s a good chance something… https://t.co/w2x4CXHVVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to the potential ID picture with this makeup... the DMV line was tooooo long. So I’ll share with Twitter lol https://t.co/EZccK7H9Us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dial this number 901 208 2427 get shopping job watch he send you fake check come find out he my color and them rode… https://t.co/qnchiUDclC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill @AlaniNutrition @HaydnSchneider @katyhearnFit It’s doesn’t interfere with BC either. Helps with skin is… https://t.co/ZlvhSKvPSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A stand for my birth country ~ Venezuela in the dark for almost 24 hours-the entire country! Massive infrastructure… https://t.co/vs8tsQVZzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristiNorthcutt Happy Birthday to you! 40 will be fantastic. Cant believe you and the Royals are the same age, you… https://t.co/lfh3Nktk37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the Green Book!!! Way to go @basteen!  Love those little learners and feel confident they were totally engaged… https://t.co/LJobFgUrC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t refuse cash. Poor and elderly often do not use cashless systems. This is simple discrimination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on to your butts.. @ Murrells Inlet, South Carolina https://t.co/D39u5WoDNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/X8A9FiKXAp: Disability org: Ban e-scooter parking blocking sidewalks. https://t.co/XJj8NFdBBe  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jared Polis, @GovofCO, talked about his hopes for all-day kindergarten funding with @RochelleGalindo at Jackson Ele… https://t.co/NWzTnWH16Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManifestRoom If you want women viewers, Zeke better be coming back. You know, like Daryl from TWD. or Sawyer from… https://t.co/enOF3jXQxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 AB not sure that “you don’t know what you had till it’s gone”- I salute your amazing God gifted talent- loved… https://t.co/xfJ0YxyWb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fluffysharp @iamlisako @esmewang @mcnallyjackson Oh no!! The one weekend I’m out of town! I’m sure it’ll be a blas… https://t.co/3EB9Z31K8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fwDstarr I don’t think my soul can rewatch the red wedding episode. Too many deaths 😭🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitie_ts13 @taylornation13 My Ellie is sad that she hasn’t got a @taylornation13 hi either. Ellie’s unite! ♥️ https://t.co/BpGqNFTX91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I believe you . Those who mock you will answer to  God.  He put you in office. They  are directly… https://t.co/OVon2HAALe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceoaetnews @jcezzz @AOC No they aren't. We had people from Seattle come to NYC telling horror stories about housin… https://t.co/FGDwrzZfZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over and over again, Twitter is telling us to listen more. Will we listen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 5 deferments @realDonaldTrump is going to Vietnam. I wonder if his feet will hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teachers! Tired of losing resources in the Google Classroom stream?! @GoogleForEdu soon to offer “Move to Top” opti… https://t.co/p268bOxErb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw the light I've been baptized By the fire in your touch And the flame in your eyes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCM_Angel @innerpeeroption Thank you for helping us understand. And I hope you stay with us to continue to educate us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsInHeaven09 True. But I almost dislike Junior even more then his daddy. Such a privileged little snot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so I originally wanted $7 billion.  I could not get my way, so the congress gave me $2 billion ; and then I t… https://t.co/ZV8yenplUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Because they have not completed the investigation, what part of SO FAR don't you grasp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I thought Glenn Close was the shoo in. Enjoyed Olivia Colman’s speech. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having a really shitty night and the last thing I want is my husband with his “friends” 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIGHER FURTHER FASTER #CaptainMarvel #bestMarvelmovieEVER #yeahisaidit #bewareFlerkens #loveGoose @ AMC Starplex Co… https://t.co/lbYHG0pil6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Yourself they Say. 🌻  Repair. Restore. Recover. Receive.  #Monster https://t.co/3atKHsQlkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump Pray for God to forgive him for all the sins he's committed. Abortion is not the only… https://t.co/J6rla2heoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rAlYnCqBTN. https://t.co/ZJmxegPuKL.     Share the memories and celebrate the brothers and sisters on the thin blue line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im supposed to be finishing my 1st draft of my essay but fuck idk what else to put😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arthur_affect @GirishDuvvuri @clarabellum I don’t agree with this. I’m a big fan of Dan Savage, who is able to spe… https://t.co/uxpVSlLkP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wanna believe Caelynn’s side of the story, but then I don’t know what to believe. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff ...&amp;...lol.. back to Nat Gio. Bloods &amp; Crips 80's LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The queen city’s very own local pap. 👏🏼 I’ll be around town too, let’s do an interview!! Message me :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VioletSinclair7 @taekeller I love how scientific thinking is woven into this story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaMarieCoon @SeanieQuigley7 @JenniferMlott @miragoto @julieludgateuk @AmyJoan97 @KikeAdennowo @ItsNikkiAmbers… https://t.co/4gfYry5I0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt y tho? ✨🌟✨ @ Renaissance Chicago Downtown Hotel https://t.co/IbfIMAsBW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[DT: most likely I will not have access to WIFI tomorrow in 🇧🇸. I will be on the island 🌴 all day. Have a great 👍 time in Miami.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_francheeese Ughhhh bes nakakadepress talagaaaa as iiiiiiiiin at this point idek what I don’t know 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJopinion This is just my opinion for what it's worth. Let the man finish out his term, if he gets r… https://t.co/6lkLeWcQt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubleboobo You are right there. And I’ve been preaching that since the beginning. Yet a lot of the fans have this… https://t.co/mZMgSWq14X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching An Affair to Remember bc I hate myself apparently https://t.co/TKSiNNkmqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[“AP Advocacy Day” Promoting professional learning opportunities for AP teachers and college experiences for our hig… https://t.co/KSWxzHpYyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malekalby @VictoriaD6363 @marinavibu609g @PatGrant7777 @AAvallones @EliLeonarda @FabDark2 @Carlosxl7life… https://t.co/F3nFywPJlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to @MarieKondo our home and so far the hardest part has been my movies. I know they’re all on  Netflix/Hulu/… https://t.co/vuB9DT9VZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen inspired plenty of Bea Arthur appreciation and a royal twist  https://t.co/ag2uyRq28O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third game of the week tonight at the AAC. Puck drop at 7pm! #Gameday #LetsGoStars ⭐️💚 https://t.co/A4b0ZeWsI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my @BECCAcosmetics #KhloeAndMalika lipstick 💄 in #CupidsKiss 💋 @khloekardashian @ForeverMalika can’t wait to tr… https://t.co/sHlUGDMPYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulaannev @ahmedhankir My mom and I are close, really close, but I felt connected to my dad in a way but we didnt meet until I 19.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top EOQ performers getting a special slime party! Rewarding excellence @Unioncrosselem!  @WSFCS_Science… https://t.co/kllWO8EXRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevor_diedrich @MooreBrett Thanks Trevor!! I will be heading your way every month leading up to the game. Hope to catch up soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterDriesenga @SteelDad @gerrydulac What did Gerry say? He blocked me]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Jacobson, son of Gerald Jacobson, says he can’t believe his day shot wife and eldest son. They’re both in the… https://t.co/khACGaP699]]></document><document><![CDATA[plz don’t let your giant dog with snow-covered paws jump on me and then not apologize!!! not even a sheepish glance… https://t.co/izh82rQ7D2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inslee is impressive and positive. Dems may have a huge field but all of them are such an improvement of Trump that… https://t.co/9RGJ6256xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosemoczulski1 @sharon_schwan @sannbs @72cricket @CSonafelt @MrsSpuds @RidenerTina @BxglL @ACog1984 YES! A late PP goal by Bjugstad! 🚨🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think it’s funny when couples have been dating for years when all they do is cheat on each other or just constantly break up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just_someNobody @devincomiskey @DeFede @CBSMiami @Patriots But it isn't legal, so he got caught in the web. #tRump… https://t.co/ycONT5I5pJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[:) The quote with the image is the best. #humor #snicker #grin #laughable https://t.co/AZlcTiPLqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentuckyTourism   As much as I ADORED Top Chef Kentucky, why did they not have the finale in KENTUCKY?!?!?!? #kentuckyproud @BravoTopChef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPistone @amsupdates Thrilled with my driver going to victory lane. Was a bit better racing, but still too soon to really be sure....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVivlamoreAJC No!! Meanwhile Harden pushes off and travels all the time. That’s why the NBA has lost my season tic… https://t.co/730tZyIhcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES. Regina King thanking James Baldwin and her mama and Go-Moses got me 😭👏🏽 #IfBealeStreetCouldTalk won an #OSCAR… https://t.co/G1qbdKXRcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MaryamMonsef you are doing outstanding work for Women &amp; Girls in #Canada 🇨🇦 and we’re thrilled… https://t.co/nvvdTqGY6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockchester11 I was wondering that when they cruised by and now that I look closer it may actually be. Ummm… https://t.co/z45iis8z8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samueloseiB ft @_yaajackson   Imma play this #Pslam100- 100 times.. Congratulations guys..nice tune..🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @RadInstitute for inviting me to moderate the #BeyondWords panel on social robots with @cynthiabreazeal from… https://t.co/SshDJymV5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work is (wait for it) for the birds!! Feat. photobomb by youngest 💖 #friday #OotD #birddress… https://t.co/zQjtdl9Brz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendentshering @SirPareshRawal And yes. Journalists at ur end are the funniest... we have been laughing our heads… https://t.co/Qn1VIaHj7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a crash on E 25th St at N Mitthoeffer Rd on the east side @rtv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realGpad @bostonmarathon Omg Gen! This scenery is GORGEOUS!! I’m so excited for you :) keep it going!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBloods_CBS Great acting tonight! I love that this show is not a shoot out every episode. It provides a glimpse… https://t.co/rjQajL4tpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @JussieSmollett @CNN @MSNBC @NBCNews @CBCNews @ABC @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @TheAcademy I saw this and IM… https://t.co/89OAVIGWC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Tork of the Monkees died.  He’s the only celebrity I ever wrote an adolescent love letter to.  #ripPeterTork]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn't @Jim_Jordan being investigated?  @CBSNews  @NBCNews  @ABC  @CNN  @MSNBC  @NatashaBertrand  @AshaRangappa_… https://t.co/d388jowx0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMooreLPM I’ve seen severallll people lay hands on one couple while so many others stood alone. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Dershowitz on Mueller Report: "In The End, Everything's Going To Come Out"  -  - By  https://t.co/AAbCxdUmKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenziegeyer21 another big h19bd to one of the sweetest people i’ve ever come across, love u more than you know 💙 https://t.co/lx08Kbi9pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BootstrapCook That’s me. The best precaution is a good, supportive, comfortable set of shoes. And it’s not a race. Take it as you can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan Some people will continue to follow Trump’s lead and try to turn our world upside down, then claim we’… https://t.co/1KnAGcEze9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Thanks for all you do for our country! You were a fantastic president and our country needs you now more than ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone know what these balloons mean? they were placed all over Topanga Canyon, in area where there appeared to hav… https://t.co/nB9hP4zsr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[after many years of internal infighting, I've finally given in and bought nicotine vape juice and a refillable cart… https://t.co/lhwW8bVfKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @PirtleStacey for being so sweet to my baby Cori and my big girl Charlotte too! Too cute...😍😍 Both of my gir… https://t.co/Ezjfcg1di7]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Name For New Pensacola Bay Bridge On Hold For Now https://t.co/UStOaHGOgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pure class! @duranduran #duranduran #duranlive #duranvegas https://t.co/yCovvgkeMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY https://t.co/ipFD1Rvqf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[also; I know my eyebrows look like poop. they need to be waxed and trimmed but nobody got time for that 🤷🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you please explain to me how when where the annihilation of the earth will start so we can possibly reversed it… https://t.co/hJpMYTkqNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[the moment the @jonasbrothers drop new music 🎶🤗🎶 #sucker https://t.co/HbSMz5yrgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barquisimeto 🇻🇪 edo Lara  Barquisimetanos desesperados por falta de agua se bañan en un arroyo por el puente las D… https://t.co/ehTlReXPSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article by @jeremyduda in #AZMirror on #DayOfEmpathy. @Arouetforgood was proud to sponsor. Gr8 job @mcirocco… https://t.co/QuvArUA67g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Kind if like the Californians.  You representatives in that state seem to be living the high life, ho… https://t.co/ElD66H1Cm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcpr And we thought The Omen was a trilogy... https://t.co/VKAdsJ4Tbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WakeUpAmerica #WeThePeople are better than this phony hate trying to divide us for politics and WE ARE WAKE… https://t.co/KKsLs96ukd]]></document><document><![CDATA[VOTE PLEASE...EVERY DAY...FOR BACK TO THE PAST!!!!  https://t.co/TCNoq94dnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a reckless person would take such action managing a family budget. You don't give away $$ rather than try to d… https://t.co/9P7ErB1889]]></document></documents></author>