<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LibertyJen That's all I've ever found, my daughter is now 15. I just add a cute sweater!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When drafting your PR plan make sure your objectives are -S = Specific M = Measurable A = Attainable or achievable… https://t.co/Raqm7KAHn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[daily amazed by the notion that the purest, most joyful and loving old soul is my husband.]]></document><document><![CDATA[? Venezuelans must take their country back from the dictator, not run away &amp; leave him in power!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Amber happy makes my mom heart happy (jealous ) but she seems to be loving Paris]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just opened my own Netflix account so I could stop using my dad's. Does that make me a real adult now? 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a @Whataburger where you are?? You need to visit and do a photoshoot in front 😝🧡💃🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Secret Squires @khscd &amp; Dachsunds!! @MsBrown1138 #KhscdAnd https://t.co/X97LJDn9ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelbb_ @Angela_Smith11 Omg Shelby this is ICONIC how have I not seen this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Thank you.    Trump you are a womanizing SOB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's move from California they say.  It's safer they say... Welp here we are. My street never was infested like th… https://t.co/8Ims323MeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn't a threat against a sitting United States Representative be investigated by the FBI? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chmurph @BrennanLM @page2frame Honestly I think about Murph being called out like this like daily 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are back 💝  #oooothisisanSOSalwaysastrugglesesh #sandwichesandsandybichs @ Struggle Bus https://t.co/DlLAKlHwm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[...... and I just realized I left my car in a 2hr parking spot, since 8am fuuuuuuuuu lol 😂 I can’t wait to get home… https://t.co/6Wi06oFzQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 months into a long distance relationship and I finally invested in packing cubes https://t.co/ozo397kYDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is your life! Yes, the stakes are high! Don’t settle for peace and mediocrity live your life full of love, bli… https://t.co/uEU4clgVeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRockbeats  https://t.co/mXp4M75vOk #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   🚀#RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope… https://t.co/GvMXvnQ2y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Tuesday which means it’s finally time for our special edition of Sex And the City trivia! Starts at 8pm sharp… https://t.co/LqjI2FtIp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Target Shopping at your Lafayette store has become a huge exercise in frustration. I just gave up today after only… https://t.co/uebXW7YP6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your #TeamworksFamily comes to town...  Good to see you @LydiaPeytonTW @momash09 @larrylongjr and @LukeBarthel… https://t.co/fArb98WXs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love me some  @DevinBook thank u for always being so nice!! @ Talking Stick Resort Arena https://t.co/8Mjx8jkxwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told my sis my boo name now she keep saying “don’t make me get Adam” to everything lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend just told me to leave and not to live w her...oh.. is like dat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexa_Merica @AllenPlake @az_sheri @Envision69 @dwbeattie @1TruCon @Crusher20152 @joearce7 @immatweeting… https://t.co/2z0YDDUegD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Absolutely, 100%, Completely, Obsessed with @OneDayAtATime @JustinaMachado is EVERYTHING! #RitaMoreno is EVERYTHING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @mercenarygraphi My guess is that he would emphatically and automatically deny everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SputzieBird @cindymccain @michellemalkin @SenJohnMcCain Not all CPAC people are alike. Just like not all left liberals are alike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes you think he will keep his promise when not one of their leaders (who actually signed an agreement) has… https://t.co/ab7F7eY5lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mowoodier @sky_mutt Dang... I don't remember druids. How about the Knights who say Nih? Want some shrubbery?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMeadows you owe the people of North Carolina an apology as well.  And shame on you for using your friendship w… https://t.co/tFIqHhJUZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armyeidyn We should teach him a lesson! Leaving us waiting like this. https://t.co/pivtk3e06c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyhunnybunny Right??  Judges went wacky there at the end. Plus our vault@scores were really low. Except@for the boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finolahughes @miamirelatives @valentinifrank @GeneralHospital @thejonlindstrom @MauriceBenard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melody unsuccessfully ran away from the mosh pit... I’m forever bruised🙃🙂☠️ #wallofdeath]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or we can just tweet out every single day that @realDonaldTrump’s tweet is a lie. Don’t retweet him ever. Every twe… https://t.co/JxYtUKdquA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be healthy and go to the gym everyday, but I have no motivation.....and I love junk food😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[me at the dr: how do i stop losing weight please  my dr: take these prescription vitamins and go to a new dr that c… https://t.co/YkkU8gz2PG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish it was warmer but at least the sun will be out for my bday weekend 👸🏽 🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @DemFromCT It isn't uniquely the Freedom Caucus that has unwavering support for Trump. It's the whole damned party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix If you think I won’t be watching all 8 seasons over the next 8 days, you’re wrong https://t.co/aQdwCngLyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get enough exercise just pushing my luck! - vintage retro funny quote https://t.co/5tMP89WlZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManilanH The Jewish friends I know are very reticent to speak out on on this because they rapidly get accused of a… https://t.co/unCusvhofM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS This soap is getting on my nerves. There is no intrigue anymore. Like really this girl figured it all ou… https://t.co/tIejsOx1PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best walls in the midwest in @CedarFalls in @Travel_Iowa. #ThisIsIowa https://t.co/JW6fRcWn0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLydecia @Rich_Holmes22 @drrichardd @Dreisrelentless @brich44 Love you guys! Hope you make it back here before th… https://t.co/i011gpl1A6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great WEBOP Latin Jazz work by Goussy Celestin.  Nice work! Sorry shows r sold out tomorrow! @ Jazz at Lincoln Cent… https://t.co/mRhdNtDCOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @LindseyGrahamSC When John McCain died, Lindsey Graham did a 360 and became a lap dog for Trump. H… https://t.co/pCqKpEucju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCMSZephyrs Just do not be late for bus duty 😆 totally guilty, maybe once.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just came across this and I am totally digging it!! Give a listen and let me know what you think. @tolka_h… https://t.co/P25wIJhzPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[‍ Altar Girl Lesbian Night Chapel https://t.co/GJ8WGDWPyt https://t.co/E4Ib7YaHn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjblain10 Anything is possible, but You are assuming a lot based on a narrative spinning in the news. Have you talked to the DNC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate Passes a Sweeping Land Conservation Bill https://t.co/uH5TxHtNWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went all out for my baby’s Valentines gift 🥰 he’s so lucky to have someone creative like me 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodOfShuffles so irritating, i wanna fight 😒 i hate when people pull that bullshit, esp on my baby daddy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can tell this is going to be a dope series. Y’all should go watch this! Also Happy Birthday Khalil!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m mad at the Erin from six months ago who scheduled a dentist cleaning first thing on the Monday morning after… https://t.co/1LNGSAybFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to dope women! #happyinternationalwomensday   Also check out this WOC owned business teeowels ♥️ @ New York,… https://t.co/DzGmFzUMrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPosnanski 1/3 of the money in Washington was going to be deferred, which i think was why that wasn’t the answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought I’d quickly share before I try to ready myself and unroll. The nausea is already starting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please go to this link and sign the petition the stop the trophy Hunters from killing the polar bears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Also in Australia. LOL It seems like a very beautiful and aggressive place. https://t.co/OR7qEFiHJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacquicollins_ Because you’ve got the moves like Jagger? That’s a compliment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smith_51 So you're an official foodie?  I've checked out some on pinterest, especially the blackberry cobbler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m getting older because I’d rather listen to classic hits then this so called newer music 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is Monday and I’m actually excited to go to work. I enjoy my job also I have new Kurig kcups to use… https://t.co/fN9SixzC59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well all they needed where Rakes??? Just as Puerto Rico needed PaperTowels. FEMA-Disasters after Disaster. https://t.co/bAtCqTu3yp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you sir are a revolting douchebag and an epic imbecile to boot.  #45 #NotMyPresident]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that NJIT now has a bachelors degree program in Forensic Science the first in NJ. How cool is that… https://t.co/ow9pah2PxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp and cold this morning.  #adoptdontshop #babblingbrook #aussiemix #adopteddogsofinstagram #forest… https://t.co/Z0wOtPjWfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a new addition to the family today.  Maggie named him Rambo after I suggested a couple of names.  She's always… https://t.co/eGTvfdOOCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beadragonne @lovenlivedotcom @GrahamAllen_1 @AOC Head over to @DuckDuckGo and search democrats wanted money to pay… https://t.co/J1ZNjobe6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read the campsites “things you need to know” section and because this camp site is secluded, bears (along with… https://t.co/xzQPcNM0Dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsClub must know how much I love anything to do with cats. LOL. 😹 https://t.co/2SzEQhXcFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous #themysteryofedwindrood opening weekend and such a lovely party. Thank you @ctreptheatre ❤️ . 👉🏻#Repost… https://t.co/A9wKLc37OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[166 PHOTOS: LA Fall Soccer 2019 - Week 1 #VglSocal https://t.co/9VoljomtCi https://t.co/yiv6G53Lhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are not a real president since you put yourself before the country you jerk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A helicopter in Kenya has crashed killing four Americans and a local pilot  https://t.co/hqUNoAkEH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Yes but will 20 Rethuglicans vote him out right now? Answer = #ComplicitGOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-Captain Marvel nosh &amp; drinkies! (@ My Friend Duke in New York, NY) https://t.co/R7Lg2eyJbd https://t.co/0aTLbWWBRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready in a few hours to check In to see my fav best doctor Doctor Conrad Hawkins #MattCzuchry I’m always on… https://t.co/LaJL2fxRng]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a mini vacation to Vegas or Cali cause everybody been getting on my nerves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pweiser The first territorial legislature of the Wyoming Territory granted women suffrage in 1869. On Sept 6, 1870… https://t.co/5Z6EcKzXPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your right. It is laughable if it weren't so pathetic.🙄What I want to know is where is dt going to get the money fr… https://t.co/h2Ldj4Arv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the #CampFire multiple law enforcement agencies reached out to offer support to the Paradise police departmen… https://t.co/iHkR7ZBRw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #TBT is from 2000 with pinkdragonchick during my #BillyIdol blonde phase . #happyvalentinesday to you.  Thanks f… https://t.co/HND5mBwptw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrystrauss @SimonBooks Et cum iter cum Boudicca🔥 puto librum tuum valde bona est.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She tried to kill herself from all the hateful comments fuck all of you. Go to hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Cassidy44 @coooouurttnneyy @sarah_y_12 Good Luck in ft Collins  this W/E Thu vs @IdahoStateSB  Fri vs… https://t.co/wWESZyhwEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear....a corporate uniform for men only. I own a really comfy puffy vest and would love to wear it, but… https://t.co/AiTiq1SLcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[bought a $15 cup from Starbucks today and it didn’t even come with free coffee at least!!!! Sheeeesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look out! Captain Nayely has taken up axe throwing!! @mclaneathletics @mclanehigh https://t.co/zsKcFBTZsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paging my Indy writer, director, producer friends: What pays your bills? (Because very few of us have the opportuni… https://t.co/LDNPTNWHdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights behind the storm #grandcanyon #nps #findyourpark #arizona #storm #clouds #usa #forumusaontheroad @ Yavapai P… https://t.co/F3YT1RzBoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siredtolightwds @OUaTPreachers This makes me want to fight even harder #Shadowhunters #ShadowhuntersChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KChenoweth Never fails...I decide to order some egg breakfast at a diner, and the table next to me is served salmo… https://t.co/rnD4hwXIrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracking_ontrek @zoesaldana @ZacharyQuinto @TrekCore We love you, two together. Stay together forever... ❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 minutes after #SVU ended &amp; I’m still not emotionally over the fact that Potato won’t ever see his dad again!… https://t.co/7Sp9ephKMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nyc see you mañana...  #Repost @OPENMICRENEGADE with get_repost ・・・ Open Mic Renegades Presents:  Conscious Minds… https://t.co/vFolhDIepn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpursOfficial Watching from St. Louis, Missouri.  Watching with orange chicken.  3-1 Spurs.]]></document></documents></author>