<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@heckyessica I'll give her a pass. If I was Obama's kid I'd have started drinking at 6 years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Gitney CEO Group 50 presenting  blockchain strategies to the Riverside Estate Planning Council monthly networki… https://t.co/FzEGghue16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__nocti__ @pog6ah @Twitch @dizzfila Same here!  She was my first pick when the game came out. Didn't even know eve… https://t.co/M8ZSAUfkda]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t take normal photos so here are some ridiculous picture of me after I gave myself a second #haircut from hom… https://t.co/BtpKk6ugla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Now Admits He Actually Did Call Tim Cook 'Tim Apple'  #WorstPresidentinHistory #WorstPresidentinHistory… https://t.co/ImjWcnBgnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jcpc80 @bbcmundo Sera que la justicia reconoce aquí que hubo error y en otros lugares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyJoeGPT @jimsciutto North Carolina should have been your first clue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/1sK6g7VE61]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCUSE ME...MIKEY SAID IT WAS..."WE THE PEOPLE " believe him OVER YOUR LYING DUMBASS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[US News &amp; World Report: At Least 2 Dead as Storms, Possible Tornados Hit Deep South. https://t.co/3hmEWTlo0c  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[What cards make up your #MTGDNA   What was the- -first card you remember being excited about opening? -first card y… https://t.co/rYvsYvOuTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not interested in cops refusing to make arrests because they think a law is unconstitutional. That’s why we hav… https://t.co/HXeoEA96Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Windsor Terrace, Brooklyn https://t.co/VadPxyFK3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mojaveb @Bayer Look at that packaging! Is the expiration date from the 1970s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hairmetalhenry No way that would’ve been a goal with Ekholm back there either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE NOT JUST A GYM!! WE HELP YOU WIN YOUR DAY OUTSIDE THE GYM EVERY DAY!!… https://t.co/rya1Ds87hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid seems like a very bright writer!  Although I'm not into prophecy, much, at least not anymore, really, I've… https://t.co/6CrJ3mlIq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @RepAdamSchiff Game on?? HAHAHA!!  Just keep deleting your incriminating tweets ahead of next week Sea… https://t.co/cnRCx06opI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone have a bunch of ps4 MT ? ... I'm in the process of buying some and need to up my sellers bid, if you can help me out lmk thanks guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malden Half Marathon and 5 Miller. #happysoles #firsttothebeer #sportthefort (@ Malden Square in Malden, MA)… https://t.co/UdXPZdBZDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfmta_muni Yep. It looks like nobody at @sfmta_muni knew enough about the Muni Metro system to know the J doesn't… https://t.co/JLOE7kym4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[.... I’m here to announce today, that obviously it’s ok to kill black ppl minding their own business as long as you… https://t.co/rTPgAzROAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@contra__culture @DrewCHallett @RailYardSports Such a nice guy making fun of rape victims. https://t.co/0bRHC9GF2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Never a truer Trumplican https://t.co/2YutWfAoCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN @RJC @AIPAC Here is what I think, #GOPALESTINE, I’m proud to be pro Palestine, not pro Israel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G2_Sua @canasianGirI @Meggodile @MsPinkZebra @jessica_r6s @Goddess_R6 Hellll yeaaaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaylaAlisha11 @ILMFOrg She's as hypocritical as it gets. What a slime ball she is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRaider2055 @GipsySafety nope. zone is a staple oh the west coast offense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbj4goat @micheal_hester @ArrogantDak https://t.co/G4u1Oq2MaE hopefully that'll get you to stfu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both #jbjsoulkitchen locations are OPEN Today Wednesday TR 11:30-3 , RB Dinner 5 - 7 https://t.co/bHbaRfxDEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is probably the only time I will ever use ALL MY LETTERS on a single play in a game of Scrabble! And I totally… https://t.co/2mzurmLzz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eCB0IoIzeS REVIEW. The complexities and challenges of preventing and treating non-#tuberculous… https://t.co/Zw2eQmUS9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a human, trying to get to me on the phone, from an unknown number, leave a message. So many robo-calls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reds have 11 hits in the first 3 innings. That’ll work all day, every day! #RedsST 🌵⚾️ https://t.co/Vt5jPB7Xqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout, SPASH trail 25-22 to Merrill with 1:41 in the 1st quarters #wisbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having ALL the feels watching the @PuertoRicoOpen... played the International Course the day after my wedding and t… https://t.co/Wxf3zhaljA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just unlocked the History Curator Badge on HQ Trivia! Use code "Migs310" to sign up https://t.co/TTv6H5FFEC https://t.co/lwxYW5uj0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are 2 hot takes:   - I liked Green Book  - Hope they go hostless again next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akosiKenChan @mainedcm both looking good 💕😔 sana kyo na lng kesa dun sa isa, im sure ADN will agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendyytee If the boots are leather definitely the boots. Good boots last a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since #FireTuckerCarlson will probably fizzle, I have another suggestion: #MakeTuckerCarlsonFurrowHisBrowUntilHisHeadExplodes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbradley311 Happy Birthday to my growing young man. You make me prouder every day champ  Enjoy your day and stay focused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams The only sick about America is foul mouths idiots like you and Democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[my film place just called me and said they fucked up 2 of my rolls but it’s boutta be free and they’re gonna give m… https://t.co/lrx6dO5VbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chasingitdown_ @shib עד הקיץ זה רק חומוס אבו לילי בשבילי, שלא לומר חומוס Sabra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonalds Why does your app let me order something when your ice cream machines shut off at 11:00? I went to 3 loc… https://t.co/eMKzyuMRNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[People still act like Terminator 2: Judgement Day isn’t a top 5 movie??? YAWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okwhodat @davidfholt @fly_okc Talk to the FAA as that is the official radio name for the approach control covering… https://t.co/222JmgPy0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Episode Alert 🚨 Direct Link In the Bio. #podsincolor #podernfamily #podcast #linkinbio #instagood #instagay… https://t.co/r2zTDedDQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[To our northern Modified and @USLegendCars teams, take advantage of @shawnwaddell being in your backyard to get you… https://t.co/at6wiyqEBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorMahlmann @YosemiteNPS More info please!! Is that natural sunset lighting???]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is as bad a performance as I can remember from the Coyotes in a long while. On the flip side, Patrick Kane is so much fun to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SegLauren @britt_otoole @MelanieBraddock It's @pwualaa's fault. But I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing socialists say Maduro won the election fair and square with 80% of the vote is.......something]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎥bobarazzi7 - “Chance Encounter” Street Photography- StreetMeetDC Model: fernandaa_romero . Shout out to bobarazzi7… https://t.co/fxGMr91GqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @CarlosAMontaner @IntlCrimCourt Un pueblo desarmado y un ejército armado hasta los dientes, a eso te r… https://t.co/F8AkkDTyHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @ManuelaDokter Ugh. 🤦‍♂️🏻 Like right now. That's crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraBoutTech Thanks for the follow! Please check out my blog:   https://t.co/BPzKPSRj1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kazanir @jvgraz The times were different. She thought she was going to be Clinton’s attorney general when Clinton… https://t.co/VnSlpzCHGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stevegr08149883 I love this kiddo so much. He came into my life very randomly ten years ago, and I’m grateful ever… https://t.co/z9mQ7IIaww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini Normal for you or me, Leah!  Tell your workout partner or trainer to keep you moving fast for the next… https://t.co/vZepGcb6NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed Capt Marvel. What a fun movie. https://t.co/AAuYBUcwA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freeenoughtofly “I often cried myself to sleep.... but then I had to keep on GOING”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnoxrevanche Ursula K LeGuin. Marrion Zimmer Bradley. Anne McCaffery. The 3 science fiction authors I read the m… https://t.co/djRJBDvJCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertTate1 Cosplay convention. Had never been to anything like that but people went crazy with some of these outfits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gentlemanvet67 @lifewithshar @dansedelamort I’m a sure thing Karl no need to break the ice 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Beckham group still has under contract county-owned land in Overtown, which previously was to be the stadium si… https://t.co/N9D7BzV3yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airbornex82nd @IlhanMN just her comments make her an ANTI-AMERICAN, she knows it, but she doesn't care, she is arr… https://t.co/By8Vux9rh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would a professor want to have class on Monday night? All through grad school this has made me mad, except the… https://t.co/gO7s63qgJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kim585 @anathymadevice @karolcummins @davidmarkbradle @pleasesaveour @mikes_booh @SuzanneWinland @McSercy @starree… https://t.co/7Q2Z9h134w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I follow Alp for his hard hitting and rigorous financial analysis and forensic accounting skill set]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @coindesk It’s not ready. And while Blockchain is secure, hackers have found ways to compromise the excha… https://t.co/01hPy6M36T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustaNut91 Busta....good movie...crazy teeth made it hard for me to watch. Fair to say Freddy could eat an apple through a fence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback💥  “All day long with Hamidou Diallo: the 18-year-old bball sensation that every elite college wants on th… https://t.co/l3mtB5K4gW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Women's History Month has #InternationalWomensDay, does that mean Black History Month has-  *this account has been deleted*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhj_24324 He was on crutches a week ago... I don’t think he will be healthy enough by Tuesday, but who knows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimesofIsrael Jerusalem in the Matrix is one thing . But in reality Jerusalem is the Capital of ISRAEL. for all et… https://t.co/1R7KhF2813]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Strange didn't here any of this when it was Bob Menendez the Dem crook from NJ who got off with nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalDrinkWineDay is @egardnerkota favorite holiday! What are your top 3 favorite wines, Eric? 🍷🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Torrie11 is only the second Ruthless Aggression era diva to be inducted into the hall of fame]]></document><document><![CDATA[This picture from  the NJ Nor’easter Super reminds me that challenges aren’t just physical but mental as well. No m… https://t.co/75QI7oxLkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #20thAnniversary to #OfficeSpace   As of October 2018, the term Ass-Clown officially entered the Webster's di… https://t.co/KfJM0Szlye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my GoFundMe campaign: https://t.co/9ZWaEfIDjq @gofundme https://t.co/t49NyOzFXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DiceTowerWest sure was a blast. We already look forward to the next one in 2020. #boardgames #tabletopgames… https://t.co/yfh2n2Yct5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I fucking hate when you're talking to somebody, trying to make friends, and you say something and they dont resp… https://t.co/g3vdqWzMPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day for sledding! Check out the fun at the Norwich Golf Course after snow fell overnight in the region.… https://t.co/GBiZ2U9GIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got 7 hours of sleep...I NEVER get that much sleep EVER! Well that's triple of what I got between Saturday-Sunday… https://t.co/iFJ2jRMVkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @mccraw_birkie5 Being born to Nell &amp; Wayne !!! https://t.co/aXgHaKVPf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCVisionZero Dope‼️ but not LiT‼️ Needs:  🛣#GlowInTheDark🔰Blazings🔰   ⚠️🚲🚸 #BikeXing signs at the driveway entranc… https://t.co/CrdtSFilAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLUE HAWKS 73, BRONCOS 50: No. 1 Exeter rolls back to final four https://t.co/Ez6CneYKjw @seacoastonline @ExeterBlueHawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkusCrane @Ericryanpro @TheJimmyLLoyd - That was beautiful #TheySaidItCouldntBeDone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still furious over his attack on our Allies -- or, probably, former Allies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer Breakfast with the team! Enjoying some good breakfast while praying for our families and our clients 🙏🏻🍳///R… https://t.co/R6V0nJAmQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHAOTIC CHASE: Accused robber opens fire at @MiamiBeachPD officers, leads them on chase across the MacArthur Causew… https://t.co/k1Ze5n0YnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 am listening to mitski &amp; having a cigarette is how today’s going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russia's government has sent bombers halfway around the world to #Venezuela. The Chinese, Russian and Venezuelan pe… https://t.co/En1O691TjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCMarrk @toomuchcountry We also had a Ford truck running in Mickey Thompson Stadium Series]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going into the endodontist in an hour. Root canals and extractions. Wish me luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got The Complete Website Planning Guide on @payhip: https://t.co/9G7SgbjMBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the FoxTrax style nonsense CBS uses in its basketball broadcasts now. No need for stupid graphic effects on replays of passes]]></document></documents></author>