<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Be safe out there today! #karenchurchteam #yourgotogals #snowday #eugeneoregon #snow #realestate #realestateagent… https://t.co/sqIibAPqSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately I have two emotions: stoked, and irritated. There has yet to be an in between the last three weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EastK3M0 wow i’m 4 margaritas, 4 tequila and 3 vodka shots and i thought that said “i won’t get over it” it’s over… https://t.co/ovRtbnhlOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anchoring with stevewgn again today! It’s gonna be fun! I know it seems like it’s not based on me not smiling in th… https://t.co/ZZm1kuN5O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJellyman @BallastPoint @StoneBrewing @badhopper @JonMontag @lhtetrick @Jagoff33 @cellmavin @farachebrito… https://t.co/GhVGKeJ7ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all of you! Can only imagine the work &amp; strength it took to achieve this. Savor your success!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehillcloster This is the best news ever! Continued success!@benpollinger @thehillcloster]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG THE BLEND, THE HIGHLIGHT, THE BROWS, BIH THE LASHES!! whew chillaaaaaaayyy. 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @BrightonFFA for the chicken biscuit this morning! Breakfast always makes a girl feel appreciated!… https://t.co/lmP3SBkkx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteRandyFine @VoteRandyFine HB141 there was a question as to where the fine money goes and why can’t you just mak… https://t.co/vTpxu5rGpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry ⁦@rebeccastaab1⁩ couldn’t join us today ⁦@WilliamdeVry1⁩ ⁦@UNCLEVINNIESCC⁩ ⁦@coastalent1⁩ ⁦@GHFantasyEvents⁩ https://t.co/T3PEqKPE6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieDonovan #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass  #MarALardass #MarALardass… https://t.co/xbjIJWefqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePrejean @tmcgrady25 What fantabulous photos of your two loves! Beautiful! 💗💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extending his “dignity of work” riff to talk in more depth about racial disparities, @SherrodBrown calls for taking… https://t.co/YEQTQqupqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local cat endures a selfie. #cat #catsofinstagram #mommylovesyou #rescuecat #siamesecat @ Worcester, Massachusetts https://t.co/qq1C3PHHTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Members of Ole Miss basketball team kneel to protest a nearby pro-Confederate rally  https://t.co/MrqpmYZ2hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All week I though I was off tomorrow...guess who’s not off tomorrow 🙄🤦🏽‍♀️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineGerani @TreyDeHuete @maydaymindy9 You look so much like her-it’s the killer cheekbones! Gorg! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends @FoxNews Hey there, @TomFitton. I don’t know where you go… https://t.co/VhQhvVMvIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am keeping toasty warm on this cold snowy Kentucky day😊😊😊 @ Cynthiana, Kentucky https://t.co/G2hAYA2bl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAristeguieta A mi ver, ese chavista “pata en suelo” fue la víctima original de este desastre. Se dejó convencer d… https://t.co/M67RRbIkw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@al3xisj0rdan IM GLAD YOU HAD FUNNNNN I WAS LIVING FOR GIRLS/GIRLS/BOYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah hilarious! You go police 🚔 department, way to have a sense of humor 🤪🤣🤪🤣🤪🤣🤪🤣🤪🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DropsNoPanties @TattedSoldier83 @TiggroAmigo @AngelsFan34 @TheReal_TMcG @BastardProphet @Sunduby @steveffootball Well now I'm blushing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angeldark13131 I hope not but i see a trend..he doesnt use email, texts, and he cant write hahaha...looks like he… https://t.co/6Q7eiwAcpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You disappeared but the history is still here, it's why I try not to cry over spilt beer. I can't even get mad that… https://t.co/LquXkEv7O6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes being snowed in is a good thing. ❄️ I’ve been focusing on myself and it feels great! #workingonme @ Land… https://t.co/hKJF7t0OAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rissacutler @carmelsupt @Carmelschools @JanetWarden So much sweet fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplelik_shay He only ate the white part so I don’t think he gone really poot that much lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodeNmeAngryMan Right on. I bet he took advantage of me cuz I'm a woman. Chinese men treat women like second class… https://t.co/FU0l7UBQ8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellnessMama I think having a routine and “you time” in the morning, before kids wake up is KEY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwbackthursday❤️ To my babe @iamjamiefoxx in #thekingdom !🕌In 2007...the same year that I?Got to see Jamie for… https://t.co/vgpbEBxsd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s Rosie? #IamwithHerTamoa #RNHATampaBay #HisCoA Did you find me at an event?  Let's take a selfie and tag it… https://t.co/CkqJyqZaJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay it’s Friday. Stay warm DFW. #fabfriday #fridayfun #fearlessfriday #TGIF #weekend #yourrealtor #prospertx… https://t.co/Wnvv4q08Eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they truly were many priests, because they were not suffered to continue by reason of death: https://t.co/N5Odo3bGFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah hi, if you don’t follow me in twitter please refrain from texting me about my tweets. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um desejo: comprar uma impressora 3D, fazer polegares opositores pro Max e assistir os doguinhos dominarem o mundo. https://t.co/bbbuBeJpvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton I know like this teaches anyone anything...oh wait maybe it teaches future liars and cheats how NOT to get away with it...😳🙄🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MazurikL Not watching that sorry arse traitor and to think how good President Trump treated him for many years...POS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really anxious. That’s one of my biggest flaws, I over stress the little things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodiousBree Scanxiety is awful. But for me it is better knowing than wondering. Hang in there and let us know ho… https://t.co/03gegWPrBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs @AnnCoulter #endthefed.  It’s called “penny wise and pound foolish “!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makin it hail at your local GAS USA with the change from my $1.25 of all quarters. WHAT THE ACTUAL FUCK IS THIS 🤣😅😳… https://t.co/DHRROlKybu]]></document><document><![CDATA[En coordinación con el #InstitutoMunicipalDeLaMujer, el Ayuntamiento rindió homenaje a Consuelo Silver, Hermelinda… https://t.co/jRY2wrNPJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who attended our fundraiser last night. If you don't live in Los Angeles but would still like to… https://t.co/XopPfYRcvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suspect in Jussie Smollett case previously arrested for attempted murder https://t.co/r8sHOoi0z3 via @pagesix Jussi… https://t.co/KO6zon1QOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 : #pourchoices ... a perfect photo op @AmizettaEstate courtesy of men_meat_wine ... the sublime tastes of… https://t.co/zf4qhwkFDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[In his talk for the Alworth Institute, Dr. Henderson credits the Soviets with some of the restoration of buildings… https://t.co/1L8kdXp2Lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We all have dreams. In order to make dreams come into reality, it takes an awful lot of determination, dedication,… https://t.co/jtgxTIabkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about what to eat to watch @IlliniMBB tonight? Eat in or pick up @BWWings and support @chs_d_marathon -- e… https://t.co/M9i2aEVZWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This journey has been so amazing that I have been too engaged to post! So here’s a little recap... Day 1 Capitol an… https://t.co/3bMmUhni0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NamasteNoelle @hornswaggled2 #Idiots The sicker people are, the longer they are in hospital, the more 💰 we make an… https://t.co/tdRFp4mcur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks college, let’s hope grad school treats me well too. https://t.co/MCgMOczrRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #daybreak8: I visit @fearfair. They have a haunted Valentine’s Day house. How cool is that?! If you and your sig… https://t.co/Do3VoSBvs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankzocalo @cablecom Pues en diciembre en la casa se tardaron 3 semanas en arreglar su “error” y aparte nos cobraron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedStripeRocco @almostablaze @CasaskullMark @ml2370 @HomonLang @ccsunflwer @LinemansLadyLuv @scottydog57… https://t.co/r7RYzuckSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like we are missing the most important 25% of the story not being told... #RedTableTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2016 I created Political Tarot. Perhaps I need to swap O’Malley out for Daniels. https://t.co/SXYuhNM5tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wkyc that is the best you could do with a fashion consultant? Find someone qualified and interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @jameskthompson1 I truly dont care what his rating is,  Trump is a Traitor to the United States  Period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshmueller I’m preparing to climb a mountain in a hurricane or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjoewolf @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews You'd like to see the guy who debates you assholes into the ground gone.  Attend… https://t.co/PRE8w4jtZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just your average proud mama here!!!....Like Mother...like daughter....we love the ocean and warm weather...it's ou… https://t.co/FukHs8eZca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardJFelton So here you are, following me no less! Got your message - big changes, and so it goes.  It's a litt… https://t.co/fjWRD8rrku]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's so many people that care about me. There's so many people that are praying for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why, but I’m really craving peppermints over the last day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, let’s get a bunch of old guys with lack of melanin talking about social media in golf  I mean, why wouldn’t we… https://t.co/weGiFHoom1]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you dont cut off the top of your kiwi and eat the inside w a spoon who are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but I’m obsessed with this shade when the sun shines on any piece of my hair 🍒🥰 https://t.co/k0LYIKwptx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so geeked I finally was able to join an intramural volleyball team and AHHH YES I MISSED VOLLEYBALL SO MUCH https://t.co/ZP8QDH72Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Britney b****  Fangirls and guys of the 90s will rejoice when shopping at Bargain Hunt! I got this Britney Spe… https://t.co/1jSEDVj5tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, just got jolted awake by a nightmare and I'm covered in cold sweat. Fuck, I just wanna sleep, but that was a doozy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieCableGuy Thanks Jamie, I am done for the night. Hope all is well with you and the water tank/heater. Have a good weekend my friend. 😍🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like old movies, screwball comedies, vintage clothes, and basically I'm an old-fashioned gal. Zooey Deschanel... https://t.co/BmkaS7EdTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @terra_studer just had a competition on who can bend their knees inward farther]]></document><document><![CDATA[”You want a revolution? I want a revelation, so listen to MY declaration: ‘We hold these truths to be self-evident… https://t.co/FDDd8mB7xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun💏💏near the ocean today💕💕Borrowed this hat from a handsome and took this photo lol.  Loved my vca bac… https://t.co/SRv75lKPO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[bad ass coffee is so fucking fire😭 (before y’all come for me i’m not from rancho leave me alone)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When the devil think he got you beat till god come thru. “ @brownjourdin I swear if I don’t make it with music my… https://t.co/wZdsNTit6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WE. WILL. NOT.  LET. YOU. BE. A. DICTATOR.  #Impeach45  #BeTerrifiedThisNutJobIsPresident]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MckMarieMur @MckMarieMur oh also put on that so called letter, why do seemingly intelligent people(in your case ig… https://t.co/FbtJDeeL74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got 2c Aquaman on itunes...i love this movie! Ive had it on 3x so far while im working! Bonus the Score is ama… https://t.co/imJ9czhbt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bourbonitis @MichalskiLaura @WaxahachieNews That development story did not need a seven-deck subhed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse No one in Germany gave a single clap when Pence announced greeting from DT. They groaned and scowled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark You’re going to be blown away when you find out white supremacy was the whole point all along! Please tweet about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I washed my hair for the first time in a week today so I consider that my accomplishment of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamJesseWatson That’s AMZING!!! It would have probably put me into heart failure, but I LOVE the Blue Angels 🤩🤩🤩 G… https://t.co/ns9yHgn3vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softpxrn Taxing was the perfect word. I need to start charging a security deposit https://t.co/Nj0dXzWgpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So its official official that PS5 is gonna be backwards compatible. I knew saving my ps2 games would come in handy one day. Value!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DoS will continue to rise and the haters will continue barking like dogs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[guys i hopped the fence to iii points on friday night and instead of getting into the festival i landed backstage a… https://t.co/zjhYfiughE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawgphonics  Kick those Monday Blue @ Lakewood, Myakka City https://t.co/Ale4uoDx8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like him, but Biden revealed that he doesn't fully appreciate how awful Mike Pence has been to the LGBTQ+ communi… https://t.co/A4PcbBXNbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bladeruss @krassenstein Absolutely. I don't understand why she even tries to lie about things like this anymore. W… https://t.co/abk9R7udbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DucksOnline Looool    When you're at Costco... and you justify it going around for another round of samples by say… https://t.co/A2x83OH3Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jude just came to us and said “I go potty” and he actually went IN the potty!!! I no longer have a baby and I’m tor… https://t.co/vYJ58SaIyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Geerryson @BEACASSO @s0phhz @urbangorillas @ScumbagMagazine @ScumbagVisuals @localwolves @BEACASSOMAG… https://t.co/N0P59Kl4cP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am positive that your groom will not be getting cold feet… but I think this... #comedy #giggle #smile #playful https://t.co/hqYqPaHoA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montferrara @AdrianDeLaGarza @JaimeRdzNL @CumbresMty @Mty_Leones Que abran lince desde Richard bird, tiene años qu… https://t.co/7IBMsOfeXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BobSeger 💙 @ The Forum (Inglewood, California) https://t.co/3FNvSLVp4G]]></document></documents></author>