<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Maestermagoo @Real923LA You're the one that thought of child pornography and molestation, not me. You're the one w… https://t.co/TiiTk63Rw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim75067247 Sorry but there is a tree in the picture. And rocks generate heat. Walk and never fart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDKA @steelers @AB84 @CoachTomlin @_BigBen7 @KingJames Why doesn’t he just go away?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubsTypical Fr tho. That Molina-Posey battle for best catcher in the late 2000s to early 2010s was something else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just jolly. #funniness #lol #grin #playful https://t.co/N9ONoITtXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/S0oQ4r6bHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @CoryBooker Absolutely right. And The Democrat Party should also be referred to as what it truly is… https://t.co/7gFfXg2DxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWeatherON I think the wind warning was cancelled too soon.. just had a big blast that brought down more sticks and twigs..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright. 2:52 am. 2/18/ 2019, yeh know , often I I have asked the question , Well, how round is our universes Sun .… https://t.co/hBn8xXmfYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of several names that will stick with me forever on this list, 5-year-old Brooklyn Youngblood, killed by her mo… https://t.co/dLlpdAixLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJLandeck @JWerner247 @GeneSteratore You think @Genesteratore is ever going to disagree with a ref. I honestly don… https://t.co/jD3xP3KYFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#McAllen police officers receiving their new badges this morning...first new badges in over 50 years #mcallentx… https://t.co/O2Jc8ZgA9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtimberlake never disappoints. What an epic show.  . . . . . #justintimberlake #staplescenter #concert #music… https://t.co/UT1WYfxpYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cindy didn’t want me to post this video because it shows the barrier we built to keep the 9-month old Pit Bull pupp… https://t.co/KHTnuLuQy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m making my daughter vacuum out my truck tomorrow! She’s got a half pound of glitter allll in the back seats.... 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching the #FyreFestival documentary on Netflix. It’s funny as hell 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julia’s getting her CIZE workout for the day in and getting ready for her April tryout for the @msudanceteam ! That… https://t.co/tgZ45JWMDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos díassssss @calleypocheoffi 😁🤘🏻 Happy Wednesday!!! Have a GREAT day. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSWhiteSox @Lamantha21 @TimAnderson7 @ymoncada19 @whitesox If Tim Anderson is going to continue to talk shit hop… https://t.co/noDmZyltaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over 1  Billion records sold you will never and can never erase @michaeljackson HISTORY! He's the best selling musical artist of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry if this is offensive the issue is #Japan has a weird culture of sham.. who they need to get over… https://t.co/6oX3hA9hto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I drop a full set from that @TeamSESH stop in Portland?  @seshcompound @TeamseshMerch @seshcompound ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Everything. He lacks reading skills, he lacks any semblance of grammar and an adult vocabulary as we… https://t.co/rItQofvAJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabionPicheco @barngrl @tearswillfall @TruckerS63 That's when things got weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker @HillaryClinton You lost Wisconsin. Is it because the people didn't like your agenda? Also, fuck you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a devastating day, not only here in Broward County, but the rest of South Florida.😔                  Communiti… https://t.co/4gIxPOG6L1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavinTheBees $15 for a month of origin access gives you access to the full game tonight at 9, and if you don’t lik… https://t.co/WockS7zpkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @SainzSainzz @xaidrafox @emilymenaxo @MsKimberLeeXXX @slutsaucekhloe @AlexisMonroexxx @thetanalea… https://t.co/Fh6OM4Wr3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like my family really be fucking fake like first of all my life is already trash I don’t think I can go any lower i… https://t.co/BdZ09IHlmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another shot from last night. Ocean magic... #ocmd #CanonFavPic #teamcanon #aquatech #ocean #sunset #surf #waves… https://t.co/qJ6aMySCp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ever complain about where you are, because you are the person that got you there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f3lkn #pb #easylikesundaymorning 🏃🏻‍♂️from Davidson Green 0630 or/and 4 extra at 0600.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge without LOVE (Biblical love) is meaningless.    I’ll take character and integrity and love any day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLoveBel0w @cspan @RepAOC @AOC If she is all the GOP has to worry about,it’s looking really good for them..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCBrigade14 @jlovelaw @bhmlegion @KColby3 @bhambackline Glad to know we're not completely out of out depth!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home...start some laundry, the boyfriend is coming over for drinks and dinner❤️❤️❤️ #GMStudio #Mil💛💛💛… https://t.co/Og3osdAoP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[God never asks if we have the money to do what he is asking us to do. He wants to know if we are willing. If it’s G… https://t.co/1LUcVStEBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my top 5 autograph baseballs in my collection. #FourHorsemen https://t.co/uNSYNYISo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boyfriend wound me up so much this morning for no reason. Not a happy camper this morning 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo creo q el castigo a César Yañez ya fué suficiente. Ojalá q muy pronto lo veamos  al lado de nuestro presidente,… https://t.co/RmX2s5UeUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Decemate @Parasite @iReedr At least w slam u gotta be right place right time. Seraph u can literally run around ego chall world star people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenp4ch1 I’m really upset that you used Ben Affleck instead of Christian Bale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju And with that, Sen. Geary exited the committee room, smiling for the cameras. His secret was safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjoseph7777 @dscc @dccc @realDonaldTrump no sympathy here. you're only turning against 45 because your money was i… https://t.co/OFyQcUKobV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choral director is blasting Mozart requiem in their office and it’s amazing. Fitting mood for the end of the academic term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickFinch @FOXSports https://t.co/I2Sxx4FFUH  But this has to be a close second]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could be ghosted I could be shadow banned I could be taking a big dump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drunk me is into EDM and comedy. Stoned me is all classical music and books. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to breakfast after this interview in the morning , my sit down with V103 radio legend is in a few weeks , got… https://t.co/s2iPY7kjlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[se te olvida que me quieres a pesar de lo que dices pues llevamos en el alma cicatrices imposibles de borrar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesnicksearcy @4inspiration2 Great just let women and minorities go and see how it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader 23 if your members voted against. Don’t let that distract you from the woman in the hijab.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only we redirected all this energy spent resenting and punishing the less fortunate into helping them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKlitsgaard @of_nhl Lehkonen is worth more than a 4th right now..if that's all you get then he's going nowhere. He… https://t.co/OeizBTYUFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This the type shit they dont teach us during black history month so we forget and fall into their hands ignorant of… https://t.co/3n4KbmSJaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, Dems are on board, just not with a STUPID wall. Talk about smart border security, n… https://t.co/yon3Y01Xy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comparing delivery positions with athletes today in Javelin! https://t.co/2WpmBtbMWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched Pats twitter for a couple of years now...feel like it’s on a constant loop...especially FA season...it’s no… https://t.co/csr5xBavKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump Looks like Jay Barrett is the only intelligent and moral person in his whole family! You GO, Jay! Love your fortitude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allend0rk It's funny that he stopped going all gaga over her on TV and we hear about this lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/TZLMONtgzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BelfastBronco @Broncos_grl Still unsure something that I want to tho like travel vlogger, radio, or just pour some Guinness 😀☘️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChanandlerBlur @BernieSanders And they are all single payer. It’s about 350M people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aunt Bob’s chocolate cake. One of the greatest cakes I’ve ever had. #chocolatecake #homemade #cake @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/sg6LgTMEAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had almost the exact setup in the mid-80s.  I have no idea where the computer ended up... probably just threw it aw… https://t.co/xy6eh8XZ9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyP776 They played good and made it into the wildcard with the win. If I lived here season tic for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mantovanicrvg Culpe seu clube por descumprir uma clausula que está em contrato. Descumprimento da lei, e de uma or… https://t.co/KjiDlAylEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Naugatuck boys basketball team defeated Newtown 66-60 Thursday night, setting up a big quarterfinal matchup wit… https://t.co/8W4qI8D9if]]></document><document><![CDATA[My my Davis, you just don’t care do you? Instead of putting our county first and looking out for our constitution y… https://t.co/cdBSygFMkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mario_bono @The1Voyce @kylegriffin1 Fools with short memory and/or Trump haters, forget our President stayed alone… https://t.co/6FmFIDzLWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMacPhils @KevinFrandsen @SIRIUSXM has all the games... Not free but nice options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WED. NIGHT FEB. 20TH!! Take a step closer to THE EDGE OF HEAVEN: at Joe's Pub at The Public at 7pm. Featuring… https://t.co/ZEKLz8Aj1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a time when the thought of spending $140 on a meal would have given me a panic attack. I was so broke, bu… https://t.co/S0ytQVCjZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprising that the man who pull out of the Paris climate agreement and said he wanted to abolish the EPA is now do… https://t.co/pMg7td5Y3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sherry_Hughes @WCPO We all know the WWA isn't for the snow.  It's for the drivers who don't know how to drive.   T… https://t.co/MZvgd1uG2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsHour @lisamurkowski I believe the House has been passing legislation, including the piece ending Trump’s emerg… https://t.co/oqFr7aS4Gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s goooooo.  redbullarena pll #newera #wetheplayers @ Hermosa Beach, California https://t.co/ZhzRquLXzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had my first real coffee from starbucks today and i can’t say that it’s something i’d do again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harlem_Finest24 @banks_jasamine So I can only imagine for old boy as that was the best 1:52 seconds of my life.… https://t.co/1Y9wQFPcwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianXpression "can't even lie fuck better when I'm drankin'" BITCH https://t.co/JzkmFiGArx]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@odacathletics Men’s Quarterfinal: @RMCHoops defeats @TrackTheCats , 79-42. Highlights tonight at 6 on @13Sports !]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to NHS Student Section...GREAT JOB last night!! Great enthusiasm and support. You were 1st Class!! Let’s fill t… https://t.co/I6Esb3nrtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a committee under control of course of the Liberals which the Liberals have on numerous occasions stated  i… https://t.co/BzamP0BJZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🏾 #MOFIS ♾  #MyOnlyFocusIsSuccess ♾ #ForeverMyLifestyle 🙌🏾 @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/BdMVfvnpCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was feeling sorry for myself because I didn't have a 60-inch TV, and then I met a man who didn't have hands, and… https://t.co/F3Ce0oiULw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#holyroar @christomlin 🙌 @ Moda Center at the Rose Quarter https://t.co/jjLJKcerJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes She’s got that DeVos “I’m as dumb as a box of Tiffany diamonds” look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanover and Transylvania will square off in the HCAC championship game tomorrow at the 2 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constantly lying and not being able to tell the truth about ANYTHING is a mental disorder and toxic as fuck. GO SEE A THERAPIST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AGTG Blessed to received my first D1 offer from The University of William and Mary https://t.co/XfwocrtVxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phil McCalister, Director of Commercial Crew Program @NASA emphasizing the significance of anyone being able to buy… https://t.co/kM5W1s1cNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monarch token Airdrop round 2: https://t.co/HTvjaOLEFI #airdrop #bounties https://t.co/9RY53f98Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to fight through some bad days to earn the best days of your life...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world doesn’t produce enough coffee to deal with daylight savings time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leominster has everybody rolling route 2 at the exit 30 off ramp for the rollover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/SEnXx1JFC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoyas247 I know this sounds crazy, but Mourning needs more minutes in the second half.  That big man is in Govan's head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got a free ticket to the Travis Scott concert my friends really fuck with me lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats Want to Rig the Rules https://t.co/iBlO0DCA3z via @https://twitter.com/GOPLeader]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FollowFriday @jhaletweets #GooseBay, #Canada's hottest actress with the beautiful blue eyes! #BlackCat-#SpiderMan… https://t.co/5GCeb1MgH1]]></document></documents></author>