<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Worn  #InstaGay #Gay #GayGuy #GayBoy #GayMan #GayHunk #GayHot #GayBeard #GayDaddy #GayWorld #GayLife #Gaystagram… https://t.co/zDfk6VpQ96]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can only make it so clear that someone ain't shit too you for so long before the move along]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannity: Democrats ignored the crisis at our southern border  https://t.co/En6a3Lyn5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[As couple you should own the following: 10 hand towels for Maundy Thursday 10 purificators 5 corporals  1 fair line… https://t.co/EXdR3SYEBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr @JebBurtonRacing @jeff_gluck Sounds like it may be @jeff_gluck himself so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you pronounce it Melon or Meelon? @elonmusk #elonmusk #tesla #elonmuskmeme #meme #memes #dank #dankmemes… https://t.co/tJnW2O3Cyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump454545 @KatTheHammer1 Is there a relationship to Kamala Harris intro. anti-lynching legislation. And suddenly… https://t.co/TlrNTwFgWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're on the bike, jamming to INXS' #DontChange ... and your phone pings.   Southside's Natalie Lundquist-Thr… https://t.co/rPHvYVbJQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elohimmusic You’re not a want but a need at any show or festival that I can possibly go to ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's business dealings, with other countries especially Russia, is relevant to the investigation of him and his… https://t.co/GqRBwAUZax]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏻Push Pull Legs (PPL) by @CoreyPas . I get questions all the time on what is PPL. Or questions asking if this is a… https://t.co/F67L5E1XDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[May 11th @SchneckMed will again be providing free physicals for all Seymour athletes incoming grade 6-12 here @ SHS… https://t.co/ksmPNFrhZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-foot-5 2019 #B1GCats WR signee @GHooper413 getting it done on the track too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last nights @NDmbb was a great game! - sad we came up short but it was a great game. Next year will be a lot better 🙏🏼👐🏽🙆🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationalLeagueH @CubsSuckClub @CubsTypical @Cubs You’re so mad on the internet 😂😂😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Carolina's education overhaul bill is a big step closer to reality]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSEMANUELSOTO1 😳😳😳😳😳😳😳 @sanchezcastejon mmmmmmm.....sabes quién fue Clara Campoamor😳😳😳😳😳....es inaudito que usted sea presidente😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decade for People of African Descent recognized by Canada https://t.co/5cn8Ohoib4]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the spirit of Valentine’s Day @SouthwestAir is giving gifts to people that sing over the mic at the gate...that’… https://t.co/bhHZu8EM92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosnitchess @pdubz32 @CTFletcherISYMF CT your off the chain lol your the man...!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#B2BS on @1037TheGame  4:30 @RossDellenger — #LSU 5:15 @ruffinrodrigue (@Ruffinos) 5:30 Jace Conrad — #Cajuns 6:15… https://t.co/pDVAcGjP7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiseUPWalkAWAY2 @jonrosenberg @JacobAWohl Noticed your @ and figured this was a decent time to mention that the… https://t.co/fq5vXEAunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Teske, but we need another big that can get to the basket quicker. Having depth in the paint next year will be nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obysv Deja tu,  mientras esos inadaptados, retrógradas y cavernícolas se andan "matando" por sus colores y "demost… https://t.co/YMuGNJ6WgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentally i’m ready for Buku. Physically i’m not https://t.co/yRDqNamWHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This college life ain’t for me dawg I’m thinking about dropping out going back to LA and joining La Onda with my rasa ese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martybalIer People be talking music without knowing their history. Sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous 4 Bedroom/2.5 Bathroom Condo. Live less than a minute from all the Eastland Ave Buzz! Unique Floor Plan wi… https://t.co/50jBAvXZig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hpcollierville “THE SECRET TO LIVING THE GOOD LIFE, TO HAVING IT ALL, IS SEEKING GOD’S KINGDOM ABOVE EVERYTHING EL… https://t.co/qO06SAOCL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calvanij @TheGoodGodAbove As Willie says, you don’t get over it, you just get through it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betofloresRG690 @gracieve @10APG Lucho ibarra y sus seguidores deberian analizar muy bien antes de publicar ... es… https://t.co/shvHJ4bzOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEEMSTAR Totally agree , but there are some authentic peeps out there... me personally I’d just like to have frien… https://t.co/DcdYpZxqA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok.. I'm gonna say it.  it's selfish to want a huge family of your own kids when they are children in need of homes… https://t.co/lU1mTIDkoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how @negaoryx just started her stream and this is already the thumbnail https://t.co/jqI9aJVYVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most attractive thing @Jellyk120 has ever said to me was “I need to find a driver to start following, I actuall… https://t.co/BJDJ1YJoPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[En medio de tanta libertad a veces nos sentimos presos!! La libertad está sobrevalorada... los instantes en los que… https://t.co/rSxLYupmK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimrome Glenda sounds a lot like Mona sincerely Larry and his cousin at radio shack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZTAdamczyk @ShakeCracklePop I didn’t mean to slide it and it did that but since you about to put me on blast I should own it🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue Are you ready to order I’m so hungry right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout Elon: @uncwmenshoops leads the Phoenix 70-63 with 8:19 left to go. #CAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcseifert Seems like we average just about the same! https://t.co/PI1bTeyQrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AverageSuperDad You trade TJ to keep Oubre who is a 3&amp;D guy and better fit for our team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves you truly are one of a kind. THIS. Thank you. 😭😭❤️❤️🙌🏽🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[It absolutely appears AB became aware of the Bills news when we all did and that’s why he took to the IG comments t… https://t.co/39DCbmuwLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity So, let me see if I understand this . . . 53% of people who just LOVE all the “democrat” policy, would… https://t.co/pv4QGeFdad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donnie, you would be surprised what is on face book. It is about your  modeling agency. Where you… https://t.co/9w7jYOvIz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieshawphilly And this would be true. Without research and data you cannot make a claim that Krasner's policies… https://t.co/uSwnTZs0Cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This goes to show Trump cares more for golfing. Thanks green energy for future generations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatDonovan 😂😂 one of the best shows no doubt I just caught up with the new season yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Say it, Daddy is a criminal &amp; SDNY will haunt you from now on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's ready for @IBSnewyork #ibsny The @Hairlabdetroit team will be there with 2 classes and #manestage See you soo… https://t.co/V7CWAu94Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vandyron001 @wizman_23 I’m still trying to figure what’s so wrong with eating ass??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/hX0xwfwP8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaMeahRacing @santaanitapark 🙋🏻‍♂️.. I could use something to do in my spare time instead of sitting in the raci… https://t.co/W0gc4hn8pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making Double Bubble just to drive trucks call me anyday lol 😂Benicia, ca to San Francisco to San Jose to Benicia h… https://t.co/z3XUfzazTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katelyncosenza @SlickBainter this is what a good valentine box looks like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe this is what we call, in the biz, a "gotcha" moment @TuckerCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoicism allows for - the sense of doom and delight that is programmed into the human body to be overridden by the… https://t.co/Rlja8iUvXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starrbryte67631 @redsfantexas @lisaponyexpress @PamelaM5050 @DollyDwyer10 @Brandonmartine @adones683 @BigPopa1971… https://t.co/bj740kk0sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of the shower and getting oiled up while on cam #bbcmodel #partsmodel #Chaturbate #cammodel #coconutoiltwitter… https://t.co/aK40mk0fpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcorn State 2017 QB Football had some breakout games in the arena league this year. #Footman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueGhost40_ That was one my favorite moment of the night and especially when he blasted McConnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaharaReporters @inecnigeria What u couldn’t fix in 4 yrs will be done in 5 more days 🤣! U r a genius @inecnigeria]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚💛Home Town💚💛  #MayYouBeBlessedWithEnough #LoveOverHate  #HateIsNotAnOption https://t.co/6V5ZKqMsUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmmilyGZ @joshraclaw @typologianista @ChickashaJenny Yeah, I'm happy to be looped in on this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSaint1188 If they announced wrestlers are signing this year again I’d probably go as Savage one of the four days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We truly appreciate ALL of you! Please support and share as we create positive social impact on of the country’s la… https://t.co/SypoaWIcG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorsemensWizard @NewYorkFBI @FBINewHaven But then I suppose that is why taking a whiz" refers to pissing.  Nobody… https://t.co/JmJUeUsSLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma will literally have her TV like full volume, not be wearing her hearing aid and she gets mad because I h… https://t.co/34mAuTpLp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satanisfemale @JasperDontFold @resistasista76 @KingRocket1 @TexasTribune @innocence I have early meetings with Ire… https://t.co/SoRUg2prgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond Meat campaign stars investor and NBA star Kyrie Irving https://t.co/Q4Etljc9vG via @adage]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUY NOW! 50% of all sales will be sent to ChicagoPD for investigative work on #JussieSmolletHoax #rt  https://t.co/FNnXJBmyZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesAGagliano In light of the recent McCabe news, I went back and found a this CNN piece which is timely.  https://t.co/x0a4TK7aY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetiredDA Good morning Martin! I don’t truly hate many people, but when I do I fully embrace the emotion. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieDoesTwitt @senatemajldr #MAGA🇺🇸 #teammitch🇺🇸 https://t.co/fNP52FxW85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @JoeBiden @VP Yes. Pence is a homophobe. You can't be as full of hate as he is and be "decent". Call them out for what they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeshinoda Hey Mike, Johnny Craig is looking for a band. He’d be an AWESOME addition to LP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomdog I’ve been farting quite a lot so I’d say it’s been some of the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiding in plain sight @byrnemetfan7 @baybeepowder @Shwill_I_Am @Eddiemolo @macho7657 @MutantCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do enjoy reading my Saturday @DMRegister while sipping on my morning coffee.  Oh, the little things.… https://t.co/zy7pJcNAcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former @clhstxathletics star bringing the boomstick in spring training for the @Pirates ... walk off Grand Slam!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MenaceQ_Society Bruh please listen lol just give it like 10 minutes see if you don’t just ride in silence]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought life after my undergrad was scary, but I'm thinking life after my college program beats that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making coffee deliveries with my sidekick “Scout”. #wirefoxterrier #bestdogever #organiccoffee #localroaster… https://t.co/GALQES4eoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 9:38am on Saturday morning... Do you know where your brunch plans are? Here is your cheat sheet... You’re welc… https://t.co/FatVmow1hL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lring86 @AnthonyMKreis As opposed to wildly random, statistically arbitrary, random ravings by one US News guy sit… https://t.co/lluvxSmiUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[playing pokemon for the first time as a 23 year old is great but also wild because i finally understand what y’all… https://t.co/y5QjewbUts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itssLaylaa_ @OhAmandaPlease I thought this was an unspoken rule🤔 Always gotta take care of your lady first]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moskova’dan pek adet Kahve. ancak Türkiye’yi #GariplerYakacak Konuyu Hiç]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to everyone taking the bar exam today! I was in your shoes in Feb. 2017.   I had a panic attack during th… https://t.co/lNDoVhX4OY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoSoyFresa_ Es que vivimos con una generación de personas que pelean años derechos de todo, pero no aceptan la res… https://t.co/ykyLbwmd93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bizkit047 I think the reason why we get it when we get it was to make it easier to traverse the final world to get the Sora clones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mst2974 Good looking endcaps, merchandising and pack down from 2974 MST Team!!! https://t.co/en7YdyvPB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome time at the RV trip to the coast. @ Santa Cruz / Monterey Bay KOA Holiday https://t.co/BSgTPG3ZJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karr_pe Until a few years ago, the same was true for me too. I didn’t even know all of this isn’t even within the city limits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a soft spot for Maria Menounos because I remember her from Channel 1 news and when she made the jump to regu… https://t.co/T7HXXk63I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[get you a friend that believes in you as much as @KF4G does that sign he passes every morning😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is emblematic of all the disingenuous criticism of Omar. This lady is standing next to a nazi, smiling! but is… https://t.co/Ria28hZEMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungBoselli I see you included pictures this time 😂😂😂 #TeamLandingPark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cardinals, look here, bud. @Bharper3407, @kidkeuchy, @CraigKimbrel46 are all available. Make something happen!]]></document></documents></author>