<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One year ago today, I ended up at Northwell Staten Island Hospital’s ICU Burn Center due to a severe allergic react… https://t.co/6f89cgDSbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[YIKES! If you’re coming in town from Katy - you definitely wanna give yourself a little extra time. Just spoke with… https://t.co/1Swzwffg2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD Almighty's design for #HIScreation  #childofTHEKING🔱 @ Hunter's Glen Subdivision https://t.co/KVizRIYuir]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting lots of emails today from stores inviting me to “shop” for #internationalwomensday. We do know this is… https://t.co/yMIypDW3hX]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of the guys out there age 45 and over: Please get your annual PSA test... it’s a simple blood test... waaaay… https://t.co/UMP5APBa7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leigh_47 This was basically the look on my co-workers faces when it was happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello!!! My favourite disneyland lunch!! Jolly holiday indeed!! https://t.co/7DmIYvXtU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Drugs are coming in from all ports of entry not ONLY through the southern boarder! Need a bro… https://t.co/BlpytalrRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Please help America’s Wild Mustangs! BLM is murdering &amp; terrorizing them by the thousands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kd8pcm @ToledoWalleye @BigRigSmith I’d pick the same, but I don’t win shit either. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainbowchaser79 Oh goodness poor thing!! But on the flip side what would be an awesome read!! A Bridget Jones’ dia… https://t.co/M4HtNJBXRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Royals playing at 8:15 p.m. in IHSAA State Championship watch on 📺Indiana provider or 💻 on fox sports:… https://t.co/ZieYXMVSu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so surreal to see photos of #WaverlyHills in operation after having spent so much time there as she sits now -… https://t.co/Hu4tERQerO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erindooley34 Sending prayers. Let me know if you need company when you see the doctor (hint from LA mom!) 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost donspiro •  •  •  •  • A night of Shakespeare with Clara Coquette seeing the legendary Glenda Jackson as Ki… https://t.co/Jyi5fp5ICL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are an idiot.. you must really think your supporters are morons and will believe this... oh, wait......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyanamariee @moonbbyjojo @mushcircles @kyanamariee ily likewise bb ❤️ also @mnfresh1 thought u would like these :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dansoncapaldi "... That's really offensive. No wonder everyone keeps invading you."  🤨  #DoctorWho… https://t.co/TqKbzantYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deaconcruise @downsouth505 @bigsexy_tote @MarilynCapps @solomongrundy6 Lawskeez. I like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classroom space of my Dept Leader. She’s returning next year, so this might be my room next year. The downstairs wi… https://t.co/qPNBpSfDga]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m done crying over Julia and Niall now   so  back to our regularly scheduled program]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning  #EduGladiators coming in from a great #PD4uandme chat! Kelly from VirginiaBeach, Gifted Resource T, a… https://t.co/zwaFo1kBgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless you are ME, in MY position, don’t EVER try to tell ME how to FEEL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Physical Therapy is Sexy Day 7 of 30 @APTAtweets @OrthopaedicAPTA @pps_apta @NYPTASSIG https://t.co/DMEBENuPrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[But as then he that was born after the flesh persecuted him that was born after the Spirit, even so it is now. https://t.co/BFyt5s4HXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[While @ronnierossva is busy shaping young minds. Team Ronnie just turned in all requirements to get on the ballot.… https://t.co/DfzC7M0W12]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition, there is an anthropological basic constant, the primitive man trained in eye contact with the wild ani… https://t.co/X99xvxUSIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthlesswench @Blabla79021362 @tpcowgurl @sansa33snark @katia__mia @L_ei8ht @_monzon322 @readnallthetime… https://t.co/QZLAvtVUOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day - Drinking a Fat Tire by @newbelgium at @skijfbb  — https://t.co/nXp4DIgbPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you watching?   Are you picking up hints and clues friends?   #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBloods_CBS @CBSWatch but that station wagaon my dad had that and we wouldn't let him pick us up any where 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am disabled from a wreck and I don't get any benefits, insurance not shit from our government ca… https://t.co/6y8HBaz4NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man it’s a nigga out here smell so damn good....idk where but everytime the wind blow i get pregnant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muna_Mire Imagine wages going up, fully staffed departments, HR addressing issues rather than dedicating time to i… https://t.co/hcjtgEFvM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wonder how homeboy would feel knowing his friends are sliding in my DMs 😂🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Shantel_Ro I think part of it was because he wasn't happy only getting 20K an episode for his show. He's also fa… https://t.co/xwlxYdGvw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPriess @MollyJongFast Looks like he is strangling the 🇺🇸 so disrespectful he should take a knee to the balls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmAnVaJa Chicken Cottage in the background making me homesick 😂🥰 #COYS ⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizcabrera55 There are good people out there you can trust. Don't condemn us all...  Pray for better instincts...… https://t.co/RB3LBQqsTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be interesting to know if that woman worked for Westminster management oand Morgan Properties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zendaya always looks amazing.  Who are you looking forward to seeing werk the red carpet tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really believe this is the MOST DRAMATIC SEASON EVER! @BachelorABC #TheBachelor @colton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CareerTips2Go @foulksd Give when unasked, you’re answering someone’s prayers which they prayed in secret expecting… https://t.co/aUgHmYSsxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A&amp;W Cravings 🍔🍟 . #food #foodie #foodphotography #foodpics #foodblog #foodblogger #foodlover #foodstagram… https://t.co/D679j0LY9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbxx2 whenever you’re going to Cali let me know I’ll be on my way there also hehe 💌 we do need to meet up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo We shouldn't be surprised about the lies. We should be shocked when he tells truth. Can anyone remember… https://t.co/gBuMyDGFcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chaaile @AliceEvansGruff Maintenant, je ne sais pas rien ! Peut-être, un peu de mes amis sont morte.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you blast Bohemian Rhapsody in your car so you hear every lyric, every vocal, every instrument, every chord, eve… https://t.co/Ad9ag66M5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirty people always say that they are dirty because their mom used to do everything for them🤦🏻‍♀️ I grew up with a… https://t.co/M5P4kzJC0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[En entrevista con Eva Guerrero comentario sobre las mujeres pioneras de la política en Sinaloa @QuirinoOC… https://t.co/2co6vsFKMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not easy at all and sometimes I jus want to run but I need to face this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolfgnagAmadeus @Dijzeltweet @Jordan_Sather_ Your choice to believe or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvorakoelling Beto O'Rourke . His relentless town halls, relating to his constituents on what truly matters, his e… https://t.co/HIRppUCOfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonebeling @howloften @HERterus @WildChild69 @theladykatie @cheomitII @MaeVic3 @Wtg4Gateau @kenziebeck23… https://t.co/U89uXlfxFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera I say no!  Was in local ER and heard Guatemalan woman trying to get free birth control from doc.  Re… https://t.co/ieVMBT72Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t hear any thunder or lightning....I think there’s something wrong with my hearing #hearingimpaired #rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turned my students into #ProudAuthors with Studentreasures and you can too! Sign up with my link and you'll get a… https://t.co/gsoxSnyuKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im going to keep a list of useful (but not resume appropriate) skills I’m acquiring during my internship with #learnedwithKHBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtM412 @P5White I was referring to Pat White era since you tagged him specifically. However, if we’re going to l… https://t.co/gLW3vIIy2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY FUNNY BEAUTIFUL BITCH @zoilajennifer thank you for always making classes so entertaining I lov… https://t.co/7pqP0Pn0cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the most fun Florida! Couldn’t have asked for better weather on this Talde vacay. Now back to the sno… https://t.co/oGuZPOmkZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NieblayHumo @PinkieWarriorPW Toda acción  tiene un efecto. La flexibilidad en el resultado negativo permite endere… https://t.co/H0YyfKm1VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[House @SpeakerPelosi Says Attempted Voter Purge In Texas Shows Need For Stronger Federal Protections #PurgeWhitley… https://t.co/9oeueaT35P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKocur @EsotericCD @Steven_Hyden That's cool!  Gandolfini was such a huge presence though his absence will still… https://t.co/quiLkLTvng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped for donuts this morning for my coworkers🍩🍩🍩 #justiceforralph https://t.co/hkrr2lPBrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My interview with @samantha_craus is now PUBLIC🤗 Check it out!!! https://t.co/BO9vNxp5Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I could there to see @RadfordMBB #DefendDedmon but I’ll be cheering from the car!!  Let’s Go Highlanders!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are no words to describe how grateful I am for how this young lady selflessly gave love and security to this… https://t.co/PTUoLFsF0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwiens @iFixit @nProctor @uspirg @scottshafer @KQEDForum @NPR You were great! Kate Rowe @aztecdahlia @AztecDahlias… https://t.co/d7JmBNewL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChargedUp at NBC’s #TodayShow #chargertrip @LeamanJH ⚡️🍎🗽⚡️ https://t.co/iWvTGMEI59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pivo Pils by @FirestoneWalker at @mindenmeat — https://t.co/rBSlysxasY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d LOVE for an additional movie about #GREENBOOK to be done, as the HISTORY behind this LIFESAVING #TRAVEL GUIDE f… https://t.co/uRpl2vWTiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3 months of non weight bearing I can walk with the assistance of a cane or crutches (depending on how confide… https://t.co/bhx4rRhMKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce Lee’s blood sin was the actor in The movie The Crow.. google how he died]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamrunes @jason_quitt That’s wonderful! I always advise others to stay in the light and raise their vibrations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m grateful for everyone that helped me through tonight but I also hope I die in my sleep. So, I’ll just leave it… https://t.co/Agik7A1x3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When you don’t protect and value yourself, it makes you furious at yourself and furious at everyone around you.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreesyDoesIt @Channing_Frye Haha. You would say that. It's actually not that bad but it's short and will probably shrink a smidge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HYPOCRITE @AOC! Your OPEN BORDERS politics is contributing to our homelessness crisis! Taxpayers dollars are being… https://t.co/4qnpm5rBjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a democracy The taxpayers are the financiers of what we can do. 3. What woman would vote for a bill that was to… https://t.co/KbF8Mbvpc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a couple of days since it was announced, but I am still so excited the boys’ babysitter, @zoienicolle, re… https://t.co/98nOD6Eeoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mary60053440 @SharonG40210896 @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @JeannaMarie32 @jeanine_new… https://t.co/AvvGo7NDc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We truly appreciate your support! @StylusPub @entretalk @NatlEshipweek @profandygold @TCCollege @EasternWVedu… https://t.co/AWGod4WFPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrij68 @RepClayHiggins Does he keep bringing up those boxes?? The boxes have already been looked at by investiga… https://t.co/xXeZMM2C1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[BISD supporting @vfcbrazos and a wonderful partner in helping children @AnjuliRenold ♥️ #TellTheStory https://t.co/hPyk2XR6qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye. I’m literally curled up on the floor rn making the most disgusting noises and it’s 6:28am.   https://t.co/ehtzPeLatP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It won't stop until there is accountability. When people are allowed to resign, some resigning with full pensions,… https://t.co/ATEeACcV8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Watkins crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 02:17:08, pace 11:22 min/mile, est. finish 9:51 am https://t.co/2g4MxjIptf #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the personalized packaging from the Girl Cookie Guide Seller.  Nice touch; makes it pretty and has developed b… https://t.co/juA7os0jDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current status: Mapping my assault on the Vegas Strip. https://t.co/bE0c7kW7GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabeth_foran Love these so much!!! You and your kiddos are amazing! 💖🎨]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t got a picture with 7dias7noches , have you ever even been in uptown? 🤯 https://t.co/Q93alu7VhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say I called something that was going to happen in #CapitanMarvel and it did Happen!!! I’m so proud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Tucson, #Arizona for a workshop! Beautiful day for a flight. ☀️ https://t.co/7buKklwdxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcverdugo @DonaldJTrumpJr That would be Hillary, Obama and all of the other deep state Soros puppets, a bunch of p… https://t.co/BnBXATCIHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of building niggaz up and watching the next bitch reap the benefits 💯 I ain’t doin shit for no nigga no more 💯💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this team, this school, this community!  @ItsonChris @mrsalexanderLB @SuptSteinhauser Thx telling their… https://t.co/IStigkqfXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing in watercolor, hand painting #artpaint#colorpaint#watercolorart# watercolor paper 140 lbs. 11 inx15… https://t.co/HeYTZDNFpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get a free pint of new Nightfood nighttime ice cream https://t.co/6PzASPIIy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where else will you have a panel sponsored by the Federalist Society, Business Law Society, and the Alliance Agains… https://t.co/YTVJGtL9Iy]]></document></documents></author>