<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In my Facebook workshop yesterday I taught the audience how to repurpose blog content using Facebook Notes to which… https://t.co/B4tGejja2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Luck @PRodgersGolf  this weeks @PGATOUR  event @ArnoldPalmer invitational. @indyjrgolf  is rooting for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One💚 ! ☯️☮️👹 Trichome Thursday! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E… https://t.co/oTwp5BRQi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[ashleywitherspoon I showed @ljspoon some new Aussie puppy pics. Gonna need your approval for a puppy. LoL. 🤣😂🤣… https://t.co/EXpYo9NFp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outrolevi @Usako99 I hope you also advocate for effort equality. I’m not willing to pay taxes for people that are… https://t.co/TU1qWfUcCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; watching this BYU hoops team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc That's because US economy is strong and ROW economies are not. Econ 101]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KeurigDrPepper 📣 announced Thursday that it will move its 🇨🇱 #Texas headquarters from #Plano to #Frisco… https://t.co/y582Wx5Hb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Kling I mean, you could just have it around Queen and Adam Lambert, since they do a tour every couple years and play it off as the movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StepOverTheEdgeFriday Do something awesome today my friends. https://t.co/GLb26cYCK8 @CnickelsonHp @KeepinItCntry… https://t.co/DkbGpvWAtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Jushin Liger retiring in 2020 at Tokyo Dome, subscribers of F4W/WON can hear the "30 Years of Liger" show that… https://t.co/JvQqKhjIZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Green_Star1 @pamellalala @speakupsal @leciamaria @yoakumgirl923 @Erikajakins @DawnSCrawford @PhillipLaird… https://t.co/Z0PItDTlYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing that shocks me is that Boston  area drivers kill pedestrians constantly and it doesn't seem to be a very… https://t.co/GidimIF263]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob52695260 @kengurnick @MLB I understand... I agree but I wouldn’t be surprised if he did start deteriorating..… https://t.co/pt6ApSopBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But they had heard only, That he which persecuted us in times past now preacheth the faith which once he destroyed… https://t.co/agNWUqNF1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAntWright Granted he didn’t play last night, but if he had a better game/didn’t get hurt against MSU, it would… https://t.co/Pp1xHdLrLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one said it would be easy...but I can say with certainty...it’s worth it! #PassionAndPurpose #GoGetIt… https://t.co/eAmR3g0i4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voters can’t trust this kind communist to do anything but destroy our great nation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anapastorjulian @Congreso_Es Ha sido usted la única integrante del congreso que ha trabajado!! Enhorabuena.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RowenaMorgan95 @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Good ! Keeping our guns loaded is no fun, we have a farm and  these… https://t.co/35WM3dvfKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[this guy is out here every morning. @ Sunny Isles Beach, Florida https://t.co/xkHAh1MZU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KareemRon33 Wow you actually are that gullible 🤣🤦🏻‍♂️ I want that to happen too but all pitchers are not in best s… https://t.co/MBLDilWcWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[los de @HEB_mexico se aferran a políticas con poco criterio para la devolución de productos echados a perder, sugie… https://t.co/Amd8mD45T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am held captive in this room against my will. I am held captive in this room authorized by my free will.  I am he… https://t.co/ZOp28nAqRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oahu_Raider808 Santa Maria seasoning is all you need imo... grilling is best]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate you.  I am so blessed to have gotten to know your family. No more Thatch home games from me, but unles… https://t.co/pcNnDwwf0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's official now! Wind Chill Advisory until Fri, Feb 15 at 09:00:00 CST. https://t.co/7CFAQr9ohM #MorrisMNWeather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Allen is here   Allen opens talking about players working in the weight room leading up to the spring. Mentions… https://t.co/T8o1LTPh5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike35033639 @davereaboi @DonaldJTrumpJr I must be, you have all these pet names for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/saJVEFPjBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening. Guess who made dinner tonight. That’s right me! Larry and John and I are enjoying the meal. Many bles… https://t.co/GV397lWMpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This government is insanity. And they govern through and with fear, intimidation, dishonesty, fraud, obstruction, x… https://t.co/kOEyHyyJkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bible_Time If you only knew the times I asked for money and sex, and did not get either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FriarFaithful69 Milton Bradley wasn't a super star but for sure a villain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dopeassmia I prefaced myself before I dm’d anybody lmao https://t.co/U8abGxJvlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadwickboseman @michaelb4jordan @Marvel we need a Black Panther video game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trllewellyn11 Thank you for making my day so special! You are truly blessing and I love you to the moon and back.  ❤️🙏🏾💯#bestwife]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lived in my house for 10 years and I still don’t know what light switch turns on what light. https://t.co/ZoMcp4pT27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attraction is a law, but it is a secondary law. The primary law is the law of vibration. https://t.co/X7XiaUYt1t…… https://t.co/UBfnNm10M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every midwesterner living in NYC is currently laughing at our so-called "snow warning" right now. A) It's more rain… https://t.co/Fb1pIF9IGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkotch I'm sorry about that. Just because the unwashed masses like something does not mean it's good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Destin 30-A Real Estate https://t.co/TDQ6aulowm https://t.co/OvFBMFXfCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrotherswdw @RideEvery @CheshAndTigg @EvaM320 @Parkeology @GKTWVillage Thanks for questioning what our true int… https://t.co/as3bz7VFjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @tjbogart33 No, just cages like they do children...  But your a candiate...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgmarkley Probably Wasn't as sunny as usual for you, but we have enjoyed all the rain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankiehuot Every year we do this.   Why cant you just pay attention. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more the merrier! We as working Americans need to demand more of the resources allocated by congress to benefit… https://t.co/0yC1RlWsWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertwiblin The bias toward today’s norms is interesting as well—most would not worry about the loss of dignity i… https://t.co/5GYoe9MB8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was hoping the bengals had changed. I was definitely wrong. My optimism is at an all time low]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was thinking about doing this with my fathead as well, but thought it would be a LITTLE TOO EXTREME 😂🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustResiznTrump @realDonaldTrump This is a man who committed treason; and supporters don't care. There is no great… https://t.co/JbGWtiwpGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_queenofcool Can’t blame a kid for trying. And at least he’s got good taste]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude Ryan tried to fight 10 of the biggest niggas tonight like I’m not a 150 pound lightweight 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfIWasAGod I’d get all the best Tea from the confessional https://t.co/WGgTey75wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy channels is focusing on the major problem which is low voters turnout, stop making people feel like their… https://t.co/S2tA0gs741]]></document><document><![CDATA[God this Bill Simons “huge show” guy just loves taking shots at Kaepernick]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally everytime i have a test, the night before 1 million problems come at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josselin me regaña peor que mi mamá cuando no contesto el cel :/ hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened before I left work...couldn't see to the top of the beginner hill. @ Pajarito Ski Area https://t.co/52ablpkAHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomeluLukaku9 This year the champions league is yours. You will play the final against Liverpool 2-0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tupmayorsoffice when are we going to fix online bill pay? Been down 45+days? https://t.co/QaDLtqgeYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #SweetNinas #bananapudding for coming in to @FOX29philly #fox29goodday today.  You made the team very hap… https://t.co/V4xTaeVMOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damonfick You think I’M claiming that even as I explicitly point out that I’m not.   I don’t have confidence you a… https://t.co/cl4Ngjvaca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @calvinswimming and @CalvinTnF both competing for MIAA Championships today!!! Finish strong #TeamCalvin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler @Alyssa_Milano  @kathygriffin   All have been vaporized by us.  #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson makes misogynistic and perverted comments https://t.co/JFkzmh8WFq via @YouTube // Here’s your fair a… https://t.co/SNViI93VVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you are not alone.” four of the most powerful words our God ever spoke. four words that have gotten me through som… https://t.co/ekwBRANdCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasmined_brown I was just reading those comments too. Don't compare black people to monkeys. It's a no go. Funny t… https://t.co/Fw1pBTEVxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Tiger Nation, Beat Me There On Tomorrow For Alumni Night. Door Specials For Alumni Wearing TSU Gear, Former TSU Me… https://t.co/OqF17xG7FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGavin1 Hasn’t he been widely known to be scheming people for years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Van Jones,  over the past several years has proven himself to be a Conservative Republican in his views and needs t… https://t.co/rtnQ2GbJT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_M_0_N @Model3Owners @28delayslater @Teslatunity @daniel_a_g86 Toonces! I haven't thought of him in forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of y’all need to learn how to shut y’all mouth’s... especially with the way those teeth are set up. https://t.co/zrXUlTC5Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[CCTV footage revealed of Jussie Smollett’s friends purchasing items they used in the Chicago “attack” of Smollett.… https://t.co/kKCVNufT9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom From the Augusta market, some ads have actually been so awful they were effective. But most local efforts are pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest installment of Overheard at the Bar...if the employees of your start up are leaving in droves, it's not them - it's you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this guy living on the same planet as we are? Over 1000 lies and or false hoods and he never heard Trump lie I t… https://t.co/AgcGvZB4Vu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tholzerman Oh absolutely. They're not playing arenas or anything. But they definitely headline bigger clubs and wh… https://t.co/onWhLY9TD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachblackjc @mssociety MS is such a varied disease depending on the symptoms one has. We have got to be better ab… https://t.co/hV5C8rRU1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also feels important to mention that jamie did this while our mother checked out books about divorce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westcoasthky Points? Why? Currently the Kings have the 3rd pick in the draft - why on earth would you want “points?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResistRR @TDPattillo @regmondo Oh come off of it. It's aimed at Bernie supporters, who in his view are somehow suspect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, one of the best followers on twitter is @RatCatcherMpls. No question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got cut off by one of those cars with government plates. G something kind of plates]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔊🔊NOTHING TO IT 🎹 BUT TO DO IT🔊  🔊🔊FOCUS FEAT. MOUNTAIN MIKE🔊 IN EVERY DIGTAL STORES NOW! SO PLAY▶ THIS SINGLE LOUD… https://t.co/Ifi5Ejp8c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[One hour left on International Women’s Day. Just wanted to squeeze in a shoutout to the amazing + amazingly intelli… https://t.co/sJgVcCif7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only took a 1.5 hour nap instead of my average 3 hour nap. That is progress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahamruthven I think Roma is the most challenging place to work in Italy, it goes well beyond what people tweet a… https://t.co/VeePI2TKEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going into a witness protection program when you have a softball sized 69 on your face should be interesting. https://t.co/fTOo8Uaarw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compared to the people who have told me this, I am technically half a fucking better parent than the majority of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without a doubt the most exciting @SamfordMBB player ever to put on a Dogs uniform.  His defensive intensity along… https://t.co/4WfsDiPwUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think people who drink a lot and eat a lot of junk food have acid cum? Shit has to be toxic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJonathanCain @ndccOrlando That’s awesome!! Will it be streaming live??]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SillyPuddy day! Ss are comparing temperature in Silly Puddy to metaphoric rocks Looking at  patterns, cause and ef… https://t.co/IKwo0ytGJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher hey asshole im from tn  and i have yet to pay a state income tax, dodge a needle, or. A pile of shit and… https://t.co/bxYJDaCK88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrecariats @Guinz @hughhewitt So, we are including suicides, which I think makes up the difference (sad).  Thanks for the clarification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reporte_Indigo Que podías esperar de la@lacra del roñas noroñas mándelo a Venezuela a vivir haber si así aprende algo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmangoldstein Also, there was of course no guarantee that we would ever get that many jobs.  And they already have 5000 here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajfitz724 @dj_red_rover Billy Hatcher or Tony Longmire moving forward? I’ll hang up and listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyCaronNBC @IndyCar Three more weeks until I will attend my first @IndyCar race. The best part it’s at one of my… https://t.co/rUVove99um]]></document></documents></author>