<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Prison reform...try something, any thing! https://t.co/yqM4TuWB1m #brazil #prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OctavioRegalado Con todo gusto Paisa... de hecho hoy comí carne asada 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[А прикиньте как они очканут если однажды к ним на перехват не вылетит истребитель?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 22nd birthday, brother! Love ya buddy 👍🏻 @ Edmond, Oklahoma https://t.co/39ebFGFkkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom You need to put out your new games sooner .I work at night 12:00 am till 7:30 am  is only time i get to use computer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVDemForum @jguaido Percentage of Women in Parliament: 14.4%  Rank in World Classification: 125 https://t.co/KAaJ961Esr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bowl of @alfreddunhill Early Morning Pipe in my @savinelli1876 320 KS Oceano, country music, soaking up the sunsh… https://t.co/tsnB0SBlIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrew thanks for taking my call.  I was never a fan of Michael’s.  A family friend introduced me.  It feels so st… https://t.co/7EV1kIYMHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soufflé Ready to Roll @chefsclubny 👊🏻👊🏻👊🏻 #chefsclubnyc #residency #spring #nyc #rolling #chocolate @ Chefs Club NY https://t.co/NkFKYItDdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supernovafiona @ErinPascoeee the irony from someone who doesn't eat canteloupe 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinStMartin And where the new Hudson Yards is next to the water, makes it worse...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dobermanmamma @ZanderKelly30 @DailyCaller @realDonaldTrump Nope just to fix the garage door light.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no! Yesterday was Larry the Cable Guy's birthday, and I forgot to tweet wishing him a happy birthday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsleyJosh @JheanelleW One of the most racist things I’ve ever heard was what a bailiff said in court in Harford C… https://t.co/FblkvdxqDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nick Boniconni movie should have been showing earlier.  Nick looks like he's out of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraHutch8 I would love to have another if I could but I already have four 🐕. I am definitely a animal lover :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse my head banging before rotation this morning 😤🤘🏼 https://t.co/FJLZ2dmtZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megi_WH @GlowstickEntmt I bet that nobody ask what the gold watchers look like without there hats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spekkers Este pendejo como que no tuvo infancia. Se la pasa amenazando al mundo con plastilina y soldados de plástico #VenezuelaLibre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally hit that 1600 follower mark. Wonder if I can get to 2k by the end of baseball season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trillmoregirls @sleazoidspod Spoiler, I really enjoyed Resident Evil. I love event horizon too and I think I'm gon… https://t.co/2iSTZNpkyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeedOfLouis Me enjoying the nice upset of Real and then opening up these tweets https://t.co/9m929J2l3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlowin Thinking of the poor people taking you seriously and killing themselves trying to "spark joy" in their 3rd… https://t.co/5A6teA5EXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good news is we have a slate of pretty awesome candidates in the Ward that aren’t that different ideologically.… https://t.co/l7CjBkB6vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[As many people know, for me it's Mario Bros., not Super. I hold many fond memories of the game. The Apple ][ versio… https://t.co/H262L4NiQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Creighton Caveat....basketball game isn't on campus and Fox pays the Big East a lot of money.😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcNATSHACK That’s just crazy talk. Drafting and developing players is fundamental to winning championships.  Reall… https://t.co/wklKZ07P7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[MARCH 9th!! Join ronnieWRIGHT and special guest Joyya Marie on Saturday March 9, 2019 at the Mission Theater! And a… https://t.co/YNrxVM7bOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[&gt; when ppl send long emails😒  GET TO THE FUCKING POINT! Email like you tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allure of the Seas today. What a great looking ship. https://t.co/nxzrFkxk2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the gym showered took a dump cooked had my shake and still got an hour till work 😳👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCarroll6 Ha. First rule of fantasy football...don't EVER  draft Bills players]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBONFOX @Cubs Under. This is a typical fall off the cliff trend for Theo Epstein. He lives off good moves by the… https://t.co/yP8wD2kxAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WomensAusOpen @GrangeGolf @LPGA @ALPGtour Some one needs to get her a driver that fits her.  I bet if she got a dr… https://t.co/KBb7z9h8WT]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Ross situation is weird trade value is still somewhat there cause you can blame coaching on his faults, if he… https://t.co/4DXcWeQ7Ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if I have to cancel my spring break in St Thomas because I broke my ankle 🙄 fml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChronBrianSmith #1 priority sign this young man https://t.co/NDVT1CCHBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@echenikeeee @ComoNTvoyAKerer 😳😳😳😳😳😳se le enganchó el cassette.....😳😳😳😳mandarlo a Rosario que allí hay mucho reparapsiques😝😝😝😝😝😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfterHoursCBS @blazerwheels @ALawRadio @trailblazers @okcthunder I really hope you get to do play by play some day… https://t.co/Shk9LNAE0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xstycat @TuckerCarlson It's easy to say things, it's much harder to prove them. I'd love to see his evidence, but… https://t.co/Qf4z32nJCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro why was i talking mad shit today bout them boys today and then i wake up to the warriors getting blown out💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two #acrylic #inkdrops in #water #notacomposite  - - - - #liquidphotography #shotonmoment #vibrant @ Nashville, Ten… https://t.co/3SAc6pA1ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannbowlin05 @WPXIScott Thanks Joann! Staying on the group for now. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wstoeckle Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thrille novel? Please check out my author's site and also see the… https://t.co/NNFppyJNp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HumbleBrag - @MSNBC yesterday, #IMPORTANTVILLE by @adamwren today! We definitely have the momentum on our side. Le… https://t.co/MB1sgIavBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @erinelsadunne @SpeakerPelosi Did u see the picture of the girl and her son wanting to come back to Ala… https://t.co/bUvW8aalow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liquor Why would you want to? What health benefits are there? Where did the CBD come from? Hemp or Cannabis. Was i… https://t.co/j5LD7oulQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life changes, people change, it’s the way it works!! Only the real stay true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ADESA Charlotte - @adesaauction in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/EwipHzDNMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmBoy time to tell your #Barrhaven landlord to have the snow mountain removed. You are losing spots in an already small parking lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcjprouty That’s what I’m saying. More star players means more majors coming our way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our cat has lost her balance, like she has vertigo, and is constantly holding her head at a 45 degree angle. Also a… https://t.co/9V90ThVjVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoUnitedFans @FsharpAsharp @flashyandy @andygreder @EthanFinlay13 He looks lost out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatclouthier tía Tatis, neta esto también se va perdonar? Neta no ha llegado el presidente que de verdad castigará… https://t.co/BuiIM7dyhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck tonight to the Tri County Vikings competitive cheer team, which competes in the Div. 3 state finals for t… https://t.co/3IVBlWJhHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R_Whiskey @gaye_gallops @11ForTexas If Christians did that they be arrested because they offended somebody]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, father and son had the same taste in eyeglass frames. Can these be acquired at @WarbyParker??]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what happens when you sign a franchise-altering player. I’m really excited to see this team play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bandupJono You only feel that way cuz black men don’t cheat however I have a lot of fun doing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Insomniac_Tink Just now seeing this but shiid i appreciate it 💯 always gotta keep it G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acakes421 Hang in there. If it's meant to be, fantastic,if not you will heal. You're being clean is the most impor… https://t.co/0EZUPUQBeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a massive difference between telling the truth and telling people what they want to hear.  The challenge i… https://t.co/G6X9EulU5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot that can go wrong with this. That being said, if we can develop a legitimately objective AI, that ca… https://t.co/vYXCra0Ey3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wander and ponder how life can be fonder. 🚶‍♂️ #adidas #hypebeast #love #art #ootd #bape #photooftheday #hype… https://t.co/fq7SEdUtaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @NHLAlumniProAm to learn more about this awesome organization. raumatic Brain Injury (TBI) is an epidemic wi… https://t.co/4d46JBBDXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuakerValleyMS @quakervalley @QVMSAsstPrinc @SusanGentileQV @DrAlovesQVSD @surloffa @QVHSPrincipal Thanks for hosting us today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to explain why I love @SashaBanksWWE and @itsBayleyWWE so much https://t.co/r6sjvETtmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKeeStory Now you have to explain to 99.9999% of the people on Twitter who Gene Fowler was. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elcompitv @Rayados @TigresOficial @RafaDato2 @Carlos_Ledezma @ReneFdz @PedroPinaLoredo @MemoriaFutbol_… https://t.co/UXbLjaczYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWoodward40 Mikah Johnson jr - class of 2020 -Newark Eastside - He also can do it on the defensive end as well… https://t.co/8qSsyLI0Sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it shows how strong the @BTCC has become plus social media gives everyone an opinion..  I admit it’s becomi… https://t.co/9ncGPYcLfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seniorday #elon #elonmbb @elonmenshoops steven.santaana elonphanatics @elonphoenix  photos by: @devo1906 @ Elon Un… https://t.co/oM5OYdLU9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaElenaArce6 Ya se vivo en California pero varias de mis sobrina han ido ala universidad por allá y nos mandaba… https://t.co/4tAv9NeVpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love stopping here during all seasons to check out everything below. #Trucking #beautyinnature #Oregon #cabbagehill https://t.co/ip1mZvfbYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt Your story is not helping a community that was just destroyed with 23 dead. If they wanted Trump to… https://t.co/99J9SQtKXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RottenAl @Latrilife @NBCSPhilly @Wendys Team chemistry is a funny thing. Boston , Philly and the Lakers are three… https://t.co/K7FVGYvwrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stefan_Keyes @ctvottawa @CFRAOttawa @CTVOttMornLive Wahoo! It should be ready in time to meet the completed stage… https://t.co/m4oOyfbm1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ontem tomei um tombo “dis costas” estatelado numa lane inteiramente congelada. Ao contrário do que eu esperava, o t… https://t.co/XUOJ8Ex9pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingofQueens13 It really takes you that long to raid the booze section?  😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliLake @jaketapper Why are we still listening to ANYONE on @Foxnews apart from @ShepSmithNews ? Why do so many pe… https://t.co/KUnXyFcM4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Center for American Progress pounds Trump over GM layoffs: A liberal policy group is rolling out a… https://t.co/JWzd3Y3PgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Japanese Level 2: Done. Kanji, verbs, and conjugation? Definitely pushed my ability to learn a new language at an i… https://t.co/GpwYFx86WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_lynch22 I was just pissed man. 30 seconds in? It sucked. Haha. Thanks for being decent I appreciate it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to invent new ways to do things. I wonder what this might grow up to be? Check out Sign of the F… https://t.co/VKcmL4POqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man had my first bomb last night. That shit will break your soul! Time to start writing a lot more.  #comedy #comedians #bomb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating yet frightening all at once. #AI #ArtificialIntelligence  https://t.co/h7VwNsiYkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gonna go ahead and put this out there because i know I can’t be the only one who feels this way, but... I was… https://t.co/7qOIcON1iG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BETTY20327692 @HackerShane Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshJostes @MattMunjoy @MFHSAthletics And don’t forget the others he’s trained that work for companies like Boeing… https://t.co/1hH6mFMKB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieJaneDuff @BadaBing52 Like swallowing a dozen live tape worms after going through treatment to eradicate them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The industry churned out 100 billion pieces of clothing for 7 billion people in 2015.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[toxicnatos ShizNit (Seat Belt Watch Strap,) grey with the sangin.instruments #atlas and black PVD #kinetic; one, th… https://t.co/CU4IBsq6nJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know parents would be mad at you for growing up??????? It’s like ‘you can’t stay here forever’ then you st… https://t.co/LkWBGfPjQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love's Theme Love Unlimited Orchestra https://t.co/n34u8XxEXP A few years later, Orleans used the same melody for… https://t.co/wCUdgJ56Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Perks of Being a Wallflower is such an important book/movie. If you don’t agree, block me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never wanna have to take another one of these pics ever. @ Street Mobb South Ent. https://t.co/Fx0zYnRVBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUalreadyawake @Evelynne24 @DavidMilley @anna_938 @rossw04 @Danbalkwill1 @HomeWorldof @canadaunited1 @SteveMilley3… https://t.co/UeZhe0Imth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ijebu_Edoboy Lmao, 60kobo 😂😂please unwatch this nonsense, and I hope this is not the same gbadamosi guy running fo… https://t.co/6h6UdXTqTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today while filming, @chrismelberger said we had to reshoot a scene because he got my balding head in frame and kne… https://t.co/A5ihzOT0s8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Blustery Day didn't Blow in any Tiggers, but We are Now Saturated with Robins! #HappySpring #NeverLost https://t.co/WCHLJlktwN]]></document></documents></author>