<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookboost #readme #circleofbooks #bookreviews Come join Rave Review Book Club as we search for our "p… https://t.co/gMETlBQ32g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itz_yahboipetey @Ariana_Arnoldd @cam3r00ny @DJPauliY @CryptoPopsicle @miababy37 So manny people get abortions when… https://t.co/eF7moJKXxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwesternMarc Hi Marc.  The original x ray doesn’t show a break but they are having a radiologist look.  I think… https://t.co/sJ92ejvV4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving this new shirt by my friend @peabodraps 🙌🏾 https://t.co/0b5UYG2088]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView @JayInslee Canadians care about who is "running" your country. 🇨🇦🇺🇲#DumpTrump Seriously, climate change no… https://t.co/Ac8T5SifcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday! Just remember #ladies - you are #strong, you are #powerful, and you are #beautiful a… https://t.co/AVb2rxXrdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy’s little frog 🐸 ❤️ @ Minneapolis, Minnesota https://t.co/V82yDkaCHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was exhausted! So worth it and a reliever much needed ❤️💆🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/JNcingmEvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wtfjag @RealityTrashh Shari and Javen are 25 but everyone else is 28-35 so it’s time to really make mature decisio… https://t.co/YmVrbYrmp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonRockets @TheofficialEG10 @CapelaClint @JHarden13 @CP3 @Esther188rod  GREAT LINE UP GET IT GOING CAPELLA TUC… https://t.co/r58LQEEoiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's easy for former pols to do that but the GOP who took bribes, are being blackmailed by Trump/Russians, and pand… https://t.co/jVPqKYEAIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Sounds like a lot of bullhock double talk. You're going to jail. Oh and your father raped your mother.… https://t.co/mmGC8663cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy_kiddo Ha!  I’m sure there will be someone in need of a roommate. Always is. I’ll be on the lookout for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im always surprised when people don’t “get” this! 😽 I’ve always been this way. It comes from being raised by a gram… https://t.co/uANsdAnzDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbyguitar5 It was soo good. Cam and I are definitely breakfast people. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que dificil es ver como el maldito cancer se apodera de un ser querido querido]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my kid’s 4th grade teacher, I love how she puts forth the effort to do more than teach standard curriculum.… https://t.co/XFgECHKFhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jed Bartlett’s speech in Two Cathedrals will always make me cry. #TheWestWing #YouGetHoynes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si me alcanzara mas el tiempo en las mañanas tendría una partida de PUBG antes de levantarme]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a beautiful sight outside the window this week at Kripalu. I’m doing a #writing retreat with other amazin… https://t.co/SFQJHktV7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessMinchin3 Actually parang wala silang gana today. Kahit blocking ni Bea and Kat wala.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datingdecisions The entire damned thing screams “We know this is all in our minds, but do it our way anyway.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday morning affirmation.  Put it out there, do your thing, see what happens.  Where you direct your mindset and… https://t.co/RupXC6IORd]]></document><document><![CDATA[*buys KT tape because my knees are stupid* Cashier: oh do you run?  Me: do I look like the kind of person who would… https://t.co/t9zdC01xxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxnewsradio @JaniceDean Reading and loving her book. Wonder if the MS doctors who were less than patient centered… https://t.co/pFBsTGJCgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @mercedesschlapp Would love to hear the conversation you two christians have with your kids about selling… https://t.co/xOaunetTbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToughGuyMankas @Tonithecat32 @buddy_gizmo @1gingerbeauty @deborah26449389 @AngusMcPussPuss @MoetBlindCat… https://t.co/wPIViwgVOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just think how many great songs wouldn’t have been recorded if we’d stopped pitching it after the third “no”. If yo… https://t.co/w98GoYlpqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSShawn17 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump They are lying because trump is a 🍊💩🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KakiGRon @ElyangelicaNews La música no será aqui, y es necesario tener dinero a la mano e inmediato cuando estos d… https://t.co/0yWdbRG4uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshly picked bangle.  #resin #resinmolds #resinart #resincasting #diy #witchy #jewelry #bracelet #bangle #glitter… https://t.co/PdCtnkv8fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xo_rebeccajane He’s so crafty and sneaky! And ruthless! When you find out that he keeps the guy that cut his duck… https://t.co/artb5V3ghs]]></document><document><![CDATA[SALE ITEMS! CLICK: https://t.co/lAjWO9cab3 #JEWELRYCANDLES https://t.co/ClFRYQRqVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just referenced a childhood meme with my bestie and said “perfecto!!” out loud in a child-like voice while at wor… https://t.co/e0qOVDNEFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so happy any time I see a story update on Instagram in green because it makes me feel like I have actual frie… https://t.co/NIMfizn8h7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just devastated! Luke was my first young woman celebrity crush! I was a diehard Beverly Hills 90210 fan! I just… https://t.co/KbhQfvmc3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 No.  Spot on.  Read that Kushners are in market for $ with a B to buy real estate in VA.  #CrimeSyndicate #SwampCreatures]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalPetDay #WeLoveRudy ❤️❤️🥰 @ Scarsdale, New York https://t.co/cwMzAGqKD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching this @DatingAround show on @Netflix_CA for hours and I can’t stop gonna be dead tomorrow. It’s s… https://t.co/6nyUlrezgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature Remember Rin tin tin. I grew up watching dogs as best friends. Good times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catholic's do not approve of killing newborns. Ashes on your head will not save you. The gates are close, but the e… https://t.co/Lt0k0uz2GR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since we asked my 5 year old sister if she’s seen the scary Momo thing on YouTube, she hasn’t been touching her Ipad as much 😂😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NWAKissAPig2019 #StopDiabetes #Hogstock @ John Q. Hammons Convention Center https://t.co/wuIoyTEisB]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 miles to start Monday off. My legs were still really sore from strength training and as you can see, my times suf… https://t.co/XwXhSaJ0TO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop 2 on the #RunToGlam for the @mptf #NightBefore.  Ran into some friends from @funnyordie getting ready as well!… https://t.co/Iizhc0qPM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately, when I turn off the lights, I can hear him sing..  lately, it’s my favorite music at night..  the singing o… https://t.co/wpXLo40ufq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on, ladies..:🤦🏾‍♀️🤦🏾‍♀️🤦🏾‍♀️  Controversial skin creams containing mercury are banned. But it didn't take long… https://t.co/Zn79rMp1ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish @HWDSB took the same stance you do over in Toronto @tdsb . Take a look and see my tweets about my special ne… https://t.co/ZbYfMia1Xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichMillington This doesn’t surprise me at all. The value that our community members’ feedback can bring back to o… https://t.co/kX1Xdn8MQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @ddale8 The POTUS is not allowed to have 9800 inconsistencies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else sing pop songs to their animals? Like the song, but for your animals? RN I’m singing a kicking ver… https://t.co/r6N2VNdDiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I advocated for veganism in committee despite representing a nation that relies so heavily on animal agriculture/is… https://t.co/LqrbSowCCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in Michigan! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Tolling Analyst at BASF #Manufacturing]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly my dad does this all the time and never fails to remind me that I’m beautiful even when I look like a 21 y… https://t.co/rIg7v0kiHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarFarrAway @lenfestinst @tylisajohnson @aneripattani @JeseniaDeMoyaC @kristenbalderas Thank you for sharing Stephanie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #fitfam jumped and biked for @american_heart today ❤️ @anytimefitness #aflove #snowworkout #team #coach… https://t.co/xsR23XLmMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please ask New York state to overturn recent abortion expansion laws. https://t.co/eOWsuX7JGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We voted for you Mr Trump but we also voted against the MSM who tried to direct the American peopl… https://t.co/VnNbuIgEnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day from my workshop! 💕💕💕 Did you hear I’m having a sale?  Choose “LOVE” as a coupon code when sho… https://t.co/FKtwbKZIZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arched back, deep stroke, white wine, weed smoke, that's my best combination]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @JJohnsonLaw Also, a organization that doesn’t share the debate questions and hide relative news stories, to swing an election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campfirewood and I are going to see X and the Violent Femmes at @CainsBallroom in May. Who’s in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday #2 of Tri-DAC auditions! 5 hours down, about 5 to go! @tridistrictarts #tridac2019 @ Richland Northeast Hi… https://t.co/W8DffInKsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:30am, and I just finished Turtles All the Way Down by @johngreen. And I just feel so not alone. There aren’t… https://t.co/kbqLPJBpwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized why I always say “drive safe” to everyone...   My mom always say it to me in Vietnamese when I left… https://t.co/2yuckOn97Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[well @judahandthelion catch me front row this halloween in st. paul! been dreaming of the day i’d get vip tickets t… https://t.co/ok9fpVmCfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s not as decentralized as all the crypto lovers want to romantically believe 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thizizezra Bitchhhhhhhh. I’m back home and now you’re back in Ohio?? -_-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and check me out! https://t.co/UIiUGKTe83   #blog #blogger #onlyfans #beautiful #bookwithme #website #ashley… https://t.co/owJmPGnjYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanderVVtm @RealityTVBliss @chandrapntx @GraceIn2021 Sorry but what does sm  stand for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorTomUdall Why is it that your ‘go-to” is always more legislation?  Don’t we already have laws in place??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mclayton1970 Thank you. I moved home to take care of my parents 2 years ago. I knew each day was borrowed time. It… https://t.co/VQqJ6HnpvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happened today. This isn’t the end. This is just a massive sinkhole in #Knoxville &amp; it’s growing.… https://t.co/AuLYgnFEsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of my problem is that a good 75% of my brain is memes and I have to hush that part while I’m interacting with… https://t.co/ihM1w7UcNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚📖ESTE SAN VALENTIN, REGALA CULTURA, REGALA LIBROS 📖📚 🐘 #Elefantesamarillos  🐘⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️ 78 páginas repletas de amo… https://t.co/FZaLdkbTi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austinnreeed I end up cancelling a bunch I’m too impatient lol. They usually take minimum 7 mins if it’s a long video]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pumpkin curry (@ Orrapin Thai in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/hGTbb2mHqv https://t.co/dUYSzr4Kti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahsaandhall Will this get the same amount of airtime? a timeline of events?  list of interrogated people? see sur… https://t.co/V5Lq0TeGOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of my lunch time walks and this is what I ran into...I am here for all this! #desertlife🌵☀️… https://t.co/e7PeBDqFzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Saturdays, I drink my puppy water in bed. #saturdayvibes #sallylongdog https://t.co/Fd0ng0L6bU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband left me on seen😒 @spadoni_joe #marriedlife https://t.co/oLQ2hpLnNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leather Circle earrings coming! I love experimenting with new shapes 😍 @ Jonesborough, Tennessee https://t.co/2wbombYW25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled for his new station in life! Best wishes for a long and steady decline into, well, possibly stormy weather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching captain marvel in Puerto Rico was such an experience as someone from the far right side of the theatre yel… https://t.co/6RLCysOP76]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weallwearmasks #dapperfoxproductions #pandashortfilm #shortfilm #cinematography #production #biloxi… https://t.co/wi9Nqt5wK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaaizzy it would be an honor to have you @BlueHazeWSISD on March 1st! Students would be forever impacted!… https://t.co/7dEG0DjZdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying that Kath will get it this time. #VoteKathrynBernardo #KCA  @bernardokath https://t.co/HyrMQNt1ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like we are back on the track... And I couldn't have a better night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set the bar for the new comers joining fitness. It’s about consistency, always!  Music by @DHaileyDirect… https://t.co/mm9gqCY4CN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexsMom123 @TCDSB @LisaThompsonMPP @MacLeodLisa This isn’t a request from a union. It’s from the school board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀 A BIG CONGRATULATIONS TO JJ SCHWEPKER !!!! Well deserved!  1. ALL DISTRICT 2. ALL CONFERENCE- 1st Team 3. ALL ACA… https://t.co/0Ne0ZUAwCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of our listing on 582 Trenton Avenue #Cincinnati #OH  #realestate https://t.co/n0zF9mFRwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The conference has an app that prompted me to create a bio.... https://t.co/UsRtzqiinb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blaming “other” stuff such as achohol is a cop out. She needs to take responsibility. But the blame isn’t entirely… https://t.co/TRUzwGYjhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rinnesixpaths_ Nah he was like “WTF YOU LOOKING AT BITCH” like twice and then got up in my face like he was gonna… https://t.co/xh2LEMNIGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is she allowed ? If you did this in her country of origin, in her Government you’d be dragged out and stoned to… https://t.co/EVvN1juFpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️HAPPY VALENTINES DAY EVERYBODY❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu you are amazing! I’m currently on dialysis and not only am humbled by what an amazing human you are, but… https://t.co/frXkBahRsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer All we can do is find out what happened where Russia is concerned and if… https://t.co/zrNVwRNI26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulAnt96956791 @SebGorka @realMikeLindell @CPAC @KayaJones Another creepy scary nut!]]></document></documents></author>