<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@YoungbloodJoe There are plenty of ways to get stability indicators. BBB, references, past work, past clients, time… https://t.co/1I9d6bIjhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm totally going to start using this. I've been typing in the location manually into cmd for directory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @Dollar_Bank https://t.co/6xOzbg8rAR @WRIGHTAUTOGROUP https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/CbczNTjzjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SECNetwork your studio host needs to know that Barry Booker didn’t make it to Fayetteville in time !]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MicrosoftEDU  #NCCE19  Amazing time in the Microsoft Acadamy. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecPompeo Listen...y'all are at all surprised by any of this are you? Perfect fucking timing Mike! How'd that happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vuwildcat07 No, of course not. But Antoine is a better ball handler than Phil. Collin is not coming out of the lin… https://t.co/oU4wnj5uk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to nap soon as I got here on this big bean bag but these kids just had to wake up man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco should come back to the 513 for this @fccincinnati home opener on St. Patty's day. I'm sure I can find a… https://t.co/eAFAcj1UY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusaTariq A life skill my dad gave me for which I will forever be thankful. 🤣🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not really, is like two cars in an highway intersection at high speed in different levels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new @toyota_global Supra at the auto show! Seeing this made it all worth it 😍😍❤️❤️❤️💯 @ Metro Toronto Conventio… https://t.co/aUgTlaiUnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#panicattack #truth #love #belove #express #peoplecanonlyhandlesomuch #reachout #abuseisabuse #nomatterthesource… https://t.co/iDjMOQBkxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say that I am so fortunate to be surrounded by these amazing women. So smart, so beautiful, so lucky!… https://t.co/7h2yVzs957]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJeffreyT Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[MFW I realize I’m only going to get three hours of sleep for the third night in a row https://t.co/d6XHzZBh5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump LOOK!!!!  CSPAN3    Live!   Special counsel Mueller... house rules committee hearing      Rep Mich… https://t.co/ZhM6FRSFHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSpec Loved Harry..All those years on defence for brutal NYR teams...with his salt and pepper hair and classy st… https://t.co/Kaz9nS8qBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[They couldn’t help but agree.  Just concentrate on the obvious calls. The ones that were missed were obvious live a… https://t.co/5Od99AjfdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps in homage to (mostly) 1990s band Blues Traveler, there have been four walks called in this game. #1990sNight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakehounshell @BarackObama "I'll have more flexibility after the election." Obama's message to Russia's Putin cau… https://t.co/vxZxT4o30S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clydetrey Perreira and Pogba bossing the midfield...it’s pretty ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[MINI MORRIS 1960 🇬🇧 classic_minis 🇲🇽ESTE AUTO 🚘 ES MUY ESPECIAL 🥇SU PROPIETARIO FUE EL MEJOR EMPRESARIO DE LA HISTO… https://t.co/53xRWJLNDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Castro needs to nip the attack in the bud and continue dragging Bernie on other issues ... 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chase_alan10 @SlanderOfficial @DruizDanny @billy_banning @codyjhaha ❤️ u boiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heater is running in Estes Park today. @ Estes Park, Colorado https://t.co/9Z46jed5gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vinyl, vinyl, vinyl —as far as the eye can see!! @ City of Richardson Civic Center https://t.co/RRu6hSTeeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every good and experienced coach goes by this.  If you want to play, these traits lead to productivity, which force… https://t.co/UnCJRPbj8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I stop my twitter feed from jumping to the top while I am reading an interesting post? I can never find it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but if a good chunk of your sport’s games, matches if you will, end 0-0 then rule changes are in order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #Eden! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/LtAH0gLjPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CONANP_mx  @SimonLevyMx @DuelesMexico_ @DiariodePuebla @Noticaribe @vicfc7 @CHEQUI51 @SilviaCarlova @BARCENAMIGUEL… https://t.co/8lwg3xKZPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisyjewel I might not have a lot,but I still give...it satisfying to my #Soul...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btvscharmedgirl @Unknownfear Yeah I had moments of shipping both. I'm a Clarke fan first when its all said and don… https://t.co/fry4BK6dqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[VTrust Airdrop get 1000 VTR for a few simple tasks. https://t.co/SFgkzi6aMx #airdrop #bounties https://t.co/ERu6FzfvAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ncrTNREFDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped metallica from the school roof to demonstrate gravity and they splattered everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @benshapiro Who the hell could be jealous of Illinois?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam Gagner goes home to Edmonton. Traded by Vancouver for Ryan Spooner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYIslanders observations tonight. We need help scoring, Mcdavid is very good and Lehner and Greiss right now are c… https://t.co/hgsgxh9BtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porlagoma Me gusta tu trino. Pero me surge una pregunta. Las bicicletas tambien las ordenan desde el dogout?  Yo p… https://t.co/CBySeahovl]]></document><document><![CDATA[dam... i need to reload my itunes acct!! im behind 2 @iamcardib songs 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verily Blog:Launching a powerful new screening tool for diabetic eye disease in India  https://t.co/gjNRaBZ41F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My night is finally here!! Can't wait to see my eleventh @Cirque show, #LUZIA https://t.co/eyKaRmcUJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[At my plow site in Forks Township, PA, heavy rain and freezing rain still, temp 32°, I would say .25" accretion… https://t.co/eiTvAyJkmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smb #entrepreneurs #CTO #CTO #Mom #Dad #wife #husband #careeradvice #friends 8 signs you are seriously overdoing i… https://t.co/aL7ElHRE9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I commented on a random fb post saying I got carts for sale and someone HMU within 5 minutes lmfao watch me go to jail rn ion even care]]></document><document><![CDATA[To prepare for the health needs of the future, we need to revisit the criteria for how we pipeline, recruit and pre… https://t.co/OLyteieEi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JP8185 I long for the day when those words will actually excite me in anticipation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich Your right of course, but the jilted girlfriend act is getting tiresome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Infamous_MoMo If I get a job that allows me to do the work that I want and pays what I’m asking, yes. Lol! I don’t mind coming back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the differences in what are considered "male" &amp; "female" sweatpant joggerd pisses me off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm feeling confused.  Does being in favor of free trade make you left wing or right wing these days?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angamardana” means gaining complete mastery over the limbs organs and other parts of the body. #SadhguruInPhilly… https://t.co/k0gk7mavLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBarchard @philly_danny @WIPPodcasts @SmarksStripes @RealKevKeenan @EricSGolden @Radiodotcom Two million networ… https://t.co/KoJ2y4IZOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dudes, snow is actually accumulating in my backyard. I’ve lived here for over ten years. This is the first snow.… https://t.co/hQFzHRBS7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[28 fucking points in the paint. What an absolutely abysmal defensive effort from Duke. The sad thing is that Coby W… https://t.co/6KwDfITIlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw He only wacked a few family members. I guess Trump would same of the Menendez brothers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendricklasaint Yeah I feel like my body already in recovery mode. Shouldn’t push it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow, I never get tired of the joy and inspiration that comes from the simple act of dropping the kids off at sc… https://t.co/6sRLYtMZCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_kings_ @Off2Nowhere @mtracey Gosh. She doesn't like Saudi Arabia.   How about the Iran Deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit runs down main street,,I can say here lately https://t.co/PrlRcdPSJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Stone and Paul Manafort...Doubles Partners in the Prison Tennis Club. ?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at @boscoesbar in #Columbus #Ohio #maleentertainers hosted by Paige Passion featuring Tyler Devereaux, Ster… https://t.co/THkiSCTBEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the @shanedawson Chuck E Cheese thing. And Damn. Also the story with #BrittaniLouiseTaylor, OOF! Intense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one for the queen 👑 👸🏽 “Kittyiana” - @TaylorHing 🌹🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🌟🥰 https://t.co/COJUSU2DjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look I’m not saying I love Shaq more than most things in life but I love Shaq more than most things in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealgroger @the_dol @KonstantineinCA @thelaurakoski @avngangel @frankieindc @ChelseaClinton We are talking abou… https://t.co/T6xvLNChfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to remember when he wasn’t a finalist for the @JohnMackeyAward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyGrewal @miss_speech How is it weird? You know how Republicans are worried about stolen elections? How many hav… https://t.co/dTxwJElzsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@proust1974 @Von__Thom @McFaul @JudithROhman W eroded our reputation a bit, and while Obama helped, our role in the… https://t.co/W7qWnyAX2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wubaseball35 I would agree. Need to get the youth more involved by watching/playing the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chacabanaboga #life #style #chacabanas #chacabana #guayaberas #guayabera #blazer #diseños #guayaberastyle… https://t.co/yNtISqFljP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRMovieNews @SpecSpidey_ It’s a great scene. Seeing Harry and Peter fight was a good one to start the film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano - Sorry to hear about Katherine Helmond.  I loved her on Soap and Who’s the Boss ❤️ https://t.co/rWfRwOvRoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ButtonsGiraffe He can come work for me. Elmo can’t type at all.  But then again he is only 3 1/2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t have said “officially.”  Just hearing from a source... also a friend of mine who works for CPD heard extr… https://t.co/yxsC7oIiVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner You sir are a joke! Always have been. NO ONE, especially Virginians wants to hear you regurgitate Hillaryanisms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The internet doesn’t have any business hours!  You don’t have any opening or closing hours! You can control each ti… https://t.co/J7EN6nOhI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished the bicep/triceps sets and finally filling the #XL gym tops 💪🏼 #Gainz #GymMotivation @MartynFord_]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is exactly why I would never subscribe. Is this the proposed football association for rules in football for th… https://t.co/5k68on90ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TairyT47 Feliz inicio de semana a la doncella del tránsito de NU Nj y Connecticut Tairy🚦🚥✨🚦🗽🌹❤️😘 https://t.co/EoXRHKEffg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @giddy81370604 Another moving story about kind, considerate people We need more stories like  this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeypotato1 @GeraldineLewis @Caliicoder3 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @DonaldJTrumpJr @KatrinaPierson… https://t.co/oTHiJoGUq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktdenise I wasn't going to insult you with a Foster's or a mass-market American lager, I was going to buy something good..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DENISE_RICHARDS plus i don’t need $1000😁 #RHOBH #rhobh9 https://t.co/LtaE7MyXeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aeropuerto Internacional de Monterrey - @aeropuertodemty in Apodaca, NL https://t.co/I3xnMvs4Q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSCLE Is 60 or 61 mph the official peak wind gust at #Youngstown today? I've seen 2 sources.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy b day to the big bro @DoctorHGoebel. Here’s a little throwback to when we kicked it with @GeorgeWBush__ https://t.co/35keXnQFFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride is taking  care of something. (@ Checksmart - Check Cashing and Payroll Advance in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/UVwqLRJERR]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all my Texas people... got to meet sentedcruz with the guys! #SB2k19 @ Sea Island, Georgia https://t.co/vbVB8SDmOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseThorn @jtkantor @Section10Pod I’m not sure, Jessy/Jessi/Jessé. But they didn’t.   So to improve the situation… https://t.co/rMRfXdJ6lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’allllll I am telling you- put out there what you need from the universe, have quiet conversation and connection w… https://t.co/REA1cidaWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockytopinfl @BigBoyVol @MrAndyNgo It doesn’t help the problem, but by God there is a problem and the GOP will NOT… https://t.co/oW2YmYinYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- what do you think about taking money to see the books? C- no Sari- why not? C- this is not a service.  I am n… https://t.co/JR0LFiFHTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling very honored to learn that our Annals article on avoiding peri-intubation hypoxia was included in the A… https://t.co/ZVTFViUo48]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a feeling @MikeMGTV is going to shine being in charge of this party 🎉 #lohanbeachclub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pastor_AngeloJ  Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinkNews This would be more persuasive if you used those hand-clapping emojis between every word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chazzus 😭😭😭 you right I think that’s my cue to log off for the night 😔✌🏼]]></document></documents></author>