<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Such an amazing program. Sign up for alerts! #bringthemhome #missingkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally push @QuinnXCII’s music on everyone because it’s so damn great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you so much to everyone who came out! so grateful for all of the support everyone has given us in this time o… https://t.co/lanFkMn5IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our State Finalists in Readers Theatre, 4th “Barbie Instagram”and 2nd “I Was There”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was such a blast but this 4 hours of sleep thing is killing me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope people in the future get their shit together and get the masterpiece Year 3000 by the @jonasbrothers to #1 o… https://t.co/vWtcxBw345]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snow maybe on the way but it won’t stop me from doing a quick #cardio &amp; #abs #workout. #dedication #hardwork… https://t.co/M0uGiahyQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guatemala dark roast. #Minneapolis #coffee #hamradio #DMR #DSTAR (at @DunnBrosCoffeeS in Minneapolis, MN)… https://t.co/FKX8tDeNDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanMellul @SteveLemongello @PattyMurray Al Franken talked in his last book about how his staff kept him grounded.… https://t.co/FldkSyGbwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CayLibrary @vetements_slav @cauboidoespasso @violaslayvis @Moderate_Rebels If Trump put Bernie Sanders in jail. Cr… https://t.co/jNutP8FzsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also 3 walks. I know Noah’s off his game today but this umpire’s zone SUCKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say all the infrastructure contracts for future building that went to Trump's donors be cancelled at once. And lock him up for god's sake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dear friend of mine committed suicide last week. I’m heartbroken and pissed off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 🏀Game Day Black Knights !7:00 vs Johnson Co. Wear black &amp; gold. Be loud!#regiontourney @theCDNation @CDHSHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I told him as I exited the train  he should order brunch for dinner. Life is too short, y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taco truck FTW! #TacoMonday (@ Figueroa's Taquería in Woodburn, OR) https://t.co/W5rRdIKbFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowling. Because America. @ Back Alley Bowl and Grill https://t.co/pXqPOnpoYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big laughs when the old WSA group gets together! https://t.co/0tweITXfMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking miss @samil0u 😭 my ass needs to hop on a plane to Maryland ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DonaldJTrumpJr @LaraLeaTrump @EricTrump Happy birthday Kimberly to a fellow Pisces/ March baby!  💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweeted bcuz Pirro is such a hypocrite and this is evidence. So far no Democrats have been accused of “minuteman… https://t.co/CQoBT10w3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johleee @creativecusp @chaninicholas Too much Scorpio in my chart to post birth chart pics for the world to see. I'm too mysterious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/IX9ne8jwvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Well, I don't know.  I guess I will have to Google for more Info as to what Party he belongs to before I answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @DEVINPOLK3 you have been a big part of these last 7 years with #WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademicLeader Thank you and I will try to post one each day.  No promises.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just you wait, our luck is going to change tonight! Go Black Tigers! 🖤💛🐾🐯🏀💛🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @GoatJerseys @PhilHecken @exposhistory @Montreal_Expos @achs_fred @JoeDeCamara @JDaniel2033… https://t.co/D5QJ4R2WRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTuglife656 @YouTube Absolutely believe every word of this. The masses call it conspiracy theory. They cannot t… https://t.co/cT4Nw9LvQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenzieGrimes20 So great seeing you this past weekend. Thx Kenz!  We sure miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on ARMY’s!! Let’s do this for our boys! 💜💜💜💜💜💜💜 @BTS_twt #SoompiAwards #TwitterBestFandom #TeamBTS https://t.co/92YG3lHog0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since 2007, California has suffered 11 of the top 20 most destructive wildfires in its history, according to Cal Fi… https://t.co/9aLGSPoeAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your girl looks pretty good for having a cold and getting 4 hours of sleep 🙃  . . . #mondayssuck #mondayselfie… https://t.co/t7T9Pv8RqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews I would certainly like to know the answer to that. I mean, I thought she was suppose to be gone already… https://t.co/IOiPJBRO9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people try to claim short term disability for having weight loss surgery 🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️ literally you’re out for max 2 weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump put @RepMattGaetz to threaten Cohen, and sit in on the hearing, on a committee he's not on to stare at Cohen.… https://t.co/zSIXXAJ6N8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: He was convicted of a US sex crime. Then the king of Saudi Arabia got involved  https://t.co/oKBqaDF2Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mnyka Ay ño!! Soy de Sonora! Hermosillo! Jaja creo que si estamos lejitos!! 😂😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know why our zija smartmix is so beneficial w/ it's insulin loaded chicory root natural pre-biotic? Here's i… https://t.co/Yrdj46Fxdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️$12,000 PRICE REDUCTION⚠️  This spacious 2-story conquistador Spanish style estate is absolutely stunning! Locate… https://t.co/VDwvoSEX41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyHChiefGen @NathanDGoodwin @RootsTechConf I will make sure to drop by his booth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggjourneys @curiositydotcom Yes! I’m so tight on my budget when it comes to everything ... but I hardly ever quest… https://t.co/Yw8OvzjpNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open the box...figure out how it works...@AliefScience @Alexander_AISD #PLC #handsonlearning https://t.co/fPU2EVDRxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Iluvinspireu @roads2 @ClockworkHamma @AnwarManwar004 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Peeperpea29… https://t.co/O6At5oY9Em]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be the first time in 27 years that I won’t have a kid with me for an Oscar party. I tell you what, it’s f… https://t.co/mE7Vj9cDdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy . . . Haré una pausa  Tal vez la noche  Me traiga alegrías o tristezas  Las cuales me recordara  Que estoy viva… https://t.co/5BI7FkRLLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see @ImAngelaBassett hit the #oscars red carpet 👏🏾 https://t.co/QW4ctKWBnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP congressman jumps into critical Alabama Senate race https://t.co/6zr4W1CK2l via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!  That wind was loud last night.  Did it wake you up? #inwx #indy #4yourmorning @CBS4Indy https://t.co/7li4yRVi45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think it’s creepy when someone who doesn’t follow you watches your ig story]]></document><document><![CDATA[lrt I will not comment directly, because no one really needs to know I have eye freckles too. But I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Monday New Week NewGoals #bekindalways #authenticity #positive #love #loveothers #buildthemup #dogood… https://t.co/6btT0YuOjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMcmurderer @derekcarrqb @AB84 Rookie weapons. Yeah that’s a gamble for real- and, incidentally, you now have som… https://t.co/IS5Df4SjuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems hopeless because the enemy of our souls wants us to think it is hopeless... We need to commit to truly kno… https://t.co/tAN1z692Q9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMHolmes0428 @essenviews If WE in the US were able to see the "confession" and pleading of Otto for his life, on T… https://t.co/IwNMy06bwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[NISD Rodeo Day @NISDLockeHill #yeehaw #thisislockehill #ThisIsNorthside https://t.co/EvzwOfKT7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedmatrix @leesheriff Come on people! Do your work... make it a Meme, then it will get looked at!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyLittau #notallhumans  In all seriousness, I cannot bear watching someone being humiliated even in a fictiona… https://t.co/0z2aNJ60o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’ve decided to leave for NY next spring. Going to KSU has been awesome, but I’m not being true to myself by ignoring my passion,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASAKennedy wow your lines are terrible and disorganized this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c8linrosee We literally barely went to Morro Bay beach but shoot catch me at Avila still 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryancallen Funny Bone Cincinnati has posted a really old bio for you advertising your appearance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakewenning10 Everyone should know I was 100% joking. I am not this dumb. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @Alcioni5 @TereOrt51687394 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @janaplauen @roberta_lanzoni… https://t.co/O1mPgThfuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAcePugh @pdoty64 @thehill I see. But its kind of an open secret if youre an 80's cold war baby old head like me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m just so happy because skz and bts aren’t having their comebacks all in one month skz is in like two weeks and b… https://t.co/OFFmI9sdyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie when Gordon Hayward had his injury last year u saw him playing on the court months after. But when Lonzo goe… https://t.co/w3nvrbJzvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just prayed to Saint Anthony so I could find my keys. How’s your Wednesday morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day have a Blessed Lovely Day with your Love ones . My Twitter brothers and sisters in Christ ( F… https://t.co/F0TQI3sMwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELCOME New Followers! @FordeEstate @HomeRunPest @Realty_Leads @ChrysteeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, we return to church! michellesthroni will be back again at ecstaticdancenyc! Come dance yourself into blis… https://t.co/RB5aQYzQ33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Rancho Mirage, CA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/f5SQjK19cg #IStandWithPP #RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that NYC is making it clear that hair discrimination IS racial discrimination. Our natural hair styles should… https://t.co/WnABeq3tzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tranganhdong I just need Netflix to stop being COWARDS and add all of the old ones like Princess and the Pauper and Swan Lake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewRikli I see as of today they have updated all summer camps with new dates, starting June 3rd!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard a man use the term “honey-dos” today. Petition to rename them: “You-live-here-pitch-ins” “Normal non-binary… https://t.co/zTfPTbsuQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it the weekend yet??? #BuaNights #EastVillage #NYC @ East Village, Manhattan https://t.co/yXqD1Z4LPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah fam- when Laine snored last time (he only does it when he’s REALLY tired) I gooogled if you can hold a pillow o… https://t.co/WAfWG1Nqe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Yonder Alonso For 1 Great Year! Cleveland Will Always Love You Man! Good Luck In Chicago Man! https://t.co/3RADHFIe9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaiah Cotrell (2020) makes a move to the hoop for 2 more — feed from Will McClendon — @bigfella702 @BG_Basketball… https://t.co/Vc260BELRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *enjoying my food* My boyfriend : “Oh shit look over there!”   Also my boyfriend :]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign your getting older. Hmmm your granddaughter thinks she can boss you around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got candy from my friends today that just said “sorry I’m your valentine” and that is true friendship]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing group of women!  It was an honor to be included! Thank you @USCCFBiz4Good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luv that they didn’t check my ticket Luv that i didn’t activate it either]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @itsjojosiwa on getting 9 million subscribers. 🎀 https://t.co/pKTO6Wgx1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥💥Flash Jamie Poll: Will Sen. Bernie Sanders be the 2020 Democratic Party nominee for President? 💥💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to start Wishtree with Mrs. Richardson @StoryLibrary 😊#TeamStory https://t.co/UwZDMnXaa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Motivation!  Everyone knows I love Toes To Bar! Spice them up with a medicine ball. Find a weight you can us… https://t.co/iITRhp5lGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't Miss Shop Priceless's $300 Giveaway have you entered yet? https://t.co/tedoC5bwZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chantibaby_ @PayBalances Paying For My Own Insurance Would Practically Make The 58% Increase Not Worth It UNLESS T… https://t.co/a9MJ5JuaBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a perfect day to release the Official #FIFAWWC Poster. A day to celebrate the incredible women on… https://t.co/HmJmZHlKYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating KSU Hockey Players Mitchell and Mason Bright’s 21st Birthday at the Golden Knights Game @GoldenKnights . Go Knights!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldReepicheep @ex_harvest In a court of law, the victim is considered a witness. I was a juror in a child sexual a… https://t.co/FvXya3tYd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SenateDems My God! Do you listen to yourself? How do you know it’s fake?… https://t.co/GCBDUtRgo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis How can the few decent reporters who work at Fox want to be affiliated with such an organization?  Seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've done it 14 times and they've always come out newly minted and enamored fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIERNES Y LOS REYES DE LAS ENCINAS LO SABEN 😈💛🙌 @dannapaola #MiguelBernardeau https://t.co/H78whhEFt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday we got cozy with a stuffed friend while reading our own autobiographies in our pjs. #theGVBarbershop… https://t.co/iwe7ozcnDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite trope is the stock film character, "The Manic Pixie Dream Girl." #TropeADope]]></document></documents></author>