<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A LA CAZA DE ROJITOS ESBIRROS ENCHUFAOS Y DEDESTRUCTORES DE VENEZUELA. Vive en EEUU pide asilo para el y su familia… https://t.co/NdPDjKJ00G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerHydrick @Jworks17 Miss st will be alright. Finding wins in tight games is a good sign early]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apblingo @kendraswork @jetset1990 @jbranham502 @l_ofrance @craigcombs @southpaw89 @spidadmitchell @NCAA Go to the… https://t.co/IhmcGUMpIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaRubicon I've had this kind of discussion with theists. If their god is omnipotent then it can do anything. Eve… https://t.co/DdeNzpcCFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWieck Shomar Shabbos!  They don't turn on the oven, they don't handle money, and they sure as sh!t don't f*cking draw!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the realest! Been at it since elementary 🤞🏻😾@seanyb246 https://t.co/uHq1CSIzjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tolano67 Muchas felicidades amigo !!, valió la pena todo tu esfuerzo 👍👍👍💯💯💯💯💯💯💯 https://t.co/PkLNvK0I28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Maybe an Echo will play it, I know the Google thing won't. https://t.co/bvJnrDZuau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordancole23 @aafiron Another two weeks and the whole country will be pulling for the @aafAPOLLOS #stickwithawinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take my breath away is truly a masterpiece! 🥀🥀 @ezi you nailed it on this track 💿💿 THANK YOU for this beautiful val… https://t.co/vSXOzaYY2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one can tell you with 100% certainty the answers to any of these questions. But people will surely attempt to. T… https://t.co/LAkLjD2HHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Echo, everything the light touches is our kingdom 🦁 https://t.co/Z94mvuHeu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying bastard NEEDS to be brought to justice and SOON..... Brrrrrrrrr! #babyitscoldoutside  #groundhoglies… https://t.co/UC1kYo3Zr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[ain’t nothing bad ass about being up this late only opossums and other varmints suppose to be awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone who’s down to go to some baseball games with me, let me know 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis quitarle lis primeros lugares alas chinitas es como querer quitarle un taco al turkey cuando trae hamb… https://t.co/3Xi6RR3Y53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imamofpeace Different opinion is always hate speech for Liberalizm,Socializm,Communizm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBrandt @RosenhausSports He’s working nothing. It’s up to the Steelers where Brown goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way.... "...the executive who was in charge of Apple's insider trading policy himself committed insider trading… https://t.co/lIqJd7ma0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billprady Love that “our” President would visit Alabama and sign a little girls Bible. He’s all about America and it’s people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“National emergency” #bulldogsofinstagram Miami style. People even carried each other on their backs!… https://t.co/MQnJ7PABBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is quite a battle such a close battle with everything on Mount Olympus even more difficult now #TItanGames… https://t.co/mUhypiINWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los últimos maximos goleadores de @Rayados  y @TigresOficial.  Suazo y @10APG  hacen su gol 100 de penal. Que sad… https://t.co/bZtBzbE7cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @Wendys likes this I will streak naked past the @BurgerKing around the corner from me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bicemusic So sorry for you Brian.  You and your family are in my prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Big mistake here in today's climate that person would be supported like no one else has. Because in turn… https://t.co/v2qyQuStBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@08Jayhawk @ChynaJoanLaurer So deserving! Her family has been fighting for it. I am so happy for them today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ferrari from way out. Cuts it to 47-44 and he's one more assist away from a double-double.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so cold out this morning that the metal holding up my apartments balcony is contracting so much it’s making th… https://t.co/GyIkVexaCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eltonofficial I'm hitting on Melania again (the link is to "Artpop") https://t.co/uSa0MuSNlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katbird74 @seaforward @lynnv378 winner-take-all, true blue, NY, my one vote isn’t as important as it could be.  I… https://t.co/GeO4O4XmDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the weather I took a 5:40am flight home from Philadelphia... a 47min flight. I feel more tired than when I d… https://t.co/P2wxXBJrqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Andrew. Enjoy every moment of the early days in spite of the lack of sleep!  It goes fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brightrobert7 @MHMwrites @AOC The smart phone you typed that message on had its earliest development in the space… https://t.co/FI3ppkx9LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Dadeville 8, Tallassee 3  Dadeville grabs a win in the season opener behind the hitting and pitching of Jake… https://t.co/5zgpfzoyTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 Nhưng cổng chật và đường hẹp, khó đi, dẫn đến sự sống thật, thì chỉ có một số ít người tìm được thôi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Youngrapgawd @TonyMackSays Lol I think he means he doesn’t want kids of his own lol wrong wording]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveForHotGirls @Nicolette_Shea You are so think and so sexy baby girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs @PressSec nothing about it is complicated. The guy should be in jail for the rest of his life. The… https://t.co/juQKNvhmAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see the segment.  Post here @TuckerCarlson we are adults. We can handle a few f bombs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For what I had ordered, one medium double double and a regular coffee, I don't take kindly to them laughing at my voice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frognerfrogner @CineMarkTheater Yeah but that’s canadaland so it’s not really a real place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Q1295tinman @occulturalism @q_zorra @Books_Anon @DigitalPatriotQ @Wwg1wgaTrump @_T_3_K @GenFlynn @Livid2point0 @Trumped18 Great question!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop deflecting.  You rushed to judgement.  Anyone with any common sense could smell that his story was suspect. @donlemon @CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceTacodip @ElegantLeopard @GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @LaceyEvansWWE Should have called up Toni Storm instead. She is better in every possible way and way more deserving,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cosmis @BillMonty_ @skibbi9 In that case, “as there’s always been” vs. “as Obama.” The framing is meaningful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USASwimming My Mom used to drink Vodka Martini’s in a #Thermos😍🏊‍♂️🏊🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doug311allen @kamilovesdoug I’m positive I’ve seen a lot of great cities I would have never considered if it weren’t for music]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dubbs_tyler Lmao let them be happy by barely beating a team 4 games below .500 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents are going around the house blasting Earth Wind and Fire on the Alexa  singing to each other, if future i… https://t.co/K0gPuUuOTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nearlincoln @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/5RMcMldvmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ytashawomack @audible_com I’m looking to connect. Edward.smith-lewis@uncf.org]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scripture of the day: @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/K3nu8GaqA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ actually "out-socialized" the socialists. His idea is that we serve Him by being the servants of other… https://t.co/BTL38RJO8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gorluhuh @purehollywood @AlKapown39 Mandy can actually wrestle unlike Eva]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weather is getting more fun by the week @robinkuhn https://t.co/OC6mQ1tS3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[So shall my word be that goeth forth out of my mouth: it shall not return unto me void, but it shal…… https://t.co/Wrjh3z49id]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Mast rejoining the fold after a 20 year absence. Come see the reunification 🎶🎸🍻👊🏼⭐️ @ The Elbo Room https://t.co/HBP3KFnGXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the barbershop on my Lunchbreak. I need a fresh fade for the weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When should abortion be ok?  When you are aborting the person that thinks abortion is ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeGendron @BairdLindsey They are scary beasts.  They eat sharks from time to time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Innovative Approach to Earning College Credit in High School @ACT #StateOrgs #WIACT with Kristel Tavare, Lisa Ar… https://t.co/VRHGknRCrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @captainmarvel @brielarson @SamuelLJackson #CaptainMarvel  https://t.co/fr0rcQl1Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackenedwisdom About 400 miles away. Should be 60° in Oklahoma City this afternoon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YTCreators @YouTube Is anyone else having issues with uploading? I always export H.265 4k and its telling me that… https://t.co/ef5YVbMjax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st brotha! Stay stafe, don’t be such a stranger all the time man fuck 😉🎉 https://t.co/zUH9LlU1Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #liftandfillfacelift with central #fatcompartments #fat #injections and outer deep #smasfacelift @DrRodRohrich… https://t.co/H6GWHnlvaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owillis @realDonaldTrump That’s a 5G ellipsis, so much stronger and more powerful than the conventional ellipsis.… https://t.co/aOCGuccWvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand Kepa wanting to stay on-It’s a Cup Final-His blood is following-emotional-wants to prove a point. I ge… https://t.co/UDLsqOOqU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz @mgobluegirl6 It’s a good thing I don’t listen to those holier than thou evangelicals. The God I ser… https://t.co/mgFe0eBhWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Une médaille d'Or pour le Vert et Or..à Winnipeg https://t.co/uPOVf5SZRa https://t.co/8eSR1ibBjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh baby - Drinking  The Smiling Nut by @CigarCityBeer at @CigarCityBeer  — https://t.co/EkCiuJdqqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPhillipsWWE @WWEGraves @TheCUTCH22 Besides the rocky steps / independence hall I wouldn’t wanna spend any time… https://t.co/6kYWkZSzR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home and away unis are pretty much the same, but some slick looking white third uniforms are new. https://t.co/uJa3mOzkXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayThoughts We are so close to helping me and my kids, please share, RT and/or donate... every little bit helps… https://t.co/OJqa7Yzdly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another nice morning on the farm 🌿🌿🚜 #microgreens #agriculture #Sacramento https://t.co/A6NCQ2BpKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gwen will be calling me “Coach”... #HipReplacement #DoNotLetHerFireMeAfterDay1 https://t.co/wkLokAwW9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlawjw The Catholics have a perfectly good Pope in Benedict.  Benedict was taken out by the Deep State like they… https://t.co/3rN3onzy8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdir23 And Pau was a legit All Star with Memphis. So Kobe inherited his best. He’s just getting older.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @Trump_daddy16 This idiotic smoothy slip in all those wanting to add theirs on #LiberalShellGame where… https://t.co/v40mc20ihn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally about to just rip my wisdom teeth out with pliers, I’m in so much pain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megdogwuff @KatTheHammer1 @JussieSmollett If Jussie action was a cry for help, and proven false and staged, he sho… https://t.co/OvEeRrGTX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of two of my favorite RM grads! They celebrated senior night at Hawaii with a win over Fullerton, and they… https://t.co/MQEsD2ADsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo to our 8th graders at Orchestra Night! Beautiful music, and great learning with our guest conductor. https://t.co/gqOnkGFWyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmallTalksMB Thank you for coming. That set fucking rocked. I need like 90 minutes of that. Hope to see you in Phi… https://t.co/ZmDs8osAXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon Jones: Gonna talk to his coaches about the next fight -- "a lot of great fighters in the UFC. Whoever it may be… https://t.co/ntiVBGRfNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKitchenista When I turned 40 I said “f” it. Now I show them off proudly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsForceBB My buddy Thomas Gary rangers in the Richmond/ El Cerrito area and has a perfect 11-year-old team tha… https://t.co/0OA0oddFtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@z__e__u__s__ eres la mujer mas petfecta que eciste no dejo de pensar en ti y en una vid a atu lado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Coño Guaidó, de bolas que lo aprobaría, maduro simplemente sigue al pie de la letra las órdenes de chávez.… https://t.co/6CmE09zICL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you k ick back an airplane bottle at the urinal at the bus depot are you wrong? Asking for a friend. Don't even....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cause I’m bored...making myself a wallpaper for my PC😬 https://t.co/aFR4ebjDzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If all you do is point out my faults and always negative, stay away from me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookAddict10 @ImDudeLiberty @Merica_Media @JoanneMason11 @emmdub559 Yes, while you actually watch FUTURAMA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms moved, my dad is moving.. ya boy really feelin alone tonight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier # when you point one finger three point back ! That’s the way God designed it .]]></document><document><![CDATA[She lit. @iamchrissyrene @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/s9zyJ4gLN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lineup for Duel No. 2. The No. 15 of Ross Chastain will start at the rear for missing drivers meeting #NASCAR https://t.co/PPxSJSKU2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xbox @XboxSupport is a joke. 2 suspensions in 7 years. Kid spammed my messages because I killed him in fort then r… https://t.co/HNyEhTPNgT]]></document></documents></author>