<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tonight im seeing onemillionmoths @MatthewBPM . Living my best life sis. @ Bullet Bar https://t.co/usisYMOpWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is before the traditional command of “ATTENTION: WOMAN YOUR WIGS!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shibez1 @stephietweets Hey did ya get a lil 🦴? I’m now living under https://t.co/9Pz3KkxHub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Ruehlman: 1) Most overturned judge in southwest Ohio; 2) Attacked rape victims; 3) In 2016 the @Enquirer sai… https://t.co/OqVTggEIcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[9. Kefka from Final Fantasy 6. He's the only villain I can think of off the top of my head who accomplishes his goa… https://t.co/aPlLJErH6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilwar_wrestlin @elijah106106 @marckis106 @amoney1770 @kolbyflank @ctrimmer713 NICE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatSportsPaige Separate (a little) from the male/female question, how on earth does someone quantify who “knows m… https://t.co/pwbOknE4zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StylingAndProfiling. “To be the Man you got to beat the Man”. Love me som @RicFlairNatrBoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[17. Let’s never forget the time Cedric beat Krum, controlled by a Death Eater, in a duel. Your boy could freaking g… https://t.co/9XBeMX8EHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the hell did @IconicPeytonR get eliminated? Did I have a stroke? #EliminationChamber #WWEChamber #WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rom_TAlan How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/ABIsMfw2XH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradWhitchurch @gmfb @casekeenum I knew you weren't asking a Peyton question, but would've never guessed.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your phone and TV are tracking you, and political campaigns are listening in https://t.co/n6o2vg7MkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Send out your light and your truth; let them lead me; let them bring me to your holy hill and to your dwelling!… https://t.co/u9RUQBl7Jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jkburke21Jim Except for the driver of the car chase....  ...aaaand Bat-Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianaLima @angelcandice Reconciling facts 11march2019 0030h — free will - march towards end for these abusive me… https://t.co/WSP5em6iic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDC_212 Well that’s why your analysis is better than mine because you analyzed it and thought it through. I just a… https://t.co/04UFnk93Lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GovWhitmer is in Sturgis this afternoon trying to build public support for her 2020 budget, especially the 45 cen… https://t.co/v2VM8nDSLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tmasterxtreme @RealMyUsername @badimo Um You got it wrong, you did it the opposite way kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Region 2-6A girls semifinal: Menendez 28, Eastside 12. Falcons outscore Rams 17-1 in 2nd qtr. Eastside 3-11 from fr… https://t.co/XyRZOak2wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The OState WR Corp of 2017 and 2018 will not be remembered like they should be..they were so underrated..and were e… https://t.co/iUXxwwufxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BT_cdetzel Thanks &amp; Cheers. If you are ever up this way, Treehouse is not to be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something unique and much needed is coming soon to Pittsburgh viewers. Very, very excited for this. Stay tuned will… https://t.co/Vqx5dYXlhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BioMarkDarrah I'm having problems interacting with NPC's who have conversations available....they disappear when I… https://t.co/3MxOcO548W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News and Information with a strong bias for telling the truth. Censored news and analysis that you won't f… https://t.co/k5oCHg7x4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCKatie He took the day off to prepare more talking points yesterday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see that here in Arlington — smaller group that objects ideologically, larger group that is concerned by effects… https://t.co/cjfKpXVT5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️🌴 spent time with #lafamilia @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/GQ8p386p6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Free solo” it’s hands down one of the best documentaries I’ve ever seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tailopez You do dirt you get dirt not a problem if you're looking for dirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bruins when they realize they didn’t do enough at the #NHLTradeDeadline https://t.co/RYpx7UDBLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidsquasher That’s all I ask I don’t wanna argue with you Matt I do genuinely hope you’re good and I really hope… https://t.co/hu5NSTGyaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Performance assessments can be chapter quizzes, checking for understanding of Latin #CANE2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cody_Nolove is not even awake yet to block me! Fuck you and your glass chin! You’re worst than @amirkingkhan !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I named it htown underground because I planned on making it about houston models taking photos in various locations… https://t.co/EDFGEcxHaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were explorers. We'd put up with anything. - Al Worden on going to space in crew modules the size of coffins.… https://t.co/K33PKbtIUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full moon today. Crazy things are happening at Lowe's. First someone crashes into a concrete column in Lumber. Next… https://t.co/UZzHIEZtwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods     You say it like it is brother....  Keep it going!  Jim]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NASCARPlayoffs here we come and the all time win record @Team_Penske! Congrats again @keselowski so proud of you,… https://t.co/egYSqaegJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's free sports pick is the Islanders -125. https://t.co/oUu1zjvJnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week has passed and I'm still smiling. My 16th #24hoursintheoldpueblo was just as much fun as the first one. So m… https://t.co/gS8Sz6siaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo esto porque vi prophet en Amazon Forecast mientras seguía con mi tour de AWS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Brunner The Bellevue (Eastside) Journal-American. South County Journal. Zoned south, north and east editions o… https://t.co/j8l3j8HVE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cruz_Azul_FC ya hubiera metido a #zombie estuvieran 3 goles arriba #VamosConTodo #CruzAzulvsSantos #CruzAzul # https://t.co/xDFlNgBn15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @realDonaldTrump Funny that the #ACLU had no problem with the real abuses of power in the flood of exec… https://t.co/46jSHXIbcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this brewery and this restaurant! - Drinking a Focus by @calusabrewing @ Charlie’s Bulgogi  — https://t.co/HyXYXAM750]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you President Trump for being our PRESIDENT and acting to protect our great nation and all law abiding citizens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué pasó ahí Sr @lopezobrador_ ? ¿ya volvimos a lo habitual? ¿Ya se cansó el ganso? ¿ @Pemex dio patadas de ahogad… https://t.co/AfGhIWgqHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kodiva22 @Patriots @MikeReiss Not to pile on....but Mike is sooo good at what he does!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 @peachy_witchy @CNNPolitics Sorry, she HAS NOT been sighted, they (CNN) keep saying she is returning to… https://t.co/tMid3pfDhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump.  America is wondering will Dennis Rodman be going to Vietnam.? Since he is the ambassador to North Korea. GO… https://t.co/kwwnFh4KeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechnoLord666 @KaitMarieox Most likely not, but the more important thing is I heard she pooped her pants at a party hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:53.2°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mind, body, and soul are one with the universe again.  @deLeonHTX @whoudini69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethomson @andrewdmoreno @tfsbuck Any recommendations on dealing with a large number of repos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 90s Crush Turns 40 Today! A Beautiful Lady Indeed! Happy Birthday To @TheReal_Jlh 🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jumping on with @PeterBurnsESPN and @ChrisDoering now on @SXMCollege 374.  Lot of SEC basketball, football, and 902… https://t.co/dKLvHahHhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EpilepsySucks @aidanaskew @br_betting @br_CBB I knew I was going to spell it wrong but didn't bother to look it up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_little_old_me That’s funny!! My boy would sing that song in public when he was like 4-6 yrs. embarrassed my wife… https://t.co/FTNwMINQk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaStavick "The forces which pushed your tooth out of place are usually still there after the braces come off.… https://t.co/VbaNtYHYZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisans I can’t remember what it’s called! It starts with a P and that’s about all I remember lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending the year abruptly is hard. I haven’t had time to do a lot of reflecting but our program appreciates the supp… https://t.co/ndAbZV39iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the two newest members of the ministry fam!! That SICK American Standard custom Tele was anointed, prayed over… https://t.co/JYBXn3m0OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EclecticRadical The fact that she has a kid strikes me as a tragedy, both for the kid and the gene pool of that community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toonimator @KyleDLarson @GlitterLeader She did nothing but stop actual events that would have been interesting to… https://t.co/KPpILXWefU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farmington has the smallest excuse to give everybody a 2 hr delay. Haha it’s pretty funny. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good point by @JaneEliz, since 1972, people had about as much trust in the press as they did in used car salesmen. #dth126]]></document><document><![CDATA[The agent you choose can make a difference 508-423-0080 https://t.co/oe2AR4k8mK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports Why you gotta bring up old stuff....RIP James..... https://t.co/59SiDPDVOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brrrr It's cold as we are sitting at 32°. My full weather forecast here..... https://t.co/zi3Lp1r2AS https://t.co/F7WeUfNwYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono Uh, I demonize anyone who kills a human being.  But go ahead and mask it as an attack on women.  Babie… https://t.co/Og1pJsMmDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiecouric @peterdaou Well talk to some of you former colleagues and get them to stop normalizing racism and hate… https://t.co/wQYBHPHQFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaymondArroyo @IngrahamAngle But Democrats love it! If you’re really stupid and believe in Socialist fairy tales, you’ll vote for them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunyabiznasbro @RepDanCrenshaw Why did Trump go on national radio and make himself a disgrace to America on 9/11?… https://t.co/TXUiVovqXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[America is a country of order and discipline, and governed by laws based on a constitution. The Wall is an enforcer… https://t.co/jFGcIhN6cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/7caihkYoHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diamandahagan I saw CM yesterday. I thought it was a great movie (excellent, awesome, breathtaking).  A far better… https://t.co/CcIpOkMYmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished the Umbrella Academy.   MAN that was good. https://t.co/7nAEHecKpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why not just act like you've done it before......the lack of sportsmanship is strong in this kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinitomo_ It scares me too. I blame the stress here in the USA. I need a shave badly. Don’t worry I will change th… https://t.co/yJFMfQ5h6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris More children are being affected by #Flint poisoned water and lack of healthcare #NeverKamala https://t.co/0Ua0XXwPlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuliettTorres_ Para empezar comerme todo eso a besos y saborear tu piel y emborracharme con el aroma de tu cuerpo 😘😍🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[So finally fully focusing on #Toonami tonight. Earlier I wasn’t totally into it even during Sword Art Online.  I’ll… https://t.co/t83iN521Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OuttaMyLaine That's such a good idea! I cant believe I hadn't thought of that. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelslat I trust you are living in a trailer, acting like you are big shit on Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayStation I'm pretty sure I know who is going to win....#ApexLegends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constructores inician foros para generar una Ley de Obras "ágil y competitiva" https://t.co/NYd7XjOTdD @CMIC_NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeOutHereRN I hope you end up holding a pretty girls hand at the end of the night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hickoryhill8520  Thanks for your like  Lord your marvelous words are living miracles, No wonder I long to obey  everything You say ps 119]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some neat technology coming down the pipe to do indoor location tracking using Bluetooth.  https://t.co/fdivFvpy8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeyMick @BarstoolNate Omg Nate, let the big boys in the big boy division talk. AFC East is the class of the leag… https://t.co/4F3pAmgth8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mo’ Money, Mosaic by @ProhibitionPig at @prohibitionpig — https://t.co/yzxatU7u15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisyost I’ve collaborated with him on charity work before and he seemed like a decent enough dude. Only recentl… https://t.co/jiAaMJeZqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so pretty when my brows were consistently done. But it’s been like 4 months]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadeNicolePerry @AzzurriFanPhil I can't wait until both of you profess your love for Milan. 😘❤️🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyvelocity Pffft that ain't an agreement with corporate https://t.co/CxgDbZRRgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤Its so hard to live but so easy to die🎤 @_cashladasha @chancetherapper @therealmarymary @Tip @BoomerangOnBET… https://t.co/yjNBlusj4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnapFlow69 Of course I am in Cali this week. I’d take you to dinner in a heartbeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Kitt and John Logan’s SUPERHERO @ Tony Kiser Theatre https://t.co/vm3reHo9KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liar, "Mexico will pay for the wall".  Your dumbass fence is not going to be built. No matter the delusions in your… https://t.co/wldbJUOaeI]]></document></documents></author>