<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm watching the Michael Jackson documentary on the first day of my period because I am full of smart choices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now does this anti-hate resolution bill include President Trump??? Doesn’t this and shouldn’t this apply to all… https://t.co/mGJUguU8IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michsteer You are living sister!!! Always love your run pics.  Way to get it done.  👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone so obsessed w my man but he’s mine  .. you’ll find ya own soon sis 🤣  it’s ok id be petty toooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCooper_TO @WrathuvCon @heebster25 @DonaldJTrumpJr @FLOTUS Idiot if you don’t have anything truthful and worthwhile to say just don’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican party hasn’t changed. They been this way since Ronald Reagan. Who decided to reduce taxes on the rich an… https://t.co/2OqBi9VzJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My living room floor has 3 bones &amp; 4 half torn apart toys on it, I should be upset because it looks like a mess but I’m not]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay, but nobody warned me that @instantfamily would have me this emotional, I’m literally bawling my eyes out rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSchrimsher It was great but it's a long drive there and back 3.5 hours each way on Wednesday night. I'm Almos… https://t.co/4tCZAcp8nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mine has Halloween 🎃 and Sweetest Day 💕 @ Mio, Michigan https://t.co/mUzu1AUpNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bholden86 @jrsteach Thank you for sharing. Joe &amp; I like her work!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronMorgan @UTexasPress @nytimes @NifMuhammad @ABAbook @tomhanks Accurate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen this tweet and just now realized the staple is going through it💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[the anklet my parents got me when we were in Mexico fell off &amp; now I can’t find it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I'm saying is if you want to post a video of you "shaking what your momma gave you" to impress us.....you might… https://t.co/gL441SdiGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSea1964 @Brenderm1 What’s a matter Stacey? Feeling left out!!! They don’t need your trailer park trash face an… https://t.co/MddC4CGHaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitman604 @screwballkid @prokaski @Alina1965Alina @kidgolferman @222222267d @eurodream @Hitman @duvidroth1… https://t.co/fuMwD61m7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥 There ain’t nothing you can do to ever fucking stop me!!! 💥 🙌🏽🎶 • The magic is mounting!!! 💫 Shows booked in LBC,… https://t.co/j2m0vtjZEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[desperates on Instagram rlly think they be quirky when they go public and put “public figure” or “movie character” in as their occupation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great show by @leftonlaurel So happy I got tickets for both! Wish I could have been able to tip more for a… https://t.co/d4YylAm0fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iskandrah That being said, you would be surprised at the number of Dems and progressives from that area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juugstar615 @KennyHowardJr @JMilionair @_timmmmy @valentinavoight They don’t fight over the colors no more this ain’t the 90s lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revistaetcetera @espiritutiflaut @SCJN @AleEsat Que termine la primaria nocturna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow we remember 17 victims of stoneman Douglas shooting. This is a tweet from a MSD student @wjxt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: this is an announcement that I watched part of an episode of The Bachelor™️ and everyone on this damn show is… https://t.co/IuCKLQbfuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are my Wednesday's #3MoreDaysToGo #Transform20  #ShaunT https://t.co/Wb3sBIUi8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omfg. Are you watching @pen15show?? Holy CRAP. It’s amazing, accurate, terrifying &amp; hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vickypham52 @DogMomUSA @Tripp_Punter1 @NatStrawn @loholmes963 @_rufhaus @TheSamiJoShow Absolutely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does a loyal chipotle customer gotta do to get the chicken she paid for @ChipotleTweets https://t.co/oPlFiX2ltH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @JussieSmollett Absolutely right.  And of course he won’t.  In fact, I’m sure his hoax will be barely r… https://t.co/dhl6Rvy76x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormLeong Apparently the journalist from #SacramentoBee was released after being unfairly arrested for coverage of… https://t.co/WZPUiaW8PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing by (@ M&amp;W Thai Restaurant - @mandwthai in Glen Ellyn, IL) https://t.co/mFI8mxnyG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[While #stroke treatment rates and timing improves, we cannot lose sight of how many people are ineligible because t… https://t.co/Bu5ft2UgGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heg3512 @steph93065 @ChantalArtist @RepAdamSchiff The truth is exactly what we DO care about. Are you so wrapped u… https://t.co/vl4cCWubK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT #ALRConference! Every year invigorates and inspires! See you next year!  @BaylorOVPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Really? Not intended. tRump is a glutton who lives on shit food and it shows. Yet, not the worst of his sins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lori_burwell @UnclaimedAna2 It does https://t.co/counqtl6pY to you Lori]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrSwansClass to post covers of 7 books that I ❤️ No explanations no reviews. I’ll challenge so… https://t.co/QMfOV7XxKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeforSchools @TracyNovick we tried and got shot down multiple times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone who lives in chicago is DEPRESSED name one person who isn’t !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just counting down the days until I say bye to Chicago and hello my new home]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeAreTheMusicMaker The dream-like sounds of @_orvillepeck are perfect for up-all-night editing. https://t.co/4XtNFrjQO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The radio station our work plays isn’t working AT ALL so I flipped through stations and the only one working is a r… https://t.co/rs5y0Ym32S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedNews Well, the local people who are concerned about wanting the wall should sue those who do not want the wall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to snicker. #mirth #laugh #grin #laughable https://t.co/HN0hzYsVtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[YO THIS WAS OUR FCKIN SONG THO HAHAHA @BrriPC . Actually no just all of Miley / Hannah was. *cue dance we would spe… https://t.co/Ov20OKG1hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @Temp0ralF00l @kroger I’ve noticed that “white women” have felt empowered to verbally abuse people of col… https://t.co/z2pu171owF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saint Valentine's celebrations of love have an ancient past. https://t.co/N2jwVd7bqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hinge is revealing to me my ratio is about 1:100. If that doesn’t make sense don’t worry about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 individual finals, 2 relays, the 5th fastest 50 free in UNC history, and the 6th fastest 100 free in UNC history.… https://t.co/jqiAKYF3xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to kick these winter time blues with beach views 😭🏝 https://t.co/rSRVmFtJkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSimpson24 @Alabamafan40 @the_silverfox1 And about 1 week of spring, before summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Yeah. There are people in jail for smoking Pot.  Good thing Trump is NOT Rodrigo Duterte huh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been studying for 3 days straight for this bio exam in 2 hrs and honestly I feel like I still don't know anything 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro fuck the city of dallas,, literally driving back to austin and we get pulled over when there’s no speeding limit signs,,, mmmmmmmkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take the time to read the article!  Mar-a-Lago is DT's place to go. This might be why perhaps???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset #hhi  #oldoysterfactory #southcarolina  #dinnerout @ Old Oyster Factory https://t.co/Au2VNjYRzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMacHoops @THECoachK20 is one of the very best!  Congratulations and good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucilles_BBQ 1st time and we are sitting here.  Food finally come and it’s cold.  My temper is hotter then my plat… https://t.co/NQpyWHzjEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@untilthespring Yes those grown *** men just think they are the funniest, but after many years I've become accustom… https://t.co/STTKdJ8X3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aperezcanedo @EnfoqueNoticias Siempre te escucho...saludos desde Juárez Chihuahua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takes one to know one! Thank you maraftery for the perfect gift 👩🏻🐻. Here’s to years and YEARS of driving our child… https://t.co/C9UA34iAsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm trying to win a @nuCamp TAB camper. You can, too! Enter for your chance to win. #TABgiveaway #sweepstakesentry]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MuellerRated1Spot #MuellerReportBilledToP #AmazonMuellerReport1st  https://t.co/317wfrwm1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefrocky413 I'm in hockey mode right now. I love that you know that I bleed Black and Gold.  You made my day Chef.😊😍😘😍😘❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyDijon @realDonaldTrump A idiot trying to act smart to a limited amount of supremacists! Donnie J is the Laug… https://t.co/jEwf3Yx8Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why all my besties wanna get boyfriends a month before we go to Vegas 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xjrh20xx @davidcicilline Looks like you've passed over to the realm of LOONYVILLE. RIP!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BABY💋ILL BE YOUR ❄️ 👼SNOW ANGEL❄️👼 #winterstyle❄️ #winterlook❄️ #winterswag😎 #wintergear💋 #winterfashion💋… https://t.co/3GY81oVhcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azsweetheart013 @TucciKaren @nilslofgren Already done! Wish you were coming to Atlanta too...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I  am so beyond blessed and excited to have this new job. I know she’s  watching over me 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[The minority of USB attacks are malware-based (less than a third). The category of Programmable Microcontrollers is… https://t.co/JNYYM7wOzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Match Marketing? We're hiring in #Harrisburg, PA! Click the link in our bio for details on this job… https://t.co/VPlfxP5W1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ando de mírame, pero no me tientes. Favor de no estar chingando. Gracias]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greens are not always "green". I got Berries and even Chocolate. Yes, you are reading that correctly.   Ask me.… https://t.co/8sZehSwzap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lisle just told me I’m the funniest person he’s ever met and that’s honestly a higher compliment to me than him tel… https://t.co/Lr18quHcjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man. The myth. The legend. @scottbradlee himself onstage with #PMJTour at the @BeaconTheatre! https://t.co/zCz8zORKbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's celebration kicked off was at the Lips chocolate event at the Faena Forum. It was kinky, fun and the ar… https://t.co/LjdcM96zUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i put my whole ass heart into these valentines day gifts so if i dont get some mf luv ill scream!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today years old when I willingly revoked my Black Card cuz I will NEVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tim_sandsquid63 @FEMA_Brock @fema I will agree. I have friends who families still live there that had first hand k… https://t.co/I4yRJ7sTKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkneec Ugh i currently have bronchitis and ear infection and sinusitis I am over it glad you feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Floating https://t.co/qVo2ghH8W9... Best Vision in The World! #comedy #giggle #smile #humorous https://t.co/dHHokt0zA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruh i stay over in torrance so much that i barely like sleeping in my own bed anymore smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga that looks like YNW Melly tryna talk to me. Bitch I ain’t tryna die 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinseyfineart It’s the modern version of Walmart!! Walmart couldn’t spell customer service until the competition s… https://t.co/sp0ECCVxUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Kids at my job asking me about Blueface. Asking me what the meaning of the song lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put this shit on top of a freshly baked brownie and be prepared to go to heaven😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesRutka shared some potential solutions for stress and burnout. #CCSOQuality2019 #ThriveICU @criticalcareON… https://t.co/J7y065lzq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paranormalara1 Planning another seance for late March.  Will post soon and put in march newsletter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be here at #2019clc!  Way to represent @ACOG_District8 and AZ @TaylorJNorton @DevinKirsten… https://t.co/dZN7ima9ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly my sister in law in my mothafuckin partner in crime forever I love that bitch ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherineBiss11 @Zeffoster @MattWalshBlog That’s the problem, Hun. Holy crap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jefftayloredits @USATODAY As a young stroke survivor it’s amazing that strokes are declining for the elderly but i… https://t.co/1HsNBGttKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/s3lI0CXNJ7. As a former Monkees Fanclub President (fun fact!), I devoted my childhood heart and soul i… https://t.co/elbXrvLy2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Single Mom Khloe Kardashian Is Living On Her Own Terms — Where Does That Leave Tristan Thompson? | Celebrity Insider https://t.co/o2Roa0F8NF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I can be an adult, yeah I can totally be responsible and take care of myself. Also me: *is up at 11:32 on twitt… https://t.co/JyH8lZn3bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a packed house as we celebrated the grand reopening of the Thomas M. Wernert Center. Now, members living wit… https://t.co/fvBPwwUPtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leesi_Girl @niamarkanthony ...and we need to keep speaking, screaming, for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejanis1 @EdKrassen Being an immoral supremacist pays off when EC voters are filled w/immoral sycophant pigs]]></document></documents></author>