<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@officialheart @BobSeger @JLo @beck lead the latest batch o' new #Detroit metro shows https://t.co/XuPDQUpMsU… https://t.co/tnIGeuAV5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[USF is rightfully punished for not fouling up three. So much for tournament hopes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "full time Security Officer" at Allied Universal? Applicant tracking systems look for speci… https://t.co/C2HiRRKlDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanOBrienPoker Actually, I did see a clip of it. It’s an act, IMO, and my hate for the guy didn’t “fall away.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much to admire about @SoundersFC on opening night. The poignant tribute to Sigi, Morris’s roaring return (pick o… https://t.co/SqBs40LdyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like or retweet if you guys take selfies every single day #morphe #jaclynhillpalette #AnastasiaBeverlyHills… https://t.co/nZQduS5g5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright.... Twitter restart.   Beginning fresh and new.   Enough of this fake sh*t... let’s get REAL.   #New #beginnings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want a way to see my @Spotify stats throughout the year tbh like,  how many hours have I streamed the same album so far this month???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCivian @Cane_alytics I really feel like I should be getting some sort of royalty off of this thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can honestly say that this was one of my least favorite assignments EVER. https://t.co/wcCoqN2hBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @uhbroncofan @Eddieonfox who is Vance Johnson #instatrivia https://t.co/vmlPuXsgJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citostyle This was brought up in a question at FSE this past year. Definitely going to be something the research c… https://t.co/UOGqhYMvPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMBParalegal Or the LSO using law firms in which sitting Benchers are partners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricGuillot14 @MichaelPawluk @HorsePlayerNow I call em...KIA’s! Know it Alls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got off work and it’s raining really hard in so cal .... so i got to complete a dream of mine real quick lol… https://t.co/AiOGFqXIBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jethroinwi @ChrisWelch77 I carry them with me in case I run into a friend on the road. I promised to mail to… https://t.co/V7fV4oxUSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget that love means acceptance. However, love without justice is not love but denial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeChuck @Mighty_LR I now have to buy a new @NYRangers jersey cause Zuccs gone to Dallas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't mean to by hyperbolic, but the RoboCop KFC tv ad is a disgrace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toneytigers Picture Day Twins! #gotoney #tigerpride🐯 #toneyes #ilovedcsd https://t.co/0bP6aRgWfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[With love, from New York City. . ●  .    #glrosario .    George L. Rosario NYC's Hometown Realtor Luxe Stone Realty… https://t.co/9Schj9Q2Lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eastside #EldoradoHS #Educator #ElSalvadorian #LasVegas #Nevada #Sundevil #23YearsYoung #GoogleHer… https://t.co/QPtjmJosEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AZCardinals All you people saying Bosa, that dude is injury prone and Keim has a history of choosing injury prone… https://t.co/bc3FeRKki8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should the #Raiders make a run at Le’Veon Bell? Join in the debate on @SidedDebates and make your case! https://t.co/4Ztu4dvll4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This will have to be decided by the courts, though there will also have to be a frank examination… https://t.co/nOmcnwmtUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadddsongs Winter will be over soon bb! It’s about to be a damn good spring/summer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s hope @TrinityTheTuck takes the crown tomorrow! @RuPaulsDragRace @RuPaul @VH1 @WorldOfWonder #AllStars4 #TeamTrinity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeeppinette @fawn_Graham @1960_don @DesireeMcCorm16 @Fuerstenberg15 @BrigitteSchoofs @RIVERA_1404 @kcropsey12… https://t.co/WStcaz63Zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did they pull the girls over? And what gives them@a legit reason to wantvto search the car? Because they are sm… https://t.co/ocIM74Il3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerKepner Solid work, as always. This Phillies fan is happy with the way the team addressed their weaknesses thi… https://t.co/rwdr6GiPV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWBone24 @hawkeyejoe601 @laughlin9170 @BigTenNetwork @stephenbardo https://t.co/tUm4uttH3l This is what's real, not Bob Knight assumptions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BASportsGuy I’ve known for a long time that Baer was a lying weasel but this is despicable even by the low standards I had for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALaboutSports This is fuckin’ hilarious. A billionaire getting a rub ‘n tug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boston__Sucks Play him as a stacked backer in the box where he belongs, limiting his coverage deficiencies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to hop up on paddle shifters. I got the next mixtape coming out in my cities 🏎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Community Harvest Church in Germantown, OH https://t.co/1s0ekBYhTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck E. Cheese’s is definitely a level of hell. It’s somewhere between some form of lust and gluttony, so let’s ca… https://t.co/5pElXCm85z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jefferson, North Carolina https://t.co/Po7lbcJSaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews @Midgespeaks Cohen won't get out of prison JFKJR CIA sealed JFK files are opened marilyn monroe Mort… https://t.co/ZVneIDdbnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of testimony from Hopkins about how their employees are scared.   There was almost a dozen shootings in Balti… https://t.co/fcP5qX5WGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibaudRich I am a Veteran too what have you done for your country that qualify's you for anything. Don't ask what… https://t.co/n0Rako59qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Sure, it was a lynching of truth, credibility and justice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalcyonTraveler @ComicsSteve Jesus, was he hoping to join the Monkees or navigate the Enterprise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_hubb21 @PastorTrey05 @SirRantAndRave @BeasPodcast Is Dooling also available? I feel like he'd a be a coach with perspective]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good dick got her knocked out She hate when I pull out She like it in her mouth 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet sponsored by my sensitivity - which I’m here to report has reached new heights, as I just cried at a goo… https://t.co/VQivaw7ItE]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S A FINAL! 8-0 VICTORY for the JV ladies soccer team over Southern Lee!! @CATSOC17 @ApexHighSchool @apexcougarclub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkinnerPm Bless you sir! You exemplifie what it means to be a real human being!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secret Wealthy Donor For AOC’s Green New Deal Has Been Revealed, And Wow... It's George Soros! No surprise there.… https://t.co/vUHp6WJ22t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subban and McNabb having a playful little rivalry in practice.   #VegasBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacked up to begin working with Coach Collier, @GRockFootball and Glenrock HS (WY)! Looking forward to seeing the g… https://t.co/Vt0cITIWXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[At wedding with these funnymen @dhaglund &amp; @JamieKaler ! #MyBoys #LoneGunmen #XFiles !!!!! https://t.co/E9p189Qnzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_VanAmburg @robdelaney @BernieSanders His position on Yemen is now mainstream and the u.s. is reconsidering it’s role there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexsteacy @WakeUpSuper *mickey mouse voice* Should have aimed for the head! Ha HA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well if it’s Don Shula, can we finally stop celebrating that perfect season when Nixon was President?]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/hcDGytyyW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 of the 15 Titan blue neckties that Mr. Fitterer tied on the way to St. Peter for the MSHSL Large Group Band Conte… https://t.co/HpUfhfqmET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC and her supporters define the ignorance of liberal socialism, she's believes with all her heart in liberal equ… https://t.co/fqDw9kN5WY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaBonzai - Seeds to Roots (2019) (New Full Album) https://t.co/QCuiUauuZr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameful, @realDonaldTrump! Of course he knew. It amazing how you believe dictators like Kim and Putin, yet ignore… https://t.co/O2otLXqgtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mszygomatic They know how it affects you because they can read your mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chahloopah Another disaster from the uninformed loud mouth, the pied piper of the leftist loons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@botellazo @ProfPBCelis @morandavid @jbo @LucioQuincioC Se arrodillan ante Cuba, no protegen a Vzla. No se les pued… https://t.co/GzmgBMGifc]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the road to NYC listening to #readingfc on @BBCBerkshire - come on URZ!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForestWellsDen Maybe? Suppose I don't see it that way. Which is fine really. We all can't agree all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not much more in the world that I need than what I have here:. A great jazz piano bar with great food and the best… https://t.co/lMCVZLGRUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standard stout, good flavor - Drinking an 825 State Stout by @EpicBrewing @ Ruth's Chris Steak House - Park City  — https://t.co/vk4LkqLIvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Sundayfunday #socialfam, this weeks #YouTube #episode is #live and I'm excited to share some new editing ski… https://t.co/7uoEzQA5a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RacisminEveryD1 Knightdale NC Government Officials gather to hear an invited speaker spew racist words when referr… https://t.co/Q9JuwBlwY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's crazy to think I won't see @jsleezer's photos in the sports section anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Making The Connection: Merging Journalism &amp; Media Relations” #NABJMillennials https://t.co/Xxh4WuajKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I get on the Tom Cruise cardio plan cuz that man be running thru like 37% of his movies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenn_k4 @MansfieldSchool @TmmMPS @MConn_MPS @mansfieldSTEM Yes- we should reach out!  I’d love to have them come in!  #iRobot]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s -12 windchill and it’s your turn to cook #beefdemand https://t.co/lefZ9ioqee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha and on that note good night, gotta get ready for another day tomorrow 😂 @ Truckee, California https://t.co/5MJpsta7ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀🎶 more very cool work from take2vinyl they can take your pictures and put them on records that need to be recycled… https://t.co/MognQBbCnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dia_Latina @Conquistador314 Well, this is an awkward exchange. But anyway... do you happen to have any citation fo… https://t.co/dtM8mlVIC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParforeTom I hope he plays well too. We’ve seen this act before though, playing well in spring so im very skeptical.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trevonne19_ She’s in the shower washing her hair  Sent with love, -Her new bae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_McCloud Yeah I forgot about him will he be healthy for this up coming season]]></document><document><![CDATA[rashida tlaib now? lol another justice dem. shits getting incredibly lit ever since ro khanna spit that fire a bit ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JB550MB @steelercam @dlolley_pgh It has. It's why I've argued for four years to move on from Lev and invest that $… https://t.co/dLe2ryMH1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[LaRue County Schools are open and operating on regular schedule today. Have an awesome day, Hawks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting defensive strategy by the Bulls to stop Trey Young.  Get him ejected for taunting Dunn after hitting an… https://t.co/k089HiXre4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have made this argument myself against many here in Louisville. Still, read this thread and quit whining about a… https://t.co/X7i1R3j2Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the@last 6 or 7 Presidents I can never remember where Democrats or Republicans actually SUE the President🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed @TrueDetective's season finale. If you went into it unaware the season was exploring the nature of time--… https://t.co/23Mv21oZpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox lite strikes again with this nonsense. This is a stone cold criminal with little or no conscience and definitel… https://t.co/3r8vp5gSCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it weird for two straight guys to listen to old Taylor Swift in the car?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freshyrosay @dts1186 I see what you did there. https://t.co/DiVDncklri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bueno creia que tenian buenas ideas, pero esra definitivamente no lo es...bye disovey y que les vaya bien..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudy_weather How much snow did you get yesterday before the changeover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shot I don’t remember writing this last night. So exhausted and slightly inebriated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like watching Feuerstake and Hicks go back-to-back today on replay and having your wife point out you spell… https://t.co/9BQ5MmiPk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPFearlessSyd @WatchGirlsPlay @IAlundra @jessie__moreno @EyesLikeGlass_ @NatalieDoerfler @nikinapalm I'm very sorr… https://t.co/G0gwd9b1Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mazel tov to Rami Malek, a first generation American immigrant.   The American Dream, where any person from any pla… https://t.co/6GJ5XSn8nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI it’s really effin cold in NYC so you better pack your most fabulous faux furs. See you at Caroline’s! @AlyssaEdwards_1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathewlenning @Michael30271076 @RyanAFournier @DineshDSouza And all this is after he hired Sebastian Gorka and Ste… https://t.co/6Ky3yjXOFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigAnt_Szn Right bro 😂🤮 he’s getting cocky asf now too like grow tf up bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tacoupdate just as I was getting comfortable he hits me with 2 quick ones]]></document></documents></author>