<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Learning to appreciate the opportunities for growth that challenges present. A lot has happened, a lot has changed,… https://t.co/XnFOAYDwWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ayyye_Geo @janaethegreat Wow Geo that’s crazy. Definitely don’t curve anyone but okay 😂🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codermeow @lara_hogan Yes! She has helped me focus on what I love to do, which is leading me to a career shift. It… https://t.co/PeRGmH5Vqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tadpoles tarragon target  @mainedcm  / Stacy  #DADDYSGURLFirstCrush  #MaineMendozaBarbie60]]></document><document><![CDATA[To reduce our infinite existence to a single physical attribute is to reduce God himself. For I believe that our so… https://t.co/wPVsCwQhhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanWohlenhaus @LandOLakesInc Likewise! I look forward to hearing the #LOLAM19 episode of the #SomethingGreater #podcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker F-U hannity take Putin’s d**k out of your #BoycottHannity #BoycottHannitySponsors  #BoycottHannitySponsors]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO DROPPING TODAY AT 5pm WHEN I FOUND OUT I WAS A FATHER 😱*story time* link in bio 🗣🗣 @ Chandler, Arizona https://t.co/gah2LH6D23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma provide reassurance and love you like everyday is your last bc I know tomorrow isn’t promised]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ultimamente não têm como não concordar com @felipeneto ! Lapada na cara do conservadorismo, nada cara dos mal educa… https://t.co/WzNM3Hvq3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStrub @TNCouncil Thanks for so much energy and helpful information yesterday! If you have a chance pls send i… https://t.co/SebQGQyWEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenMeister @siano2020 But then they'll cry "rigged election" as they always do. No to Bernie. Besides, the new r… https://t.co/ZCP0dN0pGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[That reporter convo that went well a few days ago? Here’s the end result...   I live for my positive quote days 😅.   https://t.co/HxlFOjS4La]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caring acts can change the world! #RAKDay #RandomActsOfKindnessDay #caring #BeKind #change #mygns https://t.co/sEoKoVYrMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[But ain’t nobody got a mom like mine -@indietrainor  alt caption: blurry anchors, and tons of school spirit from DT… https://t.co/fbjgMQ58W4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally worth a read! This was my “Aunt Bubba”, or Roberta B Tully, but she was more like a grandmother to me. This… https://t.co/NXQ1hUzCqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yall_cuckin omg. i kinda want to try red also? but i wanna grow my hair out before that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just feel so small and stupid. I try to imagine a version of me that isn't incompetent and alone and it's impossible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who names their daughter #Huskey? #NikkiHaley did. #PoorChild  https://t.co/gYKVpVYceZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenmorrisonlive Congrats Jen! So glad you found something new to make you smile :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their chicken livers (I don’t do liver - ever! Well unless Emeril Lagasse pan sears a thin layer of foie gras on re… https://t.co/KmXbutxkm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz If you keep this up tomorrow it’s your reputation not cohens going down the sewer even lower than now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always need to look my best in case I meet the man of my dreams. That’s why I wear my good pajamas to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you go to a new sushi place and end up ordering way to much food. The guiltttt 😭😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟 Red Carpet Superstar 🌟  #CaptainMarvel Star @lashanalynch looked absolutely stunning her #RitaVinieris gown the o… https://t.co/r39EMOhiOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to leave Port St Lucie and I gotta say, I’m never missing Spring Training ever again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump I wish we could afford a wall for brainless Demobrats. Especially new kid on the bl… https://t.co/HxmO0tBrS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The socialist train just lost 2 passenger cars! Connecticut had two new #Republicans in office. Wahoo. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy sweet mother of Buddha. I'm in love. - Drinking an Orange Kush by @HeavenAleBrewCo at @chattanoogajoe  — https://t.co/TgZGbusIOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cascada de Basaseachi, Chihuahua... Acabé bien bañada pero si la bajé y si la subí😎😉 YO SOY DEL MERO CHIHUAHUA, DEL… https://t.co/MNbIOJY7ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasta night. Different types of pasta OR stir fry. That’s good too  #southern_rys19]]></document><document><![CDATA[James 5:16 Confess your trespasses to one another, and pray for one another, that you may be healed. The effective,… https://t.co/9mZ7balgqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s a desperate need for @CCSTorg in my home state” —@mirzayanfellow Meg Ange-Stark. Same here, Meg! #AAASmtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skornhaber  Reference to Kavanaugh is mean-spirited and unnecessary. Be better w your gossip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been eating atleast 4 avocados a day for the last like week. That's normal right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we wishing @johnmcusick a happy birthday today, people? Because GOSH DARN IT WE SHOULD BE   🎉🎉🎂✨🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capitolwatch But in all seriousness, wondering how Nutmeggers feel about Medicare For All and what a world free of… https://t.co/4jLrE4TRAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need @Dropbox to explain to me why it’s taking 48 hours to download 190 pics! What!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayle_lynne Hello there!😁I was'nt on Twitter at all yesterday and I just now saw that it was your birthday.I'me so… https://t.co/b2oTXkoMC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basedinfidel8 @fellspeaks @Chriskl70208387 @TH3R34LTRUTH @Americanthatguy @AlexWY18 @johnw299 @AJuM809… https://t.co/L47Mg9fEEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS @daytimediva @CJLeBlanc Louisiana man there.  I would take that team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pompeo: Trump didn't say that. Tapper: It's a direct quote.  https://t.co/9uJ06AqG9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @cocoameka ・・・ 🚨🚨 Limited Slots Available ‼️ #valentinesday #Mixtape “From The Trap 2 The Bedroom” Hosted b… https://t.co/Rstavcyz8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes that is in fact his Heat jersey i’m sleeping in as an official #shacker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachdreaming44 I’m sure they’ll kill off mine before I’m done but I like the twists and turns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also...I think the description fits me...kinda. 😉 https://t.co/N33xnLau6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’ve made three 5th grade boys cry at conferences showing them tough love, you know you’ve made an impact.… https://t.co/IGBJ1nwBRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt MIMI saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea Gender: female To adopt MIMI ➡️… https://t.co/yCypiri0I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliesteiner @yottomusic @Anjunadeep Yessss been wanting to add this to my deep playlist forever but didn't know what it was called 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson But ok to play a blue man. Hollywood is ridiculous!  However, I am unable to laugh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot: Kirsten Gillibrand says 2020 campaign is "run for and by people, not corporate PACs."  Chaser: Drug company e… https://t.co/D7vYrlfRi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abba Padre - Conquistando Fronteras https://t.co/ZETBjpmwCN vía @YouTube 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the tribalism of online networks (FB, Twitter, etc) fuel ‘otherism’ in the world? Discuss.   via @ireneau on stage at @Wisdom2conf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beauty of Portuguese bars is they don’t card you cause they really don’t give a ffffff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I ever told you guys how much I LOVE #theguys. They are my ❤️❤️. And their joy, laughter and WILLINGNESS gives… https://t.co/9kDX673T07]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby P: Hey mom. Enjoy never being able to lay on your back for the next four months. 😊👶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math hurts my brain. I was just told that I make 190% more than the average minimum pay in Tennessee.  #ummWhat 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya estamos aquí.   Y aprendiendo de los grandes del campo: Nina Spada, Patsy Lightbown, Kees de Bot y Nick Ellis, t… https://t.co/dPwpHgVQyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[aGaGSKSHSKS IM NOT EVEN KIDDING THIS SHIT ACTUALLY SENT ME IVE BEEN LAUGHING FOR 10 MINS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I got a full body search in security AND they had to search my bag 😂 each individual bag was swiped for residue 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[While Ryan @Ryry4211 wasn’t called up to wrestle at Districts, I got to spend to spend one of the best nights with… https://t.co/RGFl8yywkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just met some cool journalist from @NBATVCanada @duanewatson @blackdragonroll 🤗 @Jumpman23 @Nike media preview… https://t.co/zALEmYM9sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[R4- Platinum Sales Award!  🏆🏠❤️ next year, Chairman Team #goals #remaxr4 #remax #remaxdynamicproperties https://t.co/VJ0eN0Nita]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump @RyanHillMI @williamlegate @tonyposnanski @TalbertSwan @JeffreyGuterman Hear hear!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful summer blonde highlights and layered inverted bob by Kristen Reed! Call us at 513-424-7662 or use the Boo… https://t.co/MfxwwDu1qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: MA state police confirm two people are dead after the plane crash]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is going to get mouth cancer. Karma is a fickle BITCH! The people that work for Trump lives will basically be o… https://t.co/NP7w7PO8sK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clevelanddotcom Stay in Cali we don’t want any part of ur commy way. Socialism. This is AMERICA]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND ANOTHER ONE! SOH proud of this Summit winner - @JimmyNg72367473!!!!!! #OHPAcalypse #teamLEAD #WinthewhOHlething… https://t.co/gbgCR3dPnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArizonaCoyotes @GanemJewelers missed opportunity for 15-14-13 (1–2-3 respectively)!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown is on.. Less than 4 hours until @kanebrown with my love 😍😍 @OlsonAustin31]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone give me a ride pls or I will either 1) freeze to death walking home or 2) get kidnapped or 3) accidentally… https://t.co/DSGq0hs4l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of : I waited til 7 days before rocky point to work out. Brb going to cry and squat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TokyoWoods @AOC You’re not the boss The American people are the boss you work for us https://t.co/LPbKpvSFyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi is finished. These three new b*tches are gonna run away with “her”party. 😜 And it defies all logic h… https://t.co/iAc9Sfyrfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to parent and research #MissingPeople cases, is a full time job.. But its so damn interesting!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Children deserve an education that is inherently meaningful and personal to them, and it should be one that humani… https://t.co/23NQeFD1UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/GgjsFpHrj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferozCarbon @CarlosBolsonaro Então, pela sua lógica,se eu roubar R$1000 e vc roubar 10000 vc é ladrão e eu não sou… https://t.co/47eQAWRoxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbantoronto We cannot allow for a Terrorist to come back home just because they changed their mind.  HE Chose to… https://t.co/4vNRT1xUEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDibiaseUgalde @UnitedWayMiami @HMLAdultEd Thank YOU for helping us create a #StrongerMiami!]]></document><document><![CDATA[E earned her first Personal Achievement Badge; Friendship Beaver ❤ #23rdNepean #scoutsdostuff #scoutscanada… https://t.co/HhgXGg7uhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Can you really tell all of us we should leave the Cohen family alone. Do you have no sh… https://t.co/W0wXsf8o46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stefy me mando uno de los mensajes de cumpleaños más bonitos y es donde me doy cuenta de que no tengo muchos amigos… https://t.co/0JOfd98NyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m kicking my habit &amp; smoking less, I accidentally did it again https://t.co/Pav0MqPt0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techguy @HollonKohtz @lenisocial @amariedauwer @MikesPastry @Colin_Hung I think I can fit in your suitcase. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSG_54 @RogueWolf2001 @NCLady50 @jmkillingnyc @Anthony4242 @AuntTritsy @TheSarge11 @louisanamom @StarvinLarry… https://t.co/9IzvB5Glvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[the European Parliament was barred entry into Venezuela after arriving at Caracas' airport Sunday night.  One of th… https://t.co/TZBspwInNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand how I could be this violently hungover still at 6pm????]]></document><document><![CDATA[#friday #fridaymood #💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖 @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/bI4Fz3nNrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socr8ive @SharkAmagansett @linds4fins @nemesistheshark @JenniHarding123 @mazzylynne @Pixieprogrammer… https://t.co/rUVANkkGAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tx_Rider1 @RTKash @wantsdong @jasonfoti @taketrumpdown @EleanorMontague @realDonaldTrump I just don’t think facts… https://t.co/Jw8iLyf9uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntiesophsoph_ Even the time breakdowns! I do this too. Honestly, watch it start late and you be “late” but on time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallowsMike @LynnToots @HuffPost I referring to LB’s comment. You sarcasm was on point!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it's time to take away fast food restaurants' social media accounts 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unalignedblog @Gneissguy62 @AtheistBigfoot @ActorwithaChip @ayagaaq @JanlexisR @iamAtheistGirl Having ‘Faith’ is b… https://t.co/ZIHe5ZHyoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF YOU WANT TICKETS TO FASHION WEEK HMU!!!! iM GOING TO BE APART OF THIS RUNWAY SHOW !!!!$ SO DM ME BITCHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other struggling people are NOT the enemy. Don’t replace empathy with resentment when things aren’t going your way.… https://t.co/TnMHhQwmrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@konagrl4554 I was like..."But...but...but...Will and Grace". Apparently, begging won't be working this time. Thank… https://t.co/9AiBz4yTJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RohanNadkarni Did you see the reaction of him and Westbrook at the end of the game?  Why do you make such a stupid… https://t.co/CkV4r6zzWI]]></document></documents></author>