<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Opening the Western Regional Forum!  @Da_Real_JMcBride  #WestForum @CB_Forums @ Renaissance Newport Beach Hotel https://t.co/FPceFP8f9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Inverness, FL? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Delivery Coor… https://t.co/L9aHEK6Fcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Angelical día! El Amor y la gratitud son el camino a ser feliz.  Bendiciones Angelicales 😇✨   #reflexiones… https://t.co/Ovln9ApZ05]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to upload a ton of Katsu pics for people to my Google drive anddddd my wifi goes out 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duchessgoldblat So much more elegant than those infernal doilies, and they don’t need to be pressed as often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letgolifeflows @CherubNation @gerrinnesmac @BabyGo2014 @pratoshnivedita @1shawnster @DonnaFins @PapaPorter1… https://t.co/ek10sd2qS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Citrus goodness ❤️❤️❤️ - Drinking a Conspiracy Tangle by @GristHouse at @bestbrewdeli  — https://t.co/AdkY9X3pTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN VENEZUELA, MADURO THE MONSTER MURDERER IS HAVING HIS ARMY FIRE TEAR GAS A RUBBER BULLETS AT AID WORKERS. AND AT… https://t.co/AXWLPvyRHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh. When will my pharmacy let me just text them a prescription number to refill it. That would be so awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakedownMRAs @Cernovich I’m sorry to him personally that I missed that https://t.co/81KMdTNvlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝙎𝙥𝙧𝙚𝙖𝙙 the 𝙡𝙤𝙫𝙚 shop 𝗹𝗼𝗰𝗮𝗹 💙. . . . #valentinesday #aurora #ontario #chamber #commerce #yorkregion #shoplocal… https://t.co/t66pM1SQOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeldebritoOk @ulisesjaitt Tremendo cobarde, PORQUE NO FUE CUANDO NATACHA NO ESTABA VIVA😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmjoonchan yup i was barely getting on the bus when people started running definitely scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HereIAm #Anticipation #PancakeTuesday @WellingtonCath #ChefsExtraordinaire! #StackEmUp https://t.co/vutzeCnm73]]></document><document><![CDATA[So close, and still so far! Literally (and I don’t mean figuratively) my entire DAY has been one loooong “delayed”… https://t.co/awMmnFT24g]]></document><document><![CDATA[kehlani &amp; musiq soulchild🦋 something i didn’t know i needed until now]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now they are speaking in tongue in a real conversation ...what happens around here when I’m not home 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC As a Puerto Rican woman i am so proud of you and how you are representing all of us as americans keep it up,Le… https://t.co/C8xcuNYJH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Dear Holy Father, you and the Curia are in my prayers. You are a wonderful spiritual leader. You always h… https://t.co/KKBDcAlbYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walder_Martz @edgarmanuel @GibsonUlises @Blizz2017 @Naty04k Ayudas con esto? Hola:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hermixedculture Cassie does not love him just as Becca did not love him back. Let her go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1 I’m the same way! I’m sure some people get annoyed but I just love my babies sooo much! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My flowers blossomed ❤️ They’re so pretty 🥰 ❤️ @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/a2itX3fvM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @GOP Disgusting. Jared and the feckless c**t were with the Saudis today. Terrorists from Saudi Arabia t… https://t.co/UveyZFdaRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shop Halifornia Apparel, get a 20% discount by using this code: AnnieA512261120 @halifornia_app  #halifornia.appare… https://t.co/o0BP7GLK17]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need this in my life. 😍 If I didn't already sell my soul...I would for this palette. 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Jordan and the republicans hit a new low everyday. The hateful disrespect is either horrifying or funny. Now it back to the Clintons 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night fun: “I side with” political quiz on my iPhone. 😂 #ThisIs32]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth is she should act like she’s a simulating and take off her head scarf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is There A Rise In Anti-Semitism In The House? https://t.co/JjV9QhvaFG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[How windy is it? Just got home to find out that, with my window barely open today, my light weight rocking chair was blown over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonMomoaNews if Jason is not on Twitter then their someone pretending to be him and messaging fan privately and that's not cool..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSeanMaloney The Never Forget the Heroes: Permanent Authorization of the September 11th Victim Compensation Fund… https://t.co/jm0XaYghRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to spike lee and rich #Hollyweird telling average blue collar workers how to vote, while you are behind gat… https://t.co/ULucNkO8TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where the Dead Fall by MJ Lee - just started reading https://t.co/oHkMaVuB3s via @lelbudge]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite feelings is arriving into @DTWeetin after business travel. #happybirthdayDTW #kramowicz #Kramlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S. can I be the official superstar fundraising expert gay of the @StephMillerShow?   Or do you have like 100 of u… https://t.co/jY9lgpHIKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Atrium Health? We're hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click for details: https://t.co/S4uDlz4xEX #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mackenz_kitchen @LeadersGC @StatCan_eng Awesome! I’d love to hear more about the custom training for data viz. It’… https://t.co/3fcKMrPqVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Ticketmaster @TMFanSupport I have tried for days to purchase Hamilton tickets for this weekend via the Ticket Exc… https://t.co/J0CmvY0jQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever fought over a bitch you weird the bitch choose up why would I fight for her bitch you can go lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I need to change my name bc idk who this is anymore https://t.co/TUvSk5rJhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up math was like trying to follow someone else's directions... That you can't take with you. Remember the d… https://t.co/bwhJKxF3u6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wagonwednesday 1956 DeSoto Firedome station wagon, notable for its optional 3-tone paint scheme which DeSoto intro… https://t.co/qZbNKmBodk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayduddleyy my playlist really reminds of your playlist you used to play on our way to church! any other suggestions 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[just saw a 21 yr old miss the world record indoor mile time by .02 seconds and finished in 3:48 on tv... not the bi… https://t.co/3C9gIOtHTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally have no friends anymore, i thought that came after graduation 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would really like to get some dinner but really don’t have the energy to put on pants 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @cspanwj @RepMarcyKaptur There is a whole Ecomomey out there ready to be Plucked...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #HiltonHeadIsland, SC, check out this job: https://t.co/PyPPqHsZdX #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working at a hospital where they teach you how to take down an attacker by gouging their eyes out is the hospital for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hdyoungblood @CarySikes @lightbringer333 I love working with “learners” and “go getters!” #greatstaff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy SaturYAY!!!! I’m on @971AMPRadio right MEOW! Listen live: https://t.co/bptjqL6AXd 🐱 https://t.co/8pZJJwRzkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to buy new workout clothes, maybe that’ll motivate me some more 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a snippet of her 643 juggles from recent indoor training. #goRush #personalbestinthethousands https://t.co/oqYXkZDRMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chelsea__Gamble Wanna hear the worst part Chelsea???  It was an ESL teacher who advised it! 🤦🏽‍♀️😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[My soul has been cleansed 🙌🏻 Thank you!!! Dr Ross!! @JasonRossOfc #RoomsTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond @marieosmond   I am done with both my surgeries. I am almost fully recovered from the second.  Now I a… https://t.co/sKYrglhTFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why get mad when I call you out when you know damm well what your doing dumb ass 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amy I've been watching you now I think from the very beginning.. felt like I went down this crazy paranormal experi… https://t.co/C8Q2AON9O6]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning feeling kinda extra blessed today for the new people God put in my life that are the source of my happiness 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Canova @AOC Was it acceptable to question the Bush administration with their failed coup of Chavis??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charges dismissed against Sini Mathews, mother of Richardson girl found dead in culvert. #SherinMathews https://t.co/gSeXB1vxRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES and parents too!!!  Your (everyone’s) words, attitudes and actions reach out into the community and are either… https://t.co/xghDJv3dTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dunno why I ask myself in the morning if it’s gonna be a rest day. I’m already awake. And this weather is going to wake me up even more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyTheCypriot @AmericanAir I enjoyed it. Thought it was quite good. I was hungry, so I scarfed it down quite quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be doing this shit for completely free my dudes and I still gotta pay for parking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Justices hold your hands on the Bible and do the Godly thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Los Angeles for the #Oscars2019   (actually for a seminar @USC_Econ next Tuesday) https://t.co/521ac1O1cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[you bet i’m repping the legends @superwhatevr about to see the dude in @mtrench kill it on stage https://t.co/WTkjC35Qow]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️🇺🇸Cool bar. - Drinking a Pabst Blue Ribbon by @pabstblueribbon @ The Bull And Bear  — https://t.co/bCpiG3dj1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicoDelainky Exactly!! The mainstream news outlets doing their best to earn the name “fake news!” Why are they MI… https://t.co/x4TDo8Sbpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engineering looms and learning about plarning in 6th grade @spmeagles @MagnetSidi https://t.co/WulJarOC7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polticallyours @rachelheldevans This is a bizarre example. As per scripture, every part of the body is valuable an… https://t.co/FUvFXwLqrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkrepp @RSP_DC @RobertLBateman @20002ist Recreate the diamond! Btw, I really feel this needs a t-shirt. I will get to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyLovesTrump @LeAnn4Trump @duckusa @dclark551 @monica_sassy @palebluecream @Luddybehrens @M8Kurt @Antoinotabot… https://t.co/ub0z066KuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t sleep been up for over an hour so what do I do wash a load of clothes n clean my bathroom smh #TeamNoLife smdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday a first timer with a light blue Afro came in because she needed an outfit for a birthday celebration.  Sh… https://t.co/6BDR6TbboV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InquiringY @RukhnamaLives @sarahkendzior Who was Jared s family selling visa to for $500k a pop?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamás me habían mentado tanto la madre hasta hoy que me quede tirada en Gonzalitos 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcdays Yes! Excited to see @ThaaoPenghlis returning to our screens and as Tony...hmm is Andre lurking around too?… https://t.co/jwwRyjJPp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week in NY at the final release dinner for the wehoeditionresidences 💫 @johnpawsonnews #architecture #bestofla… https://t.co/ehMMnzXfA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump SO, why U so worried about it? Why U so worried?  Vote FOR WHOEVER!!! WE ARE MAGA 20… https://t.co/TOEA4msu10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to everyone including the love of my life Woo Jiho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithbarbv @rebeccabguinn @RepMcClintock Here's why Tom voted NO Tom gets PAC money  Tom represents special intere… https://t.co/Xqg80BFkTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The feels when.... My angry neighbor prefers 6 empty houses rather than vetting good families at a normal rent.  #inheritance #StAugustine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDGXC I saw those results! That’s some crazy depth! Your program is IMPRESSIVE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realised I’ve only worn air force 1s in both of the music videos I have...they’re deffo my favourite shoe, thi… https://t.co/yffIxygjOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the simplified eating article. As I've aged I do change what I eat w the seasons, but keep it very simple an… https://t.co/0r3HM8tvjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @1SweetLadyBlue @realDonaldTrump They should be. This is the biggest, worst part of this terrible carnival… https://t.co/g4pVTnuPN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_D_Boyle @43a6f0ce5dac4ea Omg...That is assault...What gives the people in uniform the right to such in Hum… https://t.co/tfz0m89kX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a lying sack of 💩. You put the needs of investors and privatizers first. @BadassTeachersA]]></document><document><![CDATA[can i mute have heart from my timeline now? i don’t care that u didn’t get a ticket]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are pics with Jim, Sr and my attempts testing my grip strength. The look I gave him in the last video says it… https://t.co/yESFO22l7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @IsadoraBright @TheresePhilaPA @iDudeness @Aaron_Lifts @GrandmaVeteran @TiffanyBond… https://t.co/7ZCo94MstQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is demonstrably better for having muted terms related to that horrifying Tim Burton-esque image that was inundating my TL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haugmoen @hermitcrabeggs It takes a couple of bad people to ruin the system for the ones who were honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[../\  /   \ |  |  | |  |  |  \ \/  /\ \ |  |  | |  |  | \    /   \/icko Mode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley I an concerned that you and Condeelezza Rice sat and had a discussion with John Brennan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you meet new people and get the same vibe as the friends you have you know in your heart it wasn't you it was them the entire time]]></document></documents></author>