<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#registration has been re-opened!Generate is a week long #worship experience held in late July in Lake of the Ozark… https://t.co/MNm7hMcsEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo  and @joannagaines ? Now this is an interesting collaboration! I can't wait! #HGTV #FixerUpper… https://t.co/U3TJ2T9xO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest Be safe and I pray the doctors are blessed with wisdom. Hope whatever is minor and quickly resolved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump THAT’S BECAUSE HE IS AN INSECURE IGNORANT MAN WHO DOESN’T KNOW HOW TO BE A LEADER!!!… https://t.co/8lv0BhxdHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieMorseNews Good morning  Still in NYC it's cold 😷 this morning  Have a blessed day and a safe one much ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @RepMaxineWaters MAXINE WATTERS HAS DIRTY LITTLE SECRETS TOO.. MAXINE  BAILED OUT A BAD BANK HER HUSBAND WORKS… https://t.co/Q8fE2YKeY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skhali dont ask me why but I just thought about the bees 🐝🐝🐝 https://t.co/5fk3cl6oiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL that the packaging for my girlfriend’s headphones has a tortured soul trapped in it. #packaging #horror #funny… https://t.co/1nY7BJe7E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YashhD_FC @Yash_Dasgupta @SVFsocial @p00namjha @iammony Happy International Women's Day To All The Wonderful Women… https://t.co/N44tlW1u9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao I haven’t had the heart to tell my mom she’ll get limited visitation with her grandchildren lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TippeyTay I think it’s learned behavior like racism and colorism. Society tells people fat = bad/terrible and peop… https://t.co/8HHDfOwPcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge @Genericpolitic1 @odetteroulette I have a hard time watching him answer questions because he gets so… https://t.co/8hoQSoH8TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-ordered. ✅ @IsaacMizrahi #IMAMemoir @audible_com https://t.co/FJAywa4KTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ERedCarpet  who is your blonde correspondent in the pink with black spots Little House on the Prairie long sleeve dress?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if these would look good with my bike helmet. #cyclinglife https://t.co/s94pvZHswg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FourthGradeL *grams is a unit of mass (weight means something different) I am not familiar with the term capacity?… https://t.co/mEKObusJxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq This woman has no expletive understanding of what she is flippantly throws around like so much red meat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya nuay respeto! Ingrato ladron, le tocó cara hacer una nueva escoba de monte a la señora.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElTabloncillo Pero Marcus Hatten fue el ídolo. Quizás @FranciscoVega sabe más al respecto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carrying my father’s flag on @Delta 2186 from ATL&lt;DCA. He always loved DC by air. RIP, Papa Smith, it’s our last flight together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll take ‘my heart is breaking but I will keep the faith’ for one million. 💗 #fuckcancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see me looking slim af tomorrow mind your business. Jenny coming with me to the gym has been hell but worth it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Live Wire by Mötley Crüe 🎼🔥🖤 https://t.co/7dWldFw6E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graygraync And this is news? It’s going to be a very long 623 days.   #2020Election]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the fact that I have thick thighs but no ass is such a disappointment and it is not fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul You have NO IDEA HOW MANY ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS ARE POURING IN AMERICA / WHERE THERE IS NO FENCE!  Bing: Tex… https://t.co/MCzWmH4bHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer I saw every single one nominated for best picture, actress, actor, supporting actress/actor categor… https://t.co/LMcjv8hRAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcradioq I remember seeing this for the first time from The Weather Network and wondering.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else notice how Bradley Cooper’s GF’s face has been frozen in that fake smile all night???? 🤔 #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Good. They are another arm of Russia as long as they continue to promote favorable Trump propaganda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥 Everyday... in-salon or when I’m traveling for work, it’s crazy to think I really am LIVING my dream ( and it’s j… https://t.co/Tac6fBtOha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me at Bar America blasting Beyonce on touch tunes https://t.co/X1PgZTiCwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can I help end this? Tell me? Please! I’m not being ignorant. Tell me how, please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now I'm sure i sound like I'm making excuses. But it's not that, it's knowing what my body is capable of.   Whe… https://t.co/Ka47z3g0no]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time I was on the air w with @DerekRhodenizer 🇨🇦 🇺🇸 🎙  Great reminders on how to boost achievement of ALL… https://t.co/o851HLIC3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sick of waiting for you to love me I’m not begging anymore... If you love only time will tell...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly why I haven’t got my lashes done yet...cs once i start loosing my eyelashes somebody gone get beat tf up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @redmartagons @AylaForTrump @jonz970 @SoulofMaga @mymynags @SealeyGerald @KevinMFerrara @stlpcs… https://t.co/EWS2rAGE0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎙Selena Tribute at club80s_bar was like a reunion.🎙🎶 #selena #80smusic #saturdaynight @ Club 80s Bar &amp; Grill https://t.co/V6dFZTr9Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TannerJDavis12 @KELLYOUBREJR Lol he did go to KU but have you seen him!? 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more simple things in life make you realize how truly blessed you are. https://t.co/2yGpz1T6AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Robert Kraft spends the rest of his life in shame. Let’s please keep talking about this rather than let him… https://t.co/geXx85NXtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm supposed to be happy for you when a different guy tries to get in your pants, but when I have a man, you can… https://t.co/ajI1WdlffU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it comes, let it come. If it goes, let it go. Let things come and go. Stay calm, don’t let anything or anyone di… https://t.co/S7rsspaK2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#365diasdegratitud #Dia49 hoy agradezco el yogurt con cereal, las velas de olor y la luna llena 🌕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lebrownlow Can't tell you how many times I have changed out of dark red because I work at Clemson and it feels kin… https://t.co/GGEaFrcfSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m not going to give you the cornbread out of my own pocket or anything, but....”]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. to the little freshmen that ran and slammed my locker after school your a little ass bitch cuz the fucking hit m… https://t.co/n8vEUg3w4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope to goodness someone has posted a photo of that Skagra cosplay at #gally1 tonight. It was hilariously perfect… https://t.co/IWFPfMd4Zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert_Rose Point 1, I’ve definitely noticed that the line between social ads and organic content have been blurre… https://t.co/WfpC4q7ptN]]></document><document><![CDATA[and now i’m on my way to integris to see @chantellwhynn_’s baby and i’m literally gonna cry when i hold her, my hea… https://t.co/UjmGND1H2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it wasn’t a smidge too small for my head, I’d totally take this home! @ The Mercantile at Milton https://t.co/NtNUjerjQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuck_a The only decisions I have the energy to make right now is “which kind of ice cream?” and “do I watch Netfl… https://t.co/ZOcCtWOgLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#culture is more important than language in tech engagement. Level up our policies and opt into #healthtxt #sxsw #techuity #hearthealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq For a rich guy friend of his who rumors to have set him up as well + his buddy @AlanDersh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbulbk An AWESOME place to get your Degree!!!!!   Campuses aroung the World, a Nursing School, fantastic classes o… https://t.co/KmZtdrqKZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever notice that skin looks like that skin on the orange under the peel that holds the orange organs inside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eleven years ago, I was trapped in a bruised and broken body unable to feed or bathe myself. I do this daily to rem… https://t.co/mGB4XJmZ8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Bug Eyes(AOC), she may have a point. Legal taxpaying Americans are struggling, not quite convinced they are lef… https://t.co/GV4hincaYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The will to win, the desire to succeed, the urge to reach your full potential... these are the keys that will unloc… https://t.co/6QYTqMvSdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OllyMead1 @pillbobaggins @themisscocoperu @LaurenB111994 @TheBiancaDelRio Until she takes her teeth out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads in the sand... money 💰 in his pocket from fossil fuel ...#GOP doesn’t care anymore..it’s just about the 💰💰💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure that I would have bought it even if the #amazoncoat came in purple.  https://t.co/GusfbLmMJV #orolay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Why do you think he started the Dare program? The racist scare tactics I was taught as a white child… https://t.co/IPV7NFikHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC interesting, when Obama, Bush and other presidents played golf the media always covered!  I'm assuming that… https://t.co/d44Bm7HJaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need one of these!!! Who is with me? 🙋‍♀️ #WakeUpWisconsin #WorkWithKZ https://t.co/TR60INjMki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elmercc Kid Rock’s iteration of America the Beautiful is sure to bring the house down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i post one guy on my snap and everyone swears that’s my guy🤣🤣 sweetie, noooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_maxwell12 https://t.co/Qjg35cFqrR! the sizing is weird so when you look at the chart, get a size smaller than wh… https://t.co/cNVu428Efh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevineb The only thing at this point that gives me some semblance of calm is that my response to most of the repli… https://t.co/jCUEiENDQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton  she probably knows you will be impeached before the next re-election or @GavinNewsom will take over!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mialka @francoislegault Il y a beaucoup de personnes qui  donnent mais n’en parlent jamais]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@APIOhio’s fearless leader @cbzeigler weighs in on Governor DeWine proposed 18 cent gas tax increase https://t.co/A8tAN3Jov2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the bomb pedicure yellow toes an nails .. Meanwhile I still feel like shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth This is so full of garbage. What is her ties to the Democratic Party or Jussie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelenaNarcisse True but still I would of said well the dam kid wouldn't listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be having 1 tattoo the size of a nickel and manage to get it in every picture you post]]></document><document><![CDATA[jus had a dude ask me for my phone number and i said i have a man and he goes me too like what lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late tweets on my fave soap #GH, even thou I caught up already on Fri 4 the 1st time!! Cant wait 2 see wat happens… https://t.co/pVICZPiOGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cullenenn @PadenTyrel @FrozunYogert @JordanUhl @AOC I wouldn’t live there and if I did I would work my butt off and save save save.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen testimony on Trump: 'He is a racist. He is a conman. He is a cheat.' https://t.co/KAlSE4ABbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora si le digo, “mueva esas nalgas” porque en Venezuela el pais esta sin luz desde el 7 de marzo de 2019 a las 5… https://t.co/OCEiaVSRKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic @LisaMei62 We are very blessed to be able to have Patriots like y’all who are mostly right on target… https://t.co/42Bdzj48iD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where the Aloft sits on NE 2nd and Walnut in @DeepDeuce Ward 7 was once the Finley Building that saw many patients… https://t.co/6duLFC6TDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6: I recently planned a baby shower with some besties! We used a Google doc to plan. Our goal and budget was set,… https://t.co/ILyS9Fvp5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, head over and order my friend book! I’ll be getting mine and will request an autograph. 😉 @CisnerosCafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Versatility is key. If you only listen to rap music or one specific genre, then you’re selling yourself short..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basedinfidel8 @fellspeaks @AlexWY18 @Chriskl70208387 @TH3R34LTRUTH @Americanthatguy @johnw299 @AJuM809… https://t.co/XIfJVVahmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful friends remembering you today and thinking of the wealth of gifts you bring to the world.  Keep going, Ke… https://t.co/Way6dFfD5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way to predict the future is to create it. - Peter F. Drucker #missysquoteoftheday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recovery time...@ Euclid Chiropractic in Upland ⁦@2Contrerasqb⁩  ⁦@CoachPerrone⁩ https://t.co/STnnM0rXRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We in trouble! 🤦🏼‍♀️ #KinderCrush #PBSlove @ Parkview Baptist School https://t.co/8aJI2AWfO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I should not talk about my emotions and keep them to myself for sure .]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel so old all the time and then people will remind me that i am only 22 and kinda still a baby. i just feel lik… https://t.co/Je5cW9Ka2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3 am and I’m still not in bed. Jensen this weekend had completely ruined my bedtime schedule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blaisekellerr That face...there is a reason God made puppies so cute. Tomorrow you will be like Poo, What Poo? I l… https://t.co/XzW98Atl5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Right! The 70's was my favorite time. I am an old lady in my 50's I feel now...where did the time go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinSoliz16 It’s kinda slow in the beginning but it gets really good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSZHorse @racetrackandy @santaanitapark Del Mar put out a release (or I read it somewhere) that they cant open the… https://t.co/HToA6T9U8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanZiering I am so sorry for your loss. We have some mutual friends and I know you spend time in CT. Wondering if… https://t.co/Ey92e0fSGP]]></document></documents></author>