<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @hibillyby James, u r a good man!!! Warms my heart that u did this for that family. True American patriot!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to watch #TheKidsAreAllRight ... so far #ThisIsUs is much funnier @ABCNetwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful night for a ballgame! Game 2 for the Doggies in Florida! @UMDBaseball https://t.co/JMyRiZvmMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up on my @ColdOatmealPod  at the gym. Thanks @ReschStrategies for getting me through the workout. Great co… https://t.co/sPl0xibgS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay Here's how the dopey dems asked the Asst AG Whitaker some questions....What is your name....? Yes or No....… https://t.co/Nvsbhc0ex0]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone tell david to get the vlog camera out it’s time to prank brandon again except this time it’s real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbiwan How lighthearted? Revisionist History is good @D_Vander_Griend recommend, Stephen Fry’s Great Leap Years is… https://t.co/6g8UxCzofo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hunter Slater doubled and Matthew Guidry scored.  It’s now 10-7, there are no outs, men on the corners.  Hunter LeB… https://t.co/HqI1FvuSQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anistonsbell See my entry up a few.The LA basin is hard to find straight people verses bisexuals,etc....]]></document><document><![CDATA[A hitting error ends a really long Set 2 (thanks, NCAA, for the challenge rule) and the Cougars win 25-22. Match ti… https://t.co/a6DWmKvx6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cocktails to Ice Cream! Vanilla Bean infused Raw Honey adds depth and interest to your meal! Buy a jar at Good Eart… https://t.co/OhUTlqgptR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have Donald Trump, he has the Clintons and Obama’s. Checkmate Bill you dumbass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN So  show some respect when you enter the halls of Congress and take that towel off your head You little terrorist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myopicrhino @untappd @myopicrhino is everything ok?  I'm seeing a large number of beer related posts tonight...  🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from your @GMA meteorologists! ;) https://t.co/qhr4riCykM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benigma2017 @La__Farfalla @SouthernGal918 @KamalaHarris Victimless crime is just another way to exploit the poor v… https://t.co/gEbNCFO9IO]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL STATS:  Friendship Leaders: Nick Farrar w/ 35p (19 of those in the 2H) and Jayden Beloti w/ 30p (18 of those… https://t.co/ZZIWWf76Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenpeace Founder Calls Jet-Setting AOC Hypocritical ‘Pompous Little Twit’ Over Green New Deal https://t.co/ajKpPe7XZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Look at that sorry face. Never has there been less character etched into a face.He is such a lowlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveanthony Maybe some of us don’t have time to cook and need a healthy option?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGatawe @BrianWincherauk @merry123459 Sorry no luck but I will keep looking as I am curious myself now]]></document><document><![CDATA[So every morning I come to work these two ducks fly over from somewhere and just chill at the front of the school 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Whispers):   D’Angelo Russell’s trajectory is eerily similar to Steph Curry’s...  (Runs away)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house at second public hearing for appointment finalists being considered for the vacancy created by the depar… https://t.co/9s0ge7F8BT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BallstonQuarter @ARLnowDOTcom Many people trying to enter the food court that was reported to open today but is st… https://t.co/hWNj4sP0AB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When's the last time you changed your furnace filter? #Amazon #Prime it now. 😉 Here's a helpful link from my friend… https://t.co/Mb42UTkEKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why eat prime rib when you can just eat ribeye steak #primerib #ribeye #steak #ribeyesteak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZMMTeleRadyo @alvinelchico @DorisBigornia Sa tingin ko Po ay babatikusin na naman ni Duterte ang CHR, pag nag sampa sila ng kaso 🤭🤭🤭🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNoahRing I feel like it's Christmas in February. @POTUS @realDonaldTrump made promises to America and he damn w… https://t.co/bpntTiFzMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soph Caden Coleman in the high jump. 2nd 6-2. 2018 PR 5-8. Good start to the season. https://t.co/sdNcxjXk46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @9975Ts @AOC 🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🖕🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🐯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisfarmwife My wife calls and says brown some hamburger...we’ll figure it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachHalverson @ChadRAbbott @KFAN1003 @patmick2626 @MarkDParrish @dsryan16 I hope your car doesn’t start]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacDcol @OttCatholicSB Thank you so much, Colleen!! It’s an honour to receive a nomination for this special award.… https://t.co/Oob5al3Kmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suisser @neeratanden It’s a sign of mental illness that you know what her voice sounds like]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spann snow total so far in my backyard from overland park kansas https://t.co/lVkNnVSkdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Victim passed away at Huntsville hospital. Suspect is at large.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling too anxious to play already but I have to be patient🥴⚽️ https://t.co/LUsU2oEzN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are too quick to blame border patrol over kid/unborn baby deaths at the border, and not the parents who drag… https://t.co/q4RQOGYaIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavenly is just ....Heavenly #skiheavenly #laketahoeispretty @ South Lake Tahoe, California https://t.co/J87i9Tc2Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanDance_1240 @Circling_Bean I will not confirm nor deny making this account]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronquille_paul @DrWhoisin @MarilynLavala @IamTheStorm8 @changeditall @MAGAveteranRobi @TheLONEWOLFE3 @OhioBot5000… https://t.co/dnJh4Ebz8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough loss for @WabashBBall tonight, but it’s been one helluva ride. Gotta keep grinding and working to make the fu… https://t.co/Y3mUUkaYJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot describe how good this smells.  It's just amazing.  Pure Irish happiness. @ The Owen Brewhaus https://t.co/n9TIDmo4Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Trump is a pathological liar.  Mexico isn’t paying for his wall.  Trump now wants to cut Medicare, Me… https://t.co/iFWXNoA5tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeYoungWWE Did you hear what @RondaRousey call me on #Raw tonight she say Dan the Man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteAbe Should not be on active roster if he can’t play back to back games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t want people with negative attitudes towards customers working for me either way. But 1)that’s just my op… https://t.co/XqhIGBxl2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you have a problem when you pull three travel coffee mugs out of your work backpack that you completely fo… https://t.co/0xegNirFD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the bigger issue is that #gerrymandering  in #Politics to this extent is wrong no matter who does it Republican… https://t.co/laRwzF3i4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, without any intended irony, complains he is victim to a "a new low in American politics". https://t.co/22LtpqTQdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pag nag apply ka ba as intern, kelangan dalin resume / portfolio?!?! Uhmmmm. Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyinBrianJr Your dad was and will always be one of my all time favorite performers.  Going all the way back to th… https://t.co/3LbCNNPFDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modern_drummer Really?  It’s not a baseball bat.  From Day One...thumb and index finger hold....the other three dance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartEyes4Brady And one more full week until we move the clocks ahead!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiefer Sutherland Says Obama Connection Keeps 'Designated Survivor' Honest https://t.co/dDyV2nusQI via @TMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontyoudarryn I always thank my future machine overlords for deeming me worthy of their goods.  You never know when they will rise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShayPhD @AOC They will begin a process to have her removed or Democrats will ne https://t.co/2EQM7xneHY much as… https://t.co/HJLXghlqmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wait. So they just stole an hour from us?? 😾” #dst https://t.co/0LuhbYuWcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @thekatiemorgan @thekenzietaylor @AshleyFires @CathyHeavenXXX @HaleyReedX @SkylaNoveaXXX @AnnadeVilleXXX… https://t.co/MWUaxaARrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[La partición de 1947 del Imperio Británico en India e independencia de India y Pakistán nos han legado una de las z… https://t.co/rCregS3gkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. Omg this is how I got my first sugar daddy. Memories 😭💖💓 shoutout to Him💖💓💖💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this... "Well, the best thing about death is you won't know about it. It's like being stupid, it's only painfu… https://t.co/NlCe5I01l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTBaseballPhoto #redlegnation where u at #centurypeat https://t.co/knntJe9qaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your craving steak. You go to the pro’s. #shafer shafervineyards harrissteakhouse #classics #bestofthebest… https://t.co/swPjCbgdc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I’m finally going to step up and say no and quit making myself miserable by going out of my way for everyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump IS this note legA-L SAFETY for All debts public And privAte TENDER SAFETY under non combat state o… https://t.co/3tJjXU4pML]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Foley wanted to come home Stephen sotloff. Daniel pearl. And countless other massacred Americans ALL wanted to come home too!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I did so far to the HSP Brontosaurus (now Pro).  Mod to the Hobbywing motor Heatsink.  #hobbywing c_lozfpv… https://t.co/F8clcJ5XKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[aoc is a turd.  yeah i said it.  i mean it.  whoever likes aoc apparently likes trump too.  please get this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbazan3 @11point7podcast Thanks my man!   Maybe we can set up an Alwayst sponsorship sometime 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Wow.  @AOC,  who needs another Congresswoman to tell her when to clap, stand up, sit down and what to wear, li… https://t.co/slige0g8kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jnunez248 If we get KD tatum doesn't matter at all And none of the players like Kyrie. Tatum doesn't even wanna pl… https://t.co/13oKQXX5DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavinTheBees Still your best tweets. Need to get these framed https://t.co/dc7e8hWEDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since day one @ScottMoffatt21 has supported our Ottawa Children’s Gala, heading into its 9th this Saturday! Thanks… https://t.co/jektjA8gHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantalStrand For a kid's show, Hey Arnold wasn't afraid of tackling some really dark themes. For example, Helga,… https://t.co/0KNl1eQWGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_Beckley @Merica_Media Are you talking about the album by the Pretenders? If so, that’s a good one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, #OasisPRIDE was on full display for our @PeoriaUnified11 job fair. Prospective teachers from around the… https://t.co/1ICBIWNGKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[66% of New Yorkers prefer renting to owning their homes. Home owning is part of the “American Dream”then why this a… https://t.co/eZjP0nIxtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: Bernie Can’t Think Of Any Legislation He’s Passed That Helps People - https://t.co/ybkMhR3LhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was nominated by @MrsGorz to post 7 book covers in 7 days, no explanations. So here’s #2 https://t.co/ypzbqcaTGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6QDrTzkH43 Past and future spread of the #arbovirus #vectors Aedes #aegypti and #Aedes #albopictus | N… https://t.co/E8mDE8jVj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJJasonNagel Come to this and bounce to V’s for one of the last shows there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blessed to have @ArmyAClub supporters/friends that bring me gifts from home!! Even if he thinks Pat’s is better… https://t.co/MMCK59apNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing @barstoolsports promoting NASCAR all weekend. It’s a great sport, people need to appreciate it more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeathSlaterOMRB Would you be interested in being a special guest on the #BehindTheMic Radio Show? #CheapSeats… https://t.co/b7J1JWkDkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatCultureWWE Didnt they say there was going to be a "big announcement" during @WWENXT? Well, NXT came and went a… https://t.co/ufy83xXGJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the Eagles get Bell and Antonio Brown from Steelers??? It will fix the  Wideout #1 and featured running back in… https://t.co/ZNnCcP9kDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEonlyMVYoung Hey that's great.  Now, again, I'll take the spicey beef and a Kirin Ichiban. And chopsticks too.  Tahnks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got to look on the bright side, even if there ain't one. Dashiell Hammett @ Toledo, Ohio https://t.co/eoR2y9Mx2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @CoachDubMaddox Great hype speech, now you have to go hit somebody]]></document><document><![CDATA[It always good when I holla a my bro @CoachReed314 . We bout to do something real big here soon!! #STL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhandiKay_ @laishalay @femt00 @austy__ @Azha_Bufkin @KhandiKay_ @KhandiKay_ @KhandiKay_ @KhandiKay_ @KhandiKay_]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great at #bnpparibas yesterday... #federer and #nadal make their tournament debut today..incredible grounds, atm… https://t.co/WtvvWLrRcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty tame final round, and I gave it to Ugas. But no Joe I don't think Shawn agrees. 115-113 Ugas here. Draw no s… https://t.co/Cgl4tXqFzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annaleen Oh yeah, ohhhh, ahhh, that's how it always starts. But then later there's running, and screaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rasnick_Kevin Make sure you bring them to the @TwinsDaysFest first weekend in August #Congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starbucks Banana Nut Bread (@ Plaza Bonita Food Court in National City, CA) https://t.co/LrptkA4C16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flepervanche @dmonsterverde El Heat está tratando de entrar en la lotería de que mierdas hablas 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAMMIT I HAVE TO UPDATE MY GOFUNDME YET AGAIN.  I hate this. The begging more than the eviction.  An attorney is ca… https://t.co/7Ocj0zLpYO]]></document></documents></author>