<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Have never said this before but Amen Oprah for bringing rape and sexual assault to the fire front lines! Happen’s in every family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAY!!! 30 Day Knife Juggling Challenge DAY #3 🤹‍♀️🎪🔪😅 Today I juggled two knives for the FIRST TIME while alternati… https://t.co/BcqyeU978j]]></document><document><![CDATA[s/o to my bff @brando_da_mando who drove all the way to arlington from cstat at 9 at night to have fun only to end… https://t.co/GLuiclmmH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muhammad told Philadelphia magazine. “I had no weapon on me, and I went through metal detectors twice without any p… https://t.co/LWBMzeizhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made the grave mistake of parking directly under a tree at work today. 🦅💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDIS Nooooooo!!!!!!!  We were going to do this when we are there next year!  I was looking forward to our night… https://t.co/n0DQzetCI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is total BS. Outrageous. When was the last time you went a day without lying? Are you under a… https://t.co/WhsBeKyaFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake Great questioning from Rep Dina Titus! She knows her stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antonioguterres @NorwayInGeneva @UN I would like more clarity on what peace has done for the U.N. in more than one… https://t.co/zULd8lSMuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roshaniel21 I would highly recommend taking advantage of all the free coupons and giveaways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryxKenshin go back let aj shoot that lady cause James wasn’t supposed to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cool_foreva You look like your namesake.   I had mine cut off once, liked how l looked so different. I felt like l… https://t.co/hBoNueuk1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RelloTooLit Nah your taste buds are just wrong. You probably don’t like tomatoes either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWillowWilson Adagio has a wild strawberry tea that tastes so good hot with a little sweetener. (I mean, I'm sure… https://t.co/A3OF2don1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are these people...?... They are Worse than Deplorable!!!   #DetainNielsenInNotCage  #SendTrumpCultToCornField… https://t.co/seDcdOThTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lumiger1 @JacobAWohl You’re full of demonicrat 💩💩💩💩👺🐀! President Trump happens to be MAKING. AMERICA GREAT 👍 AGAIN… https://t.co/pCZIVBce48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods I wish you peace and I hope this situation doesn’t stop you from blooming into a boss ass bitch. Take… https://t.co/BPWKIgaLAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME Actually it is not true what this article claims about the Fernandina  Tortoise.  It is not extinct. Scientists recently found one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow what just happened?!?? It was 78 and sunny in my world 2 hours ago! Welcome home to me..... 😳❄️ https://t.co/gNiylGpglG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers Holy shit!!! Preach it, it needs to be heard all the way to the capitol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yolian_ogbu WOW, congratulations!!!  Another amazing adventure for you this summer 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTGily really out here turning 21 meanwhile I thought he was 25 the whole time 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking through my Spotify playlists when I was in middle school and all I wanna know is... WHY WAS I SO SAD like girlllll if only you knew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RihannaFreak20 Idk I don’t know all of her work but Looking Ass Niggas was more flames for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple pictures.  Siding is looking awesome for the new spec house, awards with Allen Tate, I was humbled and exc… https://t.co/CU53pWtIgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Charlotte: overcast clouds, 34°F 64% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1019mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ant. 3 Let us joyfully praise the Lord our God.  Psalm 147:1-11 The loving kindness of God who can do all he wills… https://t.co/dHaANANIct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molly_sear @julietsear_18 @joey13matthews @thatropeskid who else? @ayleneeeee @caseyyvanv @mrazbrandon @brookem1517 @katieeromano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 174th birthday, Florida! Florida joined the union as the 27th state on March 3,1845. #7thgenerationfloridian… https://t.co/z9ptRJIZIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior @ClaytonCuster3 had a big 3 at the 8:55 mark for @RamblersMBB to get the lead back to 16 over Bradley.@WBEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I feel like men will just take whatever is there in front of them at that moment. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA @old_mum I'm lost???  But if it's a good thing then cool!! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not worry About anything; instead, pray about everything. Tell God what you need, and thank Him for all he has d… https://t.co/29DriemCv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any way to have the open (and probably super crowded) meet/greet with u in a more private location for my teenage s… https://t.co/mA2hJyAXc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I love about Dre is that he has SIX comfy ass pillows on his bed 👏🏼🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdvHntr @monaeltahawy I can't believe she's using the "in the journalist, therfore I know better" argument in 2019… https://t.co/tQCxEpWRCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at McCarran International Airport - @lasairport in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/JiQyCeDXGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[beginning to think I am completely utterly (and disproportionately) incompetent at getting laid given my relative hotness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Svob_Stewart43 two years of putting up with me and he still loves me unconditionally. https://t.co/1YxMvYvBmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods So much for her underprivileged childhood. Sounds like it was pretty good. Too bad she repays it by… https://t.co/jGk1xq04ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi loves! I’m selling Scentsy to take the burden off my study abroad costs. If you or anyone you know likes scentsy… https://t.co/PtqnnjFU2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cali_astrocat season 2 got the green light today! so now it’s just a waiting game. i just finished season 1 of Misfits and loved it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAndyNgo @OhioState The ‘liberation group’ forgot to add the word ‘Marxist’ to their title. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[dead ass upset as hell that Q passed away. like i think that shit has finally hit me now. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martin Yu crossed 3.1. Time 00:28:02, pace 09:02 min/mile, est. finish 10:57 am https://t.co/fDhRiOths5 #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would agree John he has been around these fake news people for years. Even Fox can be disappointing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Proud Boys” Extremist group White Nationalist. This is who @realDonaldTrump calls good people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gorgeoussss_e Block em real quick 😂 my mom was the same way til I had to remind her that following me is a privile… https://t.co/UiW0Ene4YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman Probably because he didn't take it or paid someone to take it for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t make it to the first @juniorleaguestj Cinderella’s Closet giveaway? There are still three more giveaway date… https://t.co/pWXHFYDieh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether it’s the #Oscars or the #alayma it’s easy to share your disappointment and opinions. Remember today is for… https://t.co/QA76gm3qgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 1 min left, I want to see  Nylander-Matthews-Marner Tavares-Rielly  Do it, cowards.  #LeafsForever… https://t.co/XwL5MB8c1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoisjourdan you are. and i’ve had to correct you countless times LMFAO wouldn’t trade it though boo 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why didn’t my mom do this when I called her blackout drunk asking how to make a lasagna ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BuffyD - Crawl back into bed, but don't even think about touching my blanket 🐾 :: swipe swipe::   #purrito… https://t.co/4N60oL1JQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics In a statement yesterday, he said he only made those remarks for his reelection in 2012. Why does that… https://t.co/d1wj6G4x5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great wk teaching PTAs about the future of our profession- never stop learning #Dramypt #FPTosteopractor… https://t.co/YZbdzhJTUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/YxlPdU3UEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of seeing the same tweet in a row💯😑 this is not Facebook stop stealing !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that you can so easily chronicle the lives of your children because of today’s technology make me insanely… https://t.co/07G5iRh4bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to a startup conference tonight and attended a Women in Startups panel. The moderator (white male) really did… https://t.co/Q9ZU2LBcgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guardian If it wants to be thought of more fondly, the Catholic church should behave better. Calling them out on p… https://t.co/uZ5MV1h5x1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking over-grown baby.  Trump threatens to block networks from hosting debates after Dems reject Fox  https://t.co/Gj27bKA0iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our job is to look where others don’t”  Alfonso Cuarón ❤️ We are so proud of you Paisano !!! Arriba Mexico 🎬🎥⭐️… https://t.co/awnv1UHhky]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a very expensive price tag to sit at the head table. Never get caught up in the hype of optics. People who… https://t.co/1LGChyZ0CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_eatz @Visit_PCB @Sostraveluk @RickGriffin @VISITFLORIDA @MattsRoadTrip @TravelAtWill @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/FruPL0SzKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jongarysteele @outlander @BarryWaldo You are sO amazing, creative, detail-oriented, and of course, adorable. I can… https://t.co/HiTTKiKrUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angiewill39 I promise you will love them. I seem to always get the banana pudding, I love bananas!!!🍌🍌🍌🍌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWPinPDX @SabineResists @ListenToEzra @B52Malmet @TheSWPrincess @ScarletAvengers @TrinityResists @DebbieDoesTwitt… https://t.co/1al1MVTRsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch for a crash on 95 SB at the beltway. Stop and go traffic reported.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom flew me home to work on the family genealogy and cleaning out my grandparents home, which I was doing happil… https://t.co/INFeHQifRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racist and by that smile she's proud of it glad she showed her true colors who Democrats are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby I think he got it backwards. I believe he meant Christians who support Trump are morons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteeleCorah @evanhayes_2 Quit using “google translator”!  ¡No es bueno! 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[just remembered how one of my friends told me "i unfollowed your finsta bc you have a boyfriend now so you won't be… https://t.co/mG1NSBuIBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to fuck with ya, just to make up with ya.. cuz the way you be screamin my name make me wanna make love to ya..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncontested...winner of the General George S. at Laurel Park 2-16-19 https://t.co/aZeGlrUFYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading time in #LusterELA! Students can pick if they read Tom Sawyer now or a personal boom of their choice! Alway… https://t.co/nF4pC8XxN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for #NYSSLS assessment examples? I could easily see using similar ones in my own classroom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[to all my lovely friends who wanna throw me a surprise birthday party it’s in a month 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantopping66 @UsaAnonomous @cali_curmudgeon @andrsngirls @jagrayak @JoeFDiaz1 @OLDFLACO @Suze2u1 @optionqueen… https://t.co/7Fmwv0PcLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drink Maurten in the shower 🛁  #recovery #longrun #40Kfortheday #NOTsponsored #buticouldbe @MaurtenOfficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cat will have more money than most Americans and that should make you feel sick. If he wanted to help animals,… https://t.co/DHmZt8zxb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amnotfunny @johnlewis And there should be a winner in Olney by now. The race on this side of the Pond is 3 hours away.....🤞🏻👏🏻😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesWStork His LOVE for US the AMERICAN PEOPLE n COUNTRY FIRST EVERY Day Shows how he is Caring about the Further… https://t.co/fIwU3Sr2BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DoorDash I am pretty sure the driver just stole my @tacobell lunch! Tracking the order on the app, they were a… https://t.co/SaffCKyKtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darling purple flower and rhinestone necklace and bracelet.  🌻 2 sets available $10 🌻  #karissparkleroom… https://t.co/nCDmfRHsa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists This is disastrous. Don’t our leaders care about ANYTHING??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelcomm @iansomerhalder @ninadobrev I would wake up in The Vampire Diaries. I was in New Orleans 6 years ago, on… https://t.co/p67xORdlQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot of nonsense that does not qualify as news trending on my Twitter feed right now. This, however, is a… https://t.co/gzEfevjtmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jana Dare (@janadaresyou) is now advertising in San Francisco! https://t.co/yKdX2v8TZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic with fire detailing for Betty M. . . . ✨ to BOOK your appointment, to check AVAILABILITY and PRICING click… https://t.co/i2IdmnTdBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow just woke up from an amazing dream.. had a dream I spent the entire day in Disney with @KylePallo 🥰 #pleasemakethisdreamcometrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always sort of sorry to the next person who opens the top freezer because I slam it shut just as the biggest he… https://t.co/WIlCFobDKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Isn’t it about time you walked 10 feet in a snow flurry for another cup of coffee?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss my Snapchat stories today! Two 3way in one day. 😈 https://t.co/hWETxH280R https://t.co/XpLOKtpKzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church Clarity continues to push back against harmful, misleading statements from churches who maintain harmfully v… https://t.co/DWWepj4PGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KammasKersch @tjvari @amandamatarese @DougTimm34 @love2runnteach @mrnultisanerd @rosy_burke @MrChanceysClass… https://t.co/8KvS1Gy7kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[ERA bill dies for good in GOP-controlled Virginia House of Delegates (I’m pictured upper right in blue w/glasses un… https://t.co/KTJVOCDFT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horseman_da @KyDeptofEd Especially by a FIRST YEAR TEACHER! Way to go, Ms. Austin! #kycteworks #kyNTIworks]]></document></documents></author>