<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jazzayers @AsiaAlexander I know if I have a financial bind I have 1. Savings 2. Multiple credit cards 3. Family. I… https://t.co/ih2XzrTHwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 14th- Cameron took these on the first night and I seriously love them https://t.co/srlnRhLtfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magagary687 @TrumpsDC @AOC AOC wants to choose the right job for everyone. And these high paying amazon jobs in NY… https://t.co/AYBl9na5NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposting bmorebeatclub:⠀ ...⠀ "This Friday look for the lights at bmorebeatclub #repost via @minacheon (BeatClub T… https://t.co/JUc233B1LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you 😍 all #love #loves #likeforlikes #behappy #like4like #l4l #silly #california #newportbeach #oc… https://t.co/SBbYjsrND3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s way too hard for me to study for my upcoming micro exam right now when I’ve got #TS7 theories fogging up my br… https://t.co/FhPPP0xmLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalRegine This is the cutest thing ever 🥺, a baby photo shoot then this ? Never]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBarzacchini @EsthersFollies @TheDickCavett @mrdavehill I'm old enough to remember watching The Dick Cavett sho… https://t.co/DxmBskj1mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad got his birth certificate when he was moving from Spain to the United States for college and when he got it… https://t.co/HCjAq5dXPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please wait 6 months to give them a fair start b4 the hunters start up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the Sunrise movement think Mitch McConnell is taking the GND to the floor of the Senate because he WANTS a Gre… https://t.co/8evqqbRRy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gains (@ Red Robin Gourmet Burgers and Brews - @redrobinburgers in Pleasanton, CA w/ @raider_dave) https://t.co/huOJU19gao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AOC is #OTT (over the top) I want candidate options but if the #dems continuing on supporting @AOC platform - I’m… https://t.co/k3tVjvUXHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@japanights Sooo you hate it but still get flowers and chocolates ugh your mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabb_mex @NicolasZuriel @lopezobrador_ A él no a ls encargados  que yo sepa el no os tenía pero puedo estar equivocada]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your mom has your location and texts u “girl...why u at the bar 🤷🏻‍♀️” when you told her u were sleeping 🤦🏻‍♀️… https://t.co/NQPk6sURst]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always game over when Chente starts playing... like where’s the tequila bottle]]></document><document><![CDATA[All good things must come to an end. And it hurts like a mother trucker! Goodbye Bomont! @ Collin Theatre Center https://t.co/sFQ4xnVtga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nessyness14 Man I was distracted backing up and I hit the whole car , god was on my side cause dude was like it’s… https://t.co/wwU2445vFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomOnWarpath @TheKatalyst_ @JonGordon11 You are right! Love it! Beautiful!🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont care what anyone says ... Yellow labs just do weird stuff compared to chocolate... https://t.co/BsUWOyP8Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Restored Relit and Ready to Rock  Las Vegas again! The story behind the rebirth of the @HardRock cafe #neon guitar… https://t.co/MOZN8CT1vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Mr Higgins u either did or didn’t believe Cohen. U say he’s looking for a break for lack of a better term. He’s… https://t.co/reVaEAuxXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY mouth fell open! How or why she went along with be humiliated like that boggles the mind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilson-Raybould says PMO restricting her ability to 'speak freely' at justice committee | CBC News https://t.co/OoxY6IGXFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the captain of your plane says “ the plane is broke,broke “ 😂💀 Bitch I’m DEAD . It’s time for us to go out,out… https://t.co/vw556BU6qy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a snippet of “4 Guys with Jobs” and their new lead singer, Stephanie Hug.  #CrazyLittleThingCalledLove https://t.co/5eA2p2P5Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generous in scale and color options, our Fugu Planters can bring a gentle and tasteful geometric rigor to a modern… https://t.co/CauZDewVGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paolucci40 @juditvalderrama Dios, no permitas que este medicucho pueda auscultar a ningún enfermo!!!🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when the Russians were given sensitive info in the WH and we all found out about it? Why would anyone thin… https://t.co/09PLulN0jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charles_worland @Corinne4Hillary @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton Yes so she can beat him again, but this time actually become POTUS😂😂👍😀‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl Ohhh... hahaha! 🤣😁😅 oh man, you're just such a misogynist! The proof is in your words. Stay right there,… https://t.co/qm5LlvyzRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY! We are here and We stay! NoChill @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to #WynonnaEarp P… https://t.co/HFNrvsqHQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia #SpreadPositivity always watch your specials when when I need a boost. You’re hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NicolleDWallace Watching you today. I’m starting my weekend with some #MommyWater 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavinTheBees "After the live shot, police say Delgado’s news crew followed the woman. Ninth District cops said the… https://t.co/1AozH9aSc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just look back and cringe at the amount of money you once spent on webkinz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson Such a great show - enjoyed meeting you too with Kathy F! Really impressed with all that's in your h… https://t.co/cNtEzWRsmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ84 @WrxChad @Susie_B_ @CLE_CLCFan (Also more sarcasm) https://t.co/rVm7ZusqVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceCordovano @NaveenBabyBob Thank you. Ohh he's getting up from his 30 minute evening nap 💗🤱🏼 #HTreads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch Been obvious he’s an alcoholic for long time... his skin shows all. :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunemmons @CurtisScoon Jessie thought he could get some of their chocolatey goodness and they fought him off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GllitterGoddess @essy_barrera @lilcheeesestick Size 10 if you can get me in on this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaymesMansfield  hi omg I tried the no mirror challenge KSKSKSKS it came out awful compared to my regular makeup S… https://t.co/mgN0oKSqQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t understand i basically went to highschool with half of them ppl at Albany .... why da hell would i wann… https://t.co/1uI3LcTu49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dakotaman98 @BaseballAmerica @ClemsonBaseball @_BryantBaseball @HailStateBB @GamecockBasebll It’s March 11. It’s okay. 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Valentines2019 today 😊 more &amp; express genuine gratitude ❤️ to those who inspire &amp; support you. Thank you… https://t.co/40i9zhVBTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi everyone! It's Wednesday, and we're half-way there to the weekend. We really are doing It.  Le Bateleur (The Mag… https://t.co/W1RBIgaOBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah these wisdoms gotta come out ASAP this pain is beyond anything I’ve ever felt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel fake posting that picture knowing the TRUTH. That was hours ago. That’s who I was. Things have changed. I’m… https://t.co/tUUFG6NPin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauren_hoggs Eric Garner, Michael brown, james too many to mention!  Join us!  https://t.co/vUtpzGrDOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how all relationships should be people! Buh byeeee toxic relationships, hellooo healthy relationships]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRaeSunny Thanks, fortunately I survived. My sons and my grand/great grandkids makes it all worthwhile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that @captainmarvel premieres on International Women’s Day. March 8th. This is totally awesome!… https://t.co/UtRsTapjAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come play Wordscapes! It moves fast and is challenging enough to be interesting. https://t.co/EtFPGOyryW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to work with these amazing women today! #internationalwomensday #EmpoweredWomenEmpowerWomen https://t.co/QJKmud47xy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t need to give him special treatment in sentencing due to his age and health issues. We have to crack down on w… https://t.co/EBk0jCmfVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mishkin thanks to @kerriebrynn &amp; @Mar_Horwitz for that. https://t.co/42Nk1dOxNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s late and I’ve had wine but am I the only one concerned that there may be subliminal messages planted in the Baby Shark song?? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night of information for our 8th gr parents! If you need any info or missed the meeting please contact… https://t.co/5mrCcCmsTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday the waiter at the Mexican restaurant asked me for my birthday, after I told him he said “oh sorry you jus… https://t.co/xkQivV1FjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@getSTUCKey If you’re thick like that I wanna be near that ass. https://t.co/8K1YcOZmsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo!  @realDonaldTrump  lacky.. yeah you. The little 🐝 O'tch that tweets for our illiterate dope n chief. Yeah. I kn… https://t.co/SOLGo0nVbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo This is how I've always felt &amp; always will!! 👿👿👿 https://t.co/7NRkAhVcIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doggie sweaters are pouring in for one severely emaciated dog named #Remington 🐕found abandoned in an orange grove… https://t.co/mkFl1EufYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my latest 5-star reviews for Finding Amor. These are ones I live for!!!! If you're looking for a copy of Fin… https://t.co/i44yB4gdG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntiesophsoph_ This shit gave me hella anxiety and my ocd would tell me to torch the place ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maricembra @BreakfastNews Yep and he could  thank his dope dealing doctors for supplying enough drugs that he  killed himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPierznik Anyways, enjoyed that. Have only met one other person who loved MJ as much as I did and he’s related to you. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obdulius @_michellegalvez No sé si estás tratando de ser chistoso o qué ondas pero qué idiota te viste. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If all the products from a Ninja Turtles commercial break got fucked up together. - Drinking a Cookie Kooks Garbage… https://t.co/RLzCeb3FCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@resist207 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Mueller just extended his investigation to September 2019. Maybe she's waiting until then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buchanan was at the forefront of nasty tricks, ugly rhetoric and vile political ideology. His RNC convention speech… https://t.co/7jK0l1qU2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #rooster #apron in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa https://t.co/EyaLAyhlGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocketWrestle @AthleticsRocket Congratulations Nicky! Gerke family is proud of you!🚀🚀🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg @captainmarvel is so 90s my heart can’t even take it 😊😊😊 and the SOUNDTRACK!!!! https://t.co/v1AG7dntnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aligatie I am trying to patiently wait for this to come out but I’m getting so antsy 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[See pic for dress up details! NOTE: Regular MP dress code enforced. #CHAMP https://t.co/736ZjpZefl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fresh Thyme Farmers Market- Waite Park, MN in Waite Park, MN https://t.co/80hhUvgsIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gav_butler “Junkie Parakeets”?? Srsly?I’d think language would matter to you. Using derogatory terms perpetuates stereotypes. #Lazy @VICE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @AOC I love “@AOC Representative Know-Nothing” 😂😂😂😂 #Perfect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayZ0verrat3d this is sad because she is very pretty &amp; doesn’t deserve to get fat shamed😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_hundred_Hyun I can't believe this is happening. Congrats, my boy. I love you so much 💗😭😭 #PriveAllianceinLA… https://t.co/tv9amCoxLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to LOVE this band, back in the 90s, however, now BILLY CORGAN had DECLARED HIMSELF A GOD. 👽 #FalseIdols… https://t.co/IhiyBjdJC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the best part of wedding planning and @C_Fitzgerald11 favorite dinner. 🍰🧁🍮🍩🍡😍 https://t.co/KR3GXuirHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This movie was so so incredibly good it made me cry, this scene alone like omg...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great time roxyfantasytour ! Awesome show! @ The Hudson Theatres https://t.co/rQ5XTBj8sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lovelearninginWB  with these @gretchkostars! #capturingkidshearts #gretchko2020 https://t.co/m6kAmiiX7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn the tea at the drive thur!! Lol #SmallTownProbs https://t.co/V58wnrmAUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[get you a man who does so much for you &amp; still asks if he can do more, literally blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ownsobriety I was told to never turn down a request to share your testimony at a meeting. I am not big on speaking… https://t.co/R4aDiNQYoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI I actually meant to use Mark and Jack for Tom and Daisy in that quote, since I try to poke at CEOs and founders… https://t.co/gRmhalfVzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evil in the name of God is the worse kind . The crooked cop, The pedophile Priest , crooked Politicians are  basica… https://t.co/lEiJCt8FAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of the amazing women... may we know them, may we love them, may we be them! ❤️👊🏼✨ #HappyWomensDay2019… https://t.co/wFZhbqlhTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Nissan is doing big business with a construction company bidding to build Trump’s wall. https://t.co/zr3rSnJA2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heids7673 @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump You win Twitter today! 😂💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what the over/under would be on @AOC references at @ScottWalker’s upcoming @CPAC speech]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I accept Cash or Credit Card with ID ” I’m available in Atlanta right now! https://t.co/yYb84NURY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to have another "Mary Katharine Ham" Sandwich so I can enjoy eating it!      --    Honey Ham! (with Natural J… https://t.co/zbKv3U1JTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie All the important issues not moving through Congress and McConnell  decides to vote on this right now? He's a joke.]]></document></documents></author>