<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@avswiftie @tarynlovestay @taylorswift13 Doesn’t look like her to me. This is from October 2017 btw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you looking for a Job? What you need to get started : - 18+ - Valid driver's license - A car, scooter, bike or… https://t.co/D0SMZF681E]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/9/2019 - 02:23 Temp: 49.6F   Hum:  91% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 29.804in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeWml7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • beck_masten_south How you feel after test driving the 2019 Sierra Denali... 🤣🙌 Test drive yours… https://t.co/mvwMQ1tt5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it. Aspen's Cassidy Jarrell snags final spot in Saturday's ski pipe finals at Calgary World Cup. Taking 10th… https://t.co/YkyC656fdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we all stop romanticizing @JoeFlacco and saying letting him go is such a huge mistake?  Great QB’s find a way t… https://t.co/GsHQXVAWM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complex - Drinking a Critical Hit by @oconnorbrewing @ Parfu's Place  — https://t.co/GjJ2uE9Gmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[At WordCamp Phoenix with some Frands. :-) #wcphx #wordcamp #wordpress @ Phoenix Convention Center https://t.co/d0270nqMtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome discussion today on our New Hope, New York budget tour. @ Binghamton, New York https://t.co/vko6M8Lnhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday February 25 - Daily Kos Morning Digest:    District attorney says 'prosecution should be anticipated' over N… https://t.co/5kDTcNaF7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anislandher Please keep us posted; thank you 🙏. Have to subscribe to #FijiTimes for updates. 💵💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislynnstreet Many have tried to make me laugh... many have failed. You sir, did not.   Honestly... thank you, lol! 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a fwb cuz its 3:02 and these hormones won't chill. I'm trynna go to sleep 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MUSIC #GOODMUSIC #SOUNDCLOUD #JUSTIINE #CANNABIS #MARIJUANA #LIT https://t.co/S0MkJcatwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyIrwinLA Why would being a great player 30 years ago automatically mean he’d be great at building a team today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenDawnFox29  GOOD MORNING First thing i see is that pretty smile.  Welcome back!!! Stay warm, ..im heading to the poconos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nasoni at 1 Million Cups Virginia Beach today.  Watch this company grow!! https://t.co/tjQ6p5VPjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep them in one brand for fucks sake!   #WWE #SDLive #GiveTheOtherWomenAChance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oerockets @markgregorich I’m not saying that he should have folded or called, but Def not worst fold ever. The kid can play]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve reached that part of adulthood where the most interesting segment of my weekend is a carwash. https://t.co/Sf8n0CazTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geofftock For real. Congrats friend. I’ll buy a section when it premieres here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant Williams is such a cry baby. He normally gets away with ramming into people but when the right call is made he cries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesthatCarlo so that everyone who gets help, has the best chance of succeeding and achieving the dignity of what's… https://t.co/rGDl3VGDNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. This investigation often takes months, typically. You are often not notified when it’s occurring or has complete… https://t.co/J67ugyk8Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[ice water slaps differently when u wake up dehydrated &amp; still drunk as shit at 4am]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Battle, Dolezaj and Boeehim out there, #Syracuse has several guys manning the ball at the top of the offense.… https://t.co/HU7MKJFQtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty amazing to me how many people consider this “disrespecting the game” when the same people are now saying it’… https://t.co/kkv3Ae08UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for the praise I may receive at @gmillener wedding for my claim of introducing the couple, which may be aki… https://t.co/vnqm8SYL0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANKS TO ALL THAT WATCHED THIS TRAILER THEN PATRON MY SITE.   EXCLUSIVELY VIEWABLE https://t.co/D1JYqb8zAr… https://t.co/ZNaKGcpeAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50Charlie53 @AJ____Leo @cjkl711 @KPCharlie This might be all we really need ..a lot can be done with 20 min of high gear!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesInSF @BASportsGuy @LOLKNBR I’m setting a damn reminder on my phone right now to never respond or tweet when drunk again 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberatingNarrs Many of my students exaggerate Japan's isolation in the Tokugawa period. This image challenges that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wholly on board with that fear and courage part.  Even those who kind of speak up soon get back in line and vote wi… https://t.co/9Dg76tXkhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[| snow day | ❄️☕️☃️🏂⛷🤩  #inbend #getoutside #snowday #pnw #localbusiness #realestate https://t.co/bsku3vGZhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golly Coach @Jim_Jordan now I see how you failed your students. You’re more worried about protecting perps than abo… https://t.co/yJHs3nDdwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Even is leavin’” was the mnemonic that any train traveling away from San Francisco on the Southern Pacific had an… https://t.co/v15C8qpZyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xandertheblue Is this the next Presidential candidate fighting for Trump's base?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @OSHS_Wrestling today in day 2 of regionals. Southside Empire brought 13 men to the mats yesterday and al… https://t.co/61frZyCZTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoobNBCS I wonder how many times you'll have to explain the theme of your list?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_Purchase dear nice to know you ,if you mind telling me that are you in charge of led products purchasement ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwhite3175 @OmarKelly Last 20 years, 36 QBs taken in first round. Only 4 won SB. The draft is a CHANCE, not a GUARANTEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adiós Monterrey, luego vengo con más calmita. en Aeropuerto Internacional De Monterrey https://t.co/Yw9ij8f6uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) Again and again, unusual secrecy protects Epstein and his jet-setting circle. His victims, meanwhile, have been… https://t.co/CvuW7y8pA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines to my loves..... @ Fairhope, Alabama https://t.co/6d1Ae61dHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Executive reappropriation of funds is unconstitutional.  (*click*)]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #internationalwomensday and a song started coming together. Dedicated first and foremost to Pat Bartavian the… https://t.co/gpzSo3jf8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Score: Harris County’s season comes to an end as they fall to Wayne County 46-42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dhild11 Yeah. I can’t buy a jersey knowing our GM is gonna let every single asset on our team go. Biggest free age… https://t.co/b2PZ8lsclY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mblucas77 @thehill Obama’s mom was born in Kansas. Why didn’t he say go back to Kansas? Obama himself was burn in… https://t.co/f5sqzgvM42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleD35 It's not hard to paint Trump as racist.  But this is juicy as hell, so I bet it gets reported.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace O’Neill said, “It was a total team effort.” She, along with Erin Sweeney and Harlem Jennings, scored in doubl… https://t.co/Cyh8kYNoJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sicat222 @Turki_AlOwerde @Herald_Reports The best way is what Turki just did. https://t.co/uDxaqXa9RS He laid out… https://t.co/3fizHhPX7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[A decade ago, I took a lousy digital recorder to #Braves spring training, pretended I had any clue what I was doing… https://t.co/RSCx5aH1Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Hey Mitch - you are so far up Trumps as all we see is a big toe wiggling. Majority leader? Nope - asshole lover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here wondering if there is any chance Harper might sign a one or two year deal, with hope that the market i… https://t.co/VLuiTv5KK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sad reality of Europe today. A rather high percentage of people polled there are unaware of the Holocaust.]]></document><document><![CDATA[te conozco tanto que si un día se te olvida quien eres, yo te lo puedo recordar😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtp15218 @VincentMTiberi @eric_gaydos @JasonJackMiller @TeddyMuzika @The_Steel_Trap @jrtiberi @redroz0595… https://t.co/NmIx4WW72D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again for the amazing dinner @ellaellichicago last night. Can’t wait to see you again. #Joined4StarRewards]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Morning! I’m flipping through my #BigGive2019 presentation and getting ready to head over to The Whitley Theologic… https://t.co/maiw6yGC7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free tickets to the 4pm #honkytonkexpress tomorrow in #Nashville for bachelorettes and their single lady friends!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeBleedBlueNYC can we get “sick individual” on the next Vesey shirt? Credit @TonyDee07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGitto You’re the hero Philly deserves, and the one it needs right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceMcMahon You’re upset and disappointed that your ratings are down?! Seriously? Your championship belt is NEVER… https://t.co/vbV4mmwRfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever get drunk and just retweet random shit on to your time line ? Cause is just did]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listed | 1208 E Leigh Ct, Long Beach CA | LIVE Auction | Live bidding from $280,000 Open house Saturdays 11-12… https://t.co/VMTj1Ww2i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbackourtax @LSTII1 @jxf74 @martine_piers @LZ181818 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump I didn’t lose my job.  It re… https://t.co/JEtVzQ4AKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrWhom42 i’ll concede that ledger is ass and i KNOW i will enjoy birds of prey more than suicide squad because har… https://t.co/VNaWt02o4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I start to even slightly believe that love is real I remember that Anakin choked the shit out of Padmé f… https://t.co/wWEAiAqlSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffLCarr @GKallet24 @Super70sSports Nah. That was the fat shot of heroin he did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I voted for you in the Democratic Primary but you lost me when you decided to back Hillary. #Bernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Silvermine River near us.  There never was silver or a mine.  #snow #norwalkct… https://t.co/AiQ8dpTYH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheistRepublic My landscaping guy .... #immigrantsWorkhard #fakeMessiah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoosierHystrcs Groundhog Day is one of my all time favs!  Not letting this team ruin something else for me 😀😀!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamGreenway @SWBTS @nrhbc @CrossChurchDFW @scottmaze @DannyPRoberts Preach the Word!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christiana1987 @roywoodjr @TheDailyShow Remember make fun of middle aged white guys and you will do great. Congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVanValkenburg @edgraney From now on, when it’s the weekend and a little trouble is in store, I’m just gonna tell… https://t.co/zSEojcNgHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtaby Support system ends up becoming the make or break in almost all situations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taxastweets @CWilliamson44 printing this tweet out, framing it, and sending it to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/fNMXMYNCIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewWolsky @Wadeyy19 Haha I’m just messing with you yeah he ain’t worth 84 mill but Redskins front office is brain dead so who’s surprised]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first episode of PEN15 has an insane number of laughs and cringes packed into 30 minutes. It's almost painful t… https://t.co/pb5ORt2ufg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddParvin @davidsirota @MmmBob Not sure why anyone who genuinely cares about the cost of drugs would support Trum… https://t.co/BK4zyitIOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ctfu like it really be all fun &amp; games until your girl abt 2 leave you😭now you sick n in ur feelings lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bungie They just dropped a huge bomb, now we know who the Drifter really is😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you jamie_auld for indulging us and posing for this picture! ❤️ If you haven’t heard, we’ve got a book out th… https://t.co/BXbbku1jo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having an amazing Crown Royal whiskey ginger right now. #diageorep #crownroyal #whiskyginger #whiskey #whisky @ Luc… https://t.co/G3i5dNrn9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this video to see the awesome event my team threw with @LiamPayne for #CheggMusic101! You might even see… https://t.co/NNHnjkLMub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you...  @RepKirkpatrick @gregstantonaz @RepJoshHarder @TJCoxCongress @RepKatieHill @GilCisnerosCA… https://t.co/GiY9Pxgl36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSBoston @WX1BOX back to all snow now in north Lakeville as of 525 am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher Donny is the last claw to hold to power for old, white, racist Amerikka. Ripoffblican Congress will aban… https://t.co/EPVN82sSzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweet below a bit misleading.    Biden got applause.   Pence didn’t.  Why is Trump not there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southcarolinafb RPI was 70.  That's not getting ya in.  SOS was in 250s IIRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's crazy how many people are considered 'famous' soley because social media exists. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[mais um concluído ✅ tmj feras #semrushar em Rush On Game https://t.co/cEpKvGifrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherw25 Lots of princess race weekend pins on ebay. Including the AP one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funeralfemme Its really awesome! Isn't the Canadian model aligned with law enforcement? I know Amsterdam isn't. I'd love to run an SIS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cicero Chick-fil-A officially opened 1 year ago today. What a glorious year it has been 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Her tweet got soooooooo many more likes than yours. Just sayin. #Numbers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making a connection at #Charlotte airport on #NBAAllStarWeekend.  Hoping to see some players but I suspect I am too early]]></document></documents></author>