<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@QueenBbecT @IntlWD @Moon_River05 @RattleDemBonez @jcorbin63 @hisdirtysweetie @mariaemma16 @fuckedchic @Wendywoo_g… https://t.co/0hgDG1fTKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you leave what you hope will be the final draft of your next book alone on your desk. Hor… https://t.co/lih1b6sNpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got up 2 hours early to find a church in this town, found like 3 and every one was closed! If this Louisiana boy ca… https://t.co/c64tZ5pxje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAU_Owls_Nest @KLV1063 @JackWhidden3 @FAU_Baseball No runs on one hit no errors and two left on. We go to the top… https://t.co/ZJdPbcE6Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoldenmuzzy I get the Ducks get a first rounder but why deal him in the first place yound dman and they arent loaded on defense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinDoory Nice.  Well balanced - I have an amd build from a bit ago, and really liked it. Current box is Nvidia 1… https://t.co/OnyUyZm98q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting my Saturday off right with @NoRulesPodcast of course. https://t.co/KpkDpCB2II]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MALAFUNKSHUN The “related video” suggestion underneath is golden 🤣 https://t.co/r5fvuz3LGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProConverters Almost makes you think there’s a jet engine in the back!👌🏻💪🏻💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta lose 1-2 more pounds before @AlphaMuOmegaAKA Founders Day! #cardio #abs https://t.co/BVNrvx6fL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DunningJon32 @netflix @rex_rexchapman Ha. No. I’m oddly intrigued by it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Browsing stats this morning...some interesting ones - Pablo / Roofe assist is 3rd (4) in the league (jutkiewcz / Ad… https://t.co/q1DFSEde82]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/lqw0yCpyw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiscoSports4 Nice work tonight. I look forward to crushing Vikings fans with you come preseason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the little bro for tagging along with me on a casual drive through the #ortegahighway74 #broski… https://t.co/8gOXaNGUy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymeadus @Airbornex82nd @POTUS Read an article about Sweden where Somalis fight the Nigerians and the Syrians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivicParent Don't disagree, but accountability is a big part of leadership, and as we have seen, leadership is wholly lacking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing about morning travel? Biscuits and gravy in the #deltaskyclub . https://t.co/0ZYgBn1HFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronNagler Brown is better then Beckham and we couldn't give a 3 and a 5 for him but people think we will give a… https://t.co/Kuwi8yWq3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex1bryant @TroyRobinson7 Fueling gaming sessions / last minute beer runs since I can remember]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanieBuss all the evidence you need  Please fire Rob and get a respectable exit strategy for Magic  Bless 🙏🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look the face of @WWE_MandyRose  She is so cute 😍😍😍😍😍  I hope you win this Championship you deserve 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kboldens Unusual.  I assume by these pics you’ve started your next chapter and I didn’t make your cut for the goin… https://t.co/7i8H43Iukg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoRavell Cállate desgraciado! Con qué moral se atreve este individuo a denunciar la criminalidad de otro deli… https://t.co/bIGnZvZwKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attended the #Cannabis #Wedding #Expo in SF For #MGmagazine. More images soon. https://t.co/eta9ffZIFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI, Science Salon #56 Dr. Tyler Cowen—How an Economist Views the World is up: https://t.co/8Khyesf5V1 My podcast… https://t.co/6HxtNmUq2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sutherland &amp; Kent both spoke to the relationship that they have built while working together as Wildcats. #BDJ3644]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erininnashville Totally understand. Thankfully my house was built with an outlet just in case. But there still nee… https://t.co/390rjpggfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agradezco la invitación que me hace @EnergiaTam del @gobtam para participar en el Foro Estatal Nueva Política Energ… https://t.co/bB2G4JW3Uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios @benshapiro Join up with the Socialists. You have so much in common. Fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bo-  what has come over you? C- my brain is working better than it ever has and fungus seem to never endingly swarm… https://t.co/fUi2ak70P9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pera_richard @Last2ndFleetCMC I seriously am not tracking here. You started this thread with something about Trump… https://t.co/A4gXjNH4Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryGiggles05 @IAmSueSue2 You literally just brought up the past with the Rockies game. 😂😂😂  Why are you like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillieStarkz Theres only one word can describe you and thats STAR, because thats what you are. Your connection wit… https://t.co/1SNabPe8uD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson @QTAnon1 DUI, DWI, is a criminal act. When you get arrested the police process you.When you sober u… https://t.co/iM0lwwiqEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Where the HELL is Congress? Digital Book Burning Must Stop! (GOOGLE, FACEBOOK, TWITTER. YOUTUBE CEN… https://t.co/3N6SlswxIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonaLisa0113h @donnambarkertn @MrsCamtini @romansebastian @lbarronlopez @TomSteyer @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Imp… https://t.co/mA6mkVXNYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes let's trade the guy who's second on the Wings in points for two picks th as t hea going to screw up anyways. Yo… https://t.co/p8GqfRVx5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only did the 7 to 11 crew do an amazing job, the 9 to 6 got the whole truck out tonight. Couldn't ask for a bet… https://t.co/a1MbhpnO2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[solid plug for @HoodooBrownBBQ on @BarstoolBrkfast this AM trying to plan @FrancisCEllis Bday...make that happen @CMSexton @willcolon66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting real with Dianna, KW legend and leader of MAPS coaching.  #kw #maps #coaching #roundup @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/Lk4GSaQmlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always considered being a poet one of my “impossible dreams” .... look at me now, honey 😌👸🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling for work and pleasure I get to see a wide variety of people sometimes at their worst and best. Families w… https://t.co/JCOjSh6pCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyRFan48 @jeff_gluck You enjoyed a single file parade around the top? Ok then lol @ABednarz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cowboyz_1993 @SportsCenter That’s or the xfl and AAF will merge at some point in the next couple years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoveTheSticks @rex_rexchapman A nice mention of your name, https://t.co/6wxpAzh6FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like Trump’s comments about the press this is designed to incite murder. Fuck the NRA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live in a world with lots of “functional alcoholics”.   They don’t start out that way, they just evolve over time… https://t.co/XBMUFNQZp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a small, easy thing to say government redistribution should generate #1099-GOV just like LABOR generates W2/10… https://t.co/cluSk27QEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephanienoel41 It's crazy how good that is. Actually it isn't crazy because Freddie could sing better than most people ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday morning with Little Billy and Caroline. #GoodDay @ The Mynatt Abode Kitchen https://t.co/shHZx9U4fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/4AP38XBfVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: #TheShield makes their #FarewellAddress as they prepare to go their separate ways ahead of #WrestleMania.… https://t.co/ouluYKl4Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway where the fuck is the Manhattan bound E train? Packed platform at Jackson Heights, no notice of delays.… https://t.co/Vq13XPA7Ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[7901-7905 Beverly Blvd 7901-7905 Beverly Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90048 https://t.co/yeqDCqh8MU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last show/concert vlog I did was seeing @PKEWX3 on election night and I realized that my videos just end there… https://t.co/A5wf7csZMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weight loss tip number #134 if you purchase donuts from @dunkindonuts and still want to lose weight hide them in yo… https://t.co/PXTk9WwhRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uraveragejo100 I’m gonna be trashed. It’s my birthday but I’m still gonna watch it lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo She’s perfect to represent the Idiocracy district. She’s really Occasional-Cortex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonLaCanfora AB hates losing. He ain't gonna be happy in the Brown eye (black hole)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derrick Rose says he would like to play tomorrow but has no idea how his body will feel in as soon as a game ends —… https://t.co/oEqQUd3PUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have you on the list Mike. Once we get to 24 people we will send out proposed dates and an agenda. I need that n… https://t.co/PTmLpatxFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nationalist_KAG @skb_sara Ignore, GOP will rise in 2020 like never before. All the socialists will go down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaHuseman Don't like thin mints but mint chocolate chip ice cream is great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fymjrh @JeremySanders28 @RealCJ10 @tammigaw @xLeeshaSx I think that could get around the having to pay everyone is… https://t.co/pdOq4O93g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpikeEskin Good evening . Will 94 WIP carry live from start to finish, the press conference of Phillies player Bry… https://t.co/wp3GUafDfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojoh888 @jsav2020KAG Sue the f****** school this is what we have to do Sue them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Vick worked with Pat Mahomes as a rookie, said, &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ve never seen that&amp;#8221; https://t.co/AI4ItQ2osk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_amandakillian After the pulse shootings in Orlando, the London mayor was critical of the Orlando racism.  The les… https://t.co/5GTJYR7GvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cshank622 @KyGuy01 He’s from upstate ny I don’t get why this is an issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a former smoker I am not only disgusted by this armed robbery but also that they were taking the cheap nasty cig… https://t.co/XcgZEWfE3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trudeau and his puppet masters are being paid millions to bring in more Islamics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT #1 De Mi Bella Ídola @anettemicheltv Como "Estrella @cklassoficial" Entre 2004 Y 2006 @AnetteMFans https://t.co/23BSWjEkzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are those that love this Constitutional Republic by Rule of law and right of all to chose their own destiny a… https://t.co/tsJIWf2GTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alainac425 You probably look fantastic. If a man can’t accept you when your at your lowest; he doesn’t deserve you at your finest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EZ_moneys @MattMcDonald567 Here's what I propose.  Pay student athletes. Pay them monthly. Give them a check that… https://t.co/f0lFY5cdEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journalists place themselves into dangerous and risky situations every day. For women in the field, the risk can be… https://t.co/BcJgMEZC2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeGameDay Jack White found a unicorn. I mean... he found a 3pt bucket... @timpreusser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC The cost is new construction has risen so much , it is putting affordable housing out of reach for most, even… https://t.co/lCH0VLaxJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerwaters En perfecto Español Venezolano: @rogerwaters anda a Mamarte un Guevo! In English: Go to suck a Big Cock! Arrastrao Palangrista!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One second is perfect and the next you are terrible. Welcome to life. Been question e why for too long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsKellyHHS @JohnMercure @wexgkb @620wtmj @MelissaBarclay2 @gmatzek @D_La https://t.co/leXjSR6cBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gte But really the issue is that an industry awards show pits films against each other. Very, very good films. Onl… https://t.co/IgvcpYFz8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Police officer apologizing for pulling me over when I was driving over the speed limit. No ticket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newolder @IBJIYONGI The model takes the observed galactic  rotation curves and assumes  that at a particular value… https://t.co/DDLizqmfc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gagansikand @OmarAlghabra @cathmckenna @SoniaLiberal @iamIqraKhalid @NavdeepSBains @PeterFonsecaMP @BardishKW… https://t.co/tprpfGKoEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spotted this world axe throwing league on ESPN and the dudes went into like 15 overtimes and didn't miss onc… https://t.co/K86rs7HsTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamBase @JohnPrineMusic @JasonIsbell @MissMargoPrice This movie has to be awesome! 4 of the greatest artists going… https://t.co/DJYZbYuiz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racheltaylorslc Flower list is tracked using @plantsmap See the flower bed plants at this link https://t.co/y4XlvKKUfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoozyBadger Someone seems to have torn his head off in the photo at some point...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_gonda21 The kids a fantastic passer, comparing him to Magic or Kidd after  60 games is stupid and irresponsible. Try again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenWalke looking forward to some  more Galactic Assault Maps in the future, anything on the horizon? https://t.co/0JPEUHxfH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ @TuckerCarlson Piece of shit. I’d love for your daughters to hear their father speaking like this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last appt for the day! (@ St Joseph's Hospital Medical Office Centre and Parking Garage in Syracuse, NY) https://t.co/NddzLJ44z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Falco. Turnt since 2010. . . . . #mrdopeandthebricks #mrdope #dope #throwbackfriday #Throwback #tbt #classic… https://t.co/b76J2Cd2Wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcleansoccer U13 boys green going up 2-0 on this corner kick goal. Great header!! https://t.co/1aBwEabJ8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @AOC Sir this shows what kind of trash you really are. Keep it going AOC. You have the Republicans scared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the Latin flavor of @karengalera_ magical voice ... Mi corazoncito indeed! #VoicePremiere @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Republicans dont offer enough "free" stuff. Easy to buy votes when a majority expects payback, in some regard,… https://t.co/Q1gCWjG5kY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rissa_leanne @caitynicmccrary @2chainz @jonasbrothers I didn’t stay up for them... I will listen to them later]]></document></documents></author>