<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Mathias1105 @ANDREW1ALBERTT Sorry that’s no reason to feed it things like that. He meant well I know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@William42870346 LOL no I had a wonderful time with my Granddaughter and daughter and son in law we went to the Aqu… https://t.co/0zwL2IasZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be completely honest, i wouldn’t mind if. @KaitMarieox’s gun went off in her face. What a waste of breath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MrsNellyMES to post covers of seven books I love- no reviews, no explanations- just… https://t.co/9mRNDBj4Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BARBIETlNGZ The only tweet I’ll acknowledge since it’s not comparing her to Nicki 🙄 y’all so annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARunner200 @Sxylilminx2 @SantaRosaPolice Nobody came after you. You made a negative comment and she asked why. https://t.co/Mekdt3z7A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColusaBrown @CapitolAlert Dude, you were in town?? https://t.co/z9iNG4taow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YLongval I don’t think your coach would be happy if you sat on them...lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found this in my saved videos. I miss this spunky old man every day. Theoretically, still holding your hand, M… https://t.co/09xSMmdrwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think I'm not your 'baby Mama'#ButIWontBeIgnored https://t.co/zHNK79Vw0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femtoduino @glowascii It's trypophobia, dude. tryptophobia is possibly caused by the human brain registering holes as a sign of disease]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankCh66294129 @Bobsoftheworld @fat__tire @ifindkarma @nowthisnews @MollyJongFast Troll]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this moment I have on leggings, tanktop(no bra), fluffy long sweater and Christmas socks. I have a closet of the… https://t.co/5AdBonnzd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing on sad news, yet with gratefulness for all she contributed to our profession. @allencognitive @AOTAIncPR… https://t.co/GKn1IYVBrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people tell me I look a lot like someone they know and im starting to think I’ve been cloned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantasia isn’t doing a solo?????? Now why they got her paired up when she could be doing all these songs by her dam… https://t.co/rjWRO92vKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyhunter44  so amazing to watch you play for #USA #usdwnt. The youth training camp was inspiring.… https://t.co/5iLEVZFzhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMITHAAAAAA lol I like it 😂 that is super small though.. I was debating if I wanted Tim Duncan or KD in my lineup.… https://t.co/7eVxDwb4MS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell It's all,in your imagination, sir. https://t.co/BKeCGOwRKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manny Machado will be a Padre.  Bernie Sanders still has no concept of reality.  Trevor Bauer confirms he must inde… https://t.co/iE2AYqqeRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portsmouth police are searching for a man accused of theft and fraudulent use of a credit card.  @WGME   https://t.co/dj7tTha9UY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I give Sam props for never giving up on their endeavors and dreams.  What ever it takes man. 👏🏼❤ . . . #Cars… https://t.co/H29G3vqeyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you never did this with your bff in the back of your dads truck... I feel bad for ya 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for all the birthday wishes y’all 🥳♥️ i love and appreciate every single one of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmaBona @JussieSmollett Come now! This isn't a play to divert attention from children crying for their parents on… https://t.co/NP3fZLtvsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an example of LAND USE, because in order for us to have produce like this, land must be cleared and plowed… https://t.co/yre3zV1lW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just watched A Star is Born &amp; i’ve never cried so much by the end of the movie 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a job so I wouldn’t have to spend my parents money and now I’m not even allowed to spend MY OWN MONEY freakin… https://t.co/rZcTa16G44]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Atomic Clock Company* “We’re not getting any feedback on the new clock from Quality Control.”… https://t.co/ARcMf1PVEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila We ❤❤❤❤you Rick. You are valued. And you are loved too! Don't you ever forget it either!!!!😁☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ This is horrific, as a parent of a non verbal child with special needs it was too much for me to finish… https://t.co/yVzkS3gIzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish some of these suck up bitches would post how clean their bathrooms or place is instead of busting out random… https://t.co/9GkhFzd8NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LewisUnderscore @GOP @realDonaldTrump You cant throw dinamite in the water and see what floats to the top thats a… https://t.co/uvN2gjP2A0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pluckyloser @pandsreid well that's too personal- he stopped sharing there 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tweeted about the lottery and, to be expected, here is my lottery ad.  #targeted #advertising #imnotalone  This a… https://t.co/bAvx7nYrom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awyliu @GMichaelNews @ChristiesInc Andrea glad you got to attend 😊🙋‍♀️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hillary Clint the only crisis in America is whenever somebody sees you on any nude show spilling your rhetoric]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS  check out West Virginia Islamic neighborhoods. Throwing Americans out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MillieBonham What a shame. So far the only people that have been violent towards others is the Dem… https://t.co/AfK302Le2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre game grub. (@ The Original Pantry - @thepantrycafe in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/N1BxoLEaHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDaMedusa @lynmac4 @RomeshRanga @guardianweekend Look The Beatles come from Liverpool. No one is calling Paul McC… https://t.co/diN2bPK3pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is she so cute?? This outfit is intentionally supposed to be not cute and somehow, still extremely cute!! It de… https://t.co/6o2yKVxhjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopJeepers @AddisSaltyDog @SouthernGirl281 @nsnelson1020 @_Truck_Norris_ @rpx53 @rhidog95 @29kyle29 @Legendary1941… https://t.co/fgTPah4XPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little art to brighten this rainy day. Ss using shading techniques to create optical illusions in Intro to Visual… https://t.co/SffHVyW9uC]]></document><document><![CDATA[us: where’s the cover @bradytutton and @sjrcalderon : https://t.co/ln5aI56X97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arthur saw the pie J picked up at the store and shiite, “PIE!!!!” and started jumping up and down. Now he is reject… https://t.co/isWUTf7fVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We support @RoyJonesJrFA       @Rayximenez tune in tonight @UFCFightPass .#texas #bringbelthome #inGodwetrust… https://t.co/PScj6aZAY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not much time left to get in on this - Check out FILMOCRACY - Movie Streaming with Gamified Rewards by Paul Jun on… https://t.co/lm3VZwAFOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookNookNuts @AuthorJSScott @IARTG @freeboostpromo @AmazonPub 💛💛💛 Sooo good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WENDYMAJESTIC12 We must stand united to vote the asshat out of office. #VoteBlue2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so proud of these @CPHSfalcons students. Thanks to @MrBlandCPHS and Dr. Tibbot for many hours of supervision,… https://t.co/6lwC7u9laR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotions by Chris Brown really puts me in my feels but i cant stop listening to it🙃🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amie_elna @blastfam I have seriously found some of my best teacher tools from Twitter! People I work with must hat… https://t.co/lNKpK0yFAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a stranger holds their phone to take a selfie, but you don’t know if they actually are photographing you inste… https://t.co/TDYOCD30pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally time!!!   SO excited for @captainmarvel with @DTCMolloy &amp; @grizjen .  Perfect way to celebrate… https://t.co/MWr4BREeCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends: Chandler Can’t Cry ***Joey, phoebe, Monica, chandler watching a sad movie*** Joey: chandler you didn’t cry… https://t.co/9Ywf0zsLaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexBetsy @MrDane1982 Born on Monday the 13th! Which I figured out way early in life 'cause I was TIRED of being asked 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnownGoodGeek Like I remember people not liking the Zeta Project, but I was pretty new to the internet then, so I… https://t.co/KJdEUQfDKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Flying East”  #pentax @PENTAXIAN #pnw #sunrise #kirkland @kirklandgov #SoNorthwest #cascades https://t.co/syFsCi9jIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaden Smith Is Making It Easier for Flint Residents to Access Clean Water https://t.co/hF43yl72s3 #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Socialmedia has become a necessity for many small businesses. Do you understand it's ability to positively contrib… https://t.co/9QdYcop4rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check them out! nailed_it_spa_ct   They are also in need of a Hair Dresser.... Message, Call or Swing By today!!! @… https://t.co/VGBLASaxwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to accentuate the bags under my eyes so my bosses feel bad for making me work during the work week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hey_peg @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump President has demonstrated a deep love for our country, and for ALL its peop… https://t.co/Z6J37U0Vhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiykeeHeaton Can u just send me a video of u just singing instead? I miss your lullaby’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet. I’m landing at 2am.  This is why. This is also bananas. https://t.co/v7TwjzhIOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivyjofreeman @doctoralexa @ElleWibble @FredMertzReal @JuliaKozuschnik @Grabsback2 @rdnk_grl @efocuss… https://t.co/mp0gPF2JoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonhennings @TedFlintKansas Double standards suck. I work in a male dominated field and I’m expected to be: 1. A f… https://t.co/VU1NMQ03zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive I agree with Dana...make your bed it makes your day start out with a good rhythm!  At least it makes me feel good! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all. We just landed in Atlanta for the weekend and I miss this city so much! #AllTheFeels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never above you. Never below you. Always beside you. ~Walter Winchell  Happy Valentine's Day! ♥️ @BoyGeorge and all… https://t.co/ECKYz0U4ER]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is exhausting, and makes me sad, hurt, and SO TIRED. Whenever I engage, I feel sucked dry. When I disengage, the… https://t.co/PNFdlFVKN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh!  Isn’t it just about time?   Expect Twitter to impede the truth.  Just waiting a or a group of Conservative m… https://t.co/GGu62J8fJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[hahaha I hope all of u who are so upset that specific candidate(s) are running for president will actually go out a… https://t.co/1iEolmmHBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Radiology Research Trainee Award winners!       👏👏👏@MontefioreRAD @EinsteinMed… https://t.co/wUI6G7Vypc]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t sleep &amp; i just ordered a whole organic cleaning kit &amp; i’m so mf excited lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @Ed08792346 @SpeakerPelosi Pelosi is worried about losing the Speaker position.  The left is so radica… https://t.co/cRbLXrt8wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost hope in everything, need something to come along and change my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is a bollard fence that is REPLACING existing fence. Jeez I can’t believe you can lie like th… https://t.co/bOES2RsDs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you used to talk to shiydaro don’t fix yo mouth to speak to me simple 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRapaport @FINALLEVEL Some of the stuff is gross and I turn away. Amazing how it’s like a train wreck, you j… https://t.co/G1q7oKkumc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennethBaer @jmartNYT That seems like a progressive value not conservative. Conservatives promotes bad frat boy Ka… https://t.co/MVt15C5GBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueinRockville @feelsyoung @Jim_Jordan @OversightDems Why isn’t he?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kayleeya1 got me HOOKED (pun intended) on @whydontwemusic and now I’m obsessed with them and #ColdinLA is so good kids! Go listen to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to all birthdays being celebrated with this kinda smile!!...2 or 50-something-ish!!! 🎂 https://t.co/PtC44PJet8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielmack @schindera @DoroBaer @mmeckel @leasteinacker aaaaaw! Dankeschön!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog has been shivering none stop today because of this damn thunderstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @senatemajldr What’s going on with Justice Ginsburg?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah true... even when both of ya’ll know they getting back together next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daily_Star @ladscomeback @piersmorgan @LiamPayne "Sorry Can You Say It Louder From The Back Of The Line Of Irrelev… https://t.co/Y3oObuLmGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[USAW Official: okay you can get on the scale but just try to stand as still as possible  Me: **tries really hard no… https://t.co/vrKOgHPMh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS @BBheathertom @don_diamont If you get them back together just for him and Brooke to start mooning over e… https://t.co/cgHuILCmKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@otownofficial 2019 Tour Dates  Tickets / VIPs are available on their website at  https://t.co/acGsgCEyCy… https://t.co/UkkX67roxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsMACH It should be made public, we don't want false history spread to the moon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop making promises you can’t keep bc the word promise is starting to lose it’s meaning...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know that it was not with perishable things such as silver or gold that you were redeemed. . . but with the pre… https://t.co/9MEFIl2tqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days I need to break out a tally counter to see how many times they say “questioning” on The Bachelor.… https://t.co/ZC0f8OQ4km]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, it's me -- but not the coffee. #FunnyKinda #HelpLord https://t.co/hvdaaAR9Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceForceSSG @AnnCoulter I did try to tell her she would never replace trump’s real  girl crush Hillary He even u… https://t.co/6ObiWr3vMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rested with baby girl #momstuff #newborn #fitmom #loveandhappiness #stlmo #cuddles @ Florissant, Missouri https://t.co/tRRHzuWREo]]></document></documents></author>