<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FoxwoodsCT @foxwoods @joanjett @ImEddieMoney Soon as I get free tix for this great show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jblazek02 @bstare_5 @NVHS_Football @UWP_Football @lemminginsider CONGRATS BEAST❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone but everyone should read this.  It’s all very well to say “Date code your beer” but in doing so you’re set… https://t.co/faHd6aVXuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowkey I feel it’s just cause it was NC if it were anywhere else he wouldn’t have been this active]]></document><document><![CDATA[RECAP: Yeah so we made this movie about catching ghosts with electricity, yeah yeah its based out of New York City...  #TURNTHEANIMAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megalodon lives in the Mariana Trench with Kaiju from another dimension and James Cameron's undersea lair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROIChristie @Lexus @SewellCompanies @DriveSewell It's criminal on their part Christie, and really, really bad business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly believe that everything happens for a reason and whatever is meant to be will be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slickness   #pfw #fashionnova #fashionfuckery #snoblife #snobshots #vlone #lv #canadagoose #yeezy #basicwhitegirl… https://t.co/zSCVgGgxqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cut that short, what other areas of your life will you cut short?  #integrity #mentoring #publicspeaking… https://t.co/OUk3cajGTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejeffcrow Well I’m watching #WonderWoman tonight and #CaptainMarvel tomorrow so they all can suck it. https://t.co/3M2ClLgySQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna sound overly confident but you can bet your house that Syracuse is beating UNC tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanEdgeHead Can we get a remaster of the first two Paper Mario games first?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self care should be your priority. It’s not something you can “do later”. It’s not something you can fit the budget… https://t.co/Fzhz9jflG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TimMilesDog our 5th grade YMCA team — the Clippers — are taking on the CATamounts today. Thought you should know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a doctor back in the 1930s understood it correctly even though he didn’t know much of the science we have avail… https://t.co/hMVPXudOFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheldonAYS @footwork_king1 @_WiFi_Ty_ @Ravens @AhmadThomas13 @Colts @jmon_moore @packers @DelfonteDiamond… https://t.co/ktCfMZw8BD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshallu Old Main looking beautiful this morning covered in fresh snow! https://t.co/exTyemgGjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayoffDWadee @DeshaunBetter @okcdom If you were the real Wade you would just said "No."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Saturday 11P-4am Catch me and nyvaporqueen bizzness_1st at @VinocoEast 223 Main st Farmingdale for the Best E… https://t.co/KrzUTzNDrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bron_y_aurstmp Wait you mean you mean they took issue with a controversial outspoken black man. They seem so open… https://t.co/xZ3AqP9Re3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPFNewsDesk @AlterNet WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS??  Obama's Kenyan Brother intervie… https://t.co/QtIGAHIsip]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to believe it would be Lizzo, but it would absolutely still be Lewis, Oberst, or Gibbard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSJ If I/we (fingers crossed 🤞) get a proposal accepted, yes and yes. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KC_Fanatic95 Colorado also waffles back and forth between red and blue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on by The World Famous @stlmattress Outlet and support Local business this #PresidentsDayWeekend  Your New… https://t.co/lPS4vj3R9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[“People who reciprocate are more likely to be succsseful than those who try to maximize individual advantage “… https://t.co/icF0A5Favd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring your little ones @ Cruz Davis Family &amp; Cosmetic Dentistry https://t.co/NPyVj5n8m2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Jordan is a divider and a liar, not to mention a big jackazz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grubbjustin7 @NWBearcatMBB They kind of blowing the doors off of quality D2 teams so you tell me. Obviously someon… https://t.co/RBDzaesWfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I should be more responsible but I’d be so boring let’s be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so no supermajority. Do you have the names of the Republicans voting "YES"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know refs miss a lot of calls and are human and all that blah blah blah but that foul call on the Pacers because… https://t.co/gRewKdHbxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikaredd30 @BruceThornburg2 @privatear2001 @JoeNBC What did he lie about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone asks “what’re you thinking” vs “what’re you doing” is a different kind of love to me.💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pagos desde $98dls al mes #terrenos en #sanluispotosi #leon #queretaro llama al 713-325-0231  /  281-416-4203… https://t.co/NSgfdq0jqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thadbrown7 I just liked the irony. It was a good tweet! Without injuries SU would’ve played 10 against Le Moyne too, I’d think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just sampled the goods and the goods are great! If you’re serious about your kombucha, or just want to give it a… https://t.co/8h3qCWzubZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SP_Marc16 I’m tryin to make it into the stadium or out for the night. that’s a dangerousss suggestion.  I’m in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @LmccaulMcCauley! How does @EmoryNursing rank within Emory College?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that they unveiled WHO the drifter really is had me shook! Lore in destiny is still too notch]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you seriously don’t tip your servers (without the exceptions i used in replies) when fallout happens and people… https://t.co/g6qy1ZUMRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I deadass cried real tears about this back pack. Like 4 weeks worth of notes and the midterm is what, next week? Re… https://t.co/IaNWtGif0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattiecolin It's like..... they were literally naked in a bath tub together during the movie. Lol. Clearly Cooper's girlfriend understands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok ... so no NFL but dang ... we have NBA Skills, Tiger roaring, No 1 at No 4 CBB, and AAF all on TV (plus Golden K… https://t.co/5PkYYi4fnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need Malice at The Palace Episode 2 where Westbrook goes into the crowd in Utah and starts beating the living sh… https://t.co/6SYsJxBMFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day. My heart (and hands) are full. ❤️😈💋 https://t.co/RSNGBycK0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once a Perjurer, Always a Perjurer: David Bossie Exposes Michael Cohen for Lying Under Oath AGAIN! https://t.co/Dc1KvCkiDI via @BigLeaguePol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night Time is the Right Time!  Porsche Design Tower Two Story Duplex | $13.795M | Turn-Key .  E-Mail📧Brad@Arnowitzp… https://t.co/8fWd8s1KWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @realDonaldTrump tweets this out in response to @HillaryClinton, I'm going to have no choice but to vote for him… https://t.co/fGPmBjfJgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSNorman freezing rain now in Woodward, OK. @KOCOMichael @KOCOdamonlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kidsneeddads I’m sitting here tonight working and I am turning the corner on so many corners in my life BUT I can’… https://t.co/WkLK8OcfJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @UberEats for wasting over an hr of mine while I waited for McDonald’s to show up that never did...oh, an… https://t.co/LCDKr3tZrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kids #hairstyles #hair  . . . . Fresh cuts all day!! . 💯🔥💈⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️ SOMERVILLES FINEST AT IT AGAIN!!… https://t.co/g74mIFDyLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Madison Cosgrove, former @PDAztecArmy #PDHSGirlsSoccer Standout for making the Deans list at San Diego… https://t.co/9khOgja4R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to @esmemurphy's daughter and the rest of the Breck HS girls hockey team as they play for a state titl… https://t.co/1cd7kufKMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just one step forward and a million steps backward with this team every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember not long ago when we were a perennial "bubble" team and sometimes even hoping for a NIT berth?   Yeah, I d… https://t.co/ANTjuiufRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Here4it4 @konagrl4554 @Seahawksgal81 @JewelLovesBooks @Jane42976731 @AngelSing261088 @VAGirlsmom @lolamare69… https://t.co/gTY4JitUQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is hilarious. 10 things every woman should know by 25 www.cosmopolitan.... #laughter… https://t.co/mLXOnUDP5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sonya_T_Harris @PuebloHotChilis @robynncollins @anagoolzbee Awesome!! 🐿 Power 🦸‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should be known that Creighton’s Mitch Ballock was 11-for-12 from beyond the arc last night. His 91.7 3pt FG% se… https://t.co/ZzKuhzbCct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call of Duty Black Ops III Master Prestige and Dark Matter.   I don’t think I could ever get sick of this game. I k… https://t.co/dTgF1z5SXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great production of Ragtime @PasPlayhouse Go see this show before it’s history...again #pasadenaplayhouse… https://t.co/lm29fY1StJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a quiet person, if I’m quiet around you that just means I don’t fw you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did rondo take 19 shots tonight? Get him out of the starting lineup]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is fucking disgusting. sorry but no way. if i want steak give me a cow]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #saldiproducer time with the number one newscast in the borderland regardless the language!… https://t.co/C39mZiZDRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MENA_Conflict Honestly, it was just the first implement that came to mind and it amused me because it flings shit… https://t.co/Ck9C5pg7Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting Side Note: Dick Cheney needed a cardiologist back-in-the-day when he had a heart...]]></document><document><![CDATA[No he visto autos franceses, ni Peugeot ni Renault acá en los estados juntos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corbydavidson @badkaratemovie @theoldgreywolf - Yep 1980-1982 we had slave day but it was open to all students bid… https://t.co/Fo5HKZgDlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I’m an Apple 🍎 person. These look pretty dope, especially with that power share feature!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnderratedGami1 @YoutubeCommuni3 I jus subbed please sub back to https://t.co/eQ57j08kvy https://t.co/bSMjbcXq8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you order a PBR at the bar and everyone else decides it sounds good]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting that in Q4, with US equities in high capitulation, Berkshire only put $5.6B out of their $116.2B c… https://t.co/2ojHFGbgS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Homemade Is Best by @StickmanBrews @ YoBrew — https://t.co/uDS0c7OYiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett while i condemn what jussie did because it was wrong.  your silence on the domesti… https://t.co/tp0e0MFl7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man... the bonds of @kapsi1911 are for LIFE!! There’s seriously gonna be like 20 guys in my bachelor party and 16 o… https://t.co/Vj4KLMJqiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[On @waitwait, Matt Smith explaining how he got stung by a wasp in nether regions explained he was “engaged in act o… https://t.co/usxqE2XNLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vladi_VillegasP @eduardo_semtei La guerra en Vzla, empezo hace mas de 20 años]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre orgulloso y convencido de pertenecer a este gran partido. #PRI90Años https://t.co/G29fEdQadg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laser_Mike_89 Unless you go through a scalper ... the tickets come for the whole tourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeez a Christ, manafort only gets 47 months for fucking what? I hope Mueller team nails trump family tomorrow!! Wha… https://t.co/xeO5oaAnAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPURGEONdotUS We are never so weak as when we think we are strong, and never so strong as when we know we are weak… https://t.co/Yh9bqVurF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertCollard @Shadbeast @Jtg1284 @Suburbanxfight @BarWrestling True G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feldmanvideos I particularly like the using of Instagram like it’s Twitter with a wall of text. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Take your foundation down there and feed the children. Put your money where your mouth is...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmares72 @JJ66616 @rmorrow2018 @ItchyBacca @expandeduniv @ClassicGlu I said a no Boi we don’t like that Robot B… https://t.co/K1F1SiOgCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So sad to watch a desperate loser try to pretend he has even the slightest clue as to what is goin… https://t.co/ILO4skDDNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, even w/ the nice seat and all, I’m just exhausted after all of this. Kinda wishing I’d opted for the whole day… https://t.co/uiTFccU0mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFC there’s a certain fella on @Inter_en who’s a sensational crosser, dribbler, comes back on D, is Italian… https://t.co/IqP7v7xvqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeripick See my earlier tweet. Thx for the invite but I have plans with my wife &amp; @GiorgioAustin - 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my a cappella shit😤💯  What y’all think??🤔💭  #houston #freestyle #music #hiphop #rap #tobenwigwe @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/dlASPCfrJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astroricardo @Microsoft Yup. The PC that clears all my Chrome cookies on exit, you know, for security, but leaves… https://t.co/eIss9dOmKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you, that were sometimes distance and enemies in your mind by wicked works, yet now have he agreed [22] In the… https://t.co/fR2C85vYaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[El vocabulario y el trato con el niño es igual o mas importante q la tarea organizada.  No sirves!  Deja de equivoc… https://t.co/OPIiSkCU9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Becky_blindmark you clearly didn't watch in 2014 when they tried to bring Batista back as a face, if this is his l… https://t.co/RCnVYge2k0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Earth is a sphere! THAT FLAT EARTH DOCUMENTARY IS JUST FUCKING FULL OF LIES! #TheEarthIsASphere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Go back home to your garbage hole country, you racist anti semitic anti American piece of shit]]></document></documents></author>