<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What’s up in the 3 inning:  -Jake Mangum gets on first after a hit to LF *Score remains 0-0*  Going into the 4th: E… https://t.co/PvzV0p7jpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the winners of the first @SONC_BeAFan @FCSchoolsNC Healthy UCS Challenge!!! Way to practice heal… https://t.co/AgJEsXWvcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is #NationalTileDay and recognizes the timeless element of #architecture and #interiordesign: tile.… https://t.co/YAPg6fI8GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love sleepovers in the same room even when we’ve lived in the same dorm for 7 months]]></document><document><![CDATA[just read an article about people forgetting the names of basic things. one was a dude forgetting the word: hotdog.… https://t.co/FVLvJsCDMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hobbies include annoying Doc Ock with all my problems and making sure he knows I hate everything and everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madyyMc I made 15 strawberry daiquiris the other night these mfs be wildin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to eat some king crab legs tomorrow after work 🤪 #Muckleshoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[If recent history is measurement, there will be nothing said...they will bury their heads in the sand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra time. They really should have scored within the first 90 minutes. At this point in the season , no one wants… https://t.co/8Busz0vM7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found behind a washing machine in the new STL house. I miss you, too, Memphis. #memphis #found @ Benton Park West,… https://t.co/VsZ6TRlYDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It doesn’t like you at all” @AdamJBerry oh my!  @WaverlyHills is amazing!  #KindredSpirits #Louisville]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took the case off my phone for a minute and it’s so pretty without the case I’m tempted to leave it off 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow! my brother got another PR (4:27 mile time) AND is rockin’ his tux at junior prom #proudbigsister https://t.co/859RgUk6Wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HavokHawk @SeniorBoobies @WillTrumpYou @LeonWhi63670221 @Atheist_Dragon @Diaper777 @truckrogers1 @GhostOfTick… https://t.co/Rx3MR7p3Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[His pothole situation is absolutely out of control. And I pay a fuck ton of taxes. Ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have got up 5 times walked to go fold my clothes and laid back down 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @eji_org Preet, I was sure looking forward to you discussing the Cohen hearing on Stay Tuned. I am so disappointed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Witnessed the #waterfall churning that #water . #Abc7eyewitness #RamonaGear #hikinggear #hiker #hikecalifornia… https://t.co/O6yHVfZQSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking for teammates for the office trivia bar crawl on may 4th bang my line]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Faith is the substance of things hoped for and the evidence of things not seen.  I am a #leader and not a follower… https://t.co/vCs3IfvzwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this wrestler that sings the national anthem @foxandfriends is pretty good! So proud of you! Keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a good girl 🙏🏻☺️ #shibuinu #DogsofTwittter https://t.co/xafJjZoE6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades a Todas.  Congratulations to All #westonzuela #doralzuela #remaxhustle #topproducer @ Weston, Florida https://t.co/IonHe26gze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acoyne Also, calling Elite, Elite Plus, Star Members, Clown Impersonators, and Joint Fitters to board... needs to… https://t.co/NCNbJSLpuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[so I get to the library, got me some cfa, got all comfortable and ready to watch some #Riverdale all to find out it… https://t.co/xTdD4t0nEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree.  There should be term limits for everyone.  Some of them are so old they can’t even walk or chew gum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertvkrueger I really don’t know. I was in HUNGER MODE when it hit the table and just inhaled it. But I think it… https://t.co/lfVL7lYOMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterMcGraw @jackcohenphoto Literally got my new phone last night, the setting was defaulted to off. So I’m not being tracked?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KardOnIce @TiredOfYYCCold @kevinfolta @thefarmbabe That's pretty epic. Video would have been entertaining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm . . . pretty sure I’ve got a weight advantage over Dame Kristin Scott Thomas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarragan @CNNSotu Not done. Have U walked the  along the border?  Have U talked with a raped child? NOT. What U… https://t.co/KBKxmkgBv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could be sleeping, or I could be having ~thoughts~ on mid 2000s pop music. Guess which one I choose? https://t.co/32O5cDVEvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @Lisa70294648 Democratic Socialism has been pushed on Americans by Democrats. We heard it, they sai… https://t.co/0dgzwyhlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Dig up her past and all that she has actually done to@harm our country.  We don’t need to waste any… https://t.co/rMiL890qRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylesellers @ib13trix @EdKrassen @JimCarrey 🙄 well then it’s about time to lift up the rugs, and move the damn fur… https://t.co/SlMY0C6kQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobsoboroff @RandyResist @SecNielsen @BennieGThompson I have  suggestion.  Let's put Kristen in one of those enc… https://t.co/3j6bJBZ22c]]></document><document><![CDATA[My exes cunt mom has a lot of balls talking shit about me when in reality she’s a pathetic housewife who looks 60 y… https://t.co/TR22CD9bEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A city of renters asks: Can we ban landlords that own too much?” https://t.co/GGNohedqpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surfin3rd @NbeHull @NBEbulldogs Love, love, love using Wonderopolis to stimulate thinking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Lassiter @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson This is how amazing Toxic 45 really is !!! https://t.co/aApODosXME]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poster is just as epic as @johnmccaa.  I will definitely need to livestream this newscast here in Corpus Chris… https://t.co/tEPnpdIAe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[back to not going on social media for a week, see ya saturday twitter ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour @MarsRovers Maybe because more of my life's behind me, not ahead is Y I felt a lump in my throat 4 this b… https://t.co/AU6ZXccBn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the waiting continues.... #hatedelays #nerd #dc #batman #dufflebag #airport #lax @ LAX https://t.co/au9aaB2iv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part of insomnia? Anytime I get horizontal, my littlest cat glues herself to me. Then I feel guilty for t… https://t.co/t4MgI16NAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The light at VDV is a nightmare and unsafe!! Please sign https://t.co/bhugo2h7mE @vdv3to5 @VDVprincipal #allin4theville]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHAKEUP: In wake of funding controversy, #UCF President Dale Whittaker offers up resignation.… https://t.co/7ZfVkOKI97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SailFishMan @dbongino if you want real dialogue and progress this isn't the way to do it. but you don't actually want that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AspConservative Look, Twitter isn't the forum to educate people about this issue. It requires more than 140 charac… https://t.co/pl8jyi4FU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get like 600 likes on the gram and like 1 on here ima still post on here tho cause I deserve a million rts 😌 https://t.co/4zSSQzbT5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a slow process, but it is worth it ❤️ #hairtransition #wavy https://t.co/7y95xkXcFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important message today and EVERYDAY! #HumanTraffickingAwarenessDay #RisingAngels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/yJ7VRxMvQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Hampton!  It is Tuesday, VK has 15% off for #seniors today!  Daily specials MUG CLUB-bottomless cup of… https://t.co/S60ShiWY21]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you graduated college 1+ years ago it would now be appropriate to remove your grad year from your social media b… https://t.co/rge8k1AuJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiusXIII2 @JamesMartinSJ But be careful, these sick people might actually like the whipping]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, when I did the live broadcast, it was a snap decision on my part. I had a pretty stressful day yester… https://t.co/VcRjSi98O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the day with a stacked workshop alongside our friends @mixpanel here in #NYC! @TWG's own @jamescosta is… https://t.co/8OywuPBq0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBUcamp @SouthernMissFB @FBU_NC @PVAMUFootball @BCUGridiron @SWiltfong247 @247recruiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reasonjp And have now been claimed by Taichi... which is not a good sign.😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belmardays So to fix it, let’s force small businesses to offer the public pension system to their employees! We ar… https://t.co/oT3Qro3KuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowToGetAwayABC #HTGAWM telesco committed miss conduct planting evidence! #dumbo!!!! Glad her ass was caught!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday, boys and girls! Get to THE GYM for MANdatory Monday’s followed by Ben and Jen’s Karaoke! #weho… https://t.co/K1i4gwuvim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second Block Ultimate Champs! #sjhstrojans @ South Johnston High School https://t.co/oigdT5Uksx]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 años de trayectoria entregando lo mejor de ti❤️🎶🤠 a nosotros tu público... Muchas felicidades...… https://t.co/CE4q3UvYJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could honestly make about 4 themed T-shirt quilts for Brandon out of all of these shirts 🙄   1. High school  2. C… https://t.co/Ia90ahAKKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ed_alca The pickers do not speak English ( big indication not legal) and live better then I do. Nice cars nice hom… https://t.co/P0r5Ryu6Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fourcornersfld @enolatonlori @EstVallChorale @PoeticPastries @MMcLaughlinsong @julie_dibble @Lead1225… https://t.co/R3Cfl8F1Hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The twins !!! Rose and Rachel Dolmovich talk about tonight’s game win over Rickards and the Final Four @DuvalSports https://t.co/zn9BGVP2cF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montelll13 I’m so glad my kids have never done that. Nathan tried but leaving them in they’re zip up jammies all day has benefits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunnyAnd70s @siggyflicker @AllAboutDaTea Wow!! What a horrible thing to say !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great day for a @TexasBarCLE! Excited to be at the 2019 Changing Face of Water Law Course.  This program is… https://t.co/yg8KXx2AEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeCalderon Pues el espurio ni se enteró que había esta oficina en la ONU. Ni por arriba de la cabeza pensó que podía apoyarse en ella.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mix that negro with that créole make a Texas bamma ⚜️💜 @ French Market (New Orleans) https://t.co/inIebpXQiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an unexpected stressor alters your life plans, it never hurts to try and unwind at the end of it. Made atmosp… https://t.co/dyC3t2Mw9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[This muscle milk doesn't taste like muscles or milk! https://t.co/F7WUzQsNIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me so happy. Thank you @Marriott for #recycling! ♻️ https://t.co/sZjc2SzuKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @BernieSanders @amyklobuchar @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @SenSanders Should have mentioned, intrigued by @BetoORourke]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/BCF1xMbgaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before February ends I just wanna say I love being black. I love being a black women! I will always stand proud of… https://t.co/YgLzAiHX2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Democrats cannot speak truth. Period. But they are slick and refined when they speak leftist babble. It blows my mind!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaxgirl @hrkbenowen Notice how they flaunt their disregard for the rule of law right in front of law enforcement’s faces...disgusting 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[No that was Mexico's responsibility to get their self2 the negotiating table not only is Beto trying2 overthrow rig… https://t.co/2t6O6JcpPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HA8BhNOAnk It's SCAD Awareness Week. Listen to your body and be your best advocate. @SCADalliance #scadisbad #survivor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at I-605 / I-10 Interchange in El Monte, CA https://t.co/q1kCQwftXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way too much to analyze 🤔. It’s like people who think racists or white supremacy only looks like neo-nazis, KKK, ra… https://t.co/207rhlFHo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakinimani @acceber910 And if Khloe screwed Jordyns baby daddy the screams would be her for miles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoDiscussions The Twelfth Doctor  😀  #DoctorWho https://t.co/ztWPYZ2iSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[He leído y #recomiendo VALENTINA, de @IsabelMataVicen Una #novela ☆☆☆☆☆ preciosa que atrapa a lectores de todas las… https://t.co/qQXMtGXvd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby is out of surgery and all went well. She’s just even more of a sleepy hound dog 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noturbusinessUH @swmrs @maxbeckaaa @therealcoleyoly THESE PICS ARE SO CUTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I change my ticket to see blink-182 for one to see u guys in slc? Discuss @swmrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently realized how easy it is for people to ignore me because I was trying to talk to someone but I’m so short… https://t.co/TiodTg9DGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, our Senators braved frigid temperatures for the annual Legislative Polar Plunge! They donned costumes and ju… https://t.co/gICE5Xk4UV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’ve only had my kitten for a week but it makes me sad that she was wandering the skreets as a lil baby cat… https://t.co/naPW6rQ3TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to hearing you perform Personal Jesus in April 12th !!  @thebandperry @TheReidPerry 🔥 https://t.co/wO9A2qEqyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BogdenJo I don't trust the announcement in Ontario.  It is Ford's attempt to bring two-tiered healthcare to the pr… https://t.co/ToFsyJhvYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeresaViejo Happy Valentine's day God bless you forever my friend https://t.co/E1PUFMosYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @HouseGOP @jheil @GOP @JoeNBC   WHAT THE FUCK @GOP?   Let me guess.... Too many Brown People winning… https://t.co/950cwJhpKf]]></document></documents></author>