<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jordanbpeterson My heart goes out to William Secord Mattson, Adam Picard, their family, friends and the neighborho… https://t.co/rz85dEEe3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homebrew - Drinking a LPA by @HopTownsBrewing @ The House of Hopper  — https://t.co/eS1qYCN5XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just4BeerLovers @beerhunter74 @harpoonbrewery @ManvsAle @zappafaye @danmayer77 @mtravis63 @wrayzors @cellmavin… https://t.co/dGm7m0jWLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump Hits Back Hard At TV Pundit Ann Coulter: “Wacky Nut Job”  https://t.co/vJoo8dqY7m via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today years old when I realized that “PDQ” stands for “Pretty Damn Quick” 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britbritmarieee @OhYesWeKam @thehill Brittany has 15 followers! These troll farms are apparently experiencing hard… https://t.co/7rN3Fzh0XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Courtne49776255 @YouTube Thank you I tired for like hours all I know is I like the song lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These companies made billions by getting Americans addicted to opioids and are still making money by manufacturing… https://t.co/EUAfnF3ROY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wonder Twins are amazing by becoming malleable to meet the needs of any situation. How do bring a bit of their… https://t.co/lwqFsdqRJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HardRockinGirl Nice . A little wine with your friend. https://t.co/u8C9tpAF2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naima Why is he speaking publicly about an on going criminal court case]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad respect for the people canvassing the subway asking for signatures so they can become public servants 👌👌👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was watching a TV Show and this one dude asked her gf named Tatiana to merry him. Now I can’t stop saying “bust it… https://t.co/JWMaKfH9CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_gagliano @theadvocateaca @theadvocatebr Awesome, Katie. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnieroye127 @AfricanaCarr #RIP Malcolm X!! You taught us about how to embrace the brotherhood of all Mankind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word of advice for future and current College Students. Get involved! Employers are wanting students that are in in… https://t.co/UlnqbbfBHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Broussard No matter what he does NO! Reason is: he choked a championship shot away at OKC then left to play… https://t.co/Dt22i3iIpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy trade deadline day hockey fans! Be aware of fakes and please only retweet legit sources. Thanks and enjoy #Tradedeadline2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quando você desafia a si mesmo você começa a experimentar um crescimento.  #meudesafio #meucrescimento #crescendo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go hard for anything your name is attached to every single day. The hustle comes before the shine.  #startuplife… https://t.co/ecqeyCKDVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AD_WYMHS maybe we can set something up with WY sometime in the next couple weeks? If not just baseball maybe somet… https://t.co/x88iNityO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see how today goes. #interviewoutfit @ Santa Monica, California https://t.co/VwXbjl5zvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could stand to calm the fuck down a lot more when responding to people about things I’m passionate about lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, even if they only did 8 bars a piece, you still got a whole ass half album on features alone. Must be some… https://t.co/L8stc1f0ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoszmanRachel @Spotify @BNBuzz I love music so much I named my puppy "Spotify."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m playing a  cool show at my barber shop Sat night! I have a touring band from Los Angeles “McFarland” at 7pm and… https://t.co/9sMGTlWCnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgfair Some forms of nationalism are really sick. This orange monster is not a patriot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Imagine being responsible to the next generation and beyond?  And  umm, it’s happening now, dummy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was definitely worth the detour from Louisville to Chicago! I've waited 33 years to formally meet larsul… https://t.co/cQ09wljm4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BrooklynBatman I don’t feel like this is at all serious. Warner Brothers hasn’t made a statement about him being… https://t.co/F5XN1alAhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beviesplace I specifically answer this question in the book. It’s too much for Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said last year that the big contest for aoty from me is gonna be @FreeThrowEmo and @HeartAttackMane and now that… https://t.co/EXPPeSGIHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedWarMutt @kayjay_official @ManLikeBillyJoe And I was calling people kids or on young side because it would e… https://t.co/jgHvRuuxhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting thread with lots of lessons we can learn from as companies build the next generation of solutions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone go see the Bruce Nauman at MoMa PS1 (it’s there until Monday)! https://t.co/NOTgBxlLSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not the guy you want to ask their opinion unless you want to hear what I think not what I think you want to hear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gjallarhornet @realDonaldTrump WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother… https://t.co/1oIpZHkg7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anm8tr09 @dokun24 That's not really the premise of the show. Origin Stories and is all about people's developer jo… https://t.co/DmGo4nr7sF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, we made it to @vice news but...     in a shitty way. Glad I never touched this trash and glad all of you didn… https://t.co/2LI0ZmYrp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[And our spiritual leaders have mostly gone into hiding 🤷‍♂️ when I was growing up our community leaders stayed invo… https://t.co/MNBgNtv6mK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up groceries (at @Walmart Supercenter in Findlay, OH) https://t.co/Tot1exc7U4 https://t.co/aYEICiHdsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Perhaps Hollywood helped him plan it. It might not be just the money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @NorthKorea isn’t that who the sonics had off the bench in the finals?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ritysayo @KamalaHarris Politics become dysfunctional with debates. Solutions require discussions that exchange inf… https://t.co/yHQTqNBSMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuel L Jackson with a #Knicks shoutout at the #oscars   ‘Hey Spike, the Knicks won tonight over the San Antonio S… https://t.co/jpSGPMyESb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle And this is the problem with our government. They can’t make a decision on anything and stick with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CityofLexington @LCSJackets let’s all get behind @MsSanchezLMS ! She deserves this! https://t.co/0CSLvBxe0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa State WR Hakeem Butler bench pressed 225 pounds 18 times, impressive, especially with such long arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting with the wedge tonight. #srqfood @ The Rosemary • Rosemary And Thyme https://t.co/FjvxsQEOEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are the scores before entering the final round!  Pitt- 146.700 West Virginia- 146.300 Ball State- 146.100  @dn_sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohammadKHasee5 @dlshadothman @Ilhan What? Being a racist and anti-Semite is what this country needed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demon time is in effect! Congrats boys, what an effort this weekend. Congrats to Coach Hanson on his 6th title as a… https://t.co/FQdhZoaohs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lacapital @leovasco666 Que astucia, pensamos que detrás de las MUERTES estaba LA venta de gaseosas. Gracias x aclarar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdabrosca @michellemalkin Oh, she made her position crystal clear . . . she’s been doing this for 30 years and wha… https://t.co/PtuU8VZwaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this kid! Finished up freshman High School swim season today with a great Sectional Final. 3 swims, 3 p… https://t.co/2eaheGxcad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csymrl @npratc You should play Hard Times by @guster as a transition piece.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/CkSPfgzWID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thes not much intrigue left with this #WVU basketball team, so let's search.  When Trey Doomes starts a game, and h… https://t.co/FJpxsWqBPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The celebrity lookalike shooting contest scene in @JamesGunn’s Dawn of the Dead script might be one of my favorite movie scenes of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The girl checking IDs at this Tito's thing just told two people that their badges don't matter and they needed to g… https://t.co/1xuEsp0OXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney silhouettes are a Classic Disney souvenir memory — especially if you have them done when the kids are young… https://t.co/I9Qqzhg8JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez is a moron. US is the most generous country on Earth. If U can't make it, U R not trying hard enough… https://t.co/rFhGDCgQdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Wisdom👏👏👏👏  #MindOverMatter #MorningChill❄🍵🍵🎧🎶❄ @ Midland, Texas https://t.co/L3Ucx9KxfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crampell @lifesafeast I'm not particularly religious but my idea of Hell is spending Eternity in a hotel room next to the ice machine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Queens BLVD &amp; 45th Avenue in Woodside, NY https://t.co/QY6bsISPgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes dessert is simple perfection. Heart-shaped chocolate cake, pawpaw ice cream and pear sorbet swirl, preser… https://t.co/EYSGKS3cf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cloakzy It would be an honor to play with one of the goats of the game honestly.. for once someone would be liftin… https://t.co/Cj4y87g17m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriisEspinoza7 to @ChrisWondo oh man this makes me excited for the season! Vamos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckoge @notJudah_ We’ll end up in prison eventually so this doesn’t surprise me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the @jonasbrothers are back together again!!! #TBT #Sucker #JonasBrothers 💚☺️ https://t.co/FCc4Vt4vdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felix Rosenqvist with Chip Ganassi Racing at the IndyCar Spring Training at the Circuit of the Americas in Austin,… https://t.co/Djr99sI5E0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gorgepulse Further the design of ATC on MAX virtually prohibits trains from passing through stations at full speed… https://t.co/ZGU1ZWDW1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rosáic by @BeachwoodBBQ_LB at @beachwoodbbq_lb — https://t.co/6bNW3SOpQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only been in my new position for 4 days and have already reached almost over half my quarterly goal. 🤑Gods has been showing TF OUT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel Good Friday starting off with a 5:55 am 4th Quarter Run‼️it’s got me feeling like 👀 #RCJH #ItsLit 🔥 https://t.co/6C46Atv3O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAshfyre @WalshFreedom He's speaking to the trump dummies. Facts don't matter to trump dummies.  trump dummies just believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[this remix (and many of his other ones) are my jam! https://t.co/dNiC8I6xjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The all-new “A220 Compact Sedan” w/MBUX📱MB User Experience📱 as modern and easy to use as your favorite touch-screen… https://t.co/IVBlK2DYPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseAGraterol PRESIDENTE GUAIDO,  POR FAVOR Y CON TODO RESPETO, NO PERMITA QUE LO MANIPULEN, HAY GENTE A LA QUE US… https://t.co/nKNzMM9sah]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re told to be at another store that’s an hour away at 5am and no one is even here.....😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buying a gun in #NorthDakota takes about 20 min... doesn’t matter if you buy a handgun, rifle or shotgun... you jus… https://t.co/Qi99YLAuqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight Madness score updates:  Team #1 falls to Bentworth 4-0  Team #2 falls to Riverview 2-1  Great job tonight… https://t.co/Tbz2gpqjsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kale perfección. Plantula casi lista para trasplante 👌🥬🥗 @CIP14 #cultivosurbanos en Hermosillo, Sonora https://t.co/PcHnlX9iYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 99000876 without the “zoom zoom and a boom boom”💀💀 @jada_elease @AngelLashay_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonamarnez cuando tengas oportunidad leelo completo, te veras reflejado...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acitrep @StLouisBlues Blues have used 1 of their 4 recalls allowed for the rest of the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piglungs The horse will be fine. Probably just wallowing in self pity and the realisation that he/she could have b… https://t.co/qFEdxk0uZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneEmbrysKids A.C. with a “He’s finished” after the Ibaka haymaker. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maria12feliz No la quiero asustar pero no vamos a poder hacer nada, tienen todo el poder simplemente hay que ver l… https://t.co/jr71Pamu9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing wretched about this! Woo! Thanks Santy! #beergreat #beerfriendsarebestfriends #MarchBeereak - Drinking a Wr… https://t.co/3nC7Rw7koU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our love will last till the stars turn cold.” ❤️ @ Vergennes, Vermont https://t.co/EpLkJ4DE91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah. Absolutely true. Sorry about that. But I always mean well. https://t.co/eyp9roVJ09]]></document><document><![CDATA[We used to ask Sophomore's to write a 6 to 10 page research paper for their final, and it was 20% of their grade. My how times have changed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this today on @facebook had to share. #realtalk #Truth #tax #TaxSeaon #IRS #W2 #Money #ReFund https://t.co/jVU88Xv2eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TicklesLaRue @GOPoversight @realDonaldTrump Don't have to prove it he's already been convicted liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News:     Eight Americans among 157 killed in Ethiopian plane crash     Via @nypost          https://t.co/cIYp2bC8zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos por @elheraldo_mx en breve. Pónganle porque platicaré sobre #cine con @JMRivaPalacio para #DeQuéva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charles_gaba @mwarner95 @IAStartingLine @adamwren https://t.co/rfoeAWj3hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulariasmtz @rhinoexplainer @lhan55 @Conacyt_MX Y ve la administración pasada todos con títulos y fue la administ… https://t.co/bwGyGdZVZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CANTDEALDOTKOM This is what I'll do to get u in the mood https://t.co/xYu01gHFqN]]></document></documents></author>