<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sarah Asher and Nick Keeling play The Common Roots Pub [3642 West 8th Street; Cincinnati, Ohio  45205; (513)  954 -… https://t.co/TCYASEJIdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaCHCH @USPORTSca @McMasterSports Congratulations. Theresa Burns is legend. Well deserved.  Good luck at the nationals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This group challenged me every week to be a better coach and role model. I was able to witness extreme growth throu… https://t.co/al1d8u1T4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Anyone who still supports Trump has absolutely no respect or regard for the presidency or for our Country. It is that simple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nashville at night...2  #WhenInAmerica | Phase 8- Last Leg | Shot on #35mm #cinestill @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/50xdBpE3ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Unbelievable what you have accomplished and you have only scratched the surface]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LasCulturistas can you please make a t-shirt that says “that’s you, bitch, I’m different” because I need 10 of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn! I think I have a sinus infection. 😳 Well, Vicks, internal drowning by forcing myself to drink a lot of water,… https://t.co/aztgxASICP]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY NATIONAL OREO DAY!! #jimmyeats These are all the Oreo products I had over the years. My top 5 Oreos are  1. W… https://t.co/f7rtIrkLvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skyhawk1 @MurderCusDoll @MetaBlackCat @Wondergal82 @SerialGourmet @GothamsKitten @RegAndy76 @Sp1derV3n0m… https://t.co/aXzLhngNAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Flyers seriously think the fans are dumb 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️ but why would they ever handle things correctly 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a gimmick trap, ain't falling for it. Wouldn't care if he beats her down in the alley she inhabits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelockhart The logic of “a blameless life” also ignores that Manafort is about to be sentenced for other crimes i… https://t.co/gBcRPSQBCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped pin Near 159-299 S Hamilton Dr, Beverly Hills, CA 90211 https://t.co/dj9NI3UPzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Assyria15 You see that date? Lets stick to the present. So how much does Assad control of his own country? Wh… https://t.co/r6e37zSCPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the tracks #subwaytrain #subway #metro #underground #onthetracks #newyorkcity #nyc #newyorkphotography #newyork… https://t.co/0px4K98zOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You weren’t there when I would need you, your the one that kept me sane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark Sometimes, putting it in is the exact right thing to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and we're off.  Greatest place to be right now. 2019 @MSHSL #Wrestling Tourney.  @MSHSL_Officials @smwoaOfficials https://t.co/ORv9aEQl4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[This jersey may not have been a good idea. People think I'm an usher. https://t.co/RIsd9CG2xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE RIGHT NOW Rev Myles Young preaching live on #holyghostradio #hgr1 tune in to get your blessing! #hgrpreachers… https://t.co/ZBMxOuPNQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teambercase @superenthused @PrinceCDev @shawngorlando @nephie I'm a pretty big fan, but then I'm easy to please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dramamind @Jeremy_Danner Not just #Dannering but the @eBags backpack as well! Love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiewhited0000 @landon10davis @MarcPendleton @TheFong @TopBillingSport @PressProsMag @ReggieFOX45Now @WOSNsports… https://t.co/HM083RD6g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been passing this place when in #downtownsanfrancisco near @stpatsnyc the @delarosasf so I had #antipasti… https://t.co/a2odUyshcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out and about tomorrow so I did my sketch a day early, but this is my first attempt at a #SundayFishSketch ! Highli… https://t.co/R2vBRRTI4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @JulieReichwein1 @jnottah @TWITMO_INMATE @sxdoc @SickOfTheSwamp @OutOfRegister @DanCovfefe1… https://t.co/h6FuqfTErb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawthorne High School is excited to announce that we will be hosting  our second annual college fair on Wednesday,… https://t.co/w9JGyerD5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Job 24:1 [ Job Asks Why the Wicked Are Not Punished ] “Why doesn’t the Almighty bring the wicked to judgment? Why m… https://t.co/f9AUROvtyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is such a true quote! Real estate is very much a self motivating business and everyday I’m constantly pushing… https://t.co/p1vNbXuNYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalMayne no, responding here to defend my journalistic practices is absurd, but I will at least comment regard… https://t.co/XMyxl9wvzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicOseiNews @WBAP247NEWS I hope he gets the same treatment When he arrives at prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost You keep up your propaganda line. Keep tearing down the government. You go baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, watching #TheAvengers for the first time: what is this “tesseract” thing   roommate: it’s blue cube which holds… https://t.co/P1JODNVn3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any good hashtags for disabled/chronically ill and similarly marginalized characters?  #writerscommunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any other artists out there battling depression, living and working with the complex relationship between creativit… https://t.co/dWtCSyxPca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many Thanks to ISIO – The International Security Industry Organization for adding a couple of my books to their Lib… https://t.co/lRlrVfIq2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the first day of March and @TCM's #31DaysOfOscar contiunes until this Sunday on @Turner Classic Movies. Today… https://t.co/bqmHevNewk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beth is such an amazing character and I’m so happy we learned more about her tonight ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lawrence Boys &amp; Girls Club in Lawrence, MA https://t.co/Z23byaqpmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJoe2019 @BDCoachCox @SultanofStat @SiriusXMFantasy Yes indeed. AL #LABR auction begins tonight at 7 ET on @SiriusXMFantasy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydney_strider @davidhogg111 @al3xw1nd @AMarch4OurLives @FortThomasMFOL Great pic. Glad you got to meet them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before my birthday celebrations start, I wanted to tweet a sincere thank you to Fran Dunphy for being a positive am… https://t.co/fPiKJwrfSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just published 2 new photos to my Slixa profile! https://t.co/yKB4RvZzIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumperSeaney @pinkk9lover There's a reason Democrats want illegals to vote and to lower the voting age to 16]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all remember when we would dance to this song?😂 @anissaf88 @__ariianaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- please tell me about this hoarder C- I really hope he is better but he filled this house so full of stuff you co… https://t.co/J1lMfa86oY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nealrogers I just read you “I Used to be. Bike Racer” piece. So while maybe not many podiums your turned out to be… https://t.co/l5szbtso5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DIorioNathaniel I'm not sure how that really changes anything. It's still not accomplishing anything beyond hurtin… https://t.co/phx2lTlu3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevetefft @NickWCVB @EdWCVB @mikestand5 @ScottIsaacs No LEG or FTD lines, either!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obsgiantscompul Absolutely. Great power. We’ll see where the contact, the hit tool and the approach settle in. You… https://t.co/MNPNRHdyU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump Sick dude on a disgusting mission]]></document><document><![CDATA[I teach a self contained 8th grade class in Littlerock, CA . Looking forward to this chat. #EdutopiaChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lines drawn, As I fight strong, this hate faint last lifelong, hyped on sights of my tribes bond...TOGETHER... https://t.co/HPHfuvWO8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @KevinMKruse How about a holiday period , with parades and stuff, to celebrate Lent? New Orleans would be perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No olvides cuidarla por si mañana, en vez de verla, te toca imaginarla”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad heated. You ain’t “adopting” jack shit from a breeder. https://t.co/70907mjZ74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini @04phuxache @MikeRinder @AETV @Scientology @Twitter I'll Investigate 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so begins the hemming and hawing over whether or not I go to my 10 year HS reunion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good God.  11 years ago, my head looked like a thumb with eyes drawn on it.   I was in a lot of pain.  Chewing MS C… https://t.co/eT4w9pdcDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/0NRs0XnNWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingHiggy513 What does the host of jeopardy have to know about the contestants?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat I think my wife is tired of hearing me say this exact thing every time I try to connect to BT. It’s w… https://t.co/qLqIO2TncL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers How can I DM you I wanna roast you cuz you’re a dumbass but I don’t want it public?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether he’s in Cleveland or somewhere else, it sucks to see his talent wasted on a sub .500 season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea you can say #pizza is my fav #food 😛🍕 #foodie #pizzatime @ Giordano's Pizza https://t.co/37IBQqtB2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatDudeJulian @anthonybuckley @NYCFirm 2013, 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018, 2019* https://t.co/pzKPCizkqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helmchenTN @CarolineWJHL Says the dude that would be crying and begging for someone to take care of the situation.… https://t.co/S7IkM69mfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 We‘re working in California to pass #SB50, the #MoreHOMES Act, which will end exclusionary zoning, legalize mor… https://t.co/pMrSmr5huP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathan_shiba Thank you for your perspective, Nathan. I too believe in a balanced education which includes travelin… https://t.co/ZnlWJ0GiFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHill1075 @WilGunter @jenjensenmorse Let's just all agree that initials are not a nickname.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJ9828 Saw your post about the barbie dreamhouse I think that it's awesome, I didn't know this and It's okay to cry! I'll give you a hug!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pantog No-till actually does till a spot for the seed to engage the soil just perfectly.  The only thing is the ti… https://t.co/WWPwHFRcwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid lager - Drinking a Zoigl Star Lager by @abcbrew @ Appalachian Brewing Company  — https://t.co/dDEmUAImxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[170: Nick Brigante (Newton) and Jesse Presburger (Mahwah) scoreless after one. #njwrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotfussxhearts Thinking of you and wish I was there with hugs.  Mornings are hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @StephenGlahn Thank God my former crack addiction didn’t turn me into a religious fanatic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am also that old, but I still have voted Democrat since and including McGovern. Never voted for a Republican poki… https://t.co/zRIM6f3rdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killer show by the @cahoneydrops last night at #wwgsteamboat . They brought some amazing vibes and funky dance tune… https://t.co/heMXKcUJ7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metzgarbage They did one for my cat but the lady singing "meow" is just too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSHSAA As a parent of 3 kids who each  played sports all 4years of HS, as a former athlete and coach, as well as a… https://t.co/ucykeMsHEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay que dejar de actuar por impulso. Siempre conllevan a malas decisiones. Ojo ahí]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new tour stop specific poster looks beautiful next to my two @Metallica flags. 💗 https://t.co/of7MDkc8eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sj_sinclair @PlayWarframe Awesome.  Now PLEASE FIX THE DAMN SOMACHORD FRAGMENTS IN ORB VALLIS!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BPhillips_SB Lots of solid tackles. But I don’t see a franchise tackle in this class after the Jonah combine. He w… https://t.co/mQdWxatHz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes @latimesopinion Disagree.   It would be a self-redeeming act by Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen was convicted of lying to Congress. Keep that in mind.  #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indigostarr777 Like I’m shivering lol I had to check the weather I thought it was gunna snow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FentonAD Great season Fenton GBB! FHS softball is proud of your accomplishments. 🧡🖤♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NFLCOMBINE (@ Lucas Oil Stadium - @indy2018bid in Indianapolis, IN) https://t.co/5WL3nAZPnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up on the BEST drama on TV. @OWNTV #HAHN @tylerperry @iamtikasumpter @Only1CrystalFox @PeterParros… https://t.co/XGzsQ9pwXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJasonKanter @thehill @michaeljkellyjr @LindseyGrahamSC Wow doc u put trump and Jussie in the same tweet, u must… https://t.co/HvRYIxoAs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you teach Latin or Ancient Greek? What is your purpose? IS there a purpose? #CANE2019 @Theodulph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fan of Texas’ basketball teams? @Rickyprep is covering the women’s home game against Texas Tech this morning while… https://t.co/LwdtuxYJze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let her keep talking. The more she is talking the better for my side. https://t.co/MENZ0AOJeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews Can you at least have the integrity to put this in context and say that this is, in fact, a ridicul… https://t.co/02O7I4V3Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haley_lagrone Just as a clarification, I liked this because I'm TNIYB, not because it's a funny tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning as I was at breakfast I ran into a newcomer to the church, a backslider as well as church members. In… https://t.co/FTxHphy96a]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOD: A good leader gets people to follow him because they want to, not because he makes them. - Tony Dungy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek #Insane mccain, daughter of a Treasonous scum for i$LIErael]]></document></documents></author>