<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hozier is extremely, naturally talented yet he doesn’t get enough recognition as he deserves )):]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new radio!!! #music #radio #carradio @ Wabash, Indiana https://t.co/USSua9Jg4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who wasn’t stanning BlackPink before Jenkai is trash af. Those girls are legends and y’all missing out.… https://t.co/HviJJte0vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[1-2 week’s before leaving #TruthNorth lovely woman at church asked:  “What is your nationality?”  Shocked. I didn’t… https://t.co/D1xfZgH5Ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[And herein lies the problem. MDs purchasing Lilly stock bc they know we can’t live without insulin, and then their… https://t.co/Q8DdprHZwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩🎼@TeenageFanclub #teenagefanclub 🙏🏼@Wallpaul70 https://t.co/MnXwaonedH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque I'm proud of Amy Klobachar. That's thinking outside the box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Montejp231 @atrupar @Jim_Jordan I had a gym teacher in high school who stood at shower with a clipboard, made us d… https://t.co/cWaAKepffL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Seattle is a pretty great place to work for women’s health 👩🏻‍⚕️ #IWD2019 https://t.co/bg2p3ceD7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book bingo night at SDE!!! #readacrossamericaweek #drseuss https://t.co/UTD05jbUM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really is spring at Mizzou. My first bird sighting! https://t.co/8Ozz7fbjew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for March Break? Then sign up for J.A.C'S #LEADERSHIPGOALS Camp! Open to young women ages 7-17 with a special… https://t.co/KA4HEUka4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to apologize on behalf of @WarDamnDarcie and I to anyone in AU Arena today, as annoying as we are on Twitt… https://t.co/HOE3RYApCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My vet just referred to my cat as very elderly—he’s 14 and a half, but in great health!—and I’ll be honest, it kind of shook me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be present at my best friends engagement party! It was the party of the season, obvi 💕 I’m so happy to c… https://t.co/J3pwURcqsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GossipisSin Speaking negatively about people, even if retelling true facts, counts as sinful, as it demeans the di… https://t.co/2uXkVOagje]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the FBI's Ten Most Wanted fugitives has been killed  https://t.co/YUmJ6x1Q5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_clinton @lay_jim @Authorfan @Charrlygirl @PaperbackMania @EdLaabes @Robert_Essig @bookmovieguy @LordFroggy… https://t.co/KtcTwpX6m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SoSoStef @PinkTacoProphet I’ve been but thanks. And since y’all are both here.... either going to reunion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so confused as to mix race. He hate white male but he is half white ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to 3 of the 4 Colored Girls, looking for @donnabrazile to complete the conversation (and sign my copy)… https://t.co/IE4YSBKWva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerDukoff She’s out of here tonight, mark my words. Colton hates fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 53.6% heterosexual, 92.9% homosexual, which places me in the bisexual quadrant. https://t.co/yatg0XWlrd via @idr_labs 😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thuggin', so fuck your opinion I'm thuggin', so fuck how you feeling I'm calling my spirit @ Warren, Arkansas https://t.co/E6KzHhG0SO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@droachnola @GabeUKSaintsFan @HutchersonYa I kinda want to do that now 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ponggay and Jules, you are forgiven. Kaya naman pala dumepensa ng ganon di ba? Sana next game ganon na agad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s Dove Chocolate wisdom: “Trust with your heart, not your head.” Um, no, been there and did that. My heart fa… https://t.co/b7S3IYsj4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyceRivard13 @HuntsmanAbby Obviously MM sent Huntsman her script for today! SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmdtecodai @REDI_Guayana ¿PAZ con armamento belico? Vayanse al coñ de su mad..... #MaduroUsurpador  Pierden el tie… https://t.co/thzbqVH553]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyansMom2 Thank you! It was so great to meet you in person!!! Hope you get home safe ❤️💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller is Porn Star like a job now?  Wonder if they file taxes and how much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MChaseRadio @AskCapitalOne Hope they were able to help and glad you caught it early. I had my identity stolen last… https://t.co/G9ov2K8K6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandparents are about to leave me alone at their place in Fort Lauderdale for two days and you bet your ass I w… https://t.co/zNHzjleTwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen it feels so good to be in the same time zone as sam and colby and jake so i really don’t wanna go back to indiana time zone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvorakoelling What the Warmbiers deserve is for someone to put a muzzle on the orange loud mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fastforward1115 @TwitchyTeam Exactly. What she said says more about her than anyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lusciouss___ I wasnt on for a few days either. I thought u had gotten suspended for being unruly again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you with a 4 legged baby who has started to lose its sight or has lost it completely. This may be the… https://t.co/cRGalsavOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the lost DePA (Deutschpaleale)? Interesting style blend. - Drinking  The Perfect Disguise by @dogfishbeer a… https://t.co/ydx4jQOnAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of sleeping alone  I just wanna be where you are, tired of saying “goodnight” through the phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to volunteer for a campaign and wonder which elected official packs the most punch? I swear, look no further t… https://t.co/97fV2iTrNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the party begin! #girlsweekend @ Lake Arrowhead, California https://t.co/lJDvsr8mY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday breakfasts before my double workout classes are a STRUGGLE. I make healthy smoothies, but I consistently day… https://t.co/AGa1oGmLU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the girls who played Beth were ah-mazing!! Beautiful @NBCThisisUs episode about dreams, love and sacrifice.… https://t.co/y8Tv06SubJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of all of our boys! Congratulations on an outstanding season. Roll Tribe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scsny also has a senior center, case management services, social adult day center (10am-2pm), home care program (c… https://t.co/oyW6gTyeZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think most people agree that you are a garbage individual.  Your kind is being and will be phase… https://t.co/7bNK6aamna]]></document><document><![CDATA['EL ÚLTIMO EREMITA', de Alejandro Cano Rubio @desandescom https://t.co/piLDDXe4De  Esta novela —visceral y real— es… https://t.co/fW1ASrVWkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing you say wouldn’t interest me, all of your words are like poems to me, I would be honored if you would take me as I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s one person in particular who will always have a special place in my heart sadly 🥴🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been just singing and dancing so much more. Love yourself, love your body and shake your booty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katy_fit My condolences on the loss of your grandfather - and I hope your family (you included) are healthy soon.… https://t.co/6QRdu6pqaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonfavs @NormOrnstein exactly. they are no longer pandering.. they're as uninformed and dim as the Fox News hosts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá dijo que yo era hermosa aun con ojeras y mi reacción: https://t.co/xEXAdyd1SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell there was a ruby red slipper theme at the @SeminoleState Dream Gala https://t.co/jkBFkan0s0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SterlingB126 @rrfosho72 @alegriselle @astros_dude Yea! The burger place!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason #127.3 why I love my job...when we are able to dedicate new “toys” that ensure the sickest of sick babies an… https://t.co/SX9R9xrdwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgilblezy @dorimonson I tried to talk him out of that story, Matt!  Don’t encourage! https://t.co/RxZfn8LInX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good grief it’s #PresidentsDay and already 539k tweets from @realDonaldTrump (it’s appropriate to exaggerate with t… https://t.co/qfIWzzLezh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissLizz I extra hate every person who has ever told me that passports are cheap]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first LIVE interview in the Tampa Bay Area for IHEART BUSINESS RADIO! Had so much fun.  What a great group! 🥰 .… https://t.co/KTHoWQpFaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always "wyd" never "let's go to Starbucks to do hw/study and then get a workout afterwards"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Shit! There's nothing like a hot, fresh out the fryer, and liquid sugar bath, Krispy Kreme glazed donut... My… https://t.co/cCAVA3Xomf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t always agree with all of his decisions,I do agree that he was the best representation of what a President… https://t.co/X2NlF3nnul]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really about to order @nberrelez10 a heart shaped pizza but he won’t answer and how am I supposed to tell the… https://t.co/X9PWyWjRKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again. Rush hour and the train is stopped 3 stops away. @MBTA @mbta_alerts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job guys in the 200 Freestyle at Sectionals! @NaplesAthletics https://t.co/4LXKKdMwxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amber Alert startled me and got my attention. That is the point of it. I am sorry that poor little girl was fou… https://t.co/PBzziADetT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy for the first time opened the car door for me 😢 is 2019 a change in men ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BailenTheBand wow...loving this group! #7thstreetentry @FirstAvenue https://t.co/nAgXQKZxEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[sofia says its weird that none of these foods are touching but please weigh in https://t.co/if2QCR1s3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why yes I have ditched @budlight and officially switched my drinking preferences to @MillerCoors!🌽🍺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg yeass! It’s been a minute. So happy to see you. Miss you much. Life is not the same 🙄 #WiningHourChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s NOTHING more attractive than a cute boy worshipping Jesus... prove me wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any movie with Anne Hathaway just really hits the spot if you know what I mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars NYC! 3.14✨ @CityWineryNYC #VINOVIBES https://t.co/jvUgFHoEPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a weekend and it continues! Congratulations to Michael who is also one of my "littles" at APA! He was adopted… https://t.co/Er41RqfkaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just from reading the chorus, the Japanese version of Could it Be seems more romantic than the English version lol… https://t.co/huGo7MIFDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#señoranivel hago que mi novio me lleve a mi casa porque muero de sueño en la peda srry babe]]></document><document><![CDATA[tristan cheated long before jordyn got involved.... so who’s really to blame here? just a thought.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Because he's waiting for Mueller report to drop to avoid screams of obstruction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at #bnppo19!  Making plans for #bnppo20! ❤️🎾🌴🌞 @ BNP Paribas Open https://t.co/Q0uQH55R7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[After she died he married his first love. The one he left for Ann. He went home and married his best friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers @thehill How do people this consistently dumb even make it to the polls? Kentucky is no better off… https://t.co/xvF72aNSt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a job? @SF_newengland is looking to hire more than 3,000 people!    DETAILS: https://t.co/c1ar0N56Xi https://t.co/LLUX9P1pCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_danii_lana Sweetie, I know. I’m so full of hurt it seems all I  do is cry hard . I find that laughing is best… https://t.co/nIriNLPJgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive home 10 hours to the World Series, then drive back to Oklahoma at 6am after not getting home from game 5 unti… https://t.co/z23f8JYkYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who sees that “momo” thing then has a mini heart attack? Bc every time I see something about it I die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Sick to death of Jussie Smollett in the news! Get him prosecuted and move on to important things. He… https://t.co/w0lkemRoBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[feels so weird to do stuff with my phone and not have it drain its battery at like 1 percent every 2 seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're representing peeps. Throw them playas in the air. When we're talking in our sleep does it listen on my system… https://t.co/XsqGtaVQAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for a fun weekend spent back home 🍎🏙. @ SoHo, Manhattan https://t.co/eGfVYuu2ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend saw I was cold and just came over with a blanket and tucked me in ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to spend a few days at one of my favorite places with my favorites person!  #UntaggableJason #adventure… https://t.co/6njnjtMVGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need this energy lol. I be buying everyone shit and I can’t even get my chipotle paid for... ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st Birthday to my Eliza Nadine! She is an amazing, funny, intelligent, kind, beautiful girl of my dreams. ❤️… https://t.co/E9WB4rdWCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[teach me how to dougie teach me teach me how to dougie https://t.co/9T12wQnfpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, it’s cold enough to wear a beanie... ✨💁🏻‍♀️😏🙄🤳🏻💜💖🌸🌹🌿❄️☃️〰️➰⭐️🌙💫✨ | 2.22.19 // https://t.co/6NIc4WTtfn… https://t.co/kzCQOuu2vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i just got told that they say I love you but not in love with you, is selfish. I believe that cause i’ve been told that a time or two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, I came in and passed the test first try without having any prior knowledge about Southern’s SGA. It’s about rea… https://t.co/wbEGRq9HLK]]></document></documents></author>