<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#mybeautifulwife - I ❤️ her @ Miyako Japanese restaurant https://t.co/LSNbwapDel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoodGlamnana46 For real; in ALL my 64 years,  I've never, never, NEVER seen anything like this! WTF?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#swipe for #scenes from #smalltown #america.... #old #highschool turned into #hauntedhouse ! #BOO #Fear #halloween… https://t.co/BD2mlyGEvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Bongino to Hannity Hilarity Entertainment for the gullible]]></document><document><![CDATA[... not just for white people’s knowledge. Black folks should know what “intersectionalit means as well.   She does… https://t.co/Ekqnoe197N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganzane512 @AlmostRaymond_ @GaryBedore Dang How did you find that out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump hard to have a campaign violation when you're using your own money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took my Valentine to a nice lunch today. We ate at #Costco. $1.50 for a hot dog &amp; drink. I’m a hopeless romantic. #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESTOS CONCIERTOS DE BAD BUNNY VA A SER UNA MEZCLA DE CLASES EN TODOS LAS SECCIONES QUIEN HA LOGRADO ESO EN PR?]]></document><document><![CDATA[im going to go insane being cooped up with nothing to do. WTT resume for job interview pst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maga1Radio @peterboykin Hes one of the Democrats trying to kill this great country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshies today #fatbike @ Borderland State Park https://t.co/rVRc8vAivJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some sushi! For a chain kinda sushi place, @KabukiCorporate is my favorite! Great service, great flavor and… https://t.co/gYCmpV1jUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times do I gotta say it? Quit sharing photos of yourself taken on your iPhone 4 etc! That phone came out i… https://t.co/PPds2v7kON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwilker I know right!? We went to a show and in a bid to seem futuristic they sell digital photos of you instead o… https://t.co/eJrmeWyGZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matunos @mtsw If he wins Iowa he doesn’t need to win the presidency to break even. He’d be in the final 2 or 3 for… https://t.co/itPYOwPzuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got home from work yesterday and was greeted by my G-babies. I was tired, but I’ll always find energy for them!… https://t.co/HsPHgPHxYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilioAlvarezI @cesarfaz @AccionNacional @PRDMexico @movimientociuda No pasa nada si se asume que llegaste por vía… https://t.co/B8B9C62mNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @switchfoot, y’all making it to Philly alright? We got some snow starting up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mara_nicole7 @blackjohnnydepp @martha_squeak @Jerrypleasure Except they shut down on Sunday’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessieflori @CavemanSyndrome @Dismattle Angie ask your dr to talk to @losangelesspine about your case. Maybe Dr. Hah has some tips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inverse: An Alabama Teen 3D-Printed a Foot So That a Wounded Marine Could Snowboard. https://t.co/2gQUORBsYD  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranncescaRobi1 Would she agree to lie down on the train tracks if he does?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Twitter, I’d like to take this moment and announce, I too, am entering the bid for the White House in 2020. I… https://t.co/JZHBUjB3Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen twice as much as you speak and watch the difference. #livethestory #dailyverse #livingwordgalena @ Living Wo… https://t.co/hVeIF5DCaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #free #book #giveaway - Ron El’s Comic Book Trivia Volume 12! Only available for today’s #book #signing, Sa… https://t.co/u5bgzQq3OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Salzano14 Also, I'll be on a plane all day tomorrow so I won't be able to watch any games or see the selection show :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering the thrill of interviewing this guy from back in the day in Hattiesvegas and so very, very glad that “w… https://t.co/bndW5Eua30]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #LeafsForever, @91Tavares got a standing O for being taunted by #Isles fans. In #GoHabsGo, Saku Koivu got a stan… https://t.co/Lfq3d52Wc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The racists already almost lost it when we signed Eric Reid, can you imagine what’ll happen if we sign Kaepernick 😂… https://t.co/KX9UAdbPQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopCraveNet @kailah_casillas Lindsay is psycho good for @kailah_casillas 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Restorative Practices training! Building towers... #FraserSchools https://t.co/mpXTbwNE8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amd3366 Lmaooooo please give me a time when I've said that word in the time you've known me, I literally go out of… https://t.co/irPasye0lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this exclusive interview at @nba allstar weekend with my brother @felipelopez13dr . Make sure you check o… https://t.co/A5y8R1SNad]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD!  #JessieSmollett stole the voices of ALL victims of actual hate crimes.... to further his career?   Hope they… https://t.co/lYk2C31tp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HCKiN1ik2j Discount Code: Escobar20  #insanelabzambassador #teaminsanelabz #insanelabz #jointheasylum… https://t.co/KilQRHo0Y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertHayden @epredator you much be taking rubbish best of luck , Honda is in trouble in UK and  needed to leave soon !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your actions speak for themselves.   The social media space is way too saturated right now.   Everyone is an EX… https://t.co/fGWkmZpUq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this is how every conversation between @JosaeRiver and Ezaz goes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Spain Park High School in Hoover, Alabama for the latest country wide news. Hoover is a well to do suburb… https://t.co/8VEb6QjJ40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinkNews @IndyaMoore Hahaha..now that's what I call pissin on my boot and telling me it's raining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federally driven environmental mandates force retirement of Plant Gorgas - Alabama NewsCenter https://t.co/d2sx9YPP5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craig Counsell dubbed Hader, Knebel Jeffress as The Electric Dudes. What does that make Alex Claudio?   “Rechargeable Battery Dude.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TetraSh0t This is the most Loren gif ever. Just blank expression of disappointment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blksuprman is it just me or do the PBC on Fox fights next Saturday look great?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii He does not have to sign the Emergency. WH has come up with $8 Billion. Now he has to Veto the Bill an… https://t.co/e6SJrnJdae]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Dr. Seuss is from San Diego and his Birthday is also March, 2nd.......that is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so dope. You gotta try it. I had chamomile with French vanilla creamer this morning. Best cup of tea I’ve had… https://t.co/wZaL069O9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the man doesn’t want to end up “suicided” by the Hildabeast @HillaryClinton...]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I'm just like well we coulda, woulda shoulda, been a thing but tbh I am not sure I want anything at a… https://t.co/rY8yZtknyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD @redsteeze So it’s not about a media that constantly rushes into fake stories without any investigation… https://t.co/x9pJcGmpWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @CNN   Total anti-American trash talk coming out of the mouths of the Commentator's and Socialists/Commie mouths.… https://t.co/XiSIQtZww3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcHochman @OfficialCrowder @ErickFalero You think Krafts balls deflated the moment he got caught? 😉🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the studio this Friday Eve working on a new BIG piece!  Calling this one “PASSION”. @ Van Slyke Art Studio https://t.co/vVIhGcP7Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Class AAA bout is 182-pounds with @CabellMidland Zach Dillon taking on Anthony Carman of Johh Marshall. Carman… https://t.co/TJma6bdIRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_wire @RealJamesWoods @RealJamesWoods tells the truth and "you cant handle the truth". Get it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Sunday #sundayfundays  Things daddy do for their princess #princesslondynrose  Daddy's job never done.… https://t.co/vR86B1y5Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I gotta say is my friends are the fucking SHIT. I love them hoes #blessedwithebest]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to an article on Reddit the other day, word of mouth barely effects podcast growth—they need to be aggres… https://t.co/2nuRNhsWM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@free_democrat The need to expand the means of productions and recruitment of material for wage labor for profit do… https://t.co/1kYL7cot6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleveland bright and sunny expecting 1-3 " snow today , Kramer said it best " mother nature is a mad scientist "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennyg my friend @rbaker201 says that Kanye gig was $100,000 pay day.  @aldente37 thinks $10,000 is reasonable.  Who’s closer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyBash was the first artist I’ve seen in concert and I’ve loved him (and his music) since hearing him on SPM’s t… https://t.co/kRAu0ZQwwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bleachers are filled with thousands of fans who criticize those plays sent in by the football coach that didn’t… https://t.co/iFaa8odezl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1043TheFan all this @TheKylerMurray talk has me wondering:  how big are MY Hands??!! #NFLCombine2019 https://t.co/w9lzVUhinm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shear lunacy!!! 30 minutes to show time! @ Delachaise New Orleans https://t.co/pgQ7XTT1bT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellieseats @realDonaldTrump What’s your issue with the great state of Alabama???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Tyron may have fallen in love with the idea that everyone is afraid to press him. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t move shoot pass or defend why are you playing at all? Brady manek has a trash Stashe but that is no reason to just avoid him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo @peopleenespanol @JLo you represent a powerhouse of focus and discipline, it is evident in your work, and the… https://t.co/yFXE4zmfZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the new @kenjeong special on Netflix. Seriously running out of underpants because I keep pissing myself. 😂… https://t.co/kpdWUnQGyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaywill70 @wjmoon @OTBaseballPhoto Growing up in New Jersey, the only games that I saw on TV from the #Coliseum we… https://t.co/yl5raWSdGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you permit it you promote it. #Missour1 #AbovetheLine #Un1ty we work everyday to create the atmosphere of lett… https://t.co/moRJ0w2dtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawgs_Wrestling @Andy_beatty7 Great season GCHS... Big props to 120 pounder David Jordan for his accomplishments as a freshman! 🤼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartanJessica @dreamsunwind0 Next winter we need a TweetMeet at your Florida house. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police sources: New evidence suggests Jussie Smollett orchestrated attack - CNN https://t.co/yBp7OE04qU]]></document><document><![CDATA['We don't have to live like this and we refuse to live like this,' said mom and event organizer, Elva Mendoza.… https://t.co/Ir0dFRKcdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joksrs How about no? You’re just gonna cry about the nerds following you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest fear is that one day I'll find a girl and believe she's 100% the one but then she will say she can't stand Eminem]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s called love baby..............................................………............... it. Is. Called. Love, babyyyy… https://t.co/t74tyGgGMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Next Level Burger in Seattle, WA https://t.co/HNKRIOB3Qz https://t.co/JzXgKMDYZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Destado1 @JamieWalton good morning and to @Nanny_Lu_Who who does this 11:11 thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Sl1wfyNpjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait a minute😲this little shit causing serious dissension among our Country? And listen towel head, @Iwasborn and r… https://t.co/TjgZ5crDKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djlavoie yes i must confess the same i saw it as a kid but i love the music..there was pathos at the end of patton… https://t.co/aeOH0DuK9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vancouver and Surrey reveal proposal to build new driverless shuttle routes. Trying to win federal grant and assemb… https://t.co/FwEepBXvek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyENicholson @DevinRubink @rob_keyes --and correct me if I'm wrong here-- in your vid you're playing Amanda Wal… https://t.co/982xlNi8mZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 Has Ukraine filed a request for Manafort's extradition?  Is this feasible?  If the result of a pardon… https://t.co/zPDWR6xQG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino What we know about McCabe’s actions scare me.  What we don’t know yet terrifies me much more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the Press is cheering on the exploitation of children right now on NBC. #MTP, #NBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSae1010 I love how good of friends everyone in Popipa/Roselia/RAS have become.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Somebody send him a copy of Amendment 1 of the US Constitution and a pacifier. Baby's crying again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty! (@ 18 Grams Coffee &amp; Tea in Elk Grove, CA) https://t.co/KkrbTYNdXC https://t.co/8vTRze52UD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you come up with this withPutin’s balls in your mouth or are you just really excited about Kim… https://t.co/WEkKnbVEan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heidiburgett Nike soccer kits are unoriginal and boring I wish you would change to somebody that has a little bit… https://t.co/yCt5y1kPgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedbauer2003 @JimCanto @katyb_spencer @alysonshane @DreaVilleneuve @TheComicHunter @MattJ_O @GabrielSurfCat… https://t.co/QDaFpb0r83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGramuglia I already wrote one (a graphic novel script), but I doubt if it'll ever see publication.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry Pull all funding until all illegals are given a path to citizenship or sent packing back home. If the 1s… https://t.co/z6AtijQJXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liona005 @ContempraINN How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/Fvjf4UgC5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlYourPalster @OregonGovBrown @trimet @DLBragdon He was in charge of Metro when you could search "bus" on Metro's… https://t.co/LNu2uWGNFV]]></document></documents></author>