<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kmac1240 I'm gunna get murdered by Villanelle while I'm there hopefully]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello yes, my tax lady just called and offered me a part time job at her accounting firm because we talked about me… https://t.co/thM3GBfcjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful @AlisonDawe1 for always showing her passion for @APforStudents ! #KleinISDAA #KleinGT #MomentsInKlein]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i hadn’t been so tired from all my bs this past week I probably would’ve saw homeboy after work instead of knocking tf out lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh to love is to feel and to feel is to experience life through your heart center.   More than not we are all lovi… https://t.co/NpThR7ft7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has ever seen me eat a club sandwich would never question why I’m single.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinosaurtime @leerjamie Jamie doesn’t have an iPhone so here https://t.co/c0LEVG5WNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dare to be a donut in a world of plain bagels 🖤 https://t.co/68MJAyyTKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Artist does “her” Art always! No excuses! 👏👏👏 Love you @culturababy        #Repost @culturababy with get_repost… https://t.co/O42he1hrT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[jay sean really made two songs and dipped @jaysean why did u fall off so hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[There wasn’t nothing godly about Chick-fil-a this morning, it was terrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA['I'm Here Too' - Short Film on Teen Suicide Prevention https://t.co/XwrVyFMGQ7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @CokieRoberts He sure as hell knows more about N Korea than Cokie!  I can’t believe the comments by media that… https://t.co/QaXs9kTIk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A trio more inseparable than the Kardashians #DECAAdvisor #besties #InternationalWomenDay https://t.co/rOay40qIOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine a man trying to tell you what you can &amp; can’t wear https://t.co/t8GkR1b2TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachelorABC DID I REALLY JUST GO THROUGH A TORRENTIAL TWO HOURS TO HAVE NO CLOSURE AT THE END.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously? Apparently even ignorant white English speaking (maybe not correct English) white women are the aristocr… https://t.co/rYpE39uI7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know,and have seen the rise in hate groups but know they are trying to get into the mainstream. https://t.co/GThEeBKLpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[No snow, only blue skies. God country, I tell you. #tooblessedtocomplain @ Sedona Desert https://t.co/jy0wzny7F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @SarahKSilverman I'm sure their parents are very proud. They were raised this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, all is well!  I can watch the new gadget video by @MrBarryLewis!!!  Woohoo!!! https://t.co/HSm8f60RC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please all just agree that the phrase is “all of a sudden” not “all the sudden”? #petpeeve #grammartips]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US Military is poisoning our service members with not only #PFAS but so much more!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSetley @dunkindonuts Please donut make this matter less important than it is. The people NEED to know. #GlazedAndConfused 🍩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EquusontheBuses @NeilevansEvans Tbh I tend not to follow them. Vice versa too, I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando me sacen de pobre vivire la vida como se me de la regalada gana pero por lo mientras... a trabajar pobres 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StripeysRiposte @manlogic2 @ColoradoMGTOW @Spirittribevibe @LamentMyIcarus @FikeMartin Oh dear. Turn my back for 5… https://t.co/8AeF4Jq7Cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deannaraybourn @UmbrellaAcad Right??? Also the ending—give me more immediately!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ABHcosmetics your next palette should be a blue/plum/silver version of Subculture, with the same formula. I think… https://t.co/O6TBRuOVKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Awe Yogi Bear💙💙 Break it Down Yogi!! https://t.co/OA4V5BuYrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH OUT!👀 My girl @jessiSmalski21 &amp; I are going to GRAD SCHOOL! https://t.co/NBRTxagod7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CierraCulos @oliviagobrien i didn’t even know she was coming what 😩😩😩 when did tickets go on sale]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to say no, setting boundaries and putting your health first. 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinManriquez My mom had to meet meiners in a fucking Home Depot parking lot on a Saturday and pay her $20 bc the… https://t.co/Y833tvFEwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Mr. Graham what a disappointment you have become...the current administration is… https://t.co/ux89MKh3xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are still conducting an investigation on an entire lie that they made up..@realDonaldTrump is so #winning in #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait i cant tell if my friends really want to see asib with me or they just want to watch me embarrass myself i-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby girl had her 4 month checkup today 😭💉👶🏻 and now weighs 13 pounds 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[really glad your band worked out so well that you now support trump and troll girls on twitter 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brody, aka The BroMan, rules the neighborhood and he knows it. All the babes know it, too.  shawnbeury felixladybug… https://t.co/xyGnmGoedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@questloyaaa @samm_v12 WE have Luna in our blood! All started with papa Ralph.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ycZYX8P94w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawrenceWilson @AmberMeowmtl Amber NEVER SAID WORKING AT A SPA OR AGENCY WAS BAD. She clearly stated that she had… https://t.co/XJ0uOOu1rW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sad that @CW_Arrow got cancelled! I don’t understand it and I definitely don’t like it 🥺💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stichomancery It's like, congrats for demonstrating that POC (even BPOC) can be tools in a white supremacist syste… https://t.co/4cI1QyPFjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinley break up with your boyfriend, I’m bored... no srsly I wanna hang :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaFamiliaFilm Is that Brad Pitt😁😁,thought it was Jesse,is that Casey,I thought it was young Ford😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong Used @IRSnews in 2011 to weaken the conservatives by disallowing non profit conservative grps to fo… https://t.co/GzePU0Cdrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[They put a pick it fence around a port a potty and called it a restroom 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[A NEW Witness has come forward in the Jussie Smollett case https://t.co/NU7duDJRdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know Walmart sells microwave-only pasta coolers at Walmart for only $10? Dreams👏really👏do👏come👏true👏 https://t.co/MtokZnGjzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently grading some pretty rough papers and rewarding myself with @Fritolay #cheetos every time I find an error.… https://t.co/K5QqAnvr1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shamanashtart @realDennisLynch @AOC It was Reagan emptying the mental health facilities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Watch “Mystery Theater 3000”... those movies they showcase are the worst! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyHagy But at the same time are also vastly increasing the numbers of endangered animals to extinct because people… https://t.co/0lR222QevC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this is what USA aligneds itsrlf with? She must go she is a hindrance to our American wYvof life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marjbadeo @honeymoon0424 @patrickquiroz_ @itsmeangelieofc Hahaha love you Patrick and lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Harriet Tubman Living Legends Award was presented to three dozen of our outstanding civic leaders yesterday. We… https://t.co/ldvVbQAgkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EPoe187 A fascinating summary analysis. I note that you have already responded to some constructive critique. I my… https://t.co/Nyl0VRXtqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Jeanine Pirro, The National Emergency - Opening Statement https://t.co/jQcTzvYxfS via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Newsflash! We've been celebrating America long before you, president moron!]]></document><document><![CDATA[luke hemmings come online and appreciate my love by following me please. 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mary_chaffin Nope, I’ll take passage of the Equal Rights Amendment please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#poetry #amwriting Turn to Stone . . . . . . . . . . . . . #poem #coffeeandpoetry #writerslife #writersofinstagram… https://t.co/wcfSsUGKLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you order everything on the menu minus 5 items   (backwards post)    P.S. get the avocado gado gado (not pictu… https://t.co/5RnPHTfIpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who hate on people who take naps are hypocrites! They drink coffee or monsters to get energized for later on… https://t.co/Z32cj9LnWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if all this Jordyn stuff is just the works of Kris Jenner to gain more media attention???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Arbor MI Wed Mar 6th AM Forecast: TODAY Flurries Hi 21 TONIGHT Snow Showers Lo 12]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AtlanticProWrestling #Bro vs #Nightbreed @trillct_ @sethoran vanityvixsin @ Newburyport Elks https://t.co/6VzxZV8fuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg_4949 @dana4bama I don’t know what it is — it’s got to be frustrating for them all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidNakamura Trump carries the black suitcase. What kind of case do you suppose Kim carries his nerve gas in? Sam… https://t.co/nDkwGZcJDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[really went to town on this lululemon outlet store today #ThisIsThirtyOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #CustomerService job in #Warsaw, IN? Click the link in our bio to see it and more… https://t.co/pnva6iKTzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey okay look. I honestly don’t care if you copy me, but try not to make it so noticeable AND maybe wait at least a week to share LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb I miss seeing you on the track, but I bet you didn't miss that pile up with less than 10 laps to go… https://t.co/kS4tdB7yFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AukeLlen You and I are gonna be good friends, Luke.    (In the interest of full disclosure, I went for mini wine b… https://t.co/5V8rjCdgsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gdinc2016 I wish you well Greg. Be careful.  Caffeine headaches are not good.  Meanwhile at Casa @Mr_Electrico ... https://t.co/mfRNfgSdfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great work Riley! We had a great time riding the @SDSnowBHills @southdakota @SDSnowEast @Go_Snowmobiling snow was l… https://t.co/BcSqAkQUD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsLmrx @siano2020 Mine were 3 12 hour days a week and then get called at 5:30AM needing nurses!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 oldest of 6- 4 girls 2 boys there is only 9 years from me to the youngest. There are 2 sets of Irish tw… https://t.co/bepyhQT9WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The faces I make when I'm on a new journey! #dontbeleievemejust 👀 #thatpart  👌🏽🖤😗🤓 @ Conway, Arkansas https://t.co/p9ADEQ8YKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Geez, if only the @nytimes had spent the same effort and time to investigate Trump's criminal connection… https://t.co/rwC7SWDFjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. This is real. Pinch me. 🤩 and share with your network! #movethedial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calm before the storm, time to get wet. See you on deck. https://t.co/PGmjxE3m2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe we should sit back and pay attention to what is causing the reaction and not just how one is reacting.. just… https://t.co/xWn2y1WxDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancun/Riviera anyone!  These deals are UNBELIEVABLE!  Book today and save! #traveling #travel #travelgram… https://t.co/89jMhPmQko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treymangum @shadowandact I haven’t been able to look at him the same after he played a child molester on Law and O… https://t.co/1lxapRgpY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All y’all are saying it can’t happen. Laws already on the books. Didn’t New York just pass a law s… https://t.co/di5GrKy7JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daylephoebe @eliyana32floyd They’re pricy but I have two pairs and they’re all I wear fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since humans are roughly 60% water that practically makes us cucumbers with feelings. #mentalhealth #mentalillness]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vqkjZzK39G Staging Your Home for Top Dollar, Low Cost Make-over Tips https://t.co/JdQvxRwVIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbsentiaSeries  any info on AmazonPrime announcing date for s2 Absentia start in USA. I feel like we, AbsentiaFam… https://t.co/UaN6NNifIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's up, @RobinMooreXXX? Did you have a good #SundayBunday? 💜💜 https://t.co/XnbZjkw8QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really sorry you experienced this (like so many other queer babies). But I’m happy you’re happy today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been able to contribute a lot to conversations about the NBA lately, not because I care at all about basketbal… https://t.co/cqiMztxAar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@healthshark7 @CWBChicago @JussieSmollett Thanks to selective screenshots it’s hard to see what upset me. The probl… https://t.co/7AmFSEAWGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, my phillistiens every where. It's coffee time. Ugh. It's not good coffee either. My coffee maker is new, but it's a cheap piece of 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaKinsey @KateFlannery Omg please post more of these pictures of behind the scenes of my all time favorite show!!! #please]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to NOLA with my best friend last spring break, now she’s coming with us this spring break 🥰]]></document></documents></author>