<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It may be almost 5:30am but I got my big hw assignment out of the way and now I just have the small ones gn😴😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nat_b__ If you can’t be at lunch, I will have them in the west office the next day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eunyangnbc  You probably haven’t heard of @GwynnieBee before because it’s better known among curvy women!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnEMarriott For a while I was following the “conservation” hashtag on Instagram. I stopped when I was buffetted… https://t.co/leqLadLUbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pablo Escobar's hippos keep multiplying and Colombia doesn't know how to... https://t.co/vN46wQM17z via @YouTube 🦛🦛🦛🦛]]></document><document><![CDATA[What bookish adventure would you join? I would want to join any Lord of the Rings adventures! You can save on the g… https://t.co/YqIloI6u21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaspersMBB Beating Iona by one at home my sophomore year in 2013! #tbt #GoJaspers https://t.co/AQGxyYkUDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a necklace expert by any means but these seem like 2 different pieces]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Almost There by @aaroncarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/8hxGPcoNjg https://t.co/t8Ec4VfsTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amaya_kelsey congrats on your PR trip! I admire your determination and passion around what you do for us, your cus… https://t.co/4TO6KaL7ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Dear Alex, we are praying for your complete recovery from cancer. We are in Houston where MD Anderson is… https://t.co/AHa00CzSLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoya97 @gatewaypundit #CoryBooker @SenBooker  A young man accused you of sexual assault in a public men's room.  W… https://t.co/HhPx66xiTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to #Taplife #rehearsal.  Last day to purchase #TaplifeHeroFoundation shirts!! (@ MTA Subway - Rockaway Bl… https://t.co/t1UOiM2AIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moi qui travaille chez Métro, sur le plateau Mont-Royal.  Moi qui voit @JeanThomasJobin :  Hey!! Vous êtes Jean-Tho… https://t.co/w5tUVKKV82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay last @gateriverrunjax post for the day. I’m hobbling around very slowly, but we celebrated with some fiveguys… https://t.co/7dFMsDd4eJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: State attorney's ex-felon husband voted twice in Florida https://t.co/IMkJmZF718]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore a red sweater to work and my boss real life came up to me and said “su whoop” and walked away.... im honestly shook rn 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life's too short to have boring hair. Schedule your next appointment with us.  https://t.co/tL4utOmi8g https://t.co/y3OZwyoIxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katjexia @QQitsMina @soymilkgoth @myuturgy Oh yeah, I just meant like... for example I drive kind of like a grandm… https://t.co/AgbK8PtFIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turn my chair around for you @kelly_clarkson   Kelly Clarkson - The Joke (Brandi Carlile Cover) [Live in Detroit,… https://t.co/o8d2mpgS49]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings from Asbury Park, NJ - Springsteen  For Everyman - Jackson Browne  August and Everything After - Counting… https://t.co/eTVR8BlfIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonsterBedir TF: I Like It Rough TFM: So Happy I Could Die BTW: Highway Unicorn (Road to Love) A: Jewels N’ Drugs… https://t.co/AcLpR5ccNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnewfry @MayhemMarquess @ljs39 @alicecstuart @resistant_cats I know they exist...and I even went to one once. Just not my thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lady in a Benz gave me a compliment on my car.  Lately juggling my bills (such as my car payment) while I’m in gr… https://t.co/ANYj2bcO0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[TXT (투모로우바이투게더) '어느날 머리에서 뿔이 자랐다 (CROWN)' Official MV https://t.co/62xKHLNZ9t via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJRMarcelin @DeannaMarie208 @DrJaimeFriedman @EmmyBetz @NicoleNugentPhD @meganranney @shawnsidhumd @DrHowardLiu… https://t.co/sE8DVy38vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Des Plaines, IL? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/m44mYID5cI #Aviation #SafetyInspectors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting late for the #CONTEMPORARYATHON but better late than never. This is for the challenge for a book I recentl… https://t.co/yXn7yIPe0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyFirstLoom.  I'm so excited to use it.  #knitting #knittingwithoutneedles @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/wGh7nwzavI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Sunday @CarrieNationBos  #dragbrunch #dragmetobrunch #bostonbrunch 2 pm Showtime https://t.co/pRmVGh2oXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that @UNwomenLA’s BJ’s Fundrasier event is currently happening until 11PM @ Westwood Village! https://t.co/J0THBNq8Uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga with the number one on the billboard hot 100 and top 200 over Ariana Grande... TALENT WON https://t.co/AMrA2xwrPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my PI gave me handwritten edits on my manuscript... but boy oh boy does the “doctor handwriting” stereotype exis… https://t.co/jEECoy8a50]]></document><document><![CDATA[A força da maternidade é maior que as leis da natureza. ♡ https://t.co/S770KJShcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenHollander @Flipgrid @McAllister_ES @thechixons @ChatterPixIt That would be one of my Gifted kiddos...he alwa… https://t.co/F65YmXPpq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think globally it is becoming more noticeable.  The veiled attacks and deference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surgeon_General I CALL BULLSHIT!!! THE MINUTE THE GOVT HEARS OF A WAY TO TAX SOMETHING, IT SUDDENLY BECOMES DANGER… https://t.co/mbPV9LcdRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been quite some time since I overheard the word "Rumsfeld" at the bar  #overheardatabar #twooldwhitemen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro dude how fucking funny and original really out here with the comedy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbwnyc @backt0nature They were giving him a bath . He has his own pasture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @StCroixHospice! There’s nowhere else I’d rather be serving patients as a #Hospice #SocialWorker.… https://t.co/VrS1HB8tNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityofmonterey wondering if you were putting fence against new walkway on Just watched an elderly man try to drop… https://t.co/FW7Owm2BMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drarubia @gtconway3d The slasher type trump keeps slashing away at our democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresCatania Sorry, I’ve been a fan of Teresa for years and last night, she blew it.  No excuses.  She was just terrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSpanberger Can you help Cortez please.  I placed her tweet in my re-tweets.  She is exhibiting strange behavior… https://t.co/QJBe1JUBlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayainsworth_23 I’ll have to try them out! Big red is my fav so I’ll probably love that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taoist breathing (infinity breath) nourishes all cells with vital chi. ☯️.             Metal is just good for the s… https://t.co/4RaMMg3CYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed my Valentine's Day with my Hunni Bunni!!!! #jamaicaqueens #likers😘 #followme #followtrain #OneTime… https://t.co/mm5pW08MJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett Boy you should be the one to shut the fuck up. You're just mad that everyone seen through that bull… https://t.co/DBXGrKAIS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanmarnold @eyeonaxs They’re actually re-branding and changing the name! There’s a vote right now. (And ugh to your Dad jokes 😜!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to WIN a Taste of Paris with Your Own Box of Macarons and a Signed Copy of Paris Writers Circle #giveaway #win https://t.co/LDCbvXsJC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy sunday to brandon’s parents who get to listen to me violently barf my brains out all afternoon, ily and srry 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC So if I'm hanging out with my black friends, am I parading them around? Are they my tokens]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll stick to my Tagalongs lol 😆 what’s YOUR favorite #GirlScout cookie? @WFLA https://t.co/CTwbIFlkrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is humorous. #humor #laugh #smile #amusing https://t.co/iPX6dx1Hpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The World thinks we are fools for having you as a President. I talk to people all over the world d… https://t.co/4NHjDric6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 5 Disney Movies:  1. Beauty and the Beast  2. The Little Mermaid  3. The Lion King  4. Aladdin 5. Princess and… https://t.co/6jQhBGfvho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because someone is your age, doesn't mean they can't mom you if they see you need it.  #Moms]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WilliamByron’s #24 is looking good today! #Axalta24 #DAYTONA500 https://t.co/rkLAToEyMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toucherette I say it every time we're in Vegas, Atlantic City or (possibly soon) Macau. #KidsAndCasinosDontMix]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalmargaritaday portense bien! Sino...Me invitan!!! #elchiquilintodaslasmañanas en Jalisco Norte https://t.co/cw0cDsUGxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your Tech Ops partner knows the perfect gift for back surgery recovery! Huge thanks to John Simeone for the ex… https://t.co/I56guJR0HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our team members bring passion, dedication and excitement to an environment that offers endless possibilities. Want… https://t.co/UN0Zj94u0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complete the form below for your chance to win $2,500! The winner will be announced on Monday, March 25, 2019. https://t.co/DdcgrnpYfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious South African food at @KaiaWinebar for the Tituss Burgess wine tasting with @SouthAfrica and Heritage Tou… https://t.co/zLYNmLDFLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonreyes @DiscreetLatino @terrencemcd @Urbanmoral @TomStoelker Oh thank heavens!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@discomfiting @discomfiting  In the era of Manufacture Consent, we are at risk exposed to fake news daily.  Please… https://t.co/9kQ4hjEjgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartyCheddarCat Remember when you used to fart? I really love your green heart🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP the bulk of you oppose this! Find your FUC*ing sense of democracy and state your opposition! Stop being coward… https://t.co/pCAvSqMbYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know on days like today summer can feel like a million years away but spring break season is officially upon us!… https://t.co/84qDae2ORW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly if you put a dog in your commercial I’m 10x more likely to care]]></document><document><![CDATA[A picture is worth a thousand words  #forevermore  #familylife  #lovethisguy❤️ @ Leeds and the Thousand Islands https://t.co/NF60PWCefD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenPompeo We’re friends in real life, it’s just a secret to some, even you. But that’s ok I know we are good...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so happy at how well our new @JresRockets 🔥Lit Lunch Book Club is going. Ss split into 4 groups based on book… https://t.co/aCCTiatcuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xOBpZEH8Hm @johnlegend -Love Me Now ❤❤❤Enjoy, one of my favorite ❤❤❤To  my favorite ❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowToGetAwayABC #HTGAWM load him with that alcohol annalise 🤣🤣  Ordered Emmit a double scotch  🥃🥃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am with you Lou! I too could ride the People Mover ALL day &amp; night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woahjazzyj_ The person who took the first picture of them was holding the mirror in the second picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen is a liar, we heard over and over all day. He’s not in our government. Trump lies every day and has committed… https://t.co/nu5hKoIuud]]></document><document><![CDATA[... so later when she was leaving she found me and apologized for “getting mad at (me) earlier” so cute lol cuz I a… https://t.co/DbAQ8jwqzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estarianne @Siubhan_H @mmelgar09 @maddpig @urbanx_f @EmmaGPaley @EugeneBu @ty_the_np @mcfunny @Just4TheCause… https://t.co/jwKQQCvMCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter This was a business contract. Chiefs shouldn’t be able to cut and run without penalty. Argument #931… https://t.co/XgvFfIqXPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have the vision. Give it time to come together the way you envisioned it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bamayodc The dreadmill is seriously no fun but yay for you running outside!! It’s the best feeling ever 👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t take away uteruses or the right to procreate but we CAN terminate the privilege to be a FOSTER parent. I’… https://t.co/jWndKLjZ9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Park life. No filter necessary, just glorious sunshine and a baby on a winters day in California. #wintersun… https://t.co/c9y1E0Z4S0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maddy made wait until after the show to tweet this. “Best date night ever” https://t.co/EP152gYjQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #1 pet peeve is when my time is wasted. That’s something that really aggravates me!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha! I was having a very serious talk with Tamar and at the end I was... #funniness #chuckle #grin #absurd https://t.co/oW9g7gjPwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Eric Prince just had diarrhea of the mouth on a British show. They're all getting caught up in their lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Cubs Win!!!! 49-41!!! Way to go Coaches &amp; Ladies!! #ccchs #ccchsshowingoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fear and hatred is the epitome of ignorance. @IlhanMN  https://t.co/gd865UaVwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBryanOnline @AmericanIdol Just amazing amazing!!!  I cried!! God bless you @LukeBryanOnline you’re such a sweetheart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to these lectures by @risd’s Dr. Eric Anderson this week at @MercerYou’s McEachern Arts Center https://t.co/zo15262Lfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @safariLIVE staff! I know I am pretty new here so this has probably been done but is it possible to have an epi… https://t.co/bo55PMtg4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbiejoyhanse1 @AlyseTobler @gottogetoutof @DamosLawSP @mjnanna @Dr1ven_Ind @livingwithabuse @TheGenuineU… https://t.co/aJUYn6unnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueegg3r @srhulsman @JenP_Williams @jrussell_t @Idarite @JamieMichele6 Thank you! Excellent article with two big… https://t.co/rp3GIVJhxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gotbeeropener @TheStraightHops @badhopper @ephoustonbill @Kenny_Leaf @DRE_Go_Fish @RedStripeRocco @BPlohocky… https://t.co/OGs36jtnVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sintillaGAMES @TwitchPluto Allllright Brad. You're a pretty good dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside Army’s Cutting-Edge Research Lab That’s Helping Drive a Big Modernization Push https://t.co/ePQsoBg8Rp]]></document></documents></author>