<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Need some new shoes. Zuckerberg, do your thing and show me the pair I want on Instagram ads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher This is all bull shit. I'm not a huge fan of MJ I like some of his music. But even I say this all looks… https://t.co/9vEmLPJ4dP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delighted to see yet another #RockTheRoadRaffle sell out for @ProstateCancerC Thx to the generosity of @TADA_CA tha… https://t.co/NtDgaPmola]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatsukawa_mnm Congratulations on your 5th anniversary!㊗️🎉 Thank you for all your hard work!🤗💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t even have to ask if this cruel idea is a republican one... That seems to be they can do lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind You can't be the leader of the Free world as long as you are Nationalist so yes there is something wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My puppy just peed on one couch and jumped on to the other and finished peeing on that one 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath This is not poetry .This is part of (Stalinizm and Hitler) antyhuman mental illness. It is one step… https://t.co/sXCyCgn2Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comic_Diva @NickDragotta @tphoto10 @ThoseBackPages @kirkvanlund @cpwilsoniii @NicolaScottArt @WillPheesh… https://t.co/rBFZpj6D2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megabyte407 @pwcdanica yes, because all those non-toll roads are subsidized by the rest of the taxpayers. You aren… https://t.co/lU6GEp1eWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Orlando, FL, check out this job: https://t.co/ZenoVbjoov #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a housefull of toys and just CANNOT decide what to play with. #toomanyoptions #GermanShepherd… https://t.co/BkLO5v3MSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMcSallyAZ @vpotus You’re going to lose next year. Enjoy your time now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Till Morning Comes featuring VERBAL [m-flo] by Kumi Koda. #jpop #dancepop #rap https://t.co/62kwF1JO9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz As a Californian, I’m proud of the strides made by Kamala Harris. She is smart enough to know when to… https://t.co/p5ejeC6iAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheleSINY @maybeinerror @nickconfessore We are thinking of a YouTube video of the next tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @AOC the truth about you is being revealed. @cenkuygur I believe you are also behind this 🤔 . More people shoul… https://t.co/0UXRw1FIRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the ways I want to focus on conservation and sustainability next. Buying bread from a big box store,… https://t.co/mX7bPhZuau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol Putin's weaponized Presidential operative is successfully dismantling and weakening the pillars of Uni… https://t.co/LlsvDybB5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATregarth @CPoTLCandC @MerlinYYC @AndrewScheer It just fit so well there was no reason to question and does sum he… https://t.co/GAKwzviizH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewLipo @DeepStateExpose @AOC Ohhh gotcha! Thank you! Haha was confused for a sec there. That’s insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do dogs go to heaven? POSITIVELY SPEAKING: For the love of Maddie https://t.co/XTkqWGNJCf via @MyWebTimes… https://t.co/bRDbf3WoBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@12nighthorror You can choose either your skin back or the box of mystery...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen. That’s what every #Habs fan’s outlook should be for the rest of the season. Just enjoy the ride, because it’l… https://t.co/8LYHVCzU7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertK52431132 @rigsby_michelle @Algiz1967 @PattyJaeger @StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Mr liberal here is… https://t.co/SsMCXfYuDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray that God gives you the wisdom to know which words your child needs to hear from you, and the courage to speak them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goingin #RaptorsandChill #TheSix #MycityBetterThanYours #TorontoLife #SixSide #picoftheday #photooftheday… https://t.co/WrQNtUAKrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NitramTSG I’m the opposite, I wasn’t planning on getting it anyways, but that solidifies it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DealsDT ...but do any y'all have something that'll get rid of this...? ...when I wake up...! ...since… https://t.co/CD27YBURsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chirodale1 @TheStevenThomas @realDonaldTrump Because, he’d still be 45 you numpty. https://t.co/uGvpCFgunX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brokenguitar1 @JimmieJohnson @allyracing @TeamHendrick @DISupdates We need to get @mdowney at the track for tech support!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobynUrback So this is you valiant attempt to distill and package this so called ‘scandal’ in an inflammatory way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amante2019 Or maybe he put the panties on for you https://t.co/P3erRyt3bR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr Hey did you bring the pool boy???? You could share him with @DonaldJTrumpJr https://t.co/z5IBKgJX8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[They poured some bourbon and champagne for us as we looked at #engagementring @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/PJ531yzAtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA You should set up a page on your site to let supporters see how far we have gotten toward 65,000/200 in 20 in real time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's just that #remax life #r42019 #booj #learning #worktrips #remaxleadingedge @ RE/MAX R4 https://t.co/gva6HrQkpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[and flash blew the car it caught fire them men were trying to exit the car the flames were too much for them the en… https://t.co/z9ZQnVmt72]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MCM Sylvester... 40 years ago today "Living Proof" one of the best LIVE albums ever was recorded in San Fransisco.… https://t.co/ZlJUOJAORN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Going home this weekend really made me appreciate home and everyone there]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a tragic shame that he still thinks he can King Felix his way back into dominant form when Humble Pie and adap… https://t.co/IrfJjHpoOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liquidlaugh @Mallernee9 RBG is being held on ice until after the 2020 elections , the Democrats think they will wi… https://t.co/rInfEvXCR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cancer2Costly @fras99 I've never , ever, walked around for 10 mins looking for the remote and it was in my hand ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWCDeuce @DavidCornDC @AOC Yeah, how stupid. It’s not like the right wing is animated by irrationality and malice… https://t.co/ZGwomiMT14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TherealTaraji getting her hair braided on Sister Sister circa 1997 is a trip to see]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting the folks in OC and going to one of my old favorites across from TPC!#parents #family #TPC @ Rutabegorz Tu… https://t.co/cKaZyw6AoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Brilliant Uncertainty of the Grateful Dead’s ‘Dark Star’ https://t.co/7HlbhS66lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cansado, pero ya voy de regreso a casa. Btw, #TSAPre worked great here. 👺🤘🏼🇵🇷 (@ Chicago O'Hare International Airpo… https://t.co/3Y886fA10H]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is both amazing and strange to be sitting in a line of #Tesla EVs all sucking on @elonmusk's Free Electric Teet.… https://t.co/AUllGGKPbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to this stud! Hope it’s been a great day brotha https://t.co/7Luiuq5V59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Progressive Left she is on your team. So you MUST carry water for her and her outburst. Hope you're great a tre… https://t.co/BUM4hTaSN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see Aaron perform his #LøVë album tommorow night in Haverhill well there’s limited vip meet and gree… https://t.co/ez5cgn4cnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter @DLoesch Are you saying that when rape is inevitable, learn to accept it, &amp; maybe enjoy it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to change batteries in your smoke alarms! @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/xDlvYhpF4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aleesyab_ @SmittyLu Thank you. I was just taking 1 for the team. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/mSJGAGPOHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/H34xr0GesY | Mobile Number: (281) 925-4954 | Email:  LBROOKS@BROOKSANDDAVIS.COM  Who do you know that… https://t.co/DLwbPkbdId]]></document><document><![CDATA[From yesterday afternoon! Easy drinking and very smooth. - Drinking a Kindred Spirits by @InnisandGunnUK @ Carnegie… https://t.co/pJLWv6HXky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @TheRoasterie , there’s an Eevee in my coffee. @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/N6hfdnYien]]></document><document><![CDATA[If illegal immigrants aren’t allowed to be deported, then liberals automatically need to be deported at once!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MsDelicious   it's been awhile praying all is well...thank you for your great mystery.... https://t.co/TyUmfUqrBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting back to watching the Tribe ah so many high school memories coming back watching this show. https://t.co/dAEm1pZBYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I feel bad for you that you went raised very well by your dad. Most of us aren't raised by mobsters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2011DerrickRose @NJBall2K @BullsGotNext you gonna bench your best perimeter defender and best perimeter shooter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tropicsea88 I have heard a lot about that place from my Yorkville pals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaHFreeman A4 oh mah gersh, no way to choose. Instead, a pic of @FunInFairfax 🤣 #usgulfcoast #travel… https://t.co/HTaaFi0Cki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lightskinKelli Lol strawberry shortcake doesn’t deserve this hate either ....what has you scarred ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoriandreD 👀 👀 been interested myself. Plz share your experiences if you’re comfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday Boo’s Day . . Model @roxell_photos  . . Tee by @REBELSOULCO  . . Photographer @MikeValen  . . #mikevalenz… https://t.co/zMjREPqyH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was President’s Day a Federal holiday and the government was shutdown.  Now think 🤔 about this, the governmen… https://t.co/ydcvZYhQiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWatersSYR Louisville amd Clemson were absolutely critical. With their horrible losses on resume, have to get t… https://t.co/i3vcHGb26u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eorlins @Alyssa_Milano HI. I WATCH YOUR VIDEO (OR READ YOUR POST) AND CLICK "#LIKE" BUTTON UNDER YOUR #VIDEO IN… https://t.co/yzuJo7wOsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuAggarwall @latimes @sunderpichai @Google @marciasekhose @RakaMukherjeee @CNNnews18 @htTweets Nah.  I got fake… https://t.co/s3vsNvs7uC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You Zucc! You have been fun to watch. Hope it works out July 1 to finish as a Ranger!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I farted loudly in front of my daughter and she asked,   "What was that?"   So I explained farts to her and her res… https://t.co/zXww3bSWTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yuppp. I’m glad I got a girl like my baby mama. She hold it down for me. Shoutout to nana one time. She got all my… https://t.co/NeX5ovEoNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hanstaekwondo #taekwondobakersfield great learning experience for our kids. @ Han's Taekwondo Academy of Bakersfie… https://t.co/CvCMR6Yfj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@619_8549 @PinkNews This is an insanely specious way to push an absolutely antiscientific understanding of biology.… https://t.co/ujnLLHDEC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏽‍♂️ A @AlcaldiaCucutaa le faltó perspectiva de género, y en vez de dignificar  las mujeres hizo un show que refue… https://t.co/tevOQCLzAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SQLDBA Sorry to say but we are expecting 2-5 inches of snow in SE WI on Sunday depending on where you are going. C… https://t.co/S5rvB94szW]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my most prized possessions is my Snoopy phone my mom got me for Christmas when I was 12 years old. I’ve neve… https://t.co/XEM0Umib6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doyouwantBACON @VitalVegas No idea. But those could all just be part time....]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #securitization costs less because the debt is guaranteed (lower interest rate) and the payment is stretched ov… https://t.co/0idvv5rBvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“False facade” is redundant. One definition of facade is “a false, superficial, or artificial appearance or effect.… https://t.co/7sLMxIH6zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This funny cause the thing is most people that got the first ones will get the second there for got more money then… https://t.co/lHjasPzoc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Pistol Of Fire by @KingsOfLeon on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/bPZDJmi5TU https://t.co/tCtjry2iQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markmartin You are also the reason why my room was decked out in way to much Viagra and Pfizer stuff than a 10 year old should have at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos Días ☀️ |  Salmos 42:2  Mi alma tiene sed de Dios, del Dios vivo;¿Cuándo vendré, y me presentaré delante de… https://t.co/61VZmdbMl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉I Love Texas👈  #MayYouBeBlessedWithEnough #LoveOverHate #HateIsNotAnOption https://t.co/1S5qsiMRq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleJFalbo @garyvee That’s awesome! It’s just nice to get that random dose of encouragement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyTeenVids 🇲🇽 I WANT TO FUCK YOUR CULO ASSHOLE MEXICAN WOMAN IN THE 🇺🇸 USA! @Latina https://t.co/0FnvjLFire]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE FLOATS AND THE FUN: Our friends in Clinton did not disappoint with their #MardiGras2019 parade today! @WAFB https://t.co/cKNFr1V7eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of Qualtrics X4 Summit 2019 #ExperienceManagement event.  In a few hrs this empty keynote hall will be full o… https://t.co/GAuAhrUaZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The clippers have 0 stars and still have a winning record in the west coast. This team is underrated AF. The lakers… https://t.co/Gbs2SstQEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galloway fans, please go vote for Anthony Arrington for Freshman of the Year in Private-A. The freshman helped lead… https://t.co/JtVAkIkrXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohhmik No...I pick them up as I'm moving around my house....on the stairs..kitchen floor...even the cat room will have them sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorId_Science Yes!  I can finally be a ventriloquist.  My puppet would only be able to say one thing though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeNews alert: Don’t let @chefjoseandres fool you, @little_spain is not little. Spain is about to get very grande… https://t.co/JbS3S40ETn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In about 8 days I am rejoining the #mlpfandom again I had to take a massive break ... @ Manchester, Connecticut https://t.co/aWyGplaSza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Your fired school bus aide!! Why do they need a school bus aide what is so hard about getting on school bus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE TREK 2019  The iconic wooden light house greets us after we cross Lake Superior on the Grand Island Ice Bridge.… https://t.co/kebe3PEv2J]]></document></documents></author>