<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am no longer accepting favor requests at this time. I will call you when there is space available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philrsquared No. Been bad. Hope they give us something good next year in Tampa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamblinGrimace @PuckinHostile @TheRinkcast Generally it takes a few years. It’s pretty rare for a kid to come in and dominate from day one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google has claimed a monopoly on intent-based ads for the last decade. If Zuck has his way, we may see that shift t… https://t.co/fJDlm6pvka]]></document><document><![CDATA[7.5 magnitude earthquake strikes near Ecuador-Peru border, USGS says  https://t.co/54OfBCtHgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @DonaldBreech Lookin under every rock for greenbacks the wrong way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuarón saying he thinks this category will soon be irrelevant. Not sure I, other nominees or most in this tent woul… https://t.co/dyQQ7cxoau]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Desert #Solitude #Arizona #Trail #Hiking #saguaronationalpark https://t.co/90EQx6IGxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyn_cade @FoxyPP1 I just can’t understand the reasoning behind this socialist surge within the party for THIS elec… https://t.co/GtNmfQM8jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord Jesus Christ, You humbled Yourself and lay down Your life that I might live. May I never forget this most prec… https://t.co/doYtRjiLwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2FE8QhvZ5x  The killing of CONTEXT. Were i smarter, I could elucidate… example: (He's not the only pre… https://t.co/qdbNUI3Oir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/vRyoqvssdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯💯💯💯💯☝🏻☝🏻👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🤘🏻🤙🏻🤙🏻🤙🏻😀😀😀😀😀😀😀😀🕶🕶🕶🕶 @ Levittown, Pennsylvania https://t.co/xNsecuWWqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP Your claim tell America it is then b/c you are the racist party of no ideas and anti-environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattirwin66 @SeattleURedSea I could've gone to that game as I was like five miles away in downtown for Royals Fanf… https://t.co/9ZrG4MKT9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the #DavidFrum immigration piece causing such a stir in @TheAtlantic. The "fascists" angle is an absurd exag… https://t.co/K52SY9QEle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFP @DennisTFP Blake’s haul in the Muzzin deal looking just a tad better this morning..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bouta go take my driving test for my license, someone please tell me how you uphill/downhill park. Like the exact steps for each]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToonamiNews Gotta respect a woman who goes to the ends of the Earth to get his man back👌 https://t.co/q2Pznswj7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatJamesDean I can’t do pullups either. All you gotta do is be able to run mile and a half in 16:00 the first week… https://t.co/ND9xEXfBSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can tell it’s getting close to #GameofThrones season because the amount of people telling me I look like Ramsay B… https://t.co/egF6ZFqnC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’ll be interesting to watch the  #Suns now w/Tyler Johnson finally getting to know his teammates. Johnson is effi… https://t.co/C8PTrKHlaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennamdeangelis Good morning Jenna hope your morning is going good so far. Have a great weekend 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week when I’m home I need to eat at Jerry’s, Hank’s, Primanti’s, Burgatory, The Yard, Deluca’s, and Eat  n Park in no specific order]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSciandra Me over here without a dog in that fight: https://t.co/GBtpMi8SqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBakerMD @GHGGuru Glad you’re back! Can’t believe twitter locked you out]]></document><document><![CDATA[442.450MHz https://t.co/zPl92Udizi DMR TAC310 (at @Hardees in Newport News, VA) https://t.co/APEMgpn1Ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sounds like an episode of #Manifest If I see the #NSA #CIA #FBI or any other 3 letter organization, I’m out.… https://t.co/ryWn7xEdy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[ohmygod dating isnt just sexual attraction. dating is a legitimate relationship. if dating is just sex to you then… https://t.co/PtrdmN1uuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s 100 goals in the career of Auston Matthews so far!! @AM34 https://t.co/Q7UCxH7ml9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landonyoung30 1 meat sandwich $5 come and get it while it’s hot also do you need your house painted or equipment sandblasted]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always a pleasure to officiate the best student-athletes in the state especially when you get to do it along s… https://t.co/yM25ZIYDSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[10k en Daytona y domingo para no perder la costumbre... en Daytona Beach, Florida https://t.co/K5D5R7rnT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■  My personal Black History,  the 30th Anniversary issue of #BLACKENTERPRISEMAGAZINE ■ ■ ■  The first… https://t.co/3iCy7ipegH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_shelton @Joe_Sanfelippo - My boys!!! Wish I could hang with you two today at #ICE19!! Have a blast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s currently 1:36 am and I just bought my @SHORELINEMAFIA ticket. May 4th bouta be lit as fuck ‼️ See you MAY 4th… https://t.co/TFJJhUBejN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutlerRidgeLAZ Don’t watch news, my coaching keeps me busy. I only remember the Marlins beating the Yankees in the… https://t.co/eMs8RUCIph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s the birthday of the person I hate the most. Happy birthday though 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set 2 is up on @kickstarter now!!! Retweet it all over the place and let’s get this successful and more for… https://t.co/3nhrIDmGfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥊🦍. Trying to get like my sensei nyc_rager @ LA Fitness - SECAUCUS https://t.co/0ShU51B0QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You probably don’t want to Bill because when heart gives out😢😢😢 muscles tighten up and you will think something tot… https://t.co/gAevrpHJnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the tools you’ll need @elevenllc for Valentine&amp;#8217;s Day Cocktails to Impress That Special Someone https://t.co/SKai3Lo6KZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Edwards crossed 5K. Time 00:30:55, pace 09:57 min/mile, est. finish 9:32 am https://t.co/qxQY1jOP4Q #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait till you see the @RealMelina career video we put to This House is Not For Sale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loriniles Killing it 😎🙌 EXCELLENT video selection BTW 🤩 https://t.co/3GzElnBf4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[currently drinking a piña colada on the beach eating a mahi mahi sandwich i’m content]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassting Audition submitted online. 20th times a charm. 😁 I’m still ready. Feel free to still come to Columbus OH for open call. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Thunder have the best chance of any team in the West to beat the Warriors no doubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have a dog if you’re not going to spend time with them and take responsibility for them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinaDeLaSuerte How dare you, madam! Johnny Impact is always fantastic! #fanboy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great, encapsulated, explanation of why Design needs to go beyond Products and Experiences, to focus on O… https://t.co/9mk55wa6R9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnA_USMCvet How could they believe the Sermon on the Mount and live as they do, immodest and wasteful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowboyss12 Teams can officially negotiate with players just not official till Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Word of the Lord Is Sure... U Can Trust It No Matter What May Be Happening Jeremiah 1:12 Express Clearly That H… https://t.co/0HQBPjU7RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheerTheAnthem This must be what it felt like when Greg Millen was in goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeautyBind Comfort foods because Trump in my home would be very uncomfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are smoking rooms still a thing in accommodations? This is gross. #oklahoma #cheapest #nocamping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger fans, tonight is a huge deal! Our very own @NLCSD host Notre Dame at 7 PM. Doors open at 6, and it's most cer… https://t.co/lYMkqEexYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope. Instead Tisha put the fear of God in to me and now I’m a terrible liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to cheer on the Lincoln Lady Tigers...  STATE BOUND!! #D7 https://t.co/wQZsbszUfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hirider750 Do a Google search for Drone Shirts and you should see an Amazon link.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are already getting excited to see our member chambers and boards of trade in #Muskoka for the @OntarioCofC 2019… https://t.co/uVwRw0rKgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Humble Always No One Will Change That About Me ✔️ The #HumbleDontStumble Bank Never Changed Me Shit Peanuts @ NYC… https://t.co/TX6UqAX1HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC No one ☝️ in this administration has ever been able to speak without lying 🤥; therefore, the perjury t… https://t.co/wTwrAOHgKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#florida #crystalriver #timelapse @ Crystal River, Florida https://t.co/LoTym7GBDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dixon_drake @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/bSoyM0ODxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @jrogers01 @realDonaldTrump As usual @Markmeadows lies..The FBI opens investigations based upon pro… https://t.co/qss7vlHZ8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the assembly of another @LEGO_Group set: 70822 Unikitty’s Sweetest Friends EVER! from @TheLEGOMovie 2 (201… https://t.co/nkDLU9aSTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to all this #RKelly whining is making me fukn cry.... @KarlsonMcKenzie @wzlxnewsgirl #WZLX https://t.co/e1Qp5dxMot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo Chris, this entire issue is a joke. You and all of CNN were all about Muellers investig… https://t.co/WUh7q4qaT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchooyah But sometimes you just have to burn the house down and start again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son 200 años de historia al servicio del arte y su cultura. Museo de El Prado, Madrid, España. 🇪🇸 🎨 🖼… https://t.co/Hk1wzX80sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect sandwich. Birthday day lunch courtesy of my boo Alex Feliciano ♥️ #foodporn #sandwhichporn #12ozstudios… https://t.co/91MlozrCsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmbutts will speak to Parliament Weds AM.  What ever you think of him and @JustinTrudeau , it should be remembered… https://t.co/Re7rewEXlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Radio1045 @JammminJessie Canadian band @wintersleep played JB's a few years ago. They'd long since dropped the son… https://t.co/YYwCc7SdQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of all my fellow Veterans! Go Ladies! #Vets #Veteran #USArmy #USNavy #WomensHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s all going to @DistrktC on Saturday in NYC? I’m debating going https://t.co/6zrZ6byywD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spy some mackerel, spring is here! 🎣🐟🌼😎 #springbreak2019 #clearwaterbeach #clearwater #florida #floridafishing… https://t.co/sQB27npUBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like that the single snowday had to come yesterday and now is gone like we never had snow]]></document><document><![CDATA[As of this morning, the Alabama tornado death toll is up to 23. Join us on @wtva9news starting at 4:30 a.m. for a c… https://t.co/Ms8fVfWE1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I probably care about no other early review but this one. Thank you @benmekler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pepe1807 @kunfupanda2 @ElRigel_ @germanamilcarsi @rlizarraga13 @Roberto47994229 @AnaGabrielaGue @ramon_flores_… https://t.co/NJNtUXJWhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @AirCanada for an epic fail in @BostonLogan. I don’t need seating or space and why wouldn’t I pay $300 to… https://t.co/o6gyYTc8y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom I would argue that communication is the best way to peace! We can obliterate him and kill millions or… https://t.co/yQuci7f8M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dirtiest place in an airport is nearly impossible to avoid https://t.co/zKnnMO2L6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peel Poverty Reduction Strategy #PeelRegion @ Region of Peel https://t.co/wQb4TRLaGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assuming he gets a big bucks deal that isn’t negated by what the Eagles add in free agency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrfangmeier @DavidASterling @MNUFC @OrlandoCitySC Who did they play. OC had a fantastic pre season and then what?!… https://t.co/d4WZXJGqrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT is the official game night in the city of homes! Join me at @nathanbillsefp on Island Pond Rd for all the a… https://t.co/XUjgupGSus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DecodnLyfe Omg this is what I was talking about. Sitting on the dock of the bay. 😂 @Demthagod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some new figures my Gf got the venom figure i just bought the Carnage figure now i need a Spider-Man figure… https://t.co/NZcI9gqcXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thaddock @PaulKuharskyNFL @ClayTravis I’d assume Paul is referring to public interest in elite figures. Politician… https://t.co/I2luEphEeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We cannot accept this as normal. This is not sustainable. NJ's motto LibertyAndProsperity warns us that if we lose… https://t.co/TScNJjQcJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kissimmee bottom (West kissimmee): Hola aqui listo https://t.co/fEXoVp8uqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Santa Monica Pier https://t.co/Sd4IQ3Gksm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKlamm another Weds night! Ears are still ringing 🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/MJIj1js1CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob32456518 @g4lvanized @RyanAFournier I agree those two are idiots. They don't speak for me. They also don't repr… https://t.co/m4785HG9i2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rim it 👅 spit on it 💦 Fuck it 🍆 Fist it 👊🏻   ...And nominate this booty at this years @ProwlerAwards 🤪🍑… https://t.co/2KZma9qeaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrindstoneSEO Majestic must be *terrible* at marketing then, given Ahrefs is mostly doing the “a great product, an… https://t.co/1Z490k3Waq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what better than having an idol? Being friends with your idol 😉 Thank you @kellywearstler for having me ov… https://t.co/NCP5fZOcCo]]></document></documents></author>