<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[🚨" 'Horrible joke' about bomb in carry-on bag gets Air Canada passenger, 53, arrested, report says https://t.co/A2f5LwuN7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken: we’re fucking scary. If I saw us at the bar I wouldn’t want to come near us. 😂 https://t.co/04nCXeUXat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why wait until April to talk about #teacherleadership?  All are invited to join this #TLResearch online conversatio… https://t.co/o8OYZ6y5Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[ON CHRIST THE SOLID ROCK WE STAND ALL OTHER GROUND IS SINKING SAND.... https://t.co/QFhBZb0Wtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this afternoon’s STARTING 🖐🏽  0️⃣ C. Johnson  2️⃣0️⃣ Chastain 2️⃣1️⃣ Milton 2️⃣4️⃣ Evans  4️⃣1️⃣ Ferrell https://t.co/XrwIvzreGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am p sure I can beat everyone on va tech in around the world and it wouldn't be close #under #underrrrr #easymoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tech_Buddha @tom_karnes @Ststansberry @doctor2pi @teachsci8 @Duncannedd @EddiesClass   #csubedte4200 I didn’t get… https://t.co/aXftS1hsh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChartrDavid @Brasilmagic @ProudResister Thank You Richard, that really sums it all up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going for a business degree, I bought a blazer today and I’m just realizing that all those years of playing bus… https://t.co/kJR3CQCWnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zipppidy No one more deserving to be a grandfather to a child who is not technically his own]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️ @DickersonforS20 for sponsoring this. He deserves all the Van Halen concert tickets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the price of the wall keep raising higher and higher? Can we impeach the piece of shit now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me sick, I hate America so bad.  This man CLEARLY is no longer a threat (doubting that he ever was) to F… https://t.co/oX7K5LaBeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DJRobNice Punch me down for what lmao I don’t know that girl nor am I trying to fuss with her. Somebody need to p… https://t.co/XycKvmAjEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cutebutbrahh Hi I would recommend these 2 TS. Both are top dominant n aggressive. Tell them I recommend them for y… https://t.co/chagn9VvIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So we decided two years ago to sue the President.” —@Kckenna of @patagonia #SXSW2019   I cannot even fathom the co… https://t.co/4l12vdQaoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve heard the name “Tyson Jost” said positively many many times on Altitude tonight and I’m very happy about that ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbharrison PLEASE tell franchise to NOT select ages that young ,NO one was ready except older women .23 they a… https://t.co/YbNvtDjOEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpecialEDxx @thehill @HillTVLive That’s why I like five thirty eight. Here’s a breakdown https://t.co/fGz3pd1O1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add your name for a #FinBanNow! Tell Congress to prohibit the sale and trade of all shark fin products in the U.S. https://t.co/XOAcR0gYUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niners_nhatty @DonCheadle @Martina Doubled down on her transphobic thought process about athletes.   Said once we… https://t.co/Rdad2sC9At]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzannezeedyk @UpstartScot Magnificent! Love these pics so much. So happy you shared them! Much gratitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women’s Day is so 2018...We’re celebrating International Women’s (read: Bad Bitches) Every Day 💪🏼 @ N… https://t.co/GEUGQ28ZuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[New work on Medium  https://t.co/W6WsAMyQvG https://t.co/1GUBh2I4no  Claps requested/appreciated!!!   #medium… https://t.co/oqSpdHgsnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us Sunday 9am as we host Wolves! @graystonetavern opens 8am w/ $4 drafts all day.   #WeAreTheFamous… https://t.co/EgCIQf8LKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@18_xxxbabes @EZBiGirl @StahlKrystal @Justine351K @herby2121xxx @D87ip28cx @WobblingGoblin @Sapphire_Blue69… https://t.co/Yl9YfqEHnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PVWISTEM What a fabulous event! Here’s to more women in science.  #WomenInSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrkenanderson I want to mr.anderson my dear friend and my self a happy birthday my the lord bless us with many mor… https://t.co/EZC3MNaDpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Customers are demanding that companies understand and fulfill their diverse needs in ways that they never have bef… https://t.co/DLpvsjKK6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rutly12 @downey @TheDesmondTutu @shepilorangos @lmchinyerere @adymunyoro @jussy85 Diversity only creates division if you let it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofonroof @MaryRampellini Looking forward to seeing you both later today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home decor things #tamaroundtown (@ Marshalls in Brandon, FL) https://t.co/4lf6XB46aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff @PascoSheriff I love ❤️ great job for your friends and your family love ❤️ please thank you 😊… https://t.co/clExiGV3cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenrogers6abc Ajax celebrating National Nap Day https://t.co/iFpsvhnjSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitklyPuzzled So true. I remember the day we lost Tim Russert. It was such a sad day. He was the reason I starte… https://t.co/gr5TBLQ3gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way I reacted to this episode of #TheBachelor shows that I legitimately have a black heart! 🖤 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game-high 13 points for MND's Laila Phelia. Cougars lead 40-24 with 1:05 left in the third quarter. #cincyhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brenden swimming Fly for the last time his Senior year. 1st place Lane 3  Now onto Districts this weekend and turni… https://t.co/Q1uVKs2sQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RwandangaRegis It's 8 episodes I'm not sure if it's the full season... already watched Killing Eve👌🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an estimated discount of 60 percent, AstraZeneca still charges more than twice as much in the U.S. for Cresto… https://t.co/tAiiR6dssY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four In The Morning. Twilight Before The Crack Of Dawnin...My Favorite Time Of The Day. #HealthAndWellness… https://t.co/dJPgSCl7AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cookies and cream courtesy of thecandyshopla #420presents #newmerch #420life #musicianlife #litlounge @ The Barkley… https://t.co/SerD8KoN8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgoold Great article! Articles like this always remind me that these superheroes are actually humans and are, ofte… https://t.co/6hERHt3Z7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you’re doing today, take some time to check out the #VisibleWomen tag. There are a ton of amazing creative… https://t.co/lWVqMu7B4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the 🌈 #AllCity @LOuvertureElm @WichitaUSD259 @FineArtsUSD259 https://t.co/Oa8tcsZkaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCray's 'Thrive' initiative on track to spend $1B in 5 years https://t.co/Pj3czCVnLm via @nypmetro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Females on social media be like: Monday- Half naked picture. Tuesday- Romans 12:2 “Do not be conformed to the patterns of this world...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I told you all the things I’ve done? Would you run away from me? “Baby we all got bags of shit we don’t wan… https://t.co/rU18FsyZ6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods And a trip to the counseling office for a reality check!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL throwback to simpler times in elementary school when I wrote for EVERY WRITING PROMPT either about how “extendi… https://t.co/u3bZjMoi8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheffbx ♥️Forever I will love🤴🏽🎤#MichaelJackson I do not entertain that foolishness. They can not erase his legacy… https://t.co/4dlX2PIvSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshiepino Thank you, my point exactly. I just feel like it makes the girl question her place. But yea, like it ma… https://t.co/lzQ57bujVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success in the Stars with Celebrated Astrologer Rebecca Gordon - Episode 010 |  https://t.co/b1Cib2802F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLauter @maggieNYT @Noahbierman @ChrisMegerian So they can cover their A*ses with rebukes, full of lies! 😱😬🤥⚖️👮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very soon All Dears of #TWBDimash will see him on TV screen and hear his beloved voice again at #WorldsBest !!! For… https://t.co/NrBLyRVqfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper @marcosanchezorg The reason i say that is because I remember which episode it came from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@showupforthis Reese Witherspoon kicks the bad guy with her tiny little self in some badass heels while Sondheim and I hide]]></document><document><![CDATA[What gives anyone the right to say I am not the only negative holder? The alien agenda man when he got angry even a… https://t.co/iistnCEbhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs a night out once in a while #catch #aria #butterfly #flowers #lasvegas #nightout @ Catch Vegas at AR… https://t.co/tleZT33ygk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg @MichaelKoman @BTuckertime @kenanthompson @nbcsnl @idriselba Loved it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our FIHS Boy’s Basketball Team on their historic season!   Link attached for the entire album of… https://t.co/w1wHz69uny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Run to catch the @METROHouston train this morning.The guy driving saw me tap my phone(card is in the phone case)Nex… https://t.co/AeLWomKBjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I saw a fox playing w/a dog toy on social media I set up an experiment in my own backyard. "Will my backyard F… https://t.co/nzk7kKjkmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FedEx She is the best thing that could happen to republicans... we must use it]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPIEST BIRTHDAY TO MY MOTHER ❤️ LOVE YOU TO PLUTO AND BACK 🌚 https://t.co/r1dPlY4GgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take the stick out of my corn dog before ever taking a bite. After I get started, there isn’t time to worry about that dumb stick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is so good!!!! After a month of uncertainty God answered my prayer today. Trust his timing💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind warnings are currently in place for much of Southern Ontario. Damaging wind gusts near 100 km/h may cause powe… https://t.co/fcdJBrQD1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to be me but it will be bc I have no self control https://t.co/Us5gVXe7Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The difference between you and I is that everyone loves you but nobody genuinely likes you. Not everyone may like m… https://t.co/OGOci0NpzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronthorp @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @wikileaks Why because he is a traitor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Creative Labs is starting a Wellness Wednesday series featuring a different class/teacher bi-weekly. Come suppo… https://t.co/MrRe0UTodD]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 Oh Donna, oh Donna 🎶 This Ritchie Valens song has been in my head since working on this sign! #artbysarahsavage @… https://t.co/ntbdHYReit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsStephGuzman @StephanieLinTV @cerretanews @CortKlopping @JuliaYSpeaks Every time I hear the name Stephanie, I thi… https://t.co/vWLrJWUUPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love a 💋 day @caitrionambalfe  Styling @karla_welch  Hair @Marcusrfrancis  Makeup by me 💋 welovecoco Chanel Le roug… https://t.co/2jYliw48vy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrinceZuko85 I love Bill Nighy and Shakespeare Head pub!!!! In Soho...]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I have the fear of failure it leads me in two different ways  1) perform ..... or 2) paralyzed   One leads me… https://t.co/kNZPmnEkYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleychestrman Visit Slovenia, llubliana, you won't regret it, and they serve in English. Great restaurants!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you clean your sink with toilet bowl cleaner?  Sure, I just did 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m watching a new X-Men prequel w/ a way better soundtrack. #TheUmbrellaAcademy⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orange you glad today’s Friday?! 🍊 Y’all have been asking for my secret to glowing skin... I’ve been testing this h… https://t.co/5B3ddVX3Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round of 16 produces the best games of the season, don’t @ me #ChampionsLeague]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating @DublinPD148’s half-birthday (which isn’t exactly half but oh well). Instead of cake he gets steak! https://t.co/ntEwufCwkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Movability @DowntownATXInfo Any possibility of rolling out on social media for those who are unable to get there in person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok i thought about what i said. I should’ve said “certain black men at CNU” instead of “football team and basketbal… https://t.co/0qm1lNDVTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @realDonaldTrump Dumpty is a Dictator A$$ kisser https://t.co/aZxxR3q0rS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Traditions in schools are great, but sometimes they need a little shaking up. Losing control can be good thing, es… https://t.co/u3yGHlGO4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch "Growing the 'Idea Garden' at college" on https://t.co/yeiKKVK9ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just smile. 😌🦄  #love #lovethesun #sunshine #sunnyday #sun #picoftheday #photooftheday #loveit #me #unicorn… https://t.co/8mg9n0tXUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonMike85 @FeitsBarstool 1000%. Petty Crocker over there can’t get over the fact he broke up with her 10 years ago 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Managing to speak at a conference, moderate a session, and see 6 baseball games + behind the scenes at chase field… https://t.co/OiTAjdSoYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to presenting with Dr Young Thursday at Medicine Grand Rounds ‘Glucose Monitoring in Type 2 Diabete… https://t.co/pSav7JBaoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro i was trynna figure out why traffic so bad on 45 and this the friday before spring break.... 💀 fucking wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take care of ppl kids all year around and don’t never have a child to claim 🙄 yes I’m salty as fuck 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4oceanBracelets buy one and remove a pound of garbage from the oceans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakWilmot @hypepotamus You bet. I will always be a big fan. #LaCamila is one of my fav experiences. #VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OurRev305 @WhirlwindWisdom @XPerezNY @Vegan4Bernie @BernieSanders I bet Bernie's in better shape than Agent Orange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grandma's so happy #littleartists #easel #crayons #learntopaint #learntodraw @ Rockport, Maine https://t.co/OyrQJydDhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clabbergirl We ad green food coloring to our scratch made biscuits and gravy on St . Patrick’s Day . It’s a fun wa… https://t.co/f782Oly69W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdyplumber @richard4127 @tripprrr @Richard65049965 @onearmmofo @deafheaven Yahhzz and Yahhzz again for Y'all Pee… https://t.co/GWYbnEhYO1]]></document></documents></author>