<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@naptimedoe Peace. I'm going to call you in the morning. Was dealing with some thangs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meakoopa And now you’re quoting Mrs Dalloway?!? Is it possible to propose to someone over Twitter?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad TV was one of those shows were you suffer through like 100 bad skits to get to one good one, but when it’s good it hits so fucking hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any guys want a few more SSL hours. Concessions will be open until 4pm. Any help is appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mind the rain but it’s getting harder and harder to keep the piano in my back yard dry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why #ottcity need to ban parking during winter on bus routes  - period #PublicTransportation #commuterlife… https://t.co/zZiji13vIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched the last couple minutes and it had my heart racing. SO glad Romeo drove to the basket this time instead of… https://t.co/WDQ0mU4Co0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enriquecidos con el sudor de otros, abuzándose con la necesidad del pueblo imponiendo razonamientos de comida, traf… https://t.co/DmStkhd1S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkyolinEnglish This is a few years old now, but here is a two day event exploring a number of aspects of these que… https://t.co/uFPMdaOAOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non-black people still use the N word like it’s cute? I thought it was 2019 not the 1940’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 For whatever was written in former days was written for our instruction, that through endurance and through the e… https://t.co/bUMxuYzsnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Momo challenge is really scary and Honestly I never wanna bring children into this world if people are going t… https://t.co/HufnOLKM83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's explore this world. I'm live on Twitch - Watch me at https://t.co/NSuEeEZWHR @VGVanguards #VideoGameVanguards… https://t.co/IHAoIv2f8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[World-class literary-philosophical NOVELIST SEEKS AGENT for ATHANASIA, 112K words of lyrical originality re the Mar… https://t.co/Ma3W7bzYR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so fucked up.   15 year old Black kid w/no record steals $100 sneakers: •5 years prison  Wealthy white man… https://t.co/fgSazPMwoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no hope in shallow pride or grand speeches. Only in Christ crucified, risen and victorious.   I will not d… https://t.co/6aq3sxwvW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNPDNashville Have a good night MNPD officers. https://t.co/RNFYdrSo2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCortex2020 @KamalaHarris Alex, how would you feel if you or a loved one were a victim of crime? Would you want t… https://t.co/FMa5iT0ooC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are open today from 10 to 1 pm.  417 Foster St. . . . #durham #duke #durhamnc #bullcity #huntstmarket #crafts… https://t.co/mSWlTriEub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noon Monday at The City County Building. #Pittsburgh #FakeTrumpEmergency   Crisis response-events https://t.co/WuvIqrv6bB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeStanton2012 @leagueofcities @BeegleME Hahaha. Would love to see the model they used to calculate the greeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AVENAoficial @LeandroTrajano8 @CarlosBolsonaro 🔺🔺AJANHE A FRATERNIDADE DE ILLUMINATI OBTENHA DINHEIRO. FAMA DE POD… https://t.co/RV9RxQ0mAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@72infidel @jax_persists I like letting them know I'm ugly up front. As far as getting doxed I'm not too concerned… https://t.co/FnMT9To6Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in next week for double the trouble when thenoneofourbusinesspodcast brings in parkimedes_310 and darnellsaki… https://t.co/G2Ouel8XlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes they are the best breed if dogs they can't that go full on to protect there owners..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying real hard to stay away here but I just love these two too much. 10/10 maesters would watch this vi… https://t.co/eTXCAjM6La]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisS2384 @_antoinesampah @TarN8tion LT was a DE at UNC, hence the #98.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda getting used to keyboard and mouse just can’t build all as good as I can on controller yet 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShatterverseEnt @GarretWATO Liberties is one thing...turning a mob-boss/ kingpin into an *actual* birdman that spe… https://t.co/lsDugSXQNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@switttch people in jail right now cause they cared about jordans too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulargenti Should @BoeingAirplanes comment now or await further actions from the FAA? Corporate Communication #tuckmhcds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Monday world stay frosty @ United States Space Force https://t.co/97G3YPrPwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigtengeek Jason Kidd's defense meeting Brad Underwood's defense: https://t.co/dm303pz3SR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao the #Raiders can’t even abandon their own city right. https://t.co/LnTnMbSJGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the looks of Twitter, I am glad I did not watch the game. https://t.co/bt4xKSNIr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[harry potter was 15 months old when he survived the killing curse and became the chosen one to defeat lord voldemort]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've learned so much about law since individual-1. Watching you and all the other lawyers on MSN BC. Thanks for the… https://t.co/dkn7pCcQ7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d GEE LOOK AT WHO  YOU ARE SLEEPING WITH - MISS ALTERNATE FACTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachStevens94 @coachbalash This is AWESOME! A polar bear D-Line! https://t.co/gdYI2qNmw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who requested the meetings to discuss removing @realDonaldTrump?  I believe this could be considered a treasonous a… https://t.co/1BIgFPHkpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @NWSL and @ORLPride,  There is still time to schedule that double header away trip (with the men's team) to… https://t.co/gVxqiGxDBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneTh36520387 @TheTalkCBS @sherylunderwood Put proof of your opinion on the table for the rest of us to see. Or… https://t.co/yznGIxtTJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adbridgeforth It was useless because he wasn’t chairing the meeting. If Gowdy really thought the hearing was a was… https://t.co/um2LEHODXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[True. Jimmy's Bryan has been heralded by Korea and Japan since forever ago. The legend of Mr. Naps is not new.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New twitter bio:  GA ✈️ IL ✈️ NY ✈️ CA ✈️ NJ ✈️ AZ ✈️ IL ✈️ TX ✈️ WA ✈️ VA ✈️ IL ✈️ IL ✈️ KS ✈️ CO ✈️ NM ✈️ Europe ✈️ DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Ok. ¿Y la respuesta es sacarnos mediate ataques quirúrgicos de bombardeo de Tuits y marchas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseyABC13 @abc13houston @StevenABC13 @SamicaKnight13 @ABC13Elita @KatherineMABC13  @TJParkerABC13… https://t.co/M8PcCc3jAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[But that’s the thing as black girls. To be models we have to be overly pretty, overly graceful...while white girls… https://t.co/J6Fvdk4HaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're at #MWC19 check out the @Vuforia+#HoloLens2 demo at the @Microsoft booth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpTicDi3seL I feel that way about everyone except Wraith and Bangalore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I dropped @jessica_r6s off and put the wrong address In my Uber dude hahah. I’m at 100$ plus Uber 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MCM #ManCrushMonday  ...except it’s just me, already crushed  under the weight of this week’s responsibilities]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these things is not like the other, one more to go... Excited to try out these Delta 12LFC speakers in the H… https://t.co/fynXltRRux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q. 36. What is that sinful nature which we inherit from Adam called? A. Original sin.  Q. 37. What does every sin d… https://t.co/1t69RbK3tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@max_rontgen @RightGlockMom @MaxBlumenthal @SenSanders OMG this B.S. article is where you get your Venezuela news f… https://t.co/Id1VGidgC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalAbsintheDay #LaVeeVerte #TheGreenFairy #HenriMarieRaymonddeToulouseLautrecMonfa @JohnLeguizamo… https://t.co/y9tPCNE8IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCAskelson That’s what’s going to happen. They’re going to lose their fan base.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gentlemens_cove @souljaswank @E_Santiago29 @TDLockett12 @young_choppo Those families did not have restrictions in… https://t.co/wY8d1tHKbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got plans to meet up with this guy in a couple days and buy some prayerbooks off him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kweidleman @tammy @jtramsay Example we have a very large gated  golf, tennis and yacht club community.  (We are a… https://t.co/qHzKLCxtX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-dawn recovery #run 🏃💨 up some hills around the neighborhood. It’s nice and clear here in #la but cold.… https://t.co/PqWT1pAu8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wikileaks He is not detained and can walk out from the embassy and let himself be extradited to Sweden.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roosevelt Corner CA Mon Mar 11th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Rain Lo 46 TUESDAY Chance Of Rain Hi 66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhoenixMcginnis @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/0UpoPJmm3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[No school today? Time for racing school! @simcraft for some laps on a rainy day. #startemyoung @ Marietta, Georgia https://t.co/nYtcYUzuvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really some actors, my young boul will move you. https://t.co/sjzqp0cu0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrackerBarrel so we came to be early to beat the crowd, unfortunately w/ only 3 servers was the reason we have to… https://t.co/jOoG5yajDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this team of mine and the hint of summer we got in the Magic City! @ University of Miami https://t.co/ZALdSeVNwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephillyt She’s queen detective agent know every damn thing. Trust me, I’m sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just had a wonderful and encouraging time with Mr Monte and Mrs Carol visiting from Columbus, In. We have grown… https://t.co/Wbr1Td7MFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:18 4th  Western 38  Northwest 24  16-4 run for the Indians over the last 5 minutes and change. It's not been an i… https://t.co/gieoq7JSpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @SamiParkerxxx @GValentinaxxx @HeyyGianna @PristineEdgexxx @Daphneklyde3 @alyceandersonxx @realchloeamour… https://t.co/jGR6afHii3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen too many Jim Boeheim jokes this morning. Not at all the time to make light of a situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be that weekend rebel. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/saVuXo9Nd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A weird power trio that’s playing kissonline covers tomorrow!!! @REJASFROMTEJAS @kyngpepe @AndreTheVirus are at tom… https://t.co/2JvMqG4yiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @realDonaldTrump Kim didn't know about Warmbier, any more than you didn't know about hush money payoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What X-Men movies are he talking about, someone dies in almost every X-Men movie Simon?? Like the only movies he co… https://t.co/kSdM1QaVpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-Dopted @ $54  #sold #bolo #nike #ShotPut #nikerival #shoes #urbanpicker #helferstay @ Maryland Heights, Missouri https://t.co/kx2ulYULhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WOW....revaluations by McCabe.....SHOCKING CORRUPT potus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoundOFF13 @MurphyKeith @GaryDolphin And Murph my friend this is the reason you're the bomb.  Thank you for going to bat for Dolph.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdixon019 @ForzaCorrado @TonyBrunoShow @Chuckles152 Hahaha yes so true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADDerWORLD I wrote a haiku about @HopeHicks44 titled Hopeless Hicks, finished #Haiku @Scara_Muccier #amwriting… https://t.co/2oYA3MJaCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #Houston #Astros team, 1965 -2016, pitchers.  https://t.co/rymANcFuI8 … https://t.co/mYZvGIEXOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome basketball game.  Congratulations to the Bradley County Bearettes for winning the state AAA basketball cham… https://t.co/wiOarb89CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2019 NBA All-Star Game had the Queen City buzzing and this guy cheesing. @ Spectrum Center https://t.co/J3lorqmDI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight made me realize why I love my school as much as I do. Endlessly thankful for my friends, family, peers, and… https://t.co/cmOEqz2FB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can a young person stay on the path of purity? By living according to your word. I seek you with all my heart;… https://t.co/pPFm1cDSH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which means the XFL or AAF team could possibly have the number one pick in the draft. I like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPSManJohn @UPSsafetyguy74 @RDWillsUPS @DempseyBarbara1 @DJEJZ Nice job]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayFeeling “What the world needs now is love sweet love” DW @scotttriggers loves this artist. @graysheartart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaSimi Hi there, I just followed u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberSM7 To the same reward that the next does. But in addiction, with rewards that work for that person, yes ther… https://t.co/wEfHRfqPxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhllauren @amandacstein @ChrisRyan_NJ @NJDevils @hughweber1 60 day LBI and in Federal Witness Protection Program.… https://t.co/VStj05lEhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If bacon and biscuits and gravy aren't in your top 10 then your point can never be achieved]]></document><document><![CDATA[FBF. Im the one all the way to the right. Youngest of 4. The Mishaan boys. Still going strong. Bogota Colombia must… https://t.co/mUoX0aRTJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifewithshar @gentlemanvet67 @dansedelamort I once was with a chick who had a mouse tail tattoo from just above he… https://t.co/xzKS8lu8X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome day at Florida State! Thank you for the invite🍢#tribe2020 @BrockWillis @WoodstockFtball https://t.co/yPXb4p1Ytl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travis Dermott is in serious pain after a hit from Brad Malone. Looks like he jammed his wrist upon landing. https://t.co/CH5eluaqpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. King criticizes the bill for being “rushed,” says they did not take the time to educate the public like they’r… https://t.co/U3fm6bYPXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mario_chan98 Those are the true beautiful females. Not the ones who are mean &amp; pretty.]]></document></documents></author>