<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@pcrowl I can relate! . Hope you got some sleep. 🤓 https://t.co/aUZrFM80of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drobsidian @WillGuzzardi @fox32news @AP @APOConnor Yes, it’s a min-wage bill. Not a living wage bill. That’s beyond Dem’s imagination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe they should call it Wreckxit or Breakxit? I wish they could abandon it before it blows up in their face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrittanyxoxo @MilffsPorn Brittany your boobs are some of the greatest on the planet. Bar none. Hun your body an… https://t.co/IBnychLHvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@banaianshow Should be interesting to see where the Amazon facility ends up, if it ends up anywhere. My guess is th… https://t.co/ux7r0GiFki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFANmornings is the MJ prescribed? Or, does it matter? Many pro athletes use MJ as do commoners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a plane ride over the Old Inlet Wilderness Breach, created by superstorm Sandy - Photos and Video:  2-14-19 -… https://t.co/oXWWRjdIp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great arm workout tonight 💪🏼 .  Starting to get some good strength and size back. @ LVAC https://t.co/1WDYFMXhub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asalciunas975 @jasonmyrt I was in the park when David Bell hit for the cycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gongalery Y tu que haces para hacerte pasar por  mexicano Español de mierda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RasDeELA It is comical that you are attempting to get under my skin, but I don’t take this stuff personal. I enjoy… https://t.co/4rl649YKSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really, REALLY hope that Brie Larson surprises me and is amazing as #CaptainMarvel because I’m definitely not a f… https://t.co/OtR19qrgF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_nasty02 @SiddaXe @DanyAllstar15 What an embarrassingly bad tweet...yep the team with the best record should defi… https://t.co/YH2GerL2Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house as Metrolinx hosts first exec panel outside of Toronto.  @GOtransit is so important to the community, an… https://t.co/TvidMgsLPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itsyab0y04 @Catfatmatty @gabrielmalor Don't hurt the poor Trumper with facts. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_WordSmiff_ Lmaoo yo put me on bro. I dead never payed that chick any mind other than that sex tape. Why everyone… https://t.co/3O4imKz4hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best time of my life co-writing and recording my next single // I cannot wait for you all to hear it // I’v… https://t.co/REOwl0YKPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Stephen A’s defense, it’s *really* hard to know what a team’s road record is when you’ve only seen them play 3 t… https://t.co/gBqDqSG4oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews But we don’t need a wall? It’s an immorality?? This falls squarely on the shoulders of democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VistaEarth yeah, well, it sorta misses out as a fantasy 'cause why is a gorgeous gal like that alone? what is wron… https://t.co/9EYS3aVUtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevincanuhearme I simply spared @TheJonasKnox and his listeners. It was a favor. A thoughtful act, really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/fUrna252ER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idea_cloudd @jgeorge64 @Jachcamo @HughPhartud @Mulmack @60Minutes Hahaha!! If this was Obama's economy you'd be praising him...stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Take Me Home by Phil Collins. https://t.co/DREKN9gbc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @RandyOrton @TrueKofi @WWEDanielBryan Xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx xxxxxxxxxxxxlxxxklxxxxxxxxxxxxxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryHedgecock23 @VincentGuliani @TheFast49 Yeah we were talking about Richards car the other night but his skirt l… https://t.co/KbiAN1PrVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMalina @FoxNews In his defense, the customer did ask him to "pass the salt".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneHelmsCom Tell @The305MVP that his name is Billy Batson and he met a Wizard named Shazam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeitgeistFilm @AbbyMartin @LeeCamp @AJENews @RT_America @theintercept @AlterNet @FoxNews @CNN @marcorubio… https://t.co/0Znmpt6Ebq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xotonironixo @JossTheGuy2 I think so too that Iris gets pregnant with twins while this current version of Nora sacrifices herself]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team is so offensively challenged, it’s insane and it all starts with Payton Pritchard. He needs to be coming… https://t.co/lTMcHUB48j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house! thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TsavaniB  @Natsufoxu  are you guys going friday to @MidwestFurBowl ? Hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The plot thickens. These are the two brothers that are “suspects” in the Jussie Smollett attack. It has been confir… https://t.co/cCwarRAkmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jo12538172 @america_12_conf @KamalaHarris @jocowboys87 Bad? No. There is now word for what this is. There is for h… https://t.co/ClJXZPs33w]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 of 5 Happy Friyayyyyy (at @NewsCorp Building in New York, NY) https://t.co/vOYShWG4LW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Uphill crossed 5K. Time 00:51:57, pace 16:44 min/mile, est. finish 9:35 am https://t.co/IvfMKvfWxI #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthoeppner I’m guessing it’s because the players like them. Also, what’s their record wearing them? Possible superstition, I suppose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My music changes so drastic like i could be listening to some heavy ass dub then boom trance, then house, and on an… https://t.co/f3L6CwOgpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yyzsportsmedia @MapleLeafs Can’t wait to see the answers for this one in your mentions. I’ll turn up my sarcasm filter on this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepizzasnob13 Good shows. I actually saw them at Bemidji State back in 82 when I was a student there and I use student very loosley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @timmackie, recently I was listening to one of your podcasts about heavenly beings. I was wondering if the rela… https://t.co/OSBjQLgXpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You done shocked the hell out of her with that needle she done come back to life” will ALWAYS send me]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am board at work I make slow motion videos of coffee making 😂 https://t.co/zOdA7IMIQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonaldsCanada Would you ever consider bringing back the Shamrock Shake made with lime? Those were so good! 😋 ☘️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well the new humane mousetraps work great. In other news: we still gots mices! #mice #vermin #mousetraps… https://t.co/lkCe0wIEQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCCOLowery Did you make out with any of them by the lake after lights out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful images and stories at today's protect Minnesota day on the Hill. Seventeen outlines on the rotunda floor r… https://t.co/hlMZbwZ95q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Who's your writer MANAFORD or STONE , YOU SHOULD get some prison time for letting these 2 criminal tras… https://t.co/N3VR4akreB]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Cause she’s still preoccupied with 19... 19... 1995!  @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios @brielarson @Kevfeige… https://t.co/TIfU9UImFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank Christ for our awesome gun laws so the infestation of neo nazis and white supremacists can buy their arsenals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 Lessons Learned From Cycling Across The United States https://t.co/KgzI2SO8vW via @buzzfeeders great read about… https://t.co/ZbgSoT4IXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobGregoryGC @brandon29us Wofford is definitely legit.  No argument on that one.  One of 7-8 quality losses for us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcuskelson @CBSNews @slsandpet That’s why they lose!!! Democrats could say let’s kill babies and they all agree 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebluejaysfan Sure did. They are going with KCP and Wagner in the starting lineup tonight.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite evidence of this is when I made her mad the other day and in a fit of rage she looked my right in the e… https://t.co/wn7hCFt0de]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope he wins.  Man sues women who allegedly called police over his 'gardening while black' https://t.co/aPGAjrin5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah don’t really have any excuse not to be my best self today. I’m inspired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveSchreiber3 @Karenbeals5 @sianetta @ADeSenze @Prosperous1776 @SURGDissection @luluHru @PushBack4Trump… https://t.co/3eiyBVhkJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keynote teaching tomorrow. It's been a while since I've spoken on this subject. I'm practicing tonight.… https://t.co/nPEsTV7aNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michsports9 It’s considered a measure of explosiveness and lower-body strength]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuff said @ The Mcdermott Athletic Center - The MAC https://t.co/eXwefgv6Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidRutz @jo_USA_ @AOC If you think about it...in the 40’s we had the red scare.  Now we have socialist and commu… https://t.co/T40wUydj2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhoebeFossil @jflier Gambling the fate of human civilization on hail mary technology in lieu of recingizing the ne… https://t.co/ijANNKtsyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When certain people are in the company of certain people they act like they don’t know you!? I know that’s that fake shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungBoselli I’m not talking about a food court and a country bar under a clunky orange roof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyHarr80861813 @SenMcSallyAZ Because you are a crazy person the military probally removed you for being crazy.  W… https://t.co/IuE2F9OY2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Here's to fulfilling your contract &amp; many more!  Positive thoughts!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, love to ride a #TTC bus when the driver is so rapt in conversation with a friend that he misses stops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we really live in a world with honest government transparency? How can we claim to be living in a democracy when… https://t.co/AR8FSVU8F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamAliSports @HAHA_Hockey @barstoolsports They have 6.5 million followers on Instagram... What are they then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking my favorite moment from #CapitanMarvel. @AgentM @jamiefrevele you’ve got to be Flerken kidding me, the whol… https://t.co/m8HXOq2k9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, but I can't get over how funny this is. This is why I love... https://t.co/myaHMLCbpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe she said “I’ve been doing this for 30 years” We should be encouraging the activism these children dis… https://t.co/WDHYEIkTSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This really some fucken work frfr 💯 @pnbrock put this jawn on ya album 🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimbal Interesting now I'll have to check him out. This is my first time hearing about him, thank you for the post.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leadershipmuse @vsnisbet Thanks Holly. Hope you’re having a wonderful day and hope you have a wonderful week!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A championship built must feel a lot different than a championship bought.  built&gt;bought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianapordios Yo no me preocuparía mucho de lo que la gente te diga. Es tu pensamiento uso estás segura que lo qu… https://t.co/NE0SQ7ZGAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit She not doing anything wrong, Americans have all kinds of race hung ups and white complexes, some th… https://t.co/TYCQMPxVb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine having the best wide receivers in the league on the same team.  👀⚜️ @AB84 @Saints]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dashawns2cents @WeAreGloryPro Enjoy.  That was a top notch show.  Really fun stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookehazexoxo #MyFantasy #BonerInspiring #Goddess #Perfection #DreamCumTrue #DreamWoman]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@G1LYARD on the resiliency of this @SpiderMBB team, “You guys can just see it. This is the best team in our confer… https://t.co/S7sWQsKP3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora E.U. necesita de México para tumbar a @NicolasMaduro pero @lopezobrador_ no va a traicionar a nuestros herman… https://t.co/LOPRP59O5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pknganameishard @Ironhorse76 @Zekedoggie ha! Thanks!!!  It's a small step but we have to keep doing what we can to protect the ocean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so crazy how no matter when I got whooped this thought never crossed my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starlasworld "Some 40% of sex workers reported suicidal ideation in the year preceding the study.... The prevalenc… https://t.co/JLFyasmK7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WJCaruso @L_DiPaolo Not even you could credibly accuse me of ever saying that, Bill :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our idea of a snow day? Working on a super cool new project for @tcbmag that I can’t wait to share very soon. Not o… https://t.co/eH807Jx7eS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearty group of 31 headed to Sub District FFA contest in Ankeny. #NationalFFAWeek #FFAJustOne #fullslate @SEPolkRams https://t.co/6I3HPm2xEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diego26diego86 @JoselineKellyx @DreddXXX @JulesJordan I dont know what it is but she looks really good in that out… https://t.co/MOlI8xoTmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileyjer It usually takes a bit longer to reach elite status in your own mind but she obviously peaks earlier tha… https://t.co/R970PIZDKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cult Take @PeteButtigieg looks like a young Joe Clark https://t.co/zHQ2BwflCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xvolaura @spaceywaycee Warms my heart whenever I see Avicii’s name. 😓🥺💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @AOC AOC is the Republicans secret weapon. Don’t tell the Dems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagniFieri @Duchessmontagu @RollingStone The @RollingStone mag IMO has become a political hack crap rag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no, not again 🙄 Bernie Sanders announces his 2020 presidential run  https://t.co/k7cM3B587z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeillBlomkamp I was taken. Went in cynical thinking Scott was outside his wheelhouse but holy shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Valentines Day gift to is what you all have been asking for 🥶‼️  JUMANJI: APOCALYPSE ‼️ General Tickets are goi… https://t.co/FPqLm11HCu]]></document></documents></author>