<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Nathansg41 O sea son super lindas y las amo pero que mala onda☹️ es que si soy muy molesta cuando veo mis películas favoritas jiji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illegal Alien Accused Of Murdering Mollie Tibbetts Requests Hispanic Majority Jury Pool https://t.co/Suk2CDx6MJ. Illegal doesn’t 2 pick jury]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um dia abençoado por aqui!! #disneycruise #bahamas #disneycastawaycay #vacations #carnaval2019 em Castaway Cay https://t.co/G01QYJRDMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kybelle1957Liz @EnragedApostate @cspanwj Maybe it wasn't the Honey...but it makes sense...I'm just glad they are almost gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Central #TX we see the same statistics - the achievement gap begins before Kindergarten. Investing in high quali… https://t.co/uPSE9IA9GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ SAVE ME  Brixx @tohanimals is 5-years-old and was surrendered to t… https://t.co/z6lJZHjz5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nihaoteeks Apparently one of T.I.'s friends pee'd on him and he didn't do anything. The 2nd part I never heard about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moodring89 @BritTaeBoo89 @lustrationsy Still working on it, about half way though so, very close to finished.  It… https://t.co/xGq2QHlUGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my free chance to win $100 in points. Tons of wins here! https://t.co/SIbFffJgZS #instantwingame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comey I learned that you earned a lot of money helping the banks who were helping the Cartel hide their money. I'm… https://t.co/7tQMxuLXYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a blessing when you find someone who helps you work to turn your weaknesses into strengths. Build and grow together!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cammy44427180 I have a fat story to tell you both but i’m too exhausted to do so right now lmao 🤣 I’m going to bed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the rain dripping from your house sounds like the dog licking itself AGAIN...  #StopIt #StopLicking… https://t.co/ySVLV41AZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asdrubalivan Asdrubal, te comprendo tus sentimientos de rabia e impotencia ante lo que nos sucede, pero no estas s… https://t.co/hHXbYt1Uzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweating out the week. @yogaworks #werk #yogaworks #yoga #yogini  . . . . . . @fitbit @carbon38 @ YogaWorks Soho https://t.co/ZhbXAnGKTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally migrated my iOS Cocoapods library to Swift 4.2! It will help you easily collapse table view sections on new… https://t.co/owcgzGUOXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting SNS has been the best decision I’ve ever made, my nails are growing so fast 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many acts of cruelty that I sort of knew to expect even before starting med school, but I didn’t even… https://t.co/dHlvF6clGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryBellerud I think I pulled that move on @tonybina31 a few times in practice! #LLTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Trip H pretty real there, had my attention, Love seeing that side if him #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Exactly. Crazy. #DitchMitch #TrumpCrimeSyndicate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @NBCNews He’s on the wrong side of history—not that he appears to know any.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForTennessee @TrueEyeTheSpy Maybe no one is supposed to go after anyone of import.  All a charade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aponte1801 @ricardorossello El unico que le puede ganar al gobernador es un estadista HARDCORE que coma fuego y ve… https://t.co/YJ8mMt4dMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My main man! 💕😁 #singlemomstrong #singlemomsrock #purelove #myrock #adventuresofjaxonoliver @ Virginia Beach, Virgi… https://t.co/vX7AzwZHGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliemason @katmar_bro Just never liked the taste. One time at Yankee Stadium I had beer I liked. It was a pretty hot night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recuerdo mi infancia,ir al pequeño pueblo de mi familia con mi papá y pasar por un lado de El Palito y planta centr… https://t.co/5ot60JwPgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenLongg Yeah if you have to wait that long you were probably quoted a long ass wait time in the first place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! Don’t miss Daybreak Duos at 6:50 am. It’s our V-Day game show with lots of surprises and lau… https://t.co/z85JdYjvfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grannyanon1969 @GodFirstGina @misspunk63 @tweets4poppy @Girl8Liberty @AsiaTater @garway95 @dfalls1552 @derp_dood… https://t.co/a4ySFEmKVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoratiousPowell @CrystalBeebe3 @Madonna @dubstarr73 @MEDUSAS_BROTHER @Sheena_655321 @YantisaJ @JamesTConleyII… https://t.co/adDgBm5Lsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy @adamcbest So it’s ok for Cuomo to work there but not the republican?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhMyMithrandir Reviewer can’t even spell Gemma Chan’s name correctly, smh. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Bastion29 already has me making his doctor appointments for him. Guess this is what being a wife is all about, f… https://t.co/he8xD55LZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate folding clothes, but I also hate wrinkly clothes so my solution is that I’m gonna wear wrinkly clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjartisC2C I dont wanna share the link til I fully stock up, but I'll send it to you as soon as that's done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out! This is Flint Creek near the boating entrance in Between Decatur and Hartselle. @morgancoema says m… https://t.co/ZAYR1x7TBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kickcancersass #acsgalaofhope it’s for a cure. @ Chateau Luxe https://t.co/icHgix8jbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[For our family’s superhero Josh 💚💗💙❤️ #cureduchenne #RareDiseaseDay https://t.co/PU26PJTj2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTweetsOfMP Why not? Go when we go..... Will have fun Eric and I can show you around. @eric67c10]]></document><document><![CDATA[historias de sus niños con canciones de maroon five... denme un tiro 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @gscherzinger52 People have forgotten that churches started the first schools in America!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been in @Disneyland for less that 5 minutes and have already spotted my first flock of ducklings!!! https://t.co/KmQSzmQWzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to support my kids Girl Scout troop, we will be set up at @BriarPatchBooks today from 11-1 hustling cookies! $4 a box!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debratankersle1 @RoadtripC @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie… https://t.co/jdf0VOrTmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayezyee i still am stacking that ain’t gone ever stop besides that was a month ago🙃 im waiting on my bday tho to g… https://t.co/3kDX9aPhDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[im supposed to half one of my pills but i was too lazy to break it so i took it whole and um big miss steak !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It brings me back to Oprah. All this wealth this woman has for her to open a school in Africa. Commendable but why… https://t.co/Hv96mCDSci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaaaay! 💛💚💜 #CantWait @AndrewWJTV ! Please tune in to @WJTV all morning long for more on the Krewe De Cardinal Carn… https://t.co/dc1CO0gCVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tax return = Costco trip  Walk out that bitch w/ 2 big boxes of Pull-Ups for KaiNoah &amp; a polish dog! 😂👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to go to sleep 😴 cause I have to go right back to work in the morning 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a:  ⚪️ Man  ⚪️ Woman  🔘  Dumb ass driver  Looking for:  ⚪️ Women  ⚪️ Men  🔘 My exit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump That’s as equally laughable as is your dad de-tanning his face before all his TV spot light interviews! What A Joke! 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG this just made my day! I read this to my friend and he goes "Wait! That's me!" Re: @Netflix account 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP are protecting their base by their antics. Keeping the votes. Let’s hope their asses get kicked to the moon… https://t.co/dJJLAVEwNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to my grandfather for always making the ladies in the family feel special this time of year. ❤️ #roses… https://t.co/3FvI086sjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaybeAlexL "Possible Love Interest" WHAT PART OF THEY'RE BABIES DO THESE PEOPLE NOT UNDERST-]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 8: Dayton OH area is very excited to host Ohio Governor @MikeDeWine for our Lincoln Day events. Purchase a ti… https://t.co/n9HzTNIuJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDanielGih @BethFratesMD @KDasguptaMD Yes! I believe I know another individual speaking on the panel as well. I l… https://t.co/ns0giO33Zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only person who, an hour before meeting friends for dinner, eats a "small snack" the size of an entire din… https://t.co/bfYBuO2UH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[6) if @MichaelCohen212  is eluding that doing business in Russia/any other foreign country is illegal, then you mus… https://t.co/pVXyOL0G8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[So bad had to hit it with the lights on Body like a stallion, I'm finna take her home She told me keep that shit a… https://t.co/TiEelk9VHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to quick workout 🏋️‍♀️ before work/school to wake up and maybe a more intense one this afternoon! 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PakistanAirForceOurPride #PakistanArmyZindabad  #Budgam #PakistanStrikesIndia #PMIKTheStatesman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile at MUNCH, there is a little crisis committee meeting in New West called DISEC (Disarmanment and Security)… https://t.co/qZsYaPMwev]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a nine hour shift today &amp; I’m already prepared to go back to bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official !!!  I have the cutest #grandson ever !!!  My little baby 🐻 bear. 💕  . . #socute #mixedbabies… https://t.co/hc6Xw8aRDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landscaperstev1 @SarahGould_SA @Itridpm @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/Acu2SXDGPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drop by the Original Pancake House From 9-2 for your Girl Scout cookie needs. Plus I heard they have pancakes there… https://t.co/kitMod22P0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wweshirtguy @TroubleDVJ @Lostal21 @NikkiPav @Bigb7893 @BrianVistaAZ Morning all. Happy Wednesday! https://t.co/W4sVKBQc54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeemitageLuke @Nathi77Bouville @CorreiaVenilde @Ingrida001 @Serpilmercanho2 @gwenstefani @ChristyVilgiate… https://t.co/Su3GMU4ZlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo shoot on rainy day? No problem! It’s game week, and these girls are ready! #builtbycatholic @montgcatholic… https://t.co/ZkfXIxlkh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spicoli007 @RepTedLieu @FBI We’ve suffered under that scenario for 2 years.  The GOP must really be drinking the koolaid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsGoPens_8771 @WPXIMikeHolden We don’t have a Chili’s anywhere close to here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Basket Case by Green Day https://t.co/TrsrgRdxAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY @GOP It all comes down to this, Warmbier's family couldn’t afford to buy into trump’s brand. If they… https://t.co/2UHDdkWkcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmd122 @ForUsNaturals @IndivisibleNet II understand it being difficult for many students and using printing. The b… https://t.co/zE766j6Ykq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s one I took earlier! With a splash #saturation and #contrast ! ♥️ #hollywoodsign #hollywoodhills #hollywood @… https://t.co/K0CcoSHuKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJHill_PSC That’s so divorced from reality I don’t see a productive discussion here. In an adversarial political s… https://t.co/uqnJDQlT4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrbrown94 and @huntsy22 tonight with their first career NHL goals... what a lovely sight to see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryRice Nice to see another shining star from not just the Sip but by way of the Mississippi Delta. April 25 wil… https://t.co/pxXL1qeiK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NISDCarlosCoon Not only does royalty rule but they also READ. 📚 Thank you Miss San Antonio, Rebecca Mendoza, for s… https://t.co/xeOwrHE7ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIN a FREE Water Heater Maintenance Service for your home this St. Patty's Day - Entering is easy: 1 - Like/Follow… https://t.co/atSffNuAxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi jj if u see this I’m sorry for spamming ur timeline with wdw I’m just very happy Rn love u lots 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[A close and exciting game but unfortunately we lost.   We’ll get them next session! 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy SÚPER contenta porque voy a ser MADRINAAA de primera comunión de una niña muy hermosa 💕!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to the great Stanley Donen who brought so many incredible musicals to the big screen, including my all-time fav… https://t.co/eV4r9geGNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Pasco Sheriff Department I'm hurt that you guy's won't be coming back have enjoyed watching the aweso… https://t.co/XA87DJvzWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[o que me doi é isso :( e eu nao vejo a minha irma desde de maio de 2018]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow flurries and bitter cold can’t stop @ObamaDems from getting the word out about @MMViverito and tomorrow’s Spec… https://t.co/jpdc6qJj9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this worth waking up at 7:30am on a Saturday? https://t.co/cWmRiN4GMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would cut off both my arms to see Kacey Musgraves at the Houston Rodeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@many_trails @hoppinmama5 @bedevilme666 @gator4kb18 @Libphobic2020 @BlueWaterPalms @RealMNRepub @404Lawman… https://t.co/Q0MHaBG3Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just this!  I ❤️ the connection of algebra in middle school to first grade subtraction and addition on number lines… https://t.co/JJdovtMiJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flags are like part 6384847 of the extremely long list of hills I'm planning to die on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaGoldberg @ananavarro It is also about authoritarianism. And this president who desires to be a dictator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgeorge48 There’s a lot of cheap but good recipes, that you can cook in the crockpot! Too many leftovers, free… https://t.co/1H1iAn6m6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The principals @NMBHigh are promoting equality and diversity  and prove that it need not be a challenge, but is som… https://t.co/IcADNgLNuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got 2 piercings but I’m going for a tat within the next 2weeks 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% @RaquelTeran is everything I can hope my students will grow up to be! Proud to know her and support her in all… https://t.co/nAABERI4Wg]]></document></documents></author>