<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Oppie had so much fun today with all her friends Sandy, Mellie, and Benny. Practiced heel, heel-sit, sit-stay, impu… https://t.co/boBw7RMnXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanhanrahan Hey Ryan what’s up it’s Justin Riker here I just wanna let you know the WU reporting station at Emers… https://t.co/6UoB73TJFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proving that Canada  🇨🇦 provides a highly valuable path forward for Growth tech companies #TSX @LightspeedHQ… https://t.co/w4a51oKa2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was honored today to be apart of the 20th annual War Dog memorial ceremony. Spent day listening to inspirational sp… https://t.co/rgYFT1mVTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoop whoop!!!  Porter Robinson’s Second Sky Festival: Register for Exclusive Presale Access + the chance to win FR… https://t.co/7jDACAblQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zags v Toreros! Flag flying for my Alma mater as a house is divided tonight for my Gonzaga Bulldogs v wife’s USD To… https://t.co/owFAkSm5E0]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIAA #basketball sectional semifinal photos: Hamilton 73, Homestead 60 https://t.co/TjUZXGyfjN @HHSChargerHoops… https://t.co/uQ6wOgmKU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading the debates on cryptocurrency is seriously hilarious when you realize what gives it value is the black mark… https://t.co/5WgptXMNoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlpear Good morning. Saw you are from East Penn. I worked With Doug at North Penn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost America's Cybersecurity is among the weakest in the world...It seems nothing is being done to give… https://t.co/aYOzpXanM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry not sorry but whom ever you may be! Just know I Absofuckinglutely love my fans and family! No matter what… https://t.co/CHBt176W7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Make &amp; Style a Closure Wig 💇🏾‍♀️👉🏽Follow @Queen_ish_ for more ❤️ #melaninbeautiesunite #wocmakeup… https://t.co/HkUj7IiK7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got chills from hearing @WWERomanReigns announcement!!!!  #RomanReigns #biggerthanwrestling #WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zrdavis "...but the public at least deserves to be equipped with the facts before coming to a conclusion."   What… https://t.co/c4i7lvjNFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @ChrisBHaynes That "load management". We're not winning, so might as well bring back this guy. https://t.co/5PMVhWaaDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Examen de la Loi sur les espèces en voie de disparition de l’Ontario https://t.co/ojjZF2f4yZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews Oh shoot me now!! Don’t run..! You need to get out of politics already!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonestRacing It’s not complicated. He was at the forefront of reporting the problems at Santa Anita and then disap… https://t.co/qYotK9hmqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I gave the newest a shot, and as it turns out, Gaspar Noe is still an asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluewinggeddog @BluProductions @TheLoveBel0w @thehill When I, like most, pay taxes to our great country, it gives… https://t.co/RvaqrVgrPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omaha_scanner @waze_omaha @551CARS warning westbound industrial from 148th there is an obstacle in the road and a… https://t.co/YqyfECLbDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would you do if you were a marsupial that saw a guy coming out of sky from what appears to be a large pouch?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_kesha Salute Coach! You did it the right way on and off the court! Major props!🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[First came @tupelohoneycafe and now @HiWireBrewing is coming to #knoxville the next #Asheville treasure we need is… https://t.co/K57TKco8rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and B disagree fundamentally on a lot of things. I say mike he say prince. I say Dre he says big boi. He says SZA, I’m jorja all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With me and [redacted], after last time, I just accepted that we would never make it as a couple but can probably h… https://t.co/mc9N6vgs0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[im gonna say it again...my beautiful dark twisted fantasy is the best rap album of the 21st century]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn_DeMore1 @rhondamint To be grossed out even more go to YouTube and search for lady gaga has balls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZionW32 came out his shoe. LITERALLY! Hope you're alright tho kid. #UNCvsDUKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang playful. hahahahahahahaha #mirth #laugh #smirk #amusing https://t.co/uxImbemGr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum @thedailybeast We could retaliate by doxxing  those at the daily beast, but none of them are worth it tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about this for a while but I’ve finally made my decision and it was a tough one too but I will n… https://t.co/c8na6537eO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zzeghedrane @nntaleb @oldlevantine @Marcellenassif @Decafquest @Extrachelle @emiliodib Ascetism=L 3ishé 3al basaata/3al khebzé wl zaytouné]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3Disruptor @Mark4124NH @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump I can't say I know what someone else thinks but I can sure tel… https://t.co/1MGqCQHo3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been watching the old seasons of #Baywatch on @netflix and I'm still in love with @erikaeleniak after all thes… https://t.co/26H6qfyERB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting, give him credit but ultimately he’s losing and as colD. He plays better when he’s not inthe loser you… https://t.co/QHENDRIooS]]></document><document><![CDATA[OU Softball won 4 out of 5 at the St. Pete/Clearwater Elite Invitational! Boomer Sooner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so excited to see captain america and captain marvel interact can it be april already? please??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Couldn't find any coverage from you on this. Kind of a big deal don't you think?  Finance Scandal Reveals That… https://t.co/U1yHT5X91b]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the rapper doesnt past the blunt to you but all his homeboys ... 👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC SO YOU CAN WRAP YOURSELF IN THAT FLAG ,,IM DONE WATCHING DAMN FOOLS BECOME BIGGER ONES ,,MY GOD WILL ALWAYS… https://t.co/ApZypjXetc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the weekend in Sacramento in the impressive thebank629j  Thanks for the great drinks Sakya!  🥂🥃 @ TheBank_… https://t.co/8m6fHCkLk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can drink an entire bottle of *insert alcohol here* and not feel anything” https://t.co/2fwTNMCGks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVC_Athletics @NJCAA This is awesome! Congrats team! Now go win a Ship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m woke but also feel like an idiot for thinking so, hard to tell what’s mf real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Why can’t the golf simulator be real and our buffoon president be fake? @realDonaldTrump @TrumpGolf… https://t.co/Ra1VD3psj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Purpl0704 I was planning to head to Knoxville today to watch #iubase play Tennessee. I'll make the trek tomorrow instead. @IndianaBase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LoveLike_JESUS AMEN! Mine eyes have seen the glory of the coming of the Son']]></document><document><![CDATA[@Envie_Secrete right here on the set learning how to fight😂😂. wassup wit ittt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddntucker @imillhiser @michaelscherer @RoKhanna @AaronBelkin @IndivisibleTeam Shouldn’t Dems win first? Just asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I’m a Hardcore @taylor_ortega Superfan when I’m desperately waiting for her Birthday so I can do a crazy c… https://t.co/ErvuKjrxzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyfarr Yes. This is why nurses are the best for this type of communication. They are amazing at communicating… https://t.co/6BsJqiVSrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gyms have so many unique people. I strongly dislike coming but I don’t want to be obese yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dodgers legend Don Newcombe dies at 92 | Sporting News https://t.co/qcY6E0hxrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This right here is what I mean when I tell people “Roman makes you feel like the most important person in the room.… https://t.co/lrYABszJlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 RAINBOW 🌈 UNICORN 🦄 COLORS! FUNK YEAH! #hailthehairking #hairextensions #illinoishairextensions #hairking… https://t.co/LGp3NT28aM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The clouds have parted... I can finally see the sun! https://t.co/7cASOASqNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When did the Twitter app quietly add the floating thumbnail video feature? Chef kissy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brewfan0419 Awe. How does it feel to be poor? Lol jk! I need that option for iPhone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longo52 Come 28th -2nd let’s win some cash bud ! @Bdhegg and @tbelt and @nate_test  will be in town .. #letsdothjs #February]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heresy in this statement is the word “clear”.  The Bible is the word of God. Franklin Graham, and his alt right… https://t.co/p7i8wzM6Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Westmont! #landscapephotography  #westmontillinois @ Westmont, Illinois https://t.co/CBodCP74lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodoldcatchy @Lady_Star_Gem "So. Cal Ocean Grown Crew" One 💚☯️☮️🤬 @oceangrownseeds DUMP TRUMP! Impeach now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumper_tantrum @TheDemocrats @OfficialCBC I never mentioned Obama or Clinton, bud. Like I said, seek help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR these are the most boring restrictor plate races i have ever seen. You need to fix it. Riding single fill a… https://t.co/A9hxc5xHUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[But it’s never over til it’s over.   I won in the end.   Keep the faith, kids. Fight til the bitter end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From ⁦@foundr⁩, a #Chicago-culture twist to a legendary #WindyCity #startup: “⁦@jasonfried⁩ decided it was ‘easier… https://t.co/xQJ4sbaGCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s insulting to have billboards and commercials and a zillion signs on vacant land and think that’s enough.  This… https://t.co/vPHJAVm6Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coromd @campbellitstrue @suetsam @IanCaveney @Acosta We'll never know about the Russian involvement.  Mueller fake… https://t.co/8PE0mKOMii]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the fam... #BamaBound @ neyows creole cafe https://t.co/tvWkM0ZXnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Some people know this and some don’t. I love teaching. Love my job very much. But my long-term goal is to get i… https://t.co/JAXqqGNQBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[the physical experience my inebriated body goes through when i hear g.u.y. is...,,,indescribable https://t.co/qdgf1pr0cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Trump for February 25, 2019 | https://t.co/eSMqRsQRgf https://t.co/NfEDpBB6Ig via @GoComics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation What about workers who toil to save the planet for our grandchildren?  Solar panel installers, windmill… https://t.co/MNlSvGov1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanTheManR All I did was laugh man I’m not taking credit for shit lol. My twitter is about positivity and love bro… https://t.co/vXy3vCuw1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMTMike @streetdogfdn She fits in with us perfectly! We’re glad we found her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullsBears : 4 to 0 against a new tax on the wealthy. @davidasman summarizes : all state unintended consequences w/ no debt reduction!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CainTheBully NEW 🔥🔥🔥 coming soon @ Toledo, Ohio https://t.co/Wsj91ZC17B]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never too early to talk to your kids about #investing!  https://t.co/z8S2RciBq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrosssx You look basically the same? I know when I was 16 even though I guess I was cocky at times I probabl… https://t.co/oE1sJmLS0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRifer @richardfarley A satisfying resolution to this quarrel = insurmountable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready to watch the #CreekCrew and those @Onyx_Rays do their thing this weekend!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceBartlett @walterolson @lordsutch Here’s more.  At this point I hope I’ve made the point that you have embrace… https://t.co/hP3gRBQuFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/23WverqgWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone whining about why Christians and white men aren't included in this stupid resolution needs to listen to th… https://t.co/AEB77Xi5Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odienator @bybowes It’s got Michael Lonsdale! I saw it twice in the theater! It’s actually pretty good until it gets really dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bao Wins Best Animated Short Film! #Oscars2019 #Oscars #AcademyAwards https://t.co/0sDQsSHl5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember talking to @chucksmithnfl a few years ago about Dee Ford. It was before Ford broke through. Chuck mentio… https://t.co/S2EX67EZR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 and we have grown men wearing light-up uniforms to play professional Xbox.  Societal decline has kicked in]]></document><document><![CDATA[The message is simple but powerful. Get out of your comfort zone and start living your dreams. No it's not easy.  A… https://t.co/74F11ql9j5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyronVernis I dunno; Honda was selling plenty of hatchbacks to Americans at the time.  Maybe the hatch/4 door comb… https://t.co/hJeagmL6fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreerksenTim MovieBlob hasn't washed up since he lost his stick with a rag glued to it in a bodily crevice somewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalMolly1 @joshtpm Doesn't matter if one is okay with it. It's the objective definition of parasite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Will Deliver You And You Shall Not Be Given Over To Your Fears https://t.co/b1OIEgUi6f via @YouTube new video today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Birdie Birdie by @BrueryTerreux/@GREENCHEEKBEER @ Space Above The Sink — https://t.co/imneUQFcxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Day 65 Self-Study to Web Dev!” by Austin Beaufort https://t.co/7K6FjpqVEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday and especially before I go on camera I make sure to use @kiehls products. The men’s line is amazing and it… https://t.co/e1shopNiKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#karaoke #SundayFunday #columbus #singers @TommyOBryansPub  8270 Sancus Blvd Westerville #ColumbusOhio 9:00-1:00  @… https://t.co/GJT1AcdOhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theroyreport Nazareth is not afraid to make the extra pass for the easier shot! That’s the story of the 2nd half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out there is a Mighty Ducks podcast @QuackAttackPod and this makes me incredibly happy.]]></document></documents></author>