<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[After a long day at the racetrack with my wheelman, I want to wish him a Happy Valentines Day! ❤️ There’s no one el… https://t.co/cPrKkAho7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe calling Jordyn a home wrecker is a bit of a stretch....... that home has been wrecked since Tristan cheated t… https://t.co/6bXr9i9Rf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 And, it would explain why so many members of the GOP act compromised and not in the best interest of t… https://t.co/llxfJ0nvbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabby_marie828 I feel you! I’m a month away from being in the 3rd trimester, like pleaseeeee slow down it’s my last!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessiejoppich Thank god, a relatable post. I was nervous to have y'all see all my bags tomorrow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna get some tattoos ... but my mom keeps guilt tripping me saying that I won’t see her in HEAVEN if I get them 🤦🏾‍♀️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the cameo that I expected to see least in this Daily Mail roundup is... @tomshattuck!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman For some reason I read Nanny Pelosi, instead of Nancy. Just Sayin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish you would have sent him to the Southeastern coast, @AidenWolfe. Oh, how I miss him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor poooppppppppppppppllllllppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppppo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying tRump 🤥 continues to insist drugs are not coming in through ports of entry to justify his stupid wall. As if… https://t.co/EAOYnGo2NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegue temprano (no me puse ni crema en el cabello por llegar) para no poder comenzar porque un pendejo no ha llega… https://t.co/4YnxLwmGNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FixTheCourt @uscourts Congress should get off the campaign trail and approve the judges Pres. Trump nominated. Do you job Congress!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristanSpoof exactly why u got dropped u live off the internet not lan 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣😂😂 Don't worry ya'll there is still the other 364 days. Hope all my friends and family had a wonderful .Alentines… https://t.co/SuljwHmJGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @valinorking @dfd1231 @DaveSchreiber3 @TigerLetsRoll @briantopping66 @raducom @garway95 @Sundncefn… https://t.co/9OU17G39GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strange question of the day: Is Breastmilk Vegan? https://t.co/v2CYdOtaUQ via @peta]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly Charged With Sexual Abuse in Chicago, Reports Say https://t.co/1aQX4UDXm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisVuitton you should really sell the Neverfull clutch by itself. I don’t want that whole bag, I just want that adorable little clutch 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_GangstaaGaby @OMARCHAPARRO Bro have you seen the one of the señora who breaks the glass bowl lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had the most asleep!-now awake!-back asleep! Night of sleeping to the point that I can only keep one eye ope… https://t.co/DSBRPY5an2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just told my doctor this morning, a mere 5 hours ago, that I'll cut back on sugar. I just ordered a milkshake with… https://t.co/xnvtFInsWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guys! i know it fucking 12a but this is me reminding y’all that i do commissions for both digital art and canva… https://t.co/9eELDY7OL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re planning to watch Leaving Neverland, be prepared to never want to listen to MJ songs ever again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chibok  Would they have asked Jamie Closs to explain her life and days with her kidnappe, Jake Thomas Patterson, on… https://t.co/a6rJG7kTtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McHalesPub51 !!! Loved the video Cabs showed me of Pirlo there though. She's the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofain Hahaha! "Clout Gang." It's like a punchline that needs no joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again dumbass,yes I have adopted three children they were slated for abortion and drug and alcohol addicted I’… https://t.co/9NRqmOfYqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fVlaWeJnD3 We live and well, playing some #Overwatch on #Twitch so come stop by]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always so good to link up with @michaelxc0re and literally pick up where we left off 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[El día que puedan ver The Handmaid's Tale se van a cagar.  Hasta luego amigos...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 @mills_abbot “...the party remains overwhelmingly white. “ https://t.co/dLxVWCL768]]></document><document><![CDATA[#protectivestyles #naturalhairgoals #naturalhairjunkie #naturallyshedope #hair #updo #twostrandtwist #braids… https://t.co/I3vPDCmyyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations Too bad his wife let him breed! That gene pool is infected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein In the spirit of "know the enemy" sometimes I put on Fox when my husband isn't around. I can only tak… https://t.co/K3pHUk9Z2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[You niggas parents didn’t like y’all when my grades dropped I got a tutor not punished]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoincianaStem K-2 students had so much fun exploring shapes with glow sticks!  Great first week of @BedtimeMath Cr… https://t.co/Lm21olpBdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[dont demean anyone unless they’ve been disrespectful or shows sign of hypocrisy #imagineaworldlikethat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever a guy follows me on anything i just ask myself who his girl is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnarls @AOC I believe the Administration closed down their HIV/AIDS department????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me n the baby chilling on the porch @ Left Brain Laboratory https://t.co/w0TyfDvFTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to meet 18reillysmith today @racep2r. Feel better @alextuch37. You were definitely missed today. @ Pole Positio… https://t.co/xLI8i75Y7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I’m wearing a light jacket with no gloves, hat, or scarf! Spring is coming!!! #winterisleaving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Screw McConnell he has Hide Concealed Covered up for the Criminals in Repulican Party including Donal… https://t.co/bzk2C2BrZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume I prefer to think that you and your ilk are the embarrassments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 great performances by @NoahKahan &amp; @JamesBayMusic at the @OrpheumBoston yesterday https://t.co/kA7ybdPcUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mar_moorah If we want to stop gun violence we’ll have to replace @realDonaldTrump he’s an owned by #NRA= #RussianAsset]]></document><document><![CDATA[thankful that fletch and my kidneys tolerated me all weekend 🤩 @ Chez Josef https://t.co/3hLdwGZn1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Culture_Content @93XRT I know! On my way to the station all on/off exit ramps were closed with cop cars flashing b… https://t.co/pMQbXvGMan]]></document><document><![CDATA[When she’s also a realist and an optimist and isn’t getting over it @dereksteez @State_Champs https://t.co/IMgkKa4T6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two @GaryAllan fans walk into an American Legion ...   Is that how the joke starts @k_fauco? https://t.co/Rq3lSTFipi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenLindbergh #updatingbaseball #ssac19 where are these tweets you’re reading?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaptrapped @mommamia1217 @putinsgay @a_patriciann @RepMarkMeadows Me thought he did protest too much😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m mad some of y’all are really into shit... who raised y’all? Like... what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALittleLexie @FrPhilTangorra @OhTHATJohnDaley Will do! If our Lord is calling you, our Lady will bring you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheckyi If her jail time is like Killery ‘s it’s going to be a long summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my life: i put my kid in a green shirt on picture day. Apparently photographers use green screens now.… https://t.co/knt1uiUNxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow These two fools impressed with Soviet window dressing.  Meanwhile citizens aren’t free to leave country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayEryssaa @KimKardashian She didn’t ask for the head start. Yes, I’m black and white and I wish I was born with o… https://t.co/Fsh9R5CqAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must be a wife from the 50’s because I told my hubby I wanted a proper washroom if we get a new home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may never get it right — but I will die trying to figure out the how many Sha-ha-ha-ha’s there are before it beco… https://t.co/tSCx81zOwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing @realDonaldTrump Maybe you are agree with killing babies or you are like them with no Conscience don’t… https://t.co/JIGVS4w5JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SealeyGerald @cgr888 @TPCLJ @krunalley @RealTrumpLady @Chandler4Five @ItsAbout1A2A @DrBoHammer @Krm1285A… https://t.co/9KkvYAmjc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my Afternoon brunch we have avocado, tomato, spinach, beef and egg muffins... #comforting #onmytabletoday… https://t.co/s6ZiOVoTGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get in my belly! #southphillybarbacoa #chefstable #italianmarket #tacos https://t.co/pJQg4Nw8sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las acciones hablan más fuerte que las palabras. 👊🏻😉 https://t.co/SF1gyRbK4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can be all the things you told me not to be, when you try to come for me I keep on flourishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janesilva760 @Ange_Amene Kamala recently said she is for some form of reparations. It was on the Breakfasr Club ra… https://t.co/K329Y9Knpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NonMaternalMum Oh my goodness!  Stay strong Mom. Let us know when he s here!!!  We are thinking of you.  Virtually holding your hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing for tomorrow.  I need lots of ☕️ 🍋 I gotta prepare everything I can the night before since I’m such an 🦉… https://t.co/ml0Tcwnr8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[N.Y. congresswoman introduces resolution honoring Chinese railroad workers https://t.co/6bTSHwEXXA via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinSLeahy @StephenLeahy @jgkoomey @arvindpawan1 @Peters_Glen Not sure if this is meant for me Kev, but my point… https://t.co/MkFT1pzJnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not on the payroll of any think tank, nor personal donor funding me (like a few female pundits whom I won’t nam… https://t.co/Yph6rOBrrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@EmergeColorado in a nutshell:  10:13: “dont call people sweetie its sexist”  10:14: “unless they dont agree with… https://t.co/W5RjMI8SoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Margstark @hallmarkchannel We have always loved Ned @Margstark @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[God if i could be a fictional character i would definitely be Anthony Soprano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great unofficial visit yesterday!!! Thanks @CoachWMuschamp @bobbybentley and the entire staff for your hosp… https://t.co/KeM0gnDvm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dogs are so happy that Joel is home we are just in an absolute cuddle puddle all is right with the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav YG song!😍🤑 So much fun seeing my baby daddy. @YG ❤️😍😍 https://t.co/rDZVIIzHZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌷Avon browsing time👣*https://t.co/s88lSmOLCq @ Pierce County, Georgia https://t.co/NG4h76m3mE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan5150Mahoney Oh my goodness!! Such blatant attempts to silence and shame!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmanuelEfunbote @marklevinshow Hey idiot, don't you need evidence to be charged with anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[hiiii this boy went from not wanting me to be inside his house to telling me to spend the night there and i don't trust that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaMacavoy @burtonkim76133 @AllAboutDaTea I love Porsche ! The only thing she ever did that I thought was dumb wa… https://t.co/3HyIuZtM4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Oh Lord‼️‼️ HERE WE GO‼️‼️😡😡😡😡📣📣📣📣🌎🌎🌎🌎💓💓💓💓☠️☠️☠️☠️ Get that SOB OUT OF THE WHITE HOUSE‼️‼️ HE IS GOING TO… https://t.co/9Gd92jgkxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never realized how much my ex actually weighed me down and how unhappy I’ve been till this past month without him.… https://t.co/BcKIAj7mh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linda_Elias lmfaooo it’s not even real tea like that  but Intervarsity did hate me for introducing one of their me… https://t.co/WZ12P9Seyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letsgomathias Southern accent?? Oh, he needs to do Lindsey Graham next!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @realDonaldTrump Thank you! What the heck is he even taking about ? And why is Chris Stewart the authority all of a sudden?]]></document><document><![CDATA[68 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/eTRUmjARDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como me superan estas cosas, los días así son horribles, y te extraño mas que nunca 🌟♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW SINGLE OUT 'CARAMEL' BY LLOYD FT. CITY GIRLS written✍ by Me(SHONDA) &amp; @Lloyd_YG 🎤🎵🎶 https://t.co/PqwFQQUC1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@familytravelck was on @tomwgnchicago in #Chicago this morning! Did you tune in and see colleenkellytravels ? We wi… https://t.co/TlGWj1dh02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolfblitzer @CNN @realDonaldTrump In my very best Kellyanne Huckabee-Sanders interpretation, I think what the Pres… https://t.co/dUekQGtwo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GaetzResign  You are unhinged &amp; a detriment to @GOP not an asset!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been nominated by @BCISTaylor to post covers of 7 books that I love - no explanations or reviews- just cover… https://t.co/oRuq236df7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Wendy501_ @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump Checks don't prove anything.  Attorneys are paid all the time for the work th… https://t.co/KPDVN2aLvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday.  "The detention of Baring Vostok's top-management has sent shockwaves through the country’s business com… https://t.co/MUf3QkWVut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamonddarling I would really blow my top off.... same prob with 9 yrs ( car accident 42 yrs ago... he was my neph… https://t.co/9WJEggMgUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be such a shrew. Joe Biden has been a good strong friend to the cause.]]></document></documents></author>