<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@maxkellerman will you narrate something or please look into voice acting work if you don’t already would be a fire… https://t.co/tTjtP2Pkrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyJaneNelson He’s going to Philly they need a pic of him after the fans throw batteries at him]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughters first wrestling show #wwesyracuse #wwelive https://t.co/LaM9WnFpn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green New Deal: The big picture trumps the details: https://t.co/rPTTcObWu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTomAlexander @aafAPOLLOS What’s up with Hunt? Had a great Week 1 now buried on the depth chart ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lewisisthename @Padres Yeah! Nobody liked Ty Cobb either dipstick, but everyone of them would have wanted him on their team]]></document><document><![CDATA[#YERP ‼️ #BodegaBoys #AOC #AlexandriaOcasioCortez #DesusNice #KidMero #desusandmero #thebrandisstrong @ Chicago, Il… https://t.co/qH5n9Hyxvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Yes get rid of people like you. Does that mean you're going to resign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithDowlingJr @JordanA_McCurdy PS4. I hate getting a healer that doesn’t heal man 😂 I be on them win streaks tho.… https://t.co/FcfCvTAuww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jongraywb Poor white men arent allowed to... *pulls out small post-it note* ...fill an entire classroom with themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at Washington Days this weekend! It was really cool meeting Montana Senator @jontester who said it… https://t.co/1AnuMXGHDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waited longer than I should have for this. The Raconteurs - "Now That You're Gone" (Official Video) https://t.co/gomNKNgiyt via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWilly1875 @Jeremy_Handler And also this...  3. https://t.co/c46mHJDhm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have one of the greatest dogs of all time - a cocker spaniel who looks like he took a bath in white and dark choc… https://t.co/6ORCixXDts]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 I made it! Haha. I literally told Logan we might be in the background &amp; boom. Mic drop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber didn’t even try to disguise what he was chatting bout in hold tight. Not even a little]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grazapin @AOC Well I’m honored to have provided something strange to you today, especially on TWTR. That’s hard to do on this site. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA would have allowed that and wouldnt have been been called a walk. He lost possession of the ball. #BBN @DrewFranklinKSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Stop your war on the First Amendment and the Free Press. Any acts of violence on media personnel will be on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i just looked up those pair of LV earrings i retweeted.......they’re $660.........i think i’ll pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha it’s so true that’s my dawg tho @tydollasign 7.9 by himself 9.7 on features]]></document><document><![CDATA[the day i went to the dining hall and grabbed something that i thought was a tender sub just to bite into it and fi… https://t.co/7nkx9XA9Lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Catering Facility in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/KavgqyCGhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMargaronis @ezraklein His is a dishonest take. https://t.co/4xVSlnQz9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or these new horror movies are actually interesting.... cuz it makes fucking sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsGetLexi i hope @hunterpence shoulder feels better soon, and he can get back out there 👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjakerman had a great performance at @thesayersclub / Hollywood, CA.- - She’s a practitioner in the music industry… https://t.co/CAfX71bqJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The DOJ should investigate the resistance movement and determine the obstructionist over throw of the government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SohiAmarjeet Thank you @SohiAmarjeet for your solidarity in this fight! This government is making real strides in… https://t.co/j1TPpJq16G]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOOD AM CLINT/GUYS🍆WelCUM TO #FF from My Sexy FRENCH BTTM Bud @AnteoCharaXXX &amp; #RodSteelOfficial 🍑🍆💦😍👍🏼😘… https://t.co/ozHq3NlrWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeygirl_CA @adamcbest That’s what I noticed the most too.   Not the rhetoric.  That’s the typical 💩 that comes out of her 👄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shut the fuck up, it’s not that deep? Let people support who they want to being a dick won’t change their mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte, NC! I’m headlining a show @HeistBrewery tomorrow night. If you work for Bank of America, there’s a $12 s… https://t.co/IKf1HW7uR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairolicious Exaxt same punch and everything dawg smh that dude gotta reevaluate the game plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sad13 @thethermals Please don't block my shitty behavior. I Iove the musics. Keep on chooglin'!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why the criticism against Kihei continues. Has he struggled shooting the ball lately? Sure. But all I hear… https://t.co/kQj1BTfkWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What natural disaster appears in your nightmares? ((For me it’s tornadoes))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro I knew it @benshapiro! You’ve rehearsed a hate crime aimed at short people! Racist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This “little” guy had a rough end to 2018, but we are glad he’s healthy again. #joejustine2019 #lion… https://t.co/XAdS1uF6mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Jesus Freak by DC Talk on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/iejzUXvxK4 https://t.co/vNGWEE7QA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[All together now 🙌🏼 @ PGA National Resort &amp; Spa https://t.co/aSBjyBKEDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’rrrreeeee baaaaackkkk! Appreciate the Baseball Booster Club for asking me and @keithholt24 to broadcast… https://t.co/biGOR8ejTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[(1/2) Happy Turn The Clock Ahead Sunday! The @journalgsports will keep you on time with stories of @BoilerBall winn… https://t.co/1qhem3raA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotPollard31 They get the opportunity to get an education for free develop themselves socially, academically and… https://t.co/cQxrM1uJlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[River Valley making unlikely run to state bowling tournament https://t.co/IoTibXbdcL via @TheMarionStar… https://t.co/BaCNzl3T9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[when cobygrantmusic and i were a cool band together. mixed by the always brill karyadisutedja  #music #production #… https://t.co/IhsgOydGMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pearl on Hagans: "Ashton is such an unselfish player and always has been ... has always gotten off on empowering hi… https://t.co/iWgGrJDr7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy valentines baby 😘❤️🥰😍 You are the best! 😉 @ Montreal, Quebec https://t.co/fXuayR0z3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st rapper to cop a i8 and park dat bitch in the living room‼️😤😂 https://t.co/AjWMq50IGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumers the BIONG! 737 Max software pushes the nose down at the wrong time and falsifies fuel economy data.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alapez Lo importante es hacer nuestro mejor papel en este convulsionado mundo, no importa si somos terrenales o ma… https://t.co/rAvshEGtSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5debeatzflame ain’t nobody harder than rofio #picoftheday @ Harrison, New Jersey https://t.co/XseVjOfS4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncgavn 😂🧞‍♀️😂they can’t stop the president and act as if their hair is on fire😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ultra pretentious “real rap” side of the genre will never cease being incredibly corny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstroShanna @Cubfan1324 @MeghanMcCain A rare birth, i in 100,100 these babies are cycloptic babies no functioning… https://t.co/P4jbiolus9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vance Romero is promoted to sophomore level white belt 2nd stripe! #graciebarrasantafe #gbsantafe… https://t.co/eJUmubwHBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@statnews Usually FDA wants 2 of 2 positive trials; in MDD 2 of 3 likely wins.. - Esketamine lauded as important op… https://t.co/EkK4gsLBXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tracking rain this Afternoon, this weekend and worrisome rain next week. #CHawx https://t.co/LqaTY6dcMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're a cop: Crime lab scandal rocked Kamala Harris’ term as San Francisco district attorney… https://t.co/hPYC4eL2Pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just learned about the @NakaweProject and their work to put a stop to illegal shark finning. When you get a chance,… https://t.co/5z4A6QGiyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azucenau Coordinadas las fuerzas armadas pueden combatir cáncer que agobia a MX. Con carencias presupuestales y co… https://t.co/FvNTIYsYhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts have no bearing in the mind of a dedicated socialist. Propaganda is all that matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#101 🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤔🤔 crazy ... that’s why I don’t believe in this stuff ... @antscottt @Matt_Brown03 @LarryBrownlar44… https://t.co/jMAtfRmcNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @chambleebrandel.  I’ve got an injured rib and a week long golf trip scheduled Friday.  Can I get a retweet f… https://t.co/yd60ggnFNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever just be like a caramel macchiato with almond milk. Because same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pham1717 I haven’t done either, I watched the play. I’m the type to bash my players, rewatch the play guy he had the One-timer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew a woman who put Confederate flag up in CALIFORNIA, wasn't a good person? https://t.co/RNlZpnk95T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bitsybee17 @JadePetersma Order matters. I’m working so I’m not being fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oOoOoBarracuda What were they thinking? Things happened in that movie that had my jaw dropping to the floor. It mi… https://t.co/3qSwzaYlm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raul Flores | Transparent cowlneck shirt, tank with gold stripe detail, denim shorts with white leg panels and hand… https://t.co/JYrBsCsw6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@copass59 Well done!  Appreciated the access and enjoyed documenting your journey this year!  Onto next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure he's the one to throw stones on realism in movies.  I'm also not sure any super hero movie will fair t… https://t.co/aC7ixwxSOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleTreacy @CalvinKlein Is this the gift?? Lol 😝 ❤️❤️❤️❤️😍😍😍😍😍 https://t.co/z1TBM0TiEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[man some people get a little fame on twitter and get a maaaaaaaaaajor ego boost 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reminder and reassurance for #Exvangelical people, like me. https://t.co/AKVqLEZ4H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep your new- born safe  Owlet Smart Sock 2 Baby Monitor - Track Your Infant's Heart Rate &amp; Oxygen Levels https://t.co/mbT5P2eWKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twp459 @Katiedidornot @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Mueller is a life long republican]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoLeanme @Arky67 @_Henn_dawg @scottplumerias @GobAbiertoBOL @AOC Cuba is multiethnic just as the USA multiet… https://t.co/FdNk8JX4uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyFerone @WhiteHotHeat23 @GearsViking Custom always beats purchased 😎#ButIReallyWantAllThoseCollectibles… https://t.co/czYWWqVSjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StoffelMatt Really interesting to see the wide range of answers.   snarky millennial Instagrammer  salty old film… https://t.co/9pyvqx9CAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn bby girl just put me on some shit through her job and I feel exclusive af! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeLickMe @_iamkinaa Do you remember the recession? Do you remember when gas prices were double what they are now… https://t.co/7c48LEcgqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSamperO Colombia tiene pavor de caer en manos de Petro y su combo , que la va a destruir ,  y que cuenta con… https://t.co/HxKcSyRwnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a hint of an earthy slightly fruity nose, bready, toffee and caramel round out the middle followed by a mild s… https://t.co/Me8vhXIm16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobBowdon @C3Snyc @coopmike48 @CPICSchools @John_Merrow @DebMeier @JoeNathan9249 @dirktillotson @ChoiceMediatv… https://t.co/lvdtXsT8Pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence @TuckerCarlson you and @IngrahamAngle can go fuck yourselves. Or each other. Just STFU and leave us alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invincibility of youth + monster guitar riff = this song #grateful 335/365 Sum 41 - Fatlip (Official Music Video)… https://t.co/bcEdLshA21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberFacts My 11 year old puppy, Bindi Sue. Named after @BindiIrwin of course! https://t.co/mbBJaZyfKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hungryhuthut Really?? I feel like you get the best music listening experience with IEMs, you literally hear everyt… https://t.co/uel9nNcdiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[God wants us to have the correct Heart @ San Marcos, California https://t.co/BCQm7tC0Gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing that the rushing forth of sorrow and the cold ragged edge of anxiety would abate. It is like a breath-steal… https://t.co/r9mSzV25hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a frozen margarita... a bit ahead on my chips and salsa, the place is packed, I don't mind the wait.… https://t.co/9muQcmKJL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedHat_RedPill @CNN America doesn’t have any religious values. That’s the whole point of separation of church and… https://t.co/djAUVhrENh]]></document><document><![CDATA[First, a follow-up from yesterday, to quote @SBriend97 -"mass doesn't necessarily equal gas."  In fact, within our… https://t.co/YvSJaY8Ozq]]></document><document><![CDATA[1:14 on the clock.  Northbridge up 50 to 46.  #MakeYaFreeThrows #GoRams #ClarkTournament]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scriobhann_si @plsleaveamsg As a Vietnamese French or British Polynesian Maori or Tahitian Indigenous Pacific Isla… https://t.co/j3uWK57xss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Package Rib Injury update:  Sleepless night.  Hurts when I breathe.  Today I’m testing out my lungs to prep for 48… https://t.co/onzXYeKrMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New single from @goldyardmusic (Austin Haze) that I produced on all major platforms, link in his bio @ Atlanta, Geo… https://t.co/8JSWfobPmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdaniels1964 @JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump Your full of it Lady a closet racist what a damn joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @horusrage @Cern_lXXl @PCribbett @BlancoIndian @CingetoOfBelgae @zapher134 @selgowiros @PolyRhuagh… https://t.co/fw2874wZrr]]></document></documents></author>