<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@matthewmerez @MNC010101 @matthewjdowd @BetoORourke Bernie needs to concentrate on VT. We are losing population her… https://t.co/FYuZGUsKXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.. seeing y’all grow over the last 3 years has been such a cool experience as a fan, and I feel so proud rn :,)… https://t.co/mKv4cKASOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PublicHealthHaiku Network of support - Critical for wellbeing - Isolation harms. @ASPPHtweets @CHPPD_APHA @APHAPHN… https://t.co/kLuiFOsmKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hope #love #faith #always  #thankfullness #life #sunset #sunrise #divinity #gracious #God #hopeforthebest   For… https://t.co/wF1GLfibvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the dunk for reference. whatever “something” he tried most definitely worked: https://t.co/aveDAoZshv]]></document><document><![CDATA[my friends hyped me up way to much into thinking I could do a back flip 😂😂😭😭🤪💀 my back hurttttts!  Sadie’s was funnn thoo ((:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do y’all groupies love to follow me I’m not here to make friends and kiki witchall 😖😖😖😣😣😣😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention #ContestAlert! Enter to #win a Best Babysitters Ever prize pack including $50 GC from @OutnumberedMama an… https://t.co/LFLvNAVOGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like that we all know his name, but have adopted #MrMiz as his new name]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t let our sweet Sally go without being honored on #LoveYourPetDay! 🐶💕 #BestDogEver @abbey_szentes @samszentes https://t.co/pJpYaYJn33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drug bust nets 33 members of Salt Lake’s Norteno street gang — who allegedly had ties to Mexican drug cartels, via… https://t.co/zC9AIbagRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luca’s snoozy Suspiria remake was all worth it for Jun Takahashi’s Suspiria-inspired Undercover collection 😭😭😭 https://t.co/RbpfBCBqoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SydneyG777 @Rick_C4242 @emdoyl @kaylalalaj I’m Italian. My god is the Spaghetti monster. https://t.co/kdS2qRCTKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m delayed but what’s not to love about a Monday starting like this?! It was very windy, obviously by the water ri… https://t.co/uqePJ4Vw7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want to do rn is be laid up next to the guy I want to be around like 24/7 😭 ughhh need to be snuggled up with… https://t.co/jVQotjHSKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunter_welcing @coachfitz51 @LZHSFootball @EFTfootball @EDGYTIM @CoachBigPete @AllenTrieu @NUFBFamily @NUFBRecruiting Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something is in the air today putting stress on relationships over here 😂😂😂😂😂 this like the 4th one going up in flames today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @NBCNews You do know that it came across the southern border first, right😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very proud of you, @marcmaron. That was an excellent interview. #TheSimpsons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boomuh_23 Dude, it was the best!!  Not only saying it cause I was drunk lol  Literally the best macaroni salad I’ve ever had]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jarrod Huber tomorrow during pink out your lil Nana a 24 yr breast cancer survivor will be cheering for you from ho… https://t.co/b6nyM7ecDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ngl pretty content stuffing my face with lasagna while couples are having 2 bites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_manton She is absolutely BEAUTIFUL!!! 💗Congratulations, Coach; we are so happy for you &amp; your family! ❤️ her name too! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elecciones especiales Febrero 26 Candidatos a defensor pùblico para ocupar la vacante que deja Leititia James quien… https://t.co/bXJBKDC5ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviamente somos la pareja perfecta porque tú también gritas bebesitaaaaa 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GNCordova According to astro, your moon sign is your inner thoughts and personality. The fact that you're a capric… https://t.co/L6WJxYjKyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If this is true (it is) IDIOT what is the NATIONAL EMERGENCY??? YOU ARE THE WORST PRESIDENT IN HIS… https://t.co/lDNHScPEIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[New chapters and new pallets 😊😊 #like #cali #mua #makeup #smile #happy #l4l #sagaftra #selfie #followforfollowback… https://t.co/NZ4PQ0mEcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a risk and shatter the glass...risk-taking strengthens confidence...and confidence is the heart of igniting ac… https://t.co/LTy3JX97XV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @WSJ @netflix @NetflixFilm @nytimes @OversightDems @politico @bpolitics Heard Netflix paid Aoc 10miuin for doc… https://t.co/leH1yg01dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was not expecting anything today for valentine's day. But my fiance surprised me just the way he does. I love you… https://t.co/vc6t7Tew4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mummy told me she misses cooking for me , I’ve never heard sweeter words]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ll always give up cause they just “can’t handle everything you have going on”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceandFrankie I think I finally understand the definition of emotional eating. - The Del is here for you my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radioverbier @festini10 @blakeshelton can you do honey bee too please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reba taking my son to school and he’s like mom I wanna hear “stronger than the truth” he loves the song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum @realDonaldTrump I remember telling my children, “Once it’s on the Internet, it’s ALWAYS on the Inter… https://t.co/gnmlHbNaCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found the bean aka frijole! #chicago #travelagent #travelblogger https://t.co/OpH0gCPCGj @OneBusyBeeEnt https://t.co/yaS4X60gr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadian_dre You are so smart to get away from the herd you traveled with]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oyerooh @sienac96  Roses are red, violets are blue. I’m not exactly sure, I’m colorblind And why are violets blue… https://t.co/2eKA52N9j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from the Stillwater Portland Office today. https://t.co/hG6y3s8zyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too shabby a start... 😉😎 #sounderstilidie #soundersmatchday #soundersfc #seavscin @ CenturyLink Field https://t.co/akaJneiBrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady I’m underground and ‘Content is unavailable’ right now and I’m crushed. 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super happy new sweatshirt designed by my friend @mileposts 💞those are a few of my favorite things, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[👍👍👍👍👍👍 Blue Water Keyes 2001 South Ocean Avenue  North Myrtle Beach, SC ❤️My Happy Place🏖 https://t.co/yJUgzpvBFI 🏖… https://t.co/3e15YEofqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Do Tomorrow: 🔵 Finish commission currently in progress ⚪ Start/finish other commission in the queue 🔵 Make a sna… https://t.co/Xx4RTb4wUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@purellnation @dandelionfox25 Nikki ur a blonde like dad was getting use to it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[i promised myself i wouldn’t do this again but here i am doing it to myself again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to perform at Districts. I know you’ll represent @fhcspartanbands  with class. #proudbandmom https://t.co/qe7NNbAUIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffKMartin1 @Shaun_Girk @HireMeImFunny @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 https://t.co/DpBkVZUO8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_caylor The amount of times I’ve thought about putting eyelashes on Tina]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Snapchat memories, I met Julian 2 years ago yesterday? Which doesn’t make sense because today 2 years… https://t.co/jGmIeSYuZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And today is a wrap on my old job. Or as I like to put it, “I got fed up and walked out. I’m never going back.”  New job starts Monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#49ers roster moves: Declined Pierre Garçon’s 2019 option Tendered 1-year contracts to restricted FA RB Raheem Most… https://t.co/2F7SGmC1TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[im the type of person to really test ppl to see how true to they word they are mfs ALWAYS fail 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-cultivate your mental space in a way that you can look at self from 9 (or more) years ago and tell that person t… https://t.co/HHGlOdy7kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Wait..What? Are we living in the “Twilight Zone “ I didn’t dream that my 67 years would be like this, it’s disheartening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m amber!  brad! Tammy! fender! Brenda! sketch!  Shelly! IQ! Lou Ann Joey!  Mikey! Vicki! Becky! bix! Jessie! darl… https://t.co/OqFpRpzerL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby girl and I are headed to see our cousin/niece in sunny Cali! 🥰 #flyingwithmygirl #excitedforbabysnuggles @ Bos… https://t.co/fjsv5tm1Aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fun to be the @FSUCareerCenter’s liaison to the @fsucge! Planning tailored workshops with @LeesaTruesdell to hel… https://t.co/0dYxESkZuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix should #RenewODAAT because #ODAAT is one of the greatest sitcoms of the 21st century. Funny, sincere, and… https://t.co/QmLT1KBW2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[PACKED HOUSE ON THE WESTSIDE!  #WESTSIDECHAMPIONSHIPS @ Jefferson High School (Cedar Rapids, Iowa) https://t.co/a07iY6S1pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having to re-wind because I'm still laughing at the previous interview  #KraftPunk https://t.co/62u3OSZ073]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Interesting how you can never back up your facts by naming who “they” are. The only “they” telling… https://t.co/F3FmALbBzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat Maybe they enjoy the fast food smell seeping from his pores. 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asst. Superintendent Dr. Cissy Perez on Student Voice, Counselors,  https://t.co/GB6QIBdrDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed back home to be a tourist for a change. My trips home are usually so jammed pack with work and catching up w… https://t.co/bPWdEi49n9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AustinMcbroom and @CatherinePaiz are you guys going to introduced the new chef to us ? Them meals be looking so damn good on snap 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briellejoness @iamErica_Mena That’s a beautiful picture. Thanks for sharing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had charisma for days, y’all, bulked up real ocky, lightskin (and I don’t really fw lightskins but MY GAWD) and his… https://t.co/cmUvCeMYbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened yesterday. I just wish I had a better picture. #BananaPudding 🍌🥣 made with pepperidgefarm… https://t.co/mKXptpG6R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing @HillaryClinton slander Bernie on TV makes my blood boil. She lies as much as Trump and it’s infuriating. B… https://t.co/ujwwaz1BPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n7OngAsubS - Getting a clear picture of arabbers' role in city]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/DSIoG7NGfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#‘tistheseason thanks Joes new balance outlet #2teams1dream @ Cozy Abode https://t.co/0TxnxlJy2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_pryce @MacDowellRugby @bcplace @CanadaSevens Definitely got to get some time in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meus dias azuis na Califórnia ✨ em Santa Monica, California https://t.co/I8vEyKjeC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milesjohnson_78 @jacksonhardy12 @ChadSimmons_ @Mansell247 @chadmcheatham @RecruitGeorgia @Coach_McCorkle @DartFootball Congrats Miles!! 🏈🎉🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinzelalderson I’VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING RAMI HAS BEEN IN BESIDES BORHAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriGreiner So far Alaska has been my favorite... Italy is my next trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GizellaGerics1 @gabryluce @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @mich_onelove @Jose93571656 @consuiglesias… https://t.co/1VnI3k6PHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renee_engle @TheTickleFox @AmposCampos @SpooksandChills @LemmeDoodis @MichaelZatylny @ChubbahBubbah @JoBella8… https://t.co/NFz32ll4pG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are NoChill Earpers are FAMILY we are here and We stay #FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccatmpt @Julianna_glass @CaththeWineLady @thatsVeryKari @AkronWineGuru @SashaEats @Cbp8Cindy @FionaMorgan79… https://t.co/z5Tb0mvait]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending a relaxing night off work catching up on my friend's delightful show. Bookmark this for later if you haven… https://t.co/YWGtrbhDin]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jwOgi7fMuF    Were the dogs quarantined and then brought to Ontario or ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this community that we love let’s ensure that all voices are heard and respected - let’s ensure that every leade… https://t.co/Rx78dS2b5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally going to plan SO MANY things to do with my mom when she’s better!!! I want us to have a packed fun spring and summer 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter and her bandmates got an Excellent on their #MPA practice  #SicklesHighSchool #band #clarinet #music]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exciting that we can rebuild neuropathways in anyone, not just neurodiverse people (though this is very exc… https://t.co/tBDcWIfuNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emo hours bc all my homies r home for spring break and I won’t see them till May :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to join us tonight! We are excited to have National Dance Teacher of the Year, @per4mers4change share… https://t.co/w848bz0Wjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jowrotethis I tried recently and ooof. There’s an ep where Aziz tries to woo Ann by wearing her down repeatedly. And it’s not good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my man dropped me I wouldn’t even be mad lmfao I’ll shoot them gators boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaijiTang And.....sometimes Anna Nicole Smith, but we don’t talk about that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[57. Через несколько дней там пройдёт церемония вручения премии Джуно - самая престижна канадская музыкальная премия… https://t.co/NbsxAeckLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited #accwbb is on TV so I don't have to listen to Stephen A yell nonsense as if shouting somehow makes you m… https://t.co/q1pWdqS8ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabetthh12 You are God's version of beautiful, just as He intended you to be. Always.know.this. I love you baby girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scomorrison @eaepanthers @JTaime_Lyons Did you hear one of the 3rd grade Ss say that today was magic?🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISUCaitLamm Got an update at our county tonight.  Good work. Tough road ahead in Story Co.]]></document></documents></author>