<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@meijer - 26 lanes available and you have 3 lanes open!  We would use self- checkout lanes but limited to a max num… https://t.co/ttYvjMY4Tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Leafs caught #VegasBorn scrambling in their own end a bit and Morgan Rielly buries one to put Toronto up 4-3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger So, because  she’s a woman, she should be immune from stories outlining what a spectacularly bad boss/human being she is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReddVencher @PCribbett @SteveMcRae_ @zypisfy @CingetoOfBelgae @zapher134 @selgowiros @Cern_lXXl @PolyRhuagh… https://t.co/7PxIXSJNcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19… https://t.co/CplqqZE7pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retirarse con dignidad a la soledad o quedarse a pelear por nada seguro]]></document><document><![CDATA[working in a prison 4 days a week already seen some fucked shit ready to b home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BossesMemphis @geoff_calkins I’ll be in at 12 to mess with my BMI, John.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIMSJ @dtcahh @BreakingNLive I still have reservations about Trump but I’m leaning strongly to voting for him.  He… https://t.co/XvmvuN9sKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, everything is turning in terrible circles right now thanks to Trump and his Republican lovers.  Just got to pl… https://t.co/ZXoASbdrIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yU2QnwMb0C   @realDonaldTrump ‘s decision to declare a national emergency over the border issue might… https://t.co/D08ZsziFnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only punch I saw thrown was from that crumb bum Ibaka. Lebronto still having its effects on the raptors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I volunteered for Tammy Baldwin's first Congressional race. I crisscrossed the state on a gubernatorial campaign an… https://t.co/Kf57sZJc9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 @steelers Steelers gonna suck now lol my browns about to spank dat a$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never listen to it’s the remix to ignition hot and fresh out the kitchen mama rollin that body got every man… https://t.co/EQpkXl6NEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anabur We outlived Video Update, which I owed them a movie from college, and never got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont fear the Green New Deal.  I fear what would happen to the planet if we dont pass the Green New Deal. #GreenNewDeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be it’s final form. I digitalized my mantis drawing and made an “ok” header! Everything is on par to wh… https://t.co/2o8ZhfTBqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeells I didn’t see another account say this but I hope you’re having a good night, pal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[after finishing my midterm yesterday, i realized it was my last ever. i'm starting to realize i only have a few wee… https://t.co/ZacXjhIXl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamCrushin101 @JustinThomas34 @JBHolmesgolf @PGATOUR What a pep talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstockelman @pauldehnerjr That’s a monster improvement. The Excellence of Execution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Kyrgios is like a sleepy bear, looks nice and 😎 but then... You don’t want that SMOKE #acapulcoopen #atpacapulco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyJennings @elenigiorgos @ParisBienert @BmoreCityDOT Trash removal, police response times, DPW attention, the q… https://t.co/YcRz80wixW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyKnight_1991 I just checked this out and it's awesome! An absolutely brilliant tool, that eliminates confusion w… https://t.co/tcqgChpyBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pete_Denno @BigAndjSchwartz @DHolla24 @JCTweet2 @arappeport If you managed to lose 24k, then you're better off wit… https://t.co/WyTIESydKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @greggutfeld Can we have a 2 inch thick porterhouse and a pound of bacon? Good dog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Uma das minhas fotos favoritas. Transmite o nosso sentimento. Tempo em que ainda carregávamos nossos filhos no… https://t.co/fAD7exXynu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could ink #stevenuniverse characters all day. Kind of relaxing. @ Akron, Ohio https://t.co/BDLWqdBf2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBohannon89 @KuraFire @gaywonk @AOC Framing it as popular makes it a popularity conflict, red vs blue. Conflict me… https://t.co/BAVG93VfTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This $AMZN argument on CNBC is comical. A very short-sighted decision on the part of NY imo. Politically fueled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gio18___ @jess_mascilli It depends on the mood, I typically prefer smooth but occasionally crunchy smacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heroldbarton @BrownieJohnston @RasnawatiR @HumbleIndian @debratankersle1 @CristinPereyra @zara_yasmeen27 @Zafar193… https://t.co/kvhri5C7GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew4duval That’s not been my experience. But I’ll also be thankful at this time on 3/19.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDogg Or Actually ask him how it felt calling that reporter a piece of shit on TV, best shit ever in my opinion...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hays101 @camero_19 @jay_mcknight365 @plainwildcatfan What??? Statmy buried. We will see you on March 2nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonGordon11 Imagine the power when one realizes that a) regardless of the # of followers that they do have influen… https://t.co/0iNG1viGDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erskinedaniel @VirtualUnwinds @steph93065 @AOC Often at work I go walk around the building just to get out and cle… https://t.co/XBhEnJ1IJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobEccleston I hate you. Everywhere I look I see the stupid bitch lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRobinsonNJ seen this &amp; thought of you https://t.co/5QGXQp7Jb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbound by Antonio P Bezerra  Antonio P Bezerra  https://t.co/fsyOhrTNVQ @BNBuzz @Google @AmazonKindle @AppleBooks… https://t.co/K1sCYkzqiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The economy improved tremendously during obama administration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.  . .  . "If you succeed in this business, it's going to be You who creates that success, not me. And, if You fail… https://t.co/FytAhYReGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah  "Candidate's son testifies that his father knew about election fraud risk in North Carolina"  https://t.co/AL5gxaiYrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone at the Tucker Center #seminoles vs #Wolfpack today ? I mean the lack of enthusiasm in the stands is only… https://t.co/wX6q10MuNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[....3:51am and Apple 24hr. store with bud (John Strobelight, thank God he accompanied me...this is annoying not to… https://t.co/pyBdpqnjaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAChristakis @HarvardChanSPH I love the fluid, diagonal contradiction to the rectilinear shelves.  Subverting the… https://t.co/6wXASLtmAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluRadioCo Néstor : Uribe no es Fuente de derecho, recuerda que el prefiere la motosierra y el falso positivo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FungalDoc @sebpoule @ShohamTxID We all bring something to the table. There are no Infectious Disease Physicians at… https://t.co/ijZzsUBq4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9to5toys @9to5mac The promotional code you entered cannot be applied to your purchase. 2GCU6SAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Felix art fair at the Roosevelt Hotel in Hollywood. The Startup Art Fair LA was far superior. This appeared a l… https://t.co/iqGqC0Rg61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsGladysKnight @TPAIN Congratulations 2u Gladys! Inspiration can be ageless! Love u and Thank u!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIIDeaton @doggymama555 What a beautiful child! Father God, I join others in asking for your mercy and healing. I… https://t.co/oXXB7wUjQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once more, with feeling:  You did it Arizona!!! Congratulations to you (and us!) Everyone’s better off (even inside… https://t.co/pLUT4maLfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin I'll be him for a couple of seconds find the tallest building and walk off the roof...... No more Bill Douche Bag Maher👏👏👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMSpinharney @NEStatePatrol My first thought, too. By the body length, I was thinking 60's Cougar. But the "taillights" say Mustang to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masonmbb Big win over Richmond last night got caitlin_d_kennedy all like @ EagleBank Arena https://t.co/rF2Dum1umL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Now, now, Mr Prez, you know that’s completion of repair work on existing barrier approved and fund… https://t.co/YQ7OgUx9Zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrezaian He looked evil back then he looks evil now! He is the garbage of this planet]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw Alita Battle Angel tonight and it was a lot of fun! There were some parts that felt lame but man, those battl… https://t.co/aCNr8XfPpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeelinMadden @freepressfree @BernieSanders Trust but verify are good words to live bye...If I were Our POTUS it would be my mantra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_David_Edward @_David_Edward , your not the one who has to mature nor been heartless.  🗡]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nicky D's Coney Island in Sterling Heights, MI https://t.co/Zr5ygIcpO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAILMANTAZ Yes they sold out quick. Yet sometimes the city shirts pop in a few days later online. If not, gonna make one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bittenapple @FACTmag The Bronx Hiphop museum😎  With lots of tax payers money? Or is this an LLC? Who funded it?… https://t.co/5wn5diMH4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins Well it’s Huntsville, so the odds are 40 percent Bama, 40 percent Auburn and 20 percent Tennessee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulLeeTicks Does anyone know the name of the investigator?  It was left out of thecsites that I read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I start to get sick at the end of the weekend? I'm ready for this fun week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewCreasman @BSNRockies Yikes, kinda think Philly overpaid for Harper......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried out Top Golf for the first time gotta say it was extremely fun and definitely will become a usual activity in my life 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_m_Mitchell @APinv @Marcuskingband Great showing of nerves and determination...CONGRATS to you and Pete !! You bo… https://t.co/zwTVL98cpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfg1010 @SacramentoKings @Bucks No I’m not but definitely watching 🏀 2 of the most exciting teams Giannis, Fox so much star power]]></document><document><![CDATA[👻 📸 ammobambino 💻 @JeffTexas210  #jefftexas #sanantonio #satx #artist #musician #rapper #rap #hiphop #hiphopartist… https://t.co/ulpgynbz31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Assuming each of the children we hear from (Ivanka/Don Jr./Eric) is good for half as many lies as dad,… https://t.co/BVYiyTAgua]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll see you down at WesBanco at 12pm and 6pm for some Women’s and Men’s MEC Tournament action. #TopperNation… https://t.co/ytvzoM5crR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for folks to #tweet that #CoreyGraves cheated on his wife with #Carmella in order to get #fired so he can go to #AEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moshe makes an important point - to eschew spherical cows radiating milk isotropically - and avoid abstractions tha… https://t.co/nyZIcTetAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vuichalla Black Panther - - - - https://t.co/xrEzWKK18g - - -  #upcycle #luxury #repurpose #gabrieldishaw… https://t.co/W9aOlvd7BM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaganAmery @HailSaganBand I’m sure you rocked your birthday in your own fashion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BecketAdams @mikiebarb Are we already calling this resolution against Trump’s hatred.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PimaMens_bball freshman standout Rashad Smith, who led the Aztecs with 21 points in the regional semifinal win ov… https://t.co/8lNiG9VZ7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manuel39503599 @YouTube Very sad!!!!! Cal. is helping illegals with housing food and medical but turn a blind eye… https://t.co/E3Q6wfbq9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews @JxhnBinder  MORE F-ING TAX MONEY BING PISS AWAY THANK U SHITFUL DEMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Austin, TX? View our latest opening: https://t.co/EkfMyuQkl8 #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forzaquattro77 @benshapiro I would support a UN peace keeping coalition in Myanmar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton just told Cassie it’s her at the end of this!  Show’s over! #TheBachelor 🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaileyCeleste i’ve has my camera since my high school photo courses i’m waaaay too broke to upgrade but like. bein… https://t.co/HPk87Fvbyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[(1 of 4) We are excited to announce that FTCSC is establishing the Franklin Central Wall of Fame!  The inaugural cl… https://t.co/t6HlpoSjMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeidiXOX0 @MikeStuchbery_ He wasn't there. The number of men keeps changing, please refer to you talking points me… https://t.co/bepaOzaZid]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite four-letter word! #sold #getutah #garythompsonteam #utahrealtors #utahrealtor @ Brigham City, Utah https://t.co/OBglgcsM7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks, apologies about the technical issues with the #On24 webcast platform today. I am commit to post the full web… https://t.co/Kxs6swCuhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveusesthis Tag champs and a Mania match was their first year.  Maybe they should have stayed on Raw instead of g… https://t.co/sbP8KXkbmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The recently reopened and absolutely spectacular @VillaRoyale_PS in #PalmSprings! 😍 I think I have a new favorite!… https://t.co/pRqxVj3NV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muse concert tonight. 3rd time to see them. @ American Airlines Center https://t.co/OjOLLB3To8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesireeRolando MIS ORACIONES POR TU SALUD Y ROGANDO CON MUCHA FE QUE TODO SALGA BIEN 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[They already have LGBT ministers. Today will decide whether they have to remain in hiding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The psychology version: I find your latent variable structural equation model to be properly identified.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cookvascular @sternvascular @AorticCenter @VascularSVS @monteromiguel @basil_trials @profawbradbury @FDADeviceInfo… https://t.co/fuX1Pvn83R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious as to why @jinglebex and @careyshook both favorited this... Y'all don't follow high school sports 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSE: Saturday March 9, 2019 From 12 - 4 PM 21401 Dahlia Court, RSM, CA  Immaculate 4 bedroom, 3 1/2 bathroom… https://t.co/w9mbWUkUrY]]></document></documents></author>