<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Listen to the newest episode of my podcast, Fundraising Secrets Show: Episode 44 7th Grade https://t.co/k1r3dfx9Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzBell3 A few cool things about this. First, what an amazing library that a.) invited me, an artist, to come talk… https://t.co/CWGSZHRZwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other night casey said “when I get up in middle of the night to change a dirty diaper I’m going to come across… https://t.co/IR8KTGSE0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilith2u @Communista2 @bunkybun @Antiwarcom @codepink @ajamubaraka @brucedixon @KittyBhagat @MikeStuchbery_ Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#God should always be In Capital G. He’s the Creator of the Universe. Father #God is a Large #God. He’s not a Small… https://t.co/8Ndo3AFeOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheilaJ197088 @fawfulfan Disagree.  Numbers of white women have made accusations with no justice.  Weve all heard… https://t.co/NBgl5xZUL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @ten24get That's not senility; he just doesn't give a shit about her--or women in general.  How oft… https://t.co/S1pWAUZwQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriCat @chrissadeghi I'm trying to remember what the box looked like...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BawlingStevn @SenRickScott @FLOTUS Haha...Flat Tits now thats a good one. Real funny. Leave your 80 year old Mom t… https://t.co/4IowZqJea8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cherrysss #rollingstones #weedtray #tray #stash @ Cherry Smoke Shop https://t.co/w8fQyQ3qVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraB16901827 Thank you dear friend. Much love &amp; many hugs. God Bless! 😘😘😘❤️🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stat_man__steve @ArmenSaryan Thanks Stat Man Steve! I was so star struck talking to @OnAirKB @DrewOlsonMKE and… https://t.co/fMuyheNVxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[the weirdest flex is when you’re clearly in the hospital and post a picture of it on social media]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and practice some heart opening poses with me this Saturday morning at 8:15am at Gold's Gym (Falls Church, VA)… https://t.co/dN45k3LPps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be such a beautiful soul that people crave your vibes 🦋💙  Have a wonderful weekend!  What’s popping? . . Hat by: ja… https://t.co/oZo1zyFWlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @elpichirilo with get_repost ・・・ Hoy 6:30pm y mañana 2pm @rfdtvamerican #rodeoamericano aquí en @attstadium… https://t.co/hE1VYDLGP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise Against Hunger @Rise2030 emergency meal packaging event is happening TOMORROW @Littleton_HS at 10:00 AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeesaRaaum @Shadz66Shadz6t6 @SmasherTrump @LucyHoneychurch I will never understand why people think socialism will… https://t.co/1kFZtVYRjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hardly @ my desk so this was a sweet surprise! 🥰 https://t.co/VPDXjfkhP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s true.  T = LOVE If you’re lucky enough to be in my life it’s because you are important to my happiness and I l… https://t.co/sFDNzd0OKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This idea comes to you, you can see it, but to accomplish it you need what I call a "setup." For example, you may… https://t.co/xbjOvgiGrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_MacCrindle I was just thinking about this other day and was thinking we needed to start to switch that up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s amazing! Thanks for your professionalism, talent and support for students and programs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me in every way. Post it please. No ones going to pay attention to that. You’re “crooked mouth” is going to… https://t.co/TLL1eVjSL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[75% of sorghum grain goes to export markets! @waynetim #AdvocatingAgriculture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great stuff on the Young Money podcast ep today, especiallyfor women 👌🏾@DasarteYarnway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ratioed: When the ratio of replies exceeds the retweets and likes combined.  If a tweet goes above 2:1, you’ve writ… https://t.co/ga85S63L0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kckfitschools I just got out of the movie. It was the superhero movie I have been missing. #MarvelousMsLoughlin]]></document><document><![CDATA[So pathetic. She doesn't know which way to go, worship God or worship the underworld. in the dark, searching for th… https://t.co/SCkNh8pUtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston Nine counting part-time gigs when I was in school. Five since university graduation. None of this… https://t.co/LBq9xuO1V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Did you know substitute teachers get no health benefits, yet earn just enough to not get any help to pay them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two girls be tweeting all in love about the same guy! Ay hijas abran los ojos por favor 🤦🏼‍♀️😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well we made it to The Caribbean in KH and so far it's just been Elliot recoiling in disgust every time one of the… https://t.co/MzaN1MvSHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take this back because I bet if it was normal to submarine lisence at 16 and we casually all had submarines we wo… https://t.co/cjuwV3MWtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living your life with purpose could be the single most important thing you do. Find your purpose, find your life. ⠀… https://t.co/DSXjMabSOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this. At this point, you may as well just schedule an appoint. #thegrind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a game boy advance sp on amazon for $550. What in the actual fuck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tessa_estock @WNHSKey @WaukeshaNorth1 I wish - wrong Linden Grove.  We are in Waukesha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck to my youngest at the 43rd annual Keith Valley Challenge a 12 hour Hockey Tournament to raise money for t… https://t.co/dcbirdvLru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my #Birthday !!! Last year I got to spend my birthday week waltdisneyworld 🏰🎉🎁😍🎂🥰🧁🤩✨ #disney… https://t.co/eSOVQyOiME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocket Turtle wishing everyone a Happy Heart Day #CumulusNetworks #LoveIsInTheAir https://t.co/lun3v30SKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the most wholesome thing i have ever seen. retweeting so i can learn to crochet my worries away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone will say what should’ve been done or what they would’ve done...until it happens to them. Game changer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doctor_PMS It taste like pot roast juice- but I get it. It took forever for my mom to drink it. Good luck. Anxiety… https://t.co/vLFd65YhV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignore the bags under my eyes while I chase the BAG! Never been afraid to hustle and make some shit happen NO MATTE… https://t.co/QGfVRijBZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 @Fahrenthold Guess he'll be having a lot more "executive time"!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle, you're low class, emulating your mentor and hero:  The Criminal Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherBM @The_Trump_Train If you only knew how stupid you sound. And all the characteristic, it's TRAITOR Trump. H… https://t.co/1FwNGtsuzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods For real she is te reason?! You big boy was with another women so many time that even… https://t.co/zQvnKi5R7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE watched movie. It was awesome girl. Ur the best. Go doctors to clear u up I want to see u Wrestle again. Love u Paige ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man next to me cracks his fingers in the scariest way I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I know what 3 movies everyone quotes the most themselves? I'm super curious.  Mine are: Joe Dirt, Nacho Libre, and Mulan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryTDunbar My thoughts? We need @ArlingtonDES to put these on all paint bike lanes that don't have parking. #PlatinumArlingtonVaBy2029]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using those Americans who suffered so much loss as political pawns to score punches against @Acosta who was pointin… https://t.co/BLOY5KAW59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Ask the land owners and citizens near the border. I have and it IS an emergency from their perspec… https://t.co/FQu6O3qwCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stanton_jones @SandwichJudge All the next level Midwest dudes @MurderBryan wants to get together only sire children Like This]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is breaking this morning for that 11yo girl taken way too soon. Thinking of her mother at this time ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of building up the social-emotional needs of our students. Middle school is hard but we love it and we lo… https://t.co/ip36gtcvU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markecianna @trin_j20 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/YF1hORfEgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenAttiah @ECMcLaughlin What do you think is the connection? It is odd, it is worrisome. Could Kushner's acquies… https://t.co/N8htNopGuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJTRANSIT Exhibit B: this bus circled  was 10 minutes late and rode right past us https://t.co/crHoVvvAEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in a relationship and I still hate/think Valentine’s Day is stupid 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbrownweather Oh did you mean only in Western MA 😬 😀?#Februaryvaca https://t.co/4cjes3W3Iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabers up for chnyst #bethesean @ Albuquerque, New Mexico https://t.co/VIi6NIDziE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_m_geezers took me to Atlantic City for my birthday. Our first stop was the Hard Rock Casino, which has been pret… https://t.co/v4WYUiYXJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarvsCount Haha. I know. But oh well, I think hindi talaga priority ni Coach Tai floor defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disscobisscuit cute!! lol please do whatever you did to yours to mine 🥺💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub OMG. Trump is this insidious virus that attacks all who have contact with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don't cry. I am here to wipe the tears from your eyes. Love is here with all understanding. I will not leave… https://t.co/fKlvwbtEsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npfallon Wondering if you e read Terry Pratchett? Vision Quest makes me think of my favorite Discworld book, Mort @clutchofficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenverTeachers Congrats 👊🏼 and THANK YOU for standing up for our students and their future. #DCTAStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StartupStudyhall @IamAStartupLady learning from  Caroline Dowd-Higgins @CDowdHiggins and Lisa Whitman. https://t.co/rit5avkaR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Flor De Mallorca @ Del Mar de Fabio Trabocchi https://t.co/P4mF1gVZG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryShannon @politvidchannel The military advisor does not belong there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewxsmith Available for rental on DirecTV but usually Vudu/prime have the same movies]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday! It’s time to get back to work-which means sitting for the most of you. So in honor of Chinese New Year… https://t.co/N7o90Dm5ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexasbunn @hollyvanreenen If Glenn doesn’t win I’m canceling Hollywood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DmitrisGalaxy Saw this yesterday and had the same thought...creepy, sick, nasty, yuck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go!!! Few spots left!!!!! @ Superior Fitness https://t.co/qg2kAf7Qgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polish_Ogre @alpacamybooks @PadmesLover @Eivor_DNaBC @RaeDeAnneR @snickelsox I advise you pour me another scotch chuckles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djseanblaze601 Nah na. I didn’t say all that. 🥴 they just not gon kill me for em. Period! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Def commission from them! I’ve gotten a few commissions from them and it’s always been excellent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the Bernie bots again and Russia helping Sanders plot once more for Trump! Haven't we played through this scene… https://t.co/MXjC44WtMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess I’m finally gonna hop on the GTA train with my friends🤣 need a break from DBD til some crap gets fixed. I’ll… https://t.co/ggMn30642U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Please pay attention to most Americans who understand increased border security, but believe  the wall… https://t.co/BbE1S5xNOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettgrant13 That’s the point, they’re only a couple hundred when they’re under 3!]]></document><document><![CDATA[allegedly perpetrated by his son.  WSBT filed a public record request for court documents after his 11-year-old son… https://t.co/iUAZ0b8U6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big fuck you to whoever took the last physics spot literally a minute before my enrollment period]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_Stands @hwmnylx69 @TeahCartel @ShelbyKStewart @kodiak149 @CajunBlueAZ1 @lovemyjessica22 @og_dbl_lo_g… https://t.co/NwGO1X99Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly, new hozier and vampire weekend in the same year?? god is good]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s simple. Work hard and be kind to people. Tell the truth. Include others, rather than exclude others. Communica… https://t.co/Zh53ysbHm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright I’m at work and someone in the room next to me is BLASTING emotional Christian music and SINGING ALONG shou… https://t.co/P1eGrGCZ2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasEDMFamily Insomniac wouldn’t put out a graphic that insanely boring 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beers300 @HippieVol @Shawn172510 @gr82btnvol @madsatan6969 @GTA_Redhead @DollyVol @Smokeyholler @gwoman9810… https://t.co/6FbqHYz9mK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@statboyslim @Me You still to this day have no clue what I ever asked you to order for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyLittleBloggie Thank you @MyLittleBloggie for this and for all the ways that you continue to touch lives with you… https://t.co/Xgw0pUY8jL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking Xfinity, Veteran hiring, Comcast Business, Economic Development and Rural Broadband at the annual… https://t.co/YasqQx8lRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @emilylathamxo because she's my only friend that actually listens to incessant babble about yee haw stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Officer Bo @HPDNC for supporting literacy through getting our students excited about reading mystery nove… https://t.co/rcFLAh2arh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win tickets to the Hammer's House Party Tour! https://t.co/ZFiaRrO86x]]></document></documents></author>