<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Images of toppled Confederate monuments: one compelling response to the Confederate monuments still standing.  Make… https://t.co/FeC16IDCe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those women wear silly rags got elected to Congress are so stupid makes me puke so conceited and smartass asswipes… https://t.co/eYloXixt21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeannkim @WCKitchen We will. We’ll get the first screening off the ground and then we’ll be out wide with it. Thank you. #Uncrushable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t move rows on the plane and then dump your shit in the middle seat… douchebag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dumbass just walked head first into a pole while on my phone. I just hope some people got a laugh out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i spent like 15 mins watching videos on that “hello i can come over right now” thread]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieLuckey @jbabybeautiful @SonOfGodAndMan @danifknbe If you truly wanted me to sleep comfortably you would tel… https://t.co/PAgq40mjQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for a awesome 👏🏼 day ❤️  🏃 🚴  🏊‍♂️ @ Pasadena Triathlon https://t.co/nrhy08aF5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was probably the most natural promo she's had since she's been there.  Alright what's up with this tag team ma… https://t.co/avlsEDzQLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomIncorrect @lauren_hoggs “Don’t think gun laws would evoke comfort.”  Yes ... Yes, they would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCSpurs1882 @THFC_Rob16 100% going to be 💩it when Dortmund score after 8 mins tho ..... haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuanceBro @PoliticalKathy Hard to get elected that way in this climate. 90% of republicans support the president.… https://t.co/cea5DMdPnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Après #snoweshoehike #comfortfood (@ Belwood Super Snax in Belwood, Ontario) https://t.co/ys3VdrH2yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrQuindazzi @peterbernstein2 @PearlMet @figue32bj @woodeneye69 @sgwade56 @tomwatson @RadioFreeTom With avg salary… https://t.co/gpHSSjHHUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Medley13 If you thought we had a friendship medley, that day is long gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂. Remember when his advisory cheated him and then he actually threw support at her?  This dude is a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COFightsBack @SenCoryGardner I wonder if he's not getting his check from Pakistan since he has come out against th… https://t.co/vq6LtnaB0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoucheVictorino You have to be in Canada in order to get it. Sorry pal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel05459666 @John_Wayyne @Jimmy_Stick @dpakman @PrisonPlanet @DonaldJTrumpJr Comparing a nation’s border to a hom… https://t.co/8dyfA9t8XL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired anew by @SenRhondaFields  at #CO Black Round Table in #Aurora. #copolitics https://t.co/eQRFT86zpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicsluo I feel like this was a missed opportunity for the Gilla-Band]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleymcnamara Books: Innovator's Dilemma; Crossing the Chasm; and Outliers.  Blogs: Tim OReilly (Radar); Pando; T… https://t.co/nCHMx0GiHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who do not learn from our human history will be doomed to repeat it. We learn history in periods, decades, ye… https://t.co/Qd1CYzFxeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scalzi Checked out a new copy of The Consuming Fire from the library (loved it) and my dog got ahold of it. You ca… https://t.co/79DupdTI55]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Austin: light rain, 59°F 63% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1023mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just love selfie’s lol @ Margate, Florida https://t.co/Ih9uY8rDiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buena noche y mejor platica con mi gran amigo @marcelo_grcia   #Friends #Saturday #CraftBeer #Metapatio #Beers… https://t.co/yh6iZmWjiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/dJWSGfockg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrick_oshag If someone is wise enough to really have an edge in something —  Do they tweet it out? 🤫  Or, is— wh… https://t.co/IUAmIjnfvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rejoice always, pray without ceasing, give thanks in all circumstances; for this is the will of God in Christ Jesus… https://t.co/QdzQsAg0YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiNarcotics2 😂😂😂 Kiki likes getting her back broke in. Maybe it’s pleasurable for the receiver, but for the givers it’s pretty trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulv48 @Tesla @elonmusk @elonmusk @Tesla seriously??? Wtf is wrong with you guys.... this is ass-backwards to be doing this to us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravusHertl @WuuUuuThuevos @hellofromthecry @atrainzzz @PapaJawnz @chiweethedog @king_felix5 @ogwieny @LeonardCowalski yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH I LOVE YOU IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE UNDER TRUTH GOD AND TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST. MY LEGAL HO… https://t.co/EVQ66FKttg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FookThis I love that song you dont see me that is played in the movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t lose weight at the moment. I’m at the point where I’m just trying to avoid adding any extra pounds  ... bec… https://t.co/RXP9YhBM5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saturday_Parlay @BarstoolGamblin The home team is getting points you say? 🤔🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD "I don't blame people for their mistakes, but I do ask that they pay for them" --failed mega attraction park owner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was summer ‘16 like everyone’s prime year cus that’s what it feels like]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJWILD7 @BeeZired @SantaPatriot @MJ33929126 @truthseekerd @HudMagy @beer_parade @222714ftw @Justanothersme1… https://t.co/4bvg8J6jXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angryscotsman81 I ditched Zelda in favor of it the month it dropped. No regrets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasThighs Courtney Ann wasn't a bit nippy &amp; cold last night...???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperChesse Cómo Siempre La Prensa Amiga Viendo Otro Partido Del Monterrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[They will equivocate minutiae from Dems with treasonous lies and criminal hypocrisy from Republicans. They will rep… https://t.co/AbUsQr3l59]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Magnificent Manhattans:  1) beholderindy - they make their own vermouth. 2) geraldines_indy - gorgeous bar.  3) a… https://t.co/0MjOGnvxXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[18 kill solo game in Fortnite   There’s a good chance I just ran into 18, 11-year-olds, BUT I haven’t had a game ge… https://t.co/hExED47pgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the headlines @espn had there.  Look today it's nothing like news. It's very little news and all opinion pi… https://t.co/cG158wfd7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tveitdal Yes, the CO2 produced would increase overtime with this estimate, but the consumption of meat and other a… https://t.co/YMccMPtJxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday The lying president is full of bullshit.  He undercuts everybody to sway popular opinion over to his sid… https://t.co/UExstiZwrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giannis stroking threes now gives me so much hope in this bucks team and him as the MVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot today was physically mark your head with if you’re a dumbass day]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the many reasons Lemieux is my all-time favorite Penguin.  The man is, truly, #LeMagnifique.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyDorr2 @LeFloJames @undisputed @ShannonSharpe Weird cuz he won one in cle and he ran back here]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, at golden corral: wow I’ve literally stuffed myself with so much food.  my failing organs:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jchodge10 You talking about this era??? You and @jd410berry rocked this 2014 Halloween party...no one knew who you were. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I throw that new @2chainz on cause my dude suggested it and 2 chainz in 2 dollar bill goes “I’m rare like mr clean… https://t.co/fneHkr78lF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@License2CarryTX @Jeffery4Pi @GrandpaSofa @AiG Well you see when two people love on another or perhaps in your case… https://t.co/mbXfNqlS4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #1 queen im rooting for on drag race! Fucking kill it @plastiquetiara ♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cesarfaz @Antonia35623148 Estos gobernadores es la resaca que nos dejó el largo periodo de borrachera despilfarrad… https://t.co/wTwuUC5P4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up about 1” of new snow on the West Jordan Bench. Gusty NE winds causing a single digit wind chill. Temp is… https://t.co/YFuuQT6PSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you https://t.co/b4gUxUOx0b for this feature about our @YouTube talk show #TwoBestiesTogether! We’re both wor… https://t.co/ciPnZN0JsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us - if you attend this event, I promise you will be inspired and feel a profound sense of renewed hope… https://t.co/y8FXymWz3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman Trump has contempt for everything and anyone who does not or cannot directly benefit himself. #UnitedNations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Championship meet another medal stand.  Congrats Reagan on the  600m bronze at MA All-State, a PR and quali… https://t.co/nCPCUEdkPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when they can’t break a hundred dollar bill, like what the fuck ya got in register if ya ain’t got no Money in it LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanessaMarie_87 @lukeprusinski @hgtv @morgan_willett @CastleHouseJT Thanks love ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great piece about my first favorite actor. Gone, but never forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy es viernes 1° de marzo. Amanecimos con un poco de nieve ❄️ en Nueva York.  ¡Bienvenida sea la nieve! ❄️ #snow #NYC #delayedopening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a single indictment of the people you mention, are directly involved in collusion implicating Trump.  Blindness… https://t.co/bcu6cNYIRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado Rocky Mountain High  https://t.co/aErpPyz02R  #jimmyutah #roadtripping #denver #colorado #bobseger #blog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the conditions of our county routes, Wabash City Schools will be operating on a 2 hour delay for Monday, Feb… https://t.co/pipNEy1Nwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, Bagley and Giles are great together.  But don’t forget that WCS has been an important player for the Kings.  I… https://t.co/BQ0BCbPQvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So all those listed of the people of Israel, by their fathers' houses, from twenty years old and upward, every man… https://t.co/89qWe3NWdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out on the third floor after CicLAvia last Sunday #GoProFusion #360video #360photo #TinyPlanet #DickHyman… https://t.co/r8CRzmJE8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XavierFiles @geneticghost Yeah man. I live in Columbus pretty close to the comics museum. Longtime member of the l… https://t.co/fV0TPvaz5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look at old messages and be like wow, I really am the coolest/dopest bitch to ever do this shit and y’all really… https://t.co/X26PyFyXXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joseph_johnson7 😇 @RockytopSports  @Mach1academyva @CoachSteveDBU @RivalsFriedman @coachscott33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deborahcrainlaw @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump And then he lied today!  What a disgusting human being. I'm in NYC… https://t.co/ovMTXGZlEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katalin_pota @banditelli @1Sychronicity @marcorubio @TwitterSupport No shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbcuddigan @RaymondArroyo Be sure to check out Frenchmen St in the Marigny and see a show at Snug Harbor!  ⚜️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took this earlier today #fireinthesky #cloudslikecottoncandy #naturesbeauty #samsungnote9 #samsungphotography… https://t.co/D5m7ptgVIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems to me like the Democrats are turning on Robert Mueller. Threatening to sue if he doesn't say what they wan… https://t.co/ghT4txIHUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon @TripleH @WWERoadDogg @ChynaJoanLaurer @TheRealXPac @ShawnMichaels @RealBillyGunn I hope the NWO gets… https://t.co/8ZzlWu5tTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them social security retirement checks are coming real soon!  😂 JK  Happy Birthday!  Still my favorite from ICE T..… https://t.co/l3rXZc1WoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_R_Berna @garway95 @KamyMAGA @AW95NJ @krunalley @BS76571 @Lisette_72 @PatriotAdjuster @NOMERCY604… https://t.co/hho9geWNn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontanaGrizFB @Utah_Football @coach_fifitaISU @DarrenUscherBSU @CoachCherokee @CoachLesMiles @ISUMattCampbell… https://t.co/WT72zeB0H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @nytimes @washingtonpost @CNN @MSNBC Donald Harris, Jamaican. Wow! Thank goodness. I was in Jamaica… https://t.co/101qzxRsUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[HS gameday is here, good luck to all the players I’ve worked with over @TripleCrownBSG, relax and have fun playing your game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Money is the wealthy man's curtain which hides all his defects from the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with little man #godfather @ Freeland, Michigan https://t.co/VYRe4TbScS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Far Cry: New Dawn team on the launch today! Incredible what you guys managed to produce in such a short time. Go buy it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 They have NO  MORAL compass! They  thrive on destruction! The lowest form of rationale is there base… https://t.co/Dm0SgbE3k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this isn't a National Emergency, I don't know what is one. The illegal immigrants are over flowing the border. T… https://t.co/HcDEVlUHXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @MichaelCohen212 The Milli Vanilli of @FoxNews speaks https://t.co/RMfCUVFlVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[hallmarks of a highly-functional team: clear communication about operational needs and shameless taunting with rega… https://t.co/QfTNHNM1B1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Again. And again.  Each time I see @mothermother I think of the first time I saw Mother Mother live. I thought… https://t.co/G1Yy3EHjLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattiaGarder @StormIsUponUs They all have that goofy little child sounding California millennial “uptalking” thing… https://t.co/wen8VrUvc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speakers from Kraft, Hersheys, and King’s Hawaiian kicking things off.   Conversation topics include the muchies an… https://t.co/3mkdzwuGg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with white libs in Baltimore metro area isn't that they are "privileged ", it's that most are dillitentes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone listen to this Ass Of Congress AOC. What a joke she is.  She must be from Uranus]]></document></documents></author>