<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[First round of NSAA Tournament 🏀 No. 4 Dickinson State 🆚 No. 5 Valley City State ⏰ 7 p.m. MT 📍 Scott Gym 📻 KDIX 123… https://t.co/Vj5OG0ucc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to subway and used a coupon to try to save money BUT now I’m at Jacks buying a large milkshake... it’s called balance 😌🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConsumerReports Thanks for the article. Will definitely by talking with my Doctor about this medication.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary I joined because of @jeff_gluck and NASCAR. I… https://t.co/R79pzhSYvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[An affirmative thought 💭 is 💯 times more powerful than a negative 👎 one #celebration #celebrationoflife… https://t.co/xBzCasMjKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does it mean you’re pretty if someone just assumes you have a boyfriend? https://t.co/pzd2NjMgRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do english professors always seem to have a “holier than thou” attitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessSullivan57 @TheTylerMount @bonitanita16 @WowYessi @arunramchan @D_Money_B2 @JeremyKramer1 Awesome stuff! 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Happy #Humpday we are #Open! Join us for #Lunch #Downtown #PDX #GetSomeLove ❤💛💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop of course you didn’t! Does she have an elegant plaque reading “give me your macarons”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA GOP had two years to investigate these allegations and did nothing. No investigations into trump or any… https://t.co/8Y2D1yun76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock @Forensicman @Kelly @Katamac1967 @pleasure_ryland @shelley_bean60 @AuntTritsy @louisanamom… https://t.co/M2lam9GxbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skyessong She is an an attention junkie willing to say, or do anything to get an attention fix. And...she's a deplorable creature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the opportunity to present on personal branding to the Lowe’s Women in Leadership @Fressh727!… https://t.co/KchJVs3twq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maureenhommagm1 Please follow me and I will follow back. I care and I share😊💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller won’t be intimidated!  He has got all the info. You and all your GOP thugs are going to jail.… https://t.co/Z26NB1nCTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinskyleigh These evangelical #individual1 followers are really delusional- worse than the followers of David Koresh in Waco TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmiliaSykesOH @OhioGabe What a beautiful portrait of you (and of blue and of car)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all voting today keep safe stay safe and most importantly  vote to make Nigeria great again #GoOutAndVote #NigeriaDesides2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir And the love continues! #futuristic #bops https://t.co/J7HzpuY11w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii What a lovely way to say goodbye. Or, until we meet again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonton Soup with Bok Choy 🍲🥟 . Have you tried any new recipes or ingredients this year? Let me know below! 👇  If yo… https://t.co/o2LUnW4HPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefjoseandres @WCKitchen Bless your hearts. 🙏🏼👨🏻‍🍳🍛💛💙❤️ #Venezuela #ChefsForVenezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petermrugg This doesn’t add much but couldn’t help it: https://t.co/RdlzIGjJoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After last nights’ wins Skyline Lady Tigers and Skyline Tigers advance to Class 2 State Quarterfinals!!!🏀🏀🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Applebee's Grill + Bar in Farmingville, NY https://t.co/DqUzdg3wZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightingOwlsHCC I was waiting for Coach Lee to get in the middle and 2 step 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @GOPLeader @RandPaul still waiting what instructions you were all given by Putin Last July 4th.......… https://t.co/BIfkVeOQpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple of my guy friends tell me every time they come to visit that I need to be “a good wing woman”   Have I eve… https://t.co/9BbslGk1RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[They don't need your money those who are generous will forever be. Even in abundance some people still lack .....it… https://t.co/jzkDE8ECbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to unfortunate circumstances, I’m annoyed with every aspect of life. Please don’t talk to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Operation Gratitude (opgratitude) with my Miss District of Columbia sister 🤗 Thank you @thecruise for the photos! —… https://t.co/gk6r7qXWbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @DineshDSouza @jguaido Brave man. God be with him and the ppl of Venezuela 🇻🇪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barkbox Ivy and Lyla. Best rescues ever!!🐶❤🐕#loveyourpetday https://t.co/iOGL8h0wZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill I had a bright yellow Panasonic tape recorder that I used to tape songs off the radio on Monkees reru… https://t.co/vSzy91wyxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk You are both idiots. Someone composed this tweet for you. SMDH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers: Leasons on Diversity in Tech @julieaelb62 @karlitaliliana and Mimi Fox Melton at… https://t.co/00zjRpWXC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheZombieJedi We accept the typo because at least you know how to drive.  Sincerely,  Idk not a fuckin idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great: Around 420,000 people, equivalent to roughly 60% of the city’s population, visited the library in its fir… https://t.co/Aj29GNwVLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that my grandparents flew to Washington to surprise me and I cried. I get to see them in 4 months for graduation 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA['This Is Not 2016': What People Don't Get About Bernie Sanders And Race   https://t.co/G0d9A69aaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TylerSkaggs37 and @debsmsoft for you generous donations to @StBaldricks! Fight #ChildhoodCancer… https://t.co/FhM5LsET9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My father was worth only the value of his house, give or take $100,000 more with $525,000-600,000. The value of the… https://t.co/wroNjoi3H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me realizing that 2019 holds a LOT of 5th anniversary celebrations for me and @Blomquist33 😍   •Introduced: 7.3.14… https://t.co/EnxhXtWDah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fly_Sistah @Patrickesque 1st, if like him to explain why 90% of VT AAs are incarcerated when they only make up 4%… https://t.co/QDLX9TSifP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenJeffMerkley for introducing this resolution to prohibit military intervention in Venezuela! I hope th… https://t.co/qx3eziaCLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pancakes Round #2 for @SMCDSB_MMO @moose995 @Muskoka411 @SMCDSB @SMCDSB_Faith https://t.co/kzwZzEdWtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeanwhileinCana Superficial material people who should really seek and find out about the youth who has had a posi… https://t.co/gimrYhWchO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzaalexander @Change In the Delta it is necessary to keep the Wild hog population down.. you are obviously a city… https://t.co/oJOGJonFio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DotWildly @amvetsupport I know what autonomy means, meaning I wasn't asking for a English lesson, it just didn't s… https://t.co/5yGAWkK01l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PodSaveAmerica Imagine if everyone got behind Bernie Sanders the way lemmings got behind trump. The snowball would roll regardless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @DrPenK ! We will surely feel your absence at BCPS, but @SumterSCSchools is getting a phenomenal le… https://t.co/q2uZ2aLVaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon I just subscribed! #doingmyparttomakehistory #FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for last night. Meeting you was the best bday gift ever. When I was in UT installing cancer machines. Pro… https://t.co/tp2Y4JWjDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will Super Bowl come back to Atlanta? City ‘interested' in return by 2027 https://t.co/pgMQhqQwKu https://t.co/nT5uEX74DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amjoyshow I am a total fangirl of @ElieNYC and @MalcolmNance and @DavidCayJ and @JillWineBanks and @sarahkendzior… https://t.co/ATLDwFCw3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNTonight @donlemon Happy Birthday Don! Peace love and happiness to you today and always!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how brave they were to learn new persuasive techniques and also a new tool that they can use!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been listening to this audiobook for like 6 hours straight what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a thing for dirty shoes since i was 10 love dirty men alike https://t.co/aQuyDowhAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off our @FlyTPA Valentines Day meeting with this sweet news: We served a record 21.3 million passengers in… https://t.co/qZvAXj3qr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyCar @IndyCaronNBC Woot! Woot!  We can hardly stand the wait! Please IndyCar don't be late!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pescatarian diet is pretty cool being that I love Cajun food anyways]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son still chooses to want to be a voice actor. It means he can even do it now if he wanted too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un día nos vemos y nos tomamos un brebaje divino en tu hermosa tierra! Va?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiantwanderin thank you so much for the follow! I love your website btw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl you look famous, like South Beach or Vegas. All up in the paper, in the supermarket aisle. That dress on you I… https://t.co/fzoGXLoXkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amid rent increase, San Francisco's only fortune cookie factory faces uncertain future https://t.co/LaAdoohwgC via @SFGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next evolution of Facebook? The newsfeed is dying - stories will replace how people get information. #SXSW2019 session with @stevebartlettsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter do your thing. Find these disgusting, repulsive and pathetic excuses for males. 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recibiendo regalos y mucho amor desde las 7:30 am, QUE TAL COMO VA SU DÍA??? ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to the love my life, my rock who I love with all my heart. You are a blessing to me and our f… https://t.co/3eV4L8bcM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Our lady girl pug and our hoping soon to be new puppy!! #AdoptDontShop https://t.co/QCX9wGWk8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Injustice at the mall..Minnesota Pastor: Mall Shook up: @FRCdc https://t.co/Dop5iKtjDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentally Challenged? This is what Angry liberals do. Insult people they don’t even know. Suburban White woman won y… https://t.co/IwyXoVQDlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[[MV] 이달의 소녀 (LOONA) "Butterfly" https://t.co/ZxbAkbQnzT via @YouTube THE SOUND! THE SAUCE! THE DIVERSITY! ALL HAIL LOONA!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse I don’t think sanders says anything worth listening too she’s just sucking up or off her boss   Nothing… https://t.co/KNyumAKWR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[School-wide drop everything and read! 💙 #ReadAcrossAmerica https://t.co/TEEX1mTH7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carabanana__ @carabanana__ lol omg haha 😂 I’m rolling 💀💀 and ily thanks for responding you’re my fav from the challenge !!!😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Queen of England, Queen Elizabeth II, that Ancient Serpent, the Beast, that smiley face enemy of humanity.  Unv… https://t.co/gbFIwweSQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump Decorum?!  Beyond his rude interactions with the press, has 45 ever looked into the pr… https://t.co/ZcVpMytSrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe if we tell people their brain is an app, they will start using it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @margaritateresa That should be a sign to @HowardSchultz that he should not run]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akaBruno @Madtarquin @beneubanks @JasonLauritsen @CyWakeman @mfaulkner43 “Others.” 👈🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[how much less man, who is a maggot, and the son of man, who is a worm!” https://t.co/gnrmE58bhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stankfunkmusic @LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes Criminals of the DEMOCRAT party https://t.co/mHjG5QCWdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are plaid shirts still cool? If I wear one do I like punk or country? I need help here. https://t.co/XrmgxB3r7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews You are the plantation owners worst nightmare! You're an intelligent, open minded, outspoken, black… https://t.co/tWw3UIjf6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually I don’t go for mirror selfies, but this thrift shop shirt is giving me all the feels. #🐱 #🦋 #kittenshirt… https://t.co/vlRGBttE8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before I took the quiz I was like “im miso” after taking the quiz, I am in fact miso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Yes! Go @SpeakerPelosi and @HouseDemocrats !!!!!!!!  We are behind you! Make calls to your Congressmen! Stop… https://t.co/2oqLzxzdTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelaceyF @CaucasianJames @cateryan4 I’ve lived in Mississippi my whole life and would be completely ok with it being wiped off the map.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's no crisis on Southern border we don't need no damn wall Trump's is being a spoiled brat didn't get his toy… https://t.co/LUjStsQd3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdMcque @PascoSheriff Locked up in Bowie, Md.  Sophie and Charlie are comfy and watching LivePd and hoping to see… https://t.co/OheUzeNTtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all want to save something? I hear the icecaps need help. Leave Detroit alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akbarb480 @realDonaldTrump F~CK THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE AND ANYONE WHO BELIEVES IN IT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcenemywithin loving this show. Very thrilling and a little scary. Love @Morris_Chestnut  much better than #FBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brimshack  This cute little guy showed up at the Nature Center this week ... he is early for the owl banding! https://t.co/n9CiiDkfyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USWNT @celinegounder @LeslieOsborne12 @MonicaRustgi I’m now a retired RN. I have enjoyed listening to both panel d… https://t.co/s05d2G0hNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtzNaturalle Come to Columbia, we got $10 Tuesdays. But for ya twins it’ll be $10 off each.]]></document></documents></author>