<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @WatchingWhatYou Crying in the fetal position on a small cell floor❓*LOL* 😎🇺🇸👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFOX7WX @fox7austin SonWedding2019 is over it can do what it like]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominicHarris8 @SantchiWeb @KiwiRowebot @OliverLewis @comingupcharlie Sounds like bad programming to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs @snowbunnyCdn I knew it would come to this. You just can’t have it both ways and that’s the collec… https://t.co/Kf7JLE7VZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[changing my discord picture to an egirl in the hopes of landing a sugar daddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaLang @RealDickTator try proof reading buddy when you’re out trolling tweets. 🤷🏼‍♂️ “Bring” or did you mean t… https://t.co/QxsmusHgCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones: Season 8 TRAILER (HD) 2019 https://t.co/utcXLMefWr via @YouTube   *chills  Fuuuuuuuuuck! I can’t wait! #GOT #ForTheThrone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoBearcatsFB @natehawk1ng ...check out my football highlights..https://t.co/EV8PUO5hDK c/o2020 https://t.co/PVdLFgQ7fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler #BeeeeeennnnnGahaaaaazi #Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents… https://t.co/vsXOV9MQIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGDornbush Holy Smokes! I just finished "The Coroner". I gave it a 5 star rating on https://t.co/ZbHsA9aP8b. I'm r… https://t.co/elZqB3gZ4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, maybe it's just me.  But I kind of feel that when one of your biggest rivals colors are green and white may… https://t.co/v9qOQu3bFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished my Cheese Flan, by the look 👀 I’m sure that it will taste very good. @ Nassau County, Florida https://t.co/7JNCmlQT81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielchipres Bro I remember you using that in English on Thursday, RIP😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized #AllMyChildren will be 50 next year! I hope the show comes back in some form for its 50th. I miss t… https://t.co/e7XrDD5g5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968 @Jr3597 @ChaliceGarden… https://t.co/IsoO6WiiO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winner of this game heads to Mt. Pleasant for state quarterfinal against winner of Alma and Flint Powers Catholic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any cowardly liberal would act like you. That's the price one pays for being a traitor to your own country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta, here I sit, in Detroit once again.   Sitting on a plane delayed over and over again. Zero crew on the plane… https://t.co/ou3BekoiGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[ya ya ya duke lost it does not count if zion wasnt in bolden is worst defender in college basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FaceToFace Comin soon!!! SPAM the comments with a "🌹🌹🌹" if you fckn wit it ... TAG who you can hear on this... 📈📈📈… https://t.co/qjiUuYnTXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cracka_23 @espn Greatness? That was in the 90s. This Clown can pad any stat he wants - means nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShauniBird @TSwiftNZMedia I’m gonna keep teasing you until you transcend time and space with your music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyArianeLee @mattgaetz How the hell did that happen?What school? Doesn’t say much for the school or Florida]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're 11-plus minutes into this game and the #Hokies haven't been called for a foul. With a short bench, staying ou… https://t.co/8jTYYyHUfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 This Tránsfuga piece of trash is a pure and simple IMBECILE MORON.-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRGWahus @MikeRinder I am being stalked and harassed by the Church of Scientology. I have been asking for help, bu… https://t.co/nyY9FdQh6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get instant billing at Verizon Customer Service 1-855-431-6111 #Verizonwirelesscustomerservice… https://t.co/C0e0kDUIpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely in awe of the work done by @Ali_Vetnar and Matt Bertram to make this piece happen. Ali is an incredibly… https://t.co/pS8BoAfgVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[J.B. and Na in the 8:43 am 3ball at the @APinv . 1) Feel sorry for Cink; and 2) are they testing @USGA rules 5.6, 6… https://t.co/M56hrbHY3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We’re all connected. We need to focus on the connections and not the differences.”  @PatriciaHeaton #RootsTech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogercee23 @RJalias @pkcapitol @tomgara Neither a bot nor a trump supporter, but I find the lefts love affair with… https://t.co/X27nFawOEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @EpochTimes Did Adam ever get charged for this ? https://t.co/5ahHANzJDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieYuTV I drive to Williamsport, Pa to tomorrow (400 miles round trip) to pick up Daughter 2 from… https://t.co/qqTzJsgvGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my form is off dammit but 375 baby ❗️  •  •  •  Health is wealth 🙏🏼 @ Retro Fitness https://t.co/SbSCWNxkXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Double Dry Hopped Melrose by @BeachwoodBBQ_LB @ Brew Kitchen Ale House — https://t.co/t6ImGgtILl]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenSchumer Climate change is real. It's happening. And it’s having real impacts in our communities. Now more than… https://t.co/r1aDvfoxmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you referring to the slavery of the Democratic Party? How many times the Democrats voted no for equal rights Am… https://t.co/VRA9xgRO9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my love  kdebrat12. Can’t wait to have some of this cake you made for us. @ Philadelphia,… https://t.co/GqLcue31jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vient tout juste de publier une photo à Jellyfish crudo+charbon https://t.co/TAGF6wTrNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see johnbcrist for the #humanbeingtour pardon the #creepyphotobomberintheback (get off your phone jlmencer… https://t.co/5raml099E6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdharm @shalomshuli Shuli!! Still got your bewitch shirt with your auto on.  Never worn and hanging in all its glo… https://t.co/YKcTA9V12l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so tired and stressed my coworkers notice it , and they don’t even know me . 😩🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really good with food. Really good by itself, too. - Drinking an Ice Day Arkansas Winter IPA by @lost40beer @ Big O… https://t.co/pRZ0tEyjRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDamage @Mattel Borderline for me because he actually got a push at one point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach, great points! I would also add, don’t let honest assessments be misconstrued as “hating”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherineQ Hope things get better for you soon. BTW, enjoyed my trip to your part of the world a couple of weeks a… https://t.co/fykf43WGs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lunes #QueTruene en bmxboxinggym en BMX Boxing Gym https://t.co/1RJd1BHP2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some lead by talking. Others lead by doing.  We do the latter.  Proud of @DowChemical and @JeffWoosterRS as we driv… https://t.co/xP916ytIna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @EdRollins Keep preaching it Lou Dobbs. They aren't getting it. Great job your doing Lou. Love you and your show.❤🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got in a giant restock order from @NECA_TOYS. If you’re in the Cleveland or Pittsburgh area stop into… https://t.co/oxk1ePbu4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ging3y93 @Deuce_Gamer For most of the first half I felt great. Or at least good. Now I hate my life. Typical.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @CodesTrump @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC… https://t.co/R7Gcf3wmTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[REMINDER: Get your tickets to the Tewaaraton Watch Party, February 28 in NYC!  See who made the top 50 men’s and wo… https://t.co/H4MII90KG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[After starting my new position I havent had much energy to attend as many meet ups as I’d like but tonight I’m back… https://t.co/5zQqtbjDTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Columbia 300 Savage Life is AMAZING! 😯😯 @eight20six teamflex_bowling #TeamEBI #SavageLife #Columbia300… https://t.co/2XHUOOaim2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Mercedes Benz AMG 63 S is all about top down performance. Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Rai… https://t.co/jNJ60CXsTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Korea Predicts ‘Major Breakthrough’ at Second Trump-Kim Summit https://t.co/PoL5ygyz9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow your roll man!  I am not a fan of @realDonaldTrump but you need to show your sources.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lons True, I think she’s just doing her best to avoid saying anything 🍊 💩 can use against her. He’s very good at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite courts.  Friendly folks from judges to clerks to deputies.  Two tributes to #Lincoln as well. https://t.co/j8MZQ0nr5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryJenkins my man!! Looking good!! Your reputation proceeds you!! #etalkRedCarpet #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonTheDude  How many of us folks in Louisville have been anticipating this concert that is now less than 48 hours away!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention all you ❤️❤️ @ Marmora, New Jersey https://t.co/HCmO7OMt7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so happy to finally see the ceiling of my bedroom. Very good but VERY LONG day @ Morgan City, Louisiana https://t.co/U9O85wR1Bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that I'm just now finding the show on diy "Vanilla Ice Goes Amish"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chsfire17 Blessings and prayers to an amazing man! I’m trusting one a bit more amazing who will meet all your need… https://t.co/6WIxLCOBVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello I’m watching the Bachelor for the first time thoughts: 1. This guys is as boring as a bag of white rice  2. W… https://t.co/IzTvkU6sR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@35metros @mariochupitero @roberantolin @albertosi1974 @QUINTERORADIO @TugaRMCF @MAtropos @tildegm @YOATAMAYO… https://t.co/GjGZFG8L1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nullterm I think I know what you are trying to say. As I say, we disagree on that point. But all good. I appreciate you reading.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtney Bowman says we need to keep in mind that computers cannot make moral judgments #stanfordtechethics]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Racial And Regional Inequality Affect Economic Opportunity | via ⁦@BrookingsInst⁩  https://t.co/dXASy9maik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigerians crying that giannis doesn’t identify with them https://t.co/2CFNudOVaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Met_CindyFitz Hi Cindy...just got in from shoveling "Domino sugar." It's the lightest, fluffiest snow all winter!… https://t.co/iVsSyW9tJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andei kilometros a pé no centro da cidade, mas ainda tenho muito para explorar. A diferença cultural é abismal, mas… https://t.co/raaytFjWKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgarthiaSays @JCbackfire The best things in life take dedication, pain and lack of social life. It’s worth it to i… https://t.co/fYMgoYFmTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate keeping up with Snapchat streaks. https://t.co/IB5IGIABKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another big victory @NHLCanes AHO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! #BunchOfJerks #StanleyCup #Playoffs #TakeWarning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikewichter @CoreyB08 @QueenLambright7 theyl b there at the end,it's been the defense lately,which is desire,givin… https://t.co/PZ22qAd01q]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s this guy in my 7am class and he doesn’t shut the heck up I’m so close to crack that dude😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whocanstopus2 Lmao yeah cause the Puerto Rican chick was from New York and I showed her what foot workin is lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMiMeDicenMune Hay muñe, me pregunto si tu haz hecho memoria o te haces, los juicios políticos nunca han prosperad… https://t.co/N0HVHzVGnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only fatality last night from  the tornado was a eighth of a mile from where I work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is worth it. Hard work and dedication does pay off. Blessings on blessings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's unfortunate for us that your parents didn't make that choice before having you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Rayden @ngmcclernan @cognisium @mydeskonthemoon @JConrad_Tweets @TabathaSouthey It also requires a test that… https://t.co/yq3fWd1Pnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the next and back at the last “weekend”- . . . . . . . #zag1  #bicycle  #cycling  #cyclinglife… https://t.co/4dCqy0WMbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeagsSportsHubU Yous doing anything special during deadline day? I’m tryna call in with some opinions 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Petnetio are the food level sensors operational? I see that the hardware is there but my Petnet seems to have no i… https://t.co/gVXO4JOhsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyRhiannon55 Do as Bradford Cox does. Mono-mono-mania! https://t.co/navO0ejag0]]></document><document><![CDATA[No amount of money or success can take the place of the time we missed out on.  #InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰🎼🎺… https://t.co/kCCHSlIVxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChowAfterDark It was last minute honestly lol, I thought I was going to see illenium but I'm glad my friends convi… https://t.co/5YQOi77PL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMPACTWRESTLING @zachary_wentz @DezmondXavier @PENTAELZEROM @ReyFenixMx That will be the greatest tag match! #IMPACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW an email was accidentally sent to thousands of people and everyone reply-all’s to get removed from the list and… https://t.co/0UYPqjFtHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge thanks to @HomeGoods for the generous donation to @TheCaryingPlace Best of luck for your #GrandOpening… https://t.co/BmFCKpTz6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srlklr @MandyLeonxo It’s better then having that one chick out a tampton in her area and put it in your face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino He is confessing, on national TV to basically plotting the overthrow of our duly elected President.  Can… https://t.co/gRLlpfnm5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kopice86 Anyone expecting this to be easy needs to go support amother club. Things are gonna get tight, we never d… https://t.co/zvXzL5M0VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to my online home. I invite you to come in, learn more about me and my work, and stop to embrace the slow p… https://t.co/NO5GV8rcfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday - have a great day! #saturdaymorning #saturdayvibes #saturdaymotivation #greatday #sunrise @ Roswell… https://t.co/v52gLeT6aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Wade_Miller @washingtonpost Mike Pence is a vile, anti-gay bastard selling out even his own disgusting principle… https://t.co/RgnFmFKOJJ]]></document></documents></author>