<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @GerbusJames I'm glad that you all finally admit that fairness matters😉 Who knew it would be over transgendered athletes? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinbinbains I don’t understand why he never seems to have more than 7 guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 Question of the day: why does the word ‘terrific’ look and sound so negative? It’s the last word I think of to de… https://t.co/2PwrFjRv70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ky1eLong Oh and Black Mirror Bandersnach, it's interactive. Cool stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏.  #followforfollowback #following💞 #follow4like #follow_me #followersinstagram #trending #facebook… https://t.co/rIKYBo0rOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[announcing a new monthly residency at one of my favorite venues fitzgeraldsnightclub sidebar! 1st Saturday’s kickin… https://t.co/3DVncqnykA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clemson CF Bryce Teodosio, from 10 minutes down the road at Mauldin HS, hits a two-out homer to right at Greenville… https://t.co/kW4LkUkPzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sens_Army_ @ThatFishCreigh I thought we get their pick next year if they pick top 3 this draft or if Duchene re-signs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry I’ll say it again. No backbone. People need to Standup. That’s absolutely intolerable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorRock3148 @BeneathThePaint And that’s OK Corey. Sucks, sucks, sucks. How many times do you say that a day? How m… https://t.co/RmJJxixYnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re on General Orders with @RepKDH in the Chair today. #ksleg https://t.co/7olCsqs2jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Got to be Ford! The others are just DUMBASSES! Ford(a doctor of philosophy/psychiatry) knew exactly… https://t.co/sQ3GuL0GgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryan_Duncan I just liked your FB page. :) If you ever come to Ohio, I gotta see you in concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames here it is in a nutshell LeBron...@Jumpman23 never got booed by his hometown fans...second best in NBA H… https://t.co/PCqeobEn4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Springfield #OR  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/AJFjNgKlT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taibo2 @amazonmex @PrimeVideoMX Mr. Taino, donde puedo comprar algunos libros en Dallas Texas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump BREAKING: Putting “BREAKING” at the head of one’s tweet does not make said tweet true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline A pack of lies it will be, right you Trump bootlicking shill? #Jail.  @seanhannity]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Justin Rutledge tune is, not surprisingly, fantastic. Love that voice and that sound. Instant comfort.  https://t.co/aTUHsOZFqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnyBrooks @AveryReedMoore The delivery is one of the most consistent in the business. You rule! 💖🌟💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Know You Rider and Turning Toward the Morning  https://t.co/5YEigECTR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaFutures @AdamSinger Yes, other tweets established that's he's right, cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve haven’t met a more upbeat, delightfully positive, extremely talented singer/songwriter like Olivia in quite so… https://t.co/KYagmAQFld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to discussing my paper, “Avoiding Complicity,” with faculty members of @UWSchoolofLaw tomorrow. Bui… https://t.co/nfvIzommqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been thinking about sex nine stop latly...the meds barely distracting me. https://t.co/rMVLPStQdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating mustard and peanut butter sandwiches. Getting the toaster French toast and only eating it if burnt black.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo Notre Dame. This men's basketball season has been excruciating and yet, here I remain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do whatever you can to #DrawSmiles in your community. #YouthKARE #Outreach #TXYouth #SRMinistries @ Ella Springs Se… https://t.co/OjkcIdt6yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArifHasanNFL @CourtneyRCronin Either of you get any sense what the team thinks of Jaleel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/weJVJbGj3E it’s going to be a #greatday #happywednesday @ West Kendall https://t.co/NPNZK5LKUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We already know that there is (Trump Tower) and there was (June 9, Papadap learning about dirt, Stone, Page, Manafo… https://t.co/ywQ9bIfPOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The water's impact on both the trees life and the reflections life . One is created through nurturing life, the oth… https://t.co/tQlIYi0ff5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this intermingling of diplomacy and personal enrichment appropriate, @RepPeteOlson @SenTedCruz @TeamCornyn… https://t.co/klXTAKPvAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats sir... more to come, just wait for it. @CoachKrysl smart for pulling trigger first. 😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! She will always make me smile with this one:  https://t.co/52WJZFLfet]]></document><document><![CDATA[12.3 4th  Minford 58  North Adams 55  Grace McDowell hits a pair of free throws for the Lady Devils. Caitlyn Puckett at the line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold morning in the desert, reminding our guys to drive safely in this weather #CEMEXCares #VictorvilleCementPlant https://t.co/JmaVNgzKoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @stitchfix @stitchfixmen for some of the best customer service ever on a return. For those who don’t like… https://t.co/wqEn5uYMT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilmourOrgasm @_DavidGilmour @rogerwaters Hopefully they patch things up. Two of the greatest musicians ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought my #gopro7 on an amazing #powder  day only to have the best part of the day freeze and only record audio.… https://t.co/7SdT3rDrWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Double standard dude!! Your so quick to spew your venom, create atmosphere of hate to so many, the… https://t.co/DMM8EKvwqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deray I've met him, DeRay. Ethical, tough. Certainly a solid Democrat, supporter of workers' rights and the Democr… https://t.co/kOWzLXTxJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#keepfighting #painrelief #lowbackpain #neckpain #mechanicofthespine #spinespecialist… https://t.co/49KNnbIXNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My greatest ideas come in the middle of the night when I get home when I’m sitting in my car in my driveway. Then a… https://t.co/bE7Sz0Nfeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen Hahaha of course, do any liptards know how to speak the truth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yankeessarcasm1 So true.  They improved so they need to battle with this team they have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlessedMMA is the type of guy to sneeze and bless himself lol #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The reason that most people aren’t Christians is either because they think that Jesus isn’t really real or that he… https://t.co/Xu7esSSZc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Conner9191 This. My first novel was filled with scenes of people driving from place to place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sometimes cringe so bad at the things I said from being intoxicated the next day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidfromCobb Can’t wait!!! I’ll be there at @HarlowsNiteclub on the 19th!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@char_stokely @craigbannister @Matthew669691 @Schmoeness @MonaWalesXXX @GlassOlive @GiaPaige @LoupRival… https://t.co/R9NELHe0Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥❗️TEAM❗️🔥 . . It’s a done deal!!!!!  5 weeks into the business and this guy has done what it took me months to acc… https://t.co/kaKPfGzJU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[the galaxy is way beyond our lax thinking that's why we have our dreams #artwiculate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, @HowardSchultz hasn't been in a voting booth in a while. NY was the last state with lever machines, and… https://t.co/3vE5zXSC3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family experienced this last year. You think about our world today in profound ways when your 5 year old tells y… https://t.co/D2fKQz0ySG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity PLUS ACCEPTED DARK MONEY CONTRIBUTIONS! Where’s the investigation Dems?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican propaganda does not just reveal their political point of view, they often character assassinate anyone w… https://t.co/5kEYZ74GeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could drive all day in the city and find parking easier then philly center city]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y vino el tercero... jeje - https://t.co/XwaNVPBcbL @90Minutos_FOX @TyCSports @EstudioFutbol @Farinella_Ole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bomb car but no luck on our side @Whitney_Dillon3 @Mariel_Lane @Dstockman3 @ahouston95 @justvoss @ShawneeWard… https://t.co/dfwxCly7tM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to play some basketball! @TerrapinHoops hosting @OhioStAthletics at 2...updates at 15 &amp; 45 on @WTOP. https://t.co/PzDdVL82fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice History repeats fairly often these days. https://t.co/eE6JzEKrBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actlightning @ChuckCallesto @TammyBerney @RepAOC Sorry 😐 but unfortunately as long as @RepAOC is in office I will… https://t.co/eAo6USnwWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rather than remediate, provide the learning experience that captures all of the skills and tools - integrate and in… https://t.co/Xy2FoEMOhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you love someone living with bipolar disorder? https://t.co/g5bLDA84Dq #endthestigma #bipolar @MHNRNetwork… https://t.co/rfWj5Xf0mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odessa Permian beats Americas for the third team this season, sending all El Paso teams into the offseason… https://t.co/sno2XouBz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerkass10 I stopped at Shakey’s on my way home from work . I still have to drive home so no alcohol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCJMurphy @EAPepper @ScottWalker You are a computer guy right?? Do you just come up with software and that's it… https://t.co/xyssHaltXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenCallesoe @dannygillette @tgonzo07 @juliettekayyem @Patriots Take that up with the state of Florida]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancydesmond3 @DCraelin @thehill @Established1791 @IvanTheTroll12 @G00SE_13 @WallaceClyde @JoseMadre1995… https://t.co/V6xXW1RWYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a difference between Making Love,Just having sex, &amp; just wanting to cum. Learn some respect💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanozIchimonji Yep it's more or less teh same as typical DOA stuff. *sigh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Wow. A Catholic citing an anti-Semite in support of an anti-Catholic dictator. That’s a bad day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Oxxo (Suc. Perimetral Norte) in Santa Catarina, Nuevo León https://t.co/m3UjoNyFdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Saint Bosco IPA by @tampabeerworks at @tampabeerworks — https://t.co/Tq8FpDmFqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was one of the MOST delicious meals I’ve had out in a VERY long time!!! Thank you Meetup!!! @ Ventano's Italia… https://t.co/VyuBgHmhXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mattcocartoons with @Geminivisions2 I really like this song, specifically these lyrics so i decided to anim… https://t.co/n35Oa26XK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraFazio Of course I’ve tried them , I’ve never not liked them , but it would never be my go to until recently if… https://t.co/9fb8JIM3JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeidraMonika8 Hi honey say Hi to Mellissa my Only beautiful girl in my life right now 😍🙋🏻‍♂️😘🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹 https://t.co/ZnvpEIkduq]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if this night couldn’t get any more ridiculous, my @lyft driver has Tokyo Drift playing. Is there any way to giv… https://t.co/JOtBlsQ08v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best...tweet...ever!! #GoBonnies #ThisIsBonaTerritory #Unfurl #StBonaventure #ReillyCenter #Bonnies #A10MBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT He's successfully convinced 25% of the US population you're an actual enemy of the country. He's inspire… https://t.co/IcaPR46RsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@updatewithinfo @RealSaavedra @benshapiro The man has been in Congress for 218 years and done nothing of substance!… https://t.co/85NTcg3tYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron gonna have a bunch of time to film space jam 2 in the summer, cause of the fact the lakers won’t be in the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New chain coming to Jacksonville. Island Wing Co. taking over Tinseltown TGI Friday site https://t.co/pbhFaGoM00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Namaste2525 You are right. In many organizations this is true &amp; needs to change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standardnews Actually @netanyahu and Israeli Military Intelligence developed this strategy after helping… https://t.co/rxfjnmtDOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkaplun @mrdodger1966 The pay in the Turkish League is a lot more than what I make.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YTCreators @TeamYouTube @YouTube   Reapplied for monetization after demonetize a month ago. I've made many account… https://t.co/U2CHvBozfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joy_nagel68 @RedTRaccoon I can't even dispute that Joyce, you're right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a very subtle detail but I’m sure not many people know that these hanging planters aren’t normally here. Just… https://t.co/S2OWIO3dGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time we all thought Olivia Coleman was going to be the next #DoctorWho? #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDrBarber That just showed that trump knows the decisions he makes are rascist based! Spike made no such referen… https://t.co/gAdEFFQ9kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot believe that @AOC and @ewarren are CELEBRATING the loss of 50,000 jobs to NYC, particularly @AOC who repre… https://t.co/7MPHwwLNiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest South Lake Tahoe, CA job and click to apply: Certified Nursing Assistant- Long Term Care -… https://t.co/z3Cpljh3p7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uzbek Linguist to work in Chantilly:  https://t.co/ja8J2y3H6R.   Central Asia Research Analyst: Regional language s… https://t.co/bShzAMsPuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump LMFAO you were serious about calling investigations into his comic-book villain novelty… https://t.co/RyWHD6JfnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot almost even bear to watch this she is so pretty.. :) https://t.co/oDPyVhMQPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for “The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee @playerscentre @ The Players Centre for Performing Arts https://t.co/qTUnpwqhE0]]></document></documents></author>