<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So proud of my girl @MarenMorris 💙 On replay until I fall asleep tonight..love you MM! 👑 #TheBones #GIRL https://t.co/jpvOYGm5pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach has been sleeping through the night for a while now yet I STILL can’t sleep 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMStedman Maybe because there was so much serious talk of starting impeachemnt proceedings after BuzzFeed arti… https://t.co/OE22RDYMcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, IM HIGH AF ON OXY &amp; MY THOUGHTS ARE WILD AF RN 🤣🤣 SHOTS ANYONE? LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why in the hell is the picture so blurry ???? We wait all this time to see him and we get a picture with 1960 quality ! WTF ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geeeech_ Luckily my dad named me cause my mom likes really ugly names. My name was almost Hilda. Lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The zoo said the woman crossed a barrier in an attempt to get the photo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASDAQ closing bell with slgminecraft slgclashroyale superleaguelol 😎 @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/6WqzL0oPu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whitehaven is having its way with White Station. The Tigers are up 30-15 at halftime. Matthew Murrell leads Whiteha… https://t.co/gIF8fT9Nd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelsomeara It is funny, I was back in d&amp;m head - thinking early 90’s and WJFK when I saw it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of filming my music video starts in less than a couple of hours and I can’t sleep... 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collegeadvisors Pity. Such a shame to turn down a potential grad student with a verbal GRE score of 167 and a quan… https://t.co/DCKb2O5sHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the clothes you were back in the day are now what the kids are wearing today.  #SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice synopsis of #CiscoCollabAnalystSummit in 7 tweets. Good to see you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #SignatureHeart necklace from @kayjewelers is the PERFECT Valentine's Day gift! https://t.co/YswSuCiDzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“develop a national campaign to promote education and training, recommend ways to improve labor market data, increa… https://t.co/UQWQhPXpMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bl33dBLue24 @KySportsRadio I walked around on a tore acl two days.  I’m not saying that’s what it is.  It could be… https://t.co/FiQJ0YAFm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the #GreenNewDeal - 80% of people think something needs to be down about climate change, but is the Green New Deal resolution the answer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prepostmeltdown @lakesideliberal @ItsMeCathi @JohnCornyn @GOP Spot on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a ton of photos of my gr8 grandma &amp; found all our other ancient family photos &amp; used… https://t.co/0HAmLyRBA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready for this Dunk Contest!!!! Let’s go @MilesBridges @hornets #NBAAllStarWeekend2019 #DunkContest https://t.co/53LqyWCaBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thankful to be able to serve at WBC. So glad we were to hear a lesson from @wife_momof3 today! Thank you for lo… https://t.co/2pQJMmGQeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @PredsNHL, I could go for a free coffee tomorrow! Let’s win this one! @dunkindonuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[i donated blood and got a tshirt, but i noticed that it and a stain on it.   sweet Madison offered to wash it for m… https://t.co/pMml9GwreQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbll I couldn't choose just one book, so here's all of my books on my one tiny shelf. As you can see, I've run out… https://t.co/GJ8hJi5crj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need a remake of you got served in a couple of years starting Mega !!! Idc!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babysandy76 @Gap I just gotta throw it away. 😞 For reals, @Gap should honor it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BingeWars That must be a challenge today we used to go to comedy clubs and they used to rip everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckyenvbrewing tasting to split. @CougPeterson @ Lucky Envelope Brewing https://t.co/qaTWrdk0rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flex FriYay! Beast Shoulders 💪@SagiKalev #BEACHBODY #bodybeast #teamac #fitmom  💦T20 - 10 Min. Abs @shauntfitness… https://t.co/YNxvJUTM3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great @madisonschools LEGO robotics team at the @alabamafll competition. Way to go, @HeritageRams!… https://t.co/XJJS1hFAcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Good luck in the Courtroom! So many lawsuits! Abuse of power is an impeachable offense! https://t.co/RF6vRflWks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potato_Chip @MeliaHotelsInt Not gonna lie this may be the best venue I’ve been to for a conference. It’s a total p… https://t.co/hRW1WqsdSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annefromthehub starting our day off right with some intros. https://t.co/9YDumXs9DU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riding past sunset 😍 🌄🌠🗻 #skihoodoo #hoodoo #nightriding #likeknightrider @ Hoodoo Ski Area https://t.co/0wiBJ2nYUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and carl wheezer out here becoming the new bob ross https://t.co/KXtg7A79iP]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. Bank is hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click the link in our bio to apply: Syndicated Deal Admin/Closer 3 #Banking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS Bernie Hires Twice-Arrested Illegal To Work For 2020 Campaign, And She Can’t Even Vote For Him https://t.co/F3xW1h9NZC via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @fentybeauty can be available @ShopprsDrugMart that would be great for us Canadians here👍 #moreoptions 🖤🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Democrats ~ remember this....  “A man I’m proud to call my friend. A man who will be the next president of the… https://t.co/VjAgIgWgf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isa 41:8 NIV—“But you, Israel, my servant, Jacob, whom I have chosen, you descendants of Abraham…  https://t.co/GRTEh9uC4V via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it sounds dumb, but I obtained my first set of fetal heart tones today at work and it was so precious 😭💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annaleclaire but i can understand it i was homeless and the only thing that saved me was I had a car ta sleep in i… https://t.co/4sCFpjr5jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj In my opinion Adults should never include children in grown up situations...It is abusive if you ask me...… https://t.co/0e9a6NBXjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met a really cool, down to earth NFL player, Karlos Williams (and family). Pulling for him to get signed to an NFL… https://t.co/dQEyRs2JWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, if that wasnt the most awkward collection of ashes...EVER😳! That poor funeral director!! Lol #LoveAfterLockup]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE STUDENT OF #life #mom #raisingscholars 🙋🏾‍♀️#momlife #boss #bossbabe @ Southwest Tennessee Community College https://t.co/rLKTJWNH8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/DPue4Myee2]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I've said, I'm not an NDP member, but @NathanCullen always struck me as the type of person who SHOULD be in poli… https://t.co/RXzf4Nnl8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you’re already late for work but seven rings comes on. https://t.co/6M7NHXDVgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaske More worried about the exuberant celebrations than the structural integrity of the GAME!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate repetition don’t repeat yourself to me I heard it once. I HEARD. IT. ONCE. I do not need to hear that shit again. lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Canyon turns 100 years as a National Park this year. Actually it was yesterday but I only realized that very… https://t.co/MBIoUoqgFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVanLaeken_MIS this is my first of seven posts of my favorite books. https://t.co/LBycASWzkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels The devil seeks aboutlike a roaring lion...(The devils goal is to distract and instill fear) STANDSTRONGINYOURFAITH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisweedies I’m sorry to hear that.  Big hug to you. https://t.co/1GYvK6G0Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[TWO OF MY FAVORITE PEOPLE!! Oh my godddddd I can die happy @MODSUN @shanedawson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me  | | |_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _  Wearing my   | cute clothes  | _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ | | | | 📍wearing sweatpants for the 3r… https://t.co/cNfTsxS5kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verabradley “lighten up lunch cooler” would be my style to take #PackYourLunchDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xian_Do @gorillastyle @charliekirk11 @WhiteHouse @LogicalTroll2 Appreciated Clinton's honesty about getting his di… https://t.co/RNV7D5VeTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Denying your religious beliefs is a bit like denying your heritage. If you're proud of your beliefs and… https://t.co/T1VLT6S38q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @mtrench which one of you is the bass in Wish You Were Here, and can we get more of that please? #Phantoms]]></document><document><![CDATA[And all is well with the world when I’m back on a softball field with my girl! #23 sierradbaldwin 🥎 ❤️ we are yelli… https://t.co/VKTXw2LJcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[dorallincoln was on-site at Carnaval on the Mile showcasing the latest Lincolns. Made me want to swap my 🚙 #MKX… https://t.co/AMdHUCtlAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddogsusie I lost my 14yr old red nose pit with cancer. Gracie then saved my Molly n lost her three yrs. later fr… https://t.co/VkVbo1p8t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny Koch Brothers are known Liberals. They don’t have any influence over the Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the type who doesn’t like being hugged or any physical when I’m crying or in the urge to cry, so tomorrow, hold… https://t.co/AhHq7EX4a3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still confused as to why we got yelled at for leaving our coats on during class in high school i distinctly remembe… https://t.co/aRdGoEyfHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES and all over my phone front and back... like did I roll around in cheese]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love waking up in the middle of the night with the flu.  Nothing quite like it 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andystravelblog @AmericanAir We met with them last week and it was truly an awesome experience to see how and why… https://t.co/eltEfBULSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally heartbreaking story .. always thought MJ was an abuser, from all the weird story’s with kids and the accusa… https://t.co/ghMOltrDjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@activist360 @NicolleDWallace It's a shame, seems Rosenstein is not really a stand up guy without being forced to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes Yeah that would be not wanting to get caught! 🙄 And I'm sorry no one deserves that!! 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl said “I had the chance to get my ex beat up.. wish I would’ve” lol does this mean we can beat u up now fo… https://t.co/NUlETecshM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow thank you for your voice.  And your teachings.  What a great session with you and your wife.  More... more.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day in Clearwater, FL. NO WAY YHE LADIES IN THE STORE “smoke daily”. They weren’t very customer friendly AT ALL!!… https://t.co/Yu9SLXEhwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that blue skies and sunshine I see !?!? ☀️🌞☀️ @icc_inverness https://t.co/FZUflWgFpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever tell yourself “it is what it is “ but deep down you know you don’t accept it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just constantly reminded how important it is to surround yourself with good humans. So refreshed from spending the… https://t.co/1ClB56tXcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoorRobin @BriannaShrum @Bibliogato Shhhh! Don’t put that out into the universe!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDePooter @MyPeakChallenge I’ve never even worn it so you’re getting it brand new :-). DM me where to send it.… https://t.co/9DTpDVlK6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly going into the office today because it seems like the kind of day they might put donuts out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feburary 15, 2019 0337 Hrs Someone please make some arrest, I am emotionally scarred for life. That Senator and Dwi… https://t.co/hkc5fqGybs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emitoms @seattlewinefood Very cool! I’ll for sure tweet you if I’m there. 🥂📷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thee Amazing Mandi! Our Local Beauty Influencer came to visit me today for a little Brow Magic!! 🎨💕  (( love you Ma… https://t.co/oKnyokJATi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, join the #sangha at #bhaktiyogashala for #manta #medicine with #johannabeekmanmusic #dcstringer #tour… https://t.co/JX28EagUKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtrashboy I watched this and pretended it was Corey Feldman. https://t.co/JKJjiFxEmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you think people don't factcheck the crap you tweet? You must be extremely nervous about Cohen's testimony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Patient Care Associate - https://t.co/UorymQk2XI #Healthcare #Springfield, MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐶❤️ Fun in the sun with this pretty girl ☀️ @ Encino, California https://t.co/JqWsQ6UnOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day One! Anguilla in 5 days! #realtorlife #momlife #adayinthelifeofcarynblack @ 1616 Walnut Street Building https://t.co/TdvIFVkaHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Said 👋🏼goodbye to the second WestJet 787-9 (C-GURP, tail 902) today. She is headed to YYZ from PAE... I sure hope s… https://t.co/JYUomSylm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats @SenateDems  why do you choose to support socialism? You see Venzuela rationing food. You are the p… https://t.co/B7PtXFG16D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sisters. @ Library, Headquarters Library Spartanburg https://t.co/5ZCPC35B7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF YALL WANNA KNOW HOW STRESSED I AM I TEXTED MY GM AT THE THEATRE AT 2AM AND ASKED TO GO PICK UP MY CHECK. I REPEA… https://t.co/EQRgPQCfnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get all 15 of my pre-k students to lay down and take a 2 hour nap at the same time is equivalent to when… https://t.co/lgZksTpLgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay twitter let’s settle this!! Texas Pete or Louisiana Hot Sauce? I’m a Texas Pete kinda girl. The best kinda gir… https://t.co/bi8GbDTiWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi familia en #Caracas #SanAntonioDeLosAltos #Valencia #Maturin #CdBolivar SIN LUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Empathy is vital to better our society. Me after looking at Twitter: But everyone is annoying.]]></document></documents></author>