<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods DTL Driver at The Genesis Open in LA starting with his fabulous routine as he stripes a Driver @ Palm D… https://t.co/17oFJz1zTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 seconds of @LaceyEvansWWE??? Seriously @WWE??? Come on!!! Don't waste a great female talent.  #WWEChamber #EliminationChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like how the Never Trump types think they’re being bold by stating the blindingly obvious. https://t.co/mk8YeK2m3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_HenryO_ @adekolapo_ So Dirk shot lights out? We thought he did but really it was Terry carrying them and Dirk come in as close it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[And apparently the next Democratic President is now justified in acting on them unilaterally without the assent of… https://t.co/TQpVBcHYRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic look at the final three possessions by @AWBridgers. Shows two really good play calls by Manning and good… https://t.co/7QueRY8Wdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @CNN and @joelockhart looking at Starr and say #wtf https://t.co/VpocvsLDEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like @stevewoz is in town (SLC, UT) tonight: https://t.co/BMpStiJkBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi favorita de Katy es Waking Up In Vegas. Suena y pueden escucharme gritando “MI CANCIÓN”. https://t.co/esUQTMcRe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lefties care more about foreign kids at the border than the kids being aborted here at home 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and @Spirit_Redeemed  for prayer 5 days a week via phone or Facebook Live. @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/G7L63HIt2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCHF_TOOLBOX last sugar check 94! I feel fine. Not hungry at all. Jittery but not due to sugar reading. Gad a big… https://t.co/wfkt41ghNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEmiliaSong @Lisetteness @radicalbruja @stopthenextutr @howardzinnlives @PayPal We're fighting racism right now… https://t.co/dm3R2Gzmon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I want to watch something it disappears from the streaming service I can watch it on]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sleeping so well but ppl wanna fuck around and call me and wake me up ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Bizzaro world. Let's spread the poverty, death, repression of socialism. Prepare to eat your pets. What absurd… https://t.co/xEDekpRjtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[my tax return thicc this year can’t wait to take that bitch out on the town]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesLGarrett Got any cool hobbies? Unique talents? Video game skills outside of things like Madden and the Battle Royale-du-jour?]]></document><document><![CDATA[...in Everett, and that similar pilot projects were implemented in other cities, is a testament to the project's su… https://t.co/cqcTOOw0IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Place Called #OldTown #Pasadena https://t.co/feYjBnj66j https://t.co/2PMHiBRF6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If cauliflower can somehow become pizza and mimosas are kind of breakfast ... you, my friend, can do anything ***… https://t.co/UqiA2yLfta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGofTheWorld Res/com. It’s San Francisco. I was just kidding around. Farm outside of the city (obv no farming in S… https://t.co/A2I3sz05Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “The US has offered up to $1 million for information about bin Laden's son”  https://t.co/c11Fatp6qF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daltonjbrown I’m watching VT and keeping tabs on the Duke game. You gotta admit — they are a completely different… https://t.co/435xSgvP9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EfrenGlez77 @elrenecito2 @luisaguilerahmo @CARLOSEES @levantamiento1 @Luperciote @ulisespena @arielvmachado… https://t.co/ZHzhpV4KVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boy_myth_legend as just a fan of both you and your fathers work, I’m sending good thoughts and well wishes to your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr.Robbins over here making the world a better place, one veneer at a time!  Just how every patient is different, e… https://t.co/ZuiYoNp3rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my friends at Disneyland today and I’m just sittin here foldin laundry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got in unexpected shout out yesterday on “The Tony Kornheiser Show” podcast. That was pretty awesome!  Access! @… https://t.co/A3RowJsZvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter And @SebGorka leaves Hannity’s green room just long enough to compare you to Bill Kristol. Sheesh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it. (@ Philadelphia International Airport - @phlairport in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/PsvzPzSWxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@castillejos_m Me podrías decir, por favor, ¿cuántos de los 19 tiros fueron dentro de los 3 palos blancos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mavs lead 79-78 after the third quarter.  Brunson has 20-3-4 and 3 steals, Luka has 17-7-4 and 6 turnovers, Hardaw… https://t.co/5nS2MurlCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachCBly Get her some “grown up” gear so we can get her back in the dugout.  We win when that young lady is around. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamar County Jamboree today at Purvis! Always enjoy playing our on county schools! JV plays Purvis at 12:00 and Var… https://t.co/4koYtdEBkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[F45 All Star ⭐️ morning #noletup @ F45 Training Five Points Raleigh https://t.co/l3jWc0D73Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[That said, if there is even a hint of these rumors being true, Giants need to send their 1st to Seattle ASAP in ord… https://t.co/zO2X1OT9dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerdBurgerCraig The same reason your delicious home cooked meal isn't lobster from Maine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJacobsRad Gee, I'm surprised the $120 million a month panhandler was able to tear itself away from another Jew-h… https://t.co/WFX6pEXcwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riomakino When you coming up so we could play Rio, or should I go down? Either way you catching L’s just like @ellisbrianr 👀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The stable genius knows only the best words. https://t.co/0itMxZ2xhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio last caller, Derrick, was spot on. As a @packers fan, hard pass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heritage eliminates Abery in the boys WHC tourney by a final score of 91-43. @acthshuddle @SPamfilis @Glory1130AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxnewsdesk Please email me at the address in my bio for further information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @alanmns China, India, Venezuela, and dozens of other so-called developing nations have another 10… https://t.co/53i06V8s3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and I didn’t mean for the “bro” to sound dickey. It wasnt like a “broseph”. More like a “boo boo”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some random shots from Monument Valley. Apparently the leash law does not extend to pets. 😂🤣 I had to take a shot o… https://t.co/6WWPEcp9A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a dictatorship  Media doing there job. .repeating the same statement will win over people that never think… https://t.co/ruG8sWmmQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @DLeonhardt @CNN Trump becoming president didn’t change the anti establishment political climate. Also,… https://t.co/780wYdSGgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneusMeister @Jake_Selig25 @Maffewgregg You should. It’s not funny. An entire family was impacted, and you and ot… https://t.co/QjbvY19y1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr tweeting about Cohen not remembering to pay taxes, while his own father promised to disclose his if… https://t.co/rtOUWXaY6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KNoelLittle @GreenPTA @lbrscully1 @GreenESLeaders I ❤️ a good WIG!!!  🎯 📈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 Omg my favorite is when you live on the edge on 1% and your iPhone surprises you and stays on as if it… https://t.co/EEtMylTwKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnightwriter @donlemon @CNN @MSNBC I worked in Media. Wrote, produced and broadcast financial news. Used to be, p… https://t.co/yLRfGxLQjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just observed the first flight of geese heading north towards Canada. Spring is on the way: The birds know...  Sorr… https://t.co/nop4Zb6MP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobWilsonWTNH8 @WTNH Personally, team sports, specifically football 40+ years ago, helped me become a better man a… https://t.co/m2oRvfkSAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSBayArea Huge gusts here on Sonoma Mtn. Just got our first @PGE4Me “wind gust” safety outage https://t.co/xhsysnXapA]]></document><document><![CDATA[-—- #ig_nycity #storyofnewyork #in_public_sp #in_public_street_photo #ig_street #streetshot #streetphotography… https://t.co/lnD5KOkYx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTroyerBB You are becoming a better person already just by stepping on campus. God will be smiling down on you 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at 9:30! A rebroadcast! Tune in to @wqed?! 17 cool artifacts that connect to our city and its history. Watc… https://t.co/Uq9vxTpEDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lofton Henderson Memorial Bridge in Lorain, OH https://t.co/Z8xDO8o6eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat Wouldn't you want shorter players because of the high altitude?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conor64 I'm having trouble reconciling that view with this:  https://t.co/Lo56NWaunR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing it with my whole soul! Car karaoke driving home from shows are hilarious https://t.co/2KwZvbv4LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barnacules @CharMemeznabel I expect Ballmer's glad, in hindsight, that it failed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaglass_  Justice will prevail. @Theodore_Decker : Will prosecution get second shot at death penalty for Golsby… https://t.co/UXh8Nq1dnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chowrilka @OakBsblTweets His value keeps tanking too.  Not going to get much of anything for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quiara @hobbsisme @CostelloeJ @exvies And a metric shit ton of Victoria’s Secret Body spay.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liel9999 @kairyssdal @nycsouthpaw You can see the sound barrier break?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominicLalli @PELLYEAH @CervantesDenver perfect time for Miss Primetime collab on Saturday for @tdizzfashizz that… https://t.co/O8aB0A9zu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley  She hits giant payday for being ANTIUNION as the Governor of S CAROLINA and her relationship with BOEI… https://t.co/CDNxomvMaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drew Bianco hits his first career Home Run to left field driving in Cabrera. #LSU leads 9-0.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulOKelly1 @ByTheMinGolf It’s the gap between golf channel leaving the coverage and NBC picking it up so there is… https://t.co/gTt1mElYgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadbensonshow I can totally see this happening... https://t.co/0h5x6eJzEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSmith4680 Thank you sweetie! God Bless you! This country is in a very sad state! Be strong 💪😊😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauralaxla I’ll have to find the uncured turkey bacon and try it. Enjoy. I need to go eat now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah... I'm pretty sure Saros should just leave the ice at this point.  Seriously... Who the f***is Ellis marking on that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmj @dunkhippo33 @impcapital “... And there's times I walk in an office, like wow this is really impressive. You c… https://t.co/p50ejHGZxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 4) The truth? There is SO MUCH to choose from, having a debate about it seems...  Futile? Like talking t… https://t.co/AVvmpV54F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in the year 2000 a Quantum Police Officer recalls the day a decorous Qubit was scolded...  "In my 30 yea… https://t.co/SKpuZv2ZCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucali’s is pizza and calzone, what else do you need? . . #lucali #lucalipizza #lucalis  #lucalispizza… https://t.co/mw1a4YlVWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch... Justin Bieber ain’t never came hard as he did on “Journals”. I had to go back and get my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogmaFree71 @MSignorile Classic case of liberals eating their own.  Can't complain there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crstl_M_Romero @KatheMazur @ForThePeopleABC Our great queen makes any jewelry look good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyscan Agree and they should Go Brewers style and yank the starters early at the first sign of trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SevaUT Pompey was a teenaged butcher, but you wouldn't BELIEVE what came next, and more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelvscott It just looks like God is saying, “AAAAAAAARGH!!” ... like a pirate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing... Millionaires funded by billionaires might be my favorite mic drop lines ever spoken to a politic… https://t.co/Jw4ANCWRFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spider_Duke If you think about it...Crippling Depression is a great name for a super villain. Or for a pro wrestler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rpg https://t.co/lBCtsGa64A  This template used as a demo practice is one of the many firsts.  To reproduce this w… https://t.co/hUB9h2Zn3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's a lifelong Sixers and Eagles fan. That would offend the fuck outta him]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Album Spotlight March 8, 2019 Featured Albums For March 8, 2019  Mystic Crock - Seduced Sen… https://t.co/PMuo8K3zF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In episode #112, @neverquitkid and I talk about the word "SIMPLICITY" and my five fundamental pillars of natural fi… https://t.co/ovddGPtWcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia lands commitment from 2020 4-star WR Justin Robinson https://t.co/rLEFebFwVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__BabyNicole There you go. It ain’t easy being a female but you think it’s easier being a guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the kind words; I listened today and agree the content was very good. If you missed it…… https://t.co/IKdLgwJ1vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJhnae_ That’s how I’m feeling in Cali right now.. be in Vegas Friday tho my G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarBombBoom13 @NHLPlayerSafety #IfIWereHeadOfDOPS #nhl I would suspend players who recklessly injure other players… https://t.co/ip5jmT9t2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well to quote the Bandit from Treasure of the Sierra Madre... "Charts? I ain't got no Charts! I don't have to show… https://t.co/oHHDDT9oaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Does the GOP have the "balls to hold him &amp; the committee accountable?? History says no!]]></document></documents></author>