<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey! S/O to all you ladies out there!  You are loved, appreciated, and cherished! #HappyWomensDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now we can see why the SDF is moving cautiously in the last holdout area - ISIS is holding a thousand civilians… https://t.co/EFhUqKWGU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nTSMnuar61 Samantha Miller of Pure Analytics dropping serious terpene knowledge here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really funny how much Spartans talking about bball sound like Wolverines talking about football (“if you just take… https://t.co/Kjq0jzEl3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winding down over a cold one, revisiting part of an idea for a webcomic that I still plan on taking a shot at...… https://t.co/quKjfXnzJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BreitbartNews Still a destructive wag, she lies some more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReddepD @thedailybeast @djrothkopf Come on man! It’s not like Trump didn’t know she was selling access to the president, him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealDom15 @BBallScientistX @BNets247 @IloveBa96385444 When did you see Russell defend a big effectively in the p… https://t.co/MHRwAwnQap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pe_rackcity @KingJames Lebron has never been as GREAT as MJ or Kobe tho. He’s never been able to win without a sta… https://t.co/tET8ixOls1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronxfuller this reminded me of goodtimes chicago when we walked into our room 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s National Love Your Pet Day...extra belly rubs for Dakota today! #NationalLoveYourPetDay @heathaleigh… https://t.co/F89F3L8YTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Titans have resigned safety Kenny Vaccaro 4-year deal worth $26M and $11.5M guaranteed. #TitanUp MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karinabarbosa @marcymila50 Lindo mensaje! ORIGINAL,CREATIVO Y LLENO DE POSITIVISMO,FE Y OPTIMISMO! Quien te los pr… https://t.co/2TSoNfDkD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate middle level education month! -March - show your passion for the middle by Changing your profile picture… https://t.co/0vSIkOj5Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko If i recall, didn't the GOP basically nix the idea of any primary anyways?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must follows for MOVIES/FILM discussion: @MaxOnMovies: So good at describing movies.  @LynnVenhaus: Devoted Film ad… https://t.co/s40KxMFRgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight #blackdiamondballto #kerihilson @ Fairmont Royal York https://t.co/cqXagObk8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defiant Chelsea Manning sent to jail for refusing to testify in WikiLeaks case - The Washington Post https://t.co/XWBETYCTr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a great actor as well as a producer just like your father who served in the us army in ww 2. I am a life me… https://t.co/Xn7IJ2nqjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahhIsSafe Huh? She the most popular wrestler on the planet. Who’s gonna be mad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of our great Lobo fans, we need 14,000 fans for our last 2 home games to break 100,000 for the season. It wa… https://t.co/Lu8lenyoL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[September 18, 2011's southbound 422 Northlander lead by "Hot from the Paint Shops" GP38-2 1809 powers through Cochr… https://t.co/WaGJA4uxRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteHegseth @AOC I finally figured out what her moniker should b. Absolutely 0 Cortex. She gravitated 2 Socialism… https://t.co/4j0rALsbhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schroedinger_ @roywoodjr Just checking the comments to make sure someone posted this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got $300 to my name to last me til summer... Somebody lemme hold something😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhengstler 6/...Not going to lie, I have been involved in some rare cases where there was willful blindness, and p… https://t.co/BKzpAKOVjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhess59 @Alyssa_Milano List????? If it's a list shouldn't there be at least one item on the list lol here's a… https://t.co/o2y3dvsyR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Friday and Saturday @TheRoyalNomads Trunkshow in Mill Valley @carolinashop 👍 @ Mill Valley, California https://t.co/2j01iwpRmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gyllennhoe @maxwellmuseums @HighgateCemeter @MarkDavis Do you see that mute button? I just pressed it, take your 1… https://t.co/sFgYtO4t65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath @MalcolmNance @RepAdamSchiff Most of Trump's crimes were in plain sight. https://t.co/6u57TTxMct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whoosh013 Like I’m gonna tell a Duggle...  You really are naive!!! 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[He forsees the NDP ship sinking under Singh and rather loose his seat he is retiring. Keeping his good name in tact… https://t.co/5MKFjVbTVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCOlivia @RosieBarton @CBCNews @CBCPolitics That’s a lot of very expensive pickup trucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love one of you bucket-headed hoes?! No wayyyyyy https://t.co/ESnn9fkuCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good things just go together. #thecigarnewb #barrelburners #BurnersMafia #BarrelBurnersUp #barrelburnersfamily… https://t.co/JlZyjRiK3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am a conservative! I support you’re stance at the border but why are you now going to let Even m… https://t.co/jQeVeYqsHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogue0113 you will be ashamed to know i have become a later in life Backstreet Boys fan 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Truth About Jussie Smollett from Empire https://t.co/vBH0PpMPyU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you fix a problem? 1st you must take some self responsibility for your actions/performance. No excuses allow… https://t.co/NEo8TJ6b6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even on a holiday to some like President's Day.  #RiseAndGrind and #LFG #DoTheWork @ Latitude Sports Clubs, Methuen… https://t.co/WtffJ4rBCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of being a chief? When your safety officer gives you a Storm Trooper toaster. Someone is going from l… https://t.co/8Wm75q5XKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTGRacing @RyanPreece_ @Chris_Buescher @kroger @Klondikebar @SlimJim @MrPeanut Lucky dog !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@28delayslater @elonmusk Kinda edgy if stock jumps today SEC may lose their 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Dub today! 3-0 for the cubbies. Great group of boys. Pitching line for the day 0 walks , 11k’s 0 runs. No walks ,no problems!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharks practice, really fun experience. Got to see some of my favorite players #Sharks #NHLSharks #SanJoseSharks https://t.co/UuZwBGJIhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely, considering what part of the country this is taking place in, there needs to be total scrutiny over thi… https://t.co/WdmSjS8P8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sums up youth sports now! @ Fontana, California https://t.co/nS2B6nUwhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec That lawsuit will be thrown out! Any citizen who joins a terrorist group like Isis, has terminated al… https://t.co/UylBtEvgVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesilberman If I were still a believer, I’d consider that desecration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmagana76 Mofo heard it from me and changed it to the first step on Troubleshooting WiFi router]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelushaStephany @PhiPhiOhara I would love to see @PhiPhiOhara come back for AS5. That would be everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old system was not that great. My current one is not much better, as it's riddled with viruses, despite the fact… https://t.co/MhgQgWkrWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[15/ Next time you want to lament the decline of historical literacy, here’s a tip: read actual historians. Don’t us… https://t.co/3E6yETYr1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSimon99 Careful, u might be suspended for that comment, might be construed as racist.  🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here they are and that ain't my signiture mine looks like this https://t.co/YmjjqNXvYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never that deep why not respect her wishes and leave her alone if she blocked you on everything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the links below and be sure to subscribe.  #Elcometer #Carboline #podcasts #SSPC  Apple:… https://t.co/ULvWCCwDMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't I say after that game that it was a bad idea to slight the city of New Orleans? When it comes to Mardi Gras,… https://t.co/wx0H00Cz8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krosakrosakrosa @wyshynski Lol I'm literally just stating that both scenarios are exactly the same. I said differe… https://t.co/1JtHHlplvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhenSeanSpeaks @Sean_WSS Speaking at Grulla High School. Funded by @WatchURBAC https://t.co/aHcUISmNts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFFBallers @FFHitman was that a legend of zelda sound effect on that first drop?!? As if i couldnt love you more! 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Ambrose leaving is all a work. Why would they feature him otherwise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akalali @RasuShrestha @ideapharma @Gil_Bashe @JohnNosta @nickisnpdx @janemetcalfe @RichieEtwaru @daniel_kraft… https://t.co/idwIOH1QZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kurt Cobain would have been 52 today. I still think about him every day, and a few years ago EW let me pull on a th… https://t.co/wIPFgHydPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what the F#ck are U even trying to say!?! A very important word? many people don't know what denuc… https://t.co/5Qt8gEGMNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyflanagan To paraphrase the author: he wants something better for his children; he doesn't know exactly what t… https://t.co/7qKiPVvKef]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Celebration Church - @txcelebration in Georgetown, TX https://t.co/Ibyd4s7GVO https://t.co/ne43n7MfqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What percentage of that is the massive tax bill you gave for stock buy backs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonforSos That would be fine, but also either a federal holiday or two day weekend voting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the House impeaches @realDonaldTrump there is almost no chance the Senate convicts him. There's also almost no c… https://t.co/CkZBxbS4fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @HOTW ・・・ Awesome People @jay_oh nice shot of you at the photo booth TD Bank wearing your pan Africa superh… https://t.co/eU1Jm68xdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A single ad set? Was there an activation funnel? Does your ROAS include the fully weighed cost of all paid touch po… https://t.co/rgWrUACTmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking out of the grocery store when only spending $100.00: https://t.co/XDNr4X5KzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillipfulmer Just think how happy we will be when football beats the hell out of bama]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, check this out: [What is a consensus algorithm &amp; why does it matter?] (via Quarry app) https://t.co/reropUG647]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Michael Bay of short stops, and the Ken Griffey Jr. of bass players that write about the science of baseball https://t.co/3F8UGK3sKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @TheDemCoalition @RepMarkMeadows So you are not racist? Maybe time for you to make official statement to re… https://t.co/HLocxLNDr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @RedNationRising @BreitbartNews @chicksonright @townhallcom @johncardillo CNN,C_ _k national network… https://t.co/ffwNE99eVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my brother from another mother❤️have a good one Swaggy P #big18 @posey_hunter https://t.co/hWkYXJHNzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentBrickman @JohnJuma2121 @SenSanders Jeez, this guy’s understanding of economics and history is at first grade’s level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileyfmilne The @SDCoyotes will lose but hey the @ArgusSports probably won't write about it until way after @summitchamps are long over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexmontejano52 @Mel_the_geek @iron_lombardi @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton Yes I agree there comes a time where… https://t.co/IeAb2DAGss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Brennan should be hung after a very short trial. They won’t have trouble finding a volunteer to pull the lever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los oigo principalmente por el Sr Ernesto Jerez, un poco por el Sr Garay,  pero cuando ud empieza con sus necedades… https://t.co/fxpPrcIC9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/EIA4POMKx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beatriz79valdes @ewarren @TulsiGabbard Thanks for tagging her so the Russian bots can come after me. She’s comprom… https://t.co/qF6CPEt5Fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellaelly There’s a book I am very interested in, but it isn’t available on any of their donors. But other than th… https://t.co/WHPG0VEqkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat You probably got multiple diseases by touching that Bourbon street]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I may smile and mean it, but even whilst meaning it out of sincerity, in the back of my mind, I am struggling. T… https://t.co/4l3klnOcly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BringBackTheBuz Been in the Epicenter all day and have seen by far more Hornets apparel than any other team]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nation of neighborhoods   [RP: Know what you are talking about...nationally, globally.]  https://t.co/Upug2O51TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reese’s Cup is by far the GOAT of Chocolate Candy/ Candy Bars and it’s not even debatable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMFC @NashvilleSC @davisjsn Revs are happy that their badge is no longer the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Blue Wave.  Funny how it’s only viewed as a wave from within the sewer. https://t.co/kFjggwG6Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecPompeo @WHNSC Just Send The American Cuban s Out of Miami Florida To Take back Cuba]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ESPN can’t suck Zion’s dick if he can’t play”. Funniest thing I’ve read today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @Charlen26100183 @highbrow_nobrow Translation: Trump is involved with Epstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHuber @varjodotcom Wondering if the $6K price tag is a function of their actual costs or their assessment that… https://t.co/8h0XsCBcye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weighted blankets are for real. I've hit snooze fourteen times this morning, and I'm probably never getting out of this bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing a girl who looked just like Megan Park on  The Secret Life of the American Teenager to me look back through… https://t.co/t0AnWpuJID]]></document></documents></author>