<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You deserve mental health support. Please, reach out and get the support you deserve. Go to therapy. Talk to a frie… https://t.co/TP1Ro9UqJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRock @nbc @nbctitangames Of course he is! He inspires everyone  to be and do their own personal best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBOUCHER10 @TheGoodGodAbove My dogs just frolic all day on the farm, swim in the pond, and play in the woods. 3 go… https://t.co/dIsd3kQQ5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you all more than you all realize.  I'm sorry to all in this mess..  This is satan's final pathetic attempt… https://t.co/XeC3y63gJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find a person who makes each day Valentine's Day....like I did. 😘 Bae and I hope you enjoy #ValentinesDay2019 today… https://t.co/GmGX9Z1Hj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Producción de crudo de la OPEP toca mínimo de 4 años en febrero, la OPEP bombeó 30.68 millones de  barriles por día… https://t.co/iuAjxhRkpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wlos @JustinWLOS how did WNC’s Maggie the Newfoundland do at Westminster Dog Show today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorArcia Vault-Tec is a terrible company. Have you been to Vault 95 yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quintenpowell I only want one, to stream Amazon prime in my room, but I like my chromecast too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PassIt2Campbell he’s open! ⁦@ArizonaCoyotes⁩ up 3-2 in the 3rd https://t.co/k94Vjaj80Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion?? big time rush didn’t even compare to the jonas brothers so if you could like not make the comparison, that’d be cool???]]></document><document><![CDATA[False alarm at hotel: emergency evacuation. Scenes outside hotel prove that you CAN have smoke without fire...  😂🔥🌿… https://t.co/p5P02rbW77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandyThomson1 Just go to your local bank cash your check and leave us out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you really living your life to the fullest if you're not sleeping diagonally in your queen size bed? #bestlife… https://t.co/B9y5ZB7wAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdesmondharris ... one day you’re bitching to strangers about silly conflicts, the next your husband is dead and y… https://t.co/Wlsy9mW4Z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minduinn Brasileiro simplesmente nao se ligo que nas urnas honestas eles jamais governariam outra vez. So prender… https://t.co/CCA0sYq3bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@likepenguins @Jennicuti @HarmlessAvocado @Accelerationis1 @SAHMvoter @SocialWorkItOut We’re going to see Thunderdo… https://t.co/XbXsfHaTC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A text message like this warms a librarian mom’s heart! ♥️ I’m so glad you are a reader @malcapps! https://t.co/gsGTuOFiEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon @FallonTonight #ImproveAMovieWithOneWord  The #10YearFacebookChallenge Mermaid https://t.co/R84sev4vQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissGabbyGuns @BarackObama @MichelleObama Keep waiting. I read something earlier that he’s going to declare a nati… https://t.co/6CKFGSzl7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥇 ANNETT WINS CAREER-FIRST 🥇  #BellAthlete @MichaelAnnett drove to his first-career @NASCAR_Xfinity victory today a… https://t.co/ycLwDuGNXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly think I have the best mom in the whole world... if you know Michelle you know it too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loneliness is a barrier to positively impacting people's health #drvivekmurthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere That’s my favorite part!  Keeping one...hashtag or the name ‘bestie’.  You can pick!  #bff #besties #anahuac2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i the only one that doesn’t give a fuck about the jonas brother getting back together ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am forever buying other people kids expensive birthday gifts ... I have a terrible habit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lovedrea @SenGillibrand Then move on Trump won and he will again, enjoy your life, do something to help not spread… https://t.co/I4qvZOVMQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teewee249 @counterchekist Paralysis being the word he meant to use but didn’t know....]]></document><document><![CDATA[#highvibes stay strong 💪🏼 @ Rancho Cucamonga, California https://t.co/uSicHx5AbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked tonight! Nothing i wore matched! But my NIKE shoes felt good- and again i tell you! I walked..#babysteps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laCheybutter We just took our name out of the AB sweepstakes, we offered a 3rd prolly they refused must've]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another reason why StFX is an excellent institution &amp; creates/inspires leaders of tomorrow 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[She did it! I’m so proud of Ms Tammy. All her life she dedicated everything she does for her family until she gives… https://t.co/eJYajw1FVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@YvesRocherFR acts beautiful in France but real ugly in Turkey where 132 mostly women workers were brutally fired… https://t.co/DknibiUJ0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metalmancave @tcm @boderek I beg to differ. @therealmstreep Stats prove otherwise : https://t.co/bpK0g1j86f]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeaaa, Yaya may look dumb with young boy, but atleast she dumb &amp; rich ASF . 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___idi Not when this hotel that I have no reservation at stole all my money 🙃 https://t.co/UBYIohwO3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@himanshuPSingh @Poseidon34Live @NaomiKyle Opinions on twitter are bad. Got it. Seriously, you don’t have to tell m… https://t.co/ySh64sEc8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[____ F. L. Y. First Love Yourself ____  ______ Others will come next ______  #MondayMotivation @ Lakewood, Ohio https://t.co/BJG2WzppLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sZUhZ3WOuk @DwntwnNashville at @KidRock's yep!!! #HotBands #LiveMusic @NashvilleScene]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu No. It feels more like “You hurt me, now I’ll hurt you with the truth” retribution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my son was video chatting w his daddy and about had a damn heart attack when he hung up . like he wasn't done gooo'… https://t.co/tWOUpxXANS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinaverner @vancelockton Great addition to the team at @WaterfrontTO !]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing review!  . . . . #georgiarealestate #middlegarealtor #newhomeconstruction #realtor®… https://t.co/xh1nkq3wFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s exactly how I feel in LA 🎨👑🌟🧩♥️ like in @nintendoamerica game 🎲🎰👾Princess Peach 👸🏼 character from Mario 🎮 pa… https://t.co/pE2ABCzp67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinnershells All the time!! Aww that just of been so much fun! I hope you had a blast!! 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t get on a boat, did you even go to #Miami?! Happy weekend travel tribe - sending you warm vibes! ☀️🛥… https://t.co/ccz53TWmPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivingMyBestLife #OneDayAtATime #ILoveMyLife #BestFeelingEver #IAmSober #Truth #ODAAT @ Positive Vibes Only https://t.co/xqW1ByVndR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fantasculine It wasn’t even the only listing with $0, like multiple companies thought that was reasonable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a good time at #CaptainMarvel Her powers are awesome, Goose was great, and the music ticked all the right boxes… https://t.co/1r8yqdDjKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So for some reason I drank dumb bitch juice today, not realizing I had a test for AP gov, and knowing I have shit l… https://t.co/OnM40c2uyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this awesome contest by @TheRogueEnergy! https://t.co/pUupENLIAQ #giveaway #RogueEnergy #contest #gaming #gamingdrink]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surfin’ through the flames  Panic! At The Disco at @theforum https://t.co/KT04ybdiJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S FINALLY HERE!! THANKS @buyIegaImeds 😍 I'm so excited to try everything! https://t.co/dRS6cL747R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold day ahead-even by February standards! #Inwx #4yourmorning @CBS4Indy #indy https://t.co/PSToXm5zEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Spider-verse 2. Coco 3. Frozen 4. Kubo and the Two Strings 5. Inside Out 6. Big Hero Six 7. Brave 9. Toy Story 3… https://t.co/YbxNS7KJh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go @OGBball Keep grinding and make it happen! #ringchasing #trophycollecting #warriorpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of my 7 day Book Cover Challenge goes to @stephaniekribs .  Post 7 covers of books you love - no explanations… https://t.co/NSbuExXU8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did research on the  @MaskedSingerFOX and the monster is for sure T Pain!! 100000%]]></document><document><![CDATA[But Colton, should you be taking relationship advice from Ben Higgins??? #itsanofrommedawg #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If John Wilkes Booth killed Lincoln, why isn’t it in the history books?” @JCBonilla23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mares62J @KingMiles79NHL @JamesBumgarner7 @ABC7Chicago I knew that 😂😂😂. That bunk bed gif A+ gif use I was rolling]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a hard time believing this is in Rwanda 😍  OMG  I spend the rest of my life here 😊😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio who are these WOOO people that’s the dumbest shit I ever heard.  #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been two days since I’ve had carrot juice and I feel like I’m dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love a musical where there's a whole witty song about hating men. #relatable (Yeah, yeah, we know "not all men")… https://t.co/i32ZwS2ymb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My galentines outfit. Happy valentines Day! What a strange day it is! https://t.co/JudBoEpvXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i could probably fall asleep listening to @ElizabeeHinkler and @EmilyHinkler voices cause they’re soothing 😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @SadhguruJV (get_repost) ・・・ An elected government is BY THE PEOPLE. Only when it does not work FOR THE PEO… https://t.co/LiCKKXY3QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a suicidal patient today   “I heard you were feeling suicidal?”  *takes one look at the doctor “You make me… https://t.co/0JhTnM3apR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeriDChristiano @DougDavidsonYR Thanks for sharing one more side of the Doug we all know and love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuidicottiJr @Th3Re4lMackyG @Honeybadger1978 @JosephNSanberg Have you ever been to Scandinavia? They’re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay is this gonna be on YouTube? Or is it now? Please I need to watch it 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subject I’ll stay awake for: who transcendence, ego repression, and how to develop a secure attachment while single]]></document><document><![CDATA[73 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/UcizXDvci0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @shuna551 @FaithWalkPeace @BenJackd1 @GodFirstGina @phillyeaglesfa1 @AsiaTater @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs… https://t.co/fPtlE2eKer]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had an amazing time with @krshelnutt today. Designing our own houses after sharing “I Built A House” by… https://t.co/bdLROYnVyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait for vacations all next year and for the rest of my life. i’ve worked way too hard😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bug82Chicago @sarah_palooza @Drudown79 @CBSThisMorning how does a parent stop a 19yo who's in college with their own job and place?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great idea for our teachers in support of our WRaP initiative. @SchoolsLb @natasha_nurse @clamarca16 @Lau7210… https://t.co/zEX7l6sOK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatimaQuishpe Mi mamá recuperó lo de las pólizas, no creo lo de las cuentas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 893 Norton Ave #Barberton #OH  #realestate https://t.co/AbN9pXVTJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my cousin Kandis yesss @ Moments Grill &amp; Lounge https://t.co/foRMk6b0dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @thomaskaine5 for continuing to raise awareness about #RealityWinner !  Everyone should tag their Represe… https://t.co/zaaZo0xAab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNormanCSauce3 @JordanHillElem @GriffinSpalding So enjoyable!  Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#evitaparty with the sis #juanasmoke #ratchetandgay #bejukupcake666 #nonbinarypride #clubkid #bejukupcake666 #beyou… https://t.co/N4bcB53ty2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#exposeanimalabuse #msasecurityisantimilitary #glenkuceraabusesdogsforprofit #msasecurity #perellaweinbergpartners… https://t.co/LVS5iRXFXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting a Vlog!  Episode one is now up on YouTube and the link is in my bio.  #linkinbio Subscribe to follow a… https://t.co/8Q7O0n9rJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was pulling children from a socialist indoctrination program and then having them vote,crazy!  Even some democra… https://t.co/5JrOa3MAb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovInslee. If the state votes to stay on day light savings time year round we will need Fed approval. Standard tim… https://t.co/EuJJAs4xng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatermarkChurch @Ben_Stuart_ What???? Is Ben Stuart preaching there today?? Will he be preaching at the 5pm service?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Herbert_L_Reed Wow, another one Bites the dust! I loved her acting and her movies! But hate her views on Politics,… https://t.co/XOOfm69fsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanWPTV @WPTV They havent learned from the Covington student. Who do these people think they are bullying child… https://t.co/4HPcoYX092]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed CREEP ... and I’m not even a fan of today’s horror films for the most part. One of my favorite films, tho… https://t.co/eDZdesQgZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[9-24-2018: 🏈MNF🏈 - 1️⃣ #Monday #Tampa #TampaBay #Clearwater #ClearwaterBeach #Florida #LoveFL #FL #MNF #football… https://t.co/mmpIz0EN5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today when I went to CFA, my total was $6.66 and I added an orange juice when I heard the total. Then, proceeded to… https://t.co/dm1lBl6hM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun announcing the Pot ‘O Gold 10k! ☘️ We’re ready for you to finish runners! @PRR_OneLoudoun @PRRunning… https://t.co/PoUDbVuhtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bavlook Then she should have made sure that was in her contract. She is mad because they ASKED her to do it for fr… https://t.co/YPNO6DAETM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard I try not to hear any of that con shit? And you just put it on your show like youare proud to… https://t.co/GQoz6aBwHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllyIntrieri @Mariska @Mariska can pretty much do anything, we surely have seen it through the years on SVU.]]></document></documents></author>