<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BazTastic77 So along those same lines, I’ve been watching the Netflix Doc on Sunderland. How do teams survive afte… https://t.co/WZm5ZAgbSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please explain to me how dancing in a club and struggling to hear people standing right next to you is "fun"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is giving the Saudis US secrets on our building bombs of massive destruction!!! Why? Wtf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been at a UNC-Duke senior night. It’s one of the best 5 moments of my life. I gotta go back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiComo @SNYtv @MLBTV double the chance for injuries and DL visits! @mets baseball fever! catch it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Midday180 ?? Are we not supposed to eat every Girl Scout cookie in one sitting....? #tagalong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge win today as i ate a yogurt before bed at 10am and woke up at 4am hungry and ate a Rise protein bar then fell… https://t.co/c15GHULCON]]></document><document><![CDATA[And mind you, it’s been 30 years since I lived in Corvallis, but unless something crazy has been going on in Oregon… https://t.co/Il1lTd90kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_saenz7 @ESPNFC @neymarjr That’s definitely happening next drunken bar night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRickScott @SenateAging You must be shitting me!! luckily none of them tried to call your cell phone... you know… https://t.co/FQskNpfo4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DotComCTO @thehill Did you see in the news recently about the young man that was raised without vaccines, but as s… https://t.co/cn1wEdE53P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 And committed to helping fix Climate Change. You need balance!  "The Sanders campaign purchased near… https://t.co/NmyqZRqeI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevekerr, A great coach, winning player and outstanding broadcaster. By the way, I wish every box score had the p… https://t.co/HYkLh2aUUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kokasses @BethHay60070460 @Jim_Jordan Well let's build the wall and keep the dinosaurs out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realMikeLindell Market research will be completed within a week and we expect expect spectacular results.  Would y… https://t.co/LdQgMjXvJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our teachers have a planning day each week. Today is the math teacher’s planning day. I overheard @MsSydney_LPS and… https://t.co/KMSYoP5DVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never sell the Menlo Park abode now matter how bad the neighborhood gets 480-418-7953  Re SPAM FROM +1 (480) 4… https://t.co/ae00qMabVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKolfage @gehrig38 @DeplorableChoir @RyanAFournier @SheriffClarke @RealJamesWoods @Lrihendry @gatewaypundit… https://t.co/BZlRzZfCrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign to oppose David Bernhardt’s nomination for Secretary of the Interior Department. Sign here: https://t.co/FT7AhH0ldR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did they show Jesus on the Walking Dead? I thought his character died.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people... That defend Michael Jackson. I get it. You love him! But the ones he abused, also loved him. He man… https://t.co/ntr9bJlC4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveDespain And they shoulda had a ten minute time out to get the backup car and take care of business!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOMAXO @Sowokeitswoke @AOC I don’t care what her religion is, I don’t care for conservative anti Semites either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Cody get into these back n forth scraps knowing it hasn’t worked for him the last few fights? Gotta feel for him #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, the Democratic party are like the adults on the Charlie Brown Cartoon when they talk. Blah blah blah as they l… https://t.co/CqXgbkwlrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisfenwick Next I’ll watch Ocean’s 11, Ocean’s Eleven, Ocean’s Eight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video recaps of all NBA games coming to Facebook Watch https://t.co/B05Am6LeSI via @inquirerdotnet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine for #GAMEDAY! We go for the season sweep of North Dakota at 10 am MT!   #PlayHST #PioneerTogether https://t.co/lrZBKCoJLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because love grows when nothing else is certain, changing its shape to fill the space required” #CallTheMidwife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - MSNBC Daily:     WSJ: Cohen directed his lawyer to ask about a pardon contradicting testimony;… https://t.co/ZJgQg9IkFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackinthebox216 I’ve already slept for 6 hours....this is intermission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marca EL TAPETE LAMEHUEV.. solari LE HA HECHO UN DAÑO ENORME A REAL MADRID, NO ENTIENDE QUE ISCO, MARCELO Y KEYLOR… https://t.co/YhBv4no0JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greiromero @Uber_DOM En la aplicación hay una forma de quejarse por esto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby In Understanding. This gun has no Safety switch. That is a Lock Out that must be moved be pulling the… https://t.co/RKZPjGQwRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...I can only do 10, so my heart risk disease must be really high. How many push-ups can you do? Study finds me… https://t.co/Pxy0lHyihp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JUBRAN_027 Orlando making the play offs, nuggets potentially a #1 seed. Lebron missing the play offs. What a year… https://t.co/FzLXX6jXy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeaghanDRoy The score in Cold Downtown Apsley is 3-2 Uxbridge Bruins over North Kawartha Knights after 2 periods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfranz917 @BernieSanders Every dollar of insurance industry profit is a dollar stolen from health care delivery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, a good sour IPA. 6/10 sourness, balanced perfectly with sweet fruitiness. Major tangerine flavor, no harsh… https://t.co/MwflNllLtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you get my premium for my Valentines Day show 😏 https://t.co/tPKNzXUvJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodtimeGibbins @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews For what? Another 20 tweets    whining about McCabe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eternal0Star @aravosis Your an idiot. And the MSM does blame every storm on Trump because he dropped out the Paris climate accord basically]]></document><document><![CDATA[FaceTiming Mila when I’m on my lunch makes me so sad, I wish I could just stay home with her ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the Division II state championship game went to double overtime, expect the Walker-Thibodaux game to start… https://t.co/OGTfjM9cGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the #BrownsTwitter elitists act as if you had to have heard of the kid prior to the combine.   It’s “okay”… https://t.co/maZLiymKfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GDB181 Y lo peor, los chairos cuestionando a esos organismos: “donde estaban con el neoliberalismo”.... es una orgía de estupidez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EITMonline  Can you put the word out to avoid oland rude in Frederick County there is a pothole that is killing cars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Well I'd be dating Jennifer Aniston if I could. Both my scenario and Mr. O'Rourke's and mine have one thi… https://t.co/fuSVL71ITA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And this they did, not as we hoped, but first gave their own selves to the Lord, and unto us by the will of God.” 2 Corinthians 8:5 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Florida. . .the state has history of electing criminals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife just told me she wanted to go to crapplebees for half off apps tonight. HUGE WIN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being smart doesn't mean you get to be rude!!!!!!!!!!! and being nice doesn't mean ur dumb!!!!!!! caring about femi… https://t.co/fpJklfvNqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeimBBQ Best ❤️day lunch!  #baconburntends #bananapudding https://t.co/vEtTRLcyBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don't understand that just cuz a car is super clean it makes the car worth more on KBB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanesHook I am a big fan of Lady Bird, and Chalamet's character has been described as a "Garbage Crush," which say… https://t.co/fZE8wBUVMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyGoGo_ If he's stupid enough to lose s good guy like you you'll be smart to let him go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @RealMattCouch There is a lot that comes into play. It begins with the liberal brainwashing in our edu… https://t.co/966EVYMm29]]></document><document><![CDATA[And throw 45 ,, Colt,,, over top of you all,,because, few, dollar seed has Ben stolen,,,and my name is the  one,,,,… https://t.co/ejnUV3Pk7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch: Colorado cops swarm and pull guns on black college student picking up trash in his own yard https://t.co/PbfU6u4pD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GxldenSubstance lol my new favorite show and let me hold something thennn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort @AngelGotti5 She was the best impersonator of Aunt Esther from Sanford and Son?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incident behind Pizza Hut on 72nd and Pecos. Entire building in crime scene tape. Multiple Adams county sheriff at the scene]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GRCosplayKid @CodyRhodes @MrsBurris12 @WWEC_ERA @smarktodeath @SmarkdownRadio @MartyScurll @Tama_Tonga https://t.co/ShAfOqFftz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. My US history teacher used it in a lesson plan.  More than a decade later, it’s known as the song that sounds… https://t.co/tq6i55pA6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the Krewe of Hermes to the volunteers at muttvillesf #HappyMardiGras #eatthebaby @ Arizmendi: Mission https://t.co/0KSnjBJm3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFelicello @casas_jimmy @rocklandboces @SESPirates @RossCoops31 @AJBianco @TonySinanis @AngelaStockman… https://t.co/a7lK0U8i7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beavis2017WA Apology not accepted lock him up. He is learning from daddy shitgibbon https://t.co/yHxWxYYRVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_tom @ChickfilA When I get my free Starbucks purchase I make them pay with some $7-8 fancy something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Onward and upward we go to ⁦@CityofTampa⁩ via ⁦@united⁩ ✈️ . #sunshinestate #tampa #chicago #unitedAIRLINES… https://t.co/pn4y3MSDat]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABC News Bullies the WRONG Person and They Instantly Regret It https://t.co/1AuLqP0DNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day started ruff but it ended with a wagon ride to the moon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RpmacPaul Good morning Paul! So, which one are you? 🤔😳😂☕️☕️ https://t.co/nHSmtCu3Zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[www.strangeness-a... #laughter #snicker #smile #hilarious https://t.co/KxO4bfUvRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinaret @hjlodge @jessidee Have you had the dan dan noodles? We had em without peanuts, and loved them. The Hunan chicken is tasty too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@srginder⁩ 🤩 meeting her childhood ⁦@MLB⁩ @royals hero, #georgebrett here in ⁦@TS_Resort⁩ #foreverRoyal… https://t.co/rg2ROizHI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTylerJohns please consider @Evan_McGuyer 6'2 280 C,G Miamisburg OH c/o 20. 2 year varsity starter. 3.3gpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffanywctv @WCTV Chick-fil-a going fishy???? How is their mascot taking it?...lol. I would try it if they have them down here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If she was allowed to return she could be charged with treason. She joined an enemy combatant of the USA and under… https://t.co/Rti6S646b8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be home, but also not.  Definitely going to move to Germany 🇩🇪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a couple episodes until I am all caught up. By far, my favorite character is Bronn of the Blackwater. Salty, s… https://t.co/XhBqpHoA7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 25 Washington leads @CalMBBall 16-10 at 14:17 of 1st half. Huskies are 4 of 5 from 3-point, two each by Jaylen Nowell and David Crisp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 9 Pound Hammer (2019+) by @bluejacketdc at @Bluejacketdc — https://t.co/SdRjj8SOFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karinamag2008 @ekbufalo @MiguelFontan Señora eso se llama improvisación,estoy en total desacuerdo con usted,mi lib… https://t.co/v3PrqiPAHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsleListenPod @Isles_Life @VainPretense How bout some of the trade deadlines when he was with the team? Hmm you kn… https://t.co/E9rJ0thQVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen is fantastic!!! God Bless #FreddieMercury GREAT singer and performer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScaryKrystal I’ve been awake since 7 pm last night so I’m not all there and sleepy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginians can now file their 2018 tax returns now that 2018 tax law is settled! https://t.co/zG2ktROChb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck moved to the shoulder in #WakeCounty on I-40 EB at Lk Wheeler Rd - Exit 297 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Une certaine effervescence au Centre spatial Kennedy ce matin.  La nuit prochaine, @SpaceX va tester son nouveau vé… https://t.co/4MWPoeqzqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got flowers from andrew for being so sick. Thank you andrewg616 #flowers #cutflowers #hyvee @ Des Moines, Iowa https://t.co/YaXgZuTX0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one:  Me: so you wanna know what I’m doing with my spring break https://t.co/nM3UeQNx18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice segment. Great commitment from Priscilla Chan. But to be clear - the “First Lady” of @tlm is co-founder… https://t.co/zn6QxCC0zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevputz I suppose you’d rather have another warmongering corporate shill to vote for. Like last time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get help before you hurt yourself or someone else. We should report you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the other girl paint with all the colors of the wind??? I think the fuck not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong @DailyCaller “Why shit, I hates Jews as well as N......s too!!!”   What to you expect from a racist… https://t.co/bEKLNhwOJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JourdanRodrigue @josephperson @PanthersBill @PanthersBryan what are some ways for the Panthers to create cap space: Kalil? Addison?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WorldOfColor returns to the #Disneyland Resort after a long absence – Orange County Register   https://t.co/QWgb96MhGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thelegomovie2 #lego #film #cinema #movie #nowwatching https://t.co/cFxinUqZI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[LaCroix CEO clearly thinks he can sell sparkling water and change the world at the same time. https://t.co/1Mwf7o90jl #LaCroix]]></document></documents></author>