<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Stiff competition with @JennyHart, who continues to beat me in the SEO game 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ditto!  Great move up @ChildrensColo Keep on keepin on @TCHOrtho_Sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieWebber10 @inaturalist There are very few that can actually hurt you in any way. I encourage them because th… https://t.co/2iNzsUXb5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful message!  Your obedience led to breakthroughs and blessings. Praying for you as you prepare this week for… https://t.co/MHWm7AMTj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay home now. Day 1 of driving: mission accomplished. I got to and from work, I picked up my dad’s birthday presen… https://t.co/kpR381hQWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support sports for kids. Of course. 🤷🏼‍♀️ #USAAServes https://t.co/YTrf62Maom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo a mi se me ocurre tomar óxido bien noche y ahorita no puedo dormir, lo peor es que estoy pensando puras pendejadas, aagg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynds_brianne Omg good luck!! I’ll be in the area in April — we should grab another bite to eat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr gave Michael Cohen $70,000 for Valentine's Day. I am sure the irony was l… https://t.co/kGkyBKGMrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybellew Columbus did get damage.  @WCBIWEATHER hasn't picked up their live storm coverage yet.  I heard they'r… https://t.co/QJSOqhn2xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayla_ebner These Bristol residents know the answer ⬇️⬇️⬇️ https://t.co/IVfNdWL9xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoisedSpeaker @straightillin48 @AnneP_NC @firstnamescott @Variety When I look at the entire school system througho… https://t.co/xfjdgT7PsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mets gave a left-handed specialist 10 million to give up homers to lefties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously? What an unsubstantiated hit piece about nothing of substance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time a mom says their newborn won’t sleep without being in their arms I just wanna yell “swaddle that bihhh”… https://t.co/12GuKLX5w4]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be honest I’m not a huge fan of NYC but on my way to the airport as we drove past manhattan I felt a strange fon… https://t.co/yWikA53jFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in your hair; don’t care ❤️ Took the boys to my favorite childhood sledding spot in the motherland. Reminisced… https://t.co/Wy3YS1uR6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #purpleday please get informed if u have a #lovedone with #Epilepsy We deal with enough w/o stigmatized guesse… https://t.co/lK3Gf2BAfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[For any of you twits peddling the "it's a work because @WWERomanReigns doesn't look like he has #Leukemia" , please… https://t.co/8PY7neFOdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💛vs ❤️🖤 still best friends. @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/eJ4UjBQh57]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOTIVATIONAL WEDNESDAY  Imagine a child running back and forth, chasing bubbles, jumping and grinning in delight. W… https://t.co/CIqzGguWCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @JoeNBC Joe and Mika were attending his New Year's party until Trump attacked Mika then things changed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNC-Lavalin paid for Gadhafi son's debauchery while he was in Canada: report https://t.co/TLV4W7v0Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elian passed the most iReady lessons last week! Keep up the great work! @SLESeahawks https://t.co/eThYVCwvKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[not suprised my little sister painted her room the exact same color as mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm married. No I am NOT interested in anyone DMing me, or anyone who's Twitter profile looks like a dating site.… https://t.co/FDYNRcL02P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of the 7 day book cover challenge. Today I nominate @MrsKCBender Post covers of your favourite books . One co… https://t.co/7ce4ao1w7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassidyWrightt OMG !!!!!!!  It’s you !!!!   You made my sleepy ass wake up !! Thank you !!!😫😫♥️♥️🧡🧡🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[- mom just reminded me of the time she bought me flowers for Valentine’s Day...and put “anonymous” on the card...be… https://t.co/EXfbOVQWxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnkurMa15287277 I am @PhiBetaKappa and do not spit on a western education or assume that my education was not dive… https://t.co/MaZjxKMnlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who has 5 jobs including 3 on campus, 1 internship and 1 off campus!! Ya girls gonna get that dough so I can… https://t.co/M3zS93A194]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support indie artists, indie music &amp; indie makers! #Respect #Salute • • • • #supportindieartists… https://t.co/MQQTeDf444]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Wells Fargo team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/Les8kVsSrj #HR #Charlotte, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon I have been to Hawaii many times, so I would pick probably the Caribbean. But would be just as happy with… https://t.co/CAwFg5k5T3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summerbrees84 @SHusvar @cvpayne Read what she attached, names them all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlidellPD That’s y I hate @DIRECTV I swear it only happens on #livepd nights!! I end up watching on my phone then… https://t.co/gLAqPygsVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidP4AD Do these investors have no relatives that have cancer that need these drugs? Or are they disguised in mu… https://t.co/dQHHz7GNFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland It took eight volunteer firefighters to pop the overweight rodent out of a vent in the sewer cover… https://t.co/iFepGLmxEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Behold, I’m standing at the door, knocking. If your heart is open to hear my voice and you open the door within, I… https://t.co/YPECUFekfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sconce &amp; flooring reflect the time period of this Old North home. #forsale #oldnorthlondon #louiselists… https://t.co/SSpByZoH91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twmadden4 @AffinityImage @_PapaulskiBCFC_ @WhiteHouse @IvankaTrump Boy, sure has aged Cortez.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBachelor how do you "break up" with a woman you've never been in a relationship? Really....tell me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah @thealexnewell singing “Ireland” is super impressive but you know what else is impressive? The fact that I was… https://t.co/l5XfrY6P4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lived here since I was 4 years old and I think this is the first time this has happened, so it’s not something… https://t.co/jGdlQJRw3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CashApp do you have any atm partners where I can use my card and not get fee’d?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna Venmo me the rest of my school tuition... that would be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keirabisexual @mattdkerr @elbirdilara @CaNettoyant Half of America would be unemployed if racist’s were not allowed to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is up to something. There's a reason why you went through what you went through...Trust the process. He's got YOU!♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’d been discussing the news, so I texted my boss a link. About 10 minutes later she opened it up, the entire offi… https://t.co/1YpSiEFyHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No he can’t - no one in America is surprised @realDonaldTrump can’t make a deal on anything positive for the USA -… https://t.co/R5TJGDXbIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa wait @aubreykmiller !! Did you see how #Jimin was looking at you! 💜🥰💜 He wasn’t even blinking!! 😂 #BTS #BTSARMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we welcomed visitors to our annual Parent Academy. 5th grade parents collected observation notes in classroom… https://t.co/fS3fr3mSVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib Really? When did Trump ever praise any white supremacists or Neo Nazis?  Yet we've seen fascist Democ… https://t.co/QWBl7sPbtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billyeichner So when r u going to apologize? #Trump2020 #JussieSmolettHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RokhySeck @jonasbrothers @nickjonas @kevinjonas @joejonas SO happy you found this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vav717 @LaLiga @HoustonCules @FCBPenyes @FCBarcelona Oleeeee en el watch party de rio! Que crack! Soooo good]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Valentines Day I’m gonna fill up and check out my bf Amazon cart... using his card. ❤️. He’ll cancel that mess so fast. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know a good dry cleaner? I’m trying to get some jeans properly starched.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SanJose not so #WetAndWild  right now but #JimCity #Napa #Guerneville another story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of people walking home from work with flowers in their hands is PRECIOUS!!!! Love is in NYC and I’m here for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenna_mozzocio @John_Mozzocio God Bless you @John_Mozzocio  for all of the things you do for NCASD! Very well dese… https://t.co/xsuVqehFiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The rule of thumb: 50% of your income goes to needs, 30% to fun, and 20% to future you (401k or funding a business… https://t.co/tl0rhKFTO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best. Day. Ever. #thewolfffarm #dayoldchicks #ducklingsaremyfavorite @ Chelsea, Michigan https://t.co/XEp8CL67XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 He knew that the Russians were interfering in the election-- he reaped the benefits &amp; didn't speak out against it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyMartyniak I'm old. Now it's 7:30-8 on days off . And it's only 7 mins. It will be all over twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost the brush I use to do my eyebrows a couple days ago, and honestly since then I’ve just given up on life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, men out here thinking they a Clark Kent but they’re really Jokers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado River’s decline poses long-term risks for Southern Nevada https://t.co/p9abcwZ3G0 via @reviewjournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTA The Manhattan bound Bedford Park 4:08 D train came and left early. How late is the 4:28 train going to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachel_w @bethdlindsay Have a wonderful conference! That's s good one :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMeade23 @acely74 She did such a great job! It was a super helpful and productive day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s better than a golden ticket? A pink one 🎟. #bestfriendgoals #bestie #birthday #chuanspa #spaday #massage… https://t.co/WhaGG3tAOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright single men of the 518, it’s National Margarita Day...who’s gonna take me out for one ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrific to reconnect and be interviewed by @DevinThorpe on the show Your Mark on the World - great discussion on w… https://t.co/Xmi2GhC9AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalHistory_ I sometimes cancel class even when the university is open because weather conditions are prohibiti… https://t.co/eWeycy65nB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take it all back. KARMA is a real thing. Day 2 being stuck at the @ATLairport has me like 😫😭😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is just around the corner 💞 cum $poil me so I can spoil you! $end to one of the links below and DM… https://t.co/0xZD2o981t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento Want change? Support @AsmKevinMcCarty and #AB392 to modernize California’s outdated use of force sta… https://t.co/FdlFZ8ghF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rosie does this at 3 am when we all trying to sleep tf I’m taking her ass to America’s got talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloCheer @McConnellWendy @Peach_Rays I’m in love with the flyer on the right, serving everyone the look!  👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cavs coach Larry Drew said @RealTristan13 (sore left foot) must go through another full contact practice before he can be cleared to return]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a couple of my favs 💖 @punkyred9 rosstheboss01 @ The Hawk https://t.co/5Mmx4tLiIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[U ever try to tell someone how you feel and they try to tell you otherwise???? Yeah haha I’m mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QVC i am disgusted you have mike lindell on your network he is unfit to be there selling his jesus pillows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelle_spenc @BubblesResists @Gary_ARSC @KristyLyn11 @broadwatertmb @Hollenbeck_Girl @Sky_Lee_1 @FireGoddessB… https://t.co/rLmnA7goIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A powerful alliance is being built between a million transit riders and 13000 #TTC transit workers to improve trans… https://t.co/bjKVg3ZQJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes God lets bad things happen so that we draw closer to him and ask him for help and talk with him because t… https://t.co/eMSvQzCcaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbrennansports App State's Ultimate Frisbee teams are the Nomads and the Nonads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Cool and come to West Side Story this weekend!  @Islands_Sharks #theatrelife https://t.co/UxrEeRm8ig https://t.co/FmNq3gjb5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimchite Yes!! It started off when a friend misspelled my name, and it was a downward spiral from there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar I wouldn't have voted for a repub anyway, but wazzisface would have lost me on strapping his dog to the top of his car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @SpeakerPelosi @WhiteHouse @SecNielsen @GOPLeader @DHSgov @CBP_McAleenan   #FixIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lil_bouz @ShawnMendes It was so rude of her to call us out. we get it. We’re older than everyone else by just a fe… https://t.co/3f5t01YTSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Conner_G why don't you try running that same comparative analysis on Amari Cooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiekroach @Jillfinee @iamValC @DanceWithMeUSA You’ll be spectacular! So proud of you. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRUHHHHHHH I’VE CALLED @i_dropbombs16 LIKE 4 TIMES TODAY!!!!!!!!!!!! Pick up my nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[It wasn’t snowing this day (oddly enough considering how this winter has been going) but gosh darn it all they need… https://t.co/esoXplepo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@ilceducators developed a strategy to use teachers to share ongoing PD with colleagues on their campus and across… https://t.co/giAN8MwvPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay focused. Stay Faithful. Stay committed to what God has called you to and watch and see what He will do.… https://t.co/FJpKSGsfMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy Cierto y Soy una de Ellas pues pensé que  tendría el resto de la semana para               ' ponerme al día con… https://t.co/0ZCdGmfZkg]]></document></documents></author>