<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I won’t tell you her age because she’d be upset with me, but it’s my big sister Melissa’s birthday today! She has b… https://t.co/iGsrHljlGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[J- what do you think now? C- what all of you do with our system, and us helping you seems to do a lot J- I see C- l… https://t.co/L9aLz1WWY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightOnNicole @united That’s pretty ridiculous as it’s not like you’ve bought a ticket from Boeing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairlemon Much of any cash transfers will eventually be consumed by increases in rent. However, that’s also true… https://t.co/hvBeG31E99]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Books By Kids” Our goal is for  kids to build their confidence  by reading in front of others while getting a hair… https://t.co/i79Pam9xgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish there was a way to find you were living in the "Good Ol Times" before they became the "Good Ol Times". I let… https://t.co/9LrGB2ibyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrueggs There is nothing better then dipping French fries in bottle of red sauce, but adding mayo...is nothing sacred....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept the 7 day book challenge from @BPS_Supt &amp; nominate @bootnumlock. My 1st book choice is... https://t.co/RVXSWwKvG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Juan my friend, if Trump has an army on social media defending him, and there are thousands more t… https://t.co/Q7MqSukAk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FRANA_OW is my weakness I think I’d faint if I met her in person! 😍❤️ she’s just so beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freeport takes down Mountain Valley in quarterfinals @FreeportFalcons https://t.co/GyR95wfghR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to disagree. @realDonaldTrump Is way to lazy. Jesse Jackson says Trump would probably have been 'with the st… https://t.co/vxOJJpOLCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[So — Captain Marvel is a must-see. Or, should I say...Captain Mar-Vell...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DVNCallihan It starts at the top with the vision and tone set by the head coach....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want the Lakers to be back on top again is that too much to ask. Tired of all the losing especially with Bron… https://t.co/6m5jk8Tt6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Werewolf_King_ @nyjets @RapSheet @nflnetwork I agree I still love bilal shore up the o line and Crowell n maguire are good enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReynoldsWolf Thank you for sharing the story of the #NeverForgottenCoast Campaign! We will be in ATL this coming w… https://t.co/vLEVaygkPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheila_Copps Typical liberal talking point. "Sheer is scary" fear mongering with no facts. How are you still relevant today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the vile responses to this tweet. "so what? who cares? not everything revolves around gays! get over it!"https://t.co/ieoy920eUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleayers No problem! You should have Keith and Jesse from @NewPlayerPod on the show. They are in the Starburns fa… https://t.co/wOUGB2B5nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyletssmoak @starmensch You’re young. I’m old. I come in peace.  Think about the consequences of those words and… https://t.co/c48Jjb7UHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah bro just quote it or retweet it that didn’t even deserve a screen shot to my phone you wild wild 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[People depend on the tax return so much, depending on the government the worst thing you could do]]></document><document><![CDATA[#datenight with my Gorgeous Wife mkfryesworld  #alive tour with @bdwmusic 🎶was a very Spiritually🕊moving show!  I f… https://t.co/4f8cOaOGp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We never know what's around the corner. It could be everything. Or it could be nothing. Have the faith to let life… https://t.co/5Kb49xUfv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the problem with liars.  They tell so many that they are bound to trip up every time.  Tell the truth, remem… https://t.co/P7PL7djQN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Ummm Congress can delegate its authority to @realDonaldTrump . Where were you for the last 25 National emergencies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoNonsenseMofo @Metallica The more you do it the easier it gets. Take it slowly till your body gets used to the routine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRey77 @AndrewScheer @Tigergeorgie Who's talking about cutting OAS?I said a raise would help more than his cutti… https://t.co/8gaqvTWyo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting to think that the @TopekaHockey Playoff Chances are starting fade. They showing that they defense isn'… https://t.co/TAjFtBGTSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman Should have made this a 10-year deal with 9 player options that include $20m in signing bonuses for each option picked up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday.  #fuckit #ramen #hungry @ New York, New York https://t.co/2Rp6aL0Xme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Renting a car at an airport sucks. I hereby amend all of my previous commentary about any one particular car rental… https://t.co/iIWSBwC0FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opuntia Microdasys Bunny Ears cactus + heat pack included in price https://t.co/ikziQiKAlp https://t.co/MLzXbsACDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[THH 10th Birthday with @zzdmo for a @FortniteGame slumber party. 14 ten year olds. Many skins.  WiFi strapped https://t.co/HadUH3fqYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC #Breaking News Alert:      FAA says U.S. airlines can still fly the Boeing jet model that has been involved in… https://t.co/e0ZjkaEt69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work with tremendous leaders like @oliverschulkin, @amy_e_weaver, @tony_prophet and @pdgoldman guiding us… https://t.co/dB3W622ikA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need an immigration system that secures our borders, upholds the law, &amp; boosts the economy. Come to the 2019… https://t.co/frApZTDg7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisvonAhn @RenatoFranco30 @VictoriaSando_ @lf_prieto @Adrian26836712 Pregunta honesta. El estado o el pueblo chino es más rico?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsweek has hit a new low.  I watched this exchange and this is complete fabrication of the facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manriquehector Pa ver tu lògica. Si pido ganar la loterìa ¿se me da? Si pido no maten Pemòn ¿Se me da? Ahhhh es qu… https://t.co/7i1X7YVuP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSherrodBrown @lavndrblue thank you , great ideas ....   @SenatorBurr @SenThomTillis you two should spend some t… https://t.co/6MxQM6yZNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiSixx I’m new to Netflix.  I searched for The Dirt but can’t find it.  I know it’s not available until March b… https://t.co/qDBhyxGdj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TuckerCarlson FYI: Oprah IS NOT a biblical name. Orpah IS however. #spellcheck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GKBDistrict @StedersDeKalb r we going on a 2 hour dealy???? or r we gonna normal time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeDGEinald @officialclanaod Woww seeing those screen names again.. this has def been on a forgotten shelf in my mind for a long time  😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaWatson @RapeCrisisEandW @EVAWuk @emmacharlotte I love you the most I care for you with the love of God more tr… https://t.co/Svk1vbAbcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I went to the mall wearing shorts and sooo many people just stared at me 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most shocking thing about this season is learning that Jon Horst might actually be good at his job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really cool story about one of the most interesting broadcast pairings in all of sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRass44 @LeBatardShow Love it! But this was a new show, one on one with Pat Riley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great thread on the dangers of estimation. Very timely given our conversation on @ManagingUpShow about estimates th… https://t.co/e0ZjnKR5tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope and pray that this stat won’t be a problem come March.  #Duke]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's amazing that @miketirico is calling hockey games for @NBCSports and of course @NHLonNBCSports but it begs the… https://t.co/JNkOU5e6Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC I would rather have someone in Congress that has our local interests in mind. That's why they were elected!… https://t.co/KAPv2FGMZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i understand this argument but it is impossible to just ignore the fact that college is EXPONENTIALLY more expensiv… https://t.co/QGuxWhRVlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in need of a Big Lebowski meme template. Because if I hear one more Bryce Harper rumor, I’m going to go mentally insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update from Pete Albietz, the @NJDevils VP of Hockey Communications and Hockey Ops: Sami Vatanen is taking a mainte… https://t.co/4HZBdoATot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennisChannel : great matches today but most fun watching killer ladies tearing cover - thnx!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonalds I may have just heard one of the dumbest things. You have 24 hour breakfast but not 24 hour prices appar… https://t.co/pWTzEb5a4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALWAYS good to see the guys in @threedaysgrace @JMoschitta @1059thex ... https://t.co/XxJdD6dHCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The was a full on Mardi Gras parade on the floor during halftime. Yes, it was glorious. Yes, I got beads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He didn't threaten him he made him aware of the skeletons he has that we know about n if already a liar n lies to h… https://t.co/CW3UG8XiDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[we don’t get our fix the shadows of reality consume us. Life’s hard, writing jokes is harder.   We lost another gre… https://t.co/3bkrFkuPXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who all do we have on the line?   Quite possibly the same as the list you can read on the screen...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesrucker247 Seems that way many times. The lack of consistency is frustrating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HectorEli_ @pavlog @RMXradio @joleberto @dnl Eh compa y el de Playa del Crimen? https://t.co/bIKnqTeWwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We broke the Top 40 🥳😭 . Huge #shoutout to everyone who’s been streaming / requesting “Beautiful Tragedy” on their… https://t.co/coChyC7MY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worked very hard for a very long time and built a couple VERY VALUABLE personal relationships along the way. All… https://t.co/N2B9jkeATT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should start a new channel that only post positive/good news only. New way to think and see the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VivaLights: El Padrino (@EricWynalda) has spoken: "We need more of you out there on March 9th. We get a lot of ene… https://t.co/hDq74UjBBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sloop2Jon @ColeKlafeta2 @RichCimini @aafexpress @TheAAF I know one thing I wouldn't have traded up to pick a Hacke… https://t.co/6IsfQVu1Ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNBORNness @JMaccabbee All should be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch A possibility MARRIED FIRST COUPLE  PRESIDENCY  AND FIRST LADY PRESIDENT HUSBAND VICE PRESIDENT AMERICA WOULD… https://t.co/gYi8b44VLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRAVExHERO Thank you so much! Found an LFG group tonight and we went ham! We lost 1 game all night! Went from very… https://t.co/GxgrFB8KxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__spoon_ Hahaha always have to plan ahead.  A little genetic preference never hurt anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks! To get started. I am offering a prize. If you and your friends are talented at design and engineering, you… https://t.co/sqEoXXB3Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selliottWLWT Imagine Lebrons championships if had a HOF coach or playmakers consistently throughout his career   Works both ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my friends &amp; loved ones ... Have a wonderful weekend! @Snoopy    #livelaughlove #shalom #wisdom https://t.co/axwKm9nNIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not written by tRump...please to many big words...spelled correctly and it all makes sense...but n… https://t.co/izzpGMQIYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver Delete this account. Such an American style of tabloid-level disrespect for Canadian decency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge series win for @OU_Baseball! #BoomerSooner #OKLAHOmaha https://t.co/bQRsrmtTyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Candy was a legend and Planes, Trains &amp; Automobiles is a comedy classic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RED ALERT! started cooking the egg without realizing there is no spatula https://t.co/aPfzz33Lh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Will_Bunch They seem to have some problems with Netanyahu and fraud, we should suspend the $38 billion we're sendi… https://t.co/zsMpq5Nqqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My, my, my...... when you learn that reparations is not about wealth redistribution but repairing what was broken.… https://t.co/JDyWbpvjsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley Hahahaha. Quite the comedian. You're about as good at telling jokes as you are being a politician.… https://t.co/MaP7yscqM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scythekain First of all they don’t lie about the Lord. Second we are saved and those of whom Jeremiah speaks were… https://t.co/U5HqoAOpTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good workout this morning. Think I have slight pull of my lower calf muscle. I’m good as long I keep moving. Tried… https://t.co/KAIzPB8KRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to watch @mtnbrookhoops play in yet another Alabama State finals today. Proud of my college roommate… https://t.co/JUQOwUc2Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@THEVinceRusso reference on @IMPACTWRESTLING tonight thanks to @TheRealDisco and it was hilarious!  #IMPACT… https://t.co/yDhDdzLqaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @IlhanMN @foxnation Because @IlhanMN  is not guilty of anything but speaking her truth. The truth is tR… https://t.co/ua1rQtwvIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since 2010 only 1 time in sec tournament  has tide hoops not had Kentucky eliminated them or had chance to eliminat… https://t.co/gjAapBkTKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much did each player get? Asking for a friend eating Top Ramen for dinner ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith is being sure of what you hope for and certain of what you can not see. Hebrews 11:1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@60Minutes If you think McCabe was fired for anything but reopening the Trump Russia investigation, I have a bridge to sell you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were able to cover six events tonight and what do I do when finally finishing work? watch more sports while 🥃 #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wings Valentine's Day Special https://t.co/sbdQ7J7rk8 via @aberdeensports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shuhbomb It gets better, when I went back to KH1 I had completely forgot about its flaws.  and if you hate the mec… https://t.co/wdmtN55IjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber $52 for a 4.6-mile, 18-minute ride? Price gouging. Horrendous. That is more than my airline ticket from Flori… https://t.co/SRZO1FYhUC]]></document></documents></author>