<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Need recommendations: great salon/spa Pittsburgh, PA metro area. Facial/skin important. Would like available massag… https://t.co/hAGtTPBZZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you live/work in East Austin come get a fantastic burger for lunch at Community First! Village. I eat them all t… https://t.co/bCRw29MeyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this Apache Gin thing isn’t a play to get publicity by pissing people off, and I hope I am not contributing… https://t.co/JA2Bdh2xCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOLO 🍕   #chicago #food #pizza #gay #gaysian #travel #usa #nerd @ Pequod's Pizza Chicago https://t.co/Lxcck1P3Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnie @abarrallen Fair to say, you’re a little less mainstream compared to the general audience... :) siding w/ Allison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix That’s not really fair, McDonald’s advertises on every single network regardless of their political slant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze The three branches of Government are the Executive, Judicial and the Investigative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/9y7L7Ut0W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won a small fellowship award for research in my grad program. Every bit helps to keep the ball rolling! Happy researching, y’all 🌲]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be seeing dudes looking like they moms dressed them up in AND 1 tracksuits like it’s 2006]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sommarsverige I think that is correct unless you purchase one of the "packages" like finals weekend or full tourna… https://t.co/D5brmEl7lB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UChicago Courage and Innovation: Celebrating Heart Transplantation at the University of Chicago #charity… https://t.co/W2GBhptRcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard to believe it was only a few days ago that I was eating these 5 desserts as part of a 7 course tasting me… https://t.co/cNDDJ4WytG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parece que no podré ver #CaptainMarvel esta semana☹️ https://t.co/i4qrM9obkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus called the Twelve to him, and sent them out in pairs. He gave them authority and power to deal with the evil opposition. Mark 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been drinking a lot less now I’ve dropped back down to 196. 182 here I come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is impressive on so many levels! Congratulations Coach Corbin!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won't miss his defense but he's all heart on the court. Good luck Enes!   #Knicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[ميخواست به يكي بگه بعدا نظرشو عوض ميكنم، گفت رگشو ميزنم (رايشو ميزنم😃). كُرد خارج نشين فارسي فورگت كرده و نزديك بود… https://t.co/7ylD4S54gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zsports1988 @AllbrightNFL So again, you're showing some fragility here and I dont think you know it. You may not b… https://t.co/jnqGcSaMO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cackless1 @TracySophiababy @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump If you want to hold those midterm results up against Oba… https://t.co/b53vzZqKtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #Apex on Olive Chapel Rd and Apex Barbecue Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Not a #constituent, but kudos on a principled stand for #article1 / #legislative #authority and powers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The men. The MEN of San Bernardino. Someone get me some Dependa for men cuz I am💦 https://t.co/jjWCjaDuXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USSunSolar @chefmsmith04 @CEOsunSolar @BrimstoneAshe How about kansas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Islanders/Hurricanes needs to happen just to see how @garik16 handles it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC After jumping ship even rats squeal when they hit the water. Make them think they are going to drown… https://t.co/4XzKbg6e3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibiOfficial Not gon’ lie, I read that as ‘someone’ and not ‘sesame’ at first glance. Thought Gibi might be contemplating the ‘Lecter diet’]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i just found out that all my professors have told my advisor really good things about me :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women can lift,  tuck  and botox every body part to make themselves younger. Hands are the only true indicator of a… https://t.co/Ytelx1KNTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sparkleloung Very Alarming: Boss of the Swamp says "Something ain't right" If you’re not concerned you should be.… https://t.co/0SQzKNz3rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea &amp; then he sits there and plays the victim cuz men are literal trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhenTheGoingGetsToughIAlways I tell work to fuck off and go straight to the bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[A must see.    For Her: A celebration of Canadian female sports heroes | CBC Sports https://t.co/VujyY0iGvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my friends first travel vlog #peru #vacation Impromptu Vacation | Peru Trip https://t.co/KyzeZ5iuq2 via @YouTube @MonSharie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Clinton Wrestling Club for winning the Grass Lake Wrestling Tournament 1st Place Team Trophy. 💪🏻… https://t.co/3xpU7dDwGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[All 12 Senate Democrats oppose Texas Secretary of State David Whitley. That's more than enough to block his nominat… https://t.co/UZx4UaXOFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejensie Jens it was such a treat to meet you. Definitely one of the super people of cycling and the world. Hope… https://t.co/jloIOapjur]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's sad, but I only recognize NFL players in public if they're wearing their uniform or and beating their wives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@30SecFight @michaelsienicki watch in the middle he starts talking to some dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[I purchased a coffee at Trump Tower and now I’m Ambassador to Liechtenstein.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought For The Day  See yourself the way God sees you — in Christ and blessed with every spiritual blessing in the… https://t.co/f6QyQ2uGdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomas13355651 @BrandToney @jmezajr44 @thebirdwrites It’s the Knicks, nothing they do will surprise me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh layer of snow bending branches. Beautiful. #snowdays https://t.co/nYYZz1Gc6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JagsChef At the time i wasnt. Mother banned it. But i did it at my friends house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio Cortez doesn’t know where philly is but she’ll grab one for lunch today. You’ve got to admit @AOC… https://t.co/xNJTRvcFiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know what’s not that hard? not being an ableist!! (And not being hateful towards people ✨)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The After the Gold Rush #5 cover will be posted on my Patreon latter today. Public reveal coming latter.  Art for t… https://t.co/JBYSAazjSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sketched up some hot new TWC vote incentives for the first time in ages.  Gonna post 'em up tomorrow, but if y… https://t.co/pwh9EGVtK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny everyone is rushing to defend LVP. I’m over here like shhhhhh let’s all watch the show and figure o… https://t.co/nK5T96QJVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@205jw Trying to find the excuse for this slam but this shit was illegal af but too damn funny! 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaezPrince_11 I’m with you!! Whichever one wins more going forward may crack top 5 all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinvallee J'écoute ça présentement, je sais pas, ça me hook pas... J'aime pas le son, trop rond, pas assez sale… https://t.co/Qtp7qFn2Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[📸📸📸    #peacoat #zara #sunglasses #nycphotographer #pose #fashion #malemodel #l4l #nyc @ New York, New York https://t.co/mYb4jbSqKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is good to read anywhere but particularly from here. https://t.co/4BvCvNaIbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamadZoror @chanelwestcoast Bruh @chanelwestcoast you really came for my brotha like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[#libertylive #worship #Godsplan @ https://t.co/fL4Hu7NDJi https://t.co/qgndQREvoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I am here to say I am afraid for my safety. Just because I am a man does NOT mean I am not allowed to be fearful]]></document><document><![CDATA[#custom #printed #transfers for my clients. #fashion #APPAREL #clothing #brand #shirts #STICKERS #Decals… https://t.co/ciAgeyakNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[They losing by 16 and on the verge of getting eliminated from the playoffs 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fister was great to watch all those years. Congrats on your retirement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7uanF No no, producción nacional neta. Chaborra como “Un cadaver en la nevera” o “La mano” ajakaahakaahakaahajajaajajajaajajajajajaas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final stage restart order: Blaney-Almirola-Stenhouse-Harvick-Suarez-Johnson-Logano-Bowyer-Elliott-Preece-Reddick-Ga… https://t.co/5JWmmgqgUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CtCathCorner @FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy It can.  One must use common sense to discern what is meant. When… https://t.co/XdzcGyIHrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gas-guzzling car rides expose AOC's hypocrisy amid Green New Deal pledge https://t.co/CUoWSRCLO8 via @nypmetro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAngryDemoCat @RepCummings @MichaelCohen212 Yes seriously you numbnutz.... You do realize the one in front of th… https://t.co/mlDwq71jeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I got contacted by @garyvee this morning. Apparently he's starting a massive Crytptocurrency program and investo… https://t.co/8nN9POAYxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing could be more true and urgent than this.  https://t.co/HDMqykbQA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mass_mistermv @toniroms @AmA2jena1 @sjerhera What a smoking hot beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreinpg @tarborott That's just vague and empty, I don't see how it's an argument for disregarding it anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone Ain’t it just like the night to play tricks when you’re trying to be so quiet, we’ll sit here stranded,… https://t.co/c8AXgcKASJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Saturday brain. Good to see you again. Thanks for helping me get a solid four and a half hours sleep. I’ll happily lie awake now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am BURSTING at the seams w excitement about my 1st opportunity to present out on the best coast!! Come check out… https://t.co/UVE2IyOkL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about playing charades is furiously waving your hands in a forward motion, nodding your head at a ma… https://t.co/gdAaWA79Md]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NianticHelp I was booted out of my account today and can’t get back in. Says user name or password are wrong. Your… https://t.co/nCpec7Os0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sees someone talk about sex on the TL 🤦🏽‍♂️😂 reasons why I don’t post none bout it. I’m not tryna have nobody lusti… https://t.co/4hXxAZMkoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woodpeckerz14 I’ve seen you be a vocal critic of Voter Fraud On this Website.  Thoughts On Harris/Dowless Situation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ralston’s rival won’t back down: ‘He’s not a victim at all’ #gapol  https://t.co/oqmeggitka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_1791 @FoxNews I guess he’s not very Hoppy with getting divorced and wants to inflict pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two rehearsals down, one more left this week. #UCBCO #UCBSO #orchestra #bassoon #teamtenorclef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrkellysays Hahaha glad to hear it has a name now, but I think I can do with out. Sure did the job for conditioning though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hungry_husky69 @DDJ384 @davisontigerfan @TeeHodges @steven_edbrooke @WFXGFOX54 The internet always wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Feb 25th 1pm on @YESNetwork - 1st Spring Training game of the season - vs. Toronto Blue Jays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BowinnMa The #BCBudget2019 is a wise move by @carolejames in the face a global slow down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Witten agrees to one-year, $5 million and 25 snaps a game https://t.co/HlKbXadO4b via @ProFootballTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meesismijnbroer Sure Sem! Thank *You* Buddy. But, I'm more of a Night Person.  However I don't drink Blood. Or bur… https://t.co/q3d5fhy5ET]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sending the next person who says "the snow is so pretty" my address and a shovel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boulder, CO Tonight for @LitLords at @foxtheatreco  LETS RAGE 🔥🏔✈️   Tickets: https://t.co/Jg4EvlHHHR https://t.co/Qqm13gMCav]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a game so far. Huge mistake from @gianluigibuffon. He has to pin that ball or atleast deflect it out of bounds… https://t.co/mbLvHkL0vZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caonews guess who showed up on my tv this morning? https://t.co/DFDEhnjShw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such terrific professionals in the @bwedgebrook office! Thank you @bairdwarner for bringing in @DrRebeccaHeiss and… https://t.co/H8huOIaQ8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[From paid interns, to providing staffers with livable wages, to involving her staff in decision making, Representat… https://t.co/FaFQk4a4aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin ti no me va bien, tampoco me va mal. Pase lo que pase no te voy a llamar]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is nuts. @MatthewLillard absolutely crushed Shaggy but he's not good enough to provide his voice? He's perfect… https://t.co/m7WbfzEPfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I luv u Jesse but ur wrong. If u only dab all the time then go back to smoking flower that shit gets u lit like… https://t.co/V43SnOoyog]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆 ALL AMERICAN 🏆 Lagi Tausaga ends the indoor season with a 5th place finish with a mark of 22.23m/72’11.25”! Very… https://t.co/nzTdn9zs8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump 😂😂😂😂😂.  America 2019 @JeffreyGuterman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasLamey1 @TheGloryFires Haven't tried it just yet. I don't often want coffee at night, but I do want the option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To2 w/ @DG_HappyFeet for @NJROD   We need 2 Saugs and a Main ICR   Dm either one of us   Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the car listening to 2000s Emo music while it rains with milk tea is such a mood rn]]></document></documents></author>