<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can Khashoggi's death be a turning point for Saudi Arabia?  https://t.co/U4B05yixsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to complain because I didn’t have enough pairs of jeans so I bought more but now all I wear is my 17 pairs of black leggings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianaConner20 @Morris_Chestnut @nbcenemywithin @J2thecarpenter @nbc Gracias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Nancy do the country the greatest thing of all and resign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Please help me promote Just want my boys to have the life they deserve after losing everything we had https://t.co/Smckb4xZNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GUHH_WEtv @LilTwist You act just like my uncle Bud rest his soul love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antiGOPaganda You can retweet that last thread of tweets to TR.. I'm thinking that was a pretty good explanation..… https://t.co/5aJtrnfd4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry Twitter, my 2 friends are busy.....I have no one to talk with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s ignore the ignorant comment to this GIF. However, lets make sure we boost @samsmith  to the fucking sky for h… https://t.co/roNzgJkpuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeatlyNoble @CFISDWells Working summer school and enjoining my best friend @GiniHowell’s pool!! https://t.co/497obvcjKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FARMINGTON #CRASH ROUTE 4 at Town Farm Road. @NBCConnecticut #NBCCT https://t.co/Gxo3vvc237]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night in the office. @ BOND New York Real Estate https://t.co/kFOdyB8y5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchwarzAndreas6 @DoingRight1 People like Katie Perry are sickening!! Live one way, tell us to live another! HYPOCRITES!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanelleCShane @ChuckWendig Super cool! I really enjoy your emails, can’t wait to hear the talk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emancipation reconstruction and betrayal https://t.co/cjD7ewZt9Y via @YouTube👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾🔥🔥🔥🔥🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rewire_News I wonder what they think is a good time frame. Considering the death penalty is pretty final and such.… https://t.co/Q12Sq9W7uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX @FOXTV I know who the bee is..the only black female singer who IS still alive and has won 10 Gramm… https://t.co/sZJzxIb7j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuctupMike I wish he was taking all of their funds to build the wall but $60 million ain’t chump change. At least… https://t.co/0GQpxbHTXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[История хип-хопа в офигенных миксах бруклинских диджеев, которе делают свои вечеринки в Ред Хуке. Откопала такое со… https://t.co/OT4NBEIWm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A customer today told me that I look familiar and then he was like “Oh I always see you at Walrus with your little… https://t.co/U15PNOkN1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPAIN on @TheEllenShow talkin bout winning the #maskedsingerfox makes my ❤ SO HAPPY! 😍 #HeIsAmazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHLRangers Gavin is so lucky to have such a great group of boys, both on and off the ice, to cheer for every week!! Thanks @OHLRangers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Labs in class today! AFM built the Unit Circle and ECM learned about using proportions to model tagging wildlife po… https://t.co/ilvu4CrRBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need to be investigated completely financial and criminally!!! It's not their money to spent it's the tax paye… https://t.co/we7YzdQhHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodyWyatt2 @mrcrockpot @Bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBINSIDER_ I disagree with you he has been right about Harper all… https://t.co/tLUxmZJ1Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Uh huh.  If it weren't for Harry Reid (and other brave souls that do the right thing) we wouldn't… https://t.co/a5RoCPC6qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafalitosarmi Ese clasismo de mierda y descriminatorio que en nuestro pais aun permanece.para mi todas las persona… https://t.co/C8ZXaSSxMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Pet Day to this goofy  girl of ours! 💕 I wish I could be home to give you all the snuggles! We love… https://t.co/4tBoYNEhIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sooo blessed, yet so stressed right now... when do things get better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be getting more cloud than the Kardashian’s cheating scandals...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I’m officially freaked out.  Wood ☑️ Groceries ☑️ Candles ◻️ Beer ◻️  I have work to do. #WNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royce_3331 @JesusBengoechea Pues ya sabéis. En Madrid estaré del 4 al 8 de julio y luego nos vamos a Marbella. Invitados estáis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to get debilitating migraines once/twice every week, they were so bad all I could do was sleep, praying that… https://t.co/WTfdTdz5ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to explain myself to people more than once, if you don’t get it the first time I don’t know what to tell you 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[(\__/)     ⠀  (•ㅅ•)    my boyfriend helping 　＿ノ ヽ ノ＼  __  me with any form   /　`/ ⌒Ｙ⌒ Ｙ　ヽof technology  ( 　(三ヽ人　 /… https://t.co/Zq2O88hqyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talkers rarely do anything. Not sure what they are talking about. What life experiences they are drawing from?  Doe… https://t.co/XNm4CffCKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me find out whose doing bs on my parents and i’ll KILL A BITCH idgaf, i’ll do ANYTHING for my family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have the audacity to talk about someone else leading through lies and deception. 😂🤣😂🤣 You? 😂🤣😂🤣 https://t.co/8n1uv6WPRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventurous hike with my favorite guy today to the top of South Franklin Mountain. I surely wasn't prepared to scra… https://t.co/VxhuLWyKVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[he asked me.. “do you see us still talking by the summer.. cus bitches tend to switch up” that nigga gives me no re… https://t.co/NAKDUEAFLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyaRognstad @wookkay47 Not to sure, i was assuming that she blocked you from the tweets. Just seems attacking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants.” - Karl Lagerfeld 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[just want all my friends and everyone I know or knew to be happy... really]]></document><document><![CDATA[am not exactly the easiest to warm up to person I don’t mince words or do the obligatory nice things yeah that’s me… https://t.co/5T1QM9jp1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganstormborn @tinman41963 @peterbakernyt @GOP I agree w/you but YOU MUST NOT give up !!!  Plant yourself among… https://t.co/veOMbDPVTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeralOtter @sistoney67 Angel behind Lukaku and Alexis playing the Mata role also a possibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha,beat beat beat,beat brat,beat that mfffff😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣🍆🍆🍆🍆 @ Bethlehem, Pennsylvania https://t.co/0K57KMmEvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Jason Momoa didn't make the top of the list? Something is very wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@archam2nina @VSullivan4NH @GovChrisSununu @cut_50 @VanJones68 @IntownManch @MayorJoyceCraig @ritchiefarrell1… https://t.co/nybDdy2eCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annamholmes Thanks sis❤️ I’ll be okay, I’m just a little sad boy for a minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahmony Freemont is amazing! I loved Old Vegas! I'm so happy you enjoyed it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't like valentines day, but if someone wants to give me something give me chocolate cake with extra chocolate 🤗🤤🤤🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom life... when you get to climb to the top of the jungle gym to catch your kids😜 • • Spent the afternoon with my… https://t.co/iS312lSJYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot about daylight savings going on tomorrow and I have an appointment at 8:20 AM so if I die just know I died… https://t.co/M1qljnsf3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the only person in Charlotte who's not invested in #UNCvsDuke #dukevsunc]]></document><document><![CDATA[reminds me of past times I’ve dealt w the law. in my past I have been wrongly accused. Cause I’ve always been the… https://t.co/Tmm8xeFXIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Zion will be OK. I don’t like to see any young guy get hurt. #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So forever 21 has stepped up with all there clothes, shoes, and accessories. I’m absolutely happy with that!😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decidimos ser honestas con la realidad del futbol en nuestro país. Con una serie de videos queremos crear conocimie… https://t.co/gHOdkyNQh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Single this Vday? Get yourself something nice. Love yourself the way you deserve. Be your own Valentine. 💋… https://t.co/FQDLXFkE0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Kick The Dust Up by @LukeBryanOnline on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/7AJd0FGt84 https://t.co/2lNCWlNVuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m starting to hallucinate from lack of sleep. (and i mean not sleeping at all anymore) y’all know how many ppl i’… https://t.co/g07JU3frTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MICHAELaCACCAMO @TCDSB @DanteAcademy @TCDSBdirector @mariarizzo @dktcdsb @DanteCouncil @susannaranalli… https://t.co/QXO59o9Sii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @ambinc1 @AOC AOC u are just as lost as the rest of.the democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdriFloZu @CHAYANNEMUSIC Gracias x compartir #DesdeElAlmaTour #2aParte #EnergiaDeLaBuena]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 more days until GRR!  My son has 6 miles and a bridge today.  #GRRtraining]]></document><document><![CDATA[ファクトリーツアーのため、ノースカルロイナ州シャーロックに来ています！   本日早朝より、創業110周年のとあるドラム工場に行きます。  写真撮影OKなところは後ほど報告しますね！ #Ludwig https://t.co/FFLReU19E8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My small victory today was folding the clothes we washed and dried over a week ago and had just left in the laundry basket lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff @PascoSheriff  thank you 🙏 I fine sir I appreciate y’all trying to get me to meet you for lunch pleas… https://t.co/CkIaaPwCeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rap30 Can’t say that I blame her! trump would have found a reason to fire her so she’s leaving before he axes her!! Way to go!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay guys the giveaway is closed! I will be picking a winner later today after work 😊 Thank you so so much for entering!]]></document><document><![CDATA[O God, who teach us that you abide in hearts that are just and true, grant that we may be so fashioned by your grac… https://t.co/O2WgG9FgPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay Facebook, let’s go thru the list. How about tackling any pages denouncing climate change next?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and welcome to a new week (: #INWX #4yourmorning @cbs4indy #indy https://t.co/OYk5sWwjAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just training the little brother at work #SiblingsWorkingTogether https://t.co/xyhMRIPECJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lake Norman of Catawba, North Carolina https://t.co/OeNZjORJne]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I nanny, I listen to ‘baby shark’ and ‘shake it off’ on replay. Then, when I come to my other job, Shania Twai… https://t.co/28NAMCy94W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This post office shit is deadass annoying af, next time I buy someone a gift out of state they’ll get it when I see them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes she does and @DorothyERoberts holds an endowed professorship in her name @PennLaw Cc: @PennBLSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the things I read recently was about how MLB front offices were now being run by Ivy League types. These are… https://t.co/JE2CSo7aca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBlkshrt Heartbreaking, isn’t it⁉️ I’m sure if he was in Belize he’d be perfectly fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You look like a watermelon,,,but like in a cutesy way.” -Madison  @mad_hayes17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone for all your comments.. This concludes My Affirmation of Love .. This one has 2017  our wedding… https://t.co/8Arj97CJ5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caryl_shaw One idea: Someone I know who doesn't drink always orders pineapple juice when in a drink situation, so… https://t.co/iiC3TojYa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalCerealDay #Lance #PulpFiction #EricStoltz https://t.co/nC1C6NHGYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PersonaDetritus Think how the media would take off with this if it was done at a Mosque]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottliebJessica @GretaSchetnan @smitchell3 @TheNeedyReader @JennatMackin @jenplucker @ethanmackinedu @klangender… https://t.co/2Cr3cNURSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful Mass today to celebrate #ashWednesday on the first day of lent! #ocsbLent]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Repetition does not transform a lie into a truth.”- - - Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Lincoln made a deal with this Bank do you know the name and who owns it? What was the deal he made to get… https://t.co/oITQmzCaWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTenNetwork @B1GMBBall @BoilerBall @MSU_Basketball @JordanBo_3 @IowaHoops @BrunoFernandoMV @TerrapinHoops “A”!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les vamos presentando parte del elenco de #LA VERDADERA HISTORIA DE PEDRO NAVAJA”. Se acerca el estreno y estamos f… https://t.co/IARun4hw8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow imagine me 13 and tweeting😳 #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/rLJ4yJbNJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to be sharing knowledge and skills, empowering people in making a difference. Coupon code “HONEY” for… https://t.co/0WldnEBBRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanawithbanana @therealroseanne @AnnCoulter Roseanne's doing really well, isn't she?  /s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth. Happy International Women’s Day! 👩🏻👩🏾👩🏼👩🏿👩👩🏽 @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/tHnUaVTD1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan bought me a star for Valentines Day and named it after me 😭🥰💫 https://t.co/WHZAvmsyA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marketmodel hi mike , morning ..nice work , thank you .wanted to ask are you bullish on this name? can it go highe… https://t.co/DIvuvs8TJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkStateAG @Prometheus_2020 I don't forget. Too many kids are dying.  Too many high powered assault weapons on… https://t.co/4640rlP9cW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets...  [Ohhh @netflix just dropped 10 episodes of a new series!]   #AcademicValentine]]></document></documents></author>