<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/QUuwOx4Tpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taught a guy on Oteam how to spell “necessary” on Friday and he was so shocked he deadass didn’t speak for like a whole three minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me today at 5:30 on 95.9fm for BTS 🎙! Today’s Show 👇 @UA_JoeDunn calls in from Buffalo to preview Zips/Bulls t… https://t.co/UklprqDKW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Moms win at this year’s #Oscars. We’ll say who thanked their moms in their speeches tonight at 11” https://t.co/27BcBSXP9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briebelIas But to Vince it is and that's what made people question. We are glad Joe is in remission and getting be… https://t.co/9JRlMaUTec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NelsonJustinC @leach721 @funder Nope......she got her kidneys bumped by a baby elephant and modeled her safari outfit!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grant_morse7 @culpie02 @RealMNchiefsfan Transvestites or transvestite. Life or death shit I don't know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLozanoA @Reforma Al Sr. Luis Romero hay quienes entienden de política a su favor y no es casualidad que algunos t… https://t.co/KRuwbYF0yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @AE911Truth @9_11_IsAnInside @FBI @OhioBot5000 U think maybe he stopped using the term when he took offic… https://t.co/00cNSwcaLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[El desear algo, es llevar tus propios pensamientos a la lejanía del universo, el hacer que se realicen es cuestión… https://t.co/z7wXTLZlLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend, it sounds like you have your campaign points to make a run at the White House! I especially agree with n… https://t.co/3FjvQnCkpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys, I miraculously almost finished my math 51 pset in 2 hrs and now that I have one problem left, I've gone t… https://t.co/ee9q0WUIWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatPoliceAssoc good morning guys I have a birthday today can I get a special birthday tweet and are you proud I'm… https://t.co/8ogNkfxFDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prbentz Oxford Comma 4 Lyfe. Grammar should provide clarity. "My favorite bands are Emerson, Lake and Palmer, Cros… https://t.co/7kWLEoCFAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone explain to me why its snowed in Hawaii and now its snowing in LA...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is beating Kamala Harris 2-1 among black Democratic primary voters, new poll finds  https://t.co/jF2vOW22YM by @ryangrim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not exactly. Many in that 50% support a lot of what POTUS does policy wise, but uncomfortably recognize that he oft… https://t.co/O6iKnKJZlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gennygoat @driplines @EdKrassen @lisgalla @3anball @amychua So then your tribe is the racist, xenophobic one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Oscar for Best Actor for the movie Bigots, Liars, &amp; Haters - @JussieSmollett #hoax #JussieSmollet #FakeNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always find time to romp on the beach... #beach  #dogsofinstagram  #dogs  #dogbeach  #sand @ Ocean City, New Jersey https://t.co/xV4dLppenu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nihilistspicer @MattBruenig (I have lost track of who we are making fun of)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outrockoakley hhh now for my parents...later. i’m still riding my wave of nervousness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KonnerBeste Shoot me an email if you don’t mind. Wife and I heading out of town for a few days. D.Saur@chatham.edu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t agree more! Genius!  And they want to run creepy Joe Biden against him! 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @mykayla_myerss hope it’s a good! https://t.co/BDStR0qtUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine. College visits begin for these too - my third round! #denveruniversity #coloradocollege #cuboulder… https://t.co/bnESEs3InK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamAndCompany @CamEdwards Correct.  And homicidal criminals don't abide by the prohibition on murder, but I'm not… https://t.co/Dr2aZHJ6V2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynamicWebPaige @TensorFlow "Baby... baby...? Vas is dist 'baby'?" --The Producers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauraolson @ScottPaterno First decent thing I ever seen Senator Casey do and I finally appauld him for being a caring human being again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom Trump called the NAZIS AND KKK OF CHARLOTTESVILLE "good people". I grew up in the Bible Belt and had a… https://t.co/uL65yJDQTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of curiosity I looked up all the college baseball scores from last night to see if anyone scored more than the… https://t.co/QxcPeOPtDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are we going to pay for late, delayed, broken, smelly ass, disgusting, slow, trains?]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: USF Dons baseball sweeps doubleheader, have won four straight - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/cTqtLVGBUy @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like AOC but I think she should stop airing her personal grievances against the GOP. It comes across as self invo… https://t.co/QTrj7zKN5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @thesheepoleon Likely because the song is unlicenced, but feel free to have your @BreitbartNews  homm… https://t.co/W3bmTOLMtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham doesn't appear to know the geographical location of the state of Kentucky, anything about said state… https://t.co/yIHWJrGjn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camaraceleste Te banco a muerte pero aca el rugby no existe!! La gente no tiene idea donde se practica, hay un muy… https://t.co/VKCqMoRmLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about all the trips I’ve made down here to serve the migrants. sure, i go a lot. But the members of this c… https://t.co/EYtJNqb0Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photos from Mardi Gras Fresno at Tower District. https://t.co/kO0P5DafpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe noodle world is playing champagne supernova by oasis im actually laughing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped off at the @crpubliclibrary for a couple more books and cd. Always surprised by how much cool stuff the lib… https://t.co/y3JoSZqXlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started off the afternoon watching 25th-ranked Washington hold off Stanford, 62-61! It was a tight game throughout,… https://t.co/VqCKbSFJOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive Since when is it okay in America to open up an investigation without a crime. So, if I'm a congressperson… https://t.co/z2fddN8u2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tippi Tuesday! #SchnauzerYorkie  #tuesdayselfie  . . . . #Tippi #tuesdayvibes #animalsco #dog #puppy… https://t.co/6CssNXNu41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swole____patrol Jesus, you are doing pretty well beforehand. I wouldn't complain, but happy hunting for your goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[02.27.19 leaked audio from Instagram https://t.co/0LGQqcVneH via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprised no Jerome fans made this same argument when they beat University School yesterday🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[JESUS IS COMING LIKE A THIEF IN THE NIGHT !!!  WATCH THIS VIDEO QUICKLY!!!  https://t.co/aai7MNqy1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was going to go with a political triple feature and watch "The Contender", but couldn't find my copy. Therefore, le… https://t.co/ya751d3yb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magic8vol @WilliamsonNFL @WesleyUhler I take Murphy even if the WRs are there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl Was he looking at Donny’s “junk drawer” there? I swear he tried to catch a peek at the “mushroom h… https://t.co/GF8DmqHY5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to realize me and Thena are literally the exact same person it’s scary 😂🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sixers coach Brett Brown said Joel Embiid’s status for Friday’s game vs. #HoustonRockets has yet to be determined.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @Michael2014abc They may as well have just said, "We oppose all hatred except toward Trump supporters."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davejosephla Did you see all the hair on the flooor??.....  .....I’m SHEDding. 🤭#dadjoke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pe_rackcity @KingJames Kuz is the REAL future of the Lakers tho. They better not trade him. They need to give him… https://t.co/ATfTPkSe9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKC metro: Wind Chill Advisory in effect from 8 PM CT tonight to 9 AM CT Monday. Wind chills as low as 5 below zero is possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SANDERS LEFT OVER MONEY WHY AT 77 HE`S BLOCKING OTHERS YOUNG PEOPLE=WORKING FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP LIKE BEFORE\THINK DEMS\\]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Trump thinks if he just put his foot in the crack of the door. He has a chance to become our first POT… https://t.co/iDWnuKSij7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoldenmuzzy That type of pace he will have 4 goals next season.  Still more goals than Val Nichushkin this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of warmth on a cold day.  #SnowKitty #daddysbabykitty #hashtag #dvda #what #doesanyoneactuallylookatthetags @… https://t.co/szBExN1f6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KINGxDABURA hey bro Guitar beats on deck for the low 🎸💯🎸💯peep credits in my bio! https://t.co/AdkT9y357Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well folks, it was a good run. I'm out of the bracket but not before @ne0liberal sent ~500 new followers my way. Th… https://t.co/9fKkmAzVM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I broke my no drinking rule for my birthday but I’m having a great time with people I love so I ain’t even mad.  Th… https://t.co/PMk0zXB0qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BkmRlm9294 @Mimirocah1 Wes nut the roadmap aka bill of particulars will stay secret until we are all. Dead. Jill W… https://t.co/RSjcExT06W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HWellsRD @tinaalva @alroker To call it impractical is a weak argument. If people can do it, they can do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my dad if I could use his i8 an he straight up said hell no 👎... I good no would have been good but okay haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice little Monday night tilt in the desert - Osaka / Collins @ Indian Wells Tennis Garden https://t.co/MRnaqEBbxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samperfectbody @EEdenxxx The portions are huge!!! Go hungry or don’t go at all!! Lol 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maureenjohnson My mom always used to want a refund after flying into OHare because she walked halfway home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFrankosky @AverageAtBest1 Not kidding, I was wearing my blue and orange Average At Best t-shirt yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moiraverse Hard to go wrong by approaching literally any situation with 1) humility, 2) a willingness to roll with… https://t.co/Q7k05tMyB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me volví adicto a la alberca de hidromasaje 😥 ya quiero que sea lunes 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Backstorymom1 WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother interviewed by Di… https://t.co/LdFARuhB95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like everything is getting pushed back a day.  According to @DaytonLeader, the SCC-SV will be slated for 8:3… https://t.co/PAm50P5iAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Friedson — I live and own a small business in your district. Construction workers for the new @Marriott hea… https://t.co/6RJd90IyhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing " You've Got A Friend " by James Taylor @ Hampton, Georgia https://t.co/DNzNXz1wDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erininknox @Vol_Hoops Haha not toooo long. A couple hours. But impactful journalism takes time, Erin 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @KingJames and his @Lakers lost to the @Suns on Saturday...NO WAY HIS TIME IN #LosAngeles GETS BETTER!!...."Who… https://t.co/ORkgCRWnE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollinSherwin @Jeff_Sharon @Spokes_Murphy BTW I am asking from League standpoint. I think for WHoops to get any cr… https://t.co/kSOpN1w9nX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I have to get so angry at work before something was finally done! It shouldn’t have dragged in for so long.… https://t.co/5wsnxEiDQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MidnightRollCall Who's up with us!?!?! @ THE HALL OF JUSTICE https://t.co/Qdly2ZxIHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinks I called CPS on her. FUCK CPS BTW. Never would I do that, but believe what she wants, I guess. It breaks me,… https://t.co/DetuxBtIfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkavoussi I suspect there's an alternate set of social institutions where that is no longer true. I suspect that p… https://t.co/7KBtSrAtpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not gonna root for Erwin Santana because he's on the #WhiteSox.  I'm gonna root for him because he's my own age… https://t.co/KvjVx5Vv8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my new favorite bars in Charleston. This place is just beautiful. @ Camellias at Hotel Bennett https://t.co/6DeOMz9NkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK the LORD I have tomorrow off I don’t remember the last time I felt this shatty]]></document><document><![CDATA[You'd be lucky to see the field, My Dad in regards to my interest in High School 🏈. I'm going to prove you wrong,… https://t.co/oFvdJ8vbWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If “righteousness and justice are the foundation of his throne” (Psalm 97:2), matters of righteousness and justice… https://t.co/N7wpIrP6NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiBelleFi Our server was great. She kept our glasses full, but offered to bring an additional boba if we wanted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every man’s “man smell” is NOT the business.  Some of y’all dicks, balls and bootyholes smell the same. https://t.co/amFsYvsjr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only he could do it is right! Worse president in history, ROTFLMAO!  https://t.co/jExH0P0vMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to walk from your hand in total devotion  Quiero caminar de tu mano en total devoción   Hand that blesses an… https://t.co/Uyi8MMEKoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dobermanmamma @ZanderKelly30 @DailyCaller @realDonaldTrump The only legitimate reason to break up these companies… https://t.co/gmmrOAP4tY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Sure he is - he’s the FACE of the new Marxist socialist Democratic Party and big believer in the way… https://t.co/fP7F0ETCAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re sick sick when you don’t care how you look or how you smell. #bronchitis https://t.co/2bb4AZIgvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not kofi Kingston , but still a good choice for the triple threat #WWEFASTLANE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know what ad serving algorithm just decided to feed me a 30 second ad in Spanish but boy did some company just waste some money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Uhh Don....oh Don? Earth to The Donny!! Get some NARCAN quick,,,you’re about to OD. WAIT,… https://t.co/IGAQg4ObbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prettttttty sure this is an ends-justify-the-means scenario, but keep striving for the moral victory.]]></document></documents></author>