<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Seeing this as I left work today made me smile.  If you look closely, you can spot where someone made two hearts in… https://t.co/TmzzHIf5Y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere @ATT @verizon @TMobile When your family is happy with tmobile but they decided to bribe the corrupt pre… https://t.co/3i9GNQCEXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none.”    @DawnCrittenden1 loves applying lashes! I enjoy accepting new referra… https://t.co/ix3rklsPyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @therealmikedean on Instagram: “#sleepdeprived @madonna we must finish this album! Let’s go!”… https://t.co/H4FJn0Eo2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevAdamHamilton I am looking forward to watching my friend @RevMSlaughter online today... just as soon as I return… https://t.co/sXkPCWq1lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good game UP! Still love you La Salle! We’ll bounce back for sure 💚💪🏻 #notosweep #notomalas #notoseason76repeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate change is happening as a natural progression of the earths cycles I.e. the ice age. It’s all coming around… https://t.co/t2sn5RFBhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @SIPwinebar @GrnLakeGirl @jflorez @magee333 @Fit_life360 @_drazzari @boozychef @sl2016_sl… https://t.co/nwgTRXOWQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi if I could get all positive vibes, thoughts, prayers and nothing but good things my way right now it would be gr… https://t.co/IG3YiRAUeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered great food at Five Guys Dedham Mall! Time to go right up and #SkipTheLine! https://t.co/wqMXb7J31S #]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance So Trump screws contractors over by having a shutdown and then refuses to pay them because he caus… https://t.co/smBy7h4aW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knox has been talking for 2 days about his Star Wars Valentine’s Day gift from jennifer.gore. Thankful for a super… https://t.co/hjLCjJgq9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙 @kim_erim #himalayancat #himalayancatsofinstagram #ragdollcat #ragdollcatsofinstagram #persiancats… https://t.co/nXbrYrNHSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We must move from trying to control the uncontrollable cycles of@pleasure and pain, and instead learn how to conne… https://t.co/wYl3DrynJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Lord Halifax” reference by @Nigel_Farage Here is the CliffsNotes version for GenZ’s: ‘Foreign Secretary between 19… https://t.co/mXDVgpH4uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llega el punto en el que ésto ya es un puto chiste.  Ni pa que llorar, así de sencillo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can’t sleep at night, when I’m laying I be having a whole bunch of stuff going through my head 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS  I wish you all the best for the new two years.  I hope I haven't had a nervous breakdown b… https://t.co/TMXvKvB0zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ttttttyler My boy if you don’t listen to the whole album right now i will fly to seattle and sing it for you personally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Go LOC Magicians 🎩 #lemoyne_rys19 #lemoyne_rys19 #lemoyne_rys19 #lemoyne_rys19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being told that I’m basically lying about my pain because the MRI said I’m fine. Like sure I’m totally lying that my shoulder hurts 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsGobbyShite agreed. but there’s such a thing as being tactful. this is not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚫 You won’t know if people can’t tell you.  Please sign this petition to allow people to share their stories freely… https://t.co/GOzQuwF8T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road to the 300lb club! Also, excuse my ugly facial expression lol Swipe to see my failed attempt at 275 😅🙃#265… https://t.co/h4Da10flWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes a difficult thing to remember in the middle of it,  but it usually works MUCH better...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald tRump took a dump The resulting lump Was actually a chump named mike pence  #HowVPsaremade]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GenesisOpen (a PGA golf tournament) has made me rethink golf. It’s more exciting than I thought. The player demogr… https://t.co/CMv5tm2hDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been on 10 all day since we got back home and it honestly slipped my mind to post about the release party for… https://t.co/u37GAf13qM]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know you’re a dog mom when you find random treats in all of your coat pockets 😆🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I can fast. You know, my fasting is different from yours. Mine is NO food whatsoever. I'm gonna pray a lot f… https://t.co/EOgSOgiEOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodakotb @klgandhoda @JennaBushHager @KathieLGifford Love Jenna! Great move NBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @ladydwinter Yea she’s a politician first she took the UN job to pad her resume.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only listened to Jonas Brothers all day... I think I have a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada vez que un hombre me habla solo quiero agarrarle la cara y decirle te odioooooOooooOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your 15yo is listening to The Blood by The Cure during his shower and you realize all your fears about parenth… https://t.co/qOHWaCrUn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are the 13 Republicans who voted against the emergency border protection? I am surprised that Obama, both Clint… https://t.co/SrODgoHzDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch: Elton John and Taron Egerton sing ‘Tiny Dancer’ at Oscars party in @GayWeHo’s Park https://t.co/9UhoC0E79o https://t.co/nkFfd5nZ4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPSHelp Yes. Can you please start asking your carriers to place parcels in protective bags when leaving them outs… https://t.co/bFSYTbuukp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A major #CastCompliment to Sidney last Thursday at the Epcot Photo Pass Service. She helped me select photos to sur… https://t.co/XGP34ufI65]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @LivingArtsCtr to see @TaranaBurke and @MaryamMonsef for #InternationalWomansDay. Really excited to hear from tw… https://t.co/CXiGtGw9Mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool 👍😎 VIDÉO: Flashmob, «coup de cœur» à l'aéroport Montréal-Trudeau https://t.co/aEMh0IAnbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dezi doing what Dezi does best 🤩 #OTTB #baysfordays #eventerinthemaking #gridworkfridays @ Shaddock's Paddocks https://t.co/D8zBRfGpt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The music in the hub is so loud, I can hear from north toll and it was super quiet then I heard the goo goo dolls start screaming Iris 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Girl Scout cookie lovers!!!  You have a short time to stock up on your favorites this year!  Head over to… https://t.co/gev7U4CMKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel She's a Trump Ho.  Took a bribe  from him regarding Trump U.  She should be out of office. But it'… https://t.co/cI1KIdfaI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21__dreamz @MaurBink @_Lenroc22 @BriTheYouTuber @Badgalkita @_slimsheadyyy @Dri But I do think this is a double st… https://t.co/PGEUy8w5ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could not think of a better invitee then the DoS.  Looking forward to seeing this articulate women express her view… https://t.co/N1UOAackME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When are you going to speak out against THIS. You created This with hatred and division towards De… https://t.co/UASdgB1WwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the best Sonic date I’ve ever had !!! I miss you &amp;&amp; I’ll come see you soon!!! 😘😘 @DimitriCrossin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Druga Vienna Pale w/ Citra by 2nd Bridge Brewing Co. @ 2nd Bridge Brewing — https://t.co/uBrpeFp4pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only @MichelleObama was coming to the Herbie @HancockInst jazz event at my sons’ school on Mon. My oldest does a… https://t.co/nEindn4007]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born This Way!  Colored with matrix Bonded with brazilianbondbuilder  Design @sharkfinshears  Hot tools @bioionicla… https://t.co/Iq2Jhe9Rnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump And Republicans Caught With Sex Spa Owner #Topbuzz https://t.co/ztx4KOgHDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[And when I get back to Cali I might be getting put on main for Wilhelmina 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Seriously do you think China will listen to you criminal corrupt clown? https://t.co/AJCVLL87BO]]></document><document><![CDATA[people always ask me “how do you do it?” I respond with the answer they want to hear]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m putting together a presentation on mindfulness but I keep getting distracted. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably one of the coolest things ever happening on NBC Rn. @esportsarena is live! If you’re not watching, you’re… https://t.co/FqT3BM5wUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very fine!  Definitely stout.  Definitely chocolate.  Definitely enjoyable!   Not a milk shake, but close! - Drinki… https://t.co/pB597dga8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear this kid cracks me up every day. 🥰 46/365. . #gabemitchell #chillinlikeavillain #vignette #myheart… https://t.co/WeMvX5sjB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[the last thing i remember ricky saying before i fell asleep last night is “come on i want to look at dirty memes!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed up on the "The Greatest Showman Try-outs!" page for Mom (Charity Barnum) https://t.co/3pWX3TrUIU  via @signupgenius]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this on SUCH a personal level LMAO. Screw that piece of shit frat guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to me: seeing Isn't It Romantic by myself.   Living life to its fullest over here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jersey_Craig @SpicyDemocrat And my right to not be proselytized by evangelicals that cheat, lie and steal.… https://t.co/x3JINjztA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget the time I was in English class and the kid across from me DM’d me on Instagram asking to hook up… https://t.co/LcLav7yJGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop giving your love away to people who don’t understand or deserve it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMarjorie8 @MKGenest I get made fun of because of my grammar. No, I’m not educated. But I get my point across. Do… https://t.co/2j1tBJIVgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal 😂😂😂DUDE,  this guy is truly not a POTUS supporter. And VERY CLEARLY an immigrant.   But nice try 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂… https://t.co/PmxFBCN07F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg You are trending  #BoysInTheBand #OnRepeat #Legends  Best video ever!! Still waiting on that boy ba… https://t.co/bFmx28fmvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all Democrats Republicans there will a day comes that the national anthem will be music to your ears and we will… https://t.co/pYR2d3gQfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WEARtheBEAR #GrizzGangVsEverybody #GrizzGangVsNKU https://t.co/hC7MCJjYUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wavhiya @TorstenVeblen @TwitterMoments Have you ever heard of wear and tear? What about the airline itself or coun… https://t.co/S1o06WjpFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive seen alot of disturbing stuff in democracy headlines and no I don't follow them either I follow good solid facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BBBSHPEC 'Blast from the Past' #TriviaNight @quintewest🎶🎉  Thanks for the invite to host + donate a #crochet scar… https://t.co/F8GwIWjAAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟❤ @GalGadot #WonderWomanWednesday Appreciation ❤🌟 https://t.co/pLlDjIkA8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dellojello @cj_isnotokay @Katrdlee I think you have to take in context the time period we are living in. Our paren… https://t.co/9c32q6lxIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @RepAdamSchiff @SenFeinstein @AOC @dbongino @seanhannity… https://t.co/bVMCO2gsja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenWolfe Exactly!  I couldn't put it into words quite as effective as yours, but that is my feeling, too.  Coult… https://t.co/FNqNR89gnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEMS RESOLVE TO WISH ILLEGALS COULD VOTE SO THAT DEMS COULD RETAIN OFFICE: The 228-197 #vote came as part of a broa… https://t.co/wXZPiypNmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[El segundo discurso estuvo a cargo del secretario general de la Organización de los Estados Americanos, señor Luis… https://t.co/EiYyLODLaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiddlesPage I hope everybody has a great singles awareness day this February 14th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cowardly or compromised GOP is stuck to Trump because the base of their electorate is now a Trump cult. Trump i… https://t.co/qqpvIHqJZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sasha_saffron @DrDenaGrayson @realDonaldTrump Q sent me! 🙏🏻❤️🇺🇸🌎 https://t.co/SCR1WHkX0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS if you had $1 million to spend at any store, what store would you choose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I can’t wait for the ex’s car to be taken away 🙄 starting a bunch of drama since he can’t afford shit...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genemarks Interesting ...as I just finished reviewing our education savings for our 3 daughters. I was astonished… https://t.co/IJcQ4RwfLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massive amounts of birth control pills? Mothers are overdosing their daughters? Trump makes this stuff up. What a l… https://t.co/J8XBYXrw3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly can’t wait for the day when an exam no longer determines my emotions and life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Handmaids Ale by @alsofhampden @ Marilyn’s On Main — https://t.co/rQCpygRZnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geekoncaffeine @astudyinsnoggy It was good! Totally darker than I thought it’d be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerickWins Lmaoooooo it’s been a year of this now. Might as well celebrate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning @NaplesBotanical #garden #flowers #butterflies #vacation #winter #sun #fun #family https://t.co/DJr3OquFW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days y’all are going to see me on tv with the @WNBA or @NBA doing what I do now...pushing buttons, get… https://t.co/NjLWieDE4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't think id have the emotional capacity for love after Andrew but boy am I glad I was wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyWrites Such a good deal! $17.99. But you have to hunt for some alive ones. The pots are super nice too. https://t.co/HPhWPLiGv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Princvesss I agree. Sometimes you just wanna have sex with that person but not date them. Overtime feelings could… https://t.co/KeCiAQH3mD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyaaaaa babies 🥰 #TampaOutcall available 24/7🌇🌃 #TampaIncall only at certain times🤷🏻‍♀️ I travel all over Florida🤗… https://t.co/NZ6tSYuXfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @KPMG_US for hosting such a great discussion at #RSAC tonight. A good reminder to listen to our guts and… https://t.co/affOfJzcIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The abuse that individuals, who grew up in Hollywood, received, would make anyone turn to mental isolation. I don’t… https://t.co/SkWzKtSIBG]]></document></documents></author>