<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I.....in all seriousness.....wud like your weed mans number😂😂😂please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now they though it would be fun to try and play the par 5 16th from my tee. Neither could even hit it far enoug… https://t.co/HLSaCBOxY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitjobnews Stater Bros brand 6=whatever has worked the best the past couple years. And it's not too expensive..😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rileylroberts @verified When you purchased my last 2 statues of Rollon, I checked! You’re you, not him. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Us1 aka Federal Highway in Fort Lauderdale, FL https://t.co/vEmeQlY8Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Score:  Ole Miss 60  Auburn 55 Bad home loss for the Tigers as their problems have now spread to games inside… https://t.co/AhPFlzVtgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andres Aquino #NYFW #nyfw2019 #couturefashionweek #cfwnyc #womenswear #fashion #chic #couture #womensfashion #style… https://t.co/8mycJZQEJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not a double #espresso, it’s half an americano...  Memories of #Prague with this super weak #coffee... I sho… https://t.co/DVec7klK4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true!  I was a walking disaster my first few years losing thousands.   https://t.co/mNNNjCfEmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ray_Touma97 @barstoolsports @MickstapeShow Lebron got 6 lol . Is that considered many times ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RollingStone I am listening..  I wanted to have the ability to regenerate like @Marvel @Wolverine   Perhaps she ca… https://t.co/ivd4vy5hEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaxdellosso With a handful of Hershey’s Kisses if the glorious chocolate-peanut butter combo is desired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EDGARHR240785 @_VicenteSerrano Estoy de acuerdo si hubiera gente buena en el pri hubiese detenido las masacres  y… https://t.co/NPQtJdEEPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching stuff like Shounen anime with friends you love or a siginificant other makes the series so much better. Wa… https://t.co/msKIZXl7cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i swear to gods and goddesses this girl can’t live without a partner in her life. i’m sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu I know somebody in Hanoi who is going to be throwing a major temper tantrum tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BungieHelp having some issues pursuing the malfeasance quest line. I need to win 3 more gambit wins to get to the… https://t.co/8mNwWLy5ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poof0017 @TracksideMikeN @PapaBeez @gabe_prewitt @horsemandon @deltaracing Time to join Wallyworld!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening Today— additional security and support for #VirginiaRandolph students after yesterday’s active shooter th… https://t.co/JzybCcC7u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarbaraLee I doubt that he was thrown in jail for LIFE because of a TWENTY dollar bag of pot! I'm sure the scal… https://t.co/O2eCOQEyNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharmCityGraphs Jesus. I’m glad we’re on the second floor. But I googled “black light flashlight” and will totally be purchasing one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathrineKryger @Pegerella @realDonaldTrump Let’s not be so harsh! I had a bone spur removed from my foot in colleg… https://t.co/0A2tP77djY]]></document><document><![CDATA[you are defeated. It leaves many doors open. No matter the troubles in your life or in this world, our only safety… https://t.co/igcJcwPOrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to bed at 5:30am, wake up (with no alarm) at 9:19am. My body is telling me to be responsible. 😩🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[NW: “Beauty and the Beast” for the one hundredth time. Maybe it’s that 12th? Lord knows? I have two girls!… https://t.co/nbfgx4TUzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PekalaLaw @IsIllinois The tuition fund was a Giannoulias catastrophe, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortuneMagazine You and McCabe are one and the same- him w/Rosenstein on the 25th Amend and you with Abe on the 1s… https://t.co/57MHvQ31ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[92-94 was the best R&amp;B music to ever come out. The list of albums that dropped in that two year span was ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honor meeting  Congressman @JoeCunninghamSC yesterday. Two Eagle Scouts, two people who value science, an… https://t.co/pD6rC9SDpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassySculptor @ECHOtheCALL Difference: President Trump is protecting the citizens of the United States. Powers giv… https://t.co/Obvo5vyZ3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's cute until you think about how that pouch smells. You know they shit and piss in there, right?   I'm just here… https://t.co/X5yQvrfHmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gn i better wake up on thursday w league play and a REVERTED patch. Ily all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky man held at gunpoint for wearing a MAGA hat speaks out #BuzzVideo https://t.co/YBdUJZzwM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylemartino Hard to compete with the “meaty French forehead,” am I right or am I right @rogbennett ?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I hear Cohen on Trump, I recall the suggestion. “You are what you say they are”. Can’t be a better example of… https://t.co/Zfvxrsih0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had some dude yesterday get pissed at me cuz I was in uniform and I got my food before him so he said I was “priv… https://t.co/dCBhvZQmud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sec1968 #Jesus met Hookers &amp; Tax Collectors - Doesn't mean he was Guilty of anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larry Ellison would take it private at $17B. What a joke, that’s the Lyft IPO range. It’s also 0.5x gross sales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialism has been going on for a long time in New York and it's very dangerous, says former Rep. @ClaudiaTenney,… https://t.co/2fXlQtD1Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[A video tribute w/lots of pictures honoring Damari Makale Herald, Zion Elijah Beard, London Anayah Dixon, Rickelle… https://t.co/IlNJySiW8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gozia_s We all continue to find ways to effect students lives. With role changes we just change how we push students :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Bryce Harper AAV at $25mil the Phillies save 8 mil/yr. Arietta $25mil comes off in 2 years, the same year Mike… https://t.co/9WLyUEsRbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bowl of soup with someone you love is better than steak with someone you hate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEvanAltman Going to be at ST in a couple weeks. Any recommendations as far as Bars, Restaurants go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey folks, just a reminder, this is our president. Isn’t it awesome? 242 years of advances and this is where we’re… https://t.co/NB5ZIVXAKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Info No Te Puedes Perder De Ver Hoy #MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni @magdaproducer ✨📺🔮🎬🎥 @programa_hoy… https://t.co/bBTs2BDzcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertONeill31 Pre-scrambled from a carton and the kicker is intentionally undercooked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Grace and Grit™ by @GreatRaftBeer @ 3 Flights Up Taps &amp; Tacos — https://t.co/iCUTnWjwlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy vOWLentine’s Day @overwatchleague @natenanzer see all of you at the arena. And good luck to everyone!!!… https://t.co/8uVruFj63P]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KaceyMusgraves Look! Apple already has an emoji of your face! 🥴🥴 https://t.co/CXYm81FTXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the late #JedAllan from when he hosted the enduring “Celebrity Bowling” from @FOXLA in the ’70s. #RIP https://t.co/SA4jQAJYun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRPSToday chief welcomes proposed legislation changes? Must still give @Chief_BLarkin  power to screen out public… https://t.co/6uRMBFilSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time I watched this i was screaming "NO! NOT THE LITTLE GIRL!" #Catitstu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman She is very shameless and would not resign, therefore she should be impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our out-of-context Vampire Night tweets are now brought to you by @DDMDcast because that's where we do game things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexiOHudson @slatestarcodex It's very existence and dna is connected to headlines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn_DeMore1 @KKL_Justice Words not necessary! https://t.co/6ZRQTMWA8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rooney with a humongous big blocked shot with 20 seconds left to preserve the #NJDevils 4-0 win. Schneider with 30 saves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we are being scolded by the social reconstructionist for cooking dinner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@think_again_7 @MichellePanchuk So, woman can't follow the imperative command and proclaim the gospel to everyone t… https://t.co/k4WpTyR8P5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssemblyCall What about the record with a "healthy" Phinisee, Davis and Green available? I'm talking Rob before co… https://t.co/2ya7JQ1TnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dilport_terry @MLB @CC_Sabathia @KingJames I ain’t even mad lol just pointing out an arrogant comment 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigJunior69 I'll bring a local politicians every Democrat we have asked to come on here fifteen times and it's rad… https://t.co/pTCF8aFGU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[اكثر مرة اشعر بالاشمئزاز والقرف بكل امانة حين اقراء اسم @Turki_alalshikh هو شخصية سادية عنصرية قذرة , اجد التوازن و… https://t.co/qGSZLnwElT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day has gone by and I still didn’t get any booty pics, the nerve of some people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fatal 4 Way for the United States Championship IT'S ON!!!! #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is I-95 stalled gridlock traffic for about 10 miles around 12:45am... Miami traffic has gone insane. #miami… https://t.co/vhZpgvRurZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, Wishing You Safe Travels To Work @abc7anabel 🙏🏽 See You On The Tele In A Few Hours! 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 21 goal afternoon victory for team War Wagon. @ Saint Ignace, Michigan https://t.co/UDLGP2adPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Racine, WI? https://t.co/tFC3aesw96 #Manufacturing]]></document><document><![CDATA[UL’s Dunlap captains all-TL bowling teams @TheTimesLeader https://t.co/6g85TUVC8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoVarnish1 Hello, my name is Luke and I’m also an MFA student. Currently, I’m working on a comic crime novel set i… https://t.co/cVWgzzKyI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas in two weeks @PatrickBish  @aj_mcnulty @HarshOnInternet https://t.co/rWCLmjAMto]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I beheld the sword. Sharper than any sword with a double edge blade. And I heard a voice from heaven say  "Appr… https://t.co/bEjIwxYd8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JairAlcala Eso es inolvidable pasa solo una vez en la vida por eso se vale tenerlo siempre PRESENTE .]]></document><document><![CDATA[And there it is. Flowers is a great player, a hard worker, well liked, versatile. He’s everything you’d want from a… https://t.co/lXHMMCiXyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are your favorite male actors of color? #AfricanAmerican #blackhollywood #bet #naacp #tvone #aspire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot I was a bouncer,,, many years ago granted, saw a biker bitch, good 250lbs of smelly shit, hit this… https://t.co/92kfnGaPNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mbta FYI for you that north Quincy’s new parking lot is full already... watching people driving around in circles is kinda funny tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome!!! Congrats Peter. I learned a lot from him on the PA craft.... #mesports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJMykaelV @smoovyseni @WHATUPRG what if i told u bet 😂 https://t.co/8y7Z5xn8Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scarlets valentine visit @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/M3D80iycaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cameron Beene’s Deacon Ordination Services! @ Unity Missionary Baptist Church https://t.co/fpqURxnX26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FISTFootball My left foot doesn’t wanna work right after 5 minutes of straight double kicks! Always closed our set with Sandman though]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All I wanna do as a pastor is bring people to Jesus” - David Livingston. We gotta hear the love part. #GC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn... you really for from slapping a naked person’s buttcheek, to never talking to them again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lrozen @dcpoll The Lucky Bastard audiobook is available @HooplaDigital through many libraries… https://t.co/7WsPRk446s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rEALLYbADiTCH @XTRDragon80 @numbnuts150 @GreatApacheWolf @HTownEaglePhan @MikeMcNalley80 @Jawgoosh @wisehokie RDR2… https://t.co/lqDtL2kLX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[*tries to do something with a post i just made but messes up* “sorry, still learning how to twitter”  thanks for be… https://t.co/HY4EhdNY0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll consider.. love you brother #ryewick #impliedpowers #leftitontheseat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you snatch your .dev domain ? Which .dev domain you want but still too expensive? Google's new .dev domain open… https://t.co/nxii1pvP6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Palace players saw them celebrating. Salt in the wound. Have to be better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El viernes pasado, fue de tremenda bendición. Durante nuestro servicio de Sanidad y Milagros, Sandra testificó del… https://t.co/bQSCYdduxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence What quid pro quo? Putin gives interest in Russian oil company to     Trump.Trump lifts sanctions on Russ… https://t.co/CNvPo4Ikvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Now that’s funny!! I watched that when I was a kid. Even then I wasn’t that into it, and I loved eve… https://t.co/yPRqt4oJ2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jlawrenceLD23. You voted for the cronyist milk bill AND it failed? Big mistake my friend. I hope your lactic boss… https://t.co/KjjXxJKn77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump continues to grasp at phony straws cuz he knows he's going down .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avery Hederman with 2 big foul shots to give JA an 18-15 lead with 14.3 left to play. Biggest shots of the night in… https://t.co/mxI3vAkV0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YPSportsChat A4: Realizing balance is essential and tasks are endless. You have to be fully charged to be the char… https://t.co/REC5FQiFaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandyballz3 @bastilledan I did in the comments. But im a big Mello fan and he’s where I got the inspiration to do it.]]></document></documents></author>