<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Norway Gives $1 Trillion Wealth Fund Approval to Dump Some Oil Stocks https://t.co/jLOWzdzmqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The problem isn’t ignorance the problem is power..” Ta-Nehisi Coates #PowerofthePen @HowardU https://t.co/8mzKuZBfYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates The goofiest girl in the world, Ginger https://t.co/LEOSRxR8cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something about this time of year I crave moon pies!! #mobilemardigras #mardigras #birthplace #moonpie #beads… https://t.co/Z1Y5AAsT7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whahahaeueueu @common @BarackObama Using our tax dollars and taking funds from other sources to build a wall which… https://t.co/F9KCrFtvbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG I feel so bad for @Jackeichel15!  What a disaster my @BuffaloSabres are 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2  After a string of his bs I sent him the suicide hotline #. Before that I told him he could chat with my husban… https://t.co/2IksbcVsha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLRIII Thanks for all the help you e provided to From His Throne &amp; other initiatives 2 assist our homeless residents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anybody would like to bring me a sonic drink that would be great 😍😍😍PPPLLLLEEEAASSAAASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenityredrox @Sister_Polygon You are living your dream! So proud of you Serenity. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoshPatriot05 @h8terbaiterlynn @Patriotmom2one @MAGATrumpGirl @johninphx @slyfoxninja More lies from tRump!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cacti and mountains, such a beautiful site.  #2019SchnurenciaAdeventures @ Cholla Cactus Garden https://t.co/oYgRYVJDM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashionegallery @SharonG40210896 @735BlackSheep @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @TeamSalBrian @JeannaMarie32 @jeanine_new… https://t.co/dKb8XSFzEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If #thebachlorette was a virgin would it be ok for the guy to be constantly talking about it? For all 3 guys left t… https://t.co/F8yhZyqpz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the read. #tlchat #FutureReadyLibs #EdChat @FloridaMediaEd @ocaemfl  https://t.co/FeYw0uyLv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏽‍♀️💩 @abronxchick @birdieglad @jihettly @pannlewis44 @graceslick77 @MarilynT4 @veterans_i @DLTrunnell @JhwilsH… https://t.co/BtQXh9kTs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesatkinson44 @angel_35 @A_Hooper25 @schimmel23 @CoachJeffWalz @UofLWBB It’s also their supporting cast, very sp… https://t.co/peMDkVIDBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#franklininstitute #philly #museum #travel #juswalkingaround #philadelphia #filadelfia #video @ The Franklin Instit… https://t.co/VyNyNmrBoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[But like don’t expect shit from me now. U showing me ur true colors and I ain’t down with how they look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerCox @Ctoddgilbert @TimHugo @DelRRobinson @DelCPeace @chrisstolle @BobThomasVA @yancey4delegate 1/2 We’re do… https://t.co/cRJ4mpNKfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flirting Friday night - "Omg feel how sweaty my legs are from my boots!"  If you're into boot sweat hmu boyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orange, CA #juliehasselberger @ Orange, California https://t.co/sZ5wFpot3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti You’re so vain....you probably think this post is about you. 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness will be found. #lovelife #loveoneanother #happinessquotes #yogitea #40daysofstrength #yogaeverydamnday Da… https://t.co/9U7XLVqwVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s this person? At least they didn’t steal the whole profile. https://t.co/PuEgO3HLHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My top ten favorite YouTubers are  @shanedawson  @JoeyGraceffa  @sssniperwolf  @MisterPreda  @ChannonRose… https://t.co/wyLuYYHNpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I’m really disappointed tonight. All @MSNBC is talking about in reference to the #ManafortSentencing is t… https://t.co/4GlLsCFRvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m 85, I really want to be able to put both arms straight over my head. That is my random, forward thinking goal of the night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy who is redoing tomcats tranny for race season has had it since Nov 16th and still hasn’t touched it. I’m annoyed 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to be home watching the NFL Combine instead of being at work  #adultingsucks #footballislife #NFLCombine2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched a video of my brother’s girlfriend shotgunning a beer wrong and honestly he may need a new gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I walk by an Irish Pub and it smells like someone I knew 🙄 #reallytho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I’m getting use to losing...its kind of fun to turn it into a game. What are we going to lose by toni… https://t.co/TR4ZC5Yt9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOMEN WILL SHINE / Forget styling food, this pile of sunny linens is a masterpiece all on its own, right?! I snappe… https://t.co/bO4dFn28uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efrisco_ @PunishedEl WWE is on and there’s scandals to watch for in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I’ve been (perhaps unrealistically) hoping that Mueller would find Trump holding a smoking gun of treason...… https://t.co/1dETvlrGeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Not one word from you about the fact that Putin has named specific targets in the US to destroy.  Not o… https://t.co/5MoVAkWVs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Africa’s Sugar Industry has lost profit and jobs after the implementation of sugar tax, which is threatening… https://t.co/DXfbKymgVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun control, taxes, recreational marijuana, popular vote, all way bigger issues right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWeather @Merrill_Corp looks like snow is coming for your birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeckertRyan He toyed with their emotions and auditioned them for his conquest. He was also a misogynistic dirtbag… https://t.co/UZK2JpOaXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This snow is messing with me! Make that “my car’s tires likely” ... 😑😑😑😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly That’s why I only listen to the REAL news and it’s not @NBCNews @CBSNews @ABC !  They NEVER can get it right!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fargosi a ella, a la kk, a clan Moyano, y otros el gobierno y la justicia le tienen un cagasoooo, terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[before my dad passed away whole time i thought the same thing once i found out i was grossed out who ever wants to… https://t.co/wJKGfwBXEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 @KimKardashian @kanyewest Will YOU speak to this?!! This is YOUR GIG, guys!!! ALL major news networks i… https://t.co/s2w81DlISl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always important to give a shout out to those companies who go out of their way to deliver awesome service. A great… https://t.co/5tgSLN474N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAMIMinnesota Please get the private, for profit companies like Securian out of Corrections #prisonreform]]></document><document><![CDATA[Switching to state wrestling.  1 state champion and 2 to go (I  hope).  Cmon Happel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He Wanted  The Shirt So Bad Cause Of The Character He Didn't  Care That This Wasn't  His Size 🤣🤣 https://t.co/DFtfAWAD40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlightAlerts_ @jamiearnoldWMBF @RockRadio Amazing.. Poor people and pilot😢🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do people rlly think lady gaga &amp; Bradley are in love in real life... y’all ain’t ever seen a movie or what?? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg_Palast Thanks for all your work through the years, Greg.  I happened to have the show on when you came on wit… https://t.co/QLqHPtaIQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This past weekend participating on an alumni panel to give advice to incoming ⁦@IEuniversity⁩ students #IEU #Spain… https://t.co/gRC5COWtGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[READY FOR THIS BEAUTIFUL DOG TO COME HOME!!!  I miss her so so so so so so so much!! https://t.co/LAQZoluKx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank goodness for this stat. Always judge a society and it’s people by how they treat animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrncssLizz Oh man, when it’s that good I’m like nah I’m all in now...  Perk of being friends with all the managers… https://t.co/7HTuXShKdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sick of the violence of attack on anyone who supports our President Trump!! Time of arrest to be made in jai… https://t.co/9UZyb1Kka6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCOGeese @UCOBronchos What are you geese doing in this weather? Hot toddies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is not finding someone to live with. It’s finding someone you can’t live without❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 George Conway needs to shut the eff up. As long as is his WIFE is aiding  and abetting and assisting… https://t.co/rxEMCBj3wW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWuWu Marcus is getting so used to the fame,  I noticed his game is alive.  Let it go to his head.  That kid is a national treasure]]></document><document><![CDATA[was dreaming all night that my Canadians were coming to visit me and I was so happy because I couldn’t wait to see… https://t.co/jw9id0rPhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[3am me trying to answer the phone at work:”????....Hi Intensive Care”  Hi?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The results of a fully threaded face!  A more effective technique than waxing! It removes hair from the roots!  Cou… https://t.co/QoLgUQNw4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥺 ‘This (more than $4 billion!) is by far the most money that any city council has ever spent in our history. Surel… https://t.co/jS8Pz5yqHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GetThingsDone #AmeriCorps #ServeIllinois Illinois.StateU @StevensonCenter @ServeIllinois]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lautergeist @jallman971 @rhondas_lil_sis @88YahamaKeys @Beatlebaby64 @Aletheia_4Truth @AmericaFirstMO @ATeamMom1 @juliematthews50 😪😪😪😪😪😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING OVERNIGHT: Authorities arrested a 16 year-old make suspect in a deadly stabbing of a Fall River teen this… https://t.co/ZooPDFwiBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TaylorLarsen When I worked nights I did this in the morning when I got home and it helped clear my mind enough to… https://t.co/ZczzGB5JkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giles_vianey I deadass hope I still have em after pregnancy. #praying 🙏🏽🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I u don't like @Cristiano or say he ain't sexy we can't be friends. I love Cristiano so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t get over this one:  I made a kissy noise calling my two new  rabbits over to me. They both came literally r… https://t.co/iqdbpuLRKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready to get all these midterms outta the way and see Space Jesus tomorrow, kick off spring break, and then go o… https://t.co/JssbnchF6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RantsOfIzzo as motivational speaker:  #WhatIlearnedToday @realBradStaggs https://t.co/Tfjet1OxLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOnion May all of your days be blessed with clear clouds on a sunny day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m so exhausted, really need to go to bed!!  My anxiety: https://t.co/yOjMk5V30B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered something on Amazon literally 16 hours ago and it’s out for delivery already. WOAH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlliniCreative @Illinois_Alma @MascotHall Eligible Mascot Hall of Fame characters: perform at live events; been in… https://t.co/U5zV3u92iV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ☕️ and 🎧 while you 🚇, I highly recommend @ForeignPodicy — the latest episode in particular!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marybethpf @Lymenews @LymeBook @liv_lyme @lymehopecanada Rally event to support this lawsuit! Please share!… https://t.co/tAfjxnD3HO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Biden understands that unfortunately our current leadership is an embarrassment. And if we don’t do something a… https://t.co/K0iXIxmRBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatemehx2 @ohheyeva @karaswisher @jack Throw in a trust or a trustworthy for the win]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before a amazing Edgy cut for this young lady @ Cutting Edge https://t.co/C6dTt2bRU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my 4th time rewatching TWD and truly I have nightmares about zombies every single time, good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lace up your shoes and join me on April 6th for the 2nd annual Black Excellence 5K being held in Lynn, MA! All ages… https://t.co/F8byTWYutl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisonjaime @mommamia1217 LET'S SEE HOW MANY "REAL" EVANGELICALS A OK WITH THIS!!! ANY TAKERS? GRAHAM? REV. FALW… https://t.co/qh3sAyXy1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLIGHTS BOOKED TO CABO   OKAY ITS REAL TIME TO HIT THE GYM UP... # 💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFunkySpoon David! This absolute #Lunacy and a waste of #Taxpayer #Dollars!  🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @sianoresist For those who are interested in learning more about Native American. Go back to your earli… https://t.co/cZRaqPIALr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf just asked if I would switch to Android with him and https://t.co/nQBkAj4mI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only was my Monday horrific, now my Tuesday is as well. This week is not my week 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[POSTRECITO DE DURAZNO  FELICIDADES JULIANTINA FELICIDADES AAM #JuliantinaEnTVyNovelas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shower karaoke time the artist today is @JulietSimmsALL love her https://t.co/mf4wYQ5YRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[chuckle with me for a bit. Funny Valentine's Day Ecard: If I worked in a restaurant... on Valentine's Day I would p… https://t.co/HnAHpvHZaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The defense asks about her hearing voices the night of the incident. She says I don’t hear voices I heard a loud thud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMurphyNBC @nbcbayarea @NWSBayArea This better change by Tuesday when I get back from ❄️🥶 Philly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSaiyanMama @DMSK2018 @Teresa_Giudice Never ever did she not deserve it. She will not be satisfied until her brother divorces Melissa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigskybabs @abigailkjohnso5 @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows https://t.co/JJFjiC3lvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making Dreamcatchers with our Junior Graduated Support Class today.. Great way to end the week before the break!… https://t.co/RaXr6s8WN0]]></document></documents></author>