<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Every Republican who was present for the vote (some flights were delayed) voted to protect those born alive during… https://t.co/cHYk5kR0D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes how helpful that was for me as i was getting stumped out in the hood by Cuomo with the wokest comms team ever -… https://t.co/w7rKLrl1i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wana buy alcohol when i get off work but buying alcohol at 7am??? lmfao my coworkers gona be staring that’s for sure 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikmartineauTVA @pbernier10 @impactmontreal @TVASports @FLord_TVA @100_Soccer @HassCamara6 @JonoBourgault @MLS… https://t.co/TYzo9BrYFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMMikayla @Mabel - “Don’t Call Me Up” @dumblondemusic - “white hot lies” @iamcxloe - “I can’t have nice things” @JairaBurns - “Numb”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkidementri great job on the Variety Club telethon-thanks for your work-look great in brown! https://t.co/XCv4vaBNRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StocksToTrade When your cell phone application comes out will it be intergradable or will you be able to trade for STT from your from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layers! Capturing today’s visit to @nikeschroeder ‘s studio for a client meeting! #fiberart #threads #custompanel… https://t.co/WdPoBt37Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This past month @MissTaylorMusic was a great guest on @FOXNashville Rock &amp; Review more music releases in 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what my husband’s first thought was? To go grocery shopping and stock up on my favorite snacks and ingredi… https://t.co/wEyprO49Nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMoochers @GeorgePapa19 @In2rug4uMcguire With AGs like WIngman Holder and Tarmac Lynch and the Comey//McCabe FBI e… https://t.co/PJen2XEvP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of Jesus is amazing y'all! #breakeverychain #truth #thereishope #john8:36 #essentialGodlyleadership https://t.co/YCQtihinVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasondingr And I beat him with my "measly" boat. 😁 https://t.co/mpBmCdpds1]]></document><document><![CDATA[100+miles, 4 games, two take out meals...and we end the day with this. #godisgood #sunset #nofilter #clublife #azwx… https://t.co/OuWH8uxRwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[5-1 again!!! 🔥🏀🔥🏀 Unbelievable run RN!! WVU +4.5💵 Indiana +2💵 Wake +4.💵 USU -8.5💵 Ball -1☹️ Miami OH +6.5💵… https://t.co/phi8OTennZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our outside stray cat #BabyKitty adopted us a while ago, and we love him. #stray #cat #adopted #kitty #adoptedkitty… https://t.co/1ju0WSUIq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I'm really laughing at you not with you. . 11x14 ink on fine art paper . #JefferyPage . #clown .… https://t.co/mfJYiPNNI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any parent of any teens should be aware of this! #Vaping is a gateway to eventual #Cigarette 🚬 smoking! | Teen e-ci… https://t.co/X8Pzlgt21k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rushtheiceberg @davidtedu @MrZiebarth @Scotteach @billselak @GustavoArellano Nancy Drew graphic novel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - Evening Briefing:    Paul Manafort sentenced to 47 months in prison     Via @nytimes @remytumin… https://t.co/p9Crt2owDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancisTheSailr I still can't eat olives without a martini's assistance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 61.3°F Wind:3.6mph Pressure: 29.894hpa Falling Rain Today 0.00in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodymacman @MikeAngelina that last caller had zero credibility talking about the Phillies batting order: Hopkins ?? Hopkins ? Geez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaclynCorin @ChrisMurphyCT @AMarch4OurLives @Everytown @GiffordsCourage @RepLucyMcBath @davidchipman Just finished… https://t.co/FWgPADMqv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peak of @SCHS_Baseball1 banners. @CoachWilson35 @HumbleISD_SCHS @HumbleISD https://t.co/w2uQWyvucH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When  men chooses to sell their sun to buy a candle  I call it 1st degree of foolishness. You're à product of you… https://t.co/LtlxsZJdWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🔥🔥🔥 New Music Video premiere on YouTube today 10AM ... show some love to ya boy!!! ❤️❤️❤️ #happyvalentinesday Fo… https://t.co/b3wPN0hboE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annie cannot even with this time change business. #australianshepherd #aussiesofinstagram #dogsoﬁnstagram… https://t.co/vig1eYNxFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliSalari1965 @ejabel2 @Doodisgirl @KatTheHammer1 @vivianmtl @Exodus2019 @NYCREMilton @Sundncefn @Jenn198523… https://t.co/yVB45VcevL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drawings from Tuesday’s sketch event at @madroneartbar . Great modeling work by violetsparadise . #figuredrawing… https://t.co/UFLrL9YsRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Guest Services Representative - https://t.co/TmWBAT67UM #Simon #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSatkowiak @GrantRamey I want to know his response to the text from the KNS complaining about access]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que USA mande un dron artillado y lo hagan explotar!! A el y a todo su grupo de Asesinos, igual que hacen con los f… https://t.co/cizviBgNwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/yUD3PQFCIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undertheskiin I’m sure everyone will find something to complain about it. Didn’t see Bohemian, not planning on seeing Rocketman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broke my phone today after a year no case no nothing crack right down the middle. I guess you know what that mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassquachcomics @SteferstheGreat @laurenshippen I had to dissect a pig in junior high over the course of half a se… https://t.co/zL6joZQ0Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattyInfante I agree. But does Grier/ Flores/O’Shea? It’s not about this players ability to perform. It’s about th… https://t.co/fPqDtQuA64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job ladies. 🥇🏆#Championships #LatePost #NeverOnTimeAlwaysOnPoint #CarryOn @ Caesar Rodney High School https://t.co/fZCOBvusqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, APPARENTLY a double date doesnt mean bring two dates. I wish someone would have explained this concept because… https://t.co/wRFS6andkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josiahlockhart @Grow_Biz @WEScotland @poons21 @LeonaMcDermid @Kirsty_CSk @yvonnegreeves YOU’RE WELCOME. https://t.co/SsTST7eIQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamjohnfoss @donttrythis I’m so intensely tired of the childish mentality that no human can be applauded for any… https://t.co/hP6Fz3IK1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlJam @Letkemann @TheOhanaFest But when will Pearl Jam play LA again???]]></document><document><![CDATA[anybody else have a day where they needed people to answer their phone only to get their vm? This day needs to end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyoPeyoW A big beautiful concrete wall fr sea to shining sea which Trump promised Mexico would pay for is a mediev… https://t.co/JJ07Y2P1Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @suzydymna People with good sense already knew about Obama's and Clinton's Iranian and Russian conne… https://t.co/2vAbfe798P]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this would be just $25M a year...Of course, it was reported the other day that one-third of the money in the Nat… https://t.co/3KroWkBVTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Rockford, IL? View our latest opening: https://t.co/NmW2tMD7C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special Thanks Too ULL For A Great Visit And Big Thanks Too @PToney @leg12tim #GeauxCajuns 🌶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBDeadlineNews Any guesses as to when Vlad gets called up?  Blue Jays at Target field middle of April but I’m worried he’s not up by then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find me Lisa I'll fuck you so good.. We can always finish where we left off Lisa I want to make you cum so many tim… https://t.co/UI2K18qIoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEYOND THE LIGHTS  Indie artist concert  FRIDAY APRIL 5th 8pm 1-am  THE HOTTEST INDEPENDENT ARTIST ROCK LIVE WITH… https://t.co/rW62xHVhDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[In celebration of International Woman’s Day I celebrate Gina Cheri Walker Director of the CIA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loinclothnation @IronMaiden @LozMetalus @jammerfal @FreewindR @Tornado0fSouls9 @UpTheIrons29 @HeavyMetalYetii… https://t.co/tsoek67pw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@OaklandEA Striking Oakland Teachers at Prescott School successfully talked this man out of crossing the picket li… https://t.co/HFq8sRjwar]]></document><document><![CDATA[tour (west coast only) next week i’m hitting 🥁the road with gP. 💙 come say hello! @ U.S. Army https://t.co/s3yfcyAE25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcmfbreakroom wine distributors openly admit that they sell the same bottle a wine that you would buy on the shelf… https://t.co/EVCAJsHlUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalNiederman @GotNoSperm @rcc1000 Traffic jammed going to the Linc now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjeong talking about wrestling he should hit up @BarWrestling #YouCompleteMeHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[But there’s also this, it’s not too late— GOD ’s personal Message!— “Come back to me and really mean it! Come fasti… https://t.co/4tjvxtf8cD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadorkables @GeorgeTakei Gun control is a huge issue but should be tackled through legislation. Same as with Climate Change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making investments into and learning new things about your craft from masters in your business is so important no m… https://t.co/gBqtKqPNlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Autographing bibles....My church going family would never let someone do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejcw @sean_meagher 1/ "...Hey, when we DO allow some building...let's require they build PYRAMIDS* instead of S… https://t.co/jAr8nizh4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsHankinsClass @O_L_Mayers @KirkElementary @jerri_stjohn @BellBreyanna @mradamwelcome @SarahSajohnson… https://t.co/TuyFFtGZag]]></document><document><![CDATA[#biomechanictattoo #coveruptattoo #eternalinks #cheyennetattoomachine #kwadroncartridges #calvetattoo #melrose… https://t.co/Apm7jWqmec]]></document><document><![CDATA[An almost impossible task to choose just one, but if I have to choose on it has to be—-Black by @PearlJam. From the… https://t.co/Ln1b2PSLWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OURrescue @IngrahamAngle @TimBBallard and gee who brought the family's here illegally???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been to Philly many times before but didn't realize until this trip that its transit is quite useful once you… https://t.co/Mjh35PTVDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[me on ellen   ellen: so i heard you like the country bears  me: yes  (The Sun Bonnet Trio appear on stage)  me: oh my god ellen you didn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ещё 3 недели до отпуска продержаться, а то я уже не только понедельники ненавижу, а все дни рабочей недели кроме пятницы.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jessie Coleman PTA Council honoring our TOTY today.  Shay McNeil represents @GMS_Wildcats so well. So proud.… https://t.co/j9SvyDTItI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Javier_Alarcon_ @Cruz_Azul_FC Hace cuanto tiempo que no tiene jerarquia 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_smedley @ThatOneSleeper hey hook up a key for New world? Wanna hang with sleeper and check it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[هو انا الوحيد اللي حسيت ان فيلم #الساعات_الاخيرة كان حابب يطلع #مرسي كرئيس جمهورية مستقل يدير مصر بدون اي مناقشات و… https://t.co/TXz45tzFIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to understand and young enough to relate... these guys taught me so much game and business before i… https://t.co/rE8UQOmtke]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you end your night after a show???  With fuckin a burger and wings from Mel's. Can't complain when it's 2 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WitnessIntimidation #MichaelCohen #MattGaetz Egregoous. Witness intimidation should at least merit a censure h/t… https://t.co/dHSVUNzEVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Like What like language is like that?? https://t.co/RbyR3vYZY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[LUIS MIGUEL - Delirio (Official Music Video) https://t.co/R7nz1WAP27 via @YouTube #Musicmakesourwolrdbetter 🎧🎼🎤🎹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remnant of winter; firehouse at CSPS/ @LegionArts https://t.co/9jUc5xCWwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyakDean @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump On phones? Forever? Its in ya school. About fake news. Most valuable thing… https://t.co/ZFesKsm9B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down here in Minnesota and it’s 0c, I’m sweating... 😅   @visitduluth bound!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SaladMasters cook show @ Jersey City, New Jersey https://t.co/ntX2MK2CC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Mary Tournament champs. Proud of Brendan for learning how to play from behind this season and going 100% from s… https://t.co/oVU9TTvT5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VenezuelaEcono @Refrigeraptor @abiudhdz @dany_bahar Nuestros amigos son los que creen que es una decisión entre de… https://t.co/wWbqkK82PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for Shaggy tomorrow night @Shoptalk ?   @DiRealShaggy  🇯🇲 #Shoptalk19 🌴  Shaggy - Angel ft. Rayvon (Off… https://t.co/X6Szt6F9cH]]></document><document><![CDATA[el queso philadelpia es lo mejor que a inventado el hombre, niéguenmelo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimLaMay Truth !!! Get a therapist!! @hgtv @HouseHuntersUSA @CastleHouseJT #HouseHunters #TheCastleHouseEstate 🏰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld You should demand a recount ... the Biblical name or Orpah not Oprah. @JesseBWatters @TuckerCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBNGordon Pat Robertson should be ashamed of himself. How dare he call himself a christian as he judges and lies a… https://t.co/BKIQhKQiq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sh_aronL @CreekCoffeeHous Good morning Sharon! None of us can catch a break. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If orchestras and competitions changed their audition repertoire to include the women and people of color in the ca… https://t.co/vc3uCBpbjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzieohreally @sam_baker 📣And now, the millennials don’t like “brown furniture” anymore, and prices for non-rare… https://t.co/MNTVlfk1Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRachelFisher Yeah. It was just another movie. Not even a film. Should never have been nominated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday - Drinking a Pine: By Yakima by @Pariahbrewingco at @pariahbrewingco  — https://t.co/fsgD6soY9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh!  I almost forgot!  I have to Thank You to Glide’s Walk in Center,  Meals program and St. Anthony’s Meals Progra… https://t.co/NyY6awp54v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandleDavid @thomaskaine5 @LumpyLouish And here I thought that it was her turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weentuguyuk69 @Terrilltf The power of colonial systems was/still is erasing our connection to traditional culture… https://t.co/ulyOEB0j9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisCrazyTrain Things are looking up Cindy.  I hope the dawn of Sunday and Monday look promising.]]></document></documents></author>