<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[An honour to be a tiny part of their lives, and a shout out to @GWC_News and @EdinburghUni for their immense suppor… https://t.co/uQbIdXfeQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplyjennyyx Spill that motherfucking tea!! Also, I want names cause I won’t tolerate that shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @mconley11 didn’t receive a tech tonight after the way he’s been treated, shows just how much of real… https://t.co/67VlxhIsGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImEricaCampbell I will forever love this woman I remember I sent her a direct message I was so in a time of need a… https://t.co/Tf9ZzVuubp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPoversight @Jim_Jordan @RepCummings is a disgrace to a Congress. He’s too old and stupid to serve. He should be out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaviota330 What a cutie. Please find her a forever home. 😢💔🐕 5 months old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Few sights are as instantly recognizable, and few sites speak more fully to American nationalism. Standing on the… https://t.co/WrmMiXB8YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Barry, Obama was a Constitutional lawyer, he knew how to read, he read all his in… https://t.co/dUesekCVpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[home is where we come from and where we will return to once we've finished playing this round of the life game. hom… https://t.co/WzIJLkXGhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krm1285A @letters4trump45 @GreatAwakening0 @peachy_witchy @TrumpRepublic2 @Razorsmack1 @DakotaGirl9 @Sequencer16… https://t.co/DXxB2mTd60]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really enjoying Love Is War. I love the characters, it’s cute and funny as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of fun had tonight celebrating Dr. Suess. Parent’s Night Out! @SLESeahawks @JanettR74331875 @quay0301… https://t.co/scbS8ZiRYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronMu59978144 @RealCandaceO @CNN @JussieSmollett You're being sarcastic right? You have to ask these days in the age of trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to workout glutes! thThe #healeamethod is known for great bums. I Hustle hard everyday and hustlestandard2018… https://t.co/TZDgBJh9ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance Did you know ahead of time, that Prince Mohammed Bin Salman was going to order the murder of Khashogg… https://t.co/aWwljALg4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone quality is shit, but Armenian barbecue is UNMATCHED. Don’t @ me.   Glendale bound. Little Armenia this cit… https://t.co/rfhswjcbOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so who gets to eat all the food from the Food Porn Snapchat episodes cause I volunteer as tribute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaybilson @Cheesecake 😂 took me awhile but my love for yard house is strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Coral Gables: mist, 71°F 94% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The child should never have been arrested. The adult needed better job training. News media: stop vilifying; stop s… https://t.co/ZYxPaKKEf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may or may not have screamed and woke up my husband when this package arrived 😬💖💖 @JeffreeStar @MorpheBrushes https://t.co/n5m0wl6hDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacyOnTheRight The truth has come out on Empire actor Smallett. it’s just not THEIR truth. It’s the narrative tha… https://t.co/SXUG3uzR1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept @JordanSekulow @WhiteHouse @Barnes_Law @DineshDSouza @GOPLeader @DanCrenshawTX @Jim_Jordan… https://t.co/E5cx0U6yWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RighteousDem @Melody28043518 Call the school. If that doesn’t work call the school board. Or go higher. Can’t let that happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesilberman @lemieuxdavid @bourgwick "...and a couple of girls."  THEY BURIED THE LEDE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterDrost Oh stop it!! You should be completely and utterly excited!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the vote of confidence fortune cookie 🥠  #sucessfulbusiness #fortunecookiesays… https://t.co/NI3KrUEPgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samtdelangel JAJAJAJAJA aguanta! Yo no había pensado en nadie desde el principio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_JayShep Naaahh it’s my mans with the tan line jacket 😭 that hoe is juice 🥤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Swifttys Schiff’s dirty laundry will come out  and it has many Soros  spots and many stains that aren’t decent… https://t.co/fdCvTZvaob]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma just told me “What am I going to do without you the day you decide to move out?”  Brb while I go and cry my heart out 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_witty_n_wise_ @MrInteriority @insane_alane @RickBColby @Sandy_HanyR @Freudky @momo_424 @Henry_3000 @renata_horus… https://t.co/eSfAQcmXI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is the car behind me flashing their lights at me or going over all the potholes: a Minnesota mystery https://t.co/r9uaXEe8Vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[No better time to get things done than the present! 🏃‍♀️💕 https://t.co/Y5MuoaOWc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrielleZolciak This show is not the same.  Boring.  Scripted.  Bad acting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no limit to what we, as women, can accomplish! Happy International Women’s Day to all the women in the wor… https://t.co/S0vwBR9oid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaladrielResist @Megresistor I guess my question would be... why make the honest candidate spend more $ to have an… https://t.co/avRDgQojRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow by Kacey Musgraves really just DOES THAT https://t.co/GXnsvl19Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanRegina For an adult who is paid to teach not humiliate our kids, this is disgraceful. I hope the family of… https://t.co/2vOziYA4PD]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Christians, we have on the full armor of God. The arrows don’t sting.  Hell will not prevail against us! MAGA. GODS IN CHARGE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sqigley the squirrel 🐿 #squirrel #cute #feeder #marieodileroy #hungry #buffet @ At Glenn &amp; Marie Odile https://t.co/ikek39M4tA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all don't understand how much I HATE people who only hyu when it's convenient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[see this is exactly why no nigga driving my car unless i’m in it cause no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is outrageous, how is there 18 shades of “I need to speak to the manager” and 2 shades for anyone with an ounc… https://t.co/nzNtlpcxAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurry up and wait. Wait for Hemp Production Plans Before You Begin Planting https://t.co/wO4YApJaqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[League champs! @travis_jeremy Great experience! Thank you! @OSACrusaders https://t.co/n84JXhxGed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elite0356 @Moes_HQ There’s a Moes in Toledo and it’s way better than Chipotle or Hot Heads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@planetjedward heyyy look what i saw yesterday in NYC😎 https://t.co/foljK22E5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the peak wind gusts measured today! I am tracking when winds will subside coming up at 630pm on… https://t.co/rfLZU6c7gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatBradley22  @CoachJimmyDykes who were the young men dressed in street clothes on KY’s bench last night? They wer… https://t.co/9glL4ZB908]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff @randypcox Exactly. If their argument is that the Constitutional solution is impeachment, then Congress… https://t.co/4K0Kpic8JU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting My Yoga On 🧘‍♀️  🎼 @julietav  . . . #yogaliving #healthylifestyle #yoga#yogapractice #yogalife #instayoga… https://t.co/WemHUnNmGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister and I are planning matching tattoos 🤞🏽💗but my other sisters gone be mad 😂😂 idc I’m the baby🙃 they better… https://t.co/Vb8BZTegiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamSeder How dare she? That is appalling! These kids are concerned about their lives and Feinstein is consumed by her re-election!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya'll check out my gorgeous listing in OC! Cruise ship views from this gorgeous rare 2 story condo with breathtakin… https://t.co/FBXO7H3lde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsypad Wow If this tweet didn’t explain my current situation 🥺 wish I could retweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you don’t have a ‘drive your tractor to school day’ then get the heck out of dodge”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to be in the room where is happens @HamiltonMusical #HamiltonTampa #notthrowingawaymyshot #alexanderhamilton https://t.co/W3MQNWwrR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @owendeline9 !!! ❤️ Thanks for being such a great friend since kindergarten!! I love ya lots 😊 https://t.co/5eGdnI5H8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FazeL_2 A lot of stuff happening in my life right now, I just don’t want to fuck it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to all the boss ass ladies around the world♀️💜 #internationalwomensday   . . . . . . .  #girlpower… https://t.co/uaRgomtrRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim looked scared as heck from the start; or feverish ? Flushed, like he wasn’t well? Too much Brie ? Kinda-look 🌿🍃🕊]]></document><document><![CDATA[And So,let us ask the Lord for wisdom and understanding so that we might be patient, longsuffering and merciful in… https://t.co/UwQOm4s17O]]></document><document><![CDATA[So her gripe isn't with the guy who she claims trafficked her (whom she oddly doesn't name) and never once reported… https://t.co/tsa1kmmBBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes are are seeing two of these gorgeous vintage 1960s Pitman-Dreitzer Colony White Lattice large and stunning milk… https://t.co/2Ofh2T43t9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be doing homework buutttttt I’m looking at flights to Costa Rica instead 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashisdtf ** i have the mind of a mas- i have the mind of mast- i have the mind of a mastermind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love capturing beautiful + bold brands. Branding visuals can make or brand your business. So, let me capture your… https://t.co/TVWB7si0Il]]></document><document><![CDATA[The babies mikey_1988_albq rocking and supporting 💜💜💜  get yours at https://t.co/OljiSHglr9 @ Albuquerque, New Mexi… https://t.co/rGDVy6BDyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best anchor chart for inner city schools, for sure! https://t.co/ap67q8BGGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morrissey_M_E @HJJoyceEcon @Docstockk Sure but what impact will that have on women as a class if they don’t count… https://t.co/PX4qWRMYVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this distinct ringing in my ears and vertigo a sign I’m having a panic attack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Star54iwas happy birthday!!!  🎂🎂😀😀 maybe one day i will be a 10th as cool as you!😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after doing the laundry 🧦 😂😂😂😂😂😂 #lostsocks @ Tonawanda , New York https://t.co/msro7xkRxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstreet Boys have new music. Jo Bros are back together. It’s 2019 people and I’m still holding out hope for 1D’s… https://t.co/QIDeW61yna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be the person your dog thinks you are. #lapdogwannabe #dogsofinstagram @ Three Rivers, California https://t.co/X6TPnLpAys]]></document><document><![CDATA[past midnight and isaac is running to the store bc i’m currently on my death bed. 😭🥰❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8terbaiterlynn @PoshPatriot05 @Patriotmom2one @MAGATrumpGirl @johninphx @slyfoxninja Sounds like you're describing yourself very well!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxMcReynolds Want me to post all the screenshots after that convo of you asking me when I’m working at the club a… https://t.co/ne9NBYTqqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Does Bernie ever comb his hair? He always looks like a mad scientist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is how we do a #babyshower. Wonderful to see all the #cousins and good friends! We have to play some music… https://t.co/v8AwXAN9TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss iamcardib did not disappoint!! #Okurrrr @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/1nM8fYV5Vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyASSETS 🧗‍♀️better than I can.  Metaphorically we all should keep climbing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedWalnut @jerry_saviano @DavidWohl @CNN @jawbrea24031485 Seriously sneaky 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a sweet little derpy friend on my route today. I called him buddy 😍 were best friends now, as he stayed wait… https://t.co/AXT0i48wDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washk12 MY BRAIN ISN’T WORKING RIGHT NOW PLEASE JUST LET ME GET SOME SLEEP AND CANCEL SCHOOL 😎✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart Well yes, first we abort the children, then we eat them. The little ones are the most tender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zabcik @cmoney_htx We make up for it by having extremely friendly pedestrians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go, BVNW! Seeing your happy daughter in these pics and knowing you made the right decision to let her and 2… https://t.co/LeEbj1v0dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Because @Jim_Jordan is on his knees for @realDonaldTrump because he is vying for s job..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCardeezy No that’s when I have two but me for now: https://t.co/4xlOgM6Qxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToonMation @CarlsAmateurHr Just a suggestion I'd make... But then I'd like a Zack &amp; Wiki sequel/remastered/both https://t.co/bsznjrvLzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear thunder? Believe it or not, we went from seeing snow to thunderstorms in less than 24 hours! https://t.co/aOPIbcUecr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ljafk @JulieYAli Did the cartoonist say it was  mistake and apologize for it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watched Sean Spicer say this whole  Cohen thing started because of collusion and there isn't any. So ... Great… https://t.co/0SQ9KZuqOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[New add to the TBR pile! TL and teacher friends, it looks like a must-have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyankoframe Pffft.  I've been in Chicago during the winter.  This was not that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only person I wanna talk to about this is below... rest with love daniel, until we meet again🙏🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thompson_DavidW @Solsticepublish Stunningly romantic-- whatever will happen???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holmans has a killer Bloody Mary bar. This hangover is feeling less deathly now]]></document></documents></author>