<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Some new with some old... . . . . . . . . . #garysasnettdesign #homedecor #decor #interiordesign #designinspiration… https://t.co/Uki6iVZe2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did my civic duty and voted, but not for the candidate who repeatedly bothered me with robocalls, automated texts a… https://t.co/FgYbn8Tdrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Royals Anniversary Launch for One Trieu Yeu Collection February 2019. @ Rodeo Drive https://t.co/CUC4NKACow]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thisweekatchurch was a great reminder to be actively seeking to be in step with the Spirit of God. One of the main… https://t.co/9iVwZYpAml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/inkQXdggiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid themed events can go sideways fast, some of these kids are outta control! #Hall6 #InternationalCenter #KidsFest… https://t.co/1alKHnHd3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yonaremu @BMPC8 La neta si, es que ya le están tendiendo la cama aunque digan lo contrario..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my good friend John McManus, who got an award today for raising the most money IN THE COUNTRY for St. B… https://t.co/vACI3wmAWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchcityblvd @Buster_ESPN Baseball. They have a better team. I’ll take Freddie Freeman and Ronald Acuna over Har… https://t.co/VpT0EebZEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two real-life stories ofGod showing up and doing the miraculous!   https://t.co/gAACBvEdsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredNBCLA @RodneyPeete9 @RogginAndRodney #futureram who played for Wade Phillips does he fit https://t.co/0jF4450ajk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suchadaydreamer It’s fantastic! Not only funny but filled with inspiration on how the course of your life can chan… https://t.co/eiTLYRjlRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonKrawczynski @Patrick_Fenelon I heard it’ll get you the 8th man in the rotation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hardcore team deathmatch 100 is the best thing to happen in black ops 4 in a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! I'm really fed up with Twitter and Facebook banning content. Such little babies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[lets see how good the #LAX WiFi is.. trying to upload a video https://t.co/8WSwbERtQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Colin Powell used a private server. I do hope your persecution is not in any way biased.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiorKamrat As if twitter weren’t toxic enough though.. can you imagine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baconandbotox @TheNateExp @Deej253 @PatBigbe I’m filming in Athens tonight, what’s poppin in Atlanta tomorrow?! 👀 https://t.co/XQE0kIiUmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because broad delegation has been among the Democrats favored policies since the New Deal, and they still want futu… https://t.co/RnfjGiURpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph N. Barometer 30.217 in, Falling. Temperature 25.8 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 79%]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve decided that I’m old enough now to own an air compressor.  Really exciting things going on for a rainy Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCMacriNBA I think he may be cutting back on whining to the refs. Maybe Fiz or DJ or Lance got to him over the bre… https://t.co/WW01VFxlIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mondays at work - exhausting!  Glad to see all my friends again, but ready to go home soon...🐾 @ URBN https://t.co/LmaJognp9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riley_Devenney6 @EmilyMaltman I'm gonna disappoint this country and its gonna be huuuge]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad to see what was once an enjoyable news room to be around has now turned into a revolving door and a toxic… https://t.co/bJymRhHU78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QShieldknight If sure like to be able to get oats in the ground. Have a hair under 1500 to do. Covered up in snow right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a special place in hell for morons that don't use their cruise control on the interstate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toca Madera 8450 W 3rd St, Los Angeles, CA 90048 (323) 852-9400 https://t.co/OAvzvi5DAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedOne23 @smockerson @JoseChavezJr @JimmyBuckets19 I figured it out. Big name NBA players are finally going to… https://t.co/ofzmIje2sS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Montreal tells committee it could be victim of government’s zeal to lower immigration levels and place more new arrivals in regions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These white Republicans hollering at Elijah Cummings.... y’all need to watch your tone! #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing the backlash on Sen. Flowers comments coming from fellow senators, my take is you put yourself in her… https://t.co/NSbYZJ6rHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daddy lying ass told me if I jacc off my dicc would grow 😒😒 shit still small 😪😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ekblad's quick OT goal gives Panthers 4-3 win over Avalanche  https://t.co/cF1jUle9lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least, five 3rd down and 8+ he will convert against the Giants this year.   And that will just be in the first g… https://t.co/s1CirLW6Gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are going to have to have a lot more distance learning and flexible schedules until the gun/mental health issue… https://t.co/9qJO3gBiBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[PM @JustinTrudeau on #TradeCentre is the Canadian equivalent of @BarackObama making a March Madness bracket.… https://t.co/gbvpUuSjOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot remember the last time I had to be up and ready at this time...definitely not about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady at grocery store checkout saw my okra and asked what it taste like. I told her it’s best fried, kind of slime… https://t.co/Cz3qWtH3d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Housing Market Will “Spring Forward” This Year! https://t.co/2m4jbYptuY #homesellers #sellingahome… https://t.co/98mAP33rzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrinajc @ManceIISociety @tonystankstan @Ty______Ty_____ Are you going to cry about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s almost tournament time and Coach O. has the Leopards starting to play their best ball of the season? Never… https://t.co/wrUCOk0nAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year (on this very day) @CreativeBlueB produced four brand new plays.   One was @RossJWhite’s Donal the Numb.… https://t.co/OeSepTInyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful examples make goals attainable, not just another presentation at a conference. @JoannaScholl telling the… https://t.co/3l0klyZtZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateHoeyMP @BBCNews @RobBurl But as it is, because your constituents voted against your long held beliefs, you hav… https://t.co/hifayXobv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#depression is real. Check on your loved ones. @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/8Yuv1KdaqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 This is so heartwarming. This is what the real world is amongst us too, not the racist crap Dems push e… https://t.co/pvM4t30lhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ended up shorter than I really wanted, but I'm sorta relieved to be rid of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redcrew Not on Lake Ontario, but on Rice Lake at the cottage, @ElmhirstsResort has a while weekend dedicated to kite skiing in February.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowballManny @Oasis65 I'm pretty sure PVD averages under 40" per year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really good information from @JonGordon11. Make today premier! 👊 #TigerPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbonjovi any chance you can help put a smile on my friend’s face? https://t.co/7N8tjnd9Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flyers goalie reviews take about 5 seconds and 99% of the time don’t go their way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssa39447149 Please Subscribe to my channel to see all the new content: https://t.co/Ao7DFVZfY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @hurtmenot2020 Ok Morons. So we get rid of Trucks. How do you move material to rebuild all the build… https://t.co/PfwBdf2w1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the 59th year in a row...I woke hating nobody in the world..hatred will eat you up: negative energy; Can’t see why it’s so popular....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may look so sexy online, and all that shit... but i got a heart to lol  I get lonely too. I don’t be fucking like… https://t.co/uHe2ACLUkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomverica @HowToGetAwayABC @petenowalk @violadavis @byshondaland Yaaaaaazzzz!!!👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickCaseyIE I'm ashamed to share a name with you. But then I look at the comments on this thread and realize yo… https://t.co/JCJcRnIrIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump As ridiculous as this sounds, he’s making a lot of sense with @AOC and gang rollin… https://t.co/pmErIIOSyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5ReasonsSports  @SwingsAndMishes  @CincoRazonesPod https://t.co/nxGun0egtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_Padraic @b4s3dFt3hW0rLd If you feel shame it is on you B nor I &amp; can make anyone feel shame. Therapy 100]]></document><document><![CDATA[Propone Diputada Magdalena Uribe plan para que IP contribuya al combate contra adicciones La propuesta incluye el i… https://t.co/LEuH2moQps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is my speaking schedule @GreenvilleUniv: Tues. 3 pm Marston Hall 301: From the Teachings of Jesus to the Doctr… https://t.co/gMohxXEaKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Coach @BJenningsEdTech !  There is literally no one more deserving!  I couldn't be more excited for… https://t.co/anG5WH7lJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawmilltaters She probably spends every waking moment working on that body. But can she cook?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving my Hound... – ♫Music Box Dancer by Frank Mills, from #SoundHound https://t.co/bx6P8Gl3yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Great Pretender  Donnie ‘Two-Scoops’ Trump  Apprentice-in-Chief  #25thAmendmentNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilMickelson last night I dreamt that you won The Masters this year! 🙏🙏🤞🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FleetwoodMac in DC with persianbearguy @ Capital One Arena https://t.co/rxt7A9nTxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ttrader707 That’s from today what you posted was what I had yesterday. Today it shows this. https://t.co/ukNt6lTSB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[what  wrong  mr trump can stand the heat  near the stove  you canot set the rule  over rule congress  get it togeth… https://t.co/IPiJSwPR5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift’s 1989 album has so many great songs on it, crazy underrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBusch Any chance you and the family are making it to Monster Jam tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t an AB issues.  Or a Bell issue.  Or a Ben issue.  It’s the culture Tomlin created.  Get some value or… https://t.co/PeECErAtQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might want to pose this comment to the governor's of New York and Virginia, they seem too Glory in the ninth mo… https://t.co/JyxT7AYy1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely missing #vikings football! Can’t wait to catch the combine next week and find out who could be a future… https://t.co/GF0mUkGPjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all keep my sister Iaya in your prayers today as she’s having a big knee surgery today. 😌🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Humidity @ChuckRossDC @ggreenwald Yes, we should all trust the President for the truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CollegeBoundDorchester Gr8 example of the power of community intervention programs in moving male minority youth f… https://t.co/phSfEgqzVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@07363b091e924df Boucher I do not care one whit about what you may or may not believe.  It is rather obvious that y… https://t.co/MYn5qd9KH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakMeUp12 @ffoggynelsons Thank you. Only Balakey Comeau slander. Looks like Bambi on the ice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretarySonny @DFBHarvard @POTUS That's 22,040,000,000 pounds, which is 22 billion for you liberals reading this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox Chapel boys still alive for the PIAA Class 6A playoffs. Will get in if Lebo beats Butler on Saturday night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aldondelport @Distancecme @DrJeffJarvis - aren’t ya glad your system is so advanced?! Maybe the book editors need… https://t.co/QT91hUTU44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey want to see how progressive the housing plans of 2020 presidential contenders are? You’re in luck!  Excited to… https://t.co/S8Yxigk8Zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son may/may not be a hooper, but if he is I guarantee that he will be the best teammate, the most coachable, the… https://t.co/edeoGCTYDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cayden Primeau 2nd star tonight in a 2-1 win...SP is now up to 92.6%.  McShane with another goal...that's 8 in his… https://t.co/SV0xeuNvxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep seeing Mounted Police officers with cowboy hats and all I think about is officer Haught. @WynonnaEarp https://t.co/N0JlDWenf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Death skipped him so now he'll die an even more horrible death. @DevonESawa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Wow people get a memory 2013 snow in Jerusalem?  It is called weather and it has always changed it is not caused by man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavy storm soaks San Francisco - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/nHMLSUN1HH 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just for the record, stuff like this has been happening ever since the President was elected. It just usually gets… https://t.co/y3PvyxcXJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Macho Man n Miss Elizabeth are alive n Well  !  They were at a Wedding in Berks County last Saturday https://t.co/XlOmVciLtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mutual sharing, concern and caring for others is our natural gift to each other and mine is strengthened as my atti… https://t.co/hZ2AZ9AhHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN They had more money to donate. Remember, Jesus praised the widow who gave one mite saying she gave more than t… https://t.co/0c7jweuCYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s usually accompanied with a slight jump from the surprise followed by an “oooooooooo”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treyarch  why don’t we have penalties for people that leave in world league ??? I’m tired of losing because someon… https://t.co/KFlxHGT7bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneHelmsCom I always remember this, despite not being there. I had a front ticket for that show, which would hav… https://t.co/VsGoboVJdZ]]></document></documents></author>