<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Until Kamala divest her private prison involvement: https://t.co/pwnlHJhnEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope SmackDown fans enjoy the next 4-6 weeks of dance breaks Because come to April 15 the mistake made 3 Raw gene… https://t.co/btHjX6ZIFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol at the two side—by-side self-driving cars dodging jaywalkers; more like sandwiching ‘em. get rekt, humans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanner34imler @morganerhea @RauschRose @JOakleyTHD @UhlikJosh @THDTHEHODGE Yay Guada!!! Rock them leafs girl!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stagg do you remember when Willie Stargell hit a HR at Jarry Park Stadium in Montreal. The ball landed in the swimm… https://t.co/DSAsPWudDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guest service tip: if you are in a business where you are required to check ID’s keep a roll of happy birthday stic… https://t.co/Kk3pDgnd0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright I think the debate is settled the Islanders belong on Long Island I can feel the energy through the tv righ… https://t.co/mQadaWUxv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOregonRA @TR0771N @Carterdsc @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/W0s5HTjybX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rxckyyyy You can’t prepare for everything in life. If you think you can you are nieve. People lose their parents a… https://t.co/7kAB8RjnAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my journey in WatchOS Development. #watchOS #applewatch #swift https://t.co/aosa4sWofe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdtheSock Don't  forget Old Spice, Brut and of course, Williams Lectric Shave. Bring back the 60s !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike got a new haircut!  Which do you prefer- the Before or After? #haircut #menshair #men #mensstyle #instaphoto @… https://t.co/IgCMuAv96A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neliswa_mrobo Thanks so much for subscribing. And I can only speak for myself on that question. I do my earnest to… https://t.co/xygXP0ifgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crock Pot Cookoff (@ Hilldale Family Life Center) https://t.co/i9YXR90gJB https://t.co/j5c7dxwbCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mavs_FFL @luka7doncic @MarkkanenLauri @swish41 Jesus Christ if we get Lauri...I’ll go Sicko Mode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @thatsVeryKari @SLBriscoe @Cbp8Cindy @FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @suziday123 @cowineco @AkronWineGuru… https://t.co/qyJXOmIJV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss sophiebatzloff The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Be… https://t.co/5RacaipVF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldtimer1968 I selectively disagree, it will take time, though I'm frightened by how quickly human looking robots… https://t.co/TkrSt2BepG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moinkbox been looking for grass fed, grass finished meat since I watched #TheMagicPill.  Seeing you on… https://t.co/G3vmLTqXnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now it’s an administrative coup ? Forget the fact members of Trumps cabinet had already been under investigation… https://t.co/36LjIjbgGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures far from home 🌎 @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/CsnRFursAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Westbrook giving away another game I see. Stupid foul, stupid iso attempt to draw a foul, doesn't even try to get t… https://t.co/HTOflkmiky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ_Sports OH,,, her &amp; her sister ever been random without knowing tested for PED's? Just asking, just asking,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me know what your Next Vehicle is going to be so I can bring it to you!!!! @ Capital Ford Hillsborough https://t.co/m4MTwaVM75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is chasing bunnies in her sleep 😍 #dreamingpup #sleepydog #bordercolliemix @ Clawson, Michigan https://t.co/ZlgE6YhdOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7uGIAY4LGM  New open access wellness journal from some of our EM colleagues at Louisville]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @PenFinancial Welland branch is happy to support the efforts of the @OpenArmsMission here in Welland. We’ll see… https://t.co/uMY1kZwgY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TornadoEmergency horrible video of building destroyed on camera. I have never seen anything like this before in my… https://t.co/eUMCNKRtn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Onna serious note, even with the discrimination, the ridicule, the stereotypes, the dehumanization..I couldn’t be m… https://t.co/nOBskRawRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🤦🏾‍♂️ TeamGrind ready to kick off the season!!  @TGrindAthletics @TeamGrind @it_zaay @SaucemanWest… https://t.co/o3MjYChmQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods LOVE IT!!!! THEY DON'T LIKE HEARING THE TRUTH!!!!!😎😎😎😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BpwPqaOb1w I made this for you. Let’s get your face on Mt Rushmore @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dee_Dee_1 @kairoschris @DevlinAdams5 @nivekwask1 @blogTO @jeffrey_vallis You don’t know how you’re going to react… https://t.co/5zQutSdqjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I was Austin last night now I woke up in Houston but I left my maleta in Austin 🥺🥺 man wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greghauenstein Sorry, I've been known to be a killjoy. Have fun then. https://t.co/EFKTToS0xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCRG If you want to be dark until 830 in the morning all winter, why not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamwhoismoses If PJ plays aggressive he will get his opponent in foul trouble. We need more consistency from this team going forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[END 1ST QUARTER: Fort Lewis College and Dixie State tied at 18-18. Like I said, frantic a bit but both teams hittin… https://t.co/ks9dXnSsy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFC_AL Don’t let him egg you on. Best center back in the world in current form. This isn’t a debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xbox @Oreo @GameOverGreggy An Oreo Cookie Xbox One X seems right up your alley! #Oreo #Xbox https://t.co/6qCSs2mXwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Canyon       #photography #photooftheday #photographer #photoshoot #photographyeveryday #photographers… https://t.co/BZTsFST6P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freepsports He was well on his way to becoming a huge weapon for the Lions until he got injured. So the answer is yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinfreeman65 @chambleebrandel Who knows? Only thing that matters is only the situation at the time. They'd been… https://t.co/SlVH1YzFYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[...Hold onto yourself by the sleeves, I think everything counts a little more than we think.  https://t.co/I9HQEVzs55]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ex-comic, Jeopardy contestant and 'youtube celebrity' posted a one-guy personal ranking that HARSHES In-N-Out.… https://t.co/dyWvOSL26S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had occasion yesterday to refer @keisdronelyk to Kurt Vonnegut’s (@vonnegutlibrary) drawing of an asterisk, then to… https://t.co/PTXW9ZdmqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raygunnell @trailhead Hi, Ray!  I saw from your earlier tweets that you went to DF18.  Shouldn’t that have given y… https://t.co/33q0j4chHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold up wait a minute buddy is climbing a dangerous rock with no equipment or support? And you cinematographers on… https://t.co/WXtY3RnVfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savagesaya would love to see you work on some content with @SarahLace20 @KittyJaguarXXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one thinking pat McAfee WASN'T good in the one game he did on fox? Why would ESPN put him on Monday n… https://t.co/AcywdWvmmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Turley loses all creditibility when he states he does not believe there is a crisis at our border! Have you not… https://t.co/sG6MGxuQzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump defends Kim on Warbier’s death? Are you kidding me? What an outrage. Trump is an IDIOT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9QSbPeXs74  Two bills I sponsored: 1). leave a loaded, unsecured firearm in the presence of a child. 2… https://t.co/Zks1riBf4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaypo1961 So recruiting players at another school is not cheating? #hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tzanatian51 I was hearing they were wanting risto and a pick for point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateLechler Really? If so, have it done up here, in NYC. I want to be there for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember always that, if that player were a true free agent at 16, he might have never played for your team and nev… https://t.co/rbwUoq9Bhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I basically broke my knee honestly I’m so over my ankle and now my knee I think I’m dying 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[💎i know that we aint polished but that dont mean we aint diamond💎  #meaningoflifetour #concert #meandmyguys @ Nassa… https://t.co/nvLTmUCEVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TemptationTV and if you truly are in a relationship dating or married and you choose to go on some b******* like t… https://t.co/JxWzQF5Eye]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote a few things... I really like this patient and fun direction I feel like this music with my LFHC is going b… https://t.co/8N8cgwyJge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGCollegeBall @PerfectGameUSA @Mike_Rooney @PGPatrickEbert @Mike_Rooney love the Socratic method in the article. L… https://t.co/zIgrk6v3NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be part of the amazing #ECMO team @ClevelandClinic and to share the story of one our patients at… https://t.co/BuyXmkXWrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @GoCamelsBSB from the Lufkin JV team!!!! @LufkinAthletics https://t.co/TcsSkCtC4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another GREAT property SOLD!!  12320 Benning Avenue, Chambersburg, Pa  Call us today for your free Comparative Mark… https://t.co/7K9dz6jKJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hankgreen Hey - I found this on a bench in Savannah, GA. I feel like I missed out on some sort of game 😞 https://t.co/0dXkAvYQQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The calm before the storm! Sincere thanks to @ccpsinfo for hosting the inaugural Virginia is for Learners Innovatio… https://t.co/qYc8y3MQ4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy family day to everyone! I'm just taking it easy after another wonderful weekend shoot. We shot a really neat… https://t.co/e92jo6w8gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wtf are you tweeting this for Donster?  It’s all over all the news channels what a fuck up you are… https://t.co/PqxwOdUpL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Thank you for joining with @SenSanders on this issue. Be sure to support him in the primary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @kharyp @MeghanMcCain McCain is playing to the pro-forcedbirth and CPAC crowd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie isn't truly working against Climate change if he and his staff use motorized transportation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliZaidiMD @drelisabradley @sasha_opo @ASabanayagamMD @AmiBhattMD @mgurvitzmd thanks Ali...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devon_haripal There’s reports of another one near towers :/ https://t.co/7dU4lnvI9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warroom congresswoman? Shouldn’t it be congressperson or Congress they, or congress them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husker_Baseball Encouraging to see "the boys of summer" win a great one while we're still knee deep in winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You go to a medium size college  cafeteria on a Sunday what do you expect to get, gotta have some awareness! Caf hi… https://t.co/Z7pvFU7aEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingston_guy @kingstonist No, the ads shouldn't interfere with the video plugin at all.  Try clearing your browser… https://t.co/SIhWN7qMFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SMB #Entrepreneurs #CTO #CFO #HumanResources #friends #family #careeradvice The End Of Work: The Consequences Of A… https://t.co/w9043dO2OB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ladiies_luv_Nay Guilty, people nosy, raise the suspense, keep people guessing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost deduce777 •  •  •  •  • #recreationssalon #nailart #youngnails #ynsynergygel #opigelcolor… https://t.co/THkpg6ijXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump That’s because the left will stop at nothing to gain their devious, socialistic, unlawf… https://t.co/Z9rr8CmPj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much is sacrificed to gain what you most desired. https://t.co/O2SrJhlRg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[All last season, @MichaelAnnett led a total of nine laps.  He just led his ninth lap today. #nascar #NASCARRacingExp300]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport in Arlington, VA https://t.co/G9wRJekaHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chelsea might be dogshit but Central Station is the absolute nuts.  Never thought I would get a hard on over a train station 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage ... Going on stage in proud in @Epica gear !! Thanks @brianslagel  @IndieMerchstore https://t.co/jal25FnV3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeMoraca @Iggyhoops2 Says the kid who didn’t even sit in the student section for the eds game lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldtimer1968 Agreed, hell nothing in life is easy, character isn't  exposed in good times, it's when your up again… https://t.co/YLUnd88GFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roommate: what's up?  Me, a giant dramatic baby when I'm sick: not much, just fighting the reaper, you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch #painting #art #draw365… https://t.co/YLy9grivAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Some kids are smarter than you. Some kids have cooler clothes than you. Some kids are better at sports than you. I… https://t.co/A2XuaLFbcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZBoylin @ReeceNickles @HotMaleStuds @querico26 @AlejandroCasFan @gavinperry60 @Darkhog1Darkhog @pman43… https://t.co/5CigVon3MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignore the reflection in my sunglasses. #sunbathingbeauty lol. @ Sagamore Hotel Pool Deck https://t.co/9ELZYPTMR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobMayeda @denvercoder Yesss!  I can hear those printers now! Think it might have take 3 progressive passes to pri… https://t.co/HbgfCTrAqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jotarshow @realmadrid El entrenador tiene mas ego que cristiano, despues de 3 partidos exigentes va a poner el mis… https://t.co/AB6Wwbdik6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shotgun Sour (Black Currant, Apricot, Peach) by Abomination Brewing Company at @taphouse15 — https://t.co/lKOuQYgMqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We used a CO2 laser to do a cavity on our patient. No needle!! No pain!!!!  Win win! #dentistry #painlessdentistry… https://t.co/TbWJFcfCBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JimJordan keeps calling @MichaelCohen212 a liar while conveniently neglecting to say HE LIED FOR DONALD TRUMP! Sti… https://t.co/d5I0MiNenc]]></document></documents></author>