<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Need a corporate or partnership tax return extension? Deadline date is March 15, 2019. Please give us a call 281-91… https://t.co/s1AXf8QEYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFLOK2Ask A2: Arts integration is a key component of differentiation. Some students need opportunities to learn ST… https://t.co/lnT7WgbafZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you can’t afford to tip, and I cannot stress this enough, you can’t afford to go out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh fell asleep while I was tellong him about my annoying ass day and I just cried while he held me and snored 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamirocs @SMMUSD @SamohiPrincipal We are lucky to work with such a committed group of volunteers. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhorta33 @christinathekid I was 16 and living in NY. We were at school and it happened during like 3rd period. We… https://t.co/9IHswJedDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMKristenBell Kristen are you ashamed of the children raped and used as sexual toys cuz that’s life altering —- th… https://t.co/bjuhHSs6BV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heidifessenden @mburnsmath I also like when she says to not listen for what you want to hear. Find the math in how… https://t.co/3bLFcV3OcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins It's like watching the movie "hunger games". Wake up world unless you want this as your future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kadariuspearson Man what?! 😂 and my grandma has the audacity to use an iPad to take ALL of her pictures 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the past month, I got a tattoo, went blonde and got another piercing. Consistently changing for the better💫 #2019Energy✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I even allowed to go to Carnival if I’m not from the islands? I just want to wear the attire and be cute 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encantaría saber decir NO, así no habrían tantas mentiras a medias ni sentimientos falsos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exavierpope He also could benefit from GED classes.  In particular basic English and phonics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know everyone is entitled to their own opinion, but it really baffles me that there are people out there that don’t like country music]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theprtyrckmnstr @gissellemarieee You wouldn’t even call it work, giiiiirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one watching this movie wants you to head off the Geostorm, Gerard. The Geostorm is all I have left at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4Livingtheory @thatgirldkat @Julie188 @KhanStopMe Yeah, I make mine identifiable but learned, when I was single es… https://t.co/ufBBfiTmL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is the woman filming this so calm? I would’ve burned the house down then caught the first plane outta Australia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad they confirmed the fraud and working to correct it; however, those implicated should face legal conviction… https://t.co/EJUFy6Y8TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryce74045204 @bobbybonesshow @RadioLunchbox Alexa play God gave me you]]></document><document><![CDATA[“NO! It is my moral imperative to have more cash money on me in case the taco cart is still open.”   - Things I act… https://t.co/O9dLIojlJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddogsusie @rbesprit I remember that sleep over. It never was a foster or adoption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Goodness I was born 7 July 1945 so we are both Christians and for fun "Cancers" ruled by the moon.… https://t.co/tQYmQseKmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are just some people that can’t celebrate other people’s success. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pharrell for beach weekend, can u ask @BrunoMars or @iamcardib to come down?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning from the best @Stephharvey49 at #TALE2019 #WeBelieveInCMS @CampbellGators @BP_Vasquez https://t.co/6ZNOhsTyJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Job that will never go away: casket rentals.  #WhatIlearnedToday @realBradStaggs @RantsOfIzzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@70_70_70_70 @eclecticbrotha @TaritaC Black unemployment, Hispanic unemployment are the lowest in history. Other co… https://t.co/FrFjA348Mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing out the V and Bean stitch combo... @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/WGG8NaeI7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhat regretting introducing the concept of privacy to a toddler. Because now everything is all about giving him… https://t.co/hyastF4nJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown at the World of Winter Festival kickoff. Food trucks, live music and ice sculptures. #Ridetherapid… https://t.co/6AJim1OWr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I secretly hope MGK had his @ZMyersOfficial PRS when they were recording. 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi I have never seen Nancy Pelosi on one of my ballots.  Yet, she has the power to stop the people of t… https://t.co/gfIR3Yxtys]]></document><document><![CDATA[My succulent has a boner.... #plants #succulents https://t.co/AZAscKDW4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay! Thank you to all of the incredible women who share their stories with us. #WeSeeYou… https://t.co/DevkhO99JQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome episode @HornetNationPro  Great feature on @ECHShornets @ECISDtweets  @OdysseyHQ  team starting at the 3:20… https://t.co/5pNot95EAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Jeff Eastlick! We saw a Bucky win! (Ugly as it was)!#onwisconsin @ Kohl Center https://t.co/ynfSOePPBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I need is a little mental power and my awesomeness 😎 kicks in!! #mentalpower @ Fit Lifestyle Nutrition https://t.co/xHL0OkYjyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kological Wow. You can’t help to show your antisemitism. Guess why you told me this because you think Jews control… https://t.co/kPDKfj9Xco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn!! She is bossy!! Lol!! Reminds me a little of, well, me. I must say. 🐖🐖🐖🐸🐸🐸😂😂😂😉😉😉 @ Fort Deedee https://t.co/Ibv5JfhjJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥰🧸🌹💝 . Roses are red.. . Violet's are blue.. . Big Sean said it best.. . Cause..  . #idfwu . . . .  #withuhk… https://t.co/q8prpra3bm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Before we leave, we’re going to win a national championship.” Madi Williams is confident in the future of her team  #Sooners]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; snow decided to fall on the last day in February in Pittsburgh ❄️☃️❄️☃️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyGDalaMD Or.....a mama who realizes that a hair cut is not the hill on which I’m willing to die. 😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[6m run but never warmed up! Happy Tuesday! . Fueled by #tailwindnutrition . . . . . . . #trimafia #fitmom… https://t.co/gAzu7H1D2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great week for fgcu_wgolf!  Team finished 2nd and we had our first individual winner of the year. Congrats t… https://t.co/3cA45nXUns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @realDonaldTrump There already is a law than only citizens can vote. Did you not see in the news th… https://t.co/oRIM9x7ZIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was just away at college a couple hundred miles away. I was shocked. And still to this day feel guilty even tho… https://t.co/8VyXRIYeMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Sending my prayers to you, Alex🙏 As you fight this ...we are thinking of you! God Bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[The speaker was Dr. David Stovall from @thisisUIC, who studies the influence of race in #urbaneducation,… https://t.co/Sz66w5DUp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[temperature down 7°F -&gt; -6°F humidity up 42% -&gt; 70% wind 13mph -&gt; 10mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 I thank God every day, that I wasn’t born in the early hard times our country has faced.  And these imbec… https://t.co/6wCNCBYXiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Feels 🍃🌿☘️ #foxyandwinston #customletterpressinvitations  #lillyofthevalley @ Hillsdale , New York https://t.co/smnRZ9WIFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakaylinEfird Why don’t y’all make it clear that we ain’t getting nun when we pull up so we can stay where we at🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itssmeeashh @1991_chanel Damn. Could’ve put a down payment on a house for your child but nope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyKinLA @Lisa_M_Borders @TIMESUPNOW She is a stand up person and there’s no reason to drag her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser @joebidden_thc What about this Uncle Joe? https://t.co/xZUtLIn85O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lenicia4 @KrysWyll @GardendaleES @NancyOrtiz94 @mymustangpride1 @RebMendoza06 The whole campus looked amazing! The… https://t.co/DAJ71ygc6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone that uses logic and has a moral compass can not continue to follow Dems down their dangerous road.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows well the Dems are what soccer moms voted in.  Now they have to pay the price.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne I never expected to see tough ass Erika fan girl out so much to @DENISE_RICHARDS !!!! 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinmhale @realDonaldTrump Still no proof or evidence of Russian collusion huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seriously sitting at my computer crying right now because I’m so overwhelmed with work. Lmao.   Why am I such a fucking crybaby 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juice0nthel00se yo i swear if that happened at a party i was as i would’ve been the shit outta everyone!!! like wt… https://t.co/ZS7WNQY466]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN BORDERS WILL PUT US SHOULDER TO SHOULDER WITH THESE PEOPLE IN JUST A FEW SHORT YEARS! AMERICA CAN NOT AND WILL… https://t.co/lL2kFQtUdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta vez, sí, totalmente de acuerdo.  #AbortoLegal #PorElDerechoaDecidirNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@prep45sports we’re getting a “standby” screen on all devices- please don’t let us miss too much of the… https://t.co/E5bTLmUAt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Pray for Peace It’s time to act on. Dear mates, pull up your Attack Mode. #ItsShowtime  #KashmirTerrorAttack… https://t.co/7XmY64Vr2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk My husband @qbcoach18 said this from day one. Staged... unfuckingbelievable]]></document><document><![CDATA[all my life You have been faithful, &amp; all my life You have been so so good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enixamyram Why Yes...Yes they are PRECIOUS...🐰🏹💜 https://t.co/PVkWjidH5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aswinn @davidmweissman Not Chinese, but try adding a GENEROUS amount of curry powder to your chicken salad. You'll be hooked. Also nuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just listed off all the places we'd go for people that tour &amp; ashley said "is there a 50 states test coming up"💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo pido la VOLUNTAD de Dios en la vida de un amigo que hoy lucha contra el cáncer 🙌🏼🙏🏼 Quiero que tú Dios le des… https://t.co/t8AlckeZZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianRSmithSr @SueThotz @MsFarinas #TruTalkEdu https://t.co/6qgpqm0QJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[99. В школу юные лондонцы идут в 4 года. Если дети живут дальше 1,6 км от школы, их возят автобусы. Те, кто живёт б… https://t.co/6Og2OPxUky]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Friday &amp; #Saturday nights at #VMC #Hollywood 🔥🔊🔥 https://t.co/9ypDih7mTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[He just lost the black voters, they love to grill as much as I do, and they ain’t got no asparagus and carrots on t… https://t.co/ZwbFhs8UnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romeh @jesstucker Can we all seriously go tomorrow, at like 3pm? LOOK AT THESE TREATS! https://t.co/GEKuDOqmpG https://t.co/UIuJAzhOmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normal offseason NFL stories.   But C'mon @Silkysims17: it's time for this dusty tree to come down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go boys!!! 💚💛⚾️〽️ #manoguebaseball #minernation #20ismyfavoriteplayer #boymom #ilovemyboys @ Coronado High Sc… https://t.co/3pU28KhL24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Momoa and Lisa Bonet are total #couplesgoals. One of my favorite couples at the #Oscars. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Remember OBama put them in cages not President Trump! If their parents hadn’t brought t… https://t.co/l0JW5l8ipJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[15° and snowing, these people had to leave their apartment building overnight in Kalamazoo while a fire burned insi… https://t.co/7qRdZHJBCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHOBH really having a hard time watching this season. Most of these women are so outta touch with the real world a… https://t.co/NwW9bbEb81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Sometimes a hands on experience is a great way to learn ! You can really see what it was like ! Gain a better… https://t.co/krTdksBNcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[THURSDAY AT 5: If you looked at Atlanta’s skyline recently you may have noticed something missing -- smog. Why clea… https://t.co/VjZTjGPPmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: zzzz  Brain (at 3 a.m.): OMG YOU FORGOT TO TAKE ALL OF THAT SODA OUTTA THE WORK FREEZER 12 HOURS AGO  Me: https://t.co/LUvGvzlti1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoopPsyduck Smh I’m sorry that really does suck, it’s for someone I know smh 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanHughes which it’s not to say your intentions were negative. the way that I construed it as an Indian who has… https://t.co/PLEN6ydz2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raising_3 Is different now. No more just going to the exits. Have you been there a lot with your kids? My son used… https://t.co/r4q2415L1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF U NOT IN MIAMI THEN DONT CALL ME ALL WEEK IM DEADASS DONT TEXT ME NOTHING 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, gossiping: he was in my apartment and looking around and telling me how much he loves art and design and aesthe… https://t.co/pDA1vUuDMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaScottLO @ateacher97 Proves that the measure of a man is class and how he treats others. @RobertCraft #Patriots is a classless asshole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope not doing this journey with anyone else 😍😘 @eva_salonem #bossesonamission 💪Experiencing and meeting amazing pe… https://t.co/dgqcfwopt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland police ask for help finding driver in hit-and-run.  @WGME   https://t.co/bK234cEbJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti My mom used to say “a constant drop of water wears away the hardest stone”. Drip, drip, drip. 💧]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve probably called some very nice people some very terrible names amidst my road rage fits]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a special idea for the last part of the series, hoping to do it tomorrow, can’t wait to finish and share the… https://t.co/mGfub7fj5z]]></document></documents></author>