<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Black leopard confirmed in Africa for first time in 100 years https://t.co/O3unztHQMB via @NatGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please stay home if u can it's so bad out took my daughter 3 hours to get to my place on a regular day its half hou… https://t.co/zGMEkWruSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I wanted was karaoke 🎤 for my bday. #temetiste #arielcamacho #comoteexteaño #leodan 🦁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sillywithsad My mom's mac and cheese.  She'd make a big, deep casserole dish of it and we'd eat it for days. Same with her goulash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JR8Ramirez @NBCManifest WTFFFFFF is what I thought about your finale!!!! 🤦🏻‍♀️😳☄️🤭😰😢tell ussssssssssss. I think yo… https://t.co/poRKf3gqEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verittaholloway @thomaskaine5 I've finally learned to do that. It was a long time coming, but I have. Thanks for the support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin NEVER BE SILENT EXPOSE EXPOSE EXPOSE EXPOSE EXPOSE EXPOSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Democrats gave us the ACA that is not affordable they knew it so they made it to where you got it or you p… https://t.co/iQrgmu1BcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful testimony! Beautiful life well spent!! So grateful for all his encouraging messages while he traveled thi… https://t.co/ols44t84IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamLaceyChabert It sounds perfect! #LoveRomanceandChocolate  @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Manchin should quit being a dem as he has too much good in him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan White folks took the family to lynchings. Had a picnic spread and beers all around. This is same old, s… https://t.co/af4sjhG2Ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ They are our future...we’re very lucky they’re on our side. They’re beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running towards the weekend like 🏃‍♀️ @ San Diego, California https://t.co/KVG5rSuAO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how a leader inspires. @grendelrick, you crushed it. #AF measures are artificial constructs..#oklaed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_Luvs_Us @1madwoman1962 @karenslinn43 @MelindaYoe @Shirley82829043 @merabethjames @11syoung @welsh_lisa2… https://t.co/gojI2GQwlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's kick this week off right!!! 🎉🔥🎶 Message me get ony VIP guest list tonight! 😉  2 Clubs under one roof! 🍷Full B… https://t.co/NFUhzXVyV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrankeyOldFart @RealMuckmaker These eyes do not look human do they? because they are not, they are faux human. Alien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Normand's current hour should be recorded for a @NetflixIsAJoke special, including this bit that happened afte… https://t.co/3CNhmOM5CC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickSherman @MrEchs @cjtype @ChristopherSlye @kioskfonts @ken_lunde It’s clever but the more I think about it I’m… https://t.co/I25iJ538zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danng, Home Depot had Chris Jericho sitting around waiting with his tool belt on 🔧👷🏽‍♂️  He was just tryin to build… https://t.co/cBxKfVe0CH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellarae tbt when the guy at whatcom started speaking to me in Japanese (White guy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle @SOMissouri Good thing #k9Lor didn't mistake you for a bad guy! Good job freezing your tookus off… https://t.co/oDajemLrnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been a fan of @SnyderAmberley , and Walk. Ride. Rodeo. Is such an amazing and inspirational movie!!😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t lose an hour of sleep because i when to sleep after the time changed 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malik Frazier wants to be your King! This week, he’s going to show you #aXUPerspective on what Xavier could be! Vot… https://t.co/KYRPc2WyKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[if there’s anything i’ve learned about older people it’s that they always zoom in when they are taking a picture. i… https://t.co/eHCb5sWfbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we near the HUGELY anticipated viccosmeticsco launch, my excitement is growing even more everyday. Here is a lit… https://t.co/kRi7CNRVbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas_Dexter Ohhh showing your stuff before you know you are the cock of the party!  I wish young girls adopted this confidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanGn @PollyPapaya @lambert_lynda @Mayo4Mz @exurbanmermaid @lynneski @sunsong23 @Texas_Dexter @patbennettaz… https://t.co/9vgl8sbZr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Capital Ring Walk together, all 88 miles), we’d bought a house, spent a year working on it, I taught art in my… https://t.co/rRDEb7osJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my website https://t.co/JZ0L7mmHC6. It has every property for sale and is updated every five minutes by t… https://t.co/Ih3gYQpNbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[if my mind could stop racing about stupid shit so i could sleep, that would be great 😪😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me 20 mins to take out my contacts... lmao fuck being blind honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Mulaney on SNL he sucks not impressed with his presentation not funny no wonder he doesn’t have a show… https://t.co/u57aXWcHHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseAddy @KeithUrban @PostMalone 30 years from now, music trivia snobs will probably be able to summon holographs… https://t.co/uv4vO7rbXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 They’re pointing this crap at a 5 year old. Rude/inappropriate comments are already being deleted and… https://t.co/uhKBEBNFip]]></document><document><![CDATA[AK will take blankets and make whole ass palettes on the floor ... this dog is crazy 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Spends 30 minutes perusing iTunes, Hulu, Netflix and Amazon*… https://t.co/q40fsU15LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AOC sustainability ideas to end world hunger. @SteveDoocy @TheDemocrats @SpeakerPelosi @DNC @DonaldJTrumpJr… https://t.co/5m1jJY5NqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 Good morning Viviane my friend 😘💙😘 https://t.co/7pR8q5xSca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msjcrx sis at this point I just be straight up lying, I'm just trying to make them buy the product hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I near the three-month mark for the publication of my historical novel 'The Blue,' I would love to share the mom… https://t.co/oKGtQPWJsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sinfrontera7 No amigo en La Paz no, pero si en estos lugares mira 😥 https://t.co/cG5nnI34T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis Happy birthday, Mr. Lewis! Thank you for teaching us about good trouble. May we always follow your example.]]></document><document><![CDATA[humanbloommusic LIVE tonight beatkitchenbar. Tickets available at the door! #livemusic #soul #randb #jazz #pop… https://t.co/fRTsBMii6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally choked at my cello recital today, but I had fun anyway. Thank emmalemons and @teamalvesbjj for supporting… https://t.co/1IApgRR2FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC11_WTVD school bus accident , Jones Sausage Rd. https://t.co/CBJE8lktHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BergenJohn211 He's ok. Waiting on a 💩💩💩 to happen to see if there's a blockage or not. Not sure we will go home tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owlinkdesign If you don’t mind me asking, where is this? I’ve been looking for botanical prints just like those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTSArmyMomMD1 @BTS_twt Heaven forbid I do real life https://t.co/FNJwKmlRaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smokin’ Mary introduces our new baby ‘Green with Envy’ we’ll call her Envy for short. She’s beautiful! Green tomato… https://t.co/KXsC3HzjQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solis Mammography believes that providing peace of mind through exceptional breast health care creates balance for… https://t.co/dtQCIxX7pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bright, frosty Family Day 2019 🇨🇦 #AdoptDontShop  #TorontoDogs @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/jxfmhCuKNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Yapkowitz @howardmegdal @JosephZucker Check the Storm shop, https://t.co/W1CMvbdpgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is in @Cheesecake in #TysonsGalleria #Virginia 🇺🇸 https://t.co/E6fOtz5f9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still listening to this song #TheGreatestShowman #ZacEfron #HughJackman #Zendaya #KealaSettle #Thegreatestshow https://t.co/n7KzXRKMe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with @LaurenSato from @theriveterco at today’s International Women’s Day networking luncheon in… https://t.co/Lq5TBd2tGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you KISS....great show as usual. @Ishippedmyself https://t.co/sKm4aZM2Im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Nice sentiment but not your words.  Too many big words for you, correct grammar, correct spelling,… https://t.co/spObwqZXCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why because their bodies belong to them at that age and picking on other girls and women isn't just criminal it can… https://t.co/1S60iaxRAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiogenesLamp0 @AndrewCMcCarthy @NRO Ask Michael Reagan yourself. He is here on Twitter. Easy to find]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Came out here too see what the fool is tweeting today!!! And here you go!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samuelmchu @JamieCSullivan We have a dinner at the same time for our members, but we’ll have to catch up later!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No longer team Cassie. She appears to be a mean girl and i'm not with that.  #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoASolis Buenos días ídolo🙋feliz sábado!!🙌 te mando un abrazote hasta dónde estés🙅🙅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristabell Adventure boy!! Donut is the jerk in our household. Bilbo gets feisty for like 3 minutes then gives up and snuggles 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY #VALENTINESDAY everyone! . ❤️ Today, know that you are so valued and loved.  . ❤️ Your worth is not dependent… https://t.co/0x7RL5B4wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 My 66 mustang with pony leather interior red paint in black interior 🖤 that car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Btw, it is good hygiene for systems if you  occasionally pick a weird shape on a dashboard, bite down,, and *do not… https://t.co/5YejxLM5ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a greatime catching up with old friends and seeing some amazing wrestling.  S/O coach Blackburn,Birden,  Huffma… https://t.co/J3HAnTfMWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double posting because today is also Victoria Day! Happy of happiest birthdays to my best friend in the entire worl… https://t.co/roVR4fxu6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my son if he knew Momo and showed him a pic and he said it was @razalasm_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGBecerra I am trying to get the Pentagon to move positively for American foreign policy. Redevelopment and Intell… https://t.co/B2eT4OAyy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS I'd love to win your phone! I should win because I'm a loyal T-mobile customer! 😉🎉✊👏🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday and time for a cocktail...with a cause! 100% of proceeds from Fashion Stars for a cause cocktail goes straig… https://t.co/pIgTBs8xWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @TBN @DickMorrisTweet This is absolutely RIDICULOUS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently dying inside because I left my headphones at homeeeeeeee....... i’m the worst!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You,yes you!Whoever s reading this.u may ignore or read the words in this image without understanding,but I tell yo… https://t.co/zECgWbOUPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing thecool3rdgradeteacher ...#motivationmonday #teachermotivation #teacherfollowteachers… https://t.co/lfWc0NdAQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oq5zXujLjn I absolutely love this idea, leave these photos and love to think these two strangers got t… https://t.co/6arI2Qj0Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to #Win @GeorgeStrait tickets. You should too! https://t.co/4UbjsjVwXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emprcelia @HYFRitsJimmy @AJA_Cortes How is it bad that it exists?! Women have always been trying to better themsel… https://t.co/igjbrwMt6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF car concert 😎🤘🏻   #tgif #bonjovi #slipperywhenwet #carconcert @ Binghamton, New York https://t.co/iIVLGLO8g8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scotty Mccreery.....the whole reason I bought these #Opry tickets!!!! @opry @ Grand Ole Opry https://t.co/lRQk1S2l14]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never felt more support after speaking out about  something so personal like  #ivf Happy #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R_Brauninger @ACFresh21 Way to go and achieve those dreams!  Proud I got to see you play hard at Texas A&amp;M!👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Eights aren’t afraid to feel—they’re afraid their feelings will betray them.” JUST DRAG ME NEXT TIME OK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideHustleWino @joneill55 @thatsVeryKari @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123 @CaththeWineLady @SteveKubota @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/ZM5W2BvHBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, politics don’t belong in the exam room. Your latest attack on Title X forces health care centers… https://t.co/sobt0tZldc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sleeping perfectly fine till my dad woke me up w/a phone call now I can’t go back to sleep 😩 #whyamilikethis]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Baldwin, "Letter from a Region in My Mind" (1962)  https://t.co/MtvKkAzVmf https://t.co/JmIR4JkAYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: BUB, NO THE FUCK NOT will I buy paper plates https://t.co/DJhe82RcK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sloantopia @shannongailmc @canadiandaws83 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4… https://t.co/iq9gTRYmZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alejandro León Maal  #Miami Capturan en el aeropuerto internacional de Miami al piloto de Tareck El Aissami, Alejan… https://t.co/CkqDpwRpaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turn on your TV at 3:45 a.m. ask yourself what the f*** am I watching cuz there isn't actually anything on anymore… https://t.co/hff3loAtks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 28th  The moon is 32% waning in the sign of Capricorn. Geomagnetic storm is over this morning. Si… https://t.co/CJ226Wjb2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WomenForTrump4 You misunderstood as I never said that I ate it nor would I. I certainly don't want to see any animal butchered either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics All I care about is who can beat trump or any GOP candidate if trump is in jail --which he should be-- by 2020!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#crafts #painting #canvaspainting #acrylicpainting #itried #shakyhands @ Swain Casa dolce casa https://t.co/gbzHzhUnuI]]></document></documents></author>