<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You know who wasn't at the 2016 Trump Tower meeting? Hillary! #LockThemAllUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayla and I are always having conversations through text message, Snapchat, and a group chat at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah @GayleKing @CBSThisMorning I ♥️ @GayleKing. @CBSThisMorning we want to see the whole thing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redeye_joe @DanielLMcAdams They are going to use his resistance to the aid trucks to continue their coup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something Unknown has just Appeared in the Sky of Mexico ... And the Vol... https://t.co/rHLSZ88Yz4 via @YouTube 🦜🦜🦜🦜🦜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me also clarify that I was talking about y’alls dream agency. It was never mine but people always try to get in… https://t.co/w7FIiGslbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @cangelos44: Post covers of 10 albums that make up a soundtrack of my life: no expla… https://t.co/wzh1MKU11w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to start looking at how ima want bebes Bautizo &amp; his first birthday to be like 🤭🥰🥰🥰👶🏻👣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProjectBetterUS That is a well known anti-Semitic trope. That is what anti-Semitic people have been saying for yea… https://t.co/AkI5HIvbmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maciehalderman_ set her alarm to play Mo Bamba in the morning...   watch out world 😂🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on down and get into the swing of things and walk out with a new Samsung tablet and watch combo! #NERULES… https://t.co/dJ09BAlUoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlobrien25 @wwilcox2 @Recker_LMS @troyschools @jlobrien25 thank you for YOUR leadership (and for being the only hu… https://t.co/i2K5YxlEUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you alternate between .tde and .hyper files? (Demo only showed .tde)  Where are the extracts placed on the serv… https://t.co/ZfqFcyfzwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewKungFuKenny @PGutierrezESPN Happy Birthday to both of you RIP Abraham Lincoln.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotionally exhausted, the ginger case worker crawls to her last day of work with focus on her only goal: the weekend. 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castleberry is not named in the indictment. County Prosecutor says her case will be in front of a grand jury soon.… https://t.co/BQGtuJbLuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikoCrystalBall @BFers10 @gaycrouton @fragilevixenfic I know right!!! What the fuck, Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone is ever asking you to send them nudes, this is what you should send 😘 #nudeglam #nudemakeup  . Eyes:… https://t.co/yIZag5C2ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaJaxx @John99Randle Good gracious Jaxx. What the hell-you just can not I see that..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats are losers. They mess with non issues and everything else around them burns to the ground....so to speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Oh, oops, reread it. Ok, North Korea where I think he would try Kim's patience quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mass production and Microcontroller advance to State for TSA.  #ptn @joeypineda99 @briscoe_eagles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I would meet the President and yell at him for hours non-stop. That would make me happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elijahsemaj_ My Daisy Scout is selling online. https://t.co/4IRnWBVrP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are the pro-lifers oh okay y’all real silent know huh snowflakes ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thank you to @angiowoman for your leadership locally and internationally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptbrasil @pucca11112005 @Haddad_Fernando @gleisi @DeputadoFederal povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[not thinking it through, i did front squat, back squat, &amp; dead lift today... my legs are going to be deceased. pray for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodneyDavis @HouseGOP Of Course Like Your god REPUBLICANS ARE SCARED OF "You" all are "LIARS"and Scared to death k… https://t.co/BF9UQcgVID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ovo10241 Think about yourself being born every day. It's like we are all born each day. It's crazy. I feel like I… https://t.co/nnZAQprTRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never know if I should go to the hospital or to sleep to see what helps me feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Estate Career Seminar....Tuesday, February 19th 6:00pm Sharp.. Become A Realtor In Two Months! Learn how to ha… https://t.co/KGvW8uz7MG]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bf hasn’t even texted to make sure I’m alive since I left the house #nodinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom sent me a package with nothing but sweetarts bc I told her I was craving them the other day. I love her so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired even MORE to continue living my best life after watching this @ThisFreeLife video. ✨ Who wants to join me?… https://t.co/BIFASrN9sA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got about 1 hour of sleep hehe cool wow can’t wait to pass out at work today]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hyacinth &amp; shelf #hypnotique by @sdekouadio #canon #art #artist #artistic #artwork #beautiful #beauty #Spring… https://t.co/11XMI5D68w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t tell me to believe in myself when you don’t even see your own worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude Montana is so freaking cold, it froze the gel in my temperpedic mattress in my sleeper. I have one spot where… https://t.co/uHBsRoqBjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night I stayed up until 2 am learning busta rhymes verse on look at me now, idk where that’s going to get me i… https://t.co/7BWIR3S4SI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thorntonsa I used this one, but there are a ton of recipes online. Most are pretty similar.   https://t.co/eWKGMkmW2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBlkshrt Will Kim give you another giant envelope proclaiming his love to the biggest moron in US history? https://t.co/cVxuEaRK3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker No doubt on my mind. Not only does Trump work on making all Putin's foreign policy dreams come true… https://t.co/JOlIONCzfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaraEAnderson @502eire @dloehr Yeah, I never had any desire to see him live b/c I heard such crappy things about h… https://t.co/19dAFDQAJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grab your ☕ and join us for @KarenMintonWSB last day 😢 https://t.co/iScpaqXMdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see a current photo of someone I "talked to" and it didn't work out or lead to anything, and they've *change… https://t.co/CU7SW1muTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADHUS_FAUHS's #nationalhonorsociety did a lesson on friendship with 1st and 2nd grade after-care students where we… https://t.co/nDal0grB5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatsleft1226 @Love_Cookin @HalloweenBlogs @rachelweinerwp https://t.co/4QhorxrhNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoniManivong Shows how much I payed attention to the video. Lol! I was too busy listening to the awesome sound!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ab*sive toronto men take up one artistic trait and think their past actions are excused and they’re now only giving back to the community]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I sleep or should I finish watching the last season of Peaky Blinders? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sensei_Indigo @nhampagnemami2 Let make a movie yeah Twists, hold you down gold slugs champion celebration strip ne… https://t.co/dq8djslksn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonSward @charlesjkenny @Morris_ScottA @vijramachandran @JustinSandefur Yes, sad but true. I’ve caught Japan’s sta… https://t.co/L8g7Bqw4tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoannaSinn @anjadeclercq How could they report those scales? Maybe somewhere else they mentioned the HC? What’s th… https://t.co/KLaDWgpl0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj I do remember being able to Vote for a President the year I turned 18...some people had to wait 4 more yea… https://t.co/1nYZdEZH7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 IN 5 TEENS VAPING: Newly released data from the FDA shows teen vaping is increasing at alarming rates. Those tren… https://t.co/LNSmxOhqWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf wrong with y’all? Like really. The edge piece really hits and y’all lack taste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss and I snuck White Claws into our coworkers 4 year old birthday party. It has now been confirmed I will be t… https://t.co/O6InzcSaTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve known my friends for about 6 months now, but I truly feel like I’ve known them my whole life. They’ve seen me… https://t.co/PzQsH5AbOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[luke combs &amp; tim mcgraw are true country kings, love rodeo szn the mostest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what!? 50% off SALE has been extended through this Sunday, tell your girlfriends how much you love our Luxury… https://t.co/TpUDTc1vOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most guys be like , “I can do that to her, but she can’t do that to me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell when something applies to a person. They go so hard to defend it and you don’t even be referring to them 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlatypusAdvent1 Fantastic!! Please keep me in the loop. I would love to showcase it when you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton @MikeOkuda It's ok, Anne. You don't need them to read your book anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCDallasMom2 we did that when the apologizer in chief was in office, so I guess he was supposed to go over and be… https://t.co/6y3KVzE2Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GH_obsession @maddow I feel the same way. None of the candidates excite or inspire me. And, none of them are even… https://t.co/4LtJNnw9SO]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the personal wardrobe of Gloria Swanson and Designed by an unknown designer. Now on view until March 10, 2019.… https://t.co/cyJ1I0rnnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My meditation window...20 minutes of stillness before the chaos of the morning hits #mcwreach @ Milwaukee, Wisconsin https://t.co/vOsg6pjTqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman even if you did, they'd be all "SO sorry for your poor heathenish children." so don't worry about it, Sarah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Oh yes let’s believe The NY Times who have proven they back democrats and the… https://t.co/quEJNlHucv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi everyone - sorry I’m a bit late! I’m Kelsey, a tech integrator in Richmond, VA! #edtechchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[When do we find out about vip @MaddieandTae ?? I can’t wait to get the biggest hug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toppgunn2323 @seanhannity Your an asshole.who said anything about Hispanics.go ahead asshole who?that lying piece… https://t.co/g7VvfGnqRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaReginaa @Education4Libs It’s auto correct but I’m glad you’re a nice person... Live in your fantasy world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Signed checks from the Oval Office to pay off a porn star are concrete evidence of violating the l… https://t.co/qq2ErF7q4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop listening to fucking sad music when I’m sad it’s not helping]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only have 4 days of work this week (because of #iubase on Friday!!) and I’m sure it’s about to be the slowest week in history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris’ team is working hard...I get like 5 emails a day from her 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see it now:  me in 10 years - juggling my career, kids, marriage, and home but STILL feeling like I’m not doing enough 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@culturaobscura @TheUncorkedLib @perthtravelers @LGSomewhereMcK @TravelBugsWorld @travelpantspair @carpediemeire… https://t.co/mzj2zzjtLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to the “Hospital-based Innovation Initiatives” panel.  Interesting hearing about what is happening in Ont… https://t.co/rgjRl6FyrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod If republicans had actually given oversight, Democrats wouldn't have to investigate so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 @lexifiercegreen Well as long as you retire here in Door County Wisconsin is for it!!  I'll lay a be… https://t.co/mJEWJjmi7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a Freebandz and radio/club DJ......INVEST IN YOURSELF  DM ME IF YOUR SERIOUS   I do 7 parties a week.... Rel… https://t.co/fnZNQu3cMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHurst @realDonaldTrump I will tweet in all caps so some people will believe my lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep an open mind! Lots of good choices!  I like @amyklobuchar  I like @SenWarren   Looking for experience in inter… https://t.co/xGsytDxuO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow The Dems/Pelosi have become the party of anti national security with a  controlling censorship age… https://t.co/1sDRGCS3dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieWGME @WGME I now have this stuck in my head 😂 https://t.co/ODvVRW6qBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The longer I spend away from this place the more I’m reminded of how much I love it https://t.co/GmDOScnkFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lizzy,  Focus on government corruption and leave us alone. Clean up your own mess in DC and your own personal fraud… https://t.co/hoK9xUGeCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikel_Jollett They should have taken him out 2 years ago. He never should have been allowed to be president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on #art to dry @ Tower District, Fresno https://t.co/AbQlozTUlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jesus #love #Bible #verseoftheday #God #christian #bibleverse #inspiration #verse #grace #hope #arkansas #b #read… https://t.co/Oab8V7ZjHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Neill5 But we beat y’all😂 and didn’t u just come from Southport like bro quit talking to me u mad cause u look goofy squating 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @TedCruz: As a US citizen, I demand to know why your campaign gave US voter data to a guy in Russia named Yaro… https://t.co/LfZ7BvIFlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice warm up today. It will feel almost like summer😎 https://t.co/U9psUxz1Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNicoleArcy welcome to @DrPol @natgeowild. Thoroughly enjoyed you tonight! @DrEmilyThomas Dr Brenda a great addition!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't believe for ONE moment! #MAGA supporters don't approve of nooses; But, I've HEARD the DEMS have a Long HISTO… https://t.co/PZjluxUgY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intheMatrixxx @realDonaldTrump LORD, BLESS our nation. We repent for our sins &amp; are coming back to you in Jesus' Name. Amen.]]></document></documents></author>