<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@k_joly4 @MeehanCarolAnne How many times do we see these guys driving around in plows when there is no snow? No won… https://t.co/Tjcr98Dmwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recieved my #freshfictionbox today and it was in a green box which was super spring like - super excited for 2 of t… https://t.co/UKQJXtZgRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can always tell when someone is intentionally trying to show out.  TIP:  Watch and listen to where and how comm… https://t.co/HdAVCUqShm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanO_Appleseed @Septembers_Song @corneliagracchi @SbredsFarm He relaxed yesterday with 🍷with the next door neighb… https://t.co/NDzmWX70FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabrinaAnnLynn’s speech before prfct in nj about how we’ve grown w/her, have inside jokes with her, how she knows… https://t.co/XO15AfgDIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that’s left to finish is this environmental cast study paper that’s due in March. It’s great when you don’t pro… https://t.co/XNYAwEYEkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[angel fell asleep too late in the evening again and it’s gonna be a nap and she’s gonna wake up at like midnight pi… https://t.co/9mxEwBfEYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nourefidel Alas!!🙋🙋 Absolutely true!..and poignant!🐦🌐 https://t.co/rstxbyqDm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevedischiavi Love it. That's one place I've never been and always wanted to go. I love jazz, and I bet the city… https://t.co/3hj5W012Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey86437753 @TrinityResists @StormResist @B52Malmet @Augustus709 @AryaResists @Sky_Lee_1 @1Jedi_Rey… https://t.co/zQyUD18GJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraGabriel_ Omg! I did not know this. Wishing her a speedy recovery Xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[That “ forgive to heal “ phrase is bs to me because it’s situations I’ve grown and healed from and I’ll never in my… https://t.co/SzNUArxPk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What are you mad about today?”  It’s 2019 and Olie Kolzig and Peter Bondra’s numbers still aren’t hanging from the… https://t.co/XQy7xXLJJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishrygirl Same reason one twin gets cancer and the other one doesn't... genetics are trippy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GYMObrad We found @YouTube to be very helpful to communicate with our grandparents raising grandkids in our middle… https://t.co/xPkXW2ow08]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momma and daughter night! Seeing Steve Martin &amp; Martin Short @ Old National Events Plaza https://t.co/zcP2KHuzcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ @blackfuel @shannonleto #blackfuel #shannonleto #coffee #thevictorian #santamonica #echelon @ Black Fuel at the… https://t.co/LyQXsVfZMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweeting this poem to my daughter @annaecarmack and her @TuftsMedSchool Maine Track Friends who are all PGY1s - t… https://t.co/xWEU2lyjnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss would fire me so fast if I put this kind of advertisement in west chester 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't go to the gym but I shoveled for 3 hours. Helped my neighbor  Mrs. Revitt (90yrsold) with snow removal too… https://t.co/ZphJ2dz07Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadeserves_ The birthday fit only for a queen! Happy birthday muffin!!💘✨🎉ily!!!😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanyaBones @IanBallinger925 @Tebtunis @xan_desanctis If it passed why does it have to be voted on again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zagaholicpod @rloyola @UnitedWeZag @campbelleric @ZagMBB @LissaT1818 Cracks me up that this is the debate of the e… https://t.co/pUqU3iWhPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunny @RepMarkMeadows But waaaaaait a minute!! He has a niece and nephew that are bla...🤔 :sigh: never mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JReinerMD Here in the foothills of the Adirondacks in upstate NY, we see it about every storm. Enough so, we made a flyer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police Harassment at CVS 78th Halsted Chicago, IL next to large new Policestation  Senior citizens and disabled peo… https://t.co/KEcfUwUEMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abel_jennifer @thisismrhopper @Quizalizeapp That’s what I thought, password protect]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving to Los Angeles during a rain ☔️ storm ⛈ is practically suicidal. But worth it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dog rolled on the phone and suddenly I was very confused at what was playing on my phone...i can watch @fbhw we… https://t.co/VKgpBJLyUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever woke yourself up crying in your sleep? The dream was so vivid, it’s creepy 😭😨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forget how serious and invested i was with some people like i let u into my life and was vulnerable like ew f u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamBurris @WhoWeNation @WFINradio @CBSSports Good job Adam! I was listening. Too bad it wasn’t a better game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgainstTheOdds_ The one I went on went last April went to St. Lucia, St. Thomas, St. Kitts, St. Marteen, and Barba… https://t.co/JZnPaxarNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ @JayneQPatriot At Least Arizona has a HEART For Our Unborn Babies!! Thank You!! 💞💞❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my HIVE family! To the fresh and the firsts. You guys bring so much joy and knowledge. We all hold so many dif… https://t.co/7t5g754hjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A tired refrain.  Have heard it all before.  I can't express how tired I am of your overhyped BS.… https://t.co/HTcTGzxCCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A itirjf f ro. Copied c o t to ofmc cdloskar t I am pr f d and rcthe comeback was good dc https://t.co/b1gDADSXdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pumping myself up so hard for this concert listening to “Philadelphia Freedom” right now... if I don’t get the… https://t.co/ZFKsLRFzwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how people get into relationships so quickly. I’m 24 and have been in 3 relationships. And there was l… https://t.co/Hjw8gVYNWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fans...are you aware of the #texashotwives?? Somehow the hottest naughty wives on Twitter  all live within a few ho… https://t.co/pgRN9jHv1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t blow like it’s 4/20 everyday , but still manage to be productive we can’t be cool tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 7th birthday to our Buckeye❤️Let’s go nuts!!! https://t.co/bapmmSkWlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Oh for Christ's sake. Sounds like you are becoming one of the stupid white guys who bathe in victimhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise during the time the #washington #monument was in scaffold while being repaired. #photography  #photographer… https://t.co/l4ZYs5sjYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slatimer76 @sagebrushranch That would be a ton of fun! I had a blast as well. I hadn’t been in years. 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Communist_Dog @cspanwj @StevenStromberg I got $1,200 tax deduction from 2005-2009 for buying my Hybrid...Had to take it in increments]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shouldn’t be a problem, you just gotta accept what comes with them period.. anybody weird if they say yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AJRyan I &amp; my hubby voted for you. Keep it moving brother. You are a Blessing 🙏🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMHS_ASB Good luck Fellas!!! The Mathis Family is cheering you on from afar. ♥️AMHS♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have soooo much work to do once I get home, I have new hair dropping. Everybody finna be cappin with this curly hair 🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herbivore_club Every day a customer walks in and tells me I look fantastic. I feel great. Look better and people around me are changing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tangible information, ready relatable and easy to understand.  The tropics broaden, the tundra shrinks and we in Bo… https://t.co/5W0pONlD6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost everytime mu watch mi movie diri sa balay ky mka sleep najud kooo. Di man ko ngani sauna oy. Sleepyhead na kaayo ko rn😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenKling @chrislhayes @staceyabrams You have to scroll down a bit to find it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CobTheOne @SonySantaMonica No joke, @itsrobdavis @CheetoBandeeto @DaNightTrain @devilpie @illermil @marcnotmark KI… https://t.co/0BsuIMggu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamRubiDilaik @RubiDilaik @abigail_pande ThankU Team🥰can’t wait to watch #Saumya exciting adventurous Journey ton… https://t.co/hYwLb1BBQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoMars your song Please Me w Cardi B is great and all, but can you please do a version by yourself?? 🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏 #Please #PleaseMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to live w hate then have at it but stop trying to rest it on my shoulders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter for a chance to win a smart TV package. https://t.co/isT6JqAjtx NO PURCH. 21 . US only. 2/1-2/28/19.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bolu_oj @I_Am_Ilemona YES GENOCIDE COMMITTED TO WIN THE ELECTION BY BUHARI AND HIS BUHARISTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azstudigital @MarthaAllan3 @outlazymedia @IvankaTrump He’s a very successful financial consultant and Liberal to b… https://t.co/IbGGuFn3ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is your favorite effective FEMALE Endorser? https://t.co/0xnlaHLmqj Let's go ADN, around the world and Maine’s… https://t.co/oTCc4ZfMaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margunson86 Glad to hear😰This is a great pic of her. Looks so sweet🤗❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockin’ Review Vol. 2 @lead4ward #BCMS @bcmsgreypups https://t.co/zeIwLLUohb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlreiner I hear from a lot of people that Donald Trump creates only the most fragrant smegma. Hints of asparagus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radulf_310 Yo tambien estoy totalmente de acuerdo en que eso no le favorece a AMLO, pero han sido mucho años en qu… https://t.co/gKBkQUzGDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reorganization requires us to develop new narrative in which the Earth is our Mother. The life giver. Greta an… https://t.co/G3T6WFPwlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spontaneous pizza date with emilyprumm at isolapizza in Little Italy, San Diego! 🍕❣️Feels good to have a classic ma… https://t.co/vl6au9uNPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisharihar @TPAIN I read that fast and saw @Train and thought, that’s an amazing Uber ride right there. And I’m sticking to that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get it twisted I can play this game too, how would you like it if I did the same to you 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm super proud of all these contestants who already won Pop-A-Shot back in their hometown. For all of them to come… https://t.co/DstKr8kmho]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨BIG NEWS✨ #YourMorningAlbany’s @JChapmanTV &amp; @danbazile have been named “Best Morning Team” by the readers of… https://t.co/f7KbZB4ALm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mean Gays The Montalbán #hollywood #meangays Discount Tickets: https://t.co/dIlXuCHqWv https://t.co/Vy7Gphoz9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've literally been running around New York City for work and a really important personal stuffs because I've took… https://t.co/ueeQvDpUNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DICEY63 @ROCKONOHIO @Oscars2019Live_ @buzzman888 @pinkk9lover @Trump454545 @AppSame @LVNancy @heyitsCarolyn… https://t.co/SOcfmxYYdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHol people outraged by their interpretation of language and not outraged when Palestinians are being killed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was wild🤪 I love y’all! @Alex_Runions_ @EmyleeOsborne @Daneshia3 @danni_wattss https://t.co/Rwz9lg69Fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@never2olde @OldKerry I could live on popcorn.  Just not with butter. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished getting my hair done by the beautiful Heather at Melody Eden’s Salon. Thank you ladies for always mak… https://t.co/snRndcZXc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watched Bernie at a rally with no sound he looks like a screaming Trump @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyEva_ The best! Depends of what you are looking for: healthy recipes, hair styles, organization, endless! Pin… https://t.co/qyJLmRR7aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish you could take doggy day care off of your taxes. #Theyarekidstoo #Costmorethanchildcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sick of all those red MAGA hats. Tell me when America was great? WTF does it mean: great? We don’t need to b… https://t.co/dwBC2H08Z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parham Eftekhari hosting a discussion on #supplychain #security with #ICIT Fellows @DonaldGMaclean @wsann Rob Roy a… https://t.co/DrlsOcr2n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@87lbofbees @MaryHeglar There's a lot to unpack here but I'm gonna go with... as if NOTHING happened? Really? If Ji… https://t.co/zlB7JGmlvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[STFU. ITS LIKE HATCHIMALS BUT FOR MAKEUP😍 MAMA DRAGUN WERE READY FOR IT🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but how cute is he!? @ Fort Bragg, North Carolina https://t.co/szzmygLMJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelecreations @7026saki @TN_Jeep_Girl I love this ♥️♥️♥️ You absolutely know 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA I wish she'd keep silent for the time being.  This is not helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The. GOP has lost their minds today. They hate that Cohen stopped lying. What will it take for the GOP to do their god dam jobs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANOTHER Leftist Hate Crime👇 WHEN will @TheDemocrats denounce the violent, irrational hate oozing from the steaming… https://t.co/2OLDSqF9FM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moving rendition evoked Marvin Gaye's performance 36 years ago. https://t.co/vkMgE9Wni6 # via @HuffPostEnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then I fall apart 🌮 #tacos @MauiTacos #tacotuesday #happytummy_702 https://t.co/lQJt3wGlFX https://t.co/I0Mj0D1A5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caribbean Cover Girl  Brushed in a distressed finish, vivacious pink wooden beads and discs join below the collar f… https://t.co/NlZIcQj5Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hop to it! @PEEPSBrand announces 9 new products for Easter, encourages fans to express their #PEEPSONALITY with new… https://t.co/TPi8RL9jnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Years ago my cousin slept with my husband..... This situation is worse I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the preworkout kicks in and @MAJORLAZER radio is on point! 💪🏾🏃🏾‍♀️🏋🏽‍♀️ #pandora]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought yarn for a blanket and poured a glass of wine... I think I miiiiiight be ready for @CriticalRole’s th… https://t.co/p0jrIHfjMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Timothy 4:7-8 King James Version (KJV)  7 I have fought a good fight, I have finished my course, I have kept the faith]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Omg! Do you not know what the word Planned Means??? Do you really think women want to have abortio… https://t.co/teMo9ZLbOq]]></document></documents></author>