<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Anyone checking out more than five things at self checkout is gonna catch this pipe]]></document><document><![CDATA[you right. at first i was considering coming back too. can’t eeeen do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pay no attention to this liar? I will not believe or pay attention to anything he says until proof is presen… https://t.co/GxA24duw2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be cleaning and packing and instead I’m watching flipping Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm...who do I trust more: future #HOF GM Lou Lamoriello or a portion of the #Isles fanbase ready to burn the wor… https://t.co/EoovSgz3bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each of these cars represents an avoidable auto trip that could have been taken by bus, except @trimet &amp;… https://t.co/dUzIfhipff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to make assumptions but I bet girls are jealous that guys can pee much louder because our stream start… https://t.co/9mnmw7uCrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t lie, me and my filmmaker buddy Steve Alper (to cool for the Gram), had a decent time at the FOX after party.… https://t.co/dnzqWennZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Taylor ready for the KISS concert at the @sprintcenter #kissarmy @ Sprint Center https://t.co/CQckD1gCrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may be my favorite ringer article in a while. Found myself laughing multiple times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KosherSoul Greensboro, NC has the only little southern diner I know of where the same menu has not only Neese's co… https://t.co/XrhSvyIeg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking Oscars, man! Fake hair. Bleached smiles. Fake tans. Botox. Fake tits. Nip. Tuck. Liposuction. Low-carb. Glu… https://t.co/zU3sjbEWv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A treble for Rachael Blackmore @rachaelblackmor as Smoking Gun wins the Racing TV Handicap Hurdle at #gowranpark fo… https://t.co/NgwzRaOAic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@becky_mi I got these at Target and it has pockets on both sides!  You can take the keys and the phone and be set for the day 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I Found Freelance  ESPN, SI, The Hockey News, Several NHL Teams  Found topic that I thought was relevant and/or… https://t.co/kNzqf4WP6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyENicholson What did you do? This is what happens when a conspiracy is exposed, they send in the cleanup crew https://t.co/8Ofdmx4eLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Weekend gotta work out .... #blessed @ GTR https://t.co/8NjCzalSWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing more rude than playing your music out loud in public is being too cheap to pay for it and subjecting everyone else to the Ads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And they keep finding witches! #FakePresident #LiarInChief]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! #denver #winter @ Union Station: Travel By Train https://t.co/cQexOe26Wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris There is no way on Gods green earth that Kamala H. will denounce an attack on a conser… https://t.co/PNHb9A8oPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgelao @TomFitton @JordanSchachtel @HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP They won’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump So @SenatorReid can call President @realDonaldTrump "the worst President we've ever… https://t.co/8xBIINXX5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Omarkabirvv @RubenGMA @Timbiriche_35 @BCSnoticias @HijasDeLaMx @ElCentinelaBCS @El_Universal_Mx @callodehacha… https://t.co/IMG00WLY0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarenMorris “Girl” You And Me Against The World https://t.co/3ddu2Hj491 Helen Reddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring in DC has already warmed 1.4° F since 1970 - and global #climatechange pollution continues accelerating:… https://t.co/wYVEdEUG4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewcilley Just because you and I didn’t agree with him, it doesn’t make him unintelligent. We hear everyone on my show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ENOUGH OF LIBERALS AND PROFESSIONAL POLITICIANS AND LAWYERS! TIME TO RETURN TO WE THE PEOPLE AND DEMOCRACY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the view on the centennial wheel #jconfloho @ Navy Pier https://t.co/25KfBcW4Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[#corgisofinstagram #corgilove #corgi #corgibutt #corgipuppy #corgiparty #dogsofinstagram #corgiworld #corgi_nation… https://t.co/KhpQVmV7Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGildedJester @SinBinVegas Lucky for us there are 30+ centers in the NHL that can put up 50 +/- 10 points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boy who cried antisemitism. Stop doing it when there is none, otherwise when it’s real no one will believe you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gay #gayselfie #selfiegay #gayinstagram #guys #dude #bro #gaydude #gaybro #nipplepiercings #gayboy #facialhair… https://t.co/AJSLJSkHrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 I’d drive straight there and let that teacher have a piece of my mind. The temerity!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_McGurk You consider anyone that doesn't belong to your CULT, a cultist.  What don't you like about Pelosi's p… https://t.co/9zrgMURlqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srmduke87 @Kris_Sacrebleu @AJA_Cortes My apologies.   I also meant to say to you: You are awesome, beautiful, inte… https://t.co/ikcxIcPSjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irlaelena Hola buenos días Elena, que tengas un excelente martes 😀. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Run, don’t walk, to the new #TRex exhibit at the American Museum of Natural History! @AMNH #AMNH150 https://t.co/LgBiwA2Zcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye esto se parece mucho a Sanders y Ocasio en USA y localmente a Yulin! https://t.co/M9wt004Xa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonPaulInstitut @marcorubio @SecPompeo Puppet Rubio Posts Pic of Gaddafi's Murder as Puppet Pompeo Says Maduro's D… https://t.co/gMYSxxI53v]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Long Beach: light rain, 60°F 72% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGolicJR57 @espngolic @wingoz  Will Apollo players have to pay Georgia state income taxes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new single “COLD.” is OUT NOW!!!!! GO CLICK THE LINK IN MY BIO!!!! 😱😱😱🔥🔥🔥❄️❄️❄️💔💔💔💯 #newsingle #cold #music #rap… https://t.co/VfTcwVWInv]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you thought #OtzmaYehudit was an anomaly, I just saw a campaign ad for Eli Yishai of Yachad. It read "כדי ש… https://t.co/SqOrn7FlLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dangillmor @kinsellawarren Well we know how one very senior (as in status) treated an intern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to run out of our 2014 Viognier, we have less than 2 cases left... The 2016 Cabernet Sauvignon isn't far behi… https://t.co/P6Gt20qTA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightfootForChi tells @CityClubChicago: “I will never treat the taxpayers of this city as an ATM machine with no l… https://t.co/xZQ5JcxL6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5NEWSJoe I also was there... Technology was lacking 22 years ago compared to today. Still,  accurate warnings and… https://t.co/Z1kC7j8E6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuckles152 @FunkNFantasy Yep Braves tickets when Phillies are in town. I have an inside connection with the Braves organization @c_zabow44]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't care u like my cousin i just  wish you just stop i quite fb and Instagram because u i don't why still troll… https://t.co/nDdTqKCUkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this is you odd little #MeTooMovement moment military edition. The problem is sec being reduced to recreatio… https://t.co/pn4I4XPtwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[😳😳😳😳😳😳me lo parece a mi😳😳😳😳😳o el presidente está muy lúcido😳😳😳😳😳....ahí lo dejo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breakfast #homecooking #eggs #avocado #banana #tomato #hamptons #coffee #fresh @ Northwest Harbor, New York https://t.co/6YKpl1kns3]]></document><document><![CDATA[China Grounds Entire Domestic Fleet of Boeing 737 Max Jets After Crash https://t.co/rCfP4AiPhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @NBCNews #ThisIsALie. Why did you meet privately with Putin?]]></document><document><![CDATA[She a super mint. Don't @ me yo. @ 3Mag Pubhouse https://t.co/UrdgRLcf31]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Recuerdas cuando te uniste a Twitter? ¡Yo sí! #MiAniversarioDeTwitter https://t.co/0Q04nwy0vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: need to teach Angel how to make brownies. Abby: I think, well, she is just... dumb. @10Mullen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurfeeJake Yeh!  Thought I’d check out the Inn it was that it the super 8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoastCoverage @stmartinsports @bshields0244 St. Martin BSB (3-0) 11 Moss Point 0. WP-Matthew Thompson Landon Panko… https://t.co/l2F7XKsbHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an One Tracht Mind by @chsfermentory @ Charles Towne Fermentory — https://t.co/yXaZZX0bzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a certain type of mild paranoid schizophrenia that confers an amazing ability to speak fluently, charisma… https://t.co/A5Abnh0MlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I have an Army buddy and his wife coming to visit this weekend, wifey came up a to-do list. Went to cross off an… https://t.co/XHCkdRH1eG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really sad to hear. I met him in LA when he was warming up a live studio crowd before a taping. Really funn… https://t.co/rYPlb15JZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday mood: learning to relax and not get anxious about the small things. Peaceful scenes like this help. ⠀… https://t.co/nxruLqNHki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowbieWan @ErikJLarsen Yes it does I always thought it was an awkward pose. Looking at the swipe now it’s obvious… https://t.co/9KtaXuvfeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re in the left lane &amp; not going at least 20 over then u shouldn’t be in the left lane srry I don’t make the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/Czlt3WaEg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryIGHO @Gunfluent @musajidda @Squawka @Pele Pelé also included his goals he scored in his backyard and in training.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BotryoidalSnO2 @LCFang1 @bopinion @Noahpinion Dude, maybe work on your reading comprehension before tweeting out s… https://t.co/g5Pwb7kMpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp He is a proven liar. A. Proven. Liar. This is not bias. It’s facts. FACTS. And definitely not 50% of the… https://t.co/9PoP2TTFkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survey asks community college students to detail their challenges https://t.co/VJDqz4gmu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see my Bestfriend this weekend @ItsKweenKay_ https://t.co/zrsjeKQW4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just backed the Kickstarter. I can’t wait for some foil tokens. @JoshLeeKwai @jfwong @CommandZone]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think in the grand scheme of things that charging fee for service doctors overhead fees (rent) in rural hospitals… https://t.co/MU7wwwepXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned today that there was a small period of time where Pepsi had the 6th most powerful military in the world and that makes me happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Kevin_T @SenSanders Let them run on that.I guarantee there won’t be a democrat left in office by 2022]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoiceOfOBrien Concerned Critter Committee!?  CCC!?  How are they funded anyway?  #BigTurtle?  I’m reluctant to sup… https://t.co/TbZmoWf21g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrowder @benshapiro @realDonaldTrump @QTRBlackGarrett @ashtonbirdie   This video is worth watching, the guy has a… https://t.co/hi471weBN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have cologne that’s supposed to smell like Buffalo Trace Oak Barrel Bourbon. All I smell is Cinnamon Toast Crunch...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seajay603 @LizNBntown @Mastermind7864 Uhm...I don’t think it’s supposed to be eaten alone. I’ve used in some recip… https://t.co/YJBoQWQMkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_olson420 The St Amgelo Special. They since closed. That was a great sub!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDL_R Si García se está poniendo mal necesita ayuda lo estará haciendo al propósito para que no lo juzguen por loco????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romyreiner Toasted cinnamon-raisin bread slathered with real butter -- mmmmm!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine @CoryBooker oh, now you won’t huh??? Not fitting your narrative is it now, you clown show??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Head on over to my Patreon account for sexy artistic images like this one. https://t.co/fAouMRZ3UQ #PatreonContent… https://t.co/etPAe2Rv2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJ_Sproseph I’m still so very tickled by this tweet eight hours later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWitherspoon life is good take one day at a time and make the best of it he country each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que hacer cuando el tal vez o el quizás es más fuerte que  de lo que sabes que puedes tener realmente 🤯🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should be removed from office!!!  She does not represent American values!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Apollo 11 is the antidote. All that terrible toxic masculinity at work performing miracles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Chinese New Year And God Fortune To All @bellagio - - #NoFilter #ChineseNewYear #YearOfThePig #Vegas… https://t.co/Z10LhADhFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattB_WOF @hiramboyd @CLESportPrspctv Fact... You are wrong about this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite Sheriffs Protests, New Mexico Gun Control Bill Advances https://t.co/uP1rGgqDDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep missing Rachael at Safeway.. I know when she works but I can never remember]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 @JohnCzer1 @marcorubio What do your do all day Rubio instead of fighting for gun control?Do you sit o… https://t.co/K611gIaZea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ed_wurd_ IDK is Barry is on set but talent always drinks through straw so they don’t ruin makeup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today I got 7 shiny Clamperl’s and I evolved 2 and ont 1-Huntail and 1-Gorebyss ✨✨✨✨ https://t.co/3cHlNzPA7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...forgotten or never learned the lessons of history...” || Hot take? The profundity of the Senator’s lack of self… https://t.co/YxPOj61Qqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbrowne93 @madsmorsch @madsmorsch I️ appreciate you for doing this tbh]]></document></documents></author>