<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Today in #WomensHistoryMonth, we honor Madame Frances Perkins, who on March 4, 1933, became the 1st woman to serve… https://t.co/2jY5RMZTib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Ugh. So sorry to hear that. I hope they can use the knowledge to bring her some relief. Hugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mid- sixth inning the Cats trail 6-3. Colby Kennedy will lead off for the Cats]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is lucky he is a white politician. He'll probably only get a fine. MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isabel1170 @JoAnnKennedyCAN @Legalator @ForeclosureOz @StayHomeAmerica @WFB_Fraud @musser_benson @ShannonKetcher2… https://t.co/SdXMFGLKYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are my everything! #youthband #yourlovesodeep #onedesire #toloveyouallmylife @ C3 Church On 78 https://t.co/CsR3htLWro]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ceremony honoring the unclaimed Airforce veteran, Will Melvin Shegog brought a big support from fellow veterans… https://t.co/kVwbHJ0nGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock @katsin @BostonGlobe They have force tapered my meds so far it is awful. Now they ate pushing a pain pump… https://t.co/Wo4zI3oJma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @joestornaiuolo Really.  I took it that SDNY is the o line that’s going to take Trump down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized the @GoldenKnights are undefeated in the #stoneage.  Feels kinda nice. #vegasborn https://t.co/98qBhS0pjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this great message via @StephenDDavey! https://t.co/5BXQAx4x7a How can we easily detect a false belief sy… https://t.co/MjatYwdIMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ekp My tech dream is never having to go to the bay area (except to visit friends of course)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allah SWT said:  أُولٰٓئِكَ الَّذِينَ اشْتَرَوُا الضَّلٰلَةَ بِالْهُدٰى فَمَا رَبِحَت تِّجٰرَتُهُمْ وَمَا كَانُوا… https://t.co/lMjDzUuwqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘i’m sexy and i know it’ by lmfao provided such an important message for our generation. it taught us all about sel… https://t.co/vzdOEr9xKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get the Jonas Brothers and 1D comparison. They’re both completely different groups not to mention the Jonas… https://t.co/Rxcb40vnLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person and my favorite food? Sign me up #DBBwithMyBetterHalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter @TEAMEVGA and @Newegg #LifeLikeAudio Experience Giveaway to win an EVGA NU Audio Card.  #EVGAxNewegg https://t.co/mlPBY0HG35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @Sammy_Markle @piersmorgan you never cease to amaze me with your stupidity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mental y emocionalmente ayer quede agotada, hoy 23F mi corazón está herido por todas las muertes 😢 respiro hondo y… https://t.co/rEJzxQ3KQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Happy Love Day Sexy Souls ❣️Place your hand on your heart and choose a state of being that brings your vibration… https://t.co/3v0SUJLNLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnawhistler @realDonaldTrump So you haters need to be clear— he went to Wharton Business School and got his degr… https://t.co/UBpMIwsSvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newmaniacs @mayawiley @JillWineBanks @BarbMcQuade @JoyceWhiteVance @harrylitman The judge dressed him down, good a… https://t.co/NXM2HMGQdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[King Calaway - Love The One You're With (Lyric Video) https://t.co/3LV6ON9FDH via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for letting me crash moms weekend ❤️❤️ @ Tri Delta https://t.co/xNDhELMueR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flipsbolts55 @KTLA Ohhhhh.  Ron is 1-0 versus KTLA throwing out that CB question.  People never like to talk about… https://t.co/RgBrh0qi4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[y sigo creyendo que si alguna película con Ryan Gosling y Emma Stone era merecedora de Oscar es esta]]></document><document><![CDATA[This amazing kid missed jumping over me by 1 inch. That's impressive! #FamiLee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're an embarrassment to this planet. Also, we are in the middle of a "national emergency" with… https://t.co/zdiDhGe1bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s impossible to explain how much of your brain homelessness takes up. It isn’t just the fact that you don’t hav… https://t.co/l2yKLnJprp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#brandyourself ⭐️Well, I talk about my favorite social profile all the time to my #brandingaccelerator students - a… https://t.co/InmjTc31cr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Person recommends compelling tv shows and documentaries for me to try..  Me: I think I need to rewatch all of Game… https://t.co/8GaZGnl90G]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady at work found out I was the one in charge and she looks at me and says, “Oh my, you’re so young. Like a b… https://t.co/xt7tVMkwmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshroz @MichaelCohen212 I know, and I actually dont believe any Trump supporters threatened his family either]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LetitRip It’s so easy to tear people down.  Let him have his day in court.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day 😘 . . #valentinesday2019 @ Portsmouth, New Hampshire https://t.co/pnfiCXfxVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyingRaptor_ @wildcatbrian44 @Ohneaux1 @SECNetwork @Vol_Hoops @KentuckyMBB @DickieV In??   Nothing has been prove… https://t.co/OfHcqtdJMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experience has taught me that prayer is not about what we want, but about what God has already done."In hope of eternal life " Titus 1 :]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithLondia @w_terrence @Bre63068675Judy @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett I’m wrong right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMarino the God loving man in the wheel chair has been your biggest fan for years. He is fighting cancer and con… https://t.co/Vi6ldb2uYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each and every one of this speeches tonight are stand on your feet applause worthy and then some.   So gracious, po… https://t.co/fPlfPIkrob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritAnimalUS You know if you could make it Rome, Italy any date between 4/29 and 5/9 that would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CausticTheClown I recently found out about this kratom stuff. I don't smoke (or otherwise consume) marijuana. I do… https://t.co/PwtP9pBaeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[She spent 5 minutes talking about Africa, centering the stories on herself and how she helped them. Instead of talk… https://t.co/dKHGPyxPVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Barnes &amp; Noble - @bnbuzz in Willow Grove, PA https://t.co/vZoWpI90qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brett_hargrave @RealMattCouch @paphotog Agree. Tribunal. Sentence for Treason..... Obama, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthsideMally 😂🤣 then she gone say my turn ! I’ll never let a bitch tie me down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @thatsVeryKari Nice quiet day here, hope you both enjoy yours!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can the democrats tear down the wall if they are elected? Beto said he would. Please don’t let this happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what keeps me looking youthful at 43? My chubby cheeks and my monthly period zit. #periodzit 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you end Week 6 with your personal trainer that continues to kick your butt every day, you get back into your c… https://t.co/WoV6RqzA6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in Orlando go to @MathersOrlando   Just make sure you have a driver #strongdrinka]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know there is no honor and no class in trump. This entire nightmare of trumpism seems to grow. We must be strong… https://t.co/hcrkUaouQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of the time I go into the forest for a sense of peace, calm and connection to mother earth, but sometimes I go… https://t.co/AgUBBn7yUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCannon @MaskedSingerFOX I have known it’s Tina Turner since the first song....can’t hide her iconic voice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing that I’m going to be close to my best friend today and not being able to see her breaks my heart 🥺💔 @ChristinaMeza17]]></document><document><![CDATA[In our fast paced technology dominated world we desire and delight in “instant gratification”.  The best version of… https://t.co/WVMWWOuBF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @SolanoSPCA @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968 @samjarvis49… https://t.co/hprY5fED8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryunnu Girl yessss, you should see some of the funky-ness I see in peoples mouths 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones I don't trust the fucker.  I believe he's somehow involved with Russians.  https://t.co/l4niYZekFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[uber eats always trynna be slick with the “hey im downstairs” well hey come up motherfuckaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassRoots @MeghanMcCain My son was prescribed marinol (manufactured THC capsule) for Childhood Luekemia about 20 y… https://t.co/FNmDc8Gj2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#candid from cabin weekend 2019. (Also these humans are ridiculously good looking.) Cheers to new friends in Colora… https://t.co/1fPzkByLgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFresch I subbed to The Prescription in my podcast app but not all the episodes are showing up. Could you make su… https://t.co/8WjPpznDam]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve all been wondering....the time is now! Come work with me! #Seasons52 #SawgrassMills Seasons 52 @ Sawgrass Mi… https://t.co/8oM41WxDNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t think I’d be interpreting scripture in my dating life, but I spawned these two spontaneous interpretations… https://t.co/jby7Cbboc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenia que ser adeca de las increíbles así como su jefe de jefe @hramosallup pura basura lastima el legado de romulo… https://t.co/JsbuY9Z8lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[transform_20 day 38 Stronger 💪🏼 Today was done in complete silence and it was a challenge all we get is a next cue… https://t.co/YDXrsgjJRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malihealikhani @gdm3000 @NAACLHLT @aykuterdemml Could you please a preprint with Jalal@bu.edu ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel time (@ AMC Orange 30 - @amctheatres for Captain Marvel in Orange, CA) https://t.co/HsZfvwUL82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another inspiring Salon Sundays chez @RachelBeider - I love meeting so many dedicated women business owners in Broo… https://t.co/nn83cXx6Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sachel62 @donnabrazile Amen.  Yes, we have a cancer within that is destroying this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am legitimately so EXCITED. Klaus just stands out so much. So adorable. 😍😍😍 https://t.co/IFhAReiNGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck cheaters. If you can’t be loyal then stay the fuck single no one wants a person like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffromthe6 Blah that's so disappointing. At least it's still practice for the interview that isn't a waste of time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like this pass was going so well too... until my ankles wanted to give out on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be shocked but instead I'm incredibly sad/exhausted. #ISeeHumansButNoHumanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate being this sad man I really do be getting myself too my lowest &amp; that shit hurts 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[A must see for any bike fan is the Marin Museum of Bicycling in Fairfax California. The museum is home of the Mount… https://t.co/BCfoVhrisB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gente pasó a decirles que estoy vendiendo un iPhone X negro de 64gb desbloqueado para cualquier compañía  600 Dólar… https://t.co/zgNHnShwEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at those realistic hairstrokes 🥰😱!  If you’re a microblading artist and want to learn Advanced strokes? Classe… https://t.co/cMNbFETtkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is how my week has been going. LOL oh yeah, Minnesota Whole Foods carries Chicago Diner cakes too!!!! WOOP WOO… https://t.co/lE83ZKEdJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[that advmdiver 🐜account when we show it their tweets after december 20  #reylo https://t.co/TJErrcEMbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @ValeLeegirl Trump and Kim are two of a kind. Both lie about what they are doing, and will do. Neither… https://t.co/hi6eD3WSr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pakistan's Intense Drought Has Caused 'Alarmingly High' Levels of Disease and Hunger💔 https://t.co/kwJ9UlWHhX #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only thing I agree with and how UNIMPORTANT this issue is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @DIXIEDOODLE12 This woman is losing it. She’s the speaker of the house? God help us🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[nick foligno to max domi asking if he wanted to go https://t.co/MED2PXGXdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan Like I said I will always say this ... they are trained to kill black man... and NO one Will convince… https://t.co/OvbGN0hkHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staciew04 @lt_gray @SheriffChody @K9Nemo Once I knew @lt_gray was safe, I may had a severe case of the giggles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkButNotToday @maddiejeske16 Come on! I'd love to hear your Australian accent everyday!! We speak Southern twang here😊😋😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!  Xoxo, Snacki x Bougie 💕💄👄 #lovelovelove thelostladynyc @ The Lost Lady https://t.co/sdihEE6Yvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#@SpeakerPelosi#@chuckschumer#@AOC #@BernieSanders https://t.co/UEC18jW4z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JNera10 @InGodweTrustYah @LeahHardingAJE My son and family lives in Lagos]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how organized they are! #LambOfGod #WitnessMusic #myfirstrehearsal @ River View, Salt Lake City https://t.co/CEL6uVc0lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a former long time member of the GOP: Walls and Freedom don’t mix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_paranoid_droid @Russo_Brothers I hope so. This universe needs some Fantastic Four goodness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ColorOfTheDay: Brown  Getting my knee checked.  It has a tendency to know the weather. I had a photog that used to… https://t.co/1KZogIzNIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EducatingDrew @ProjectLITComm Weirdly enough I just downloaded the audio for the authors first book #Allegedly—but… https://t.co/zdeFVZoda7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer Your writing is evocative! I not only intellectually comprehended it your words, I felt them. Spot on!]]></document></documents></author>