<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tweets like this make me feel so lucky to work with young people. Thank you, Courtney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation @PascoSheriff Come back soon, we’ll miss you. Some of my favorite 👮‍♀️ officers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And so I said to Leo Sayer...”. Gracias, LA. @ The Teragram Ballroom https://t.co/f9k7uFgbtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@concavo_convexo @JPOMBOPAK @ChBronson777 @MariaCorinaYA @jguaido Nosotros los adecos no pretendemos ser los únicos… https://t.co/Z7U0B70vO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Oilers will need 5-7 players who make around $7-800,000 next season to make the cap work for them. Colby cave… https://t.co/d0Iz1B9Q6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may not know this but forced arbitration likely impacts you!  @TerriGerstein sets the record straight. The Amer… https://t.co/O8agKEwwzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of u niggas never had to grow up wit depression as a kid and it fr shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got the best coach in the nation !!! walked up in coach J office i said wassup he smiling saying he tryna get one… https://t.co/e4xaVYVx7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All this from someone who filed bankruptcy at least 5 times and put this country into the highest… https://t.co/WAw9KHJFKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You should know, you don’t go to the restroom without Putin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Day WOD   Bloodshot   5 Rounds  20 kB Swings  20 ab mat sit-ups 20 wall ball shots   18:43… https://t.co/vjRioq8i2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of FROZEN SASQUATCH https://t.co/9PuoAfaqt1 @wineandvicodin @screamfix @AJ_VonDoom @PsychoDriveIn… https://t.co/5PhgC6lXKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my Armada ‘04 Elite team for winning the ASG Invitational this weekend!  Great effort from all the girl… https://t.co/koxkH0saE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[For decades, we have advanced our client's interests from an independent and unconflicted perspective, informed by… https://t.co/umhdtIvKZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ted_Niki @DanleyJd @Ilhan @IlhanMN @Ilhan should be on TSA’s no fly list &amp; Treasury’s no pay list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here with  Maggie and Laura  the Birthday Girl  to see the long awaited  Captain Marvel!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sanityreturn2us @RyanAFournier We don’t have to tell Europe to take anyone back. These nations dumb fake liberal p… https://t.co/J8jtwLXvF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle @AdamWylde @JesseBlake hope you haven’t recorded yet.... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imnotlaika Hell yes. Kick some serious ass now. Show all those naysayers how bad ass talented you truly are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblando2 @rahim_shaw @Andsoithasbegun @emanuel0ss0 @SportsCenter Haha how many times did Jordan get an elbow to… https://t.co/85vVOJ27Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Wow! Can you remove all context from his joke.   This is so not true.   Really pathetic click bating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: if you put one of these in your car, you get arrested the second you drive across the state line into Ken… https://t.co/AbPedJniJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can't afford good #CraftBeer, Bud's better than being sober. Plus, who doesn't like... B E E R ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyKenna5150   Luke Perry Passed away today after his stroke https://t.co/Os9XPt2mSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are your own worst enemy. #WatchYourself and join the Untethering at  https://t.co/xv3SpkVbcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WithoutHisEyes @anish_koka @Analystdoc Correct. They are succeeding for themselves and all the other intermediarie… https://t.co/G6cAORIBXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewtwalk Let it simmer for at least 10 minutes - then rinse. Good for your gums]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin dudad, esta noche: Muchos más militares esta noche sin duda, dejaran la filas del comunismo y se unirán a Guaid… https://t.co/Duhd6NUJnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounded better in the description then it tasted. - Drinking a Push Up by @Natchezbrew @ Casa de Hammer  — https://t.co/i24bOl5NYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 Why then doesn't he just go get that evidence?  Seems investigation is unnecessary, just go to it. Why… https://t.co/Holds2wSPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets INTELLIGENT enough to know that he MIGHT avoid JAIL by slowly putting some distance between him an… https://t.co/8zUi71ZxJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesOnFSCR @NHLCanes @JustinWilliams @JustinWilliams it’s hard to see you in another Jersey.  You were part of th… https://t.co/CpTkFlWz3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great story, but also give one of our new FMSC contributors a follow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HTC_Lainey @TexansCheer @HTC_Speaker Beautifully thinking about spring breakI might add...Have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna get close, I haven’t been the same since Ioved that hoe, I haven’t been the same since I lost my bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old habits die hard! @JalenAvery0 learned how to get on the floor at a young age @KySelectAAU in Covington, Ky!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Gaetz should be censured &amp; muzzled. Was he sober when he was tweeting   https://t.co/V34v35FljY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondull Do you know the people who you assume have never worked for a label from one tweet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHillsCountry @overthefarmgate I've lived rural my whole life and I'm still considered city. It's something that… https://t.co/k3Cjwscpu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[UBER/LYFT 2-MIN WARNING. @katskiles elizabethwarren @berniesanders #uberlyft2mw #kooterkountryklub #usa #america… https://t.co/tpjpis7rnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsterLuu @rsbravard @chrislongview @KaylaraOwl Sounds like @AsterLuu was being supportive to me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHeidikins @Colettod @sarbjitkaur1 @GailVazOxlade 😂 this image probably did more damage to political careers tbh… https://t.co/5u0RmsrQfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one tells you in highschool how hard this adult shit is. Glad I know the Pythagorean theorem though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisonraehart Yea, don’t do that . I think I can speak for the most of your followers that we enjoy your content .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennahasredhair You're Beautiful without but I appreciate the enhancements 🌷😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another link and a little background on Plotkin's lecture at the Peabody Musuem at Harvard on Feb. 20:… https://t.co/VRJqwppf2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnjulieRao With our powers combined, WE ARE [INSERT SLIGHTLY IRONIC, CLEVERLY TITLED BUT STILL PROFESSIONAL SOUNDING NEWS OUTLET NAME]]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy hump day 😂🤞🏽  Work today so one day you won't have to "work today". @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/t2sNyQAU9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hagan with 7 assists to 1 turnover tonight. Think he heard the talk by Jay Bilas that Bone was the best guard in the league?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fed up with Gloria M. Woolfe trashing me. 🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬 . . . . #gramoftheday #acting #actor #actorslife… https://t.co/77p3we25AJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo quiero amanecer contigo, bailar contigo  Estar contigo, hacerlo en una esquina contigo  Y sin testigos, darte castigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Understand this, my dear brothers and sisters: You must all be quick to listen, slow to speak, and slow to get angry.” James 1:19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does your fam make you ask for it a second time before they agree to it? Lol. . We had a great time at the Texas Le… https://t.co/xId8f1a1Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #monday you all have a great week now :) @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/V2qeDtIlsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly @DNC @GOP We the @GOP are the party for all for the people. We want less government and to be able to… https://t.co/EwFLnFMocO]]></document><document><![CDATA[VC money is like jet fuel–if you add it to a spark, it makes a giant fire. If there’s no spark, then you’re just co… https://t.co/FMjjTblToQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway through this old stash @CardConnector  Everything in thread below so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe he should start with #lgbt rights here in the US? Trump administration will launch a global campaign to decri… https://t.co/IkRCdB6qJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthew_leal @KPRC2 @KPRC2Cathy @KPRC2Amy @KPRC2Haley @kprc2owen @KPRC2Britta @KPRC2Sofia @sdeebocane… https://t.co/uVT4lNCBCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[That would  be really bad. But you know what’d be a whole lot worse? Russia attacks a U.S. ally—say, Estonia or Lat… https://t.co/BrCOfZZot8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day for @FurmanSoftball at Auburn University. 1230 versus Drake and then a clash under the lights with the hos… https://t.co/wn7mb1VD2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well here’s my two cents. First, the people voted in a completely uncontested and non-controversy way. So, maybe in… https://t.co/heYYoJdycK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Trump is destroying China economy.  Happy, happy, joy, joy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YahooSports @SportsCenter Brutal  5 second rule ? No defensive effort  Lebron demonstrated his dominance over players]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t it about time he is designated as an “enemy combatant” and given a one trip to Guantanamo for some enhanced i… https://t.co/vhi6IA54Dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blacketologist Just wondering, is the list based on now or potential? I’m terrible at ranking lists, but am curiou… https://t.co/fS5XghWiWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@griffinbikepark is free. I took all I could get tonight.   #outsideisfree #rideabike #lifebehindbars #bicycle… https://t.co/zXVf2ffnjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me importa si lo sufrir todo mi Vida sin nadie. Por que todos valen Nada a mi. Me encanta que yo estoy solo y quiero mantener ser solo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GPS #FujiXT3 35mm-1/100th@ƒ/1.4-ISO640 #directions #help #lost #unionSquare #Candid #streetphotography #Fujifilm… https://t.co/Q7OVhgQWSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to use the Secret to win the lottery by visualizing myself not worrying about putting meat with big bones… https://t.co/coXAzrqEe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CornersParadise  @StormHour  @ThePhotoHour  @SGeorgianBay https://t.co/HLxhYI2Hob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chozen Martial Arts Academy can help you get started. Go to https://t.co/vIiiplnbyt @ Chozen Martial Arts Academy https://t.co/c12s9Jk9Yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nballaccess Seriously averaging 13.7 on 49% from the field and 46% from 3 guy has been solid all year Mr. Reliable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting my day here in Detroit...#shishi #fudog #eternalink #eternalsponsoredartist #h2oceannothing #h2ocean… https://t.co/rt5nL40wqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@some_zero @bungarsargon @IlhanMN @SpeakerPelosi #YouStandWithAntiSemitism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being so stupid you can’t find the correct seat on an airplane lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tatyana_AA Ну не знаю, живя в стране фастфуда, питаюсь в основном дома, очень редко в ресторанах, а вот фастфуда не употребляю.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not funny.  My Mom did that to me one year.  The wife and kids think it’s funny though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you. #Grateful https://t.co/NFVzAneHo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Hugh Crance helps Notre Dame men’s lacrosse handle Denver in Pacific Coast Shootout: Hugh Crance d… https://t.co/sMPILFLxLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta say, I’m digging @MarneyGellner home run call. #Twins #BetterCallMama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseArreguin You ate in such a rush to criminalize the poor that you wouldn't even give Ben 2 weeks to fully present his idea. Tsk tsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely great body language from Lebron James here. I’m sure his team really appreciates it and will only play b… https://t.co/zVayuChkLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr instead you have made it harder for Americans to get any kind of insurance. You are a fraud!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMRAnswers A troubled soul. May she rest in peace. #SuicidePrevention #SuicideAwareness #hcldr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanADeSimone 2.) After passing on adding an Edge Defender for the entire 2018 draft, or bringing a proven one in… https://t.co/peuqK3eSb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnbachmann80 @nationwidescott Thanks for coming on. You’re a rockstar]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we all put our yangbucks together we can buy a boat and leave this shitty country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out for breakfast the other day and there was two men at the bar.   One made the statement that they had the guns (… https://t.co/AsL0AjnGJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nzinga of Ndongo and Matamba:  17th century queen of the modern day country of Angola, she aggressively fought agai… https://t.co/73fD6yv7vV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luka is having an amazing year and is clearly statistically better than Trae Young, but Trae Young is right there w… https://t.co/gn8jFtGn38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna get through this Monday thinking about UVA crushing Tech tonight. 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alan_R_White Did you have to remortgage the house to get it? Terminal 5 - too rich for my blood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 The congressman should be recalled by the people in his district due to the lack of res… https://t.co/Z65aA0Dg66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KleinUla @DrDecKavanagh @nbgarret @zugenia @fantasmascope @zugenia we’re both there! I got to read Emily’s presentation which is 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew Because democrats care about you so much. How much does it take for people to realize that the soc… https://t.co/lFgTSxUx0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to start painting where can I get paint and canvas for a good deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking through this thread made me slightly emotional lmao 😂 I love seeing people love their cats ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[:-BOO CITY".    Democratic National Committee chooses Milwaukee as host city for 2020 convention  https://t.co/QbtgvBjbSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justicedems @AOC Does anyone in America pay more taxes than they have too?  Many of us pay people money to save us money when we file.]]></document></documents></author>