<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sueellen93 @YihsiangT @Koji262 Even downloads are fewer,but you can still  get Y Classical Amazon  music,no more cds anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Doors Down. #3doorsdownconcert #goldennuggetlakecharles @3doorsdown   Best acoustic concert ever! @ Golden Nugget… https://t.co/1LnLdQvU0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jchawes was wondering if you had any further news on when and what channel you and the crew would return to parano… https://t.co/ff6rF92btr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwwwwCats How did u get kitty to do that ? mine will lay with me but not like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning (yes it’s 2pm) to everyone except professors who put material on the exam that they didn’t include on the study guide]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is literally a series of unfortunate events. From alcoholic drug addict parents to a crazy Mom who hated me… https://t.co/eU0eXDRzQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's mirth all around us. parents-01 #funniness #tee-hee #grin #absurd https://t.co/gcEzXjwRIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wholeFoods #ValentinesDay2019 #CakeCakeAndMoreCakes https://t.co/rZjYjXJli7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be in NY the week of the 23rd! I hope your enhibit is during those days, so I can go support you and meet you!… https://t.co/utxd7wjZEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ne manquez pas SPORTS ET SCORES ce Samedi dès 10h00 sur les ondes du 92,9FM CFUT Radio Shawinigan.L`écouter c`est f… https://t.co/M6sb84wjVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t make a pernil as good as my dad or my aunts. Or papas rellanas or alcapurrias.   Sad things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a man hit on us by offering #GirlScoutCookies  Night made #wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@th3j35t3r She probably is getting a little jowly.   You can’t see it in the other picture because she is smiling.… https://t.co/RFP9UT7KEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to  @PCE_ATL, @GA_Production, @atlfilmsociety, and Set Supplies for the PA Academy today!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: #NCTEchat Boundless could mean learning from past mistakes, from listening, from new texts. Quoting Angelou: wh… https://t.co/eer7E7RSOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg 🙌🏼 so true! And even throwing a quote from Jesus HIMSELF in there 😉🙏🏼 (10 years of catholic school right here 😂)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I applied for my job WAY out of my league and I want to delete the application because there’s no way I have enough experience for it🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate4Queen @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @TwitterSupport I blocked that bot long ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellesammet Yep! $10k to my OB that supervises my pregnancy (she wasn’t even on call my delivery date and I als… https://t.co/tMIKAlcmyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Pres. Obama had done even one of the DISGUSTING things this FREAK or his family achieved against the United Stat… https://t.co/9MqJZOl8Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradie and I woke up, made cheesy roll ups and had an exclusive Jonas Brothers concert in our living room. I am an adult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgriep1 Cool! Thank you fir the opportunity to work on this and the mention! @NebraskaEPSCoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWords @hecallsmePP Let me know if you’d like some ears! I have a bunch up in the shop and I can do a custom pair… https://t.co/Jc3PG32XGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I sent chris a photo of french onion soup and now he’s making it for me for dinner.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to seriously think about this. Why are so many schools out of compliance? This is an equity issue. https://t.co/riPA5vn0ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing-&gt; Argure -&gt; ima cry-&gt; he gone try to fuck -&gt; ima get mad -&gt; restart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a lot of respect for her, but hope she doesn’t run for prez again... don’t want Bernie or Joe either. Time for… https://t.co/wzkS5J1sRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snack time!  Mini Brie Bites &amp; olives. #keto #snack #brie #olives #nom @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/7uAT9zadBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[600 dead dolphins turn up on French beaches. It’s a lot. And there’s no explanation given]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCoronell @UniNoticias @jorgeramosnews @NicolasMaduro Liberan?!? - No lo creo, porque se reporta que están detenid… https://t.co/tvrMgLwJh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatkhalid omg i can't wait!!!! this is gonna be the vibe allllll summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That really makes me wanna slap the shit out of my siblings I miss them :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re live outside the school this morning where that teacher is still active.  https://t.co/9x9P8QGGHf @wyffnews4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Plumbing is like your body, it’s a science, and you have to keep things flowing in the right directions...think ab… https://t.co/RnJsq3ZtLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris If you are a collector of Bibles as some of these folks may be, you have Bibles signed by members o… https://t.co/bGlGhuRUzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many people are listening to #JonasBrothers #SUCKER and ONLY THAT SONG? #JonasBrothersareback]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así le pasó una vez a mi hermano, le dieron una tele para su depa, la instaló mal y se cayó a media noche JAJAJAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th bell wraps up perfect system review. We spend too long pronouncing “mansī” correctly. I spend Bell 5 in a Mega… https://t.co/GcMemjXUOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoniLoren Looking forward to it. I am almost done with Cal’s book and looking to do a digital declutter in April.… https://t.co/iCE9N2WGg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCPlanning, @galeabrewer, and I are encouraging those who live, work in, and visit #SoHo and #NoHo to come out to… https://t.co/XKgP0anpk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Youre a POS. Rep. Omar has never seen war. She was brought on board to politics by the tons of tax dollars col… https://t.co/5Yl8CIgTQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of yall never wanted to work as a waste management worker so you could ride on the back of the truck &amp; it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graytwinsmom @TheMartinSystem @gehrig38 @fred_guttenberg https://t.co/3XJk2ETvgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, I had a dream that I was at a fundraiser with @S_C_ and he was running around doing all the legwork to… https://t.co/2SmyKGAI3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i wish i had a school work permit so i dont have to be working late night shits lmao 😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want for Xmas is you... 😍#slothsofinstagram #slothlove @ Kitchener, Ontario https://t.co/7UdAXAHaus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultrahottie2000 @dayzedconfuzed @SuusGodsChild If you watched todays episode.I found it awesome and funny, Chloe w… https://t.co/XYiiPd9djz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4uConservatives @Brendag38323989 Most 16 yr olds are incapable of making their own Dr appt. But you want them to vote?  No thanks...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not a question of IF there will be another Kac Nrgantic, but WHEN #pipelines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting Now, don’t you understand what the man is trying to say?  If only all you mean old blacks would stop… https://t.co/9l4AFPZMel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabo de captar que ya tengo como 3 años que comencé a comer mariscos... y si, me perdía de mucho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was going to link a song in a group on Facebook and this happens I'm so glad @andyblack is getting this push it's w… https://t.co/yhkcdVvz7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillerMadeline You know how the ms. goes. Fingers crossed. I'm playing the waiting game, but I wanted it to be as… https://t.co/V1kXliofz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we have class tonight the same time as the Oscars! Understanding the Age of the Martyrs- During the first three… https://t.co/rzOj8GoBul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir @GulliAz The fact that it would be illegal 4 trump to do this has never stopped him before. He thinks… https://t.co/RbIKMlR74L]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way to get to perfection is to practice everyday! #esthetician #skincare #terrifictuesday #goals… https://t.co/b1vMDjyQGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are Proud of our #D31 #DH helping out opening the Mt. Pleasant Store #OrangeFamilia #TeamPlayer #MoreSavings… https://t.co/I3UvBZyuLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker bout to be in here thinking ima do all this other work cause people called in sick. Aht Aht Aht I’m doing wtf I do and dassit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the flat earth documentary and i suddenly want to become a scientist just to destroy these fools]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two ADORABLE Easter shades are available now, LIMITED EDITION 🐣🐰💐  Hop on over to get yours now:… https://t.co/RvNQYlfeJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJSayWhat @LoseyLaurice @JackPosobiec @OANN @w_terrence Thankfully, he’s SOOOO well known and loved on here (and p… https://t.co/eV2SKvE1l8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I was 17 when I realized #TheOscars were all about business and our love of spectacle rather than art. Inst… https://t.co/qK6Ii9HaCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poland pulls out of summit hosted by Israel citing 'racist' remarks  https://t.co/hPgGV5BQKH @noa_landau]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I left a piece of myself in Montana. I miss it so much already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivingMyBestLife #OneDayAtATime #ILoveMyLife #BestFeelingEver #IAmSober #Truth #ODAAT @ Positive Vibes Only https://t.co/cHCJc9r9Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all due respect,  the servicemen's benefits he voted against throughout his career weren't known by him; nor w… https://t.co/KfNTYHbyiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is humorous. Free printable minecraft Valentines Day cards for kids. 12 different designs.  -- Dannon will LOV… https://t.co/2NXYqe9RNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá en la mañana me envió fotos de su carro cubierto de nieve pero resulta que yo iba despertando y pensé que e… https://t.co/2CDmJncbAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We asked you if anyone knew...all these Luberals are just avoiding answering a simple yes or no question   https://t.co/EFYgAnVfnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s safe to say I had the GREATEST birthday cake ever @jamessmurray @BQQuinn @Joe_Gatto @SalVulcano… https://t.co/PEKRJr1Xkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the clouds this winter out here in Cold Springs, NV. ☺️❤️ #clouds #winter #snow #beautifulplaces @ Cold Spri… https://t.co/kYCXMcMjrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I havent been so genuinely happy in so long. such a happy girl, so in love, life is so good 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up next! @RebeccaCressman @FM1003 #UtahWeeklyForum Talking coronary calcium risk scoring with @Intermountain… https://t.co/RcKhGzH7eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venusinlibra_ I just did an online chat too. It’s neither cancelled or renewed but all chat transcripts go somewhere.   I forgot. My bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pit stop for the @Art_o_mat in St. Cloud! #bghockeyorbust #ayziggy #miniart (@ River's Edge Convention Center -… https://t.co/iwpoETSO5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[working in fashion is great for people like me who love getting paper-cuts and enjoy sitting on stray pins]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible babymoon with my amazing hubby! Until next time Miami 🤗☀️🌴#babyjd #7weeksandcounting @ Miami Bea… https://t.co/k21Fxe4SYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJackson_NYC #HarmedSuburbanFive @HarmedSuburban5  @OssiningSchools Children THANK YOU for standing up for them ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What actually killed the dinosaurs? Volcanic clues heat up debate. https://t.co/f8cu4x1egr via @NatGeoScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are lucky to have such hardworking crews across Washington. #thankyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onethrone_ Omg 🙄 the taco joint I go to down cells called Papi’s sells it. It’s call “elote”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBlankenshipWSB Good mornin! Mr. Fred, I’ll be at the studio tomorrow for a tour, along with a group of homeschool… https://t.co/8xWp9rDNiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representative Omar fires back at Trump after his call for her resignation: "You've trafficked in hate your whole l… https://t.co/1nkdzrBASm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentCrypt46 So is it all being orchestrated? Was she supposed to say that and Bezos is also being controlled an… https://t.co/EMB2iIO8V7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my work schedule has changed &amp; I’m lost without my Ryan’s 🥀’s in the morning!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even after sharing before, there is something scary about sharing my progress pictures!  6 weeks of hard work, heal… https://t.co/CWAlvfUs7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstevensradio @BriannaWu Or made at home. Gee even 50+ years ago ppl knew how to make a gun. They were called “zip guns.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Not to state the obvious but Nancy doesn't even know what day it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigontheair Shame on you. You took away a spot from a WOMAN to be played]]></document><document><![CDATA[@friezeartfair Hot pink is the Frieze color. #artistsoninstagram #LosAngeles @ Paramount Studios https://t.co/GQcGyfqj7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Samsung Regional Training Facility https://t.co/7pkuGv9afg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurvaceousCodi Girlllll! Imagine trying to have this convo. I had the Travis Scott gif face on whole time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @BernieSanders If by authentic you mean repeating the same things almost verbatim while delivering al… https://t.co/SYHBNCmVao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump BUILDING THE WALL!!!!!  THANK YOU LORD AND THANK TOU LORD FOR DONALD TRUMP!!!!!  MY PRESIDENT!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body hurts so damn bad.  I’m using coffee and preworkout to pretend it doesn’t. #isthisadulting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made pork tenderloin with onions/roasted potatoes. Roasted acorn squash, roasted Brussels sprouts and an Asian… https://t.co/sUgW1nUERm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly I wasn’t with her when this happened because it would’ve been on with this fucker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraNye4 @steveabril @JamesGleick @TIME UR ONE BIG LIAR AND DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs WARNING, @potus lost his way as appts #EnemyOfThePeople chamber, apple FOREIGN CHEAP labor crowd destroye… https://t.co/CFYK3vKIEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carpool Karaoke with your lover is one of the best feeling in the world 🎶 🎤 🕺🏻💃🏻👯‍♀️💏]]></document></documents></author>