<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[ok @openargs what even is the point of sentencing guidelines if this bs is going to happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby bad y’all!!!! Happy Valentine’s my Queen beyondd.31. I absolutely love this journey we are on together and… https://t.co/GWmOb2Vo6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s so good at basketball he’s affecting the stock market... we need you to get up Zion https://t.co/9wacysOEgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanCenter @PennState @PennStateMBB @PennStateWBB #WeArePennState #StateCollege #harlemglobetrotters… https://t.co/1eHWCEyjzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Kroschel @CBSDenver Thanks for your intrepid coverage! I’ve been wondering whether there’s been any action on… https://t.co/quHZH17gjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverAveBlues @JLo is richer, she might have paid for it or it's a loaner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zashrie @LSUbaseball yes me watching lsu disappoint every year screams bandwagon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s support among Hispanics and Latinos is real. Don’t assume it will fade. - The Washington Post https://t.co/P1YrKAUIAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the KISS Paul Stanley signature guitar needs to arrive... #bcrich #bcrichwarlock #widowheadstock #nobrand… https://t.co/6HXiOD5xLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tears of Green (w/ Motueka and Citra) by @cptlawrencebeer at @innovokitchen — https://t.co/BTToIJwnIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clydevanel UAE 🇦🇪 Saudi Arabia 🇸🇦 Qatar 🇶🇦 Kuwait 🇰🇼 4 must stop places on your trip you know what to do just close bring @cmesi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theneumann64 The fact that the Morning Joe crew is so angry makes me like it more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything for my students! I am still in need of leveled quality books for my students. Any help is greatly apprecia… https://t.co/Ufl5ZLUbvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a man thinketh by James Allen is a book I believe every man should read!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People better come together real soon or there are going to be some very nasty times ahead. If we don't stand now a… https://t.co/W8cdDtUDJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexArboleda20 @Rangel_DM @Arboleda__ @sondelaB_ Jajajajajajajajajajajajajaja mrk lo juro que yo no quería jajajaj… https://t.co/YLpvl3NvEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we Face a situation we Can't change we're challenged to Change our situation. https://t.co/ptrYr6pXZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official day one just about in the books! Unofficial night 3 about to begin! #NASP2019 #BmoreNASP2020 https://t.co/zmdF8SHayb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain marvel // blibspeedreview: fun then flat // blibscreenscore : C+ // blibs place in the MCU :15th // blibs f… https://t.co/RrtUU0n5A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeusZissou @Crypto_Goku_ Good point.  Id like to remind ya’ll that scooped a bunch up at $83. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOSfanatic @jm10zepeda @realmadrid @ESPN_JorgeRamos Yo no pierdo ni un minuto escuchándolos desde q aprendí q ello… https://t.co/bPtihUKPVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure why not join a drum circle after a beautiful sunset 🌅 #drumcircle #fortmyers https://t.co/na4K9eZvwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best songwriter in the world (IMHO), and one of the greatest people in the world (also IMHO), releases her new… https://t.co/zoLhbyobX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine - find your centre and do it for someone else if not for you! Motivation #3 this week for why you sh… https://t.co/jPj0jcY75J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marx4all @AlexBNewhouse @SenSanders To be clear - this isn't a poll.  It's a comparison of a non-random sample of… https://t.co/nXrMTf8JEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you, California, you're the greatest state of all.  I love you in the winter, summer, spring and in the fall… https://t.co/2lNq6rQoKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeFreedomLove 80 Foot tall- 80 foot tall, that's how Big, I want my wall. make it Big , and make it last, do it q… https://t.co/gOSuIptmYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama increased sharing of intel massively as lamb duck prior to Trump swearing in was by coincidence????? Ring lea… https://t.co/xx9qxaeo6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t a political tweet. This is a literacy tweet. There’s so many people with whom I’ve shared views with tha… https://t.co/TgP7P4GwWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapperBRad @Borg99754177 @FlipMyBeatz @wav_Dr @JuanitaCSAthome @DavidDiehl20 @KittenheadLa @ELEVEN11_STUDIO… https://t.co/yLOuWSaEf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Neon Snowsuit by @levelbeer at @theonebige — https://t.co/fmdVPG6cAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another,what would republicans say if Obama or Hillary said that moment??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissedinHistory  learned some local history today! I feel like Mary Titcomb was a past episode or got a a mention.… https://t.co/tuXSPa9oFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Salad from the cafeteria at work! @ Intel Corporation https://t.co/oeZpzEEBnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #FranklinCounty on Louisburg Rd and Flat Rock Church Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatimavee8 @JovanaBanuelos Who wouldn't wanna buy burritos from Jovana 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be DDing from now until about midnight for $5 a ride! All of the money will go to the Children’s Hospital in O… https://t.co/TMY4IwABBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 (@ The Lodge Bar &amp; Grill in Randolph, MA) https://t.co/KmMMzwRZhV https://t.co/JH8hzFoZAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fast break for 2 in a 92-71 win for #SwampBoys of @GreenRiverCC #NWAC #Basketball #Dunk #Jam #iampoweredbynikon @ G… https://t.co/f3NZOrCTy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get the most questions drilled at you than any of the 4 people 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregRenoff Love that, I’m Dave or the Grave😂✊️🤘all the way... although, I love Montrose and Sammy solo✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PlayStation This is how I feel about consistently noticing on a regular basis series randomly disappearing from m… https://t.co/y3kAr9XxYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que el clima actual no debería ser motivo de júbilo sino que deberían estar alarmados y CONSCIENTES sobre el cambio climático.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRogersTech Likewise my friend! You’re so good to me and my students!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra arts education boosts students’ writing scores — and their compassion, big new study finds https://t.co/AT0JbeHfOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth...#JHF #Fireproof #FSUICIDE #Faddiction #FPTSD #FCancer #Livefree #NewSouth #Truth #JustHavinFun #Maniklife… https://t.co/O5wGTOdYiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women will pull men into conversations they have no business pulling us in 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed that they work out because I can’t deal with the plantar fasciitis and left hamstring/hip pain from… https://t.co/eo2uOQxkNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Furious by @surlybrewing at @jakemelnicks — https://t.co/v7x77YdfJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheap flights on the skiplagged app. Hidden-city ticketing aggregator - travel light, no checked bags. Kudos to… https://t.co/7QeGSMNj9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gunna say one thing... “NO MORE MAKE UP!” Can this be a movement or nah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The North Korea thing is nothing more than a Con Man (a better Con Man than you) playing three car… https://t.co/En1zJFnObU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s no dust on my bottles cause I drink them to fast”- @EvanHuttunen]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we can’t wait to see you scramble when they are measuring  your shirt and pant sizes !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecuainm @MashiRafael @fherrerarauz Todos estos politiqueros son la misma mierda roban y unos quieren visa american… https://t.co/5852Ttn1gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pop on the blow the #Spurs received coming out of the rodeo road trip chute: “It’s pretty difficult to lose your po… https://t.co/l3fCCIV1Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chan_ing I wonder what took her so long.  No competent government would *ask* her to weigh in, so ... I don't know where that leaves us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhendry40 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump But it's alright that your president did Obama  started this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDunn21 No brainer. We don’t appreciate tea enough as a morning alternative]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellycass @juliemartin @JimCantore @GregPostel @AMHQ @weatherchannel Im disappointed barely a dusting even though… https://t.co/durX2NM80N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belief is likely the most critical factor when predicting success.”  Attitude is Everything  https://t.co/lKr0SFd33s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rothgar @CloudNativeFdn I'm giving a talk and participating in the #Kubernetes panel on Saturday. Haven't signed u… https://t.co/5IviJWbTg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@no_silenced @BernieSanders @nychange @MaketheRoadNY @MPower_Change @WorkingFamilies @CPDAction @RWDSU… https://t.co/kDMwlUmeb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisoaks2007 Yeah. Kind of a slow burn, but tons better than the demo. Getting more fun every mission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweatsntopknots @yourmusicsucks @CanadianBeave13 @MomO5Tiff @sdeebocane @KPRC2Amy @TFeemster @EveInFlow… https://t.co/fRuv88aISo]]></document><document><![CDATA[REVIVAL 9:30am Today @SBUPC w Evang Nick Mahaney ~ be on time, no Sunday School, new Jubilee start time, bring a fr… https://t.co/2hyjYbMocL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phragmites also do not provide habitat or food to native wildlife, reduces native biodiversity, injure animals lik… https://t.co/KsxfNVQMpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Euro Rampage ‘92.   Macho Man beats HBK with a second rope (almost) springboard cross body.   What the fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonya_Stylz @norvina1 @kamm_lester @glamgawwd_1990 @_Kingkouture @GlamByWill @Mikey_Luvs_MUA @Carlosbeautyy… https://t.co/JZVKiDvMRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlsVocal #TogetherWeWill proud how our groups support each other in their competitions.  Good Luck everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0neInLemilli0n its cause most of the games dont appeal to a large demographic of people only game that got allot o… https://t.co/N5A6FrLJQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm elected electric spy I'm protected electric eye  https://t.co/Sj80lPWcTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Expittriate Ugh! We need blue line help Tim! Not give away our best D man! God!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[En todos los turnos, había al menos 3 cocineros... el chino estaba solo. Sacaba la cena de médicos, también de enfe… https://t.co/CY1VbYO0Jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[People on Facebook marketplace be like:  Looking for a reliable vehicle, must be less than 5 years old, must have l… https://t.co/bJkppfSwpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great.  I another benchmark day like garbage day to tell me what day of the week it is.  #retirementbliss… https://t.co/elWysGXHfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day has come. A @QuinnipiacU story has made a @espn top headline. Also, not to mention that this led off… https://t.co/7SGhaOvQOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singing22u @EminenceSchools @thomcoffee @BuddyBerry @Meghan_Lawson @RobinAWiley @AConnerNews @AmyCrouse how's this for PD??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sampling of a groovy and ethereal set by Chiyoco ✨ New original untitled track https://t.co/36BhH5eQN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman Every time I read one of his tweets that claims the press is the “enemy,” I’m just gonna respond w… https://t.co/PGUrxZsGA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Huntsville #Birmingham #Alabama #US SHE THE DEVIL #Band We'll be announcing two #CdRelease shows soon. So get read… https://t.co/0A1ObMowwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I’m so done splitting bills with hoes and getting a Venmo request for $20 and I had ONE drink! Look I know we… https://t.co/jFs8TxmHHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollyringle @ProudResister O my God molly try reading the bible u all will see one day every knee shall bow and ev… https://t.co/k9GwR0bl5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kibblesmith @joemcadam ...or F-  Probably not a lot of room in the middle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnicableOficial @NiurkaMarcosTv @miembrosalaire @burrovan @negroaraiza2 @LeoGarciaOf @MAU_MANCERA 😜😛😜😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[The simpler jams are super cozy.  This was pretty fun to try just guitar with drum machine.  Would've sung but I ca… https://t.co/KI5kEH6c2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! • • • • #GreatDivide #Denver #Friday #TheChampIsHere #Love #MyPerson #JandJ @ Great Divide Barrel Bar https://t.co/quk0pv4HP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyoYagamistyle @gunswordfist @Skyhawk1 @AmazonGoddessD @Wondergal82 @IrishPatti1 @OceanRageM @hollyanderson30… https://t.co/xgHPumNU6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaruCampos_G Como siempre hemos dicho los panistas; #ElSurTambienEsChihuahua]]></document><document><![CDATA[And let us not grow weary while doing good, for in due season we shall reap if we do not lose hear… https://t.co/q3tWnLeiJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing “We’re not gonna take it” in Memorial Gym is almost comical at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I tend to be happy now.  I look forward to the next day, the next weekend.  I don't get bored.  I am… https://t.co/fG6cMaItOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[1321: another stack train with 2 pulling and 2 pushing #trains @ East Lawrence, Lawrence, Kansas https://t.co/fJM8Oax0A9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ycmmat much better with Bon,still good though, give me any 78,or 79 songs over that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan trump lies constantly. You should take your own advice. Sooner better than later]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going vertical #OnThisDayAWeekAgo. #McMullenCreekGreenway #CharlotteNC #Charlotte #NC #NorthCarolina #CLT… https://t.co/lzJ4g96Rvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rudy’s self induced cigar smoke haze has finally caused total lapse of cogent thought. Feeling sorry is poor excuse… https://t.co/mE0fYgCymi]]></document><document><![CDATA[In fact, I got a DM from someone who recognized the name of the company that donated the VT320 and its keyboard, be… https://t.co/y94f7N5xVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3_ShortCircuit @F3Greensboro @Bodett_F3 @F3Explosion Great beat down short-circuit! I certainly got more than my money's worth. Great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iajanus @nibroc @GeoffreyHuntley Apple is noteworthy in how secretive they are. When I was at Cisco, customers had… https://t.co/WNtj3tEz2h]]></document></documents></author>