<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[From the father of Jacob Wohl, the noxious pro-Trump troll who was recently booted from Twitter. Then what does he… https://t.co/n1XLk1uB9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CrownTheRink ready for #Beauts #NWHL #Playoffs https://t.co/uDRZySyYlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is your most precious resource.  Its value is amplified during an attack.  The more time you save via early se… https://t.co/AslPp6WccH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose the @POTUS @realDonaldTrump could partner@with @JussieSmollett and flip the script on all these losing… https://t.co/MAhbbEmVIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With spring break comes girls Instagram content for the next six months]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not such a good hair day. . . . . #badhairday #funkyhair #myhairhurts #ididntknowitwasathing #itsathing #hathair… https://t.co/I9LbFtAw1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[These talented Knights, joining forces with Grayslake artists of all ages - what a great show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw, and was able to catch up with so many friends today I haven’t seen in a while. My heart is full.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coverage of Tomatoes and rest that we have seen in Indian Media is far from a composed media. Pakistani media d… https://t.co/kKL1DDxIwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tossinghydras It’s a 3D printed tower my buddy @crazyhorse1321 made for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 13 grandchildren, so this matter deeply concerns me. Racial profiling must stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it is because kind of the way girls have become with all their "rights" and stuff  they just don't seem to… https://t.co/DrPKO4OcBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMossfritch @mitchbytes @KasieDC @RepDebDingell @HeidiHeitkamp @RepSeanMaloney @PhilipRucker @KenDilanianNBC… https://t.co/gQ7GSjEyci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDDetectives @NYPDnews @NYPDTransit @MTA @ManhattanDA @NYPDTips @NYCPDDEA @NYPDChiefofDept @NYPDONeill… https://t.co/s2DT6qAIxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to thank @LILBTHEBASEDGOD daily. #thankyoubasedgod https://t.co/JtcagXW670]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of the love to my boiz in. @theyaredancer played a killer set last night. So proud of all the work we put in. 💗… https://t.co/t3m2FFfIZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good deed done 👍🏾✊🏾 so I was in Walmart today with my kids grabbing valentines cards. We forgot the candy on the ot… https://t.co/RQzcMXn4M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Session 2 (1A): @SigourneyCSD’s Mason Dye (113) tech fall win over Mick Schroder 19-4. His day is done, but he’ll b… https://t.co/Kttvnl555r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg so am walkn down the aisle  at work and a shit load of files jus can down on my head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaquinCastrotx @Rosie_G72 @realDonaldTrump Good job, dictator.trump When the Dems are back in control, they can d… https://t.co/5m1W02nP6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee stout with a little kick!! - Drinking an Out Of Mind Coffee Stout by @AveryBrewingCo @ Arvada, CO  — https://t.co/ZXrsYk5vzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NahBabyNah @LadyRedWave Guess what color 1st man 2die in a revolution was I got fake news. Most valuable thing on… https://t.co/v7Iiq4JOhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBLawrence33 I wouldn’t do it solely on the fact that wastes so much beer lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEEMSTAR @realDonaldTrump Correct,his stupidity is funny. He's a laugh a minute. Do we count all his lies as stupidity too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncanDaHusky Mmm. I think maybe it’s just that from Alaska, NOLA is only a little farther than Seattle, so why no… https://t.co/MMDfpE8Hev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EeeJaye9 It's worth the time and money. IDK if it's still in theaters, but the DVD is out and includes video of Qu… https://t.co/6w62CYSodZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson 🤔 Isn’t the 25th Amendment part of the Constitution? How can it be unconstitutional?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alvarogmc50 @MelMora08 @tottusperu No esa no es válida. No existe etiqueta "bajo en". Las etiquetas válidas son oc… https://t.co/vWnS2A772r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoConScores @SamfordXC_TF @samford_sports Congrats Karisa. We remember you fondly as a little blond girl running w… https://t.co/rbZiYyiTvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLammy The torch of Freedom is in danger of being snuffed out, TAKE A STAND AGAINST THE FORCES OF DARKNESS! https://t.co/t0Rp3LzHvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCochraneMUS @MapleLeafs It’s going to be tough sledding the rest of the way, but hopefully gets us ready for the playoff run!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nextdoor #Massachusetts #civillaw The woman boasts "Enjoy your Chow?" and after the child shouts her statements. "… https://t.co/9JpSMfVY29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have the day off? Are you working from home? We’re serving brunch from from 10a-3p! Throw on your snow boots… https://t.co/GVNok8dX8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acting like you don’t hear about Max Domi’s dad on a broadcast every game he plays, or how Trevor and James van Rie… https://t.co/M53ljebf8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoCubsHQ he just needs to sign with the Chicago Cubs and every thing will be all right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chandabell @USATODAY Very impressive.  Congratulations ! You have made a lot of children very happy. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyyyy thanks for sharing @cltcheap!!!!  Cannot wait!!   It’ll be a LATTE fun!! ☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️… https://t.co/2xn3ebDTw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview: Dana Perino Reveals How Christian Faith Helps Her Overcome Worry https://t.co/70iCae2XtH via @faithwirenews @tregp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a great speaker and gardening how to lineup @ArkFlowerGarden show this weekend. Come out and join us.… https://t.co/Mlsr53Hkat]]></document><document><![CDATA[And by the way, if there are any pretty, rich blondes out there, please introduce yourselves. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t pick a useless major and go to a college that will leave you with massive debt 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever see one of your siblings and just wanna punch them. But you can’t cause mom will punch you 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exceptional Children’s Week is right around the corner (March 4th-8th) and we are selling T-Shirts again! The shirt… https://t.co/wJZSHfcILD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was working 9-9 today but I looked at my schedule and I’m only working 9-3 https://t.co/zXKmRw1oxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t give a fuck if your white, black, Muslim idc if your join ISIS you can stay there 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfahrer @rubytuesday1985 @bariweiss @EmanuEl_NYC Is that what she said?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back home in Dallas, Texas... I was born right around the corner in Arlington. When I was a kid I watched this towe… https://t.co/dlu1buFoa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[These SUCK tbh!! Dab of ranch....more like a cup full 🤮 https://t.co/xTKEl5Knr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Klairreeee I almost got expelled because I refused to try on the exercises and then made all platinums lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum “Do you think Jimbo Fischer will super glue Ed Orgeron’s ass cheeks together before kickoff next year, Paul?”....#MattInSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRODUCT SHIPS WORLDWIDE GET HERE👉🏿👉🏿👉🏿 https://t.co/Nhsl50eFOF #instadaily#instamood#instapic#love… https://t.co/ghGBHpxFV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Advice of the Day: Show an employer what you can give them, not what they can give you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryceWeiner @adamscrabble To be fair, you had me at time travel. https://t.co/obcMLMWM0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[以賽亞書 33:21-22   Chinese      21 在那裡，耶和華必顯威嚴與我們同在，當做江河寬闊之地。其中必沒有盪槳搖櫓的船來往，也沒有威武的船經過。 22 因為耶和華是審判我們的，耶和華是給我們設律法的，耶和華是我們的王，他必拯救我們。]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffMetalNinja You're an inspiration, bruh. I wanna be like you when I grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was the president.  I'd okay my mom's rent, Free my homies and nem .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigHPrivateEye nahhhh hes too annoying and could actually cause harm. jeb was such a dweeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to make a quick stop for some steak bites that's all I wanted @ IHOP https://t.co/dVCLpkQ3rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Empire” star turned himself in Thursday on the charges of filing a false police report https://t.co/2YcUtQNrQt via @TheWrap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitLove88 @Jhogan552 Roseanne is washed up more than Dog the bounty Hunter and wife Beth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain's stopped. Sun is rising. It's a good time for enjoying a hot, tasty #cuppajoe and to be #nowplaying Michael K… https://t.co/7qOFiniLtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You should end now In politics. You have no life experiences. You have no idea what your talking about. Your j… https://t.co/Tjves8mOBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saprogressive @IlhanMN already getting comments from Dems who simply won’t allow any criticism of Israel. Trump wo… https://t.co/cgAb0BKjrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @EAMaddenNFL,  My only wish for Madden 20 is for you to get rid of the douche bags who go for it every 4th down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/PxKBMsFbzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish i can send u the music im listening toooo... damn the technology]]></document><document><![CDATA[Armchair GMs on #nhltradedeadline be like: #HockeyTwitter https://t.co/KFqEMKOfcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson @KelseaBallerini @BrynnCartelli you ladies killed it tonight. So freaking good. Powerhouses.… https://t.co/YcgmhZvHKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnieBlack2 @HuffPostPol As for facts, the whole thing started with a fake dossier paid for by the Clintons so as… https://t.co/8ehJ7kkiB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinesseCapone If you’ve done it, I done done it before player. Ask the streets if you think I’m Lyin. You got it though, I’m an old nigga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way the man who you're arguing his legacy for sees his legacy is irrelevant?   ......oh...... logical]]></document><document><![CDATA[They always shooting and fighting on St Charles’s during parade season 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillBredderman @LeoGlickman1 @erik_engquist @nypost @AOC I imagine Will speaking in an incredulous Seinfeld voice,… https://t.co/mz5ISNgn0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossTuckerNFL @Steelersdepot @RapSheet @ProFootballTalk PleaseBeTruePleaseBeTruePleaseBeTrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoirMale presents a legendary movie from the producers of milehighmedia / @noirmalexxx  An incredible movie starri… https://t.co/Gkzrj673Fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence If this was a boxing match, Gym Jordan would be Chuck Wepner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wingalesio Estoy en las alitas plaza real Monterrey y me atendió Jessy con un excelente servicio Recomendado!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI Miami has won 7 of the last 10 meetings. 36 years. 3 wins. Florida will forever be Miami’s little brother 😭… https://t.co/IXlOnfswf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go #Findlay. Growing the region and the state. @JobsOhio @deanmonske @daytonregion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I'm in the type of bar that has the unedited version of "Down With the Sickness" playing on the juke box]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to this. I don’t think I’m driving home first thing this morning... 😒 https://t.co/EdkNHLI2Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMtz_16 @kimprobablynot No it was because of a damn fire alarm at 8:15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump That's exactly what I just told the moron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora somos un país arruinado pero potencia militar ! Donde se irá a esconder este psicopata ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realPolitiDiva @UpInTheHills Kinda like “Planned Parenthood”.  It sounds do nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump and Trump Administration have “0” mention of National Women’s day, to late now to try and act like woman matter @MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realtimwilliams One for the team...................!  @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler @kristafrances 2/2 - ...and the fact that Congress isn’t turning up the heat on all the players simul… https://t.co/VIzPyrBdxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start with Congress and Senate payroll! That alone will fund the wall. It was democrats that shut government down!… https://t.co/bffnIUaTuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kloekardashian #blackhistorymonth @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/pvh7O2TjXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been rambling to my Lyft driver about how happy I am to be DONE with Oscars week. I’m 80% sure he doesn’t ca… https://t.co/e7VXgAbiOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tonight ought to be FUN. Drinking right after work (PreGaming) and continuing at Washington Ave! #WilbeTURNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLSUKShow Inchy the master and the crafter. The king of trophies and glories 👑!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayekAndKeynes Trendflowing has not worked - on average - for 10 years.  Not unlike value.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about a rain run? You can't tell if it’s sweat or rain, so you push harder to stay ahead of it! @ Lon… https://t.co/synM3ox1ml]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are temporary, so enjoy the time that you have with them. When they leave, you just have to know that they a… https://t.co/9YdrIY2tCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFroling @brad_tunney @grdrive @ErieBayHawks Some NICE names on those charts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fun Choreographing for these ladies for the movie #WomenIsLoser in San Francisco! You were all so lovely!!! Than… https://t.co/Wffksfpnnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdschade @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump ...The fact is, we are only one group, American Citizens. Republicans don’t… https://t.co/aiD5Iv63O5]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you tell someone something nice because you know what it’s like to feel down and depressed where even the smal… https://t.co/9iFGGGk5n6]]></document></documents></author>