<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@m10penny @CMThot20 @Justinnolankey Congrats!! Well deserved! You have a very bright future!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may or may not have watched one too many pimple videos with my child. #cicisworld #pimplepopping #pimplepopper… https://t.co/74T9eOxn8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the most amazing dog in the world. She is so cute and wonderful. Tweet tweet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of the consignment sale! #oakgrovepreschool #stephsboo #shesmybootoo @ Oak Grove United Methodist Church https://t.co/uZjWodSQdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not bad opening #LSSC but why am I so distracted by your shade of makeup tonight @StephenAtHome ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the crackhead population of caldwell county has increased drastically since the last time i was here in december]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm out on the town now but will catch ya later if I can 👋 have a fun stream man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMBATMANakaBr1 @adnilxa @ivyjofreeman @doctoralexa @ElleWibble @FredMertzReal @JuliaKozuschnik @Grabsback2… https://t.co/R8lZL03ZMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was looking back through old images and I found this one I took in 2016! • • • #milkyway #photography… https://t.co/OsERZOLjPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hah, or not.  No check mark on my badge means “seek alternative viewing options” https://t.co/3MVaF4yUiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna hangout with Jake Gyllenhaal... chat, snack on some gushers. World ends... yes😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fan-girling today all day! #JonasBrothers #JB #InLove https://t.co/szYKb6jkNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also nice to be able hit breakfast after a 12 hour shift with the entire unit. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindness is a gift everyone can afford to give! Let's stand against bullying together! #PinkShirtDay2019… https://t.co/y5adIuWqL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I wanted was to take a road trip this weekend but that doesn’t look like it’s happening 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pat fell asleep on facetime and hearing him snore makes me feel like I’m right next to him again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveweis2001 The headlines are confusing people...this legislation only ends the biannual ritual of turning the c… https://t.co/o6jxm0KN7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEXXinthe_CITY Love this! Your hair is sooo nice! Natural Lexx hits different lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The digital humanist and historian in me is VERY excited by the possibilities of this. Yay for technology making hi… https://t.co/vx3kVJFzYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada @IvankaTrump You know not of what you speak , oh privileged one . As the late great Governor Richar… https://t.co/bEcu4eF2zO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I die please remember me as Emily, a transgender girl who tried her best despite the hatred, discrimination, i… https://t.co/OqQ3WXt4qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We finally remembered to take a picture with all of the 10:30s today at the turn around point for the halves. Ended… https://t.co/zujL4vei87]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN = Crap News Network. Their junk news is not worth reading on their dot com website. Their Twitter news isn’t wo… https://t.co/PuykesKsmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @dtrumpnation @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews I got this sir...I never miss you..Rush..Sean..Tucker..Ingra… https://t.co/khYztc71qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alt_NASA Sitting next to a radio listening for a snow day school closure notification. My Dad was a high school te… https://t.co/GzKeMMW3AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday Eve Balloons from my mom.💖🎉#birthdayeve #almost26 @ Starbucks https://t.co/YyQqkgskUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @DonaldJTrumpJr @BreitbartNews @RealJamesWoods please go and volunteer at the local Senior Center....]]></document><document><![CDATA[a false witness who pours out lies and a person who stirs up conflict in the community. https://t.co/aqUZ0jfnwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femmina This happened a lot as a chaplain!!! And it threw the dynamic off?? Which made me be like, should I stop b… https://t.co/YJEjLv1B5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what, @twitter? When I want to see"Top Tweets" you'll be the first to know... Otherwise, stop changing my settings. Okay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the morning planning for multi-agency grass carp control efforts this summer, then on to Ann Arbor to revi… https://t.co/w6RXRanGJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep to save my life anymore !! 7 months pregnant , can’t get comfortable &amp; I can’t hardly roll over 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article! It's wonderful to hear more about the companies that make Fort Wayne unique!  Thanks,… https://t.co/snyynyBULE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spicy #ramen on a rainy day is the best! ❤️🍜 @ KAITO https://t.co/O7sKZ9cplx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEUonamission @POTUS Trump is mentally ill so nothing he dose should come as a surprise. He is very jealous of Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of Tampa w @amberdurrence all summer long https://t.co/sw7PBTtiLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[BITCH WATCH THE WAY U SCROLL WHEN U ON TWITTER  WHEN LURKING CUZ U MIGHT END UP LIKE SOMEONES TWEET FROM 6384737 YEARS AGO FML]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some entertainment. #humor #snicker #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/WouERpjYMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #SantaMonica, CA #Retail job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: shift supervisor -… https://t.co/9jvTwBm4vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eye_brarian @Target Any successful trip there is one where you spend less than $100.  (I love that nail polish ide… https://t.co/SUx0KXf5WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanklish **making a mental note to ask you which laptop/tablet you think is best when it’s time for me to upgrade**]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 11 thirty central I reach stage 1 of the madness. Gonna do a few laps round the terminal and see what comes up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[interesting that the yesterday movie used james corden instead of graham norton. obv those were the only options bc… https://t.co/0DEfrlD204]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man @OfficialMonstaX means so much to me. Thank you for bringing me so much happiness and some of the greatest frie… https://t.co/SLB3YYkHY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Bd of Elections has already received 10K mail in votes #ChiMayor19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump God bless you Mr President! You teach us how to let evil roll off our backs, as you use the power… https://t.co/fAcyNB2voj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiseFallNick Well, where does he keep putting those sandwiches? His body has no girth. (and yeah, I know he runs a… https://t.co/Hmsp0PbdGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong day tomorrow- currently Men 15th Women 8th Team 11th - know order of events - see you on deck - new black TYR shirt tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson You're not too swift, are you? Judge Ellis didn't say that there was no collusion with Russia. What… https://t.co/oRPmmyDAZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the fact it didn't stop there many were found in dumpsters and dead in boxes yeah I better not be seeing this… https://t.co/fDFBKYKg16]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the park bathroom is cleaner than the @Target restroom ... Great job @cityofcape.  @Target ...😏 we’re waiting... 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieTCouret Unless I think of something, your girls get the hula hoop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for this. I’ve never done financial work with a museum. Interesting...I guess it would be hard to put a valu… https://t.co/jy68Z5vTIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It rained LAST NIGHT and people don’t know how to operate a vehicle all of a sudden]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao y’all niggas with fever blisters got herpes on the low y’all better stop laughing at these comments 👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you drive for Uber or Lyft? Then you’re a small biz owner! Find out about the tax implications at 7:15am from Fr… https://t.co/pYQsZtCvvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney @JohnCornyn I’m glad that they did. That’s what a lot of us want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemini men... you ain’t slick. Y’all the fuckin worst, hard to stay away from because of the challenge, but we all… https://t.co/ROeogsXdBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GUTOFERNANDES33 É sempre assim. Ele ouviu minhas reclamações de lá haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollytheshihtz Have not had snow at all this winter. First day without rain. I thought it was time to build an ark… https://t.co/tJbe8bi4cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "PRODUCT / EVENT DEMONSTRATOR - PART TIME" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about… https://t.co/EEc20kX5Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rationalstoic @NJviDs Yeah, Leafs fans wouldn’t act like this if Matthews walked- sushi row shows up halfway through the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey I am appalled at the language you and Becky are using. My grandchildren play games on my phone and I h… https://t.co/f7a4QzKZun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whignewtons And if we are going to talk about weaponization. Let's chat about arson to repro clinics, bombings, da… https://t.co/MT50LaFTTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a statement on Facebook from JCTA, they say they didn’t cal for a strike, either. The association is concerned “… https://t.co/a5TKcgJUTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz @Brooke_Babineau a bigger deal needs to be made on how inappropriate Mrs. Thomas has been and continu… https://t.co/QXHh0Phj5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[1704 Indians attack Deerfield MA, kill 40, kidnap 100  1708 Slave revolt, Newton, Long Island NY,11 die  1749 1st e… https://t.co/M2ua7wiZ3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ireadthestory @JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr @JerryNadler Damn right! We need Our United States back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Stay outta Texas or our faslrtihg cows will stampede you out of TX...dont mess with Texas cows https://t.co/9gcCm4f4UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched #ICanOnlyImagine for the first time... Lord, I’ve never cried so hard in my life. @mercyme - this is… https://t.co/MPxHmTvl79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for this https://t.co/l1XZzaQXkW 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 @ Bowie High School (Arlington, Texas) https://t.co/9uAWdktgOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always fun to wake up at 3:20 (not as a morning person) and find out that the 4:40am Amtrak that I take to get to w… https://t.co/8EPaJHl8mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up with this tune...🤷🏻‍♀️  Don’t stop. Get it. Get it. _______________ Sporting the best friend bracelet in… https://t.co/y4qY1AFRv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furries:  [Sees post about how a furry got married] *moves on*  [sees post that says “free art”] *spams like button… https://t.co/pdBrvBbt0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro wtf is wrong with me. My grades are not doing super hot and i have no one to blame but myself and honestly im p… https://t.co/RQAGBk1dfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/oFDQlB7x7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew Well @KamalaHarris is with the BEST LIAR of all time... Remember Al Sharpton and Tawana Brawley Ho… https://t.co/YiNDGNeIUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think well of others, you will also speak well of others and to others. From the abundance of the heart the… https://t.co/GUET2u298k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Never voted or would vote for that disgraceful organism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Whiteopal is the new black 🌈 Follow tatsactopiercing for more safe, quality piercings✨ • 🦄Portfolio ||… https://t.co/Uv9g49E4k7]]></document><document><![CDATA[John McCain was a straight up liar. As a former constituent, he never failed to lie to get re-elected. His family a… https://t.co/cMQLcntE6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl is so bi-polar with me. She’ll add me on Facebook or follow me on Instagram and then when I accept her fr… https://t.co/8MSj8XcAwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling scentcy as well now too ❤️🇺🇸🎶☕️☮️ however unable at this time to get to my dashboard bc @ATT suck! https://t.co/Nhbf5b7xys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolegertf @SuStewartAlta @caudillocab @MLiliandx @Enzomillo6 Anda a comer pan !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry I unfollowed u on IG ur story just made me throw up and I never wanna feel like that again !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethiopian Airlines: Flight to Nairobi crashes, killing all 157 on board https://t.co/5SGPGdw2GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday, birthday twin! hope your day is as awesome as you are!! 🥰🎂 @leandra90426791]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseyGrammer Thought you would enjoy this :-) https://t.co/1gn40ZWCOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO , I hope you’ve read this.    Deceit is not the way to gain respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cookiewallace77 @kimisanauthor37 We have a lot of race tension in Oklahoma City. When I moves here a few years ago… https://t.co/QSFoFKUmnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoraBro48052347 @timand2037 I can tell you globally that the world ain't liking us regular citizens but I keep tel… https://t.co/lYLe6EnxzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner So you’re admitting of all the other crimes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GYMObrad Damon Thayer has a gender change bill in waiting for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 hour delay start for @washk12. NO AM kindergarten district wide. @abc4utah https://t.co/943OhVGZv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m late to the party but ‘Americanah’ by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie is very good so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuestro mas sentido pésame a la Familia y Amigos de la Actriz Christian Bach #ChristianBach @ChristianBachtv por su… https://t.co/kGK32DgWVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanieHegenauer @jstmejeff Damn right! I just got one of my Magic gear  orders 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan Thank #ObamaIsEvil strategic placement of refugees to ivertake towns, cities and states.  Ultimate… https://t.co/PC4QWakudK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m terrible at charging my phone lmao once my shit hit 10 percent I take it back off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lxrryxmofo Puppy Look on the Bright Side ...You Didn't Have To Make A Speech 😜 Lol...💞 We Love You Liam 💞 You Don'… https://t.co/ZXKDvstGMK]]></document></documents></author>