<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Shut up https://t.co/grYcZ2YP4b buddy gives a fuck about your opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all the post-Oscar self-congratulations, @ampas needs to address this unforgivable oversight. R. Lee Ermey wa… https://t.co/7joZW2PJy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnDavenportTN @3HL1045 @KaceyMusgraves @theryman Considering you’re smokin’ hot, I’m sure you’ll be able to pull… https://t.co/c3LLlfOp34]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized me at @M_Helton11 both grew up on Michigan football, WWE and Eminem. We gotta talk to our parents a… https://t.co/BeFpXhPp0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wouild like to sign up for my direct email newsletter and sales email fill out the form in the link. All inf… https://t.co/9U7rPQ644F]]></document><document><![CDATA[First snow fun since I have gotten home! @ New London County, Connecticut https://t.co/l8bYIXYtmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a great reminder from #acts19v11_17 Amen @ Tuskegee, Alabama https://t.co/TdNj5gr7vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertwickens @AlexanderRossi Look at that Spoke Count... even your chair is bad ass!  Can’t wait to see you back… https://t.co/VNGUeKxLVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Queens’ own @awkwafina - for posting our @NY1 piece about the @NYBG naming an #Orchid for her for this ye… https://t.co/USENolk5F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So all the times you said there was no payments made at all was also truth??  It's hard to stay up… https://t.co/r4sPJzYaNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! (at @PaneraBread in West Homestead, PA) https://t.co/riR48w3T4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Roger Stone did to a Federal Judge, you couldn't do to a county judge and not be sitting in a cell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom 🤠🤠🤠🤠@PCHdotcom_01   Get These all soon.  DVD Blu Ray Laser Clearner https://t.co/FSubg5YZuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetBenMax @CoreyinNYC @JuanMaBenitez Ya mismo tr caen  mentiroso. Fuera a todos esos lameboca que hacen morir de… https://t.co/kmC5vPtYDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Harrington will now forever be the knee drop snipe I always remember. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[SKT in League of Legends.  Astralis in CS:GO.  OpTic in Call of Duty.  Me in Mario Party.  A dynasty was born in th… https://t.co/mtZ9tcd6eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaithersburg 'Angel Widow' is a fierce supporter of President Trump's wall https://t.co/J8qBuePs3i via @WUSA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigMacCormack @chris_neto #AVTweeps Now they tell me?!? Wish they had this @NSCA_systems #BLC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Good_Lt @politeworkacco1 @Rsho85 @warybear @nypost I’m mad Obama opened the door to Socialism via Communism. This… https://t.co/sLNq4e23rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahnollwilson Thank you for this tip Sarah! If I meet with someone I can bounce through the ideas perfectly and… https://t.co/Iy5GSVkE7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @American2b @MeltingInMarana @TimRam1 @DeniseF78650342 @gator4kb18 @jhudson176 @Michael_me… https://t.co/6be9A19v4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Called in twice both times was over 15 min wait. Then put on hold for over 30 min the second time. Not once did a r… https://t.co/IFdlvSNVe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrettMahoney lol, you have some weight in the industry but only have 290 some following you? People know you are whack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a disgrace to our country. A draft dodging lying racist stealing treasonous disgrace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeehanCarolAnne You might be chastened! No plums for you guys! Do you understand how the “controller” works? 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @lsb and loving @BorisKodjoe and @nicolearip in this context cause they play such mean and difficult chara… https://t.co/fuKVvcJ1wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahead of the March 6 release of the full 2018 trade data, remember: “The trade balance is a poor gauge of whether a… https://t.co/cwbcRNh1Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacedOutRadio @DeepTalkRadio @WQEE99ROCK @kzfxradio @kdunradio @ParanoiaMag Killer show so far brother..sorry cou… https://t.co/Rz6ZfHYJff]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment a photographer tries to take credit for your evolution... boy bye... I’m never the type but when you ma… https://t.co/4a49mt2aB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:40.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMakara thanks for following me. Check  out my website for more information about our products and services.  https://t.co/IjyZqkAAox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jane Miller gives me the lowdown on low #sugar #chocolate from @LilysSweets at #ExpoWest2019 #candy #retail… https://t.co/0wPCcnUJsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DinnerIsServed #RealPho #Pho-filling #Espresso #CarpeCaffeine #MedSchool #Awesome #Amazing #BellyBulge #Beautiful… https://t.co/ge7eWWKX9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not how hard you get hit, it’s how hard you can get hit and keep going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning run.. Have a great Thursday! #fortlauderdale #florida #beachlife #amazingweather @ Galt Ocean Drive, The Be… https://t.co/SOlXeGeeP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #SXSW-ers! If you're in #Austin and in need of city recommendations, Culture Trip is your go-to. Whether you wa… https://t.co/UVeomf5GGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not seen McCowan miss so many shots before like this. #MissSt #Missouri #NCAAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcinTyc W połowie lat 90tych byłem na Kubie i mieli podobny rozkład lotów na lotnisku w Holguin. Patrząc na te f… https://t.co/gzOhKF2dl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/HM7oTopYkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blacksmith Shop 069 Spotted on the grounds of Ringwood Manor in Ringwood, NJ. @ Ringwood Manor https://t.co/dEvWapBG3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t know you could set ur tv to turn off when you turn your xbox off. character development]]></document><document><![CDATA[New AG William Barr MUST act against Deep State treason by McCabe and co-conspirators to save our republic https://t.co/OLsxbVWuW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art #writers #words #artist #passion #expression #thelostart   The lost art of crafting words. A love letter shoul… https://t.co/UIFfz0a4a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GKCdaily “Aside from the art, Rome is Bakersfield in tomato sauce”—Victor Buono]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unlimited Open Training Sessions Monday - Thursday. * Meal plans * 3 additional Fitness Boot Camps per week * Inter… https://t.co/UEMz7Wl2be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting back to Skitters and Glitch with the homie Discipline 99 on some sounds you haven't heard yet, this Tuesday… https://t.co/QICOSOr715]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support anything from Sac that’s of high quality n positivity. I may even support the negative shit out of Sac as… https://t.co/CkzQQXNGyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 2019, it's still legal in America for women to be paid less than men for doing the same work. That inequality i… https://t.co/wwWsmCCQqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamvictoriaangelyn samuelg_official #matzoball #christmaseve #hollywood #2017 #trophies #inittowinit @ The Hollywo… https://t.co/2CYacyb7kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmw_337 @noza_byers Looks at this studs! Feels good to support a winner. Not like our friend here, getting man han… https://t.co/rN0ZckcTlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[World News:     Billionaire Patriots owner Robert Kraft, 77, charged with soliciting prostitute;        New York ha… https://t.co/e742bWShUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoAndretti @marta_andretti Wow you look beautiful. And Marta too. LOL Just kidding. You both look great. Rememb… https://t.co/ZAu5pzfmi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@151Reno @USUBasketball @Call_It_UState Well when SDSU beats Nevada on Saturday USU will be outright champions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emmy Fabry finished with 11 points in Dark team's comeback victory over White.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickySKron @parrotsnbees @LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary Hillary won 317 counties Trump won over 21,000 counties in America really]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Information regarding course selection for 2019-20 will be shared today on @NazEagleVision as well as through Scho… https://t.co/I0TU5wCr7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HFiskJohnson @SCJohnson Plastic problem is certainly of high concern however it is mostly a visual pollution and n… https://t.co/AnCJjzMV5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A toast to the pioneers and innovators that helped make this province’s beer scene what it is today.   https://t.co/fZmFFHUqzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring break day 6 🍹 🍸 ☀️ 🏖 #michigan #fortlauderdalebeach #cityoffortlauderdale #ohio #fortlauderdale #ftl… https://t.co/fG87FpzWTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one kicked my butt this morning while reading Donald Miller’s “Building a StoryBrand”.⠀ ⠀ For a long time, muc… https://t.co/ZIz8zP0kQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU NEED TO DROP THIS!!! PLEASEEEEEEEEE❤️❤️❤️❤️😭😭😭😭 it’s Valentine’s Day you need too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittypunch903 @BaldBryan @adamcarolla The eye infection was hilarious too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Yankees haters are you Ready! @Tony51Martin @VilmaRoman50 @RositaColon17 @maver23 @EndColonial1sm @1503Millie… https://t.co/tV355lXB6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 5 plus Jalen, Obi, Jheri, Dwayne, Jordan, Ryan, Frank &amp; Trey #Sheesh #NCAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2  Had the best fuckin’ birthday last night listening to some of my favorites 😎🤟🏻 I can’t wait until the next con… https://t.co/JS84I8egFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorplus2 @MikeStuchbery_ @tom_watson But here: you no see difference between one man go to house and be watched… https://t.co/VQfIDC05Qy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramiro__torres I know!! And I LITERALLY just... I don’t feed their conversation at all lmao my boss is never aroun… https://t.co/yonA2nHGFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti It's only a peak into his lack of self control.  Imagine it, being a child in his domain....  God help the child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the kind of thing that’ll get you to your breaking point on a bad day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never ever been a fan of Duke.....but Zion and RJ are fun to watch.  Maybe the Knicks can get both of them in the draft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A Mexican environmental activist has been murdered before a referendum on a controversial thermal-electric plant a… https://t.co/yvcf8SV4qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Ququad West Leasing Office in Austin, TX https://t.co/PEii9lw6K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HallowsHaunts @XboxHorrorXtrem @gallyteramed @sluts_guts @sootygrunter79 @AwkwardGothma @jedimasta79… https://t.co/fY6e8um5Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the lakers some how make the playoffs and some how make the finals would that help make Lebron the greatest ever… https://t.co/csvYUlxwiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec That's actually a poster for the consequence of human trafficking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantFelldin @vachilly64 @amvn90210 @RayPoetry @codeofvets @FredDoucetteNH @STUinSD @T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @MalcolmOutLoud… https://t.co/8FqufzoHGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwiens1990 @patr1ckw @Newsweek Nevada is becoming blue because of the mass diversity that exists there. If I’m not… https://t.co/LZP1y4UJis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Dorval Carter, President of the Chicago Transit Authority at the @SharedUseCntr 2019 Summit this morni… https://t.co/1XgbYvLqP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egleegolobato Yap, y los que no la piden, cómo ayudarán?.... solo para saber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Connellybooks "Judge Atticus Finch..." .... Nice.   I expect Breaking news any day about Amazon picking up the Ren… https://t.co/ZMMegqPD0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always an inspirational post by @ArleneDickinson - and such an important reminder of the challenges still faced by… https://t.co/SnD3bCTjb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[High schools a book, college the sequel, life’s a trilogy, for now it’s a mystery]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing. It’s incredible how fast executives (anyone really) will pivot a meeting to fill an unanswered que… https://t.co/IVeyP57PW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr @nascarman_rr I wish they could very least make it like it used to be...The progressive banking ruin the track]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimForgot @EmmettMiche11em Indeed I have and it’s crazy how prophetic he was]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my prof would actually teach the material tested and not ramble on about his kids and other non important things… https://t.co/zFOoqdEbQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @BuzzFeed article (language warning)  is hilarious...and fascinating. How many of us have a different online p… https://t.co/S0KJm3CIP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickelodoole @teri_carr @Veteren1971 @ChrisBragdon @CuriousHobbyist @luvnewinfo @JulieReichwein1 @CaliRN619… https://t.co/SxLfq8vNU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maceyfix @kdbxoxo please just beat the crap out of me with a baseball bat, i just want to feel something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPhil @AmandaCerny Wow Dr Phil, Amanda must be a social media star and not just in her head!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @blacksocialite!  You’re an amazing person. Hope your day is everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @UN Venezuela is becoming the Holodomor of the 21st century... it’s the responsabilty of the world to stop this genocide!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, considering the billions of dollars flowing into sports via TV/internet money, merchandise, ticket re… https://t.co/A5qIUc5v8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nashville 11, GCMS 9 — END 1st Quarter — After getting out to the early lead, Hornets take control to end the first 8 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karleegreyxxx If you was my woman i would suck them and wash them five times a day starting when you wake up every… https://t.co/QRm3OIzhXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Williamsburg, Brooklyn| Marcy Ave and Broadway| NYPD CIS For A Cyclist Struck and Killed By An MTA Bus| @ Brooklyn,… https://t.co/A8kgsu6x0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSSportsDaily @KaleSteed I concur with this!  Unfortunately @KaleSteed you know who I have to deal with here and i… https://t.co/KtT5tos67l]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA Sports Council meeting today.  Beautiful day at Dodger Stadium. @ Dodger Stadium https://t.co/Vbbqz6wICW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marioredondo No es solo falta de voluntad para alcanzar acuerdos. Es también la incapacidad para pensar en grande.… https://t.co/cVfKtX0c45]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/4/2019 - 06:39 Temp: 22.6F   Hum:  63% Wind: 3.0 mph Baro: 30.424in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document></documents></author>