<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Free melly yeah he killed his two best friends but he made good music tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[My reaction after my therapist pinpointed where my anxiety stems from in my childhood: https://t.co/daQP0V3fn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got myself 2 refills of popcorn yesterday, as well as a cookie. @ Disneyland - Theme Park https://t.co/o0g3TEqf6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matcha Latte almond milk. Gave up coffee. #metime @ Swallow Cafe https://t.co/wMr50yQp4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The members of the White Rose are among the most heroic figures of the 20th century. Their resistance was hopelessl… https://t.co/o4MNNHkn2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #US! Something like that #Tatiana in October 1997.... 22 years ago. I had a map, my car 🚗 and radio 📻 . And you… https://t.co/sWU218Eoav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toni9555266 @SlLVERSTACKER @jiveDurkey @KamalaHarris And have Mexico pay for it!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassy_mummy Ha! No way! Thanks for letting me know (I’ll clip it for my mom’s fridge.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electronimity @keithkinnibrugh @GovMLG And if they aren’t law yet anyway then of course I can still buy a gun....… https://t.co/orAVvqT5Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kymztime @guypbenson @BarackObama Guess what? Besides the original intent of the tweet, I also have an old white m… https://t.co/NQZBqZdepJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got flowers, a lil panda, a cute card, and dinner yesterday. Maybe Valentine’s Day ain’t all that bad. 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year’s Big Ten Swimmer of the Championships breaking more records in 2019! #B1GSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland "The immediate world-wide reaction to the initial video led almost everyone to believe that our studen… https://t.co/YuptFrDvsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then they formed a successful Thruple and formed a foundation to save The oceans. Goodnight Goolies thanks for the… https://t.co/EDrXq2Nkbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @GatorWorldParks of Florida in Wildwood, FL https://t.co/Qd3WGQ8XuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just laying in my bed harmlessly smoking a b &amp; Courtney wants to tell “I WISH A BITCH WOULD”  ok no more marijuana for u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from TPC!  Ready to run the Golf course. #rundonna #jaxgalloway #vippinks @ Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/5gaeVFqLyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time I see a friend in a commercial I am like "YAS BB next lunch is on you!!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SquidDespair @politicaljimbo @AOC Falsely informed people are the worst. Keep going with your lame hashtags to try… https://t.co/FnbuZ96mYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews God bless you, President Trump!!!  So thankful for you every day!!!❤️🇺🇸🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelleridge Yes, I know. But people keep talking about it. And it’s annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nem vi as meninas do grupo. a câmera só mostra de longe. não sei se arrasou ou não.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@VP is coming to Columbia tomorrow to visit a movie theater in a low-income area with @SenatorTimScott, a way to t… https://t.co/6LO7IrXIBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCHSChoirs Grrrrrr... I'm assuming you notified admin...any cameras in area that can narrow down the culprit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbaby1908 Mines is too. He just prefers to move in silence. One of his nicknames is Silent Assassin. Quietly makin… https://t.co/wLIovvjNbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 Was the Abe/Trump handshake before or after Abe turned down his request? I'm seeing things in a new light, lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Living” for this teaaa! 😆 Ugh trying to be patient here, but I kinda need new music right meooowwww!… https://t.co/IFXQj2B7kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Pretty sure there is some reverse psychology going on here...trying to boost weed sales for his pal Boehner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's just always something about fountains in malls... #DeadMall #NorthCarolina ⛲✌️ @ Signal Hill Mall https://t.co/SvC6yUMVwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good one Keira 👏😂👏  But if you actually did this, I think you need to work on your aim 🙄  #kidsofinstagram #life… https://t.co/D4wzn8MYtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mathildabee I’ve seen all the programs and listened to the podcast. Well-versed on this one! 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most talented drummers @RobOrtizETF 🥁🎶💯🙌🏻 I can take polaroids of this guy every day and not get bored.… https://t.co/seAEObVCew]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't even know what to say anymore, except I am ashamed of our country. Our society keeps turning out people lik… https://t.co/TGFeiJZfQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @RepCummings @DNC I so love you and Brian Tweeting along the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either my eyes are going bad or everyone has their brights on tonight omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be focusing on the message of this video but slightly consumed by the thrill of seeing @haileybieber rock th… https://t.co/zfV5rjhOws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetsyDeVosED Did this conversation include special education, and ensuring that voucher schools follow laws in pla… https://t.co/TYi5h4v4gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cec021 @nypost @Mets Haha!! Funny! Well Cano was brought up in the @Yankees organization, I thought you had to hav… https://t.co/3MMNFhrqJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoaa_its_joe oh god you should’ve told me yesterday she went to a psychic fair in elyria]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, the apple can fall far from the tree....Kamala Harris' dad says parents are 'turning in their grave' ov… https://t.co/8AkE4drS8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did not defend or fight for our Country one more reason you should RESIGN!!!  Spent more time with… https://t.co/KchNHF6S2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TCU’s lefty, Brandon Williamson has struck out 7 of 8 batters faced in 2.2 IP (credit @wboor)   Follow here:   https://t.co/4JIUltGVWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost It is a major initiative in the labs at John Hopkins Hospital. The key is early detection]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really excited for this month's thefirstfloorwas Final Friday event! Why? Well, where do I start? My amazing n… https://t.co/kVlTMR6LmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being with people that truly want to make a difference in this world one step at a time...that’s all it takes… https://t.co/j3gdAVyWci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @lcblazers we are a Distinguished Project Lead the Way school-2nd year in a row!  What an impact PL… https://t.co/AEt6eLJ67v]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨🌿💜Sooo EXCITED to be here with my awesome team!!! #Hempworx #HempworxRoadshow #Anaheim #HeartCenteredWellness #CBD… https://t.co/iks7Ko4aVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@animalcrossing Here’s to more great things to come. I’ve been having fun with this since it came out. 🥳😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what it’s felt like to get to #FridayFeeling  Also, they just don’t make #slinkies like they used to… https://t.co/JqBCZEbqEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKingFenrir Happy Valentine’s Day everyone 💕😊 https://t.co/RNYD0MViHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wow... I’m SURE you loved it, right?!? I had heard so much about the story, the lyrics, the rapping and the sing… https://t.co/Fj3PnwwMvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StandWithTucker #StandWithTuckerCarlson #IStandWithTucker @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews  https://t.co/IqASUgYxgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beer company's first brew, Melody Maker IPA, a tribute to the Smiths' daughter who was stillborn, will be relea… https://t.co/gsa9UMZHqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in a really good place right now. I’m happy and I have people I care about that care for me in return. That’s all I need💯✊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROP_Doc @GlobalGenesisGp @CrimeAuthor @JasonHarney72 Tv? Really? That's awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimbcbs4 Jim I think it's important show the entire video. I'll see if I can find a link for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm. Subscription furniture? Definitely makes sense for businesses but consumers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for my film to win the @Filmaka #documentary #shortfilm contest on "Gritty Gutsy Women" to inspire and empower… https://t.co/x8e6qSU0OC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“X”, this year’s Valentine Heart in Times Square #NYC #HeartTSq  . Read for more .. https://t.co/eGnCL7nh0C . https://t.co/yHERDbgBNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We decided to do something a little different this year for Valentine’s Day. The Lower Elementary students chose to… https://t.co/ckG1fFpTDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever have baby fever take a flight with like 5 screaming babies. You’ll be cured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[shits gonna hit the fan and blow tf up and quite frankly, I’m so ready for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't let this drop. The media has already dropped it, but we can't. #babymurders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finnelcl @DeirdreReneeNW @CliffPoncier1 @AthleteAlly It already is. With trans women competing with women and trans men with men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Podcast interview with @jedliemagic about my #ChildrensBooks, “Rainbow Crystal” and “Murphy: The Phat Cat” ~ check… https://t.co/gq3gcuAyzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember this song like yesterday. My introduction to East coast hip hop I was in the 7th grade. Here’s a song fo… https://t.co/ue2xr235ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MichaelJackson had mock weddings with his small victims. I'm disgusted at these children's parents. I will forever abhor him and his music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinoskaPerezC hola nino! Podrá hablar en tu programa ! #El alcalde #cubano de Hialeah #presenta carnaval este sába… https://t.co/L91yGDsohC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@will_roland Was lucky enough to see @BeMoreChill last night!!! Good luck with opening night tonight! It was AMAZING!!! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erdayastronaut Good Luck and God Speed. ⭐️You guys are superheroes!👨🏻‍🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 feet apart cause they’re not gay #Nightingale_LA #andresrigal #laurence.s1 https://t.co/qRclcvOERK https://t.co/C1VCIpQsL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating disorders can affect all kinds of bodies and you cannot tell by looking at someone if they have an eating di… https://t.co/s9DRvbCdlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got charged for an @Uber ride that my driver canceled... seriously Uber?? 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[We whacked the ball around. 🏓 Love laughing with these guys. @ Punch Bowl Social Indianapolis https://t.co/xL1lv3QICZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[why everyone keep telling me i’m weird for having a snake :( she’s so nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhigDeskHQ @AviWoolf I have three by my nightstand. One in the bathroom, another in the kitchen... I'm notorious w… https://t.co/ZBZDsgNGXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricGQuintana I’m thoroughly confused. Wouldn’t his technical ability be of benefit in getting out of tight spaces… https://t.co/15ZNlSZWqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/Hw1qIEnIAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a high school counselor also means waiting with your student for AAA because they locked their keys in their… https://t.co/RmgIKeLUog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell @Mikel_Jollett If I want to love someone and have a real bond with them, then I have to understand… https://t.co/AxcRcykMkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLenkov @ngm322 I just did the same thing—it’s the only way I can get my McRoll fix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I moved in: it's so nice to hear the rain on the skylights  Me now: shut the f up I'm trying to sleep here]]></document><document><![CDATA[You knew #OpioidEpidemic was bad here in #Massachusetts, but this bad?? “Opioid-related deaths here roughly 2x the… https://t.co/kGcNQ1OPID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetNorvena @NGDAverk @frostgirl11 @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @hjhollis93… https://t.co/iceTZlUhGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met a view people at #CaES19 who have not heard of the #emailgeeks or the amazing @WomenOfEmail. Say hi to us! https://t.co/PVIeJiIOJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Readathon Day! ❤️📚@RES_RSSS @RES_halexander https://t.co/9EnLPrCega]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep and tomorrow (today) is a travel day. I wish my brain would shut up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selena gathered all the fam who could come (not everyone fit in the pic!) to sup on some delicious middle eastern d… https://t.co/dK7RCeXMjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awful!!! He DOESN’T speak for ME, or other Conservative’s  that SUPPORT LGBT people. Sick! Sick! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me choca tener tan sensible la piel y que por todo se me hagan moretones 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJESSsayin87 I remember when a white neighbor moved in my grandma hood it was weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wouldn’t have finessed the cop with my charm lastnight i would have been in Jail until Tuesday and missed my flight to LA 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kendallmm Yesss! I love my DAD and you! #mykids 💜💙 #familywhoravestogetherHEADBANGSTOGETHER]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we are having our ninety hundredth snow day tomorrow. https://t.co/YHHxaNQQXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mag06687070 @proturnedexvax @Dreadpirate42 @4everleather1 @JackCDLee @Charbrevolution @CplBart @boglethemind… https://t.co/mwrBjr6oiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s Nomination for the Nobel Peace Prize Was Apparently Forged. Twice. https://t.co/O423nIQH8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of NASP Regional Leadership Meetings (RLM) in Atlanta, Georgia! The key to my success during RLM and NASP is… https://t.co/Kjtkx1ufFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I saw them at Way Home I surprised myself by knowing every single word to every song. Only other time that hap… https://t.co/IqftizcO6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Huntie48 @ginger_punk @lexcogis I have never loved three people more than I love you three omg 😭🥰❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wackyvorlon Yep! I got it fixed and all put back together, but now there's some other mysterious problem to figure out]]></document></documents></author>