<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is where trump belongs behind a WALL away from People . . .  #ResistersUnite  #ImpeachTrump  #DumpTheTrump… https://t.co/OBoXBmkzea]]></document><document><![CDATA[this woman is our strength, our light, our motivation, our warrior! I am so proud to be your daughter! i love you t… https://t.co/C2zAL6rTXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[*doing math homework* those were probably supposed to cancel so I’m jus gonna cross em out]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was last year’s birthday... Looks like @SCSUHUSKIES_MH got him the same gift this year! 🏆😁 Happy Birthday, Dad… https://t.co/6c61IDyhA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your love language is donuts and your honey takes you to Asheville to @vortexdoughnuts where my homies saved m… https://t.co/mVCh75RE8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[i reported a cop when i saw one on the freeway and waze let me know that i helped 22 people and this is the greates… https://t.co/PocklRpYSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaMariaAussi @BillOReilly @realDonaldTrump I hope we get the wall. I live in an area w/high illegal population… https://t.co/M0JzYOpXpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you have a child sex trafficker/ child rapist ENABLER in your Cabinet. Why?  HOW in hell can you r… https://t.co/jwjqCJiuJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinARed @BlazeTV @glennbeck @scrowder Wow ... that’s longer than I have ... I discovered him his first week on… https://t.co/PRb50lFsgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booking my weekly eyelash appts up until the end of March gives me some sort of structure for the next couple months #yesigoonceaweek]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Recognize- PND ft Drake  2. Girls Need love- Summer walker  3. Middle Child - J Cole  ....top three tracks that describe my life rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me la he pasado pendejeando todo el día en el trabajo. 😂🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/UpKke5G2ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Congressional Reps just voted on this bill. Click through to see how your reps voted on @Countable https://t.co/1OHDkc7dpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este jueves es perfecto para iniciar con todo en #VivalaviEnEl6 junto a @carofuentes @hugosantos11 @labrillanti… https://t.co/pHumTcTtWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catlien I got my ticket today! Thank you!!! Looking forward to the show! @tusdheideman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haudricourt @Todd_Rosiak have we heard any recent news on Jeffress' progress? Any throwing yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katperkinsmusic @KSTPsteve I thought so.  Thanks for validating....We love you and your talents!  xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela #VenezuelaAidLive #VenezuelaLibre #VenezuelaAidLive #VenezuelaLiveAid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Wow! @abbya_music ‘s “Georgia” just blew me away! #newfan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys. BoschBot is literally the only good thing on this goddamn website.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if St. Valentines drank coffee or tea at least occasionally! He sure is representing that 1%! Lol I’ll drink… https://t.co/CasB4ou2Qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Victori23030640 @spkeller11 @Goss30Goss @realDonaldTrump I served this country during the Vietnam Era.  Also, unle… https://t.co/bQ2m06iI55]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned more about John Locke editing my son’s term paper than I did in my political philosopher class in college. 🤔🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanieDeveny @Kimbchr @DRFWelsch @KPMRacingStable Yes I didn't watch it after I heard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took 30 minutes to drive from SPOT coffee on East Ave to Wegmans on East Ave https://t.co/gA0MCfr9fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDeVaul thanks for snapping the pic with a @NBA legend at #NBAAllStar. https://t.co/VBZDZrAbwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tohstaficionado @ChueysWorld @emmapaygee @ABC Hollyweird will back them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh😌 Heather Meadows and @Kechi you both were so phenomenal! You set the bar so high! I have no idea what I'm goin… https://t.co/ei44yStiR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rocio__1 As a rule, milk shouldn’t be drunk because it contains sugar. I’d recommend unsweetened almond milk but m… https://t.co/V26I8Qc2br]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBridenstine - going to the moon, in a sustainable way, with commercial and international partners. #Moon2Mars @NASASocial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you watch this with me dougy ?? @thetempertrap https://t.co/gbOAHxNlTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottJKyle1 I go riding when i need too reconnect and feel gracious for the beauty around us. Nothing like fresh a… https://t.co/vvIAJSTUnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@columbusairport tonight was second nightmare Sunday in a row with baggage. Last week waited an hour to see a bag.… https://t.co/UBu50rozAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This to me is a threat and it should not be ignored funny how we are supposedly the violent ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews No no no no no. Your society brought this victim fashion into the world. You deal with the consequences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[well @mattel did what I wanted to them to do for a long as I can remember a @barbie with a disability. #barbie60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you like to spend your Thursday night here? #forsale #homesweethome #floridaliving #lovewhereyoulive #remax @… https://t.co/5EdG5onkgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momness1 @cspanwj It's like a disease with them...And The Right has got it bad...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Publicly would like to apologize to my girl @BriannaCudworth for missing her birthday it was a busy day for me I hope it was good tho ❤️🎁🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zoeeeylucas Ugh imy and the fact that we have different spring breaks makes me so mad &lt;///3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s go park somewhere and listen to songs that make us cry” is the ultimate mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmorgan @RIRepublicans Solar City/Elon Musk has a solution that helps everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!! #snowing right now again in #lasvegas #wakeup #strongerthanbefore #cold #coldweather 😱❄️☃️💧❄️☃️❄️ @ Rhodes R… https://t.co/ItcEMqwOBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sit in the office on my lunch to watch the cameras and it’s time for me to go back but I see a line so I’ll just… https://t.co/z67MHCn7OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaLolaRoman It belongs here, for sure. Same thing, different scene. Somehow related]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abates04 @avery16fan @MSL20174 @GypsyRN212 @cabernetfanc @betsyffj @DebsNYGiants69 @SusanKinsella1 @audreyp77… https://t.co/iJsVnT5ONp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I am hoping that he go to jail enough is enough  being nice to a fool always will backfire https://t.co/MjuSHIh7UG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethanyMartino1 @Seesaw @CMolinero181 Every time this pops up on my wall I giggle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when my 1 year old won’t sit still long enough for me to finish her hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hull MA this morning. My little Prius by the fence. Nantasket beach behind my neighbors' houses. https://t.co/5CDLbnqqKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this girl!! Her hard work and dedication definitely has been paying off! Congratulations to American Tw… https://t.co/hNADULDI5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unseen1_unseen I don’t get rich democrats. Why support the party that wants to tax you at 90%?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yDyylan I like many of Imagine Dragons songs. I don't know if I could just choose one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He hasn’t talked to me in two days and now at 2 am he decided to message me WHAT DO I DO DO I TEXT BACK ? Make him wait what 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Me texting my bff about what to text my man who’s not my man* https://t.co/vYwdtWi30U]]></document><document><![CDATA[This drink is on fire 🔥 @ 4 Kahunas Tiki Lounge https://t.co/ju5Gq9sMLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#casamexicosxsw se volaron la barda!!! Loved it congrats to all the amazing team &amp; staff #extraordinary… https://t.co/NwtBbDuTTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone having a tough week...I understand and it’s almost over. #SpreadPositivity]]></document><document><![CDATA[now when I was solving this in the audience, I 4D-chess'd myself into a pickle 🤦🏻‍♀️ I thought it was referring to… https://t.co/78xmPGZAnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! Fuck you! @rogerwaters is awesome, and the true voice of Pink Floyd! You're nothing! Bye Felicia! 🖕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThyResurrection Oh trust me I believe the Bible teaches that woman shouldn’t teach men in the church, that doesn’t… https://t.co/p1Xf9tzx7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping #ThankYou to all… https://t.co/MTMjAJGVoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonESawa on the news. It's happened. All I needed was the picture and my mind went there. 🌲🌲🚛🛣⚰ https://t.co/0Qal7Kd7ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maher is the perfect example of the difference between populist, principled Democrats, and arrogant, elitist Democr… https://t.co/g72Bf2xyjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving up can be self-love too.  Repost @atribecalledsis ・・・ 2:5 https://t.co/Ix8axNrXp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’ve never talked, aren’t on good terms, or you’ve literally just have heard of my name do NOT use me as a refe… https://t.co/gmzEfUfvlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ate a 200mg edible &amp; I'm currently waiting for it to kick in.. 👀👌 God help us all lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of when I took Izzie to the zoo and she shivered when looking at... https://t.co/EjoXzdcJ42]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so happy for you! What an amazing thing...and so deserving. It is a effing  awesome show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready on time for once!   ... ok I had a head start since Alex took a nap 😅 https://t.co/L4SVIpOjXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out there is a comic con event going on today in the same venue as our robotics competition. Space characters… https://t.co/A9YHTBjnZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be forgetting that what you like pops up on our feeds. Y’all nasty 😰 I ain’t need to see all that 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this!  Dog’s name was apparently Duff.  @vregalmacduff delighted with this coincidence. ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaconBit22 @jeffgreer_ There's really no need to be so condescending. I was in a hurry and made a mistake. I admit… https://t.co/idUh6CjiQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much!!! I’ll be back on my regular shift tomorrow. Hope you are having a terrific weekend, Joe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rain stopped just in time for a quick afternoon 5K! Cheers to better weather!🙌🏽 #CLT #queencity #runners… https://t.co/mnhMz6Seg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeithSmall So stop bring her up. Meghan is a social climber, and is putting on a show. However Karma will be her d… https://t.co/h2ZMEm93Y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st Tournament of 6th Grade year and a Championship Game!! 2nd place and feeling great! #ladycards #onceacard @ Haw… https://t.co/SzniL1eDG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz So you’re telling me flattery is not a foreign policy strategy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Manistee, MI? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/FeJMtn1PPZ #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Interim C… https://t.co/RQ3iOYR891]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister How can republicans and Trump supporters think this is ok. What has become of this country??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we need a shift in perspective. Indeed.@NetPromoterSys @FredReichheld @TRGArts]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again Beautiful Crazy is my FAVORITE song and one day I’ll be able to sit and l… https://t.co/eIYPf3yo2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the golden days.. 🦋 ✨ . . . .  #goldenhour #selfiesunday #naturalmakeup #rednails #beckiejoon @ Huntingto… https://t.co/wawwN4O358]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Cohen has nothing left, nothing to lose and no reason to lie. Remember; Sammy “The Bull” worked for John Gotti… https://t.co/NGZok4MLHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the Oscar winners but especially the Marriott Bonvoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking towards the @HunterMuseum from the Walnut Street Bridge in @Chattanooga  #Chattanooga #Tennessee… https://t.co/njpzive8Of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colton @kristisunshine3 Colton if I could have my chance with you,I’d get you all the chipotle you wanted. I’d be… https://t.co/nubS0UeN8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickycarruth Yes. I see some agents advising yet they haven't had many sales under their belt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Single serving yogurt/side combos have an improper yogurt to side ratio and there is always leftover plain yogurt a… https://t.co/7fq9A3WdbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[ojalá por lo menos que me lleve la muerte para no verte tanto, para no verte siempre en todos los segundos, en todas las visiones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJTitong #breastcancerawareness .collateral damage - "you look ok, let's act it didn't happen" - BUT nothing is th… https://t.co/rYd64fJjLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRipkowski I started watching the Santa Clarita Diet. It’s really STUPID lol but I can’t stop watching it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio “Why Don’t We” by @AustinMahone can’t get enough 🤪🤩 https://t.co/3BXZjqzUEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith is the currency of Heaven. The most powerful resource as a believer ~ @bwhorne @nccfamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForUsNaturals @katiet121 Ah yes to be sure the world is shaking their heads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsWordBMS I live right in that area if you just send me a direct message I can get a time and place from ya to pick up anything you have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlie_adler @TalbertSwan @BrianPaulStuart Just don’t take a knee during my National Anthem &amp; we’ll be ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rusty_pharris @realDonaldTrump Central Park 5, housing discrimination shit hole countries...]]></document></documents></author>