<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I can't wait for season 3 of the @TheGiftedonFOX I loved the Age of Apocalypse Blink cameo @jamiechung1 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got out of class and called cindy to see if she wanted to come over and eat chick fil a and i get to my car and s… https://t.co/slMJLunKFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow - just wow.    The @TorontoStar says Wilson-Raybound could not work in Parliament because she had native backgr… https://t.co/FFCMHAdtlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewAlanJames @ejokiller @EpicRecords You know why it feels faster ? because it’s not happening at all,artist ar… https://t.co/ZTpT0JqBOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tania_con_i Y les echas pedos y se hacen los dignos. Pinches princesos susceptibles!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaNCPA @GlenBirnbaum @WKTAAUS Tat make sense to me and was one reason I didn't want any software changes before this tax busy season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I negotiate with food terrorist , these country folks can cook !! #existtwolive @ Rose's Noodles, Dumplings and Swe… https://t.co/JfrnhMNNWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night @birdlandjazz was 🔥. Thrilled to be a guest of the incredible #SusieMosher and her #TheLineup. So. Much.… https://t.co/nAmaXqkDLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Certified_TonyG Did u see Gus on that one?  OMG, he skated away from the play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMelissa sooo you already had another thing lined up and Justin was a pawn for a free steak. Poor Justin]]></document><document><![CDATA[motherhood is so rewarding &lt;3 @ Loyola Marymount University https://t.co/CoEaSL1QF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JK4D7 For some reason I thought of this Always Sunny clip after seeing your tweet:  https://t.co/BFW4ZGw5F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cincywx Ohio River may once again approach, if not exceed minor flood stage per latest forecast from @NWSOHRFC --… https://t.co/L2PcsdSxHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccaffreyr3 And he dares compare his work habits to Lincoln, FDR and others. Time awake is not time working. He la… https://t.co/bNRvQtVMb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray you’re wrong, but I fear we’re living on borrowed time. Had Pres Trump not won the election.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie, I wanna know how much of the overall budget was spent on WETA animating Pogo cuz that was ridiculous @TheUmbrellaAcad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than the "big kids" hanging with elementary kids.  Thanks to the PTO for inviting us to family game… https://t.co/dOLqRwM8wT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx to an all star author group @CMichaelGibson @rwyeh @DrTimKinnaird @TarekOmarNafee @dr_mosama @DrHBulluck… https://t.co/9RUxxrq5Kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey  you fucking idiot.. tax cuts for who??   THE RICH  ! while the middle class have to pay more… https://t.co/uIAUOuukC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MQdcYQ0Dc9 It about time for a New Game !! Sincerely yours Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to love Tomatoes. 🍅👍❤️ . . #thursday #thursdaymorning #thursdaythoughts #tomatoes #funnysigns #producer… https://t.co/HLOoEr6kBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeking an edge, U.S. landlords turn to tenant experience apps https://t.co/LqTP3CmznC]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a serious note I totally can relate to this woman cause lately all I’ve felt was love because of YOU! Thank You… https://t.co/oSW4k0jnom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of overblown negativity about Home Depot this morning. In my view, it remains a solid retail player with good… https://t.co/CQRnPbJ2jR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNODC @YuryFedotov @UNODC_HIV Marijuana is my healthcare and I am not a criminal! 70 gram Medical Exemption at por… https://t.co/WQ38CHrIiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has been six months since we moved from #STL and have missed Bennett working out with michaelmesser30 and… https://t.co/YdWe7Ix2ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:56.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mind is all over the place but at the same time, it’s all coming into place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Haven’t Worked Out In A Year Or More, No Physical Activity At All Really. My Body Feel Like It. Thank God I Eat Somewhat Decent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spotted at @701Whaley (an occasional series): @SethRoseSC  @terracio4rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nike Demand Planner @jmodahl came back and spoke at his alma mater today! Great message and passionate presentation… https://t.co/DGXuZNe99w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TueyRankin @TraelRobertson @Frenship_Track @RandyRosetta He ran the 200m and the 4x4.  Blessing to just be healthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE 10:47 AM February 26 weather: Sheldon Pool, City of Eugene and  Echo Hollow Pool, City of Eugene will open a… https://t.co/fb6j8HqQWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absurd. Many 16 year olds haven’t taken an American Government or Economics class. Most could not simply de… https://t.co/Bd2O8W44Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for softball season? #softball #shaunjones #sj #sjrealestateteam #team #success #sponsorship… https://t.co/PkK0eEWfpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mercedes and Sunset with someone special @ Malibu, California https://t.co/Qytss14xF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Dakota was even colder but it was just considered baseline there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMarino @AmyGDalaMD @GoodishIntent I'm sorry we are still in the development phase so that information is prote… https://t.co/TuSLE1smrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class got cancelled tonight and it’s been a long week 😵🥴🤮. Time to shoot some hoops 🏀 and work off the two Shopper’… https://t.co/mXrAewDJAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[if fans have to endure like a minute long bear hug thank you have to sell or go to prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerryhenz @apeirophobic @AlbertaCarlotta @RealSaavedra The so-called state capitalism systems are really “extracti… https://t.co/Ax9XCtcwaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Case H #StarWars #hotwheels  spotted @justinlasalata @CollectCantina @ImpHolocron @FLYGUY @FanthaTracks… https://t.co/NK66LTtEpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schenley34 @4funswimbikerun @MapwifeJodi @TucsonVoice28 @sabine_durden @Acosta They are all so proud, yet remain f… https://t.co/XXk943RUfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good finish to the week for RMF Echo, 2nd place in the FEI CSI5*$72,000 CaptiveOne Advisors 1.50m Classic… https://t.co/uCijcS0ptv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lscreeden Watching at home, losing my mind. The first truly great sports moment I remember.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one :   @PlayoffDWade  : D.Wade Is the only player in NBA history to average 22.1 , 4.7 , 5.4 in his career whil… https://t.co/mlzWjlKPkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell y’all ima start dressing even more cute y’all better believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend and favourite person in the whole world told me he loved me Happy Valentine’s Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkinXbox @Stargamer_space I had only played the first level all the way back in 2016 on the fat One. Now with my… https://t.co/bg4YN8422t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerySpeaks @OUGrizzGang It’s a commuting college, like U of D, Wayne State, etc. If I have nothing to do and I had… https://t.co/mxf5fmlNrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex It would be the very first time in history that reparations were given to the descendants of people harmed… https://t.co/hk52mLFEC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Kingsley as Trevor Slattery during the big reveal is insane/awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndresVelasqz que mas paro que este del fallo electrico, @AndresVelasqz ? Ellos son los que estan precipitando todo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Job well done from @NTHS_Titans performance art department ending the week at NTHS Black History Month Performance… https://t.co/X7OmJJnWHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study in Color and Lighting. 🎨 . . . levis  @pacsun  @castingnetworks Make Art Every Day. 📷 . . . #Chicago… https://t.co/chdkV5CnDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought @RealGDT was wonderful at the Oscars. He was ill and still made it to present the best Director. Good Going !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalterK103 I'm just shy of one thousand followers but that's very good advice. Thanks for reminding us all to think before we post]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValidGarry @CoreyStewartVA @realDonaldTrump She's always been unpopular with liberals, ever since she flew the Con… https://t.co/6VZw1EEqJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owillis She’s wrong, in the majority of cases you can change a person’s behaviour by using a carrot and/or a stick… https://t.co/aJit4vGLqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franky Medina in the hole on Mat 10. Wrestling for fifth place. #ArrowsUp @RHS_sports @cecil_joyce @WGNSSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Make Magic ✨ New Headshot 📷 @JamaalDM @ Hollywood https://t.co/mcMggqSj37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@l_tucc Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caro_milanesi Side-eye skepticism is warranted. Facebook’s only hope of restoring confidence is by delivering. Eve… https://t.co/n1AfHLC9Mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[World News:     Brexit backers to U.K. prime minister: Don't delay;     Video shows U.S. cop on car hood firing at… https://t.co/5IxL5N2qlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano When police tell you to do something, Just Do It! Something tells me this honor roll student that wa… https://t.co/hHrFfxvgzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[3% scale model of XB-70 ‘Valkyrie’ Mach 3+ aircraft tested at NASA Ames https://t.co/YT4OHdFsQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting this evening planning for my time with @miltonhershey in the next couple of weeks!  This is one of my favor… https://t.co/cV8JtQX71h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Borrowed from @cfottawa... I think this genius! #DaylightSavingsTime #GlassHalfFull #ByeWinter https://t.co/8K0xMqGeA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KDanaeM Well you know I want that pwussy on my face so I assumed 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all be by y’all phones bothered, shaking in anger and allat cause u ain’t heard from ya boo all day. bitch text o… https://t.co/MLj3sXEJd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to a playlist one of my old friends made me and now ya boy sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending the day on a high note with the boys @Wager_JYNX @CODwitty   @PlayApex  Main Bangalore 539 kills 130,234 damage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching @SpidersWebMovie #thegirlinthespidersweb I’m so  #clairefoy right now! https://t.co/vz24qgDcof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjfisher72 As Napoleon once said - never interrupt your enemy when he is in the process of making a mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuskManiac @Jimebs20 People should watch more college basketball. Rarely is the longer possession 'quality'. They… https://t.co/3kNbGErmuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insuRestaurants I would hope so. I know that works for them but I would love to see pitchers marry one style more… https://t.co/tlCYCqPH1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RetroSundayGaming Konami needs to bring back #ZombiesAteMyNeighbors https://t.co/1hz6gAzW6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @katiepro23 @KatieLinendoll @CarrieKeagan @carrieanninaba @bonniemcfarlane @Crapgame13 @torreymspears @Lord_Gow… https://t.co/YTH8IJd7pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know the real story of what’s going on with Bryce Harper and the Phillies? I got it last night. You’ll get… https://t.co/XbogETXoM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newyscruggs @NBCDFWSports Just some thoughts. I feel they should be able to profit off their likeness. $50 for an… https://t.co/zCfBhWdLPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 3rd and a 5th? @steelers your organization is trash for letting this happen! I've been a Steelers fan my whole li… https://t.co/oRzvfYk1G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNBooger Not unpopular just your bout the only one with this opinion 😂👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denverpost We also elected Ken Buck to Congress. Sorry, Colorado. https://t.co/tvyxNsjxHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were evil, and had a hand in building the Hayabusa that just touched down on the Ryuga Asteroid, I’d use it to… https://t.co/0rxrXpovqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine paying hundreds of dollars to go to the beach for spring break, to just go sit in the cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sara51892631 If you don’t enjoy bible studies don’t attend. What is wrong with these dopes??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most truck stops understand: Castor Oil is a great way to call Grandma.  @billmaher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseNBCBoston Good BREEZY morning Denise! Winds have subsided but are still "busy" out there! Stoneham OBS at 5:… https://t.co/H59KXPljHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[New song [sunflower serenade] out now on SoundCloud and bandlab #music #Originalmusic #SoundCloud #BandLab #indie https://t.co/5pKwkj9CDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga ain’t tweet in months and this the first thing he say. I had a gift card try again lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgshepherdvan There are things don’t like, but he resonates with my age group..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what is your big plan? C- keep going, do more with what I make, finish school, draft every month, get organized… https://t.co/opAmsSrIt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was really taken by surprise #backstreetboys #karaoke #iwantitthatway @ Roundup Saloon, Lafayette, CA https://t.co/hi0d1IMlfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the headings in my sermon for tomorrow at churchnbethesda. #LOL #BethesdaDrift @ Church in Bethesda https://t.co/SVZuYEU4Rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm often asked, what sets me apart? Well, in my opinion consistancy, and you get variety on many levels. I don't a… https://t.co/fmu0zBTxhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom swears Baiamonte is saying FUCKINNNNNN WADEEEEEEE instead of DWYANEEEEEEE WADEEEEEE and I am deceased]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would I do without @holliesmiles telling me I need to wear a winter coat when it's 20° outside with a wind chi… https://t.co/HVvKITqoLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horowitz39 She forgot to mention it's a Kennel of Rich Men's Dogs. Wholly owned rich mens mouth pieces who exist t… https://t.co/kCzd0AOjB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth She is losing it! Good. Like how long until she is beat up at 2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got a hot take. JA Morant is going to be a bust like former Murray State legend Cameron Payne. Those guys just never pan out]]></document></documents></author>