<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TammyBr64310863 @Golf_4Life @realDonaldTrump 😂😂😂 another one who knows me so well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkline56 @currie14_kelly @Stephen57036680 @tsmcgee1 @Qrealmsmfake @roddy202620 @SealeyGerald @SnakePlisken10… https://t.co/r9C00svCSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I have children I tell my cats to calm down at least 10 times a night 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauragduvall @kiyamonnai @GetFlickkmyBic_ Not at all.  Introducing and demonstrating the power of a gun is good fo… https://t.co/5LOi1RZhkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rambo loves watching the fights #frenchbulldog #Frenchie #mma #ESPN1  #ufcfightnight @ufc @espnmma @espn https://t.co/BMLEUDx8qL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never expected to become emotional watching this comeback stage. From the intro video package, to the boys standi… https://t.co/2rpo13wGk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liprap @KevinAllman @AynW @christylorio @TPrice504 @NewsCarolyn Holy moly guacamole how did I miss that?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why lie? @realDonaldTrump  @PressSec @IvankaTrump @jaredkushner  @RepMarkMeadows  @LindseyGrahamSC  @SenateGOP… https://t.co/GZ1zOXqWYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burialstan Buy a full weed themed outfit including accessories I’m begging you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlindPebbles @Tonithecat32 @1gingerbeauty @AngusMcPussPuss @deborah26449389 @buddy_gizmo @Cleo_sMommy @EricaGoss… https://t.co/G7q9OjC4hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was a good fucking night. Risks were made and I’ll never regret it @Abbeypena98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold day spent getting printable data sheets ready to go up on the website!  Now... if I could stop getting distrac… https://t.co/yl76XK9mYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t agree more. Apparently our higher education system is completely broken. Where did free speech on colleg… https://t.co/WxiRGsAfLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet class of 2020 senior Model, Shelby. Shelby attends Warren Central High School where she is in Student council,… https://t.co/cF8PXIsR1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you registered???? Would love for you to join our team (“tylerstrong”) and see you there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep @ 730 and woke up @ 2a to get ready for my interview....   my interview is not until 8am 😲#prep]]></document><document><![CDATA[A really special guy   #illustration #watercolor #ink #watercolor #painting #illustrators #moonkat #Drawing… https://t.co/Ce8pNf3Xll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bumpin @KalinWhite is always a good idea. Plus I was feelin myself 😋 https://t.co/7Jz1ZHuwul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryandDavid will my oranges arrive in fresh condition? They are in transit for over a week according to the tracking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz When you have low self esteem, you make sure others know you are praised. When you are confident in your… https://t.co/5uU9tKI8TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@americanair I may only have 24 followers (twice the 12 dollars you gave me for dinner) but I have a degree in tech… https://t.co/UurDWI3TPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Too moderate. Or too bland Maybe Biden/Harris. Not as centrist. I see more chemistry there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghastly_Spec @DisneyDude3 Anyone can afford AP! Nothing special much less exclusive about AP 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleynmitchell People making a cool $260K for one task can eat a lot of 💩#CohenTestimoney #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police: Two brothers told investigators they paid by Jussie Smollett stage attack https://t.co/DZkEBahEWN MY MY! WH… https://t.co/y3DZJA82xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt BAMBI saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea Gender: Male To adopt BAMBI ➡️… https://t.co/AeEUuwsjsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Events transpire in less than a week! Industry Showcase, yes please! March 11th @ 2pm and 6:30pm! Frozen Chocolatte… https://t.co/LphRDdiemk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Like for a tbh and rate from me and my bff :) &lt;3” https://t.co/2tWg9ix5o5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #IWDay #InternationalWomensDay  #DiaInternacionalDeLaMujer a @TataCalde no solo por ser una luchadora, si no… https://t.co/gfeHU4N26t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @SimySemsem @angieservellon_ @consuiglesias @mich_onelove @TereOrt51687394 @Viviane6677 @Alcioni5… https://t.co/3AsWNAQmE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[all these side girls finna be upset they ain’t getting no attention tomorrow and i’m here all for it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @FriendsofOI my hubby and I are traveling exclusively to Canada for our 10-yr anniversary in June, and all tick… https://t.co/sISAJX9IF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @GOPLeader Your President says supremacist are fine people, really! You have no room to say shit about any… https://t.co/M8dPG4ikhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost 5am &amp; I don’t know whether I should even go to sleep anymore or just stay up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi yes @reileendavid is the most precious girl ever and I adore her. #babe #beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M4LAHIERBA @JulioMoranW @ilveten @HistoriaEnFotos Entonces según tu punto de vista nadie tiene derecho a ser nombr… https://t.co/yUOKxz0ZpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannottttt wait for the day I have a baby so I can throw a piece of cheese on it’s face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it really midterms week if I don’t hysterically laugh and cry at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Srslyomgwtfbro Kelly Clarkson sang that song when she was in Dallas. If I could love her more I would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao ya’ll remember when i actually liked guys? hahahahhahahha shame on me, right? 😂😭😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeAdamOnAir what are your favorite songs on @juliamichaels #innermonologuepart1 ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsudailynews @BallStateMVB @lewismvb @RamblersMVB @GoMasonMVB Wish you guys would come back to SIU Carbondale.  I… https://t.co/Jz3uQG91l8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlythSeeker @CaptainsLogAz @dobermankintch @BrookeMorenso @2017Gamora @romanticskeptc @VoldemortsCat_… https://t.co/wUYC02ptkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA Michael Cohen reveals Trump’s dark secret: He thinks Americans are suckers | Will Bunch… https://t.co/yhN7wiTdlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a Birthday kinda morning! I’m feeling the love 💕🧁🎈@949WQMX #ScottAndSarah https://t.co/tHTcPjxkZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[hennabyfarrahg is killing it with our Lubrandao Henna! Are you giving your clients the Red Carpet treatment? repost… https://t.co/E5Zagk4yUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier So what, America does not want socialism. We will fight back. The Trump Train is ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachV79 @CardinalDolan Thank You Cardinal Dolan for reminding of us this great Saint we can exemplify]]></document><document><![CDATA[La noche de anoche 😍😍😍 @julioiglesias #Abrazame #MiFavorita #ConEstaLloro 💝💝💝 @ Fantasy Springs Special Events Cent… https://t.co/2AxfGnkrk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherylUW @AKupsh @ewags76 We love playing your team. A-train is a shining example of a pure athlete and friend ❤️ like you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northport Pipe and Drum Band - Bay Shore Brightwaters St Patrick’s Day Parade ☘️🥁 #pipeanddrum #pipeanddrumband… https://t.co/azALerD6QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewOldCharlie Nah, if it was you - you would have done or tried something perverted! This guy was a gentleman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @AndrewCVasquez for never failing to be my biggest cheerleader. Thanks for supporting me even when I’m… https://t.co/YnVKXSZsR0]]></document><document><![CDATA['Never knew I could feel like this Like I´ve never seen the sky before I want to vanish inside your kiss Every day… https://t.co/yABhyEPfG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me la explota cuando voy a los restaurantes sola y pido una mesa para 1 y me preguntan mil veces “para dos?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPElem @MrsCrabtree6th A mothers love, being able to identify one of your kids by the back of their head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MFW at the age of 60 @SnoopDogg will be 420 in dog years. #high #ThoughtOfTheDay https://t.co/lR5kubzziL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse I hope your golf game goes better than your attempt to sound out the big words in the New York Times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKalenAllen Thank you so much for a great night of inspiration! Can’t wait to connect with you soon ✨✨ #TUtakesLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a lot of parents that don’t want their babies to be vaccinated.. This one time I sneezed and this mom freak… https://t.co/fMeXy0dIgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCMOclub So much fun! Thanks to @TheCMOclub for letting me show everyone around the 1st day of  @SXSW19!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Does that mean we won’t have to look at or listen to you? Now that’s what I call winning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge fan of fried intestines now thanks to gopchangbbq Beautiful array of intestines cooked at the table are oh so… https://t.co/mmWBpqqs1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ssk8kayaking @SSK8Tampa @CCopeland01 @cangeletti49 https://t.co/8BSOb2kqJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curlyygirlly @netflix Hahahahahahaha. I’m glad you know ima call your ass out😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for #Shadowhunters! I’m ready to die lol! #SaveShadowhunters https://t.co/Yalpv0Fy5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hazel_River12 @dokta_foth @cinbashaw @akach5 @ecclesias @FredFriendly7 @jeannefisher17 @elias_julie @AugrEdmonton… https://t.co/kDu2ivFuqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX @JeffGordonWeb @amsupdates @TeamHendrick @TeamChevy @NASCAR Can you talk about that loss to Kevin Harvick for his first win?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally had a chance to watch this and I neeeed sword-fighting Anna in my LIFE 😍😍😍  Also, the animation is drop dea… https://t.co/3ICRty0bQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was fortunate enough to see Brody at Oddball I’m Dallas. He was the host for the side stage of mostly local comedia… https://t.co/cyJMAnqSId]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏍Con Sue Photography and Design🏍  🏍Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏍  🏍These designs were created by: Connie Wheele… https://t.co/KCHrtJwMuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrietFuchs1 @FLOTUS @NatlGovsAssoc @POTUS @WhiteHouse And how many languages do you speak?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Valentine’s Day Patrick sent me an edible arrangement and the note said “thanks for letting me be your side piece”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barkingdero @Hyper_RPG @Frankly_Emily @jessicaverdi @AlizaPearl @zaceubank I have a weird relationship with centau… https://t.co/IC2JCMqIHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great furnished rental 1/1 plus den 2nd bedroom walking distance to Bay Harbor Shops. Message me for more info… https://t.co/IWScvUDJHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This checker has to stop to talk and use her hands. She needs to be using her hands to ring up those damn groceries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's humor all around us. #comedy #lol #smirk #comic https://t.co/WDI1wPcCFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigdaddykfc @NBA @ESPNNBA @espn @russwest44 @okcthunder @Tjonesonthenba 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sara_Y_Yousif @YasserEljuboori سؤال: يكولون الطفل يجي وياه رزقه. شنو رأيك بالموضوع؟ 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poppa's tattoo on his chest is finished. #inkredibleart #inkredibleartAdam #tattooshopsmithville… https://t.co/Hbv4hZ1Jmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APA @APA_Journals This is great because many people believe that they only need to sleep to be energized. It’s more than that! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest Born night person here.  I cannot even sleeps days since 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJMasks When you have EVIL Plans and it considers stealing the SUPERMOON2019. #LUNAGIRL #OWLETTE #GECKO #CATBOY… https://t.co/KHuQJvDQ1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blockchain: Learn what’s happening in NEO March 5–Entrepreneurship Series: Blockchain Technology at Hudson Library… https://t.co/ss4cvfbi5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another “warm” day to get out for a run!  @turtlegloves #turtleglovesbr #bibchat #bibravepro #pregnantrunner  Futur… https://t.co/DWjL2dPqbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MusicMakesMeFeel #WeAllBleedtheSame #JeremiahLloydHarmon #AlmostHeaven #GentleGinger #FeelThis https://t.co/yq4vdbOQNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome To LA #BryceHarper AKA #HollywoodHarper @bharper3407 @kayyharper8 @dodgers @magicjohnson @bryanharper45 @ C… https://t.co/QrWjljFNY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you even shave your legs and everything but he falls asleep every time before we cuddle🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 63 years old and I have never seen a President be attacked as much as our President Trump.  The Socialist Demo… https://t.co/DgkgfJitdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudes be havin your number but hit you up on snap just so they can see if you’re really ignoring them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Οταν λέω στον γιο μου... "το μισώ οταν το πρωι με κανεις και τρέχω σαν τον Βέγγο"! Εντωμεταξύ δεν εχει ιδέα το παιδί ποιος είναι ο Βέγγος 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte NC Sat Feb 16th AM Forecast: TODAY Rain Hi 55 TONIGHT Chance Of Rain Lo 39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeTheChange800 I will always be here for you. Thank you sister. I'm drinking for 16 hrs now, gotta be honest, we c… https://t.co/vaRi9PSwvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/bWAxv3F9B2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbsballard @timwells51 @viclorette @cormac114 @thefr0g @maybrick350 @IlhanMN Everyone should really study more abo… https://t.co/YSAprN0GAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polskawruinie2 @lis_tomasz Trumna ci nie pasuje czy kwiaty, pustaku?...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the learning continues...Day 2: Alycea Ungaro’s #realpilatesteachertraining Program — Beginner Seminar 💦💪🏻💯🙌🏻🔥… https://t.co/AfBrKcANP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhhhhhhh!!!! This is not a drill the @jonasbrothers are back and this song is amazing!!! On loop from here on out!… https://t.co/PVXDchZylG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of the Peter rabbit movie! #lol #yeagerlife #yeagerlifekids #peterrabbit #lilmissyeager #xoxo #winkwink… https://t.co/JizRizQPeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/GFq13xNcBO]]></document></documents></author>