<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Pirates pitchers seem to be more worried about the runners on base then the guy at the plate. Playing one of the be… https://t.co/KqrtCx6cIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby, 1. i am @marchmadness  2. Go Cubs 3. it's been known that i love girls from the Midwest a ton! ΠΒΦ, ΔΖ 😇🐢😍💕… https://t.co/2YWPV3EALT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoolCaelLee Wild sensitive. Shits trash. Everything is offensive now 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biscayno @UniNoticias Eres un total racista , así suena tu comentario... y este país no necesita basura racista co… https://t.co/dk6dTAkntf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you stopped eating trash you wouldn’t have to go kill yourself in the gym.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so rude that apple Face ID doesn’t recognize me with sunglasses on]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's been been cynical, incorrect assumptions about average tax refunds this year, that relied on very early dat… https://t.co/Tr7Wlt1fCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lons @_willthompson Also, I don’t want you two to worry: I GOT https://t.co/i93aKAstIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Still confusing racism and Nationalism...? Look them up, lazy slimers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earlflynn @TalbertSwan Again, you don’t understand because you don’t have my white privilege.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video: https://t.co/IOo6XfsF7H.    #asilomar #pacificgrove #surfing #surfers #beach #avocet #plover #beach #waves @… https://t.co/u5pIHYJqnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother lost his life, it turned me to a beast... I been through the storm and it turned me to a G. #wings… https://t.co/xSphUc9fli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who cares. Destiny 2 Season of the Drifter is bringing highly requested Gambit changes plus shotgun and One-Eyed Ma… https://t.co/UErkTyiZJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesLukach @Cents_Baseball @LBDirtbags Can he get eligible by tomorrow’s game lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the GOP is just embarrassing fascism out in the open now huh? My Grandad didn’t fight the Nazis and the Fascismo… https://t.co/pDmmUahOQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danieltheratkin @HellboyRandom @artofmmignola That's it, that's the context. It's a great story in a great book, I… https://t.co/HTDQcUVIIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hwallace87 I’m serious though. There were 20 ways they could have fixed that chorus but they chose to handle it li… https://t.co/slSJ42DUMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bucks could win the whole damn thing and people will still argue if they are the best team in the East.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s not enough Pepto to soothe all of that hateful bile in your evil little tummy, cupcake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_eel They don't like it so much when they find out it's not really free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of South America today 02/22 Real-Time #GOESEast #ABI TrueColor/IR and #GLM Lightning Group Density with… https://t.co/BfkqSstusK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfDadFoundOut I ate the last cookie in the package, I'd be wishing that Mom had a new package hiding somewhere close by.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se anexa el link del vídeo. Dónde cínicamente además le da la espalda y le pide ver la calendarización. Le recuerdo… https://t.co/TahvJUqStm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando te descuidas de tu telefono y tus hijas te dejan una fotito cuabdo abres tu telefono! Las super mega hiper a… https://t.co/yJHjxDlVGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint I'm sure you've had a hard-on since he announced but we're ready to fight and take him down. P.S. Super sa… https://t.co/a5sL6Mt2of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NedRyerson1957 @zaava Said it before, make the announcement WD-40 will finish season, will not return. Get a head… https://t.co/k8Rxc1wKNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kclemson Thank you for all the recs! I think we are more looking for the keto equivalent of a nutritionist but I appreciate this too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norman Binkley Multicultural Night is March 26! We’re looking for a few people to share a cultural performance that… https://t.co/oAHb5nR8cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats: A party without borders https://t.co/Avm1t38ZH0 via @AmericanThinker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhcmd @NaanDerthaal That's correct!! Therapy and mental well being!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaAmore14 Of course no matter what we still think our common love the @TheEllenShow ^^ Love the reference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaMcClou2 i’d say it won’t happen again but we both know that’s a lie😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week in worship!! #stressless #focus #creeksideworship @ Creekside Christian Church https://t.co/Y8EVmuRTIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @KenzieReevesxxx @mssnewbooty @LilyAdamsXo @Honour_May18 @EliciaSolis @ANGELAWHITE @evanotty @OfficialKMBooty… https://t.co/UJ0YzXDL00]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: Here's some perspective for ya: after our teachers went on strike, central office is taking 150 job cuts to pay… https://t.co/eq7sPznZwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would tell you people who THE ONE is...  But EVERYTIME I DO (pull a rabbit from the hat) @FoxNews and Greg 'Gutle… https://t.co/LHeQaECsVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredTJoseph They must be in the White Students Union https://t.co/G3n7NWWGax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hit a drive thru someone compliments my lights in my car😂 “those lights hard cuh”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sseason 2 of #OnMyBlock trailer  #Netflix #ChristianPOV #CanWeTalkAbout #IKnowNothing #blackactor #blacklove… https://t.co/5m8VXBso6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckcrs Oh, I know historically our nation has been part of far worse times. The Depression, the World Wars, Vietna… https://t.co/P2kxQHTYSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtariVision @CrunchyKong @replicantpinky @mbthegr81 @Retrogamebrews @wrytersview @AtariVisionWife @bigwayne13… https://t.co/BNo335z0oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUCO coaches: Don’t email D2/NAIA/D3 programs at the end of the season saying your sophomore is getting “D1 looks”… https://t.co/IQlZdCYgwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do yourself a "Favors" and take a look at this guy for #dfs tonight. #draftkings #basketball #fanduel #sports… https://t.co/5fyKMAJTYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salsart39 The small amount of the money they R  paying now for a wall that may come in handy Open your mind things… https://t.co/2B64bRCeV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I EVER mix liquor and beer. It's one or the other @TristyMc you bafoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyGoggles you’re header makes me think you’re like Charles Manson...and kdot looks terrified and macs just like “yea I saw it comin”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahershala Ali is an outstanding actor. Well deserved Oscar. Can’t wait for the True Detective finale tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sounds like @dreamtheaternet had a total blast making this record. I’m not sure I’ve ever described a DT album a… https://t.co/hC7ey3nMj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying Zion Williamson’s injury is “the end of Duke’s season” makes you sound dumber than Lloyd Christmas… https://t.co/wjWjNo32hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corderophi678 That's one of those words that doesn't sound like a word if you say it too much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this new @Frontstretch feature! Race weekend info for all three #nascar series.  https://t.co/3BEhTPBPFG… https://t.co/AD5hr5ohi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for #coding, conferences with families led by students, and school to be in session tomorrow! I’m wearin… https://t.co/SI7JdcHtp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, @standatlantic, @waterparks and @ONEOKROCK_japan we’re SO fucking good tonight 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec If that teacher touched my child, I or my wife based on the gender of that teacher would have put som… https://t.co/PYyUbZHtrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Ilemona @DoDeRightThing @MBuhari "The fish starts to rot from the head"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably won't speak to you much if you've talked about me right in front of me or you know the other thing to. Whi… https://t.co/9Oupcmwk1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USGA_PR @JustinThomas34 Another “fumble” by the USGA... or, more popularly known as “The Gang That Couldn’t Shoot Straight”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I don’t take naps in between having bad sleep, because then I do more bad sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Support Technician" in #Birmingham, AL. Go on informational interviews. The best… https://t.co/YJHaGHliRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDRBNews I’m surprised WDRB would report it.  I thought they loved all things anti-UL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering how a psychic whose #Strip show has hit a terrific contractual snag didn’t foresee that problem ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SancadillaNorte Raro hubiera Sido que no lo marcaran....no hay partido en que no lo hagan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo TFTI its going down....#secondwardhouston #cmonboard #downtownhouston @ HAM Houston - Harrisburg Arts Museum https://t.co/OKSuBqxtmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVUBaseball Days like this i wished i lived in or near Morgantown. I would certainly be there. I will follow/watch… https://t.co/pDruZAR3Se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youdoingtoomuch Lmaoooo listen sis all I know is I saw something that looked like a spoiler so I needed to start p… https://t.co/NvPaDSSwP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmicaAli @JohnEHooper You should write a parenting book. “Patriotic Parenting: how intelligent parents do it.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Thursday Feb 28th 10pm #MxxnShineRecords presents #UpTownTopRanking with vinyl selections from : @Jnfrancis33… https://t.co/Oh7srxQgcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/PSmux1pZEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been thankful to survive off of just Freelance Gigs since I’ve been here. Background Acting, Paid Audience, Ba… https://t.co/8DbjCtt0x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels good to be back home in #SinCity vegas #wildwest @ McCarran International Airport https://t.co/sdbnxZUb3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I message the randomest person and just hit em with a compliment]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Cambridge, OH job and click to apply: Respiratory Therapist(RRT or CRT) - https://t.co/LgkfNpb2FK #HealthWelfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the exact hue of his skin wasn’t the most vital thing about Serena’s dad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@famousb23 For the record no producers wanted famous b except @CM_Roach and @chrisdejoseph. That guy prints money imo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebpike @mattallardACS If you want to get into the weeds check out wowza servers and JLplayer custom video playe… https://t.co/i8VLUNfHoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillCun45428725 @livingforjc Romans 8, which teaches his grace, which is what keeps me from despair!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_5th_Turtle Californication is still one of my favorite music videos. I love how they basically made it a GTA game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to work!!! It’s been a minute. Blessed to be in this position. Hustle and hard work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Happy Presidents Day Mr. President. You are doing a great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your quality of life is a significant factor of your happiness and success. How much perseverance do you have? #10xlife @GrantCardone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_austinsydney Have you not seen yo pinned tweet ?? 🤦🏾‍♂️😂😂😂 you got a trophy for It]]></document><document><![CDATA[@affinity292 @realkerryfrench @RubensteinAdam @IlhanMN @HelloLauraKelly I have been to Bethlehem I have met with a… https://t.co/h9hyEi3w7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holliesmckay in your recent article (https://t.co/tilztSOth6) there is a mistake.   #Pakistan(not #India) has aske… https://t.co/hqdXowzzAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @EricTrump Really well JFK considered himself a liberal! Here is his acceptance speech in ny in 1960! He in no… https://t.co/xr9sLtrSUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't go chasing Riverdales, because this graphic has nothing at all to do with that 90210-on-goofballs show. What… https://t.co/mMq0octPRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen 🙏🏻 I was let go at Nickelodeon because I voted for Proposition 8 in 2008. Guys in truck warned me Nickelodeon… https://t.co/kafSJwYtbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandrahunter @SouthernMissMBB Same with me!  Got choked up watching it! Great bunch of guys I got to know over the… https://t.co/2SEmTdxGPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wrong DUMBO, their going to put you and ALL your associates in your crime family behind bars where… https://t.co/aTz3aIiA4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexa_Merica @jajones338 I think it's because they crave American women and cover their own up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume It stretches the definition of the word “journalist” a bit too far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittMcHenry @yashar @cindymccain @MeghanMcCain Britt you support Trump and he said the same thing just a few week… https://t.co/IbCk22inbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anitavandenbeld Brainwashed cult of Bozo groupies show similar signs  of blind devotion as Charlie's angels https://t.co/437o0MW3Pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristaKaiser IF you were out with a guy you liked then learned his online nickanmes were Ipoophalfgreyhalfred and… https://t.co/QL9hIvlSJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I BELIEVE - Archers up 57-32 over Bulldogs end of 3Q. @DeanPWPTA21 @260sports @PrepSportsNEI @GlennMariniWANE… https://t.co/vuvWVDF8sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamal forsure forsure about to get written out and most likely get killed off on Empire 😂😂 going out the sad way during Black History Month]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkbunnyr Wasn’t that awesome? We were like, they’re playing ABBA in Disneyland do we started singing at the top… https://t.co/OErtfiI47X]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Seattle fans booing Diallo because he’s from OKC was my favorite part of #AllStarSaturdayNight https://t.co/uQYsKW7Wrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to junior guard @prestolawrence5 for being named 8-6A 1st Team All-District!🏀🐾 https://t.co/iBho9N9YzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling into Ft Myers to throw down w/@CodyJinksMusic https://t.co/TkFES6NUxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched this game last night. Young man I know went 3-5 w/ 3 RBI, not bad at all Josh👍]]></document></documents></author>