<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Shihomi0305 I know that space is limited.  But, don't they have a place you can take them to process for drying or… https://t.co/4N88A3GCnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because this is the way I roll... #sfgiantspopehat #lent #hollisterca #sanbenito @ Hollister, California https://t.co/9yKLCznq4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that fruity natty light was some fake internet bullshit but it’s actually real? 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uselesscoin_ Yup I was there haha. Torts signed my record and I exploded. Fav band ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveneLG @KelvinROfficial @KevinSa07052659 @khallbooks @KMillTweed @LailaDoncaster @laina_ruff @lancpok @LateTide… https://t.co/b5zVYJ6Mah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBurgner1 @NEWeatherWx Yeah, but it’s so far away! So much can change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Governor Cuomo to speak. Thank you for the invite Assemblywoman Raynor, District 18! https://t.co/BsXRhbrutu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN EU-Arab leaders look to tackle regional unrest at Egypt summit (DPA) ..// a Long List.. best to take the Bait… https://t.co/xaVp4HRUzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whosaysno #SSAC19 seeing controversy surrounding Zion injury, and whether he should now sit to protect his value,… https://t.co/EWCyAXIGZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kschwenky According to Ali, it counts as long as it hurts you to look at it. https://t.co/gLBJonbYf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever been so attractive to someone 🤒🤒 beautiful people everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domjvasquez And you'd think a state employed referee would know to teach their kids you have to control to the mat 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @seanhannity @RJNewsflash @RealJamesWoods @realDonaldTrump @dbongino @michellemalkin Many Republicans we… https://t.co/Jf5NoginzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AztecFemBone Tecs better be ready Saturday night or Machado will disown them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyKappell this is what I woke up to this morning here in Pittsford.  ___________________ #TeamKappell 🏆 https://t.co/MtEKmFCjNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ahem, it’s call democracy and remember you’re the leader?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venezuelancon @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Can you present the factual evidence?    You can’t make these sweeping… https://t.co/bpUwRTseF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one knows what it’s like....to be the bad man. To be the sad man, behind blue eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #racistbarbie @TomiLahren or @FoxNews barbie?? I like ignorant barbie!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycer17 @anyrmontes28 Fue la subestación de la electricidad en la ciudadela justo donde está la pasarela de concresa/humboldt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait , so now the girl’s soccer team is competing for state ? https://t.co/5KkimrQVMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXI @WPXIMikeHolden Hey Mayor Peduto, No bump stock, No assault weapon, NO back ground check.  Only the most comm… https://t.co/ISWhCILCHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr8tjude_08 @realDailyWire or is it once again double standards for Democrats it's obvious now days]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matchie Maria. Indigenous shaman from Argentina. #bestshooter_portraits #portraitstyles #globalportraits… https://t.co/afYPPXgraq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsTheBrandi I had the runaway slave theory prior to dude's interview, so it's not like it's not an organic premis… https://t.co/7kFfaZbGUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PG13 keeps proving me wrong. Guess he just wasn’t fully healthy last season because he’s BALLIN this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrepHoopsAZ @GreggRosenberg1 @japrephoopsaz @PrepHoopsNick @MattReynolds___ Call us the big three haha 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurcioChris @RBlatthew Had a funny feeling you were there on business and not pleasure...]]></document><document><![CDATA[As my #chevyvolt2012 approaches 100k-km, I noticed it on this auspicious kilometerage tonight.. 👹☠️💀 @ Uptown Victo… https://t.co/Uf8Sqet8Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/iWfnaiSRfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've spent 24 hours a day together for +7 years. how can you be so cold to me to at a moments notice toss me to th… https://t.co/xxOkSglLpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There isn’t a more blissful moment in life than walking into your work bathroom poop stall  and it having just been freshly cleaned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know who this drum crew is, but they were playing in Union Station when I switched trains today. https://t.co/fYwdXBGXAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ideal_Dating @DatingSinglesOL @kissfirstdate @SnapThatGirl @LittleGirlBoob I love read heads and I really love her perfect boobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio There was nothing there! This James kid would make a great walk on at Duke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @maggieNYT McCabe was fired by the FBI. So why is he to be believed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteBlackburn Are these the same fans that have them ranked last in the league in average attendance?  Nice of them to show up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not saying it was not good. Seemed like a launch movie to get Marvel included and it was. Compare it to the First A… https://t.co/gUQkY2VE3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to love the Earth. Love our planet and it will love you back...]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you try to charge your iPad but have the wrong USB cord &lt;&lt;&lt; 👎🏾👎🏾👎🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hate my uncle he just loves breaking my things like a child or throwing my clothes in a bag and thinking the… https://t.co/eUMvraQovj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaSkies @Surgoshan @BillZoeker @nickdorazio3rd @truongasm It may be the best typo of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaprikaSix You know that’s among the least alarming things I’ve seen at third and pike]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adapted Screenplay - #BlacKkKlansman   #Oscars #Oscars2019 #FilmTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Pretty Lady” is making her way back to Broadway again with the new @venicetheatre production of ““42nd Street.” @… https://t.co/SDh2M6p2Sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @KyleBusch @ISMRaceway This is bull crap!!!!!!! It's like a professional bowler winning games against high… https://t.co/HYQkhpflze]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I find ironic is the number of supporters of abortion who oppose the death penalty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwadaJacob He’s just the most complete player in my objective opinion 🤷🏾‍♂️ stats support lol. It’s one of the best debates in sports tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you ❤️ #CMBYN as much as I do because you can now buy this original made-to-order, embroidered… https://t.co/SzjDLgUCoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelawareDOT: How about a post informing commuters of the wreck on SB I-95 at the DE Welcome Center? #DeTrafficAlert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCMacriNBA I really think these guys will benefit from playing with legit stars if we can land them in FA. Pressur… https://t.co/SaWm7hV5AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sid's stories touch the human soul and capture his early life in Philadelphia with wit, creativity and realism. P… https://t.co/s4kBy1KUV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pop Hops Brut IPA by Urban Renewal Brewery @ The Fishtank — https://t.co/YQX5KRU7An]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another very encouraging Cup of Joe with Pastor Jim meeting!  Love this brother and thankful for his wisdom!… https://t.co/AI22sYwy8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife made some gnocchi soup on Sunday night and after eating it for every meal since we finally killed it tonight and I long for a bagel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Man, that apology is almost as sincere as a Thump marriage vow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great 10K to start the day. #Runner #RunChat #RunnerBliss #NotTrainingForBostonThisYear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scituatehoops @HHSIndiansBBall 34-34 at the half. This is High school basketball atmosphere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4golfonline @HendriksenGolf Have you been asked if you two are brothers...........or even twins 🤓🤓?  Next up, side by side in blazers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga won she won I’m so happy 😄 #Oscars she deserved it!!! 👏🏼👏🏼❤️👏🏼❤️👏🏼❤️👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrknPoet He’s Phileena’s ESA (also, CSA = Contemplative Support Animal). 🐶❤️🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katzish @melodyisdestiny @Jim_Jordan is an odious criminal with no credibility. Cohen is a reformed liar. Jordan i… https://t.co/uRlK3EXIxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckySmirks Its seems that Tim's mom did both then thew up!!!!!!!! and look what came out .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been penniless and I've been 1% and back again 2x. I've lost more money than most will ever see. And I've seen… https://t.co/Xq6YZCg9os]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Pronouns are hard” WELL GOLLY GEE ITS A LITTLE HARDER BEING TRANS NON-BINARY IN A VERY BINARY WORLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[$10M Claim Blames Ducey, State for Uber Self-Driving Crash That Killed Woman  https://t.co/uXYd6Ai41D via @phoenixnewtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@havameow @BeauHoward12 @pckarma112 @bernathys2cents @CNNPolitics The distance between your head and your butt may be closer than you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop in today at the 2019 South Carolina Football Coaches Association Clinic @RiddellSports https://t.co/XaVFWitwiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jocelynpaigey “That’ll be $25... oh! I’m sorry Miss Obama, I didn’t recognize you! I meant $80!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Asheville Regional Airport in Fletcher, NC https://t.co/Yj0wFEi32C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Imperial Marshmallow Fluff Nutcase by @listermann @ Listermann Brewing Co. — https://t.co/M5Km1fkzX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck It’s a good thing they aren’t running the aero ducts here. Can’t change or do much to the sway bar because the ducts block it]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an attempt to briefly explain the entire Bible...on a scale of 1 to 4...with 4 being the most important, how imp… https://t.co/BtNVq3cEjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an amazing story. Love it. This is our foundation. The 54th Massachusetts regiment! #BlackHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[DW it's supposed to be back at the home at 5 p.m. he must have an escort back because they won't let him in the fro… https://t.co/Ds2A7O4daJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn don’t say Lebrons not a good free throw shooter on twitter... youngins who never saw Mike play go after you 😂😂… https://t.co/dmnayA0Ran]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZanetto7 @TheLeforce @mvaughn22 @BenParrish90 Wofford has a perfect schedule this year, set themself up for an… https://t.co/cMZ732I9kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Husker/All-Big10 Conference pitcher, Kaylan Jablonski, will begin giving 🥎 pitching lessons today, March 4.… https://t.co/E5Qab5PHzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/9nArOq4lX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moment I’ll remember forever!!!! . . . #New #champ #photo #confidence #King #champion #Happy #Focus #family… https://t.co/dqFPhmwkdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usmarines @USArmy @USNavy @usairforce @uscoastguard #impeachthelyingbastardnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pairs well with a quick date night - Drinking a Dabble by @sixpoint @ The Gavel Public House  — https://t.co/i5Pbv9qNZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin And we’re not buying that you’re as smart as you think you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB'19 in the Most Magical Place on Earth!!! @ Toy Story Land https://t.co/AWIUCwUmYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i stopped wearing jordans when i camped for the masters at finishline and when i got the front of the line and was… https://t.co/jvgIRya4xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this dumb ass bitch broke apart 5 FAT ASS BACKWOODS. I’m mad as  fuck I had already poured my champagne smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big yellow orb in the sky. Not sure what it is. Hurts to look at it. Will investigate further.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ChrisHewitt @HelenLOHara @jamescdyer #CaptainMarvelMovie question. Near the beginning, one Kree asks another K… https://t.co/RjwhNzhSDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently in Virginia Beach, Virginia,  2/20/19, 21:00. @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/EGFFhzpMCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I grew up in my parents generation. Times where people knew what hard work was, knew how to handle their own… https://t.co/f2woQyImNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people afford Spring Break like you’re in college, you don’t have jobs??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Wow just saying a lot of your witches are going down!! Now it seems we will have the repo… https://t.co/DIyjSJU9SE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milfjr85_ @weembust @EASTBAYDFRESH @abel1408 @Medfordniner So does your boy Joe.......he called me “white devil” i… https://t.co/fArMYROnXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[this only has four likes and I think i’m gonna actually make it at 10 and then y’all can kick me out and be friends… https://t.co/Li0LYhhf5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baroness_Nichol @britishairways I'll do that for the next month for sure. I'm having a month if @delta now. Thanks for the tip!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere We are currently seeking Extras for the upcoming Episodes for Days of our lives, if interested kindly s… https://t.co/P9veTGa72d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets No wonder he worked so hard for Jeffrey's slap on the hand prison sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emokidsloveme Also Frances Farmer will Have her revenge on Seattle, negative creep, and radio friendly unit shifter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al aire #RumboaMitadyMitad con @ErnestoChavana y @labrillanti vía @multimediostv Canal 6 https://t.co/T9NWOrP3sA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegionRat14 He underachieved at Texas for years on end.........At a school like Tennessee this 2 year window is go… https://t.co/dWPlpdxt8N]]></document></documents></author>