<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you get your taxes done and almost cry tears of joy because you're getting a solid refund. Feeling blessed. 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kidseatfree  @RWBsChowBus is at hiveaustin until 8 offering a free kid’s meal with a $10 purchase. Chomp chomp! @… https://t.co/l14y27mdlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APendletonP @StephMillerShow @rudepundit @EricBoehlert @sarahkendzior @JillWineBanks Stream on the internet on WCPT Chicago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[«Y creó Dios al hombre a su imagen, a imagen de Dios lo creó; varón y hembra los creó» Génesis 1:27 #creacion https://t.co/GujGuPiIaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey DJT, how fast you FORGOT (guess because you are old) you lost the popular vote....you got luckily and won the e… https://t.co/QB9hSmolro]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nephew dead ass asked me “Jaja how come you’re not pregnant “ ...... ha Jayce don’t worry by next year I will be 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalmartSupport I got my pre order copy of @CapcomUSA_  @ResidentEvil on Sunday (backorder). But no pre order bonus. Please help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Well I’m not the scalper am I? I’m two guys named Nick” literally I was in the middle of a panic attack and that l… https://t.co/zjDbRsmNIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️#NYFW “@barrymanilow performed Copacabana at New York Fashion Week”  https://t.co/Lg3hzXD3pG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily morning shake: 4oz. Pineapple juice, 4 oz. alkaline water, 1 oz Source of Life Gold liquid, 10 drops Cell… https://t.co/2TkvWymG0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsANiemeyer @TalkingWithTram @thegreenlady4 @Miss_Wiberg @MsContrades @blueridgephysed @MissWinkler110… https://t.co/xDC9ih0ZB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my first meal of the day (ramen) while driving to my 4:30 lab so clearly, I’m adulting well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo clopens suck, but this ones really gonna suck cause we're springing forward 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen! GOD bless President Trump and GOD bless the USA. We are fighting a spiritual battle for the soul of our natio… https://t.co/I1dERtbbMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerminatedAcct1  you are a pathetic excuse of a man that you have to go around and use women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Holi! This was our first year participating the Hindu celebration of the return of Spring and reconnecting wi… https://t.co/a580GsdEVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyaAndCraig @Jakeshears @scissorsisters @ImSuchASamantha @MadonnaInn Love this song and album]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tacotopia    When is it ever too much Cholula? I was super thrilled so be invited to tacotopia_ and do go with one… https://t.co/rGBwIr2ZUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOUR FREAKING BLIND... TO NOT BE HIT UP THE SIDE OF YOUR HEAD WITH HYPOCRISY ON THIS ONE... WHERE WERE THESE PEOPLE… https://t.co/qibuJXZyyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I’m just a theater geek but I believe in 2019 we are quickly approaching a time where the #Oscars commercials… https://t.co/Lc0Mwkyax6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone who kisses you like @ItsRamiMalek kisses #LucyBoynton.😍 #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[You love me and I love you, your heart hurts mine does too, but it’s just words and they cut deep but it’s our worl… https://t.co/VX3K5eJPIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 3 weeks I’m having my Spring Chair Party, and you’re invited! Signature cocktails, interesting people, and of co… https://t.co/1JlTl6J4R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed Guys! We got @IISuperwomanII AND Eleanor Shellstrop. #20BITEEN is off to a great start. https://t.co/WpoIBRpFp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobDuffyROC @LollypopFarm @RochesterChambr She’s beautiful! Love black cats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hintofspy @OS_LaurenD @HomecominFL Wish it was readable without a paid subscription. :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDreamGhoul Currently in the same position!!! https://t.co/FS2YkwsH8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geez — do we get to see these as permanent records not able to be destroyed? This is so fucked up #inners]]></document><document><![CDATA[aff.. que mulher maravilhosa, que show! 👏🏻 🎼🎤 Céline Dion 💛 em The Colosseum at Caesars Palace https://t.co/mheBNQX1SV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright @marybar41015771 @MNettiePalmer @mgranville1 @adirado29 @Bravewriting @MrDane1982 @eclecticbrotha… https://t.co/FIYanXrJP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @barbmullings Trump feels that if he throws it out there it becomes real or possibly that it may catch!… https://t.co/6d7dTpPUWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more is it just enough to pander to black people while offering nothing. No more will we put what we need last t… https://t.co/HK7Z0Axa7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s going to be a good lazy Sunday when the SYFY channel has a Harry Potter Marathon ⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It certainly is illuminating realizing that so many of the female artists I liked as a girl “fell off” not because… https://t.co/8AKNSIE1gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the Federal Data Privacy Debate, Regulations May Impact Healthcare https://t.co/C98fqR2pQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just learned about the momo challenge. I hate everything. This is why I stay off the internet!!! Ugh thanks world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I am so sorry to all the dudes out there. I just texted a guy to see if he wanted to go see a movie and the… https://t.co/ANssKrLk2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkblackpanfah @willfromclt @ShiannaLemon @steadystackin__ @LetYoSoulGlow I LOVE FACTS !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg commitment to saving lives from gun violence sounds good to me. The whole #commonsense approach - ho… https://t.co/QjJV0i6dk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markstevensonYT He said that a lot...like I wouldn't sacrifice an entire day on the drop of a hat for family. Come… https://t.co/vqgmDVXlmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trending product that I will be trying out in 72 hours is… https://t.co/y4FogcD4sc https://t.co/wuTNFobqX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@readingin6th @DisruptedTv @cultofpedagogy @jesslahey @hiccupc Good resource for the work you’re doing.… https://t.co/cwAqMlD7NV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Omg I just sat on the toilet.... but whatever. It’s probably more clean than most of the men I sleep with tbh.” -… https://t.co/oxIlVyuGkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriots let's keep this in mind, lock and load for civil war before giving up your guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu queria que meu corpo e mente tbm achasse a maconha a solução pra todos os problemas como a grande maioria dos ma… https://t.co/XMDuSKkA4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resistance lip sheer and wing hair stick by @42NerdtasticPl and Billy earrings by @scoutstiel https://t.co/RXfnmuuKV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys.. we bought another house! Time to enjoy the awesome backyard and pool area! Visitors welcome! #newhouse… https://t.co/JTElt5mkzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twobarrels @ThomasPThomson1 @chip_peck @PattiSc08960854 @BebeLibra @Pb4ugoBev @bn81159 @kenell10tt… https://t.co/d5dhhmQUsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Bend over, @realDonaldTrump , Kim is planning on fucking you. Love talk, Not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odyssey158 @GinaPustor123 @NancySimonds1 @ClanOutlandish @Outlander_JCF @AthanasiaTrian1 @DJZJCZ @gaby_im70… https://t.co/iuSa01bjU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a Bernie-bro, but I get it, becuase he’s often right about these things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really convenient you can do currency conversions in Spotlight, shame they are totally inaccurate though… https://t.co/x6RENu3qoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney Republicans kill babies. They have late term abortions and do it in the name of the Lord. They lie about it just like Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Son_of_Gods @carolyn_from @MelchizedekGal @ThomasHawk241 We got 2020 preliminaries coming up. We gotta know th… https://t.co/WiCKeIaECi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhonda__e You’re right Mama Epps. I’m sure all involved learned a valuable lesson from that. Tell them sweep it un… https://t.co/pWjEg7U4Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatBrigman @ginasanderson @michaelschweitz It was the most disgusting display of a Presidential candidate/standing… https://t.co/oq18qSyfQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had such a good time in Ohio the last couple days. Obviously not the fact grandma passed, but seeing all the fami… https://t.co/eOLyMt45ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am already on my second cup of coffee! Who waits until 7:15 @NikkiBurdine @neilorne @WKRN @BrieThiele]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hemingwayslut I have a list of ones I’m sad we don’t have studio versions of. These are both at the top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O Cheifah Gang @Thechefbooth Exclusive Interview we had on Wednesday on the @dagr8fm on _battleofthesexes “Battle… https://t.co/ElNyFESYWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahem ...  📢 IT’S SUPER SATURDAY!  See you all at the Cage. https://t.co/rdAnxk73Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 Why not?  The evangelicals have already declared him to be the 2nd coming of Christ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“From the outcry at Heshbon even to Elealeh, as far as Jahaz they utter their voice, from Zoar to Horonaim and Egla… https://t.co/cfIdW15G4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I refuse to.... but I’m here on this motherfucking app.... like i need kicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustSayn2020KAG @VanidaPeters @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump @JudgeJeanine @TuckerCarlson Hey I love the picture, Thor… https://t.co/tFWVVw14xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out here... @ Palmer Pavilion At Arnold Palmer Invitationall https://t.co/S8v0AJGJa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Green Line conductor announces its going express &amp; half the train empties out... #Boston @lolMBTA https://t.co/3WzFzfoAMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting isolated pics at the Bean is tough! She killed these tho. I need to go back to Chicago for Au Chevals. Nike… https://t.co/ipEOheh2zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD @hightow05819648 @RepRashida @RepMarkMeadows @LynnePatton Yes she does! 😡🙏🏻❤️🇺🇸🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t this clown a doctor? Seems pretty irresponsible to me. And what’s the deal with so many doctors in Congress (… https://t.co/wWkB4IhPeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[All points bulletin...if you are bored 😐?  #Office reruns are on all day (yyyeeeesssss!).  ❤️-Ms Michael Scott]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam Yah @realDonaldTrump wants an apology... he’ll get one after millions of Americans get one from him... never]]></document><document><![CDATA[i be going through so much behind closed doors, but i keep faith. something good is coming soon. 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[The compensation fund for victims of 9/11 is running out of money and will cut future payments by 50 to 70 percent,… https://t.co/Nw68O1KJkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[As soon as I let go of wanting to return to the classroom universe to help the teacher shocking himself to motivate… https://t.co/gwsQG8ka5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielvmachado Pues sí, las mujeres no nos enfrentamos ni al trabajo, ni a los gastos médicos ni a nada de eso con… https://t.co/NmkRCFNMN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcaneKnowledge @cacoethes_carpe @Goonobody @RonPaul4Constit @Kath3853 @Charbrevolution @_lets_do_it_ @Just2BiZI… https://t.co/nF8r5sVBcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTylerZed @ProjectTupac He's lost all credibility and shown himself as deep state since he ran in 2016! The thi… https://t.co/dUAg4lChxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is correct! I don't know what we will do without her! I think we are all in denial😔But I hope she will still b… https://t.co/rfZYrrh8uA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the one day I may choose #red over #magenta... #HappyValentinesDay 💋🌹🍷❤️ https://t.co/UPh6BB5geF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathleenFOX5 @POTUS How many crimes have they been involved in? So much corruption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sblackmoore Well, what's interesting about it to me is that folks by and large don't understand the tax system. I… https://t.co/jMXCKEW1r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve literally never heard of any school’s dress code allowing students to wear hats. This is not newsworthy😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[On sundays we share our bibles not our juuls 🤘🏻🤪 https://t.co/HVBN579Dqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m finally done with narcos. this is really sad😭 i’ll miss listening to javier pena narrating episodes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss Ember is finally down for the night. Write mad woman, write! #amwriting #writerlife  #Writingcommunity… https://t.co/VmPzqf4V45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdynoel Right. Definitely counting down till this after work nap ima take today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow Just like the kids who are separated at the border from their parents.....they still are being separated aren’t they?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it wasn’t a good idea going to Verizon right when they open cuz there’s like a million people waiting🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman, 26, fatally struck by taxi in Queens hit-and-run: police https://t.co/a0EW5yAiRY via @pix11news]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Spring selling season is right around the corner. Take action and prepare now. #marylandrealestatepro… https://t.co/3daCdsbwSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. And same for the University of Texas regents. @GovAbbott #txlege #YCTCON19]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is well timed because I always just kind of fake it till I make it day to day...but I do have a haircut today… https://t.co/KztrPfp0ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to recognize and celebrate phenomenal women amongst us @WSUPullman. #WomenWhoLead #GoCougs #liftaswelead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Deashay Listen to this then Full Video On My YouTube page Under Tanna Mann https://t.co/sMZgCLzMbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that our 3ac pollinator habitat at the @Bayer4CropsUS Williamsburg site helped contribute to the Million Gard… https://t.co/nNZT4PZgI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VI5PjVSvIn Keep up the fight teacher friends &amp; parents!! Sign TODAY! Your voice can be heard!… https://t.co/GKEOVApFhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I am getting ready for my First Gig of the Day: at @brooklynmuseum in the early AM for a… https://t.co/blgTy1R2Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[To a fresh new day...#EndlessPossibilities #FindingJoyintheLittleThings https://t.co/36UbWslazg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC This is DC... you need to make a decent wage to live here! Good that your team will be paid fairly]]></document></documents></author>