<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not to be outdone by a pregnant Spaniard with a first-born at her Baby Shower in Pearl River, it was time to strike… https://t.co/MZMuUdZPpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intellectual crushes are the BEST!  @GoRightBook is now available for preorder 😬  📕: https://t.co/pIQM7RIMSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaBeez I don't think so, no trade clause plus no buy out options tells me he's stuck in philly for life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plan the work &amp; work the plan. Push pass your limits!  #workout #hard #fitness #gym #boxing #pushing #limits… https://t.co/9awd0voRY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no coffee like free coffee. Thank you Starbucks for the free birthday coffee.... venti flat white @ Starbu… https://t.co/J1gnZnQDKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawtc Ha.  CANT WAIT to hear your thoughts on Miami Driving. https://t.co/zhkbtPslq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Symbo1ics @debasishg The typical response is that actors model the real world at some level (independent concurren… https://t.co/zQKcfGXmh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great event put on today at Jefferson High School by the National Football Foundation of Tampa. 60 high schools and… https://t.co/X79o1wqbgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m following via @KCMO @YouTube. @portofkc in full agreement that we must have a #newKCI terminal for our continue… https://t.co/S0N2xBZ68S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would take Spielberg’s @netflix position more seriously if the Academy hadn’t been allowing its voters to watch s… https://t.co/oZjz6BN1yU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxRadioGeek Poor location here and couldn't get in. Any chance you be on the 1815z AO-91 pass? Tnx!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersTalkESPN Injuries killed us big time. Magic got us LBJ and he will get us more Stars and other good players. I believe Allen!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations king!! @ItsRamiMalek Malek - Best Actor - 'Bohemian Rhapsody' - 2019 Oscars - Full Backs...… https://t.co/hSXdspTjpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want help with promoting events for your company, a SALE, or products, or whatever helps you more. We have the BEST… https://t.co/X6nElMvmyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! RT @nopunktraders: Great call in Kroger doc @jonnajarian   Today's 60 Second video from @investitute ECB… https://t.co/WN7P1K1cLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LockItInonFS1 This is always a Russ kinda game to take over but i am laying it on Joel]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wonderful invention that is remote start has made parking lots strange places early morning... lots of idling empty cars 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brenda_stinnett Gifts 🎁 cards or candy can’t express my love for my wife after 30 plus years . Happy Valentine Day .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've said it once and I'll say it again, Montrezl Harrell is the future and the truth! #Clippers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano Well, that’s what a loser does when he can’t compete with the big boys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥤🥤🥤 . . . @worldofcocacola cocacola #cocacola #worldofcoke #worldofcocacola #atlanta #atlien #hotlanta #georgia… https://t.co/ud3jKuFC5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas be stupid how u got Jhene Aiko n go back to Ariana grande 😂😂🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayoitselaine For this pic, I imagine a wizened elder, seasoned by loss and the tides of life. For them, the entity… https://t.co/UPNAScynzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahKinke Bro it’s just funny to me that you gotta hate on me imma junior bro just tryna grind and get somewhere u… https://t.co/opEa2LEogc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Times the Illegal Immigration of 2017 Levels at Current Rate https://t.co/JPrZiGNw8b via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claudalb13 Hoy que jugaron de lo mismo quedo totalmente desterrada la teoria de que Gil le da nas movilidad y ritm… https://t.co/yO8G6wmLcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ShareAMC #nolife #AMCPrime @AMCTheatres #AMCSuperFan  #amcstubsalist2019 #singlelifesucks https://t.co/g9zIAF8e9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan do Donald Trump on the other hand that cold water comes from his anus I mean Uranus oh well what the he… https://t.co/xzg1ExK62B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_sipher A regime decapitation strike would be far more effective than swearing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrbacon50 @MhawkRetland It's much more likely IMO, that either the whole party essentially flips toward progressiv… https://t.co/bxPNkpKjRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APAndrewTaylor @jpaceDC Maybe a little too soon to think this is the new norm but nonetheless refreshing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop stealing my tweets #SMH I can’t believe in this day and age real tragedies still happen https://t.co/bZVwifyOef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos #MhoniFans Quedamos Impactados Con Sus #Predicciones 🔮 #MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni @magdaproducer ✨📺🎬🎥… https://t.co/mUldZmoXgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch did she just eat Hot Cheeto with a fork?? No we suck them off our fingers. We don’t claim her sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[If If’s were Buttes and Candy were NUTS we would all have a Merry Freakin Christmas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vous souvenez-vous quand vous avez rejoint Twitter ? Moi, oui ! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ZKGM8RxtJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy continues to inspire so powerfully. Another great story about him and his courage and optimism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stanfordkp One slight downside I thought of tonight, and it’s all relative, but it’s not going to be easy to integ… https://t.co/SxWfxmCiF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always enjoy reviewing some of the answers to the school trip worksheets. #museumadventures @ Children's Science… https://t.co/emgJJHvUTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must believe in your success before you can achieve it. Access to success is through the mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t say: My life has a purpose... rather say, God’s purpose has my life @KenDillingham #mobilize #mission https://t.co/1daB5jA9WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @AKimCampbell @JimCuddy I took a piss with him in the next urinal.. Decent fellow for a lefty. Didn't know… https://t.co/Xlpre3mk5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[*in the future   Someone: Did you get dropped on your head as a baby ?  The kid : nah I flew and hit the fucking  c… https://t.co/WiDsUmfORt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ambarabigail9 Emilio,  tu eres dentista de profesión,  que haces recibiendo ofensas,  si bien puedes abrir tu prác… https://t.co/pqdKYcL6Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los pensadores de basura operan desde las tres de la mañana ocasionando que todos los perros de la cuadra ladren al… https://t.co/a5iE9kyuYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Law Office of John Nwosu PLLC celebrates this day with all the beautiful, strong women in this world.… https://t.co/f5KO7vtMFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realidad indudable en 🇵🇷: a pesar de que estudiamos ingles un promedio de 9-12 años en las escuelas no somos biling… https://t.co/i7gdrAtIzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[OTD in 1947 Truman thanks Herbert Hoover for aiding post-WWII reconstruction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @NBCNews Zero huh.  30+ indictments and numerous convictions.  How do you call that noth… https://t.co/gU20g6LPXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn STRAIGHT 110% ALL THE WAY ALWAYS STRAIGHT Damn STRAIGHT IN NETWORK corrupt cali CLIQUE📲📡🖥🖱💻📡📠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jobansfire @chriseatscheese @TheKOQ Flavortown is a great place to visit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been awesome to see this program develop over the past few years. Great piece from NBC. Also, did you hear… https://t.co/ZmRpOudhC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saralynsmith @fabernackle I was gripping my pillow while totally freaked out! So intense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @CherylS13478522 Every attempt possible to win an election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Blackhawks blueline has been giving away too many chances for awhile now. The (somehow) winning has masked it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NowApocSTARZ Not that I haven’t always appreciated @Beau_Mirchoff, but I just wanted to say thank you for your con… https://t.co/ZdjEDGqu77]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw obituary of Edward Victor Allen, Korean War Veteran, in Sunday’s @DMRegister. His daughter, Gail Graham, is D… https://t.co/wMZPiIjZ7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely a vibe #NowPlaying 🎧 @detroitplair if I can get the clearances I see u walking on stage to one of their… https://t.co/jtcciZjy9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[The unprofessionalism I experience while cold calling businesses is astounding]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: 32-year-old Justin Gaston was arrested in Lynn. He’s accused of shooting and killing 33-year-old Haki San… https://t.co/elktLABSqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your work Fred. This year my wife and I travelled to Pine Trails Park on the anniversary.  We were mo… https://t.co/ZQjZby4Y02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tilt shift. #runyoncanyon @ Runyon Canyon - Los Angeles / Hollywood https://t.co/zaRPooGtNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gotta say...after a long day’s work in early March, South Dakota is a fantastic place to stay in your hotel ro… https://t.co/ZKj35K5vG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retired61016 @EWDolan He denies there was any threat and it doesn't appear to be recorded in the substitutes' writ… https://t.co/LVSUmu7sbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great group of 55+ runners heading out for 4 to 21 miles!! WeeDoggie!  #runnerdudesaturdaygrouprun #grouprun… https://t.co/MgY6k7Sk5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look I love Vans and primarily wear then but this Vans flipping or Vans theory shit is so dumb. They are bottoms he… https://t.co/PwbHi2hwkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad I had to get up at 3:30 am only to have @AlaskaAir delay my flight, bump me, then have me wait at Sea-Tac f… https://t.co/lpvo8qzgUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[What? It’s after noon... - Drinking an E.T. Wee (2019) by @THBrewery at @thbrewery  — https://t.co/hUV3J2WG9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ver a dos Titanes @alfonsocuaron @RealGDT que hermosa era para ser Mexicano, pues nos enseñan que chingándole los s… https://t.co/dUyoVWn2x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mango Coconut Smoothie by @DecadentAles @ Decadent Ales — https://t.co/q4562NN9Ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_N_Edwards @BaseballFreak_9 “The headless golfer” - in a serious note - don’t you think head/eye position contribu… https://t.co/c24kWZlizu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 I wanna run with you Aaah-ooh We can be wolves Howlin at the great white moon I wanna be by your side when we lig… https://t.co/xjMciVYlKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I visited my first Medical/Recreational Marijuna facility yesterday. I was truly surprised at how many people were… https://t.co/J3fDVWV14R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing to do now but Wait For It.  #RiseUp #Hamilton https://t.co/MnTFR0IMXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[But nonetheless I’m about to go cash some paper...money feels better than a Nut to me😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[El joven de hoy es hijo de “lo rápido”, es esclavo del “click” y se ha vuelto incapaz de proyectar con visión hacia… https://t.co/Tv9NUjYwv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doubleyewdee We’re doing the same thing, except Cari had seen season 1 and part of season 2 a long time ago. But t… https://t.co/oYSwgSmc6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @power1051 with get_repost ・・・ Replace the wine with henny tho 😂 @ New York, New York https://t.co/xVqMnlXbnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naby Keita is slowly but surely getting to where he needs to be in this team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THINK:EXP Think Floyd Show Live @ https://t.co/c1po6ndCDe https://t.co/Nw9Ipp6kEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jockmania @Chuckywoowoo @BigArm1983 @Chawgo Oh baby. It’ll fit in well because it’s a baseball environment. Celebrate winners]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eye6919 @Rupp_Arena @KySportsRadio @KYgal_Heather @BirdChampion @ChadBlue83 A wasted ticket...someone could’ve rea… https://t.co/BVFLu9uYOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn @ChickfilA hella slow at the @ATLairport this morning. This is unheard of. Somebody must have called off or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to watch it all over again, lady I’m talking to wants to watch it. It’ll be fun hearing all her scenarios and n… https://t.co/e8GEGBzVyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimitrrra Boehiam Rhapsody was great. Then again I’m a Queen fan so I might be a little biased]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m becoming more and more convinced that the never ending and unnecessary confusion around nutrition is for the so… https://t.co/iYKHM2Lt7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary You are in charge of that Committee so get it done.  .@POTUS #Q #QAnon  #MAGA  #QArmy  #WWG1WGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The humans that work in the server room at Blizzard that run World of Warcraft are non physical entities from the p… https://t.co/dYrM6ob26A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ushikins Traveling is so much work! I can FaceTime my mother for her 50th, I don’t feel like another obligatory family gathering]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:22.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shundoee2 hey stud how’s it going!?! Beautiful Man! Nice pics Great Ass!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas black woman sentenced to 5 yrs in prison for simply VOTING in an election while she was on probation. VOTING!… https://t.co/ayxIBg8ish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too little too late, hope you eat #bacon in #hell. If such place exists. 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepGosar is a Fucking embarrassment and disgrace 💯💯‼️‼️ https://t.co/s6fbjWqCtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunyabiznasbro @RepDanCrenshaw Most of my family also served in Vietnam,  the Korean war,  so on.  Almost all woul… https://t.co/VdkJxjONp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyD Exactly! If you don’t vaccinate your children then that’s child abuse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP She will not resign, the Dems are in for real trouble with her and a couple of others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anezbitt “Okay, let’s go over the ground rules. You can’t leave first until you chug a beer. Any man scoring has t… https://t.co/789ClPH3DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelercam @JB550MB @dlolley_pgh He made that decision. Without an overt public apology, seems impossible to recover from his actions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @fliflisky Joe Butthead Biden is and always has been an embarrassment as a representative in our government]]></document></documents></author>