<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Love what you said, I am telling you right now you got the next election In the bag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump This is the 1st time I’ve heard anything out of @realDonaldTrump’s mouth about th… https://t.co/ovUpdxIHUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been circulating. Photography is so powerful ❤️📸https://t.co/5ZZNOZnbWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always gonna be my fav Lent meal @ House That Funk Built https://t.co/3ORtSzhptX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fishies las tqm🐟💕 @vanesaoyervidez  @mgarciapruneda https://t.co/nGNAOT8HLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are these fools on the left still talking “climate change “? That whole theory was already debunked by real sci… https://t.co/fN7KD68UX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pad 39A looking a bit different from when Neil Armstrong, Buzz Aldrin and Michael Collins launched to the moon near… https://t.co/NzlH5o6bCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tip for exec producers: don’t compliment your editors on how fast they are. It’s either be fast or be fired. We don… https://t.co/VacnRAOOIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboroPrincipal May her soul sleep in peace. May you find peace and reflect on her life instead of her passing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I see one more buzzfeed article with the same information on this whole Kardashian thing, imma lose my mind 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhyesOhyes2020 @PastorDScott @POTUS Omarosa didn't wake up. She was an obnoxious b*h user who took advantage. She… https://t.co/6O31wkNdTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[can y’all BELIEVEEEE that this time last year i was gettin cheated on??? and this time tomorrow i found out ab it ?… https://t.co/0GpPIVULyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[One for each of us 🐱⚰️👶🧟‍♂️🔪 Which cover is your favorite?  #sometimesdeadisbetter #nowreading @ Los Angeles, Calif… https://t.co/GvDGzpiH25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speech time in Pre-k! Talking about body parts♥️ https://t.co/IOJC5jbXmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y según la RAE:   • golpista  1. adj. Perteneciente o relativo al golpe de Estado. 2. adj. Que participa en un golp… https://t.co/OVnJNJcsEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HailGaryATL @ohkristinnicole Actually i looked it up myself and you're correct! Looks like most illegal abortions… https://t.co/Vx9pV6onlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anaclarapupin @rosalvolopes @felipeneto Ou leu e interpretou igual o “tonho”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahBookbinder @weareoversight If he didn't, he's the only guy in the whole administration not fleecing the taxpayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you take your ego out of it, it will liberate you.  President Barack Obama #QualtricsX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planning to see this Tomorrow!! And the play in April. Going to miss Aunt Madea!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday Fight Night at Suspension House Fitness!  5:30pm every Friday Night! Book your bag! 🥊 *Reminder, please… https://t.co/SffEuScF1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Ratio oh and stop writing opinion pieces. No one gives a shit. Anyone that truly cares about knowle… https://t.co/e3ftEdSVqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[l’aluminium se renforce à une température au-dessous de zéro. Il devient moins cassant que l’acier pour la même épa… https://t.co/XbHC86LUyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamTPHandlers Kanina pa ako gising! Excited bako sa price ko admin hahaha  #POPSSSSMusikero]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why the first three seconds is better than the whole original song]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! THIS! Coming from cities with a larger #s of TOC it amazes me how we are not talking about the serious implica… https://t.co/NbVZUewtWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i miss u so much pls stop hating me and hang out w me soon. thank u for being the best ex and not being too stupid 💛💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t see that coming.  Lauren Bacall in To Have and Have Not: "You just just put your lips toge... https://t.co/n0ir1OJo5q via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpringHillEnt @JaredSawyerJr @wbpictures @WarnerBrosEnt @mavcarter @KingJames Whatttttttt https://t.co/i7IgonHPuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a passenger has to give the @GreyhoundBus driver directions because she doesn't know how to get to #Guelph! 🙈 #helpme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheryReeks @DonaldJTrumpJr TIME WILL TELL YALL TRY AND BE NICE LIFE IS A GAMBLE LETS SEE WHO WINS WERE ALL STILL G… https://t.co/jfBADsUeDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbelJRojas1 @_Saeen_ @NitaLowey Yes she did. Her comments were antisemitic. If u can’t criticize Israel or AIPAC w… https://t.co/pRF8vNuLnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning HAPPY MONDAY let’s make it a great one ✨ #buenosdias #TodayInLA #morningshow #traffic #Team4 #4you ☕️… https://t.co/jco3fHrXlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for all your hard work to keep our students safe @1GreatLakes2013 Happy #LRSAppreciationDay @PeelSchools]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never had such conflicting emotions about the last season of #GameOfThrones 🐉 🐺 #soexcitedyetsoheartbroken @GameOfThrones]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe that rejection is a blessing because it's the universe's way of telling you that there's something better out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mas324ora you know the dark secrets of the English language far more than the native speakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is actually a thing? I almost got struck by lightening just reading it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @Twitter STILL hasn’t removed this account. This is harassment and impersonation. https://t.co/NpDtY8LUvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariley815 I agree.  I love Future Ready Librarians on FB. https://t.co/h7PFjaYB8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya no aguanto mas Me iré a dormir un rato Nos vemos en un ratico Dios los bendiga ❤️ #sosvenezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost MaryK: Stop the tape! IT Desk: It’s not a tape MaryK: Rewind it.  IT Desk: It’s not a tape  MaryK: Ok.....S… https://t.co/7Fma5GEtL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews That is so freakin funny I nearly pissed my pants 😂Obama’s role models not that’s hilarious😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The battleship is steam powered via coal. Coal fire heats giant boilers which generate steam and generate electrici… https://t.co/1kCkEhR3Fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MancillasEISD @JRod_EISD Thank you so much I had a great time! Enjoy your Spring Break Ms Mancillas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought our date was Saturday and not tomorrow but apparently John is taking me out twice. https://t.co/0jfrqqIknt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly y’all be tweeting racist/homophobic/transphobic/sexist tweets on here for why? It’s 2019. Who tf cares wha… https://t.co/UqOIvcjqhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s enough #poli for a week, or year. . Pardon me while I island for awhile. https://t.co/9EF2FMNUTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS @THEEdarinbrooks @KatrinaKBowden Bad move Wyatt.   You don't invite old girl friend to meet new girlfriend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinaiyak mo ko @eyalaureee 😭💛😭💛😭💛😭💛😭💛😭 Proud ako sayooooo!!! Congrats UST!!! #ParaKayMilena #KamiNaman #GoUSTe https://t.co/hrNnGiTjge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr Tucker Carlson is a Twit  and I don’t support that trash.  Positive I’m not alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #CellularVision for all the #Boostlove you have put into your new store! Thanks @Pincus_NEast @SellWithLG… https://t.co/IreMnhDuiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want it.Enter the KOA Behind the Sign Giveaway and you could win the Grand Prize of a Keystone Passport 175BH, a… https://t.co/2HJN1kSM8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VoiceYourLove ALS research @alsassociation for people like my sister and brother https://t.co/G1xUpKx8W6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoteshockey I'm not gonna be at Thursdays game maybe they'll have them out Saturday thank you for thinking of my 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartmindy @PatriotSmirk Oh this is so true. The very large populist communities would rule, no matter their affi… https://t.co/gtvhs7FaJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of these parents are so mad at YouTube about these Momo videos.... the bigger problem is how worried everyone i… https://t.co/JNCRdlPKX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball travels to #1 ranked and undefeated Norwalk in the CIAC Class LL quarterfinals tonight. Tip time is 6:00… https://t.co/pwpu1jmZfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stepdaddy666 Absolutely. Preferably when those same two baristas are working!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#releasethevisas #saveh2b - #savesmallbusinesses -Help Needed @realDonaldTrump @SecretaryAcosta @SecNielsen https://t.co/TYo2fKRDu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChetPowell I don't like it either. Reminds me of when people act like their kids are dating. I hate that stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is hilarious. 'When all hope of Katara/Zuko being canon was extinguished. Dark Horse Com… https://t.co/YOMuOSIfFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Congress should demand you and your Families TAX RETURNS for the past 10 yrs.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking through my phone and found this from @snailmusic back in december lmao https://t.co/ETYSgad6wF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @CricketixSue I believe @AOC covered that with her questions in the hearing. Like a lot of criminals… https://t.co/CN4T8sN2Vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenalauroba @JordaMarilo @despistao1 @SyP_tve @evelascoq @angel_syper @mystery_XX @gloriazuri @CF_EduVelasco… https://t.co/40OH6C0IW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they ask how I did this after a week long cruise, I’ll say “Never Enough” Berry Martinis for me! djrolandbelma… https://t.co/ZrsQo2WeXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faithandsoaps @joshgriffith59 @YandR_CBS @YRInsider @SteveKentSony Sherry, I agree ☝️ I just read an article that… https://t.co/nBfiaHk4ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im unironically on gun girls side in her beef w that barstool guy. I bet he’s the one that pooped his pants at a pa… https://t.co/N41HsaUDbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soundlyawake I’m a Sagittarius and that’s why I gotta come back home with you guys tonight. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyDoyleSequel tell them the only safe milk is goat milk but THEY don't want anyone to know that]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang amusing. #mirth #tee-hee #grin #ludicrous https://t.co/IinmOgETo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnus needs to just be given his powers back #ShadowhuntersLegacy #ShadowhuntersChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi friends! I’ve been using a new twitter for a while but figured I’d tell this one about my EP that just released… https://t.co/FDgrOFpULO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an entire gym but you decided that directly in front of the dumbbell rack was a great place to jump rope? https://t.co/aLlF9rKYzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertgp421 Would be the same rage I would have if I had access to a really nice MacBook and then find out the tou… https://t.co/izP4Upf4mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeebus, I hate late night guilt trips from Mandee. I woke up at 3:30 AM to get shit done and there was like 10 fuck… https://t.co/DQgS6Rbsa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_withoutalcohol Thanks! Got good news this afternoon. We received their placement letter which means they are for… https://t.co/N5Xnf63glo]]></document><document><![CDATA[High on top the #mountain. The #melting #snow formed a gossamer ribbon of a roaring #waterfall cutting into the she… https://t.co/DK3aYyev3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KClausing @JohnJHarwood Thanks for nothing Trump! Your Tariffs hurt our country as do you🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just one work day and a flight away from the #BackToBedside #ACGME2019 pre-conference! Can’t wait to delve into our… https://t.co/hlutAm1AP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Sympathy For The Devil - 50th Anniversary Edition by The Rolling Stones… https://t.co/P6GXvqifNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefutureyousee I think that’s fair and accurate. *indulges in a further five seconds of blank gazing*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinker_Bell_04 @GOP This woman is dangerous. Vaccinations are the most important thing we can do to stop unwanted… https://t.co/bv01RpsCuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que servicio tan de la chingada tienen en Culiacán @Uber_MEX no sé para que existen aquí.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what sucks. Which I totally don't blame her if she just packs her bags and goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gntsmusic Michael Joseph and I would like 2 THANK You ♥️ for that mention of his music! 🎶 @kmichaeljoseph and Emil… https://t.co/C2CQKgMIGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmpiresFate @Scott05143867 @McAllisterDen @KamalaHarris You never will... you follow a Conman so SAD🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman is advised she lacks standing to participate in a discussion of motherhood by... man. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you EVER have ANYTHING positive to say? Is the entire world and your entire country anything but the enemy to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craft_curiosity @beerkulture This is the legal equivalent of “He didn’t HAVE to sign the contract. He didn’t HAVE… https://t.co/Ear4ZxB9jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found the lost tank top in with my other laundry! Well, now I have two 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[josi saying he’d love to have nino on his team... no u can’t have him. he’s ours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Packers send: 19th overall pick (which turned into Tony Smith)  Falcons send: Brett Favre]]></document><document><![CDATA[This crazy weight loss journey is getting better and better. I can’t wait to see the final results!! https://t.co/1RoP13TpgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is your favorite outfit?! - I did this in my stories recently and had so much fun... thought I’d ask your opin… https://t.co/dlkftGZ41e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally at the #beach #naplesflorida 🌞🏊🏻‍♀️🏝🏖#yumandmore @ Naples, Florida https://t.co/YIEJpyjylm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBerrySho @EsotericCD We did.  Although some in our group didn’t get it. But that’s ok, they’re like superfragalistically smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spent the last 10 mins frantically looking for my juul that I thought I had dropped on the ground outside..… https://t.co/T5ORO0qEu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nossa amada #timessquare Na #fashionweeknewyork  Cidade linda c ele drbrunosalomao  #newyork #timessquare… https://t.co/FhwlshaaQb]]></document></documents></author>