<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Qué genial sería contar con un equipo de @MLB en México   ¡El mexicano Roberto Ramos pegó jonrón en la 6a! 👏🏼⚾️… https://t.co/uwtRBpWVpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, awesome to see my pal @hairmetalhenry last night. We need to get the band back together soon. @KellyRippin… https://t.co/BlMDz1xBVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Society by King Tru | Free Listening on SoundCloud https://t.co/Kj73BRMcpM @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe… https://t.co/GqtMp30hND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOGTayMac Idk for real start a rumor see how it goes.. make my decision after 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerbRider Probably because people like me who like LW because it was fun, universal thought it only needed to try… https://t.co/p66wcfSHVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEALTeam_MIA @SealTeamcbsfans @ToniTrucks @SEALTeamCBS Damn right! She’s such a natural!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19 #mvsu_rys19… https://t.co/gyFmAy5mJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlSecurity_ @SebastianBae @RANDCorporation @WarOnTheRocks @StaciePettyjohn @becca_wasser Unintentionally left… https://t.co/6xHHjkvvlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to find people u can trust these days legit people will act one way when ur around and when ur not around… https://t.co/SqCGc80pH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it's dinosaurs that watch us fuck 🤔 or dinosaurs were actually aliens 😮 https://t.co/iwuaX9K4Ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are the #Nuggets playing that #BarbershopQuartet team from the commercial? https://t.co/DM7dlze1ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp @amyklobuchar .. she has ZERO plans for anything ..  #popularTalkingPoints #fakeProgressive #Murica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoUte If Alabama and the Patriots can manufacture a chip on their shoulder the Utes ought to be able to manage!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cucogzz1 Si ellos metieran todas o fueran más contundentes mamarian hasta a Tuca. Pero como Fallan un Chingo toda… https://t.co/OU3gHRqIIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 In my late teens I worked with a couple of guys that were gay, and hid it. They were nice, always frien… https://t.co/17mwzJPHtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kurkjian_ESPN I dont know what player you are watching but looks like Dustin still has the hop]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next car that’s parked in my carport spot when I get home from work is getting set on fire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines everyone from the curious mind!! @EOYIreland @OBriensWine @LeitrimToday @PalmBay_Wines… https://t.co/2eKCAw92GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for posting youtube videos featuring halestorm inthismoment Ghost band]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tabby_tabtab3 Lol yeah that’s the logic I’m goin with too. 2 Chainz never disappoints tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we found @chelsea_janes pun replacement for the Nats. @meganemcconnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 That's one sturdy crib. Not usually made for 200 pound babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStorageNet @CTOAdvisor We can scale to infinity as long as it is within a single data center.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 4 white hairs (that I know of) on my head and idk if art school is just stressing me out, but I’m ready to start my midlife crisis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive Hey Juan if Trump should be removed for paying off a porn star what should be done to congress for having… https://t.co/kN1H35kWOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...Well, at least it's not you #posthumous #biography!  #lol There's still #TIME...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Of course it's a record crowd...they all are #FuckingMoron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precip tdy@ Colesville,MD 17mi NNE of the WH:0.6"snow/0.17"liquid;Mar snow tot=2.3"making this 7th straight Mar tot… https://t.co/eFFgN45yiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad behind amazing father-daughter photo series shares his secrets - https://t.co/PJaXRUjAmB - SO cute, silly fathe… https://t.co/egAS9x6W2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic moving faster on 93 in Andover. You can see some pavement. Plows making progress. Changeover continues, get… https://t.co/SAZx1SlJk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJoeMarino @DraftNetworkLLC Drafting like a raider... https://t.co/daiJ89bekg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does ESPN let @damienwoody talk? Heard him on a Broncos segment today and he could barley spit his words out or… https://t.co/dKuBo3dCei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp 25 degrees this morning!! Hope this kills off some of the knats and mosquitoes @ Watson, Louisiana https://t.co/pbJ7ii6xvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @TresaBridges @SSG_Davis_Ret @Birdseye1 @CarolGarofolo @intelligent50 @Whichsideareuon @Muttonchap… https://t.co/fDAlknPwgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedrunkpenguin @Rasnick_Kevin I vape now, just because of the quitting smoking thing. Well I’ve had a nice mod fo… https://t.co/hjvPoJkzXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apoure25 Got a pair of their 747’s in Shark Fin livery and an older-design 707. Some of my favorites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld @TheFive @FoxNews  Great, succint summary of the basic, important difference between #capitalism &amp;… https://t.co/ZqxgZwMUo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[thankful for the lovely @Emily_Welford after i woke up this morning i had a black eye from u 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I'm heading to a social affair (hanging out with other humans) I briefly, but seriously, consider purpos… https://t.co/aQT973S9Qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A passerby heard a newborn crying in a storm drain. Four hours later, she was rescued. - CNN https://t.co/7C303I9lcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomMobile I am extremely pissed off. I switched over to your pay after billing. You said NO INTERRUPTIONS. Ton… https://t.co/SHSJdjENOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMediaGB @ExtinctionR @GretaThunberg @uoftsu Student have a democratic right to speak out, oppose, lobby, prose… https://t.co/mK9IyYJRvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to play rock n rock! #blues4life #howigetaround @visitmusiccity @ East Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/wBO72iNlwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to host such a dedicated group of teachers this past weekend. Your enthusiasm and thoughtful ques… https://t.co/BWeBHbUlJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been working in Odessa office all day...leaving finally  #AttorneyDeAnda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orlandomayor @citybeautiful Proud graduate of the Mayor’s Academy - truly a wonderful program providing great insi… https://t.co/lgZPGF24cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to do a hardware test. The proof is in the Purple Monkey Banana Pants. https://t.co/yGDUTPTngR]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk. 33 Examples Of "You Had One Job" Ok, maybe it's me, because I'm an artist, but... #hilarity #tee-hee #grin… https://t.co/3EGs2CtbU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Truth Barred  A collection of work by nine writers at the Oregon State Penintentiary  Get your copy by contact… https://t.co/GiSD41t437]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NijmieZD If I forget be sure to remind me, I don’t have the time this evening, but I have a bunch of really great… https://t.co/KEIpv5fyJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #StormJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowboycomputer I agree w ya on the Irving/Gregory thing 100%  GO COWBOYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hans_zollner What BS. All the CC leadership has to do is order that when a Pope, Cardinal, Bishop or Priest is acc… https://t.co/F3ZEscX8n4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenEyas @DVRK_NoVa That reminds me of when I had to heal both of you asses in Sophia ex when it dropped. Y’all g… https://t.co/zntAaYmBSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t find this empowering and stunning than your a sexist bigot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macdaddyrhodes As soon as I saw that I was like yeah that’s a knee injury]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a conservative who’s a stoner to revolution gun rights and marijuana rights because this America the way our 17… https://t.co/dP3nZKC4ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great family dinner tonight at stateandmain Barrie celebrating these two siblings @afuters19 and instagramless Aust… https://t.co/h1JfCO7YUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twinkletoes42 @kathygriffin BORDER SECURITY. DONT MOVE I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth… https://t.co/eH6zPgiiyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thornridge Regional  1:52 to go Rich South 56 Hillcrest 63 #RichInStudentSuccess  #RSStarPower]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugeneCar2 @thesavoyshow They were trying to get her in the big money club and she was crying about pennies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superconfirmado eso suena como silla eléctrica.. tranquilo por lo momentos no la tienes lista pero pronto muy pron… https://t.co/2SUKS36W6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come in and see various works by Fever Furnishings today from 10 to 1 pm inside at Cecy’s. . . . #durham #duke… https://t.co/afjgLxpurm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerynoelia @JosueIsOnline Exato.Votei em B 17 mas político existe para ser cobrado ,jamais endeusado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccpecknold Conditions that make it easy to abuse: [Catholic hierarchy secrecy, no zero-tolerance re Bishop account… https://t.co/rYzQkfolIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatChickMickky Being in a group is it random? Or I can choice not to be with minors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is #Jesus depicted with a #magicwand of some kind as he raises Lazarus from the dead in this art from ancient R… https://t.co/qoYXOT7uet]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s now a cat who legally has more money than I will ever see in my lifetime https://t.co/fPgEg5WJD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raini_Rodriguez Cool commercial! Fun fact: Sam Gordon, the young female football player at the :09 mark in this co… https://t.co/Nr9sQeJ2PN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trash day in Michigan! #yesmichigan #trashday #thestruggleisreal #PolarVortex2019 https://t.co/jEdbBiaD6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[With God, there is more than one way to quench your thirst...#LifeWithGod #Luv2All 🛐 https://t.co/tbLax6j0yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend and i are gonna make the cutest mixed little baby can’t wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me before the National Emergency vs me during the National Emergency https://t.co/DavGdy8A0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvmypittys @prosa62910191 @PhilMcCrackin44 @DNC @AOC @SpeakerPelosi @chuckschumer @HouseDemocrats… https://t.co/4Cfcnl86te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davesportsgod @NBCSportsRadio #I got it fam!I’m hyped up about hearing you on @SBNation RADIO 📻 #Dave Smith! (Don… https://t.co/6N9iR3J97K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cshanny55 @ThunderT16 @DerrickOnSports Hey sometimes the dirt shit passes go into the net like on Saturday 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how the two characters you unlock in Apex Legends have the worst ultimates, thanks @EA 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Hammill - Still Life (Berlin, Quasimodo, 26 May 2018) https://t.co/kk35KJY7vK via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Sen. @TomDaschle for joining our U.S. @SenateYouth Alumni Assoc. awards dinner to receive the Rosalie Wyn… https://t.co/paXK6BvTDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letterkenny is wrecking my vocab, like right now I'm "headin' to the offy to crush a couple praccy exams, jus' given'er ferda."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaulNazario @UniNoticias 🤣..no puede haber persona mas ignorante q tú.. Crimen es la acción voluntaria de herir gr… https://t.co/eSKAeSlPUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbeyfern @Telemundo48 @nbcbayarea ¡Thank you Abbey! And you rock for putting this together 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻 I know you’… https://t.co/vlktKdwbUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told someone I don’t appreciate homophobic slurs towards lgbt community people,even if I completely removed said… https://t.co/wB8sg5mJNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This big guy was trying to hide this morning... great coloring on him.  #redcardinal #inmybackyard #hidingabit… https://t.co/BCviQxniXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had a chance to add a 26 year old all-star 3B/SS. A position you need to fill. You were willing to go to repor… https://t.co/2PEDXjWUWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mullins The monsters.  They were so preoccupied with figuring out if they could, they didn't stop to think if they should.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un wants renegotiate the Louisiana Purchase with Trump. Trump's response: Ok, but I'm keeping Louisiana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/nqHeaqqOW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[With NKorea Agreement, NKorea can have denuclearization and disarmament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wonderful #dinner #losangeles #greatcompany #enjoyinglife #great #talks #inspired by #myfavorite #actingcoach Javi… https://t.co/ZRm9b14410]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been calling games for this squad for 4 years. Congrats boys, enjoy the stretch run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @poroshenko @ashrafghani @NATO @jensstoltenberg @POTUS You are apparently as delusional as he.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreFirezTV It was literally the perfect thing to have while traveling past couple weeks. T99 is still top of their charts too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horsesandbeer Same here and paying even more for them since separation]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:45.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekyJerseys @Lototheran this is totally you. You need to win the Pickle Rick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseOyuma @sistervpaul_ @disciple96 @1207go @EdIsBackKAG2020 @DrSueDVM @Lampasvlad @NaranjoFdez @Matthew82060400… https://t.co/OrlL2YIuLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrAvgGF You definitely were the most creative. Felt like @UrAvgConsumer went back to the normal stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @_cingraham @yashar Wait, is @yashar the new Oprah? What a time we live in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jko410 WHERE  IS THE FUCKING  FCC AT.   GOD DAMN FCC DO YOUR FUCKING JOB, AND SHUT THIS SHIT DOWN NOW. SHUT CNN DO… https://t.co/twNn9D61R8]]></document></documents></author>