<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I wonder what Will is dreaming about lol he sleep talking about “what chu thought was gone happen” 😐 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gany760 Happy Birthday! Hope you and Sis have a great day!❤❤😘🎉🎉🎉🎉 https://t.co/Qb2ocJW9I1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JhaveriVatsala @Communism_Kills @EoinHiggins_ @AOC I just can’t help but go back to this tweet now that the backpe… https://t.co/kSKeN1WDHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone plz tell me why he does this 😥 lol . He usually whines when doing this so I initially thought he does it be… https://t.co/Ug9HBYxtTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@sup_romeo FaceTimed me and caught me red handed drinking wine in my gma pajamas on a Saturday night 😂🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[my prof just started calling on every person to talk about the chapter we were supposed to read. 4 people have walked out so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell us how you are or what you do... Tag your website 💥💥💥 https://t.co/zEyAB2YOh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOT my president @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @Jordan_Sather_ @Jeffrey16122997]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealStanLee @theblackpanther @SpiderVerse STANNLEE U ARE MISSED EACH AND EVERY DAY AND MOST OF ALL U WILL ALWAYS BE OUR SUPER HERO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VemVerReality @stdaniela Perfeita sua colocação. Clara era gigante, merecia muito mais. Eu e @stdaniela estávamos… https://t.co/hXvzjfretf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodHillis1 @NJ_2_FL @RL9631 @jonz970 @amicah1 @rdrhwke @ncar999 @Sekusa1 @clovis1931 @mymynags @arkiegal411… https://t.co/clDG7KrCE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like sharing cool jewelry.  Place a bid and get some very cool earrings. Beautiful Blue Abalone earrings.  https://t.co/bnUy951Z38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting today, I’m tracking what i eat and working out everyday bc fuck this funk I’m in 💪👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I replaced my cracked ass phone screen and now I feel like I got a new one lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque los hombres cuando hablan con su novia adelante de su familia o amigos no le dicen amor?, les da pena o algo así?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple hours of video shooting and a couple hundred photos on my phone later, we’re ready for admit day🙃 #HESM https://t.co/OO8DCvHyt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__ashh0le__ Exactly! I’ll never understand it or the girls who find the guys who have nothing to do with their chi… https://t.co/xOJraER7SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @Bren_O1967 @MySwilly @TonyaRBlue1 @social_stars Lol! Have a great one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 11:  (okay still kind of day 10)  The atrocious humiliations I suffered as a result of a few poorly timed cough… https://t.co/2oony6wTOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[just one thing that messed up everything but i would do anything to make it work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @BachelorABC there better be a fence getting jumped tonight!! @LisaVS49 it better happen!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmccaff100692 @DorisZelaya5 @darrynzewalk @zane_beale @IAmZombieRae @arnie_bragg @BkcProv3110 @benukoro Amen! Then… https://t.co/YnS48ylKa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGAEItaly @ilvolo @ilvoloesc2015 A great honor, well deserved !!!!!!!!!!!!!💙💜❤️🇨🇦💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[С тех пор, как я переехала сюда в ранней юности, мне пришлось выслушать невероятное количество лекций по географии… https://t.co/gVQ50tMRF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thabigdonSean @dbongino @seanhannity Won’t miss it for the world Dan love you and Sean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMCervantez @rome869 I’m never tired. Why are people always complaining? 💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Approaching 6hrs since this parade (Bacchus) started and it still hasn’t ended. Unreal. Mardi Gras is loud, crazy a… https://t.co/18oE264zKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWDFamilyy Carol won’t stand for Henry being mistreated. Alpha is about to meet her match. And Carol please cut yo… https://t.co/XX0rNMhZGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annie_cornett Wow bitch you need therapy for your traumatic life issues it seems if you gotta make shit like this… https://t.co/GcWYPFmU6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smile #smilemore #abrahamhicks #enjoy #allow @ Laveen, Arizona https://t.co/AY1VV4Zocz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I think it's time that the public gets a lawyer to then to protect our votes and our rights we voted… https://t.co/Gz1fzTuLlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can knock this meeting out today, I can come back home and sleep. That’s goals. 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature But I will find them. Ha-haa. Hey I have to eat too you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DENTIST APPRECIATION DAY  Even long term patient, Griffith, got in on the love!  😊 Thanks! It's been great watching… https://t.co/3zyekVzx9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingPrideSimba Mufasa's eyes are a bit smaller than yours in size, but other than that, yeah you two do look alike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on the amount of hair I clean out of my brush every week, I should actually be bald by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_Lindahl @RMFifthCircuit I'm completely the opposite. I love taking notes 😍 Usually I show out with multiple po… https://t.co/mhQPMTKxyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro Viva Maduro. El de vero presidente constitucional de estado soberano de Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missy quite likes Clever, but Twelve doesn’t seem too amused. #cleverdoesgally #missy #twelfthdoctor #gallifreyone… https://t.co/CmdmwuCPim]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @nomiprins loves my comedy...All is right in the world! Love you Nomi...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weoutchea in these pre-mardi gras streets @ Soulard Saint Louis https://t.co/mOtQwbR7NA]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Me and Syd watching The Boy in the Striped Pajamas*  Syd: ... ohhhh they're not really pajamas  🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceandPamela Bruce did a good job this morning opposite Jim Sharpie (Sharp)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so can we be done with this Momo nonsense now?  We love to get hysterical in this world.  I have enough to worry… https://t.co/l3yoZdIPEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[School will be closed today, Monday, February 25, due to high winds and road conditions. Stay safe! https://t.co/1zJNmdFyIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Well behaved women seldom make history.”  💜 I am confident Laurel Thatcher Ulrich would’ve been my homegirl for su… https://t.co/2pxO60Q0Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s take the doors out of the @Jeep and take pictures! 📸 by @doseofmoraa  #CIAS2019 https://t.co/j4POHUqVZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY VALENTINES DAY!  Christi Jones w/ Russell Stover telling about the process of making chocolate covered strawb… https://t.co/fglhcnxpvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImMicahNelson @WillCun45428725 @ACLU IMO, doesn't work here though, as sonograms improve as well as surgery done w… https://t.co/WnlMnNRTWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s no secret that our society is plagued by guys like Ryan Adams, but I think it cuts more deeply when it’s an ar… https://t.co/WJBilFYPsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: this Studio 54 documentary on Nextflix is very good and you should watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Stuff your fake apology where the sun doesn't. If you're not disbarred, I hope Speaker… https://t.co/MTZO60GWmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump surrounds himself with liars and criminals. If/when associates like Cohen flip, who exactly will the @GOP con… https://t.co/zv2YSYQZQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellen Hunt, Named a 2019 Trust Across America Lifetime Achievement Award Honoree - https://t.co/2PuXEbYDsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was lit tonight been a minute even tho I’m connected to this Machine for the rest of my life I ain’t gone let th… https://t.co/9ONJ4IPAwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Once you get into team sports and you see how you are succeeding, you understand it isn’t about you. In order for… https://t.co/b8C1xmLXwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carlsbad break in the rain @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/xg0c6Revk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieunderwood and @YolandaAdams got me like... #ElvisAllStarTribute https://t.co/3MZsjeyThk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck sex can we drink &amp; vibe? I mean we still fucking but I wanna drink first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnhealth I’m sure the street value of special K is cheaper @ALostAstral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@purevictory7 @howshehustles Great to see you again Nicole.Thanks for helping Emily with all her #howshehustles eve… https://t.co/YkU60BC2ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul KY hates you now you've blown your career and embarrassed the people who trusted you with their votes as… https://t.co/YI7IhcVYLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EuphoriccDreams I have more where those came from but just never posted them bc some people would be offended by t… https://t.co/yGMfbWCu4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LabradorYuki I’m sure the neighborhood appreciates your constant vigil!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaniebianca @MichelleObama This is the best thing I’ve ever seen. #GOALS]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sis &amp; i are FINALLY going on vacay this year w just the two of us 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSLosAngeles Thank you for sharing! We have such great viewers that share great images with us! And THANK YOU… https://t.co/w81OLQRUS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: I love letting the ss go into the spotlight by sharing what they are learning and helping each other throughout… https://t.co/P5Whq9Kjj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstn692 @haifabale @sonajera7 @_chris_jones @clynnsouthdfw @ChrisShepard001 @Kendall_NTX @brittgit03 Thank you… https://t.co/WRfDqFOW0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are out of your mind - trying to sugar coat the green new deal - People - seriously if you don’t have an extra… https://t.co/pNcFcscVYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great session yesterday @CFISDELs ❤️ I love walking away with new learning! @edwards_latish @MindyHidalgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Share  *I Do Not Own Copyrights To This Music  Never Thought I’d Be My Own Boss All While Doing Something I Truly… https://t.co/h3LmPRfVcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also this wrong thing was tweeted.   So now you are caught up. Sorry. https://t.co/4nNXC5GZeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iberia_en y’all have until 10pm to get my bag to me or you are going to have the angriest bitch you ever seen on y’all line]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to get an actual photography camera to capture more moments 🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump It's rich when a trumpuglican bitches about 'malignant arrogance' but supports that… https://t.co/1EaxxfKu05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes life is gonna scare the shit out of you. ⁣ ⁣ Your body is gonna scare the shit out of you. ⁣ ⁣ Your job i… https://t.co/RO1fqeFhmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATOLE CON EL DEDO por @lopezobrador_   Series of increasingly tough actions in #Mexico suggest #LopezObrador has tu… https://t.co/DysjGrKlOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on lawyers lets do right by these girls, this is disgusting.  Steve Hansen would have already fryed this guy.… https://t.co/c4Fnr6lb2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my #birthday! This is the first photo of me 🥰   Photographer: Dad Camera: Disposable Lens: Plastic @ Central D… https://t.co/Aepw3Kifn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul is so wrong in not voting with #POTUS and in no way is it an abuse of power. I would expect Mr. Rand to k… https://t.co/mu9TfCnSCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR Right but @Netflix hasn't figured out sorting their low volume and grainy streaming quality.  Amazon has but n… https://t.co/rTpuMKoK51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guilty. I have crossed Mt Gaming to get through the Mountains of Distraction and found myself stuck in Social Media… https://t.co/bkSOeB8eoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transgender girls are very interesting because in many cases they go from average looking guy to a beautiful girl!… https://t.co/ZTirgVXNGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJL_Edu Also, can’t wait to see you!! You’re getting a major hug, just like @wargojon! 😘 https://t.co/R7Lsi66kit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine's!! Happy Love day all!! ♥️♥️ #ValentinesDay #love https://t.co/513xym9bdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th Grade is learning about...The artist John James Audubon who linked “Art with Science.”They will learn about dif… https://t.co/tPQ6XbdsXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StringAndRudder Exactly. I don’t want to support/give money to a company like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful #contentcreationcompanies constantly repurpose their #content and add images and #infographics to furthe… https://t.co/jNztmCzbqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shiny happy people. @ Atlantic Ave - Delray Beach https://t.co/oPFIoaaa1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This coming from the biggest liar the world has ever seen! I would believe him over you any day Do… https://t.co/qTNtERPsC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trace_reyes Sure. Just choose what kind of shipping you want when you check out at my store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted my challenge from @MrsHerrera_WCB to post covers of 7 children’s books I LOVE: no explanations, no re… https://t.co/CeNAQ5MOMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTBR313 Definitely! It's also why I keep a reading notebook (mostly just a list of what I've read...) but this… https://t.co/vluEKKhZEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[just took a long hot shower— sometimes i forget how therapeutic that is. #yesss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coconut-lime rice with red beans and mango!! This is so delicious, it's been a minute since I last made this🤗 @ Ana… https://t.co/P7iSYicGVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianacoronadof El tráfico y todas las tiendas, perdí unas 3 horas de mi vida gracias a eso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJacobEspi I found some of your roughs from portfolio just the other day. Great stuff 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren’t a certain minority you littlerally can’t speak on what it’s like to be that minority. Let them do the… https://t.co/ZhQAg6lzq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found my mother's Henry Lloyd sneakers from when she worked on boats in the Exumas in the '80s before immigr… https://t.co/07Nutzz1WP]]></document></documents></author>