<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Interesting and informative that Lib members voted against having Butts testify under oath and he also declined tha… https://t.co/AjvHfqVCrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views lowkey grew on me. I think I just wrote it off so quick as trash cause i was 16 at the time I dropped so I aint really care as much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday mood!!! Don’t hate the player... hate yourself for not leveling up! #GetchaMindRight #TGIM🦁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaminaSnuka You should’ve superkicked her @LaceyEvansWWE and send her back to NXT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm proud to unveil the cover for Origins: Rabid Apocalypse (Book 0)!   Pre-order information will be available in… https://t.co/murR1chXAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[These faggots in the church messing up the lives of people’s children must be exposed everywhere and made to pay th… https://t.co/1O5wSz7Lwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteakNBake2 @Benaskren Barbarena literally just got slept like 2 weeks ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bezos, Buffett and Dimon name their health care effort - CNN https://t.co/FBIKgFBi5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[shownthe full replay again @TheTraeYoung nudge @KrisDunn3 thats why he got slapped dont play slick homie big ups to… https://t.co/gcgYdlHlkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanMorrow LOL! Not much to say. Like @PhxSaltyDog said, Brian Green has this program rolling and the Aggies loo… https://t.co/DFC4KmfwwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thejessicakorda I have both of you on my fantasy golf team. Get well and three cheers for Nelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaran_13 @javiparada Nunca mas se puso sobria.lastima por el gran apellido q lleva..lo mancha..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PreservationHouston held their 40th Good Bricks Gala.   Congratulations to all honorees and the outstanding projec… https://t.co/8opyfuHW0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh, Hello - it was a passing hypothetical comment in a pile of issues being bounced around. Let’s not be hysterical… https://t.co/HgLS6uEpfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eadoyle If this happens again and you need a lawyer to get mean, please lmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the 2020 general election, I will vote for whomever is the Democratic nominee for US President. Full stop. Perio… https://t.co/4sgdxR1hy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you a supervisor but don’t know how to change a fuckin ice maker wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[PULIDO, SANDRA charged with POSSESSION CONTROLLED SUBSTANCE PG 1  1 - 4 GRAMS in #HOUSTON - https://t.co/AaVbDnBXxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1AmericanMama @10thAmendment @1776Stonewall @actlightning @2018MAGAMidTrmT @AIIAmericanGirI @2runtherace @Alisand3… https://t.co/ZFnAgSKYdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter when are the Giants gonna get players from free agency...  I’m waiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Democrats don't care about the American people!! Democrats only care being in control!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit tougher than normal to get hockey photos out to you guys when it’s ... you know ... raining on the ice. I’ll… https://t.co/F8sZRKmxWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headcoachead Need more tweets!!! Yours are my faves and totally put me in the right head space for my day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In order to have a good perspective, one must climb up and look out. 🔻 And truth be told, you'll be knocked down an… https://t.co/BmzoDVoRIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tj_hunter @TLHBeerSociety @DannyAller Good to be following the leaders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyBoyCasey It shouldn’t have even come down to the last few seconds. Sixers can’t keep blowing double digit leads in the second half]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was always something more important to do. Or something more enjoyable. Or I just wanted to chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#notetoself : after an entire workout + some extra (3x5 back squat 215lb + 3x5 bench press 155lb) if u wanna a litt… https://t.co/NNgQYoHrkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completing our #loudjamz three song #beck retrospective Devil’s Haircut featuring @analogwalrus vocals… https://t.co/SuSDhyTs3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedding Photography . . #kcphotographers #wedding #weddingphotographer #weddingphotography #missionkansas @ Kansas… https://t.co/NXY2WR0dUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like morning sex but nothing in this world that I like more than checks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill and Ted had it right... "Be Excellent to Each Other" https://t.co/UuPXd4BwST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmileyYYC @jimrome He’ll rip it away, it’s all to add drama and tweak people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeyciLaExce @ArcangelPrrra Ponme en el top 1 aqui mama bicho jajajajajjaajajaajajajaajja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapRogers2020 @1IronMan2020 Expectations are gas prices going to 3 dollars a gallon thanks to trump sanctions on I… https://t.co/AxxWUpvZbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh hell nah.. he would've gotten more than just one punch #AmericanSoulBET]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just about quittin time on this end. I’m off to hunt protection roses after this. Protection roses keep you sa… https://t.co/fhqOzhfg1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a HUGE #meteor shooting across the sky! It was super bright and went all the way across. One of the best I've ever seen! 🌠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_pence @realDonaldTrump @MattBevin #LGBexit #TakeBackPride Recognition of The True Gay Community in June by… https://t.co/46pzPgYUeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise @ALTHEA595 It's hard to understand why the democrats keep doing things that hurt our country, Steve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chikinstu @EdLambdaTeos I’m really happy you’re enjoying it, @instagahmy and I watched it together and it was so f… https://t.co/6kJLAVPezh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaNESSIEp He’s a UFA....you know we won’t re-sign him so you need to move him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jomar didn’t pause for the corner 3 to win the game and Newdini pinched instead of baiting and gave up a corner 3 t… https://t.co/VbvLnpXngB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hurt people that love us  &amp; love people that hurt us. https://t.co/AJn8g9sxv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony will take care of ya!! #like #collision #paint #repair #dentremoval #bodywork @ Wilber Auto Body &amp; Sales https://t.co/UHGBwVbik2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanDCarballo @garytalmeida @ShaqsBaq @WWE @shanemcmahon 2007 vs. Lashley]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard order @Starbucks today. 1 tall coffee w/ 10 pumps of vanilla syrup 😳 #sweettooth #sugarrush #helovesvanilla #SXSW2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MutCallahan @GerryCallahan Get rid of the guy who can't talk please??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris Is there a report that states the correct number? How far off was his statement from the truth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter Maya, loves to draw anime characters. I told her for fun she should put together a picture of her famil… https://t.co/DcbFK2E8bR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mall or Big Top? #mall. cfsherway @ CF Sherway Gardens https://t.co/Qnq1lWNfr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does beer taste like after a peppermint patty? 😖🍬🍺 https://t.co/EEkVB0tGFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh, got my custom heal/toe shifters on my scoot..it never ends🤘💀🤘 https://t.co/zohpvNZhj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[An accurately scathing critique of the Ohio State Legislature, charter schools and urban school funding.  Charter s… https://t.co/YmX6lmr1gP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Radcliffe I truly hope they can master that system. As a note: I rather defend well and score than having pos… https://t.co/txJgPx8SAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BootscootinGMaw @FarmChicJodi @DozaEric @IHboog @kelcey1992 @GardnerKatyg8 @scoopermomma @Clint__Taylor… https://t.co/z3jYymxeyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to be continuing my partnership with @pjuractive for the 2019 season. Looks like they have set me up well for… https://t.co/TVy87SWbP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuggets Worst nuggets fan ever, I'm ashamed this is allowed. Racism is not for #Denver not for #Nuggets… https://t.co/UWTO7aBSAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The director player personnel in charge of all recruiting. He will be a man in demand if he is not all ready. Schoo… https://t.co/wXsUCOB5Iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks like a @JoeGibbsRacing show at @DISupdates #Dayton500 @NASCARONFOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new #Pokémon games remind me of this #PokemonSwordShield https://t.co/D9L3KKavsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[MTune to Channel 69 News at 4pm with @JimVaughnWFMZ @Melanie_Falcon and @Joy_Howe]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember when Perks of Being A Wallflower came out and every girl with a Tumblr thought they were famous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lincoln Abes Basketball had a great season with (2) D1 Football Prospects “Simon Brothers” anchoring the team. https://t.co/qsB7XMBvMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenFulop It does bring up an important point: forced parking ratios (mostly in suburbs) are a big factor in ris… https://t.co/6kUmjhDPEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELL!! That was SO much fun! Always great to be at the ballpark and saw SO many friendly faces and got hugs and han… https://t.co/0yuz278sA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[14.5 seconds to go in a blowout game, 85-68 Fort Lewis College. Guys jawing with each other and refs feel need to h… https://t.co/9PURXDvzIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaSolar @MKerryFuller @woods0419 @CloydRivers Good for u! You're right, too. If it's not from an Ivy league uni… https://t.co/d8cFPgviDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ask_trim Does it cancel the subscription for you or just tell you what is active and (potentially) what you might want to cancel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Wednesday, Feb. 20, 1861  James Buchanan is President Abraham Lincoln is President-Elect Inauguration Day is M… https://t.co/OBK8UQHqrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Set__The__Tone @TaylorPurus27 @girlpool @HOOMESHAAKE @KayakJonesIA Haha thank you for the kind words brother ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceyZeee @MarkDice @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews While CNN just cheats and gives Clinton questions ahead of debates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewJayEvans1 @seanhannity Whitewater, should still be going on with the Clinton crime regime. Also not costing… https://t.co/9J622nYNfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @BuschBeer @KevinHarvick @StewartHaasRcng @BuschBeer Good Morning staff, crew, team,… https://t.co/QrBaqqVM4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMGduji @johncusack @akroncivic You owe everyone a refund for tonight. What a debacle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone First Prototype. Got destroyed in one particular fight a dozen times and just quit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss @RyanKost'swonderful @sfchronicle story on the historic matchbooks and ephemera of SF's fabled Tenderloi… https://t.co/e5ln2tUxTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[She marries a guy theee times her age for his money. But keeps her hot guy on the side. #ForeverAmber: The Amber Ni… https://t.co/eSrmD0WbOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my bro @Michaelconery70 glad I got to play ball with you these last 2 years. Can’t wait to see wh… https://t.co/r7ueycI7xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinTake2 @Mimi_Can_Voice @stevezaragoza You're supposed to do a lot of things. But cold syrup doesn't pour and… https://t.co/7HZJNRm3Tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet me at #ExtinctionRebellion #Chicago #RXchicago @ExtinctionR #ExtinctionR #occupytheneedact #theNeedAct for all… https://t.co/tk1p0Yr6C0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven't heard already, check out the band Dead Sara- I've fallen in love with her style]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @AllaiyahB (get_repost) ・・・ #GOODMORNING  total_kaoz_krew will be performing at our show tomorrow!👑 You don… https://t.co/AHb2UO0bXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 Why didn’t the ones standing there, watching and videoing do something ??? 🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another freight free weekend!!! Awesome job @SilviaT59002460 and to our freight team!!! Thank you all for all the h… https://t.co/CAWFRTzWxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoMasure mais quand le peuple est mal alimenté, il y a presque toujours ce genre d’interprétation. Le pouvoir m… https://t.co/nCuwD5QOft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hat Not Hate video 2019 is live for 2019 is live.  https://t.co/PnvYoKFDfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnyGuyEv @D_man951 @eortega06 Who did he have the last 3 years Evan. Tell me who he was throwing too]]></document><document><![CDATA[thread:  i put this on my insta story a few days ago. i wrote this song in november/december 2017 while i was in a… https://t.co/LRDQJPNPPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Parker Broadus, he wrestled in his very first wrestling tournament ever off of three weeks of practice… https://t.co/pjJ1XWc8uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un favor: Alguien le puede decirle a los reporteros que asisten a las conferencias mañaneras de Amlo, que le pregun… https://t.co/2F3dhdMKwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ the keyboard &amp; touchpad on my new MacBook... so much better than the prior version. @ San Diego, California https://t.co/r0YbGf6A2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't have to watch the doc to believe the victims and know how a person with power can abuse that power to hurt… https://t.co/5td7hRH0Jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Austen @arjunblj Dunno. Worked for 5 of them. Schools track that first job, especially Lambda given ISA. But that’… https://t.co/UVVTITXRFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still unparalleled in the division of house dressing. Still the best lasagna. (@ Biagio's Italian Restaurant in El… https://t.co/MWTGnG4Uci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clikasNG Send me email to ldreditor@mchsi.com and I’ll send copy of what PC sent me, all I have in notes is final… https://t.co/WNX3JdE5JN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never see players from other sports doing this.....Another reason why hockey is best!!! @itsmarthab… https://t.co/P6n5iwrnF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rodney_D_Pumas @thehill You’re not presenting facts, you’re presenting inane quotes, so your point is invalid and… https://t.co/oAQdItImrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePhang Hi Katie! Here’s my thoughts on the Otto Warmbier case, drastic maybe, but what else is there when the… https://t.co/gpCtkMioJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unconditional love: Known as affection without any limitations, or love without conditions. This term is sometimes… https://t.co/sMAjmXWYwb]]></document></documents></author>