<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A knuckleballer needs PED to what, get more spin on his knuckleball? https://t.co/QFmThD1Sxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/ A #FreePress is granted the ethical obligation of informing the public of what they cannot see. For what they ca… https://t.co/zMMSkDxH9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajcaleca @jalemoine @petroleocrudo No! La respuesta correcta es crear una economía competitiva donde sea muy favor… https://t.co/wVGfeoFxNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunshine22kas I get so stoned I’m surprised by what picture I have up everyday 😑🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom say “so here’s the tea.” And my dumbass got ready for some gossip and she just hands me an actual cup of tea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevebristoluk @realDonaldTrump @marklevinshow Or playing golf  #impeachTheMotherFcker https://t.co/XJEWht60UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taco Bell after church tonight seemed like a great idea. #ItWasNot can’t do it anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a real bro is never doing cardio eating fast food and still getting in festival shape]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FireTuckerCarlson   Hey @CapitalOne stop advertising on @TuckerCarlson's filthy show. Or I'll take you out of my w… https://t.co/5xz2uS3aH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennis78382 you should watch his videos. He’s got some good information on living in your vehicle. https://t.co/lKtxd1C9DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenickisaac @MarceloJPico @EM6211 @ReelBramz @JordanApps There’s a guest suite in my condo for $100/night. I thin… https://t.co/u4t2d17ruS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @emartinnn Didn’t hear anything wrong with that speech. He was talking about criminals right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocean healing. Standing in San Mateo, view of Bolinas and Pt Reyes. 📸: nintindo 👕: neutokyo @ Devil's Slide https://t.co/18x5Mxo1d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlziplocked So I got to show up for them @ the end, wish I could’ve been clearer with myself about how much ange… https://t.co/l2EMV5LszV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy gave lots of time to capture him inching, rubbing his head against the tree and using his feet to scratch… https://t.co/cz5XMHDupg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strellakat04 nice video sweet heart u look a amazing honey so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so s… https://t.co/lH58kLdXCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wafflenbaitshop @freep Medical-marijuana edibles are legal, and states with recreational marijuana have come up wi… https://t.co/nFq7tt2ZO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro. BRO. Let people date/marry who they want. Y’all sound so bitter on here talking about other people’s relations… https://t.co/NiF0LTnVXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 It depends on when you hear Democrat do you think Baby Killer ? Or 2nd Amendment hater? Or Deep State? Or their news is Fake?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barton is stinking it up something awful tonight! Why is he in there? @ScottHastings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haciendo esto por ella, por ellos.  Las palabras se las lleva el viento dame hechos]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m that guy who goes to music shows alone super early just to stand in the front.   #nerd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euroscots @2351onthelist Yet I’m not the one living in a fantasy world. Show me some evidence that Scotland would… https://t.co/26gQthZ5YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[145K+ views of my TED talk!Thanks for seeing how @BTS_twt shows how journalism can be more effective https://t.co/kH8zbWSiHk. @bts_bighit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The time for honoring yourself will soon be at an end! #MuellerTime https://t.co/2QnGMFZ4YF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I not commanded you? Be strong and courageous. Do not be afraid; do not be discouraged, for the LORD your God… https://t.co/z93Br5rOKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing what @Coachheard and the ladies in red and black are doing this year. Keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve loved doc for a long time, but this just adds on. Of course it’s LA fans that don’t know to do this… https://t.co/5hNBktDkqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNSotu @SenJohnKennedy @jaketapper Look at Kennedy’s lips. Is it proof Trumps dick is red? https://t.co/YV3giEQW6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LicJorgeAaron Hi; I am so sorry for the late reply!  For some reason I didn't get this message until today.  Would… https://t.co/9LcAEzKL1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enseñanza por el Pastor José Cabello @nuevavidacc #escogidosparaadorar #escogidosparavencer #escogidosparaservir… https://t.co/sZIB6EMTMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgirlfierce11 Unless you’re in law school or med school, 200k is ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3_ablock @Jedi_F3 @darkhelmetF3 @F3_Royale @F3_Spiderman @F3_CakeBoss @F3_Zima @SkateOrDieF3 @talbaugh03… https://t.co/k5HLuKqpY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toughLoveforx @NewsNeus @EnggMainR @dcarli @innov8tor3 @RayGallon The keyword there is “decode”. I must lack the c… https://t.co/MHOTaQ6HBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiskee the Sled-Dog   Just sleddin'    #julian https://t.co/WpSYYtecwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @DonMartinCTV asked a panel if the #LavScam scandal was reaching people outside the Ottawa bubble. I have bee… https://t.co/WDToyl7OWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@synredae @Observer2541 @Elinor27652146 @ITDave2 @Atheist_Dragon @deelane @YeshuaLover1970 @DB_Grimwalker… https://t.co/hvUhdqRDAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta remind yourself! @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/qGBqjZxf6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MusicCity  . . @grantgarland en Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/Dj7N1fsIGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDeMuro I know the guys up at Poway Honda and they have a "new" 2013 Civic Hybrid in stock. I worked there in 2… https://t.co/hjJue3QO6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexandriaRae_ They’re dumb. They have this misconceived notion that being mean to women works in their favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool story about this: Wilt was shooting free throws underhanded (taught by Rick Barry) and was as efficient as he’… https://t.co/F4FLwOuVNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigAllanLaw @TomAhink Looked like the players were about ready to go takedowns right there on the court. Most BB… https://t.co/WFTZ7fcFQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool to discover that @nbcbrooklyn99 has posted my scene to their Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook.… https://t.co/VCUrZOIfWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rightofmiddle21 @schris110 @thecjpearson No tantrums or name calling. Facts and the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Classic Years – 1970s - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/j6oGXXUXcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejasminesims is such an incredible spoken word artist, and she’s performing in concert this Friday night. Oh, an… https://t.co/IGNGWnlozN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate #InternationalWomansDay today - @XylemInc holding a ton of events across our company.  Everyone has uncon… https://t.co/TZt2qHyErH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBouzas There are a lot of triggered men out there who feel like the Capt Marvel movie has too much girl power… https://t.co/nowM3sJsDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Club105 w/ @djgonzoWNCI is LIVE till 4 AM!! - @Y105mansfield (WYHT HD1) | @iHeartRadio: https://t.co/ck1a20Tdfp 👍🎉😀📱🎶🎤📻]]></document><document><![CDATA[No culpen a la gente que se molesta con lo que sucede en Venezuela. Han sido 20 años viendo como mueren nuestros he… https://t.co/6mwiMTTY8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm scared for the U.S.A.. Trump attacks investigation into him daily. He is replacing head people at DOJ with pupp… https://t.co/gRyVj1bBk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Are you kidding me why would they debate on a channel where they trash dems all day and they have a separ… https://t.co/LBEaoPeEfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most likely, this will happen to you this week. Are you prepared? When you're entering the zone of… https://t.co/b8ncYolswR]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as we tried Mother Nature prevailed. 138# of wild persimmons kicked off with Indian Hill yeast, see ya in a… https://t.co/0UwWGvdjeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how @JordynneGrace is like "Yup, we're done here. Let's be out!".  Lol!  #ImpactWrestling https://t.co/nJ6cMuNXJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IHboog @Clint__Taylor @thebirdfarmer @FarmChicJodi @hkerkhofs @HaesenAnita @AtlantaAgCurt @HedrickJessica… https://t.co/tacF66i4Ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ottawa O-Train shutdown will be longer than expected https://t.co/fihP4HjWNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder how many Nashville area folks are saying to themselves well @LukeBryanOnline Rain Isn’t A gGood Thing . ...… https://t.co/OXIBCIbywc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkolligris @BiscottiNicole @heARTISTatWORK @HOWareyousmart @aweninspiration @tracyscottkelly @MaireCervenak Don’t… https://t.co/dtWF6njxX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl Maddie and I have been doing fundraisers for @SpecialOlympics for 8 yrs now, but today was the 1st polar pl… https://t.co/SOXkkpW2wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBrandan It would fuckin suck!! I lived in the country and for some reason the sound of the train in the distan… https://t.co/psIesyqRgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN If you think trying to clear this up is going to help you, you are more in the weeds and I thought you were. I… https://t.co/fpWMfPxFkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gone get crab legs til i realized my girl don’t get out of work til 1230 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grow your interpersonal skills in a team-focused environment. Now hiring: Customer Service Representative… https://t.co/yBiPbcPdVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelynDenton Ha! That last car might be mine. Actually it probably wasn’t as it wasn’t as busy when I went through… https://t.co/KZGkBVSkOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comey ...nor numb to those who have made it their mission to hate him at every pass and use their office to facilitate that hatred.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been watching some of @MStrooo6’s prep before / while he throws this week. The core strength manoeuvres he incorpor… https://t.co/iWODYz1HMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grbenny @benigma2017 @SpeakerPelosi Supplemental coverages that could occupy private insurers are buy ups, dental,… https://t.co/UiEEHGk5KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOSfanatic @jm10zepeda @realmadrid @ESPN_JorgeRamos @Espn_JorgeRamos no puede estar bien de la cabeza. A quien se… https://t.co/0K78SIvRMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, this used to be me but honestly if he doing all that you can just go right ahead and have him just let me… https://t.co/s9pPhTH8T7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in Mother Bear’s and they play the full version of Poker. 10 year old sitting across the table from me… sin… https://t.co/7U5tcKRp4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was a little hesitant doing this 3by3 with 275lbs on bench but I only missed one rep!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miel @IvanNov99 Yeah this is bribery but let’s not forget that you could’ve just accepted the apology for somethin… https://t.co/dJyOqpqrS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DodgersNation Years ago @shawngreen15 threw me his batting glove after hitting his second homer of the game as a m… https://t.co/etbsD6n5FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Habs last 7gms of the season:  Home: FLA, TB, TOR Away: CAR, CBJ, WPG, WAS  Ouch. #goMiraclesGo https://t.co/qK5asSlxp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilton resident and actor Joey Pantoliano stopped by the #HandsOffOurSchools rally in Ridgefield today. Joey will b… https://t.co/RdVZ03uJeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren announces major policy initiative that directly impacts millions of American families yet this is the story… https://t.co/XrQjTnYxXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freefaln94 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Dude. You really need to find a new source for your Kool-Aid 'cause it's… https://t.co/NHzK0BpqAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLAMEthemovie @MuseumModernArt @nadia_alexander So fancy! Take good care of them, @caryn_coleman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truefalse I love the "oh my god" comments from Dessert/Disaster leaking through]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJWJohnson51 @waterwars2019 I was talking to Brian at Walmart. Trying to remember the name of the kid who glued a… https://t.co/DKsxLyEzpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rashadd94 Oh yuh I’ve peeped his EP he can spit but we play that hoe at the functions]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your judged about your life and circumstances https://t.co/VcEG40manO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmh8899 @paoramos @marcorubio @AOC En la práctica el socialismo no a funciona. Cundo tú prometes y vasa un sistema… https://t.co/kR5be5rbds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrFatEng @sirensoIiIoquy @EconTalker Maybe they really believe their own baloney. Reality is harder for some folks to accept?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameGrumps @egoraptor @RubberNinja Coming soon: God Damn It Ross 2: Electric Boogaloo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This maybe a bit controversial, Lamar Jackson Plays like a Raven.  He will not back down to nobody.  Here is the pr… https://t.co/fZQfLdW4TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday morning, I baited my trap to apprehend a feline which uses my yard as a potty. Instead, yesterday afterno… https://t.co/a0pvAVxVOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TampaBayTre Trev, what’s the read on Jordan Scarlett? Projection for him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 65th Birthday to former Toronto Blue Jays catcher Bob Brenly! https://t.co/LMGaIoLSHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish I had a workout partner to stick with me through meals and call me a bitch everytime I needa extra push:/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juventud divino tesoro... Y yo jaja  🤟🏻💥⚡ en Don Burro Foro Cultural https://t.co/jINVqJo36I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KissaSins roses are red violets are blue you kissa sins are sexy cute https://t.co/LuePwDp4QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One month ago tonight, I got to meet some very inspirational people in NYC. This was definitely something I had loo… https://t.co/J8fPeSKvT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I lied to a cute boy and told him I’m a lawyer and now his girlfriend is in a custody battle and aski… https://t.co/tlt6qFryVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verizonfios  sucks. Once you schedule a payment they do not have the option to cancel. I’m switching service ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was a native New Yorker like me, and died in childbirth. It seems that when she married in her mid-30s, she did… https://t.co/jrU3ABL6p6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MConsuella @JW4Hillary @rubycramer @BernieSanders Here is Bernie's scam. He rigs the election in his favor https://t.co/h2gbBw6VHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human knot in FCA this morning! Problem solving at work...lots of laughing #AllInEWA #EWAFCA https://t.co/vsvV4uHJp7]]></document></documents></author>