<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Another weird thing that people sell on yard sale sites is make up. Sketch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton Which is precisely, why it is your #DUTY, #JohnBolton, to remove @realDonaldTrump, under the… https://t.co/SiP6Nvc7QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByJenna @MDVancleave @BMPPhoto @AmSwedInstitute I read this aloud to my hubby this morning over coffee. We loved it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angtrip @LisaVanderpimp @lisarinna You do realize you're not talkin to the real lvp? Read her last name in the twe… https://t.co/mCqBYdvcTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite photos of my favorite people. Who's your squad? 😎 https://t.co/SQNjAwGVGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleylavo Bitch I have to wake u up every morning don’t pretend like you have alarms]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man left outta town for the weekend and won’t be back till Monday 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drives me insane when people don’t watch their other team mates. Like they keep gathering shit while your dead. 🖕🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putzday_ você viu o que a psicanalista disse? é exatamente aqui: as mulheres daquela casa estão ali pra procriar e… https://t.co/yVs2WBs8aD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickPonticello Because teenagers have a different “clock” classes should start no earlier than 9 AM. Science cours… https://t.co/hhF68QWHUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man says he discovered tape that appears to show R. Kelly sexually abusing girls https://t.co/RpBv5oDeW6 via @suntimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fairfightaction @AVoiceForAllGA @ppppolls @GovKemp @gwlauren @letamericavote @GeorgiaDemocrat @bluestein… https://t.co/5HxdyzZgws]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pricked myself a lot pining the fur onto pipe cleaners i glued cotton balls onto for the arms. https://t.co/icE7i9682C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only want what's best for the people I care about but I can't help you if you don't want to help yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#betohpt @officialhpt  whereyoboyzat @ondgaspromo #ChevyGang   My Dream Truck on a super lift kit with the tailgate… https://t.co/cOXxfP4XQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @pence_lara @melissa5215 @FireshipMedia @MagaGoldHat @ProfSchlitzo7 @Hkmac7 @SavedSoul1990… https://t.co/iJPiTyHHio]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think I’m cool when I’m sober you should see me when I’m high. I’m just the same amount of cool but really quiet. 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[For any kids tryna do stats. Don't just run random t-tests against your groups instead of a post hoc  Don't report… https://t.co/PduHFVRLHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chloe McAllister on #XFactor I think we could be related! My family/ clan traces back to Northern Ireland! You’ve got mad vocals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to dance like a granny 👵👵 #AsWeCrawl #musicvideo * * * * * * * * * * * * * #sarahgolley #c15imaging #dance… https://t.co/854f3ebtcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WILL be at the opening of toy story 4 and front row at the Jonas concert this summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArizonaKayte Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE… https://t.co/hNOhC2BNaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly you guys should be thanking me for keeping my morbid death jokes to myself this week.   Crimony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a couple of hours, I have the chance to get the scoop on this season of @AGT!!!! It premieres in May.   Any ques… https://t.co/pGiPe5gD1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of our Journey on Day 1 @RRHSNTA #InspireTheDesireToTeach https://t.co/DRvAyNWn9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy next to me on the plane told me Happy International Women’s Day and it was so nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen @Eykis That he feels no remorse or responsibility for anything!!!🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmSteveHarvey Hey tweets a Fantastic Friday morning to you all have a great weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday night workout !! Cold shower and awaiting for a good rested night ... #soniatovarnp #loveyourself… https://t.co/2YrGcJbfjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police search for men who passed fake $100 bills at several businesses - WPRI https://t.co/zluHN3wtJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbdulElSayed @StudsandPearl Wealth is meant to be inherited, that's how a business dynasty is achieved. Ideally yo… https://t.co/7uuV7CMjvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janehardygan @Mintmintdoodles Just out of curiosity,  do you know where the photo, this gif was made of, is from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the redeye back to CLE and I came home to find a massive blizzard outside and my apartment thermostat read 31… https://t.co/hhRjuEASwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHammActor @gigirules7 @JustJane2019 @PoloOrtiz9 @CattMcCreary @BodManip @KMFras @mfarca @awlasky @bill44077… https://t.co/MmXJ74QYYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonBream I agree with what the President proposes, protect our citizens of all ages, conception to death at old age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels really good outside and you know what I’m doing? Working. Always. When am i not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join our #podcast LIVE this Saturday at 11am EST.  We'll be chatting with @gottogetoutof, Stewart Thompson, a fanta… https://t.co/HOxuwnYMKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Lauber Ohhh my goodness.. I was appalled. We edited out the slamming part.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What other band gives you a coloring book? @ASITISofficial https://t.co/dlBQaP57jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devcondetect @GlasswingVC @caseyellehester Boundaries are totally my thing too 😂 @caseyellehester @null0perat0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmexreece defending ur culture is never bitchy, do what u gotta do girl!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed!!!🤞🏼❄️🌨☃️ #winterwonderland #getoutside #sledding #snow #love https://t.co/kvBkMvQqpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to ALL the dog owners who are dealing with all this rain and muddy paws during bathroom breaks #itsruff 🐶🌧😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyfollen BUT THINK ABOUT HOW COOL IT WOULD BE IN A MOVIE TO LIKE WALK AWAY AND PUTTING YOUR SUNGLASSES ON.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime I pay off a big bill, I treat myself by buying something I've always wanted 💁🏻 #balance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler I"ll pass..might be good for lining the bottom of bird cages]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisemiliolopez Yeah it’s a pretty big festival, there’s games, food, drinks and everything lol it’s really cool lol i love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizabethMay has been razor sharp in questions and analyses of #lavscam Too bad the media hasn't caught on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What hypocrites; the biggest haters in the USA are voting on a resolution condemning hate.😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liden_rob Yeah, I was just hoping someone had strong feelings about a specific kind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyDFriend Both great choices. They came up as part of our discussion this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Sam Houston would have been just as frustrated to wait 26 minutes to transfer from the 41 to the 9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people can’t figure out how to use #BirthControl to prevent #UnwantedPregnancies, then let’s focus on saving the… https://t.co/NlKV4de7Oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew #htown is a foodie’s heaven!   Sea Salt &amp; Coffee twist🍦+ toasted marshmallow + cotton candy #nomnom https://t.co/PC4R4o8aGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESTE MARTES EN EL SHOW DE MARTHA Y TERE El Profe TODO EMPIEZA A LAS 6PM PACIFICO ENTREVISTA A LAS 8:30PM POR:… https://t.co/8p7iBsmaZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brady trying to rap “Uproar” :  “What the F though? Where the love go? Five,four three, two, Alejandro!”   Me: that… https://t.co/iXdvtDLAiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should make for a fun start to the day. @sierranevada #asheville #nc #beer #vacation @ Sierra Nevada Brewing C… https://t.co/NF1DsclUzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th graders at Yorkshire Elementary working in Sumdog to sharpen math skills  on DLD? #pwcs, #DLDAY, #VSTE https://t.co/j5BNMU08yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImprovedJesus @steveturpintwoc @KYGOP I’m sorry Lord. This is horrific pain. #LeviathanAnn #TaraAnnMoons https://t.co/fWrLhYRuSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kramergirl Their chemistry is undeniable! Could you image how freakin beautifully talented their children would be 🙏🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsGeorgiosP @GillDoc5 @1ofGMsLovelies @SigMoncur18 @zisekaiase @AnneMarie_GM_1 @CanadianSyrup @MSplendor… https://t.co/n0f81zjL6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve watched the whole thing - and never believed a word they said because i’ve educated myself enough to know thos… https://t.co/eau83cerc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @chasitymorales2  future #superstars #f45training @ Aloft El Segundo - Los Angeles Airport https://t.co/8gCgiaseiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RpSensenbrenner now that's funny RINO!! Your other comments aren't funny....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revitalized_Dem @CapnMAGA @swicklepus @1Beau1969 @BwaHh @ricklundl @cspanwj @nytimes @katierogers Remember the emo… https://t.co/wNGBbI8WXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“As soon as girls start moving from ages 14-17 to 18-24 and older, they don’t believe they have the same opportunit… https://t.co/3YDcfq4Ajr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeeleyFox29 @SeaIslePD @FOX29philly Too much liquor puts people in bad situations and not thinking clearly. Glad he was arrested]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’mon on @DonCheadle Stop playing and tell me who die’s in the opening seen of #BlackMonday this is my 20th time asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_wrapsbylexx Most piercers/ shops that charge $$$ do that because they’re licensed professionals with professional… https://t.co/CBzQ4medKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones Emoji’s and announcement of 19.2 today! What a day! 🤯 @CrossFitGames #CrossFitGames #FortheThrone]]></document><document><![CDATA[how come everything I’ve done in the last 5 days I almost instantly regret lol E V E R Y T H I N G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vowswithinhb He’s the best player in the league by a country mile, that’s why I say the signing is just a way of k… https://t.co/CxmZkivxia]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s and 00s Girl Epicness dance party thanks to our loves @whatthefloat and @peteydunn #danceparty @ The West End L… https://t.co/HeJnO7vT8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really trying to get these #pdcupgriphandspring , thanks to @JacobKujoLyons ! one step at a time!  📹 @alex_erin585… https://t.co/iS28Z4S7fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewitchbrmclst @vairton5550 @BrendaFlournoy1 @Alexa17101614 @RoarLoudTravel @Jay_Rombach @TathamSmith… https://t.co/iwlRSdaxx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendesBRA Ai que aflição de ver todo mundo comprando e saber que eu tenho que esperar até dia 7 gzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always wanted to be a singer when I was younger and I still want to be!✌😱😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertCreekmore truthfully I don’t know enough about it to comment on the legitimacy of it. but I find it very int… https://t.co/8VfAjsAHDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaotaoTasi It was! I was actually thinking about this last night bc someone was eating a sandwich and pickle on tv. I’m very weak-minded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rudnus @renders_carla @malaysiakini @nathaliepeace1 @gsondheit @BobbiFotsch @AnimalsBelize @GoLLLion @Cat_Kapow Pu… https://t.co/28DPEBOHIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my coworkers and my time with patients on night shift, but HATE everything else about it. Actually mostly ju… https://t.co/j7Ys19eaPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennSlowpez My tweets never do well any time of the week, so you at least have that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out these young @KISSOnline fans at the American Bank Center in Corpus Christi. Check out the story on… https://t.co/ydOIYIM14f]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I get to my 11 am and realize my dog jumped on me with shit on his paws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smalls available...We have 7 different Flavors 🌈 of Biker shorts for you ladies get the while they are Hot! Shop th… https://t.co/kpuFn2q2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning my luvs, I hope all is well. Happy Thursday. 💕💕 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/xyAXU6Vvef]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want a friend to spend v day w but all of my friends actually have a boyfriend so like this is awkward]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday bb gorl @haileystricker_ hope your day was wonderful 🥳🥳💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCostantino @TheOrville @SethMacFarlane @paddywarbucks @planetary_union @Jasonpjclark I miss Tharl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who says it never snows in the 🌵 desert. This is a picture of my mom’s yard this morning in Pas Vegas #snow #desert… https://t.co/mxlJSHovNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A perfect treat on my special day! @ Olive Garden https://t.co/sujUNlZ67K]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚 SAVE THE DATE For a Traumatic Brain Injury Awareness/Fundraiser Event. APRIL 25TH, Chicago.  Help me, a Kindergar… https://t.co/zjQep8GmY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DateDateline @SherriRush @KaislerSoze @AundreasMom @nataliebannon @MKBlum I am so honored!!!  I'd like to thank… https://t.co/TbcMQTd2Dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@droel666 @lady_ov_rage @BriaNamtar I'm normally pretty personable, but holy shit, I'm not smiling 24/7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representative Dr. @AliceMann4House (an M.D.) notes conversion therapy is fake science. “At best, it does nothing.… https://t.co/F7GGoxrEbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler They weren't. How hard is not to lie and mis-represent what she was trying to say. She used anti-semit… https://t.co/HM5R7qPuqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW annoying is it when something shouldn’t bother u but it’s really pissing u off and u can’t make it stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMcMenemin @hornswaggled2 It's only the children you already harmed with radiation and chemo that no longer have a… https://t.co/m86SAeRaet]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this hilarious there's something wrong with you. #mirth #giggle #smirk #absurd https://t.co/lHqg9QCoNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay there imma stop eating bad bc summer is coming and this body ain’t ready]]></document></documents></author>