<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Iulian68 @JonaLendering The apartment building version of that is this, the block I’m on right now. https://t.co/XMyFBX5Ylb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguimos Catando Tasting... #GrandsEchezeaux #Burgandy #PinotNoirs #NYSommeliers #Wines #Vinos #Vinefilos… https://t.co/t5eNVrKDjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of maxing is done. If you stayed the same you might want to check how many days you came after school or… https://t.co/taJxsmjZKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no better feeling than going out to eat with your family and paying the check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RYAN_D0UGLAS @jeffromcclellan @WWE @WWEAleister Finn yes, too soon for Black]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday stumbling on something new... Love art even better when you find art where you don’t expect it... art love… https://t.co/Z5ouh1gw80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tims_Burner @TeeOhEmm Yeah but when you factor in Internet it’s like the same price]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck opiates and opioids. never take pharmaceutical drugs fr that shit bad for you mentally and physically. Your wh… https://t.co/6Y9ZSQcNKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nice2meetme88 I cannot believe she said that!!!!! He BEEN cheating! While I dnt believe Jordyn story im more on HE… https://t.co/afQxWKd6FT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoweStencil @Morning_Joe @SteveRattner @realDonaldTrump When Reagan went into the Oval Office, he always wore a ti… https://t.co/7eVAq4abLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love having my power turn on and off every 30 seconds. Keep the lights on and you can have your own dance party 😐 https://t.co/sIK9RObVqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC @kenvogel @CPAC @HillaryClinton @CNN Hahaha, that guy, always joking around. What a prankster....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroljsroth Liked group projects; did the least amount of work; and expected equal gains. The beauty of #socialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dodgers:  Resign Machado.  Move Seager to 2B.  CT3 becomes ultimate utility player.  Win third straight pennant.… https://t.co/zLNU4ofC5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDLHughley @YouTube that video is sickening ... @RepRashida is absolutely correct trotting out your black frien… https://t.co/f6Fi2dHewm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevieVanZandt Hey Stevie, hope you and Maureen are doing well man. Was up in the Adirondacks last week and did a… https://t.co/6kDmuwxKtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got a couple of people @FINDAWRENCH making cold calls for the first time today. Thinking about videoing it fo… https://t.co/Vo4yESl6j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great @buffalosabres win yesterday. Definitely worth the drive! With illusiondaydream and Ben (unfortunately his fi… https://t.co/2uoRrbB3aB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨UK #geotweeps🚨 I am heading your way in early May to attend @DEVEX_Conf! If your around London or Aberdeen, would… https://t.co/ZhvkhLSUCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[But also do nothing to help restore it. I'm not trying to shit on anyone that doesn't want to go, that's fine,but i… https://t.co/8RN7dpqh37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I don’t believe them. I think they threw slosh.snow balls at each other and blamed it on a maga hat wearing street clearer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinadunnn @patronusisotter So, why is it fair to say that one set of voters should have to fall in line for t… https://t.co/qGiFqjdmAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHarmon_BYB I’m still laughing at that tweet that said John Elway making sure he is cemented in as Denver’s gre… https://t.co/xz9U6LbCNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading a five hour fundraising training has me like... https://t.co/0I1mXOCPU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esos CABRONES que estan por el mundo apoyando al CARNICERO de Nicolas Maduro debieran ir a Venezuela y llegar a un… https://t.co/3li9MUrvr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump You show a significant lack of facts but what should we expect  from someone who supports Pinocchio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbenderatl @ElementHotel @downtownatlanta @CityofAtlanta Edit: I think it’s a Hyatt Place that’s currently under construction]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just made my vote for @catjiratv in the 2019 #CammyAwards! Vote Now on https://t.co/pL4yR4KjiE https://t.co/cFckmrDVZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBigby wait a second the first tweet was sent in december of 2019 how’s that possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller This isn’t what America stands for regardless of political party. Let’s denaturalize him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndersonWilva I've been redoing my boat it should be ready in a couple weeks...just got my center console in today https://t.co/I3BAUtO8nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing some of the usual sports' songs: 7-Nation Army by White Stripes, Thunderstruck by AC DC. Thought I heard We… https://t.co/gB6XHsV5ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoisyAstronomer @LycomingCollege Headed there to pick up Daughter #2 who is a junior there. “Spring Break” is an o… https://t.co/6hokoFTWmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I love these alternate covers for crisis.... I have to wonder... Who is taking these photos?… https://t.co/OkApc8XPiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Magician Robert Houdin’s #magicwand was so powerful, it made my #Prius partially levitate in our host’s driveway.… https://t.co/FNyDklmdsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks hogfish_bar Bobby, Michelle, Chef José! We loved the delicious #seafood #platter at Hogfish yesterday!… https://t.co/WQrAYdvLrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beyondchron So it’s not inevitable that voters will oppose housing policies or candidates. But it’s also important… https://t.co/48kCIJeXp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNCleveland Lol good man! @KingJames wanted LA, hey man enjoy! Nothing to be sad about @TheRealTRizzo Thats on Lebron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_Magaro @KSATRJ @PaulGarciaNBA A lot of their players dont get love because they do things no one values as much… https://t.co/hDfdxMPD54]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great Presidents Day weekend, everyone...#LifeWithGod #Luv2All 🛐 https://t.co/l925iSmjwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjhogo @maceversmith @jjones9 Yeah so you liked how Lebron left for Miami ? If the teams had a hard cap and made i… https://t.co/kBg9ZV2hdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NalaSaysStuff @NathanEames1 @TRHLofficial I’m asking for numbers to support the argument. Believing things blindly… https://t.co/3bvjTKhins]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Funky Time! Can’t wait to finally see @Benaskren fight. It’s been a long time coming!!!!. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSheridan12 @_youhadonejob1 Too funny!! Must feel the competition from The National Inquirier!!😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelci_ly @Sprint_Ricky Of their socks get knocked off, we need to get them some #SprintSocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on guys eye the price we are paying for all this happy BS They bait an switch If obumer made any deal over sea… https://t.co/9p4M3T69LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Your father didn’t denounce David Duke so you can piss up a flagpole Don.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMCalgary @martletman @allcatjazzband @mikekean https://t.co/gkIBu7USlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hand rolled and fresh brewed happiness in Ybor City https://t.co/iOEDzKRJuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skoot62 @AP You sir have not been watching the hearings, Cohen is speaking the Truth and your in Denial like all of his Followers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of Alex, he’s in 5th grade at the Imagine School in North Port and today he had his @USYoungMarines prom… https://t.co/KW4h68V22c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is short Buy the tickets, miss this months rent, get evicted, end up homeless, get fired, lose your friends, r… https://t.co/w2VmtWREVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you even imagine being in a band with your parents? That is awesome! 👏🏽 #VoiceBlinds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyMystique_01 @P69Jordanp69 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logs @SouthwestAir Yeah, but I don’t care about “everyone”. It’s all about me Logan!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airport thoughts 1  You should not be allowed to wear sweatpants or pajamas to the airport]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiltonHotels The Diplomat in Hollywood FL (a place NO ONE should stay) gave my room to someone else and put me in… https://t.co/rvIo87v6rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaiah sacrificed his body for the team. Huge charge on Murphy! Takes those kinds of plays to get things headed bac… https://t.co/i47HdzICZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fearthewalkingdead is too much of a soap opera to ever be half as good as the original #WalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im again looking for a new place to park and live in my RV trailer at! Preferably a house with enough property spac… https://t.co/qgbZ8VL7jY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Liewehr crossed 5K. Time 00:31:00, pace 09:59 min/mile, est. finish 11:25 am https://t.co/4qM5qj6fZH #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[pardi gras szn #laissezlebontempsrouler @ Cathedral Square, Mobile, Alabama https://t.co/KftcfLWwS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BcoBicentenario La mujer en la foto lo ve como diciendo,pero si este banco es una mierda !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump After tucking your tail between your legs and running home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a race card was played. Buy ignorant vulgar gutter talking Tliab  kudos to mr Cummings for defending a friend… https://t.co/ywVOdLuyoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC #Occupy2Decolonize/RunningWolf ELECTED Mayor 2 STOP FUKUSHIMA which has Made Tokyo SOIL Nuclear Waste the 3rd… https://t.co/s2T8zNuI7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aunt Wanda in the kitchen, listening to Benny Goodman and cooking up a storm. Things are finally getting back to normal around here. 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macariomx La cosa es joder, joder, joder y joder. No se cansan estos becarios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Podrías pasarnos exactamente los 4 valores de gasolina que hablas? Porque se oye que hablas al chile!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President is lying, this administration is guilty of conspiracy that will lead to RICO Charges being filed. Wat… https://t.co/7JMgOtBcn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emergency will be tied up in court until 2020, at which point he can claim the Dems blocked him but it’s temporary,… https://t.co/jwJ5r4oCYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyoki_renee If your 3-4 hours from me I'll date you I'll just come see you on the weekends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber drivers and Lyft drivers are only doing what every driver knows they can do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalChiliDay ! Whether you like your chili topped with cheese (duh!) or with a side of a peanut butter s… https://t.co/ML34ERLlzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, but the way Otto Warmbier was disrespected by #Trump today is not getting the due it deserves. 😡That… https://t.co/GtDzITTwrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #NHLJets with a great chance right off the hop as Patrik Laine makes a beautiful pass to Mark Scheifele, who is… https://t.co/duY2xxBb3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haunting This is great news. We surely wanted that. #TheHauntingOfHillHouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:30 am... Sunday.... I try to sleep in on weekends... LLAG 🤑 N we GRRR’D 😈 #entrepreneur #biggerbizz #loveyourself… https://t.co/IuS6prhePu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolute no-brainer after what he did at the Fort Lauderdale Intercollegiate. #CountryClubSchool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out some of the beautiful custom laminating and print options @FoxLaminating offers.  @Promo_Marketing… https://t.co/gW8sEM50HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuesaVerdades @lopezobrador_ Cambiar todo, secretarios y al presidente no sirven para nada solo ocurrencias estos 100 días]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy 27 de febrero, a tantos años de ser independiente, nos gobierna un partido lleno de corruptos, hombres y mujere… https://t.co/bISuaKkeQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixed doubles was Venus and Andy Rodick battling back to a five to five tie and then winning In OT.   Men’s was ten… https://t.co/oV7W77iyjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop doing this to myself.... I have to leave the house by7:15 everyday this week 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benny Gantz calls on Netanyahu to step down. But key: No pledge not to join a Bibi-led government after the electio… https://t.co/JFpmWBaaWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGMAdvertiser When I stand behind you and hold your breast it's wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Morning Ferry ride @ Staten Island Ferry Whitehall Terminal https://t.co/Mb4fNbUsII]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bruh asteroids changed the name to nacho flavored nuts or I just bought the wrong thing???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jackie_Redmond Be sure to follow and share @The_DanKShow via @YouTube https://t.co/aQsWeiH5LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chad_bowen That's why my alb is black. Actually, it's because black is slimming. #ILookLikeFriarTuck 😕 https://t.co/nWO2cWVBNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #hydro rates just went up.  Where is the media outrage? The right wing indignation? Or, as always, is it only a… https://t.co/aZ39c1TZPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenKirkman Of course. A friend of @sarahcolonna's is a friend of mine (she sent me to your NY show in 2016). Glad… https://t.co/RxcaeoHxpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a cold front moves towards the area, a line of heavy rain  will push through. https://t.co/sx8DtRD1yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleeting and snowing in Woodville, AL believe it or not but here is some video. #valleywx #alwx https://t.co/Uxe8c2Pw8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garway95 @USAFVet18 @ncar999 @Michael00799877 @Bigbillshater @jonz970 @mbales250 @JohnDSanders1 @Mac55885201… https://t.co/D7PF56BsND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Jesus On A Forklift + Horizon Line Coffee &amp; Vanilla Bean by @exilebrewingco at @centralstndrd — https://t.co/wZgFewsTdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How a stint with @MBball_cghsnc helped NC State's Jarius Morehead learn new leadership and coaching skills going in… https://t.co/UodYGJ2YRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HNYEYD Jenna, a harpoon might crush your chest -- but this, this will crush your spirit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see it... you’ll know. #life #joy #married #cats #are #from #outer #space #they #are #stalkers #and #funny… https://t.co/zf8nPgl5mC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasure to meet you jamesjudecourtney ! #Halloween #MichaelMyers @ Hilton Charlotte University Place https://t.co/VeQU28AuUG]]></document></documents></author>