<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Notwithstanding ye have well done, that ye did communicate with my affliction. https://t.co/tkWtT9icxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: *showing my cousin a picture of josh and jake* “i’m a whore for these 2”  my cousin: “whatever you say, virgin mary”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GKeile @KatyTurNBC @realDonaldTrump He came back in a coma. Trump played footsie with his executioner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjf39 @ABC Hoda Muthana was witnessed chanting: "Death to all Americans"  This woman is a vicious hateful enemy of… https://t.co/R35YKTBDW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@how2girl I agree with you about the parents but I seriously hope none of it's true. Love n miss MJ 😢🎼❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw my favorite professor from last semester and it literally made my day so much better :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[May be hanging out in Iceland for a bit — delayed @Dulles_Airport on @Icelandair ... I know it will all work out -… https://t.co/yrCQqT3g94]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the various Trump investigations are based solely upon the strong and verifiable evidence of immature emotional… https://t.co/HpANbgltRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fireandicelv @MargaretJosephs If you would give @danielleshaub a thank-you I would sincerely check your moral comp… https://t.co/HBdnDKLzay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm. If this were Clinton or Obama the right would have sooo many conspiracy theories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True. And ironically he’s a strong Republican he claimed and was ok with her Democratic wife taking campaign money… https://t.co/CdW1ma5Rmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sunset finishing up provides a lovely scene for dog walking at @centrecopaws...until the wind kicks in and you rea… https://t.co/TGE1BLz2xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RansomSeries Never too late to tell the truth...Right Eric!!..Maybe we all need to remember that!!🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Agreed the GOP”s Russian comrades hard at work and people still falling for it. I’m not a Bernie s… https://t.co/sJnpmbJ7cW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I agree! President Trump is involved in ground-breaking anti-nuclear peace talks and all the headli… https://t.co/w9nnlmRVQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poem #2... “Megan Married Herself” by Caroline Bird. She’s on 🔥! #RSDproud #iampoetryoutloud @ The State Museum of… https://t.co/Ow2mNRnrF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[how you almost 40 years old and still a acting like this.... imagine getting away with cheating this many times and… https://t.co/ioBtyPJlYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancel all my meetings. I will be typing in every location I can think of for the rest of the day. 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby She is a fucking moron!!  Figures it's Faux News. Hey, can you please follow me back Aunt Crabby?  Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NandoRaptor Or maybe they used it to snort some coke &amp; were embarrassed to put it back cause it had residue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings lead #NYR 2-1 with 12:51 left in the 3rd. Shots 35-25 Detroit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcale1776 @realDonaldTrump People are turing toward Trump!  They see his greatness!! Yippee!!!  🇺🇸🎈🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbmanning12 @vegastheo VERY proud of our CCSD teachers....smart, sassy and dedicated to the process. Thank you! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moshthefatyank @whatmaddness Oh my sweet child, look away from this abyss before it consumes you. Does dirty laund… https://t.co/K2UGDJ9r9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then laughing at these ain’t shit niggas who wanna try after you fucking leave them 🤣🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza .....not even including a future federal charge of sending terrorist threats through the mail.....… https://t.co/ohPSBtyZnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 260 Cleavland Road #PleasantHill #CA  #realestate https://t.co/KE4W9M0tWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BestBuy Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/0OIjCatd6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Vero Beach FlightSafety Academy student pilo killed when plane goes down deep in woods during solo training… https://t.co/fIGCb8vUMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Namaste_40 @rtemair We should always be thankful when our parents treat us good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have super deep convos with the ones around me and I give as much advice as I can and I try my best to help them… https://t.co/f9JVl2zJ8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gombe is not in eastern Nigeria.    North Eastern. Infact more north than east.   Also nigerians do not sound like… https://t.co/sMcedh06hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddiesClass @EDUcre8ive @azasoski @doctor2pi @Tech_Buddha @tom_karnes @teachsci8 @Duncannedd @WeVideo WeVideo is a… https://t.co/8iEt4q9Hk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t even TRY to talk to me unless ur name is esteban julio ricardo montoya de la rosa ramirez]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally saw this in the @MCO airport when i was 12 this is NOT a new concept.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @MichaelCohen212 Some one once said almost daily that today would be a good day for @realDonaldTrump to release his taxes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone aware of Afro beat or Afro rock? Because I feel like everyone is missing out on some amazing music, but a… https://t.co/dMlKnz8MFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday's with these two #DJ #EDM #vocalhouse #deephouse #gayDJ #soldoutclothing #denlapresents #weho #ladj #gayweho… https://t.co/0YEgKcq0mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbuquerqueTurk @larrybehrens @GovMLG Don’t we have separation of power for a reason?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr Josie Johnson. “Minnesota is one of first state to pass fair housing legislation.” 1962. #truthTelling… https://t.co/lRUlOs9VeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinpurcell I survived raising 9 kids. Being president will be a cake walk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadiandaws83 @howllr @DoloresManley4 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @roseoleary58… https://t.co/VcxZNVlAju]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES. We just got a new centrifuge that beeps when it’s done, and it’s terrible and makes me panic every time.… https://t.co/F5Fbz0HOsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sibling Selfie.  First time for everything. @ Rockaway Beach, Oregon https://t.co/7LHUgnloOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[a guy at lions head last night told me last time he saw me I was drunk and crying...  clearly I make GREAT first impressions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey state of Oregon - WRONG! A qualified doctor, and ONLY a doctor, gets to make this decision. Punishing the poore… https://t.co/q2f2UATg0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You were the prettiest girl at toads”  I didn’t go to toads... “Ok, but if u we’re there, you would’ve been the pr… https://t.co/su7wlESg3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Extremely proud of them they are our future may God bless them all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me coming up with a lie to email my professor on why I couldnt do the assignment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar This is amazing. My dr recently suggested i be tested. I began reading about adhd and it was like i were re… https://t.co/b4mtuFkPg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @davidcicilline "House Democrats" messaging: 2/  "As Democrats, we fail our founding fathers, we fail our Cons… https://t.co/VjtVj6WBJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Jahan @Burberry It’s just senseless @Burberry tell your designers to stop creating while they are on cocaine PERIOD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing a party hat, licking the window. Normal Pierce stuff. @ Wayne, Pennsylvania https://t.co/lKWe8kEL0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Measuring our friends with different non-standard units is always fun!!  @batts4lisa @Leesburg_ES @BowTiedPrincipl… https://t.co/qWMWXnDM2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emeraldbulldog We had to give him the benefit of the doubt and not accused him without having evidence first you k… https://t.co/sQT1vzD7VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusLoverTed @SonOfJmkWalkow @realDonaldTrump @MSNBC You officially win the internet for the dumbest tweet ever.… https://t.co/fdkprgjpuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow-up: Everything fit...except for the cups in the black onesie were way too big. #ittybittytittycommittee4life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmergingTrail Yea I guess we’ll see how it shakes out. If she was your daughter, what would you do? (Just continui… https://t.co/1A2kxZSped]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chingao yo le grito “Aaaaaaamabel” a la mía y nomas me mira con una cara de “que quieres wuey” 🤣🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this exact time next week I’m going to be getting out of lab and walking to the parking lot to my car and drivin… https://t.co/YDl1p4J4sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[they don’t even know Im feeling pain, they don’t even know how I feel inside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't be denied, who made us happy, we were happy to see Maine celebrating her EB. Birthday, but happiest when Jame… https://t.co/9LNdZTh6oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are so cool! I can just imagine the history behind these. 👍🏻 16th Century Boxwood Carvings Are So Miniature R… https://t.co/AzKT4Q6fOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamoSassymama @steelecreations @Shelli69jeeper @kickmudgrl13904 @JenniPrickett 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders has the White savior complex in spades! He thinks he knows better than Blacks how best to make us whole fin… https://t.co/bzdhFQKeS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still thinking about this place. 🍣🥢🤤||  #happybirthday #holyshitake #chicago #westloop #japanesefood @ Chicago, Ill… https://t.co/4BOmu808Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey Oh you again. How about pointing out that it took 16 yrs for your favourite party to make this all th… https://t.co/wEYaqENm7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanObeidallah @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs Was it McCabe's meeting with the Gang of 8 that left @SenFeinstein so shaken up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what I was saying, but at least the #violist approved! #music #musician #viola #concert #orchestra #stage… https://t.co/ClNjjjLrwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeCarrollAZ I walked away over 20 years ago.  It’s not my liberal Jewish parents’ Democratic Party anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I had a dream that I had to have all of my teeth extracted and I was sleep talking to Lijah and told him about it 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daryl needs to go watch a movie and learn to check and make sure the big bad is actually dead.  #thewalkingdead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryJaneX710 @Valerie_105 @ultabeauty @winkytinky @Tina15Marie @lizardbrooks99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr.Seuss brought several friends with him to visit us @BrittonOkcps The Fish Lady reads her favorite story “One Fis… https://t.co/qgacyLTJxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[adan is adan because magic mike the father just picked those papers up off the floor. #mexicandynasties #bravo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went through my darkest times by MYSELF so I don’t owe nobody shit❗️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn this kid is getting in deep with the feelings... #TheWalkingDead #TWD @WalkingDead_AMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely my favorite to be the next Bachelorette out of everyone who’s left the show so far 👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[7. Minecraft ost Any Pokémon soundtrack more specifically lavender town but also a lot of other towns throughout those gens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristophersZen Lol I showed/explained your board to my husband after we got married. It still makes me laugh every time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I leave the house drunk I come home with a new crack on my phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Well, it's about darn time you get this roster out! Looking forward to @JoyceWhiteVance opinions.  She… https://t.co/gNodQSmI8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorites from my maternity session 😍 https://t.co/5nXGbhhua3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Scott31 Yep come get @B_2wavy Stud @ Klein Cain High..Houston Texas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thearmchaircom @andrehenry @ZakiyaNaemaJack @lisasharper @RubyNSales @WilliamMatt22 @prophiphop @LatashaMorrison… https://t.co/PF1OSiget3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 15th Birthday Audrey Caroline!!!  🎂 You are beautiful, smart, funny, and wise beyond your years and I could n… https://t.co/k8hr7Smhz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maurice Nelson has been sentenced for abducting a woman and assaulting her in the basement of his home over the cou… https://t.co/K9jMqwO3YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice Blue 💙💙💙 @DinaAlonzi  ⠀⠀ . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . #DAbrideTO… https://t.co/Ulp1yDtf6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaxbot @NYC_DOT @KeithPowersNYC @CarlinaRivera @NYCSpeakerCoJo @TransAlt @Outcycling @bikeloveny @DavidOumpeace… https://t.co/voURudoLYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka DEMS HAVE THEIR VOTERS SO WOUND UP! THEY’VE BECOME VIOLENT! AND DANGEROUS!  THE DEMS ARE OUT IF CONTROL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy in art club today. The projects are really coming along!  #plumlearns #artclub #plumproud #artmatters… https://t.co/yiKTpiWrbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@interstinman @KiberMoon @purplehaze1106 @cntrystrong42 @TruckerTiny @SidsteViking @LaurieSzaroz @thejewel4… https://t.co/Q2brneIU4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[... when you’re listening to @TJBucholz and the @VanguardPubAfrs team talk Michigan politics with @ZachGorchow and… https://t.co/mRTWl4YwUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instagram I’m trying to recover a business IG that was set up with a personal email from a previous admin. My subm… https://t.co/vH9qy20YfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[dropped 1 hour ago @nickjonas @kevinjonas @joejonas back in business boiiii https://t.co/WLo8iTJenZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't outexercise your bad diet!! It's 80% nutrition and 20% exercise! That's why you're not losing weight even… https://t.co/9mIcBvukKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obianuju Agree, that is the snake oil salesmen that the PP industry is, they have always been a house built in sand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macabeso @MagnumMexico @macabesord @barbara_lopez21 es perfecta combinacion a me encanta la magnum 🤤🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally me watching that Daddy Yankee tribute 😏 https://t.co/m8Rn1UAnRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing @GordonVoit ! Great story, a must share! 💪🏽🏀❤️ #BasketballMom #Results]]></document></documents></author>