<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dropped pin Near 1965-2005 S Western Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90018 https://t.co/dfkrPxhIDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan chose to play party politics for his closing statement. @RepCummings proceeded to give one one the clas… https://t.co/HZ1HTybtGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:61.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissamcewen @dylanmatt Dylan, I really doubt that a study with that design would in any way affect your prior if… https://t.co/loXg3Vz3t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dangerous allure of victim politics https://t.co/V17kYMtZ3S via @littleatoms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Wake Forest I’ll win the spread but need ya to help out with the over ya bums.  😆🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these new photos I’m working on look straight out of a National Geographic magazine 🌄🦢]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's wrong with being a 'slut'? If it's with one man - YOUR man - it's actually needed. You need to know how to s… https://t.co/mUAnfRPc5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SzSz_velSek @MSZ_RP Wiemy juz, ze zrodel zydowskich, ze " tak postraszylismy polakow, ze w poskokach przyjada do I… https://t.co/rzM5MhkA7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[actually, every time I try to order @Caviar and I’m logged out, I just go to @UberEats]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is something @samomatseye is seeing that the guys on @TVCNews_Africa #JournalistHangOut are not seeing,my per… https://t.co/ruLQ9E9p6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up in 5 hours to be awake for 30+ for the kids! I couldn’t be more excited for my final Dance Marathon. Its… https://t.co/QOdpheaKOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a slice of leftover birthday cake today, but walked around my house while eating it, so I’m calling it exercise!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internet, Why are you making fun of @NatalieRacing ‘s crew member with the fire extinguisher 🧯. Instead you should… https://t.co/BjyEh3fpiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man @PremierLacrosse is killing it this week with these announcements. Any more guys?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghlandon @BriMartinezx3 The right side of my back and arm is not present today😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Marvel would fix the lighting during their fight scenes. It would be nice to see the ass kicking instead of… https://t.co/EbFBT9kCbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySinatra Jerry was one of the good guys. I miss him. He gave me a ton of laughter. Thanks Jerry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do Republicans care about anything except possibly writing a book, (to divert attention), destroy our nation and pr… https://t.co/sO0oa1MqPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @andreamwatts makes fun of me for saying please when I ask the Alexa to do something: https://t.co/FCK1hdruNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel This is bound to make @realDonaldTrump nervous. TIME FOR AN ALL CAPS TWEET WITH MULTIPLE EXCLAMATION MARKS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preseason High School Baseball  Beckman 15, Garey 2 @SGVNSports @IESportsNet @James_Escarcega @InsideSoCalSpts… https://t.co/rdRXl0857H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @bhmlegion for making the ticket buying experience so easy! I just bought my tickets for the first match… https://t.co/OZS98ECLIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevecook84 Damien Williams is exactly why you don’t sign a Le’Veon Bell. I love Bell, but I would never pay a RB… https://t.co/s3Mz7rFKXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ladysugestiva Es el teatro "el ateneo" ... en Buenos Aires, Argentina ?  Por la Recoleta!... me parece !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @Todd_Gutner temp in Topsham is 5 crystal clear skies and a calm wind we picked up 2" of snow yesterda… https://t.co/LRAI0Sk3O5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Quality Inn &amp; Suites Kissimmee by The Lake https://t.co/scCqJiuBfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanajill211 @HouseJudiciary @SpeakerPelosi So you think guns are protected in ways that speech and religion are not? Quite a crazy idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryyppy @replit @reasonml Yesss it was a lot of fun! We built 4 different versions of asteroids, the retro game. Wi… https://t.co/NsLVQ3hioO]]></document><document><![CDATA[give a girl a couple followers and she swears she’s a celebrity these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joesabin @AnthonyDiComo Why is it different degrom is making 17 million this season while Harvey pitched 220 innin… https://t.co/HcCPwXZjL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only person who doesn't believe Cohen is telling the whole truth?  What's he got left to hide?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played @DraftKings for the first time last night and made like $50 on the backs of Otto Porter, Zach Lavine, and Lauri Markkanen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTylerKSR I need an update on @2ReidTravis2!!!! https://t.co/EX1knRO5CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenaciousTess I will beat it into thier brain. Working on cars, and swearing for 8 hours straight. That's what I do,...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Lani Kai, you never disappoint. #BAR#six @ Lani Kai Island Resort https://t.co/XuprtR8i0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevensonhs @SHSpatFB Fired up for coach Becker!!  My first position coach, one of the best MEN I know.   Texts me… https://t.co/2SOXgZtmob]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had this on an iPad at comic con this past weekend! It was a super fun way to share our #Kickstarter at our boot… https://t.co/kUJ5cA1JrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AureiiKeon @Freeyourmindkid Maybe you're not a good arbiter of what's racist. N.b., saying that racism might be ok… https://t.co/ujPZc4KHTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check his shed. N under it. I’m certain. He’s got a cemetery back there with dozens of missing ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first rainbow ring!  Made of layered, glued 1/64 inch strips of dyed white pine.  #woodturning #woodenrings… https://t.co/roM9zKhd8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atleticopantoja @radafil_diaz @nyredbulls Como esta la promo en las afuera del Felix Sanchez]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fourth installment in an ongoing series of cinematic musings is now published over @maakhaus: a look at Elia Ka… https://t.co/vwqSPllSUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to @K1RaceGear driver Parker Klingerman for qualifying for the Daytona 500!!!… https://t.co/ZfjuYC5tqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sallyjung @WilldeFries @DCheverere @dcarterruff @mailinpodcast Man Sally good thing you added that comma]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My parents never gave me money. They gave me media coverage, my family is RICH and everyone wants to sign me for m… https://t.co/dmSwa7bBpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariekeWalsh We are being governed by unethical fools @MonteMcNaughton]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1 I would introduce someone new to SEO to Googlebot, and how it crawls the Web and Data on the Web; both what Page… https://t.co/97afMbuTyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[SDSU vs Wright State is a must with this!  Will be disappointed if it doesn't happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at Houston Baptist University this past weekend! Just wanted to say thanks to @ZKittley and… https://t.co/Kj7HI0GseY]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗳Voted YEA on #GAHB239 to establish a Georgia Business Court. Passed 156-8 #garepvotes #gapol #gahouse #houseleads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmagic17 @OwenNewkirk @dfwticket *Extreme @junior_miller voice*  Also: “we don’t even do it anymooooore”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @pboeckner @DarrinCates @ShelbyFenster @Travis_Klanecky @MConwayKLKN @nicolecousinstv @LizWhalleyKLKN… https://t.co/5fjGR3ZGsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBN_BillC Thoughts on what 2012 A&amp;M and 2018 A&amp;M would look like had Sherman been given 2012 and Johnny Football?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oilmanms Having driven Uber...you’re correct. And no one is out driving for 3$ an hour when they could do something else and make more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out and thanks ms_dunn cne.fashioncloset for trying out the experience and support I appreciate that .. 🔥🍹🍬🔥… https://t.co/LjMtuWSwuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Gr0sera @CimarronesFC Mientras el balón pueda rodar en la cancha sin tener charcos para un bote muy seco se puede jugar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearties nation is ready #hearties #WCTH #HeavenWouldBeSeasonSeven @hallmarkchannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveStaeger @LizKotalik @KylieBearseWX Need more clues. Funny actually look forward to watching the morning news with Steve Liz and Kylie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like I’m officially a goth now that I’ve been yelled at in the library for playing Bela Lugosi’s Dead too loud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the day when wwe went into commercials and you and your siblings be doing last man standing match. The bed… https://t.co/JLNiohDUll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Missaamarissa True but still not ok for her to be the only one that’s being publicly shamed. Even tho she says she… https://t.co/O81BFt91eN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmenglish_ @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump When did mueller say there was nothing, did @FoxNews tell you that lie.… https://t.co/Tp9gdvk9dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustineLavaworm It’s one of my favorite movies, but I could definitely see you hating it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh so true, I cannot wait for them to get caught in his wrath of bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want you all to know that she said this to me while drunk off of my whiskey last night and it blew my mind. Nikki… https://t.co/SYvMyZr3gp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parislg16 You shouldn’t feel like trash when you see a guy who doesn’t like you, because I know you don’t what guy… https://t.co/2IY3yQfsI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[YouTube will soon tell you that the world isn't flat, vaccines work, and other obvious truths https://t.co/z6t4RornEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just drove over a Modelo can in the middle of a country road and honestly nothing sums up my hometown more than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanhemsworth (Remixed Boss and One For Me) said he wants to make another song with @Tinashe and she agreed. Storm… https://t.co/CX5YbgPCmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[First @nyrangers game Go Rangers!! @ Madison Square Garden https://t.co/xzIBfTOnFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to take a little hiatus on going out until St. Patty’s day. I’ve been going out too much the last two months… https://t.co/YPeEoznrzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was for impeaching GWB for war crimes and I am for impeaching Trump for his prior crimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering Bush and Trump both became President without winning America’s popular vote I’ll only care about popula… https://t.co/hgyrlFbCNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, she came on to me Khloé. You know I love you and those hips babe gurl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sg939y @MidAtlanticHeat @GeorgeYearling @MASWreckingCrew @VMoncada_ @EchoEddy928 @RGordon_757 Straight 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smugdingus When all the shops in Indian Springs were shutting down, how was Wig City able to survive? Not Dillard’… https://t.co/KfIVhw74kH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBookDrag0n Me too.  Only my friends and family.  My kids friends are my most important betas.  Unfortunately, t… https://t.co/9RaIPY24Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattklewis I don’t agree with Omar, but go ahead and line up her words against his - then let’s talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and have a big ass smoke session with @SnoopDogg  Anyone that knows me knows that's on my bucket list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris I would love to see a return of the middle class that Reagan splintered into upper/middle/ lower clas… https://t.co/HwsUNDGsX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steigerworld Part 2 moved a lot better than part 1, it was boring but also felt like it was a must watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so sorry to all my Burt’s Bees for how often y’all go through the washing machine. Thinking of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonmyrt Probly from carrying Andrew McDonald’s anytime he’s on the ice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braydo1987 @LVGully @MisterVegas1957 He said what he said. Mark asked. He answered. You can’t force a narrative to… https://t.co/x6aXgeVpXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mez_merrill @goodenough_fu @CAT1PRO @ViktorMochalin @BobKillman1 @johnnyrockhill @frances_van @a_nowtime… https://t.co/C8Chl0Gijt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're down to nothing, God is up to something. The faithful see the invisible, believe the incredible, and th… https://t.co/igCL4AP86n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece on PBS with @WmBrangham about FOX as Trump TV based in part on on New Yorker article]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Shouldn’t he be arrested? #AOC #AlexandriaOcasioCortez #JerryFalwellJr #CPAC2019 #ImpeachTrumpNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanfrank6 Try this.  You will have to log into amazon to do the review.  https://t.co/FQ7VlWS6Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend at the polar plunge for the Special Olympics @ Center Lake https://t.co/Xx5ZJ8BclY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicIris @DavidHarris707 @JaimeNelsonW @d_ast777 @SeptemberJulie @RosaDeliadelos1 @JudyMcAferty @CatholicForLife… https://t.co/DQqSn15V5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alvaroarivera18 Yo no dije que no sea, digo que Tigres tiene igual o más recocimiento y sin ganar algo internacional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amiller78 According to who? Him? Lol. I split the atom in my basement. Where’s my article?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Release orcas and beluga whales from the “whale jail” in Srednyaya Bay - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/cdx1Zss8V4 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, it's the outro song not just the song in the shop. I don't remember much just various things that don't even ma… https://t.co/XPfDO5Vas4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guidomotors @goose2448 @uncensored_seth And I was directing my first comment to gooses remarks about not seeing the likeness.  Not you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derek_mafs @AOC Looks like a conservative snowflake had his safespace violated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicBergerIV Tim has always been genuinely (and likably) naive videographer with an interest in pointless subcultur… https://t.co/j2nZ1WzifA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EamonJavers asia time! travel safe my friend and thank you for outstanding reporting]]></document></documents></author>