<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kuriuskat @RyanAFournier 😂 😂 😂 And you're a typical liberal - nasty and hateful spewing insults rather than articulating an argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queeens96 tells me to “hurry up” as if I could possibly run all the red lights I’m hitting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JR_24X @Mitch_T13 Storm cheated the cap substantially worse though so I don’t think they have a reason to be upset either]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Universal Studios Florida - @universalorl in Orlando, FL https://t.co/BuqEO9I7qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare moment this morning where cat and dog where lying peacefully in close proximity to one another.… https://t.co/8qxcEYVXkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get a headshot for 2019? We are offering it for FREE! Wednesday, March 6th. Register at… https://t.co/GsHEIMtilz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EileenisDOPE Hmm. I'll have to check my schedule 💅 https://t.co/kOyinb4JKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday Look at all these large companies getting back millions in refunds from the IRS. The middle class owes t… https://t.co/jZmtMTshce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T19Riley all the time. I struggle to declare a minor or double major bc I find so many things interesting and thin… https://t.co/h2ukUMzkBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit... just watching “Surviving R. Kelly” and I am completely floored. I’m so embarrassed and ashamed that I… https://t.co/Ji2I9tawLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment you are on set which most likely won’t wrap till after 12:30am only to find out you’ve got a call time o… https://t.co/wWipm8YLNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s really the IT guy, they could’ve put someone else in the car so that no one ever calls him to testify...  I… https://t.co/WdPFcq7W13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm currently leading a workshop on the seasonality of produce in Wisconsin. The bars represent dates of harvest an… https://t.co/NCKP0lhctJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best and relevant books-YouTube series I’ve encountered for the Christian believer.  Do yourself a favor… https://t.co/G9b9Cumwwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birdman8272 But I get it if he does....  I will keep my FAITH IN HIM ....Until he fails. I don't see that]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE is detaining 50,000 a day  HOW many are held in FOR PROFIT PRISONS working for far below minimum wage?  WHO is… https://t.co/OB6aLm4Slr]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the couple who STOPPED DEAD IN THEIR TRACKS RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME TO MAKE OUT:  Thanks for hugging me and stoppin… https://t.co/AfWG0OqYcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenny_detten @WynnWilliams1 You'll have to fight me and @TXSrecruiter for that job. We love Wynn!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG @MarenMorris album came out today and @Spotify was kind enough to alert me and now I'm jamming out #GIRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sisters we got some work to do! #womeninoffice #InternationalWomansDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[aww man i know what you’re going through! I had to put my cat down the day after valentines. Just know he’s in a be… https://t.co/IFuPpSEbJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many kids I run across during high school visits that have never flown!  I hope 🤞🏽 they are afforded the chance… https://t.co/BlmVaGQItR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, I follow you because this is history repeating, not because I enjoy reading how low the Republican regime has… https://t.co/qJiXMlvyaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle His deal with the devil was that he could only keep his human skin for a while.  His true reptilian nat… https://t.co/Ut4BStMJn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate my Lyft drivers who wait for me to get inside my house before driving off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first thoughts: what will this mean for Arlington?   https://t.co/l0VV8yL4Xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and nothing even happened yall i just seen a tweet that triggered me. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎁 🎉 Nintendo Switch Giveaway! 🎉 🎁  Anyone can have a chance to win this HUGE Zelda prizepack.  To enter:  1. Follow… https://t.co/aNnUrVUQ45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I have never been so disgusted, but determined to stop their evil. I pray God will give us the wisdom to stop the madness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorBoehm6 I strangely was just talking about this! I can take vodka shots and not flinch but bring out cold medicine, absolutely not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeForClimate I don't know if it's because I came from the UK (where ABA isn't a thing) or because some of it jus… https://t.co/O2KHQFqPVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLairdMD @supportprop @NBCNews waking up w/rods shoved N2 spine, recovery room closed so all surgery patients pu… https://t.co/TrBRmQhSot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Couldn’t agree more Kamala. His sentence is absurd. It continues to be a rich, white man’s world when… https://t.co/rhf2SM3N3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TribeOfMa @smartieplum @rotrujo @Hannover_ETI Mr. Clubber looks intense today 😳❤️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth! How it works... #science #physics #mathematics Forever #curious! So.. I wonder what it really means to touch… https://t.co/ZPVIEAec1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Go_Taylor @UnitedWayOttawa Congratulations Mark. I look forward to working with you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisamdanish @superkash Yes. I mean, he’s already engaged to a different little girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROWSBUUD @gmich3lle @madii_renee This really did make my day better ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s honestly terrifying that you really can never know who you can trust]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC She Needs to Be Removed from Congress immediately that's VERY Dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @realDonaldTrump oh you are so cute, a grown man coming up with something like this, wow, you dems will… https://t.co/6pBuOXzli9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristaFagan @SSC_CA Thanks Krista!  No plans yet! But it’s definitely in my future ... and I’ll be sure to let you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_Dockery Very high percentage. And many still support him!  I just do not understand the cult mentality. Than… https://t.co/jbrM6WewYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kem &amp; i have been on the phone for over an hour &amp; all we talk about are books 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Give this guy a medal to have the guts to say the truth for once !!🤗🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[A snowy birthday celebration for my now 7-year-old nephew, my mom (who went on the toboggan with someorangeguy and… https://t.co/nye90ThkGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideHustleWino @DivaVinophile @MacrinaBakery @BainbridgeIsl @nofussgourmet @SteveKubota @SashaEats @GrnLakeGirl… https://t.co/NjX7bPR4EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that more #WomenInGovernment are needed to advance gender equality today. Do you agree? #SheBelongs… https://t.co/2iS1yGHaR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Watermelon Wilds” 12x12 in., oil on panel. #LittlePiggy continues her adventures into the jungle-like folds of gol… https://t.co/jQk9W71SI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“First things first....”  How you finish that line gives me all the information I need about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTVChart @WHOTheBckstreet @BTS_twt @jonasbrothers @onedirection @backstreetboys If you are a BSB fan you have to vote and help them win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grgbkr37 If we follow her thinking, we should deport her to China or Japan. I am almost sure that @AOC is indigeno… https://t.co/tZzIbWdk9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, Tristan is why your family broke up. You lost him how you got him, sis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desire to understand is not a flaw. @ True North Mediation https://t.co/DGF05RXRlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, my friends, it is true; I will not be blogging for WordPress near the end of June after 6-1/2 years; Find out… https://t.co/gMlKa4xQwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarriaMendoza @_dacey24 love you harria!! But they really haven’t felt me yet🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magssca @CompaTiger @gio_designsla I haven’t thrown up in so long but if I do I’ll record it]]></document><document><![CDATA[haze -&gt; scattered clouds temperature down 42°F -&gt; 35°F humidity up 56% -&gt; 100% wind 6mph -&gt; 3mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @washingtonpost @AOC @SpeakerPelosi Not knowing the Law is not an excuse!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aschulte17 @CamNizguy @AafLegends I have no Idea, it makes ZERO sense to me...I want to say his year at UGA he was… https://t.co/enxxB9IVCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleas to @realDonaldTrump from Venezuela. This is what @AOC @BernieSanders @ewarren and @KamalaHarris want for you,… https://t.co/1ABYpqm3lU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni That's putting it lightly! They judged many people for their "sins" but didn't judge themselves?! Horrifying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WK15D6 workout. Flew back in late the day before and there was no stopping The Train LOL I had to throw that in the… https://t.co/G67Ym2U6z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cotytolly I get super drained on days where I have back to back counseling sessions...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Example: @MyBravaHome is SO COOL. How do I get one?! #AOEInnovators @SAMCEDA https://t.co/natqZOYVmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/fne3kLDEUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craving a heartfelt apology from all the people that let me down in the form of an etransfer]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am trying soo hard not to wake everyone in the house up right now lmaooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/bringing @amazon to New York is symbolic. As Wall St and other legacy industries go extinct, NY has to bet on its… https://t.co/6K32J18Qhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 21 and a half tasks to finish, and my boss just asked if I could handle taking on an entire month long Soror… https://t.co/AGoTDMLTOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t wake up in the middle of the night to hydrate your skin, what even are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wowwww everyone was wanting to roast me when I wanted Cortes’ a long ass time ago and now they’re a whole ass trend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Respectpolice63 @SheriffChody @lt_gray @Goldust 🤣🤣 is this from the new movie? If so, I haven’t seen it yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Ewing’s 3rd graders @baucomes rocked their Perimeter and Area review today! I got to share @PearDeck with… https://t.co/bLiX32j0LW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often glorify a task or experience I want to do so deeply that it can almost never happen they way I want it to u… https://t.co/BVfJINkKeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgetting Those Things Which  Are Behind, &amp; Reaching Forth To Those Things Which Are Before Me.… https://t.co/Myl3b75ht8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @AllegedButler for the great reporting on our March @CityofIthaca1 Council meeting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun building 2D shapes with anglegs and naming them based on their attributes! #MondayFunday #HesKindMinds… https://t.co/1g9bfHc7FN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Whiter than our beautiful crop of cotton last fall...before hurricane Michael.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to laugh every time Dr Fumich pulls up in his big F 350 Platinum Ford truck and the PAs literally have to jump up into his truck 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @pchandler45 Scum. Epstein sits on his private island doing who knows what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_Rankin @Nika_Howard Hey does Tanika wanna get out of the truck? Does she wanna die?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump The Romans were right to punish and nailed Jesus to the cross.  Jesus was an illeg… https://t.co/zsENwvWZPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to remind myself that i work 12 hour days 4 days out of the week so it’s ok if I’m not working out often or… https://t.co/ociZy7H2qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanFillion Yes but I'm the parent of a 3 year old so it's gonna be another 15 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovernorVA what is wrong with you and your wife.... Paint your face black she gives raw cotton to kids touring mansion.... No moral compass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity it is not "we the people" It is you and our shady administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-Mobile sucks you can't get service anywhere what's the point of being that cheap if I can't get service God forbi… https://t.co/KzA4GiHphG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow shoveling means snow cats! (And I totally shoveled too!) 🐈💖🌨 #ctweather #snow @gilsimmons @RachelFrank_CT https://t.co/wrN1mMvMUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this also my heart trembleth, and is moved out of his place. https://t.co/Iem7SnN93z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading “Introducing Uber’s Ludwig” by Jesus Rodriguez #machinelearning @TensorFlow https://t.co/lpzy3sJYVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs @BigBrotherGOD1 @az_movement @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @POTUS Deporting costs money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All i can think about is how i came home at 2am the other night and my puppy starts barking rattin my ass out to ev… https://t.co/teFP4C9qZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear dude in the white truck,  running a stop sign at a busy intersection going 40 isn’t cool.  Sincerely, The girl… https://t.co/kmw9Ls6QuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you ever thought slippery slope arguments were invalid: Senate Dems Block Born-Alive Bill… https://t.co/5j3oAujlv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSnodsEnq @Coachlazar @mlaughman @JRichardsonENQ @EnquirerShelby @JWeberSports Congratulations 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwoleyAnderson @soberworldsws See I wish my brother would tell me that :,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaffeinatedMike @MarkDice I've been calling them "mister lady" in a Jerry Lewis voice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge to be Curious and explore ideas and opinions that are different than mine. See how you can do your part at… https://t.co/B3SjAis9T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This s@$t is getting real. So excited to be in the studio in less than a week. Want to help me pay everyone and mys… https://t.co/oIb3DAEh6V]]></document></documents></author>