<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TraceyWJZ thanks for always brightening the morning for dayside shifts. Your smile always made ME smile. Congrats… https://t.co/rkuB6KgNav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surgeon_General Spiderverse is great! Nicholas Cage is in it, need I say more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since the day I gave up my food 2 u, u have always been in my ❤, You'll always remain there even tho we're apart. I… https://t.co/8oI6lj8jFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hugocarvajal4f @AlbertoRavell ¿Y este criminal cree q se salva con una conversión de última hora?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has there ever been a more perfect sitcom casting job than @AndreBraugher as captain holt on brooklyn 99?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break in the rain yesterday. Took a great walk up to Divide Meadow in @PointReyesNPS Hung out with coyote for over… https://t.co/ez9NvkMfHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post-Sundance reflection. Bliss. #clemencythefilm #sundancefilmfestival #grandjuryprizewinner #canonportrait https://t.co/orVIoMGxNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLincoln The science fiction short story: “I Have No Mouth, And I Must Scream.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hazybuchanan omg I saw that, it looks so delectable!  They also have a cauliflower gnocchi that I really wanna try 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amir_barnett1 Proud of all you’ve done. Always believed in you big guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the #kcicio18 t-shirts ready for #CUE19 !!!!! https://t.co/iKwrwMM4uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@alcidesescobar2 Thank you for helping the @royals bring another WS championship to Kansas City. Wishing you all the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yucaipabaseball plays Tuesday 2/26/19 6pm against South Hills. @PEcom_preps @Inland_Sports @latsondheimer… https://t.co/G4Fi4H2cvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is a big mess.” Numerous popular apps send sensitive information about their users directly to Facebook, @WSJ… https://t.co/aXGTOW7Ty3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMSZN24 Proud of you fam love you and may God continue to Bless you Happy Birthday 🎂🎉🎉🎈🎈 https://t.co/UlKwGKNN7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billbarol Actually I meant “Our Man Flint” (also Goldsmith): https://t.co/EW5e9IMCht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRock @Jon__Reed this would go nice beside the Volunteer Vodka at fan run studio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Groupon idea was novel but failed to develop a sustainable model - recurring revenue and now 13 th consecutive… https://t.co/hCWKXtKDgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_TMatthews Check out Brian Daughtry Jr's Player ID on National Prospect ID @NationalPID https://t.co/gJ5JYttp2s #NPID]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Cuse_MBB takes on #18 @LouisvilleMBB now on @ESPN. #CuseMode https://t.co/FCKj19a2Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww Shit.. Hoodnite!💕 #HVD!❤️ @ Hawthorne, California https://t.co/GjAwP9ahdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's loyalty obsession could lead to obstruction case....No shit!! #MARINESagainstTrump #VetsResistSquadron… https://t.co/ADVKqny9Zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dame_Lillard @adidas @adidasHoops can anybody please tell me what dame has on his feet here??🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PMCimpact knows no bounds and #PwCBoston is incredibly proud to be a long-time sponsor and corporate team. Can’t w… https://t.co/KuyU5guUb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be thankful for each day is one thing... To make the most of each day is the ultimate Gratitude… https://t.co/4H0vYIHwK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very pleased to represent @1CUSBA and @dickinsonwright by moderating this panel on #crossborderinvestment with… https://t.co/19xIvbWhX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @joeylogano @LVMotorSpeedway His tires were a matched perferct and staggered special... Thats the only reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericasTeam_21 @DeMarcusWare I love D Ware but we don't need another senior citizen #DallasCowboys #CowboysNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the most wonderful time of the year... @ Foster City, California https://t.co/nuK1XD7ZAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mholtefarms @surlybrewing Todd the Axe Man is my personal favorite, but I can get a 30 of Busch for what 2 4 packs of that costs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our varsity girls in the Regional Championship. Location: @lenoirrhyne Opponent: @ForbushHS Time: 4PM… https://t.co/t8XtFf68oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Harper contract is gonna blow up in the Phils’ face in about 3-4 years when they don’t have any pitching or money to spend elsewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hope that when we talk about changing politics we do it from a foundation of not everybody who is outside of you… https://t.co/mOZbek7W2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScooterRegister @TXewood @tcraigjones Always, Coach! Hope all is well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_Walker21 @Marcus_Hooper12 Marcus said they aren’t stingy and I believe him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop and go traffic in #WakeCounty on I-40 WB from Gorman St - Exit 295 to past Hwy 1 - Exit 293, wreck to past Hwy 1 - Exit 293 #traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerrymiller @AOC There's a fairly reliable test to determine bigotry: do you support the bigot occupying the highe… https://t.co/hjLKLoXKzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTtTos || 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The… https://t.co/clbzvWzuol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel tonight can’t wait ✊🏼 #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/PZrfW5WGG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DAM_Nation_ @Shelbyobrien41 @AngieMachado1 @BeaverBaseball @Nike Didn’t one of your pitchers fuck a 6 year old ch… https://t.co/xjvCcIpHxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTAMUTrackXC sweeps the @LoneStarConf Indoor Conference meet! #TraditionInMotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump No, crazy scary is the Russian stooge sitting in the Oval Office!  It would be a DE… https://t.co/W3vqO6C67s]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way, @desusnice and @THEKIDMERO both called and nailed it. If you didn’t watch @SHODesusAndMero you’re dumb… https://t.co/rOIn7jc9mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KitsapTransit My mother has already contacted you. The loss of routed bus service is NOT mitigated by the ACCESS b… https://t.co/0TKBqewxoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghotican I’ve been meaning to start listening to Boris, where should I start?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans, that’s right, Americans must band together in future elections and replace this group of Washington scum… https://t.co/TZZZEtMhfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen 🙏🏻 bendiciones para todos feliz viernes @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/FTvSYQW2Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be covering the Huntington boys sectional semifinal game tonight. @SamBlackburnTR will have coverage of the… https://t.co/upu3P348hD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseDresserG Que bueno que no representa “un cheque en blanco” ❤️🇲🇽🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Barrel-Aged Jifforia - Fat Elvis Variant by @MainAndMillBrew at @candlewood — https://t.co/T6Zyw39Q4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickadamsweb Thank you for taking the time to read it. Hope it was the only drama you encountered while flying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random chick follows me. Wonder who she knows that i know.... lmao @CodyC_33 https://t.co/ItWdl0Zzvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que tiene de malo ? siempre se ha declarado chiva de corazón , era una pregunta de 2 respuesta , mientras responda… https://t.co/w41Xbo9Ba3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth is without Lebron we’d have a good 16 wins right now. Thank him don’t hate him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the key to a good defense in boxing is neutralizing your opponent's offense.  #Boxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNoahRing Cannot be done without taxing everyone and that means it is not “Free”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God starting to bless me more i guess he heard me one of them night's praying !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired: I can't believe the Rockets traded Ennis for nothing  Wired: I can't believe the Rockets got off of Ennis' player option for nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread on #AmazonHQ2: Apart from celebrating,I'm still struggling w what were #Amazon real motives in pulling out o… https://t.co/VwlLlSoqUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGTA_FPL Now that is a nice piece of data mate... way under xG and XA no doubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JLEdwardsIII’s tweet game is a whole other level tonight.  Cardigan too warm? Hiding something in the pocket?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizkcurtis @StowNathan @DavidHolst9 @SpecialDara @akaurer Wait the other side of the history before make conclusions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buttercup is too damn hilarious - "You replaced me with a bestie named 'YOU'?!" @savannahlmay @hollyhuebner… https://t.co/7zdoib6Nx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we loved about this extraordinary diningroom is the dedication put on every chair as well as in the edge of th… https://t.co/2IB7Pk183I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGard17 After amnesia that night 😂 Oi Gaz, what was that one Sven Vath dropped Da Da Da Da boom boom boom #Banger @Garilee11]]></document><document><![CDATA[... Another step to precede that is to get permission, casually or otherwise, to ask about my involvement with diff… https://t.co/0VYaRXzA0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaraSetmayer You worked for Glen Beck????? Well, that explains SO MUCH about your political and personal choices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJHughes45 I hatched a shiny Articuno last week. Do you have that one yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImTroyG For real 😂😂😂 you know we gotta analyze the hell out them lyrics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLondonDance Good opportunity to do something for yourself,  something different and fun!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bphesq @HaffaAlan Not detaining asylum seekers who have rights under international law, to which the USA is a sign… https://t.co/uYoJEIy6Rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing killing my vibe today is its still freezing outside but other than that its finally March, its Frida… https://t.co/tKOKqLMJUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottyarf how many feet of snow does my daughter have to clear off her ‘soccer’ pitch to get a signed team Canada… https://t.co/KWAZQQPvwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandiACaras @WhiteHouse This whole Cohen is a waste of the taxpayers money.  The Dems have spent over 25 million o… https://t.co/SLf3gDuw0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you can start with dropping the carbs.  They can’t hurt you anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's my first, and second, blog articles from April 2005. I'm talking about virtual communities and connected lea… https://t.co/dSggiXjAyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The absolute last thing I wanted to do this morning was get on the treadmill. I did. But #daylightsaving is kicking… https://t.co/d0rGAMi6VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenTremendous Didn’t even read the other three options after I saw Ben Foster’s name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[really the only major flaw with #tetris99 so far is that you can’t preload holdswap/rotation during timefreeze and… https://t.co/28uFJncXEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet They will start answering as soon as they come up with something clever,  seeing as though they haven… https://t.co/Qzm009jFiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the one that infuriates me the most. When you make the move from IT to security, your focus should be on wo… https://t.co/q1rqKFh6bO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIRED Bienvenido  Sí. Eso es correcto.  @jack it probando nuevas formas de globalizar  ya sabes  conectar con la g… https://t.co/OL8Ae45N5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerLetsRoll @DoingRight1 @YeahIGotBacon @ElaineEbk @livin2bsimple @leahbirdjohnso2 @cjbj731 @JulieReichwein1… https://t.co/oraM1QkzJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farberyanki @IsraelUSAforevr Can you check that store, to see if they have a bottle of Weibel, looking for Green Hungarian 1981]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS. We'd really love to have more pedagogy and teaching abstracts as part of our NEASA conference this year. Just F… https://t.co/qYEXhnb2Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Z5twtU9ZOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael Todo apunta directamente hacia Moreno y su familia con pruebas contundentes y reales.Un cínico d prime… https://t.co/Y7nW9r6aDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpottash knows darn well this wouldn’t have been half as good if it wasn’t for him bringing some structure to madn… https://t.co/c8svTrkacV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang this game is pretty! Character models also look pretty awesome compared to masseffectandromeda I’m having a go… https://t.co/aVwJzlkMeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamCarpoolKaraoke on @TyltEnt—'Carpool Karaoke’ is the most fun musical series https://t.co/eDYzPSxTil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @CivicCommonsUS partners @Driggs16DC &amp; @mslynnross! Thank you for your impact &amp; leadership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Old Pro by @unionbrewing at @holidayinn — https://t.co/yXY9YhWXr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy looked fantastic and he was what, 80+?   Wonder what he ate for breakfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its Well anyway I stumbled across a dogging session in which a man and woman were on (what appeared to be a public bus).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idahogal1006 @cspippin @dwaynecobb @veterans_i @greensnow @DarthSpader747 @deepdvr1234 @PoxNewsCEO @Hell_HasCome… https://t.co/wePqSxwJW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re reading this, you are a leader.   Unfortunately, we all know of folks who think they are leaders, but Cal… https://t.co/JA1XO0j2MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great truth I couldn’t pass by this morning...listen closely active Christian... “Busyness does not mean yo… https://t.co/X1SJ1vVYtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlonVzla @Messiatico @ChampionsLeague @realmadrid Siempre veo el #missuniverso soy Venezolano. Y veo fútbol desd… https://t.co/Vfw5ufrPdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnivisionSports @Chivas Esa cosa no sabe nada orita no es perro es ardilla ya le ba ala amierdica]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces no dimensionamos el alcance que tienen los pequeños sacrificios que realizamos día con día]]></document></documents></author>