<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "School Speech Language Pathologist - SLP CCC" at Supplemental Health Care? Applicant track… https://t.co/qGm7l8jrui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all for shitting on Green Book, Peter Farrelly, etc, but maybe leave Bobby Farrelly out of it. The reason he di… https://t.co/TASPJJ71ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellTech all we do is win win win no matter what... Truly inspiring future #iwork4dell https://t.co/5YnwWFa115]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan So you are still trying to undermine the Russian investigation that was an attack on our democracy.  WHY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman The Catholic Church has investigated the incident and cleared these kids of any wrongdoing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot walk bc I have the bones of an 85 year old and I stood for 13 hours today https://t.co/IMnliXiLl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djsziff Of course, people want attribution when it gives them additional social capital. My question is why I should care what they want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight savings is rough... but hey at least I’m not fighting sunset during 6pm live shots anymore👌 https://t.co/M7N5MFSuRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheSwap #JustBeYou #MOFIS #BE #MyOnlyFocusIsSuccess #FuckGucci #GUCCI #LOCALBRAND #Columbus #ColumbusOhio #Ohio @… https://t.co/eX4a7Qfu5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bas Peaky Blinders. That’s how I dress but always listening to that #Bas flow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @poroshenko @ashrafghani @NATO @jensstoltenberg @POTUS https://t.co/4IwKZQGQoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaddySoBroke Dude I loved watching them fucking squirm or get all awkward when they got called out on that doc. Th… https://t.co/tbCv7ShYjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gil333 @EdKrassen @karynmelligan @realDonaldTrump Problematic. https://t.co/t9GinOSTxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixed reality allows users to remain a physical part of the class, with the digital visualisations being included i… https://t.co/tPGZWCeXCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean cats like DSJ have things to prove, they don’t care about ping pong balls...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Block or charge?🏀⛳️🍻🥴🤢   (💰game. No gimmies.🤷‍♂️😊)   https://t.co/1ZqgGByVKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kibblesmith As a quasi-professional lyricist, I hate you so much right now for doing this better than me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffCoo09850101 @PeteButtigieg I completely agree. He and his husband @Chas10Buttigieg were so delightful to meet… https://t.co/XHU1x1njOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible 4 bedroom home in North Oshawa's Taunton community sitting on a premium sized lot!🏡 Beautiful open conce… https://t.co/1YolZForQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToyotaMex para cuando la programación que permita mostrar el display en millas ? #RAV4 https://t.co/66WmRsbleM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oswguzma Dejarias entrar a tu casa a alguien que se quiere quedar con tu esposa y matar tus hjijos,,yo no.. Parabo… https://t.co/Pyo5e3GWf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% waterproof rigid core vinyl plank It's good at everywhere, bathroom, kitchen, living room, bedroom.....… https://t.co/6VYVM1c95p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachplumgirl @HarvilleScott @peterdaou @NRA It’s a good thing us white men have guns because of people like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE this story! People in Wisconsin are sending photos of their dogs to help cheer up a little girl battling a bra… https://t.co/JLIb04PcwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusaliaMudavadi Good job3 mheshimiwa  and prayers for a quick recovery sent to the Kenyan legend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReckoningComing @o_marianne @WomenForTrump4 @SaraCarterDC Good catch. They are trying to string that out as much a… https://t.co/XJe0MrwOmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronhorton75 @KipHenley But u comparing mediocre to perfect. Get it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingMinos777 @LauraleeB4real @ginatognoni @YandR_CBS @CBSDaytime https://t.co/Riscag4lKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the same question. I’ll tell you something that I inadvertently stumbled onto - hold up your phone like you’… https://t.co/IrzIO5Zcvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great first chat tonight! Thanks for the experience @mraspinall #CodeBreaker]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time that money and corruption made our laws is on its way to the history books. We will not stand for the few… https://t.co/iHNC39614x]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIP  Dejah Thoris sketch pencils by Eric Blake as I try  to put my ink stamp on it.  - - - -TAGS. #drawing… https://t.co/gBsJx8HdhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few things are more irritating than interviewing for a job, only for them to come back over a year later and ask if… https://t.co/WFVhM4wLKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were joking on set that my Bald head looked like Powder. Totally forgot about that movie and had to re watch. Fo… https://t.co/d1JanIA5ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkillsCommons @OLCToday Excited @SkillsCommons is getting recognized for this work!  https://t.co/PNffdq2JbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to remember when Conway’s criticisms of POTUS were wry and understated.   The evolution has been rem… https://t.co/AendIlzViV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyKappell if we all write your name in on ballots for county legislature would you take it? Really don’t won’t… https://t.co/qHOGsvCMWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten @itsgettinglate If fans are under the impression that Rogers isn't going to pay so Vladdy walks duri… https://t.co/vaxbkYftrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BJUBruins @BJUBruinsWBB @kyleeleffew10 @BJU_PR Proud @ccsladycougars @COLONIALCOUGARS @colonialindy alumni making a difference!]]></document><document><![CDATA[R Kelly hold ass bitch hope your ass go to hell devils child  you are gay ugly you are wrong to insolent women and… https://t.co/EcZ3PcX4mZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive safely #Dubuque and remember... "Success occurs when your DREAMS get bigger than your excuses!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico She was trying to make a name for herself so that she could be Clinton's AG. She is corrupt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talbenhorin @NCState Bravo! We look forward to having you down our way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is a joke. #Reno (@ West Second Street Bar in Reno, NV) https://t.co/nzIIcTWbHs https://t.co/tDdvoylQNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[17:57 Temp. 57.6°F, Hum. 54%, Dewp. 39.4°F, Bar. 30.26 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 137° 2.1 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I didn’t get shit for Valentine’s Day today not even a snap from team snapchat😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKavulla @jt_hammons @drvox Sorry, my reading of the bill is that it is very different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigSkellz Lost a lot of weight and size moving back to the chuck 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mykaelata @malmond98 Lol you two white knighting for yourselves is comical truly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TairyT47 Feliz Viernes a la doncella del tránsito de NY Nj y Connecticut ,Tairy 🚦🚥🌹❤️😘🌟✨⭐️ https://t.co/dFEdvFsbQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ain't about Bernie either but all these so called "progressives". Ya sitting there mad that nobody is giving y… https://t.co/pRxacP6SaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo NBC won the weekend for putting on a great tribute to Elvis. A worthy win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brink_Sensei It's like staring in the sun, don't do it or you'll go blind! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillcrest Coaches with the "legendary Christian Coleman" https://t.co/CvlkHviQUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShopRiteStores Please help me set my expectations. How many times should I have to call my local store before they… https://t.co/mZdtXvDpFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevin_smedley @DynastyFrank @MikeClayNFL @evansilva Not Evan, but i can answer. The Giants will be mediocre and wa… https://t.co/qmihY6Zn1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheItalGal I was just thinking my twitter account is awfully quiet today.. Right now I am watching the #LondonKnights game ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliLanyonABC27 @AmandaABC27 Simply unacceptable for such strong, smart and beautiful women like you both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anyakristen Awww....I don’t dream much of anything anymore, LoL! https://t.co/TqoHap9Y7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenpencils @morgetron Thank *you*! I spent an hour scrolling through your insta feed, saving several posts in a co… https://t.co/kuHiaibiN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamiya1980 @LINDACREAM @minoru_official @Ukjamesmason @TomLaRuffa @joeLEGEND @queen_chesca39 その辺食い合いにならないようにしてます。]]></document><document><![CDATA[What bout trump’s repressive and feckless regime? Where are the vountries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper My least favorite Memphis song, but “Walking in Memphis” by Marc Cohen also Rupert Holmes’ Escape (t… https://t.co/cThHkUvkQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just going to say it. 🗣️🗣️THE HAWKS ALSO GOT A GOOD PLAYER IN THAT TRADE WITH DALLAS @ColeyMick @MickstapeShow @TylerIAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compré un cigarro al intendente de la facu y me dio una paletita ❤ esos son los chidos pinches rascuachxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheXXXTeddyBear @DJChiChiLaRue @CoachThomasHARD @zardain65 @GuisCumGuzzler @FullyPumped @ginissaquah… https://t.co/JcVAuoFG5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbsheriff can we please stop the booming sounds here in Orcutt PLEASE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The drove buy news forgot to mention our GDP up again 2.6% not bad for a place Obama said would never hit 3% and we… https://t.co/Dmlvyi3LDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HammerPike @BlueDevilNation Crap I was thinking of Brian Williams from Arizona. Nevermind still Scott Williams. Still alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Jaylee Moore three at the 7:24 mark has Hartshorne down, 34-31. #OKPreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_business_  i just finished GoT for the first time and now i can finally refollow you]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I hope to find someone who loves me a lil more then I love them. Not a lot just a lil. Tired of being on the opposite end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandHTackle @thgrace78_grace @BaldBandit43 Sounds good! Do you paint ice fishing jigs???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronmoxley Things are great! I’m a dad now! 🙌🏻 we are also about to open a new cafe this year which is crazy exciting! DM me your address]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metrorailinfo Trains are usually sitting/leaving when I get to the platform. Point is I know the sign is capable o… https://t.co/YNctQaey8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like at least three times  out of the week I have:  (say this out loud) Casual conversations  with cops over coffee… https://t.co/nhzacx0JVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroJetsHockey pull the goalie and @nceccarini14 puts on on top shelf to tie the game at 2 with :20 remaining in regulation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Houston, TX? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Secret Shopper… https://t.co/7AQrgcvKwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annual 💰 Update: Maine based No Small Potatoes Investment Club made $34,800 in new loans last year and have $70,852… https://t.co/FX98Szkha7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My. God. The amount of genius in this clip is unquantifiable.  https://t.co/iO2bHV8hZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigMeanInternet As soon as I read this, I was wondering what you’d say about it…]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHISTE  ¡policía!¡Hay 2 mujeres que se están peleando por mi! ¿Y que problema hay? ¡Pues que va ganando la fea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jposhaughnessy RE: GroupThink Omaha is a long way from Wall Street  Charlie don’t surf Warren don’t tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[My main gripe against WOL and why I think SSE was better is because SSE actually felt like a story mode while WOL w… https://t.co/0W5zfXOd3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhfrith @souzaesilva I just finished presenting on 13th century petitions and SNA...at a medieval conference... I… https://t.co/sb7oaqwT1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats lose interest in server conspiracy claims linking Trump to Russia's Alfa Bank via @washtimes… https://t.co/5gEBPi4xdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @rjeanroberts I remember seeing footage of Japanese citizens suffering from radiation sickness in the… https://t.co/tjy1RrP5yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine - find your centre and take one small step. So now that you’ve made your list of the six areas you w… https://t.co/jKvH3YxBdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/XdtGZzor05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QubanOTMT You got that Russell Westbrook agression in ya bars....keep up the good work]]></document><document><![CDATA[nakEdtruth: Innocence to Experience Interview (Part 2) https://t.co/zKYyG9GOIT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[World&amp;#39;s Top Bridge Player Suspended For Doping With Synthetic Testosterone https://t.co/m9WiGhlusj via… https://t.co/IuZfr7DmMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebroalan That’s if you’re trying to get big, I’m trying to lose weight do meth is the way to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all in the video. Do your best!  Then beat your best!  And forget the rest! #homeworkout #homegym @ Grand Chut… https://t.co/pW28u4yp66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathySabine9 Terrible conditions too in Lake City...Hgy 149 closed due to avalanche near Slumgullion Pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuel and coffee and rolling westward. (@ Love's Travel Stop in Brigham City, UT) https://t.co/fgVy77rC3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealChiefRizy @brk1sb @SportsCenter You can see the exact moment his heart breaks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump announces American freed from captivity in Yemen: President Trump announced Monday that American citizen Dann… https://t.co/fFUhBmfIIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say that the world heavyweight championship looked better on @DaveBautista than it ever did on @TripleH #Raw622]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever miss someone so much that you start getting an attitude with them and you just saw them last night...]]></document></documents></author>