<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/dAAe6oq2uT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErichZimny @racehorsereport @JerseyTom Damn it forgot to switch to my burner account ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi   You go after Omar I will never contribute another dime to Democrats. She is right. You are just to… https://t.co/XaERAp1a4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we have these rooms at work called “focus rooms” where on break or whatever you’re allowed to go in there and ta… https://t.co/659uV9lbiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro You say anytime someone says it’s going to pay for itself you’re being ripped off so when Trump says th… https://t.co/woFu0t0BFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobFoxThree I used to nobly think I could never work in lawn care because the pesticides would eventually kill me… https://t.co/Xd7RREfEOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mid_madness Vermont wins 56-50 in a defensive battle in Burlington. AE champions for three years in a row! Go Cats go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESCochrane @maggieNYT I believe this is a game he plays to keep GOP in line. Take the pressure of the other then d… https://t.co/TifrUYdFyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u In high school and get up 2 sharpen ur pencil wit them fresh out the box kicks...👞👞]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I gotta ask..., vintage @oakley RazorBlades, who wore them better @yousewgirl or me? CC: @mhall_WVU https://t.co/Cf3uS5pzMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joelafferty12 @TulsiGabbard What does that day about the current president who belittles everyone with nicknames?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday! Before you turn your clocks ahead an hour, enjoy the @journalgsports worse stories on the… https://t.co/Ii1ogTAbSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Have you seen what straws can do do Sea Turtles and other creatures. Can you not drink without one. May… https://t.co/nRYj7FYGOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[they're all on hulu now. pls recognize. i'll tell you h'wut. 🤠 #kingofthehill https://t.co/g4ge5VQA2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealbignslim invade Houston for the 1st stop in the Doomsday Tour. You don't wanna miss this 😈  Tickets in my b… https://t.co/zB8VKtA7pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Thank "God" that police officer is protecting us from that big bad marijuana bad guy. Goodness gracious, h… https://t.co/G4YADfl7Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can acknowledge Donato is doing well with The Wild and say The Bruins made the right move]]></document><document><![CDATA[my poor irls... I'll be sitting here minding my own business and then a pic of pstump will show up on my feed and I… https://t.co/ysKNu9CBfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lemonnlizzz and then hit this hoe at the end of nicki’s verse https://t.co/yy2HulMMx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill5926 @YJV_24 Is this how you trying to undersell Pete so you can trade me Hoskins for tatis and Honeywell 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good piece by @MikeWickline on lawmaker mileage and expenses last year. https://t.co/3hq7yPLssT #arpx #arleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARLOSEES Qué puedes esperar de los que ponen masa de maíz dentro de masa de trigo para comer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apiecebyguy @canisterism Can we just preemptively arrest this guy now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mobil in San Nicolás de los Garza, Nuevo León https://t.co/ikSwwECMDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying from one paradise to another! Back to the Midwest and Madison, South Dakota today! Definitely saw some futur… https://t.co/Ye0VyKlViN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perla_mont Está permitido eso? No trae rodilleras ni ninguna protección @parquefundidora]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews So now you’re live-tweeting his show, too? This must be what “executive time” is all about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctseto @michael_nielsen This is one area where a small policy change could do a lot of good. Right now, using gran… https://t.co/X5lax5QYdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaBlackburn How much did you accept from the industry?  That will tell us what you are doing. SUNSHINE exposes… https://t.co/dlHcWb5kCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D1Overson @ShimonPro @ABC7Chicago How do you read what I wrote and conclude what you wrote?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, The Order might be one of the worst shows I’ve ever seen, but I can’t stop watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 will be the year I stop putting up with people who aren’t willing to put any effort into our friendship/relati… https://t.co/v3AuG9kOXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really just all ends on- so these Towson hotties seem like the Real versions of themselves.. so f and when we ,… https://t.co/trbpw4CCNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at TriMet Stop ID 2566/200 Block of SW Harrison in Portland, OR https://t.co/CKOrv5k4m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekly review: final snowshoe series standings, weekly stats, ice run &amp; product rec — yaktrax… https://t.co/kpMkZaUqUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBurkeShow hey Shannon I am in Altamonte Springs, what’s a good hole in the wall seafood restaurant around here to check out. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teriobrien @frontera_julie @marciarusso @VABVOX @ttodhunter You’re ignorant and your political reviews reflect tha… https://t.co/lR7dkE091r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Windchill -24, and peek of the sun. Guess March is charging in like a frigid Ex with a score to settle. Stay warm,… https://t.co/XSE1ps16NI]]></document><document><![CDATA['These Are Her Beliefs': Scalise Says @IlhanMN Must Be Removed From  Committee Over Anti-Semitic Comments!   She’s… https://t.co/T2rh6XWqkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skier017 @thecjpearson I never said a word about party changes. That would have been you and the person that initi… https://t.co/jXLEvQmpKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MethuselahsB @johnnyatab @thehill @HillaryClinton But I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth… https://t.co/fRKHbnaPip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesstersDead @EricKoeckeritz @BernieSanders I believe in facts too...Ever heard of Kyle Kulinski’s Secular Talk Yo… https://t.co/4LpMHeE4VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many high end chefs talk about sustainability. Would love to see more lead on cooking fuels by going electric in… https://t.co/5boikueKV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[the notification read “BREAKING: BRYCE HARPER TO PHILLIES”. all caps on the headline after the “BREAKING:” was not… https://t.co/0i5vVXFV7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just nominated @Catjiratv for 2019 @XBIZ Cam Awards presented by @MyFreeCams! #xbizmiami https://t.co/fKWKxmWg5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke laying so many bricks maybe they can build a new arena...Cameron is a dump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! You people on Instagram who vacation all the time. How you do that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step out of the shadows and #BeSeen #Legend @GhostLifestyle @danplourenco @ryanphughes https://t.co/HEmBxrw5eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goldfinger Miami Vice (2006) Spring Break (1983) Scarface  Parker Gator]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_McInally @petrolmat @pnatevp @jsteele78 @vel_cav @Alyssa_Milano Nope. I didn’t ask for an opinion on the high… https://t.co/6jcW1jSuu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_f4m @Nick_Mudry @vApathyv @t_ferrio @rileyadavis Live look at Nick tomorrow: https://t.co/WXl4cHW4Ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abihabib You are an idiot. Might want to focus on something else like... tourism in Mauritius. It’s in the same neighborhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You should really keep your projections and crazy fantasies inside your tin foil hat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_hiscock @ttupuola1 @RamsNFL Well your hot quarter back had the ball in ot. Sorry dude you lost . The rams have… https://t.co/V0VD1TFTOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell them ,,,you,, will come riding on the clouds https://t.co/dcYSdHCY5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody: Me: “I will not pick it up and break that shit down for you , whom do I look like ??” https://t.co/flAtHHvAvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL BORREGO DE DRIVO  Life in 40mm  #voigtlander40mmf12 #a7riii #gratitude https://t.co/hjglaT8FSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/JMT9FsOJcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoddBaxley And who so eloquently asked that question? I think what Roy is really saying is hey Cole Anthony come to UNC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perryfarrell Shakey Graves amazing artist listen to a song called Roll the Bones .Amazing!He has had quite a progr… https://t.co/GHIEBtv1V3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hammermor I am hoping someone caught all of it. He fully got his pancreas pulled through his asshole. #AyGevalt… https://t.co/BD2QEw7vUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janetshoemake @roosterpisces @Marizellell @CharlieD2749 @DoodlesTrks @azredhen @yrwol7 @WmScottBlair @KentSailor… https://t.co/E26Htb6CbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fair warning to those playing footsie with fascism from @madeleine Albright #uspoli #USPolitics #cdnpoli #cdnmedia… https://t.co/icI5tzhb71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayrose12 @Oscars2019Live_ @ABCNetwork Maybe it's streaming on snapface or something...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarai 🇲🇽. La última persona que aprovechó la promoción de febrero. Este mes, me fascinó que varias mujeres me busca… https://t.co/5qi5hvSPmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5 CougarHawks travel to #4 @Harwood_AD this afternoon for a d2 Girls Hky quarterfinal game at 3:30pm ...… https://t.co/kCrpDMwyC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good friends, marginal weather and a Rodfather photobomb. Happy Wednesday! @ Toscana Country Club https://t.co/sEur3XNCyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Individualism is the greatest threat to black economic persistence and wealth creation.  There is strength in numbers and togetherness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xychelsea I wish you would find me. Instagram marccolarelli You, Avenatti and a while tag team to lift this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Be careful for nothing; but in every thing by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your requests be made… https://t.co/ZU7RORubfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @BTstl! Always good to see @AKarSTL #ArcusAwards https://t.co/j2NGPnkIBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWBadgers @BadgerMBB  Coach, Coach, Coach, How can a coach allow such a negative run,  UNBELIEVABLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alauretta PS what happened to the black kid who sat next to me? Did you notice he was getting mobbed (subliminal c… https://t.co/fGdb0eZ0UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NinetiesByNature returns on Friday March 1st inside of Blnd Tiger. Book it!! https://t.co/FdDoLPuysS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please #Padres !!!!!! Try and find some extra change under the couch cushions 🙏 🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[SITUATION: A PEG-LEGGED PIGEON IS CHASING A KITTY-CAT. KEEP YOUR DISTANCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm kinda in the dark now wondering what's up with the results for @BankyW . I hope he won. Or are they still count… https://t.co/sEgoQ5gitL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mRiah Apparently you've never watched 10 episodes of 30 Rock in a row, bc a "you still there? You need us to call… https://t.co/Cwp4Cs1hut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamZagoria Why did he move all those people, mascots and camera wires and start the dunk from a completely different spot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also think it’s ridiculous that Lunardi and Palm still have St. Mary’s as one of their “first four out.” I don’t… https://t.co/7zpLhNoKgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auburnco2000 @auduncan @AlabamaFB @AuburnFootball Thanks, I miss them terribly. If you showed up for Dad’s gym sat… https://t.co/IXYedRcyh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howdy from Baum-Walker Stadium.  #ThisIsBaseball  Arkansas' 2019 season opener with Eastern Illinois coming up in about 45 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @TheNewAgenda In that case you should be paid the same as a waitress. When you actually start serving the peop… https://t.co/uRyLEzqCJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGT That's crazy!!!!! I think it should of be done a different way. Only going down to the top 2 and that's it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_NancyMD A 15 sec look into why most of us went into orthopedic trauma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come learn with @SchoolStatusApp! We're hosting Webinar Wednesday on 3/6 Sign up here:  8am:… https://t.co/cVg3QzJYj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to watch #SmackDownLive cause I heard @TrueKofi was on another level   Wasn’t disappointed https://t.co/qNeWIfBxO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alita battle angel (@ AMC Webster 12 - @amctheatres in Webster, NY) https://t.co/TAGloDAnj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[2000 is so hot right now. 🔥🔥🔥 #2000 #bordeaux #comtessedelalande #hautbrion #chevalblanc #whatyougotson @ Santa Mon… https://t.co/cMiHMSwgbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSAnchorage https://t.co/1nNLWf7Z7p  Aaron Jacobs fm Juneau wud like this loop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Will_S_7 Yeah in terms of who sells the most tickets/videos etc I’m not sure how to figure that out. I’ve never se… https://t.co/oyIjfB4iR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjilopezalt Burger place here has one dessert. They batter and fry Oreos. Awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baltimoresun @BmoreDoc A resolution for expulsion has been drafted by an unnamed legislator in the Maryland Genera… https://t.co/FrHFB14pfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_hibert @GlodeJo07 Que gusto te da que desaparezcan los partidos, a mi no sabes, por que es.el.preludio al partid… https://t.co/Zky3RvTYOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepUnderwood @SenatorDurbin @SenJeffMerkley the big LIE is that we are preventing asylum seekers from crossing the… https://t.co/mhghPDdVP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today 2 members of the @UCWV_Baseball family swore into the @USArmy as 09S’ w/ contracts to attend OCS➡️… https://t.co/6x5ikm3awc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PG_Nakkiel If I had a physical copy I would bring it over tomorrow I s2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro  thank you I graduated Reed 12/ years before you. Same program as KH.RNc Seattle @Chefjustinreed @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[End the New Jim Crow, legalize marijuana. Sign here.  Sign On: 5 Ideas for Reforming our Justice System https://t.co/qkiEAFPfT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjone1000 @thehill "Envy"? More like "righteousness". Rich people have their money not only because they worked ha… https://t.co/3f8SkfSsn9]]></document></documents></author>