<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's still Spike TV to me, dammit! Great catching up with the old crew. Proud of all these folks' progress (includi… https://t.co/pMAmDGhJbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coacht77 Sorry - I had to re-read.  My mistake. Apologize.  I don't get it.  He plays every day.  You cannot be a… https://t.co/ah14TTBc3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeanTorvi @SpeakerPelosi @OversightDems @HouseIntel Justice of what?? Hillary had a server in a closet with no pro… https://t.co/Nt9mgiwXV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metalbender00 @CNN Yeah because CNN reporters are analogous to ISIS fighters, ya idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great list of restaurant-industry-focused accounts to follow via @ToastTab cc @_rachael_perry w high5️⃣s to… https://t.co/DhiV21MVtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcm_ct Right now I would agree 100% with this. Although my recession call was out 6-12 months the incoming data su… https://t.co/pjYiOhpkKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latinas At https://t.co/SivopTLug0 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!🇷🇺… https://t.co/b9otOnLyY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[17,200 Scientists Dispute Global Warming Liberal leftist Climate change Propaganda continues from the technology gi… https://t.co/jEKt5c5lPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well here we are @WillParchman had thrown down the gauntlet - @MattDoyle76 care to respond?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these chicks out here really deserve flowers. Sorry you ain’t getting anything in advance lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshhoward1233 So very true - there's no time that you feel better than when you're being productive and feel like you're accomplishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjohnso6 @SalSpice Lack of suitable matches is way more of an issue. I've never experienced a woman who demanded I spend $$$.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max cow bell is always a must #soundboard #canyouhearmenow #morecowbell @ Whitewater Christian Church https://t.co/epLa9AvBYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of the 4/4 anthem. All about it.  Also the @sixers won the @NBA championship this year, so it must be a sign h… https://t.co/Qdmhq2R3ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google’s Hope and Dreams In India https://t.co/trg2JxaIw6 via @FortuneMagazine #india #Google #innovation #economicdevelopment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe you’re in the middle of your journey. You might feel that youve blown the early opportunities God had for you… https://t.co/iZkNcYVA7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vivian is Just Awesome! The Nicest and Funny Guy! I am still on Cloud 9 getting to meet and talk to him!  Listen to… https://t.co/zpW7SqMS2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STA_Hoops March 16th...Steve Strand Last Dance. https://t.co/zl2DioleXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Providence-St. Mel beats Cissna Park 52-29 to win the Class 1A title.   The Knights last state title was in 1985. https://t.co/yPmT8YLNqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBuenAbad Para el veneno existen antídotos , sin embargo el socialismo chavista castrista mata y asesina para esto… https://t.co/pVHheEcVo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russia puts Pentagon, Camp David in nuclear crosshairs amid U.S. missile treaty pullout via @washtimes… https://t.co/rMrjhekGej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Cmon Maggie - after the great stories of the past week or so, we are back to acting like we don’t follow… https://t.co/PgGdBsm2xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just for fun, I went to https://t.co/A5wmp2pz7H to check out the archive. My heart still pangs for those days livin… https://t.co/DHxjmwrqpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romans 8:38-39 ESV—For I am sure that neither death nor life, nor angels nor rulers, nor things… https://t.co/G9cBBFaZh4 via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning drop off where harryvarty and the @tcsbears U14 Basketball finals. @ Trinity College School (Official) https://t.co/ms6A1rMwK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrierpaq @harvardmed @HarvardChanSPH I do Crossfit every morning and typically 14 hours into a fast. If anything… https://t.co/nx5Oxr20HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be the best typographical error, in all of this year’s College Basketball Universe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrRealDad68 @HoopsNBrews Wrong. It’s was contested but still should’ve made it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wbw That time Dieli met Burroughs at Ohio HS State Wrestling Championships One 🐐 meets another 🐐 Without Bob Dieli… https://t.co/zIelnV3Zf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWifeYouLove It's a good movie but the ending sucks ... Same as message in the bottle...same writer.. wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gracielak2 @Fulanodetal1983 Entonces voten por otro en la próximas elecciones, o monten un referéndum para sacarlo de la gobernación]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uploading My New Film 🎥 To Get It Ready For Netflix 🤗 And Now About Train My A** Off To Show The World 🌎 Why I’m Th… https://t.co/WjTjvwWcUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow hits Tucson for the first time in over 40 years https://t.co/owrF0JV85L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s must-hear!  @rushtheband, top 5 band of all time!  #airdrumming the shit out of my office! https://t.co/m9R9ibeYmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all rather take the easy way out in relationships when your kids ask how you meet daddy and what y’all gone say o… https://t.co/V5E54EFEEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don’t get how jimmy didn’t get an invite to the nfl combine shit jus crazy to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiazCanelB Un auto atentado.... otra de los crímenes por los q serán juzgados. Ya queda poco #fuerzacuba… https://t.co/RPtYt6Nhc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow traffic in #DurhamCounty on I-40 EB between Page Rd - Exit 282 and Aviation Pkwy - Exit 285, delay of 3 mins #traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that’s Tukka Time! Four unreal saves in final minute of OT to give B’s on last chance for 2 pts https://t.co/iAvkLB4HXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdonaldson93 You’ve always had the uncanny ability to bring out the best in people. Hope we can get together soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it fair to say @GaryGulman &amp; @realjeffreyross that if you can make it on Twitter, you can make it anywhere? #LifeHacketts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are just a few of the images in this weeks Best of Long Island Wildlife Photography 3-1-19 -… https://t.co/8MZ7aNxOwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well #Molinari has handcuffed the #NBCGolf team. Now having to talk about how much each dropped shot is worth in $ and holing out on par 4’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Two foreign policy achievements may come out of this summit - one for Kim, the other for Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estrella de Cine o Que 🤔 #hablenmeclaro 🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔 @ El Zol 107.9 https://t.co/WKndp82YeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fivefifths Oh yes, exactly this.  "Free" speech for this crowd has and will always be, "our speech alone, with impunity."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athomas_tr @Triseum @KamalaHarris @NPSAlumni @npsfoundation @techreview @HarrisCorp @ACT @USDOL @elearningnetwk… https://t.co/aFwDtN7dTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyrefakes Him: I’m done w/ this cheating lifestyle it’s just me and girl from now on!  New Bitch: I like them li… https://t.co/yFSSiANWt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reee_ya I really didn’t think this through I’m so embarrassed haha lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to sleep at 2am woke up at 5:30, and no nap in my immediate future. I’m gonna crash hard when I get one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wellness for Warriors! @ CoxHealth Fitness Centers https://t.co/OiUlrmK6IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie My Globe online subscription will not be renewed in April FOOLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lainey_babyy 😂😂 damn pho so good ! I always feel better after eating pho...ramen not so much lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WISAPE123 @zuletista71 @ELMASGODO Yo soy de la Universidad Nacional, soy de Derecha, pero se, que hoy hay una mano… https://t.co/rZ27pbTPR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NenyVolandoalto Buenos días Neny, que tengas un excelente martes 😀🌷🌹🌺. Abrazos!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen. @ Jonathan Club https://t.co/VnWYpMVJrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigiByteJack Swimming in LTC, starting to doggie paddle on BTC, drowned losing my DGB on Cryptopia. SMH. Hope… https://t.co/oEbvGlQZvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariSWOONick Oh well then this is understandable!.... All jokes aside Anxiety is definitely a bitch. Just take it… https://t.co/JBEyL1Vvkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpieRoberts313 @raider_rob24 @benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @JustinVance9314 @njhunt02 No worries, man. He’s… https://t.co/TIqWR2iP69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shortman5427 suspect he cannot actually do that other than to beef up his Socialist credentials?  Can someone say… https://t.co/Kg7rIYdgyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chelsea Dungee (@chelsea_dungee) plays with a level of passion and emotion that is intoxicating to watch and it inf… https://t.co/tIvb6d7qP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw Captain Marvel, Thanos is so fucked lmao it’s not even funny 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pappasito's Cantina - @hiltonhotels in Houston, TX https://t.co/SrMQfAMjBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @LuvEvelynClaire @APOLONIAPORN  @XandraSixx @AshleyFires @KalinaRyu @HaleyReedX @sarahjessiexxx… https://t.co/ZIs0AoHdMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DropkickMurphys I get to see you guys next week in Austin at the Stubbs Amphitheater]]></document><document><![CDATA[Substance Abuse Awareness Week to Run March 11-15 Across Arkansas | University of Arkansas https://t.co/UtHsON41qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait... I could be wrong... but doesn’t he play on the same team as... no that can’t be right🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here on couch. Boy is in his tent watching YouTube kids. Wifey on other couch.  I tune into what boy is wat… https://t.co/GMMDpzFvPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickheer The rendering in Mojave really is abysmal though- it really does look terrible on on non-retina screens.… https://t.co/0ua34o9kih]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lil dude Alex was really in a girls phone talking about “you know that boy (me) knows not to tell me nothing”… https://t.co/GeqXWUcNCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackBergerMDPhD @AKaletMD @L__Krishnan @DocLennyF Love this! #ProudToBeGIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nsrivera18 Jajaja organica es easy relax(nadie dijo esto nunca) hajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roomway @sportingnews Kentucky got 1 seeds in years like 2012 where it didn't put in "same work" as, say, Ohio Sta… https://t.co/i8SRnHJxZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[With just one senior and nine total players, Grovetown has developed a can-do attitude as they head to states. We'l… https://t.co/WUUAJwbTAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to watch Captain Marvel by my damn self 👽 at least I get to watch in in DBox 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who do I have to arm-wrestle to get @Belcourt to hold a screening of Triple Threat? Can international independent m… https://t.co/S6YpuxMrag]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Popcorn , please @CBCPolitics @TorontoStar @sunlorrie @MercedesGlobal @DonMartinCTV @globepolitics… https://t.co/njJCxG8He0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrible last 8 mins for the terps. What defense was that at the end?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[***JUST ANNOUNCED*** @watchtowerkw acoustic night 2.4 ft @joshwarrenn @nickvokey31 #talkboy @kleistmatthew and… https://t.co/Xsq0ApUum3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noregretsejf71 Ok, I’ll just have a coffee ☕️ for ya, hopefully that osmosis thing will work lol, hopefully your b… https://t.co/ToeMsyiySV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This St. Patrick’s Day, I’m giving back by supporting @GuinnessUS and #StacheForCharity. Are you in? Learn more her… https://t.co/UlepKmi9dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My platform that chocolate should be cool and refreshing aligns with the York Peppermint Party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaferWeigel @fox32news A whole lot of folks on the Left are gonna have answering to do.  And most will fight to th… https://t.co/L6Y7LZInk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to #jakegyllenhaal  #tomsturridge @publictheaterny tonight... @ The Public Theater https://t.co/TKNH7MsjHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sixers owner on looming Butler, Harris free agency: &amp;#8220;We&amp;#8217;re going to try to keep them&amp;#8221; https://t.co/QTVwB9IPHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[the perfect woman does not exist just look at Miley @mileycyrus #mileycryus #VanityFair #Oscars en The Hamptons https://t.co/gOGPbm6bJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amanda has a phone interview with another physical therapy group today, she really needs a change. Prayers are welc… https://t.co/2LR6UcmSWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avalanche why on God’s green earth are you playing Detroit Rock City in the Pepsi Center??? #neveragain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveLemme hey chicken F@#$r cant wait for tv show....you and farva... lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Kane extends his point streak to 17 games with his 35th goal of the season. #Blackhawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @marshmellomusic - check out my boy - big fan - decided he wanted to look like you and made his own mask. https://t.co/sBH6MGOB4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to know that the team has not lost the cohesiveness they had before all the trades.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAMerritt @AnnCoulter Ur parents obviously beat me to the punch they’ve already bred you. I believe in an el… https://t.co/1CbKLX9Xkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[People pray and get mad when God answers and it’s not the sign or answer they were looking for]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you bust a nut and then she lets you be the little spoon&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cardinals Arenado is off the table. SIGN BRYCE HARPER. Give him the Stanton contract. Front load him for the prime… https://t.co/jE5eDAgOaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21EChard Imagine Dragons are literally a modern day version of Nickelback]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stress testing the power supply and motor drivers. @ University of Louisiana Lafayette C L Rougeou Hall https://t.co/kOU3lk2MLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHarvell Hadn't thought of that in a while. Curious name for a product.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you come in the ring against @wow_thebeast, you will not make it out of here alive cause she will viciously de… https://t.co/GtfNLLq7XU]]></document></documents></author>