<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows You had 2 years to do oversight of the executive branch. You relinquished. So sit the hell down and… https://t.co/HnS1jOrNOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthaig1 Is that original tweet a fucking joke??   And you are right - be a man, don’t tweet dumb crap like telli… https://t.co/qdsG6Boj28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an adult is depressing but at least you get to meet cute men at times so like it’s cool 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pot roast  kinda day . @metrodiner  Half order strawberry butter waffle.   #mistydayokcfoodblogs @ Metro Diner https://t.co/YhfmnFTv7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four women who left water and food for migrants in Arizona sentenced to 15 months probation &amp; $250 fine.   https://t.co/CqHjSKduwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannity blasts House investigation into Trump as 'gruesome display of modern-day McCarthyism'  https://t.co/vv6PxYUyGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonLeto @blackfuel What a wonderful birthday present to receive.. All your hard work is paying off, wish I cou… https://t.co/1wCmbctNYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[gente um cara q eu conheci a mt tempo atrás percebeu minha cara de morta e disse “don’t study so hard”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling much better, but should probably go to bed. Having to interact with someone who hurt me and refuses to apol… https://t.co/OzHbAXWX6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live in El Dorado and this is definitely a lie 😅 it was 54 degrees yesterday 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of permanent daylight savings time, why not just reverse it so I can see the sun after work in winter, but… https://t.co/MT9zpdJV8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve said this before but i’ll say it again. if i see any UNNECESSARY hate towards anyone i won’t even hesitate unf… https://t.co/bCvxoI6bkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[working at ups when sick feels like you’re getting hit by the trucks you are loading, while loading them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @Skepmi He's really off the rails of sanity.  He knows that the democrats are going after every little… https://t.co/u56ewLABgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swatcbs Was in the hospital but i still did not miss it. Feeling better now and seeing my favorite crew always alw… https://t.co/3cGbFGVuiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[School cafeteria menu items: raw fish, depression, anxiety, heart attacks, diabetes, lunch ladies, diarrhea, all th… https://t.co/zE1C7hZ9dZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annkillion Melissa, doing comedy AND pulling off serious? She is an amazing talent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Whaddya mean "Let's" leave the man alone??!! Nobody else but YOU threatened him in a pu… https://t.co/jtrd4Vof3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really political. I’m not a Trump fan either but i have a little warm spot for him calling Tim Cook Tim Apple. I like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Picard_Resists @retail_recruit @fordnation @MacLeodLisa Absolurely should resign immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He never misses a chance to insult McCain or the memory of McCain. What an ignorant AH of a human being.  I more an… https://t.co/xCDFkfyRzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the shout out from @ToddGloria during @JuniorLeagueSD ‘s 90th Anniversary celebration https://t.co/IZyN8hBv6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for a friend, then seeing a movie. (@ Cinemark Buckland Hills 18 + IMAX in Manchester, CT) https://t.co/NAyAVb42km]]></document><document><![CDATA[over and tell him I need to know what happened and who did it. Well, he wasnt talking; just side stepping. But he s… https://t.co/7KbVk6AxJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t to get married so my husband can handle all things car related, there’s nothing I despise more than trying… https://t.co/TvVThFRqQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Legalized robbery.  Hard working tax payers should SUE the cheap Democrat exploiters for blowing our… https://t.co/mFFZ8A7iEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell do turkeys do if theyre not gETTING EATEN?!  -Chad Hankinson, government instructor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cstrohm @SuMoh7 Of course not. He'll do the job for which he was installed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paigewolf @michellemalkin @SenJohnMcCain John McCain was CLEARLY A TRANSPUBLICAN RHINO! https://t.co/BMA9Bw2bCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BucketIzzy @rickjones2323 @teles_gislene @AppetiteForGNfR @adritessis @GUNSNROSESDAiLY @jenedler @hanne1611… https://t.co/G7mxRfvjVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice fog this morning. Every few minutes it falls in brief, thick swirls of snow.  May need to walk at the park late… https://t.co/DqufiYS1Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave with extra time to get to your destination this morning! Mist and fog may slow you down out on the road… https://t.co/7rTkjLYYhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re dehydrated and tired.   *At Starbucks*     “One iced white chocolate mocha with two extra shots of expr… https://t.co/eouTJ6RkiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot fathom the emotion you felt at those outrageous live concerts. I would give my, well, whole body to feel t… https://t.co/DpETwxhhCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @AlconaTigers @AHSStudentSect9 for the birthday song! I’d give y’all a perfect 10! #DistrictFinal… https://t.co/Dbr93hteB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most comprehensive “Medicare for all” bill is out. Here’s what's in it and who supports it https://t.co/vVz67VOE2O # via @HuffPostPol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the best moment...one of my little Knights is spreading kindness and delivered a rose to me at my house!… https://t.co/KOnI69kQvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am loving the “7 secrets of storytelling success with data” with @jdschramm #QualtricsX4 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SrtaWalpole They’re doing a Pecha Kucha about la familia - real or made up. They can describe people/likes/dislike… https://t.co/TrJ7IjmOFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You really are that fucking stupid, narcissistic, and delusional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One #contentmarketing planning tool you MUST HAVE in 2019 is a content calendar!   Download THE  ULTIMATE 2019 Cont… https://t.co/GPaisLZbkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff The sun came up today - NO COLLUSION!!!  This wasn't even about Trump or the campaign's "collusion".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of unanswered questions about Omidyar funding for The Bulwark. Its editor, Charles Sykes, is an advisor for… https://t.co/hQuE7gwNTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the love @RestaurantsCA I’m having so much fun! Your best show yet! Day 3 here we go! Get your tickets n… https://t.co/EpxoBpUx1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimAlle97055825 That is awesome Tim! A-List while working full time and having a family. Be proud because you worked hard to get there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saviynt 's architect, Diana Volere--an up and coming industry expert in #cybersecurity #identitymanagement has som… https://t.co/hVtgJu0avk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two would be dates have turned me down because they’ve already seen it! I’m late to the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get between a girl and her couture 👀....When we launched several years ago we started with one city and only… https://t.co/8H6dCvuR6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have to go out with my boyfriends family an im still drunk still? rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be here for senior night @GW_Gymnastics 💙 https://t.co/hUvFrwABfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting outside 8 hours a day for a week . I earned $957 and this is what I did most of the time ☹️🥺❤️ https://t.co/QWZ4OC4lGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only I would get up early on one of my days off to go to rope drop in Magic Kingdom 😂💙 https://t.co/zlP3Bgdnz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnGrahamDick1 Millions more muslims are brought in and settled in key cities all over the U.S.  They are allowed… https://t.co/LJGMIVW7Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcfiddler Congratulations to a very nice family..what an addition to add to your greatness..enjoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 @Katascadero "Oh honey, I took care of the weeds in the backyard flower beds for you!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @BEERGUY201 @The_Fool_Monty @Nick23929445 @MelissaFincher @gr82btnvol @Shawn172510 @jamesonandbeers… https://t.co/P3JCYCpiLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KatiePavlich NO ONE is coming back! You screwed them with your tax break for the wealthy, you lie… https://t.co/Upq8x3piXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending love and support to all in my extended world. Please reach out and check on those in your community. Love t… https://t.co/3NoiC5CUke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Talk about a dick face.. nice 70’s porno stash dude!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends • Please investigate this; regarding climate change, who are the scientists that make these claims?… https://t.co/rnU4zQtAzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a problem with individuals in my life who tell me that I need to empathize with their bull****. But they can… https://t.co/HDJoCGyYXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiahthomas So happy for you. A Celtic fan but an Isaiah fan too. Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me chuckle. When I get a headache I take two aspirin and keep away from children, just like... #humor #giggle… https://t.co/ZHNrJxELym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo mío es muy lindo 😍 Bendice Señor mi tierrita, mi barrio, mi gente, mi cuna 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humor Heals - So Laugh Often - FB!  #LisaDCTComedy #MinuteToSpitIt https://t.co/0gOqFhM0cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Capreezie OMFG 😂😂😂 i saw a video you made too the other day lmaoooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanQuinonez @luisarmo @JRegid @Samanthaiag @molina14karen @DanielaGomezF27 @CamilaVelardeG Ya vuelve q lloro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AD_TheWriter @charliekirk11 @speedprayers So glad that you're family! ❤🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is normal in life to be challenged. It is unbiblical to be defeated.” @JDShuttlesworth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NORML @Surgeon_General Poverty more severely impacts brain development and impedes future success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWant_NJH That’s true but there are still people in Hollywood that deserve the same punishment that nobody brings up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Iowa City, IA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/A8WIyQWKoD #Corridor #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 🤣🤣 My sister said this is not that uncommon and that Hillary did it too. I never knew that before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliepastor7 @DavidCa29908830 @boudet_stephane @AAvallones @Rimiquen_DSM @CoquetteEric @chasseurdimage1… https://t.co/PBtRi8Aiat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Eric and Mohammed on 1st Place bridge TSA regionals.  @briscoe_eagles @joeypineda99]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to celebrate black truffle season than with one of my fav lunches...The Black Truffle Pizza at Dune… https://t.co/BM9F4KryNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That special bond between ski instructor and students. ⛷💞❄️  Thank you Hayleigh!!!  @skisteamboat #skilessons… https://t.co/hgm0rrkqGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you tell us how the foundation/concealer wore throughout the day??? I tend to be on the oily side so they start… https://t.co/5XxWl4s4iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business After Hours with the caldwellchamber and @pioneertitleco #goingbeyond #pioneertitle #caldwellidaho @ Pione… https://t.co/kAhjSQUBdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikaLSanchez “What else was in the woods? A heart, closing. Nevertheless.“  Actually, like a good 35% of… https://t.co/w7V6cjbRjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[South African Schools Are a ‘Death Trap’ — so the Government’s Vowed to Take Action https://t.co/FDgZbBmhc5 #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERuns @wyshynski I’m legitimately begging you, this was a joke from my friend and she egged me on to do it and I’m… https://t.co/IKi0xq5wUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone! We will have live coverage on air and online of @realDonaldTrump's second round of talks wit… https://t.co/8lq3qn4Z3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just spent literally 40 minutes on the phone just to be told "we cant do anything whatsoever for you and you're b… https://t.co/CMids287yT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickcarter Thanks 4 sharing @nickcarter!! I'm even more excited than b4 4 the #BSBDNA tour!! Cant wait!! See u in Toronto in July!! 😘🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s something wrong with your character if opportunity controls your loyalty]]></document><document><![CDATA[My giveaway with @croghansjb ends TOMORROW so head back to three posts ago and enter! Swipe to see the my favorite… https://t.co/kXKZPdKQA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @mcbridesworld for giving me the blues this morning.☺️@oberyhendricks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please God I really hope I finish this essay that is due tonight at 11:59pm that I’m working on at the last minute🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s beauty in the struggle. Ugliness in the success. Hear my words or listen  my signal of distress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensaste que nunca ibas a ser de lo que no pueden cenar pesado a cierta edad? Pues a mi ya se me llegó esa hora a l… https://t.co/d6Ti4whXgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonaayy Look yo momma trying her best not yo cuss you out in Spanish and English.....just show up for dinner!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY is there no delayed work opening?? I want to lie in bed longer and watch the snow fall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8 of introducing the new #lonestar #books for 2019-2020: #nevermoor book 1: the trials of Morrigan Crow by… https://t.co/pVl5y2WhkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m obviously catching up on #keepingup right now 🤣🤣🤣 every time my bf says something to me that’s what i’ve been saying back lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yeah_Nah_Cunt @Geemme @LibyaLiberty I always liked this song as a child. https://t.co/sCtM2UYWhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosivz @Diego_Luciano_ No entiende como llegó @Diego_Luciano_ a esa conclusión 🤷‍♀️a mi me pareció que en el capít… https://t.co/Y1fSv1eKO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro Hijo de míl putas lacra humana. Te vas a morir de Cáncer en el culo igual que el otro]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a great choice: 10 years I suffered from losing my son. Then Stephen Sondheim told Betty Buckley to sing:… https://t.co/sbCyO4NMkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fluffyguy Next time you're in the San Jose area, you need to go here: https://t.co/Pv4O17P2pC]]></document></documents></author>