<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The @NHLBruins nearly score as Fleury loses track of it in his crease.   #VegasBorn #NHLBruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Yes, Trump is and always has been, and will remain, pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was trying to think of a funny Valentines Day tweet, I couldn’t come up with anything cause no one actually gives a shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I think of presidential harassment, I think of the birther movement against Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I had the opportunity to work on these edits 😬👍 congrats to all of the honorees #D3Hoops #SRSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel That's just Klansman Carlson speaking his mind about what he loves to hate. Anybody not white]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow @K1erry I thought heels 👠 up Harris also used that terminology?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t feel like being home bored this weekend, haven’t gone out in like a month 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleInCAL @JussieSmollett @Chicago_Police Why did take so many to solve  this besides he hasn’t even gone to trial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ What does this air head think abortion does, pop a pimple?? It's unconscionable for her to even imagine… https://t.co/mccsGrAOtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews @ThisIsAmerica @FacebookWatch @ROMACuaron @aliciagarza @domesticworkers X HAY LES ENCARGO Q PASEN L… https://t.co/D4yP6twfwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVietor08 @SenFeinstein treated these people as if they were an interruption of her 'real' work.  Senator, they ARE your real work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Shall not be infringed means Fuck Off to “sensible regulation”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posting that Instagram video of Coach Tomlin’s locker room speech was the beginning of the end of AB’s career in Pi… https://t.co/xqmYOKLtlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NdeQuadros Hard to believe everyone seems to be cool with just leaving it there... what’s the drawback of removing… https://t.co/radIM9LMjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[bring the laughter. Funny Pictures Of The Day - 95 Pics https://t.co/LAYvesxmek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeKST They also made a Once In A Lifetime DVD...we will see the Shield again]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever want to meet the funniest man alive, HMU because it’s my boyfriend https://t.co/aGJdD7U1CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarolinaMMA Nice!! But are your eyes opened or closed when throwing your punches?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbarastarrcnn Actually although you are correct it is also a Hercules (base). And all that it is lighting up in… https://t.co/1yPAnfuagI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So who remembers? After a string of adverse legal decisions, Napster, Inc. began its death spiral on March 6, 2001,… https://t.co/xDmie8up9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kuhb00m @jamusp @SpunkyTrucker @DocThompsonShow My goodness people. Doc was my friend. I’ve known him longer than… https://t.co/2eGoFPJNJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iancmclaren Playing next to Bergeron they'll finally see he deserves the Selke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me llevas delante del trono, muestra tu belleza quiero ver tu rostro ❤️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekaceykasem Dorial Green Beckham for fantasy purposes. David Wilson for real life maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lot of fun playing @BaseballAGHS @CoachCBSkinner @Will_James_21 last. Always class act. You guys have a great bunch… https://t.co/s6R0nvJMyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legendarylaq So you’re right the moment social media keeps trying to get people to depend on it in order to be see… https://t.co/ke4XWjiEoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeast donuts with caramel icing 🍩 yummy. #redsdonuts  #redsdonutshop @ Reds Donut Shop https://t.co/8MesZPsepT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBenHueso Have you seen this? I get the spirit of your bill but it may have unintended consequences:… https://t.co/BKdfdMsrI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best article I’ve found so far on: Heart Rate Variability vs. Heart Rate https://t.co/BnCsv45rDA via @jasonmooreme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bartbarber I have officiated two memorial services this year that fit your observations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂 this is pathetic,so Tanimu Turaki is your lead lawyer,how many landmark cases has he won in his entire caree… https://t.co/EFO8j3ewpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaboyblue357 No amount of encouragement from any of us will change who you are. We love you how you are. Having sa… https://t.co/Er5G7xweJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LShay That’s a shame. But I don’t think us cis males are the best at self awareness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KREM2 Oh yeah this’ll work as well as people staying out of the left lane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have they heard the audio tape of Warren Jeffs RAPING A 12 YEAR OLD? Do they know he got a 15 year old pregnant? An… https://t.co/TAoDYgQWJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a little time to make a big difference. Won't you?#redcrossblooddrive @ LaGrange, Georgia https://t.co/4AGbJ9lD7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother, Thelma Marie Thompson, read me a story when I was very young.   First published in 1943 called “Chicken… https://t.co/qOPlqmPHqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agonists and Antagonists muscles by @Chrisfittt -- Agonist and antagonist muscles are the primary and secondary or… https://t.co/RlMwUsujaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I think it’s the right move too. I admire her but after...all that...I really don’t think she should run again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wisdom #truth #eleanorroosevelt #girlpower #women #dreams   FIRST LADY WISDOM! 🙌 @ Century City, Los Angeles https://t.co/WYKb93SK49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawtt_Dawgg I knew it was going to happen though. He hasn’t been exposed to anybody fr up until this point 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar should definitely be removed from office!!!  All Muslims should be removed from office since their goal is to… https://t.co/EKgVI3fNaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to the family of the @NYPD102Pct Detective who was killed in the line of duty tonight in Richmond… https://t.co/d21Tyjdc8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tillerextension #jonboat #jonboats #skinnywater #mercury #mercurytillerext #mercuryoutboards #siliconegrip… https://t.co/wiKKQF3zqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@augieray Her Trump/MAGA clutch collection's gonna go all Imelda Marcos soon ... https://t.co/Qo5dpk1lh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl i work with comes in SCREAMING every damn morning and i can’t take it. pls shut the fuck up its too early for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamsamkeller if I already have a laminated thing can you laminate it further? I want it to be impenetrable and I d… https://t.co/U1dxsoicGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JesseBWatters Several so called "FACT CHECKERS" are actually giving THEIR OPINIONS as FACTS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s that Salvadorean Brazilian left back that Real Madrid had my boy Abner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hospitality is a real job.  I guarantee they work harder than anyone in Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell Obamacare doesn’t allow it, but you wouldn’t know it because you got to keep your doctor...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_nor @nationwide88 @AlexBowman88 Stay looking Good there in 3rd but need to see the power and make a move befo… https://t.co/I5G1SahQnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Please stop giving time to @aoc who sounds like an idiot while wearing expensive clothes put togethe… https://t.co/KveS8eMJ5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te estamos buscando !!! #saltillo canal6saltillo en Eii NRT Saltillo https://t.co/ysXONFxd3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[And....yeah. #justthereforthebeers  #andthehipsterettes #edgyoldguy #coachella2019 @ Tustin, California https://t.co/Isuqa06Obe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinHatch @zimmergren @StfBauer @bniaulin If I don’t see a date (and sometimes I have to scroll to the bottom to… https://t.co/Zy1K9qRWcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zimlive The 1st Lady wasted resources flying to Binga just to officiate a fish pond.... @nickmangwana @InfoMinZW t… https://t.co/ruxGl4nirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vietnam's Danang poaches tourists from Phuket and Bali https://t.co/9Ebe8UnYYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ_TacoJack @Jilchrest @emiliemunson That is the goal of the fascist democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wrong on so many levels. #legendofzelda #mariooddesy @ Catoosa, Oklahoma https://t.co/36FZOvjZrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read the NEW #PRSResidentChronicles blog, "Inside Scoop: Hand and Microsurgery Fellowship in Ganga Hospital," by… https://t.co/ftXbI5zWtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@al_rasheed @vcixnv @KCDAutomate @aaronbuley @importcarguy @vgigacast @gsxesx @arielsanchezmor @MattThatITGuy… https://t.co/Np990eLbY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weightman_gary3 @TheSteveKon @TonyEBoggs1 @MichaelLeeFree3 @Lucy61241811 @JUSTICE_MK_1 @RMFT_Roy @o_plaisance… https://t.co/mZH0RQ9PIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to start embarrassing you thots but y’all better look somewhat like your pics or I’m just gunna say yo… https://t.co/S4E1vkg3dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or, more disturbing and more often the rule, they don't even engage in conversation about the problem. If I don't h… https://t.co/XmStELcj77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frances_Coppola @JackMallers You can learn everything you need to know about Bitcoin and make meaningful and signi… https://t.co/6KgGYGG6JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Our great President DJT waved his MAGIC WAND &amp; turned the Economy around from bho’s disaster!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLS @TaylorTwellman “Chili’s, Outback, Carraba’s?” Taylor wants to know:  “What are we doing???!!!!!” https://t.co/jueUCuGK7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeGrove55 regarding Galaxy’s Edge costumes I definitely agree with you, also I’m losing my mind with how great… https://t.co/c24jRpFUcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@love_laiah ❤️❤️❤️❤️finally!!! you deserve everything coming your way and more!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntifragility @RichardDawkins They are all fictions, just the same. It's how damaging they are that warrants debate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE good luck Becky Lynch at wrestlemania &amp; at fast lane love you girl!! ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shark615 @mitchellvii @gatewaypundit @CrazyAOC Alot because I haven't seen any electric tractors , combines, semis… https://t.co/7c5tZwtNWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazAltitude I mean, if you are going that far you might as well go all the way with the striped tube socks to acc… https://t.co/Be5wkYCgde]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI, Michael Houser became the Cyclones' all-time winningest goalie this week with 64.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't believe it's been a year since this awful day! Thankful for the promise of heaven! https://t.co/EknE1bgdll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillcrest with 5 straight to open the 4th qtr. Normal U High leads 51-45 with 5:12 to go. #tribhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yes, Christopher Nolan’s Batman Trilogy is my favorite movie of all time.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espresso martinis w/ @_reviewmypaper  at the @Starbucks HQ to start vacation off right. https://t.co/BM8ecuQ8Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @jvonelling @sportingkc #sportingsmiles #sportingkc @ Sporting KC-Soccer Stadium https://t.co/u0P5f1X90l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start investing with @Stash today! Get $5 to invest when you use my link: https://t.co/MM304SrZAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second air rifle relay in 10 minutes.  WVU Shooters Milica Babic and Ginny Thrasher are gearing up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power's out. ⚡🚫🤬 I heard a generator blow just before 5am. @EversourceMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthoApologist @BOStoPDX @nhannahjones I don’t think it’s common knowledge that rich kids of any color go to poor… https://t.co/Vhw3WYVtPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiwireportfeed I wouldn’t click on this link if my life depended on it.  . . . I wouldn’t click on any promoted tw… https://t.co/eo5Wm8IIS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if you don't like the baby you give birth to, you can have it killed or cut up for parts and try again? Sorry. I… https://t.co/u0dOpcN13Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about you but Blake Griffin has shown to be the best leader Detroit could ask for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth is, we interpret things every day. Every time we read something we interpret what we are reading. We don’… https://t.co/fo63gushgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @zappcomics with get_repost ・・・ @zappconnj badges are available at both @zappcomics and zappmanalapan locat… https://t.co/sBXuPahnNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joekeegs Rarely confident going into the dome, but feeling optimistic. Jays showed lots of progress in their win a… https://t.co/meFEyk9rBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest In Peace @sambassartist   He was a positive influence on @NASCAR as an artist. A friend to everyone he met. Th… https://t.co/VkgkzAYD6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Washington Monument on Eakins oval • #monument #statue #bronze #eakinsoval #Phila🥨 #Philly #GeorgeWashington… https://t.co/3rJm68M0rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of bourbon and lots of bacon. Sunday is recovery day after an awesome night. The axe throwing was a nice addit… https://t.co/P8DmJYlwtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slooterman I also have had a hard time tracing any original study... only less and less reputable news articles an… https://t.co/xXLheMWNQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When you are grateful, fear disappears and abundance appears.” — #quotes #dailyquotes #followmyquotes… https://t.co/jblpxfaOqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan Sounding a bit soft over this. Maybe you should join too. Be the first bitch to join the Girl Scouts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 10, 2000- The NASDAQ Composite stock market index peaked at 5132.52, which marked the beginning of a downward… https://t.co/E7m9wvq3w3]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you smirk, you'll do more. Clary and Jace Quote "When most girls say they want a big rock..." Follow link to... https://t.co/A3S2rJhMSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt @Dewald_SRO @WVandertie Maybe he needs to think about the meaning of “it’s a great day to be alive” an… https://t.co/6yuKfcjtzl]]></document></documents></author>