<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Live near Chicago? Wanna go to C2E2? For freeeee??!? Learn how here:  https://t.co/5HDLSASwFh   #C2E2 #C2E22019 https://t.co/c6NEZckxVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Californiagirl solved this #wheeloffortune round! 😜✌️😜 #beachboys #californiagirls #songlyrics 💁‍♀️ @ Chino H… https://t.co/xaGfMOxKci]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly tho my mind doesn’t shut off when i sleep it goes for a fucking marathon and then gets in a race car and speeds to its heart intent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi hermana me acusó con mi mamá por pedir tacos a las 11:00pm like si se pasó de lanza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a few more days! I am so close to my $5000 goal, but I believe I can raise so much more! Lets #BuzzOffCancer t… https://t.co/xluWjV6ZPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexthetrapgod LMAOOOO me bouncing around know deep down instead I’m about to find a reason to shed some tears https://t.co/z2skLrnY1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrewerNation Got it, the Brewers twitter just confused me when the said 2:05 CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a last minute opening on Friday morning and a spot for a cut on Saturday left! Use the link in my bio and co… https://t.co/ixXK1RuoeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseball_hits From playing softball as a teen to now my son playing baseball. We have always used neatsfoot oil. E… https://t.co/67Xtzx07mU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freddyrace14 @MAGANuggets @__CassidyRae__ @establishmentno @Finn_American @DogsBCool @NikkythaBee @bromsisa… https://t.co/ypBPVnvvgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julie_Hancock32 @missouttamyway Agreed. I loved A Star Is Born so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each one of us can play an important role in the struggle of bull sh*t!  @JohnVPetro | #TEDxUNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Joe Buck announce the World Series over Matt Vasgersian, please fix this]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0Jnx60dIjx 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum… https://t.co/Cf1CIK2C2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you following me on Instagram? Check out my new story posts and vote for an outfit for my photo shoot this week… https://t.co/CQJsnNPC2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stella’s really busting it down 💀@lizzygea1 @johne_taylor https://t.co/Kc3KYb0XUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[These socialists must be stopped this is the same as Obamacare was or worse!! Healthcare should be our decision who… https://t.co/fHUhkB0mUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallyCummins @ngabler4 @RossBjorkAD @sixpackspeak @stoolpresidente https://t.co/yCSx1Y1REB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of the mission of @cruatunc is to help students explore some of life’s hardest questions. Join us Thursday nig… https://t.co/ptKOEPmNwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will never let go of my heart. I just need to learn from my mistakes and never do them again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Things You Should Delete From Your iPad RIGHT NOW, According To Tech Experts  https://t.co/vPOwg0NDyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBylenkov @Margosha_S_I @belyi_seryi @poroshenko @MunSecConf Вам бы самим не помешало. Но это же ниже вашего (мн.… https://t.co/O8unM2z3Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jengerson Partisans don’t think - they follow blindly. The rest of us are sure as hell doing some listening and thinking though]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what @KamalaHarris envisions for the country. Free college, free drugs, free rent or just camp out and slee… https://t.co/tK6PpBPxSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoTurnUnstonedd 💯☑️🍆💦.... it’s sad and utterly ridiculous!!! Dana has no shame these days. Very disappointing... highly frustrating 😩😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Skeels The Bruins have been very high on Donato for a while, he was probably their #1 NHL ready prospect. I'… https://t.co/Er5yp3hK72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Copped those @IPrevailBand tickets 🤘🏻 May 13th can’t come quick enough!!! So excited!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarateach77 @MegMoore821 @LuxSCounselor  @4theLVofkicks  @Jennife48859562]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jestevesT2 @TelenoticiasPR BRAVO ESTEVES!!!!  Mantenganos al tanto.  Los tenemos en oracion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made #LBJ cry for the first time today. I wouldn’t let him go into another hotel room he thought he was in troubl… https://t.co/NJEIhawSUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free #webinar on #RiskManagement &amp; Continuous Monitoring - https://t.co/ItNAyUZjs6 #govcon #cyber @threewiresys @FedInsider #risk]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@thegrandtour: China's Drive Through Door Factory https://t.co/zmqoe0VHDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to remove my mother from being able to view my tweets because she thinks everything I tweet about is my ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NIISH13 @Arthur_Lindsay @DavidTaormia @OWingsgirl @OccultPriestess @aderb66 Ô NIISH • ~ ~ •]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatsyResists @NBCNews I guess you just ignore this law. The same way the Obama and Trump administrations ignored t… https://t.co/m4betxlIFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya lil hoes be ugly when you think your better than other people...cuz your followers hittin 1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 Please send some warm temps up here in Andover Township, NJ  - everything here has a good coat of ice o… https://t.co/VyNklZQWhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Combined with the real Super WoMAN RebeccaHHeels to fight the Heroin Murder wars...Liberty Ranger..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @MalcolmNance does he not understand Kim IS the regime. Someone needs to explain "dictator" to him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been in desperate need of a haircut and hopefully on Thursday these dead af end will be gone 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya no espero nada de nadie y creo que es mejor,por que a veces las personas que menos esperas son las que mas te sorprenden]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously wish I could sleep thru this entire day! It’s only 3:52 AM and I’m already depressed about Valentines Day 😫!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got new pictures of my head! Everybody hire me!  . . . . . #actorslife #headshots #headshotphotography… https://t.co/D9DEVplDJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bergenstables @Kerrycouch4 @theolballcoach1 I’m sure He will do Well!🏇🏇🏇He is Indeed a Beautiful Boy!🏇😊🏇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Punto malo mi primer Sebastián ya no lo veo, solamente a travez de instagram 🤷🏻‍♀️, azares del destino]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sit next to a guy that was in the marines... he crazy af. I swear the military fuck u up. Hes NUTS, and its so entertaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr you have been a total disappointment because you failed to act as an independent branch of government… https://t.co/04JOdN1D26]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-fold learning 2D attributes and teamwork @quizlet  #TxEdTuesday @HewittElem https://t.co/iqdnQF0nAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristaldarlinn duo for drugstore and house of lashes lash glue if you can splurge]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s officially panic bc bikini season is right around the corner season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time @Topgolf I'm Mt. Laurel NJ with @Davefunksprint https://t.co/RzbwFlGpl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Havana ooh na na!! Thanks @DMTM_INC for letting us bring out our spicy side at the Havana Fashion Show! Que noche… https://t.co/PcLMgpUT4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Chase through several metro Atlanta counties ends in crash in DeKalb County: https://t.co/dLT4N3jd9W --… https://t.co/gJfknd4buu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__vaalll rt y’all ain’t demanding and y’all just keep it chill and not judge me for being a weirdo 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the 80s were full of bad music ideas but what the hell were the Styx thinking when they let Dennis DeYoung take over?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road Closed due to a Crash and Road Hazards - on I-15 in both directions between SR-146/St Rose Pkwy and Jean in La… https://t.co/1xJnzpw2SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGinLBC @pattonoswalt Patty Smyth: 🎶Shooting at the walls of Heartache... Robin Williams / Dead Poets Society: car… https://t.co/PhZnTfHB7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My talk got accepted to #pycon2019. Super excited to be talking about  @Python_Pandas this year! Hope to see you al… https://t.co/irASJidZQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha je prendd les mêmes résolutions et j’arrive toujours au même résultat que le votre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago yesterday I was laying in the middle of the woods with my leg literally broken off. Remember that thi… https://t.co/nGttaPAECa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnamacbabe @dutchingmarkets @barney1481 @frankokane @markogorman06 @ShoneMUFC @Boripa211 @AshAsran… https://t.co/Uy7sw26qeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton is dumb dumb... he falls for the crocodile tears every time  #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @realjoeyfatone This was great so much fun to watch I laughed so hard #blockhead for the win #BoysintheBand 💓❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nosso coletivo de mulheres brasileiras pela democracia está no Instagram: https://t.co/tbshmPLidN https://t.co/WkmReF3t1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends mom took a pic of me meeting Joe Jonas in 2008 and never gave it to me after I asked 100 times so I just… https://t.co/00Vv3no370]]></document><document><![CDATA[COMING UP: Meet the first winners of the 2019 @ChickfilA Everyday Heroes award. Scott and Josiah started a group ca… https://t.co/hL46Bvq5YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finale Day of African History Month! My 1st Period Piano Class stepped up BIG TIME! ( they didn’t know they were Pe… https://t.co/tpmAzNGpwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARSantos1946 Good morning Amelia. Have a great day.😘❤️🤗 DST begins at 2:00 A.M. tomorrow. Thanks for reminder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great day @centergrovetech with the Computer Science Curriculum Showcase! Lots of reflective information/curricul… https://t.co/YgBSL0Oknt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire dept: Bibles, crosses not burned after church fire in West Virginia - ROCHESTERFIRST https://t.co/Hof7bAWAbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[two years ago i was so unhappy with myself and the life i was living. crazy how things have changed. i'm now living… https://t.co/bOuFGttYt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylavalllie Half way through my pregnancy w B my times switched up, I’d stay up all night and sleep all day 😩 and… https://t.co/1K6IJYrbb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/TMzDnmaGpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sugarmama3000 @khloekardashian You Got That So Right, No They Just No Their COCKS R Bigger N Wider That's All]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, are we all in agreement that #MahershalaAli should win the #Emmy for @TrueDetective Season 3? Outstanding Lead… https://t.co/pv1Jr3TKcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker doing some training out in the real world, he is here for one of our residency programs. #stayandobey… https://t.co/qvmzrIoDCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad not captured or considered on teacher evaluations since we as teachers are to teach to students.  These qua… https://t.co/JlMzEFmCwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you César Cueva Urruchi @oteushu for retweeting my poem! Happy day!💙💜 https://t.co/uZrztFoahs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fahimanwar @BrodyismeFriend This is so fucking sad. I just saw him recently. Heart breaking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of it is but I haven’t been to the barn in two weeks now because of rain. Our team training has been canceled… https://t.co/sVdXfIoMln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfalfaTheRoach @pyg_ma_lion @Queenoflunatics @bucketofROBOTS @rgbhex @mewTripled @tuyoki @charmwitch… https://t.co/RtKminn2EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be honest... Why would you ever want a gun that close your lady bits? Vaginas over guns 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Разумеется, история этой земли гораздо древнее первых европейских поселений. Коренные индейские племена населяли эт… https://t.co/LtoIuDXubZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy  Just watching part 1 of #RHNJ reunion @Teresa_Giudice is so gross. She is a #bully the show was better when she was in prison!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[in the last year, my anxiety has gotten so bad that i cannot be around people. i get myself so convinced that every… https://t.co/0lf4Hkzfap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelhconnor @RepClayHiggins @GOP @cspan Maybe as a replacement for Arpaio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a sad story. A husband and father from Bowie, MD was hit and killed by a suspected drunk driver. It happened o… https://t.co/7rMvgF3XCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched a full day of @WACsports 🏀 games today and I’m getting more and more excited for #WACVegas on both sides! W… https://t.co/3uUSvnFfnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so apparently there’s a difference between being “tall tall” and “fine tall”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisaKabas @realDonaldTrump It’s not his job to condemn, that’s God’s on the final days. It’s his job to do what he has done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mutschlerfarms @precision_plant You can see the furrow still on the cast closing wheels. They don’t cover as well… https://t.co/inHpHtrIqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCCOfficials I don’t remember inviting you into any conversation https://t.co/b1z4su8oAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyMaLaine @srlourdes @frfrankpavone @ginaandben Peace be with you .  I really don’t care to be right or wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ps_hiddles I want to get a tattoo that is an Anna Karenina quote in his handwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump At least he did his duty and didn't take the cowards way out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate Apple products. I have an iPhone for work. It's a foreign language. Apparently there's a software update? I… https://t.co/JC2a5lPd4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Sukoon in their eyes...❤️  #MaNan #MaNanHamesha #KaisiYehYaariaan @justvoot #Nititaylor #ParthSamthaan… https://t.co/2rLxfvm1SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlerocket0 i woke up today w a rihanna song stuck in my head this is so weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[7k retweets for your man to buy you tampons? 🤦🏽‍♀️ She tell me she gotta headache &amp; I’ll buy the whole Walgreens pharmacy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We take #brunch seriously around here! 🍳🍞🥯🥐🥟🥧🧁☕️🍾🥂🍹#sunday #squad #horse #weekendvibes https://t.co/q8ZmfIPUGK]]></document></documents></author>