<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What an inspiring story! Great job @jacobunruh @luther_high @LutherAthletics @bgunnlions @LutherBasketbal… https://t.co/denYejyqJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigletish This is one of the funniest tweets that I’ve EVER seen! There’s just not enough LMAO to go around 😂😆🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, not a joke.  Still deadly serious business.  But it’s nice to see such a deadly serious organization display a… https://t.co/YsHNaKOSeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHulett @crhall64_hall @scribblepotemus I didn’t have a chance to expand my thoughts on poverty and sin, and sin… https://t.co/p6CbX4WaHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I hope is that more people become ok with not being liked. That's the key to stop this unity shit.   Be u… https://t.co/Vswv5xL6Dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to my old cloning ways. #ReactNative you're too good to me 😍💙 https://t.co/qG7nsLB5IH]]></document><document><![CDATA[New dash mod @ Litt Up Custom Mods and Audio Upstate SC owner/operator, Gavin Seyller https://t.co/JtR2h0pD5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulPabst Well, he’s obviously not getting that toilet advertising gig anytime soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kuda_Chizura @___kweenin Crazier things? Okay I'm listening lol I gotta hear this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarheelmark @PatrickKiser1 @NorahODonnell @ScottPelley @60Minutes Hey koool aid drinking Dem moron- it’s a coup attempt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might super Capricorn of me but few things make me as happy as wearing a nice pair of dress shoes that click as… https://t.co/RkuiWBlfeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callmeBD_ @Chaucerjr @BahimbaJr @kingmjoseph900 oh you’re Michael Myers in this bitch 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muted and reported them as being hacked, if anyone sees if they were in fact hack or just gone batshit insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom made pea soup on this cold snowy day 👍 @ Numidia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/ge9tQqgMov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregfenves He was a pleasure to work with during my time in the Texas Ledge  a great America   God Bless😃🇨🇱tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your coworker who doesn't believe in sleep. @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/60XXLSBDZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously the NYPD is made up of people, and people are variable and imperfect, and sometimes arbitrary, and God kn… https://t.co/4Ab9xVlvdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a law that after so much time has passed, you can’t come up and press charges on someone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL @PolarWhut I don't want any of those things. I would like Republicans to quit racking up the deficit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Coppell’s Brooke Massaviol took second in the girls 148. #txhswrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronniehowlett3 @SuperheroPOLL @PollsOnMovies @Moviepoll2018 @Road2Oscars @InSessionFilm https://t.co/qLrrHrmQPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The formula was not to talk about the bones, but to talk to the bones.” @whclife @MedinaPullings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it's early, but I'd say there's at least a realistic possibility of a #Campbell-#NCState matchup at PNC in t… https://t.co/TsFHucZ8CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BringBackTheBuz @Bojangles1977 Wish their food was as good as this ad https://t.co/AAi6ixW6Ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the State of Utah, you cannot buy firearms or conceal carry if there's a restraining order against you. THE REST… https://t.co/dZyZh19MgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier What is this idiot doing? Being a bully. Trust me. I do know how to deal with that type of buffooner… https://t.co/rGmJ0TEQE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leeward904 @Bharper3407 @Phillies @Braves No way my man he wants that HUGE deal Phillies are about to pay that man!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_bluntsnblondes @Subtronics @ziasounds @heshmane @SullivanKing @squnto https://t.co/YKUqUcAfUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealMcCoy Come on...according to what is on the Internet you’re worth like 10 million...lol 😂 us Hillbillys know t… https://t.co/zSmH7wMyvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notlarrysabato @jonesjay Charter schools in the inner city. Change the system if the problem is the system.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brittany1golf Congrats! You 2 will be amazing parents!! And a good little chocolate lab brother as well!! Lol 🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I crazy or am I one of the few people that doesn’t think the newest x men film looks awful like everybody is saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skyeattolah @ArashMarkazi Visiting team fans will have at least 30% at each game. Once schedule comes out, they wi… https://t.co/eM0WdMMie5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm grandma's special #valentine today...she says I'm super special and the ladies are lucky to have me! 😊😅😇😈❤… https://t.co/PFujsrumBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that really the first time Beilein has been ejected during a game since he coached at Erie Community College in… https://t.co/Ek1s5GQZ4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning intramural treat from a sweet and caring girl. 😊☕️🙌🏻 #D45learn4life #kindnessmatters https://t.co/V3NbvEK7qZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! @IndianaMBB with a huge win in double OT! Finally a #Hoosiers victory. ⚪️🔴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbusKrystina And when she tells the one child, "you didn't vote for me"-does a representative only work for the p… https://t.co/LBeuXoXrT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron put any team he go to in the run for a championship 🤦🏾‍♂️it’s him every year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvspharmacy i have a extracare coupon that says its valid through 3/3...does that mean I can use it on 3/3 or no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Enfermarse en Venezuela es1condena a muerte”:entrevista a enfermera  Mientras Maduro intenta impedir a toda costa… https://t.co/MaV8Gj7LmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 decisions were made in this bathroom stall at the gym today:  1.  Screw my New Years resolution 2.  Yes it’s tota… https://t.co/sWguBR015Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[News. Music. Politics. Life. A wedding. A career. Beautiful travels. Good ideas. Friends. A baby. And then suddenly… https://t.co/X47RZGzsBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@symboliceon @AOC This from people who voted for a man who talked about grabbing women and moving on them like a bi… https://t.co/qJZXNQsYH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @PremierHA Susan DeVore: we have killer Apps, we still killer use and integration of the Apps! #HIMSS19… https://t.co/WsETYkENiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chonito928 @CoachellaCUE @HollyClarkEdu @Flipgrid @Techy_Jenn @Simonometry @blemus28 @flackahh @edtechamatics… https://t.co/7GxUpeNkDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark @shannon_last @redsteeze @SohrabAhmari Will you guys stop fighting! STOP ALREADY! STOP IT STOP IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanCentral_ They are going to make loot changes, they've said it themselves, ncremental changes in the present wi… https://t.co/Oj9ntil8ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I would hate a politician more than @realDonaldTrump. But @RealJudgeMoore may have pulled it off.  https://t.co/s7OAZ7SVKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora si, a ver si muy chingón, @NicolasMaduro éntrale a los madrazos   c.c.p. @aigoncalvess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bea__mar Me parece muy bien Beatriz Espero ya hayas terminado tú día de trabajo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i walked in my break room at work and this super bad chick said “happy valentines day Jonas”. Should I hit her with… https://t.co/BkEQwZalIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A champion is afraid of losing. Everyone else is afraid of winning.” -Billie Jean King #WednesdayWisdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hunter23Kelley You remember this? The girl singing karaoke never stopped 😂 https://t.co/D4Kn48y4pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does #EmilyBlunt and I have in common? We’re both #pigs!      🐷 🐷.  #yearoftheboar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WECTWeather 3-5-19 snow on Hwy 87 Bypass near Elizabethtown #ncwx #SeeItSnapItSendIt https://t.co/0BmbEG3bqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyGuiliano @RevGrey @jazink I really appreciate you listening and being curious. It means a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radio1041 Hey what is all this pirate talk that is happening right now ? https://t.co/vYZtnzZ3HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iamdesignsjoel #mymorning @ Lafayette, Colorado https://t.co/bxIqX72iFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love Landon Collins.  He's one of those guys who always wanted to play for the #Redskins because he id… https://t.co/RmLF2av1lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandonBarbarian @lifesafeast @JackPosobiec @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/sGbLkJIcG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Provide 4 areas that are critical when planning for next school year?#hornetedchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Imagine being this demented lmao. Liberalism is a mental disorder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got introduced to this during my brief stay at Wake Forest. Blew my mind to see primetime shows pre-empted for bask… https://t.co/m1AJqABI5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[it hasn’t fully sunk in to me that the @jonasbrothers have reunited. like. i’m still dead. @latelateshow #LateLateJonas😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a lifelong Caps fan since 1974, I have endured countless 💔 inflicted by the Penguins. This small token of irony… https://t.co/4sCBb20uUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAKE A TAG that reads~ "Money is scarce and times are hard.  So I'm giving... https://t.co/GN0d36HabH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lineup is all over the place. Can't call it bad though just woah. 😂 Shame I'm not in the area for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has to be a mockumentary. I do not believe it. #AbductedInPlainSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Highest trade deficit in history, added over a trillion dollars to debt, tax scam hurting middle a… https://t.co/NW4dxYtFKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[216thebeatradio #Team216TheBeatCleveland ❗❗❗TONIGHT❗❗❗ all new jam pack episode at 7 pm on #BlazingTuesdays with… https://t.co/KQ1m2DrQOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know something if me And Michael were professional wrestler and if we had match against each other in a 3 stage… https://t.co/lYS5HnLLGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine the last three years with a Democrat acting like Trump, do you see the Republicans in Congress defending hi… https://t.co/oiBIPUDnB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck @TheMikeBagley Love me some @Daniel_SuarezG  Go Amigo!! 💪🏼🏎🏁🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory The cow doesn’t care where it shxts as it’s going to the meat factory!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexaBliss_WWE Would love to see @DanaBrookeWWE  or even  @LaceyEvansWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seananmcguire Did everybody else know about this...? https://t.co/9JMxuVDxdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larry_mowry Back when they putted on grass, and accuracy counted. Greens are so fast today it’s all about “getting… https://t.co/Hc8iejkztV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broncos Oh no , is the Broncos gonna continue with making our city the retirement destination for all aging QB?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMensio That’s my point. There’s a double standard in this Pittsburgh rift. Is AB immature at times? Absolutely… https://t.co/8DuDNipHwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump He’s wrong every time he wakes up in the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to my sweetie in SM, kathykonst.  #SantaMonica Compliments of @oveliapsistaria in astoriany @… https://t.co/gdxnFxt5SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianajanae_ @spicebae_ Exactly as I got older I realized just how blessed I was]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aallen2130 @nathanfenno @Husker247BC I saw they think it’s Creighton and TCU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The oscars are so much better without a host.   It seems to be going by a lot faster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cena de despida del R1 #congratulations en Hermosillo, Sonora https://t.co/UEXJyLFu1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManagedByBlanco "Here lies Blanco, he was a kind soul" 😂 https://t.co/uIto12MFHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few words to live by, @tia_cummings3  Daddy loves you and will always support you! https://t.co/G5081txJqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Antonio v. Rodriguez, among other things, is often read as a rejection of the idea that our constitution guaran… https://t.co/93B077GgAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 47 minutes into my shift and I’m already fuming because of these dumbass Medical Assistants. Forty-fucking-sev… https://t.co/eophEUUMGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both @CNN and @NBCNews reporters had this story.  Other news outlets really dropped the ball. #journalism]]></document><document><![CDATA[michaelangelofranco there’s your friend! @ Portuguese Hall https://t.co/ZcKlJbIoXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1976 we were able to cross the Atlantic in 3.5 hours, today it takes 7 hours... 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryan_dob @mikemayerMMO His stuff and age should start him in Bingo IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow the bro @2fourhrs did it again #ValentinoTwenty https://t.co/dcqxrpHMtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15bshall97 @BrandonBJustice I would actually love to see this.. i think they would be civil toward each other.. would love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camachoosunajj @Conapesca @RaulElenes @EDF_deMexico @NiparajaAC @DukeEnvironment @Mexico_TNC @mereduka No que todo… https://t.co/sSIrDaHktx]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Pell remanded in custody after bail revoked  https://t.co/J91MrP91BX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a dumb choice we have between the majors: the Party of big government, or the Party of even bigger government.… https://t.co/PGHpOWmrn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: God has a sense of humor.  I started a #mementomori Lenten devotional today. The only water damage is to th… https://t.co/pF6MsYwnOL]]></document></documents></author>