<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#askmeek @MeekMill are you going to do another tour in the states later on in the year ? Like summer or fall ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight Oh what a night! Neighborhood Services never disappoints and the veal schnitzel over spaetzle dumpl… https://t.co/LRgYuYK3uT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A GOOD DAY TO PICK UP SOME HOLDS at the @BKLYNlibrary !!! https://t.co/iZE0xfqtoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy tuve 1 de esas crisis que como foráneo piensas que ya no puedes más con tantas responsabilidades y lit me estab… https://t.co/LPM7YzduSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What’s it like when @Themowglis play San Francisco IN San Francisco?” PURE. FREAKIN. MAGIC. https://t.co/Z6BQ5dBbec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HistoryHeroes People have a TENDENCY to stand against injustice towards blacks. Even some blacks. For the sake of… https://t.co/O7JGUSZzYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesmadz Four years later and he would still do the same thing lmaoooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocketShip726 @HoYeahPeggy You just missed the funniest thing with @blakeshelton and @kelly_clarkson and the "whit… https://t.co/8SqhUCIiIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feisty Ladies - Kick Off Your 2019 Training Season w/ a Wahoo KICKR, Desk and Mat! https://t.co/K0TvITWhlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Yeah, I wouldn’t trust @SenatorCollins as far as I could throw her. She screwed us on the Healthcare… https://t.co/FZHDxHLYiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I cannot wait!!!! Seriously this series should be a movie , tv show...something. Edge of your seat entertainmen… https://t.co/nNQm3mCo8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicole1124 @RL9631 @WarlordDaddy @mymynags @Aug1405 @kbq2251 @RicharDeanAreMe @ZendamaParanorm @CunningMarkJ… https://t.co/DtmDb03v6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srjeanp I had a number of bosses who screamed regularly and threw documents around often. Yes, they were men too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the perfect makeup routine for combo skin https://t.co/oWYZE9rb8U https://t.co/Vgo3clrV5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @JetBlue what’s the deal not on agent here it’s been 15 minutes - I’ve #got2get2Dublin https://t.co/oYYHD12Ds8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gorgeous wintery mix (not the snow and rain type🤣)! Star of Bethlehem, roses and astilbe!  Simple and yummy!❤️🧡💚… https://t.co/cCU2KhzXEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet peeve: "could of" people, people, people... it's "could have". Also, "would have", "should have" etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: honking at someone as you speed past them in the parking lot after not letting them cross in front of your car… https://t.co/gAKOf2xJsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmberkeley @AardvarkPhantom @Bravewriting @NobodyUknow6969 This is an absurd observation. You are basing your opin… https://t.co/K5g48LNaHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been woken up thanks I'm dick if this happening and them being running scared I'm also sick of the way that tr… https://t.co/n0otBFhaYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDGoins21 @Rosie @Sharkaycat48 #UnsealEpstein #UnsealEpstein #UnsealEpstein #UnsealEpstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinclair1977 @BBCWorld It’s worth a try. If he doesn’t have an audience he might have to try to be a human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re having a special today at On The Grind, I’ll be ther at 5 🌈🧡 https://t.co/S4bLItPn4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHS_gbball Awesome sauce!  Perfect recognition for an amazing team! #empowerthegirls #TigerPride 🏀🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is a more flagrant offender of this than the Cheeto in Chief, @realDonaldTrump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I don't know what poll you are looking at but it's a FAKE poll!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“is it all just a game to you, i’m wondering” -cold in la #BestFanArmy #LimeLights #iHeartAwards https://t.co/DUaenWLDME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repair is for EVERYONE! Here's my story: https://t.co/Yznx0fYTWO. Now, let's hear yours! #ImAGenius #righttorepair… https://t.co/KLd99uA4vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaricakesTTV @queenpamm @DianaAlba3 @hobocita I'm home! 😊 I didn't win. 😥 I was in time to hear the Peacock "Beehi… https://t.co/c9BFOdrpRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi hi, friends, could u lmk if u can think of any (far) left faith orgs (other than Catholic Workers, Christians fo… https://t.co/aIbfRAQYaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiggafras @gtconway3d That threw  me to He was  not found guilty of collusion or conspiracy at his jury trial This… https://t.co/S8BcdHMuH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former MVHS prep @EmmaCochrane12 is headed to #nationals in the 400m! 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derreksena @senatothesophia 🤗So funny - I’m old &amp; thought time sure flies. Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A ranting Trump suggests 'retribution' against comedy show; calls media 'the enemy of the people'  https://t.co/TmXsVNnp9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrochicana I was in Germany when I had my kid. I paid less than a grand, incl. insurance, the whole year. Anothe… https://t.co/614zRzGbVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is good because the tulips outside Smith Hall are coming into bloom ☺️🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamezjorge    Hola buenas tardes  ya no hay respeto, a que esta oscuro  el cine. Y en parque fundadora esta igual… https://t.co/yfyOEJ1OAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When we talk about ending homelessness we need to talk about dismantling structural racism. That is the same conve… https://t.co/njASE082uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avantmusic you were amazing tonight and it was bullshit they cut your time. #onlyreasoniwent]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day of complex feelings about women and work may be just about over, but the month of retrograde has only just… https://t.co/Cgjxxi8TY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally get myself on an awesome gym schedule. And after next week I gotta change it to mornings. I might die y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddoggVlogs Oooo that shit sucks big time. Glad your feeling a lil better. 💜💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy I know told to he’d give me an electric blanket if I came over AND I CONSIDERED IT as I cranked the heat and ignored everything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve cut so many people off because of loyalty. That’s just something I take serious and if you don’t then we just can’t be friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kristen, I love this! We need to help students see math as ALL of these things - it’s so much more than just for th… https://t.co/ON1ZeGyEV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VipKaylaKelli @RomeoManciniXXX That and the staff sexually harraasing the women and then offering a free trip so t… https://t.co/HKGyI2cqJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousins and I used to get on opposite sides of the road and pull a fake string when cars would come lmfaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everyone was of the same ethnicity (white) our country would be pretty boring, in my opinion. I believe every pe… https://t.co/YAM5LHjtR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of Sean being recognized for the DAR Youth Citizenship Award. A special thanks to @BrandyPanagos for no… https://t.co/FuB1DO3ceO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elosisofficial Thanks. Yes. Depression is very very hard. Praying the battle gets easier for both of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Louis to host Champions Showdown https://t.co/TXRlaPpORj @WOMChess @FIDE_chess @EuropeEchecs @chessdom https://t.co/XB7l1C3ZI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men: in case you’ve never really understood #gaslighting- this is it. #PSA- don’t be this dude- ever and def don’t… https://t.co/un26s4SxXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump PBJ is good if you're hungry enough.  Stone is not hungry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made my grand return to work last night after three days home with the flu! And my grand, I mean I had a massive co… https://t.co/Ex7D04e9n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m going outta town tomorrow and I intended on just balling out the whole trip. But I need to purchase this tri… https://t.co/2nVR1TbIB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic concert tonight in Asheville!!! One we will NEVER forget!!  @OldDominion #OldDominion #botetourtgirls https://t.co/O4lnO4gFcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I want to argue about movies, and then I remember that our President signed off on children being locked… https://t.co/3R6cCSIufs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a social media break today 🍃 feeling refreshed and ready for the upcoming week ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aterry65 @ADigesu10 I never said you did! Read the tweet! What I said was name a coach we can get!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is a lot more simple when you're camping. All you have to worry about is staying warm, having enough food and… https://t.co/zg40PMYF19]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my final leg from Philadelphia... see you in the morning Liverpool !!   #GirlsLovetraval #liverpool #TheRedWay… https://t.co/zbRB7BW9Gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann When will Russia break? Here, now, we defeat communism. It is W's men, and Trump is deposed, indivi… https://t.co/EHHCbmV6KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t believe my friend when she said she sleeps with a butchers knife under her mattress but she proved me wrong https://t.co/H2BQBKXkCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdonna2 @Phil_Lewis_ Since he got off on it, he thinks he can do it again at if accused that'd be double Jeopardy,… https://t.co/CKBU1Qg4kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talbertson7 thank you for tweeting about the hockey game. I was unable to attend. I appreciate your diligence ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still in awe from seeing #VirginaWoolf’s writing desk yesterday. #500YearsOfWomensWork Thanks, @buxton977!!! ✒️ https://t.co/ztx390bMCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawsonmills01 Thats just radical feminism. You could use the same antitheses about radical religious groups. I sti… https://t.co/n11WpkGrqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TSS2019ATN Look forward to sharing about #kimochis and #kintsugi .... sharing tips on how to use them effectively… https://t.co/3HsQFgNAvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom's handiwork at its finest... 😂🤣 #mymomkillsme #gottalovethisfamily #ohmom @ Akron, Ohio https://t.co/G5omCFnICO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So powerful yesterday @ladygaga ! Always an inspiration! Buena semana a todos! ❤️🙏🏻 https://t.co/E8MVnGrTjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the seven wonders of Georgia - Tallulah Gorge 🌲🌲🌲 @ Tallulah Falls, Georgia https://t.co/PlNLMgJ946]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear classmates,  Just tuck your bag under your fucking seat so people can walk through the rows. Staring at me lik… https://t.co/gMCB3IZZeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deesteinzy I agree. While I love Bernie, I believe he would better serve our country in a cabinet position.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I reach out to one of my group members that I’m now competing with at another school and the bitch called me “… https://t.co/9IBtlxiBNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought these for the gym since I made the mistake of wearing my NMDs and that shit killed my feet! 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure how any of these vague bills regarding infintinismally rare and highly complicated medical scenarios a… https://t.co/UtyU1ogQKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin Gave my $27. The San Francisco @OurRevolution chapters have several hundred members. We all gave, and… https://t.co/6VGGahYnRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh god I’m suddenly remembering all the things I’ve given up for Lent in the past... chocolate for 40 days freshman… https://t.co/YV4LojDg4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3littleredbones Larry Kump has missed most of the session with major health concerns @johnisnerwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowling with my family @ Brunswick Zone Bowling-Birthday Party https://t.co/1l9lbert1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Financial Analyst" at Corning by asking for referrals. It's a great way to get a me… https://t.co/NBLVBttPi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ran into @NorahODonnell in the hallway and told her this stunning dress totally popped on TV this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this! #BoysInTheBand   New Kids On The Block - Boys In The Band (Boy Band Anthem) (Official Mus...… https://t.co/Qz4jfBhlm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I try to be so nice and all and I still get no respect at all that’s just sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was awesome to meet the face @DavidHThornton and the mastermind damien_leone behind Terrifier. ⁣ Really super co… https://t.co/w2ehHmc32s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Personal Training is offered at my gym for both Adults and Kids.We also specialize in all abilities an… https://t.co/8P3SjbU2q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Feel Something by #AdamLambert. https://t.co/n201CLeUQy #FeelSomething]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @ccatmpt @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @Julianna_glass… https://t.co/J4FEznMO3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol have you watched Temple ? They've very much been a live by 3 type of team at times this season... They can esse… https://t.co/1leXC8VTpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre he pensado esto 👇 es como una marca de ganado del hombre señalando a otros hombres: "esta mujer tiene dueño… https://t.co/lJt8TjMtSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cameron Ganci throws the pitch, batter hits to right, Dylan Ganci makes a jumping catch to record the 3rd out.  We… https://t.co/XqsSbeaL4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook is such a weird place. I am always so hesitant to get on it and then I do and now here I am laying in bed… https://t.co/2YNyugDUec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizBorden4 @RepMaxineWaters Thank you very much. I’m sure my brother appreciates it.? You don’t expect to die befo… https://t.co/14mS4JkkBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got an automated email from a news channel, it said Heavy Mix in Everett. I have no idea what they are sayin… https://t.co/QCluA00QjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[An understanding love - a love that sees the good in others - will be our goal! Mother Teresa #wordstoliveby @ Syra… https://t.co/fz7DujUQSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach it. This is what a Great America looks like. All colors and genders having a good time economically. It is n… https://t.co/s7URl4Wr60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Omg @SenSanders WTF 😡#WakeUpAmerica and for god sake sheep 🐑 #WalkAway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eric_barrett12 ABSOLUTELY ERIC!  Where do we start?    Could we start with the Ethic Committee?  The AG?  HOW do we get Omar out of office?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Coffee Goals Achieved!! #coffee #coffeetime #yum #skytoplodge #skytop #weekendmode #weekends #sunday @ Skyt… https://t.co/wc8RJG13in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolute day maker: Dino acknowledging me on Twitter. I love how this man actually makes that few second effort to… https://t.co/A7ax4Q5BNx]]></document></documents></author>