<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jamesgarringer Pretty sure there is a lot they haven't heard of.  Been "exposed to" that they didn't know of is pr… https://t.co/bUZUPF6KPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is without a doubt  the funniest thing I have seen in my life😂😂😂😂Im madthat I know half the people shown in th… https://t.co/wyLeIIrMqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/vMCeaWNbOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEPFuller And if you actually ask them how to create jobs, the answer is usually absolute nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an important point when people joke about #fakemelania. Gun violence survivors are often hounded and harras… https://t.co/ftmqLl6Zo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyleeWhitney Thank you Rylee... it’s nice to know someone cares about my presence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Listening to @60Minutes. You really believed Putin over our own intelligence agency. Really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealDBell_ @WarriorNation_1 Spoken like a true champion. Proud of of your character and accomplishments on and… https://t.co/Wpl7FTE2hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Cañada’s Sophie Garcia will face Birmingham senior Vianeth Jimenez in the opening round of the girls’ CIF State… https://t.co/8ZTwh6TDIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaDuran @abc7breaking @utepnews I was reading up on her last night and these seem to be the same things I read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you keep ending up alone things keep not going your way maybe you shou reflect and start to blame yourself and change your ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex Went by there on a peacemaking (USN) cruise up the Black Sea to Constanta, Romania when Ceaușescu w… https://t.co/qIeMcum5o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gassigirl88 Much of this due to social media. Cell phones are addictive. See my wife’s TEDx Talk Saving The Magic… https://t.co/WOUAMirEyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they say port is warping the way people perceive sex I wasn’t expecting this 🤷🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharkBoyNet @TheRealDisco I can’t tell if you guys hate each other or always joking. I thought he was your shark dad in the hospital]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewoodentulip sounds about right. our informal seems to involve pyjamas 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[We join #NC09 neighbors in thanking @NCJews4Justice Charlotte Chapter for their tireless efforts advocating for our… https://t.co/jTTRcjxh9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staying Out Drinking Till 1 in The Morning Knowing You Have to Be at Work at 4am!!!  #fml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartOTXHeartMD Much more likely to happen in US than any other developed country. Health care should be a right, not a commodity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@internetfaggit Well doesn’t everyone wish they can be this independent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy smokes.... today is Friday! Just realized it because of this tweet..  Ps. Read DoW = great book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @howard22205 @Danielmoatsphi1 @JonHeyman Better baseball town than Flushing, NY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGrace73 @corvomancer @dontbignorant @bopinion @business Ooookay. He hasn’t even come up with anything to take to… https://t.co/gwnHMOVRol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laura_Rojas_ @lopezobrador_ @CONAGO_oficial @JTrianaT @ferbelaunzaran @AlvarezMaynez @marianagc @JCRomeroHicks Zag… https://t.co/gG7nKO3DtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_SAVARD @OntarioPCParty @fordnation You and me both brother. This entire caucus have proved themselves foreve… https://t.co/Qk2x2iUnZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX2Erika @langeamyFOX2 Cool!    Michigan DNR confirms rare lynx sighting caught on video https://t.co/qRmQvzJgJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball tournament games cancelled due to poor field conditions? A trip to the Bosh to see the @DiamondHeels on a… https://t.co/nHe4M6wkDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victoria sues God. It's not what you think. But it should make you think. Because some elected officials in BC sh… https://t.co/QAAsQBFvBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the new logo for @WagnerAthletics @MatthewMcCord4 https://t.co/i6auko4usM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston, MA: and then the computer took over my life in 1987. Complete shit registered from state to state. Crap fro… https://t.co/G7hRt5r2ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandalorian_Ren @Eathbound420 @FixesItself @NewmannMichael @minhtngo @sarasotamike66 @Putzy2010 @TezHug… https://t.co/oxSkvLV2CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk When you were writing the book, no one expected senator Graham's embracing of Trump as his new aut… https://t.co/2jj7EwJYLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenf00 Estoy viviendo en Virginia. Llevo casi el año. Los vi en DC. El de Atlanta es el domingo]]></document><document><![CDATA[World Peace . . #subway #streetphotography #shotoniphone #subwayseries #mta #nycsubway #nycstreetphotography… https://t.co/RMIFkftquk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charomeo Stop lying... Kobe was an all star all of those years and dang near matched him in points each finals. Sh… https://t.co/7XjJt8OWiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thunder games will never get old. Thank you God for the game of basketball 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CagninaPaul @7News I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOME Day1… https://t.co/pZbLc2Ruwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christi49738072 @thehill @AprilDRyan @HillaryClinton @staceyabrams Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDLCC I do. But I won't click because it's sure to be another plea for money. I only donate to animal causes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misstashamillz America blue Pali straight up Aunty ..denouncing that Green P 🇳🇬.. y’all can enjoy PMB and all .. a… https://t.co/0ADBLNiUXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertstark79 @AP Where did get ur facts? Trump supporters? Here this is called a "reference". Where u back ur arg… https://t.co/F0Rkrhf6l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is in 10 minutes... still taking applications for a date for dinner🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the @JaguarCanada I-PACE the 2019 @AJACanada Canadian Utility Vehicle of the Year. #CIAS2019… https://t.co/ti6thDgryC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all kind of knew Jessica Jones and The Punisher weren’t long for this world after the others got cancelled.   My… https://t.co/yjEseGDbMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fill your baskets and hide your eggs! We are stocked up on Easter goodies! @ Ali Cat Toys https://t.co/y80q1CpmiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton Bpth. Setting new high today #busy #MoneyLaundering  #lovemoney  #cashcows]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I once held the door for this old Mexican couple for like 10 seconds because one had a cane and they litera… https://t.co/NT0O3QPy7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[February Agent Spotlight - Meet our Agents. Wendy Simpson is an Award-Winning Agent at Royal LePage Oak Park Office… https://t.co/DIf3bc3jK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortuneMagazine The recommended film "Max," has the ironic/flaky premise that if only people had bought Hitler pai… https://t.co/H30q4yea3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovejohnkimble I dont game online with other people either. I have trust issues    lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolarToday Acaso Guaido necesita apoyo de Grupo de Lima para tomar decision sobre acompa~amiento armado a ayuda hu… https://t.co/bPHW0CA3cF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinvarley @kcemerson @knott_michele @Kpteach5 @IowaAmberReads @KReilley5 @barberchicago @kelleemoye @thebrainlair… https://t.co/7DkcMc1aqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthBankNadim Nadim - your response is perfect. I never understood the hate this guy received especially given hi… https://t.co/tsGD8CyNaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTO716 You are a clown. #sabres 🐁🐀🐁🐀 😂😂🤣 sabres are a joke of a franchise. Eichel is all you have. No goalie… https://t.co/5RLbt3X86L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @washingtonpost I hope he gets the paper and he can fire all the journalist and start over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats and thanks to Antonio Wilkerson on his #nissanaltima Thanks for your business. #grateful #bushsellscars… https://t.co/ogoK4DqLZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald has been in a fight with reality for years. Reality is winning bigly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Adapted Screenplay   My pick: IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK   WINNER: BLACKkKLANSMAN  9/18 so far   #Oscars⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠… https://t.co/9ZPgozJJAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Artemishowl_ Your wish is granted. Her name is Sandee, and shes 14 years old now. Best pupper ever, true story. https://t.co/4i1Z5YpjjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well its Friday, and we are supposed to get a  storm. Rain,to ice, to snow. Lincoln Nebraska, you have PLENTY of  t… https://t.co/pzx4PFD4bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HockeyBabbler There was a leaked release date this week, but not sure how accurate it is obviously. It was acciden… https://t.co/MyKID5GQqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos for the people of venezuela we should have a massive air drop all over the country of food and med… https://t.co/vQMXYY5naT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snark_tyranny With this never ending investigation plus the hard left wing line up of candidates Trump should dust these loons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poppa Sauce Drippin at Prime Bar in Dallas Tx  Sauce Walka put on one great show last night Ooowwweee!!… https://t.co/NYeNZID3X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the homes I showed today in Woodland Hills. $750k. South of Ventura Blvd. I like it https://t.co/sZ7QH5kC22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope — and in the same vein, those who are willing to be patient and put in the work over the years are going to wi… https://t.co/sran6ovilW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Hillary Clinton announces she will not run for President in 2020 — @FoxNews  When you run for President twice, an… https://t.co/thCFpGXS4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[-38° at the mine. Lol wtf Montana better start acting right. This ain’t Antarctica 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Flaunting your power? Enjoy your time in DC you have less than 2 years to go. Unless of course you are exposed… https://t.co/MDHtOjKdSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan No, it’s espionage. It’s treason if we’re at war. However, it isn’t Rosenstein nor McCabe that’s c… https://t.co/kojd1SGjjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if we needed more proof @JLPtalk was a fake pastor and a disgrace to the race, here it is. How DARE he talk abou… https://t.co/vLynOdLL9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Star_Gem Couldn’t agree more. I have always considered myself a moderate leaning far left on social issues an… https://t.co/VWyprFwoqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barack Obama's '44' bomber jacket wins praise on Twitter, has fans wondering where it came from  https://t.co/TRvkhGWqbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting: South Bend’s West Side.  Time: Just before 3 a.m.  The latest on a short pursuit involving the driver of t… https://t.co/SR32BuXJ5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to be supporting my friend @NMalliotakis at her kickoff fundraiser for Congress! Cant wait to be on th… https://t.co/PBbK9qH2Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @texasfreedom101 No @CAIRNational loves some terrorists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earl_Thomas Only problem I have....  It's him first, then the team.  Basing that on their record    my two cents.… https://t.co/XSO3moqwxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Deporteando  ⚽️ Hey Alfonso en esta encuesta te falta @hugosanchez_9 por favor es un candidato jaja #ESPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new startup Maze Therapeutics is launching today with $191 million to discover and drug "genetic modifiers"--ge… https://t.co/Ygm0DUpRsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to the week on a Tuesday.. #haveagooddaybesafe https://t.co/7RsSSQd1pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM everyone this time going up a hour this shit is crazy but have a great day @ Uptown https://t.co/0iTFYBeZ8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I wish I would’ve really fucked on a girl in any way while I was you, the way you’re acting. Yeah cheating is c… https://t.co/Q7Iy7fYxDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedDlicious Are you freaking out? This seems like it came straight off your vision board]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m good at napping so I’m going to do exactly that now..” #MondaysWithMerle https://t.co/HMQO5VMFkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Sanctuary in California - No Peace behind Nancy Pelosi's Wall https://t.co/1ElH0MDAiO via @YouTube #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PacerV @AmyMek Sounds kinda like what Congress did with the Anti-Semitic Language from a Particular Congress Woman.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at work and a father is watching his kids play and run through the toy department. Hopefully they don't leave a… https://t.co/F4tsLY9y5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump This Scottish farmer would make a powerful case to all the voters that democratic st… https://t.co/cQjyvtGa0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I physically feel myself getting lighter, the tricks becoming easier, and timing becoming automatic. 📸:@kainadirah… https://t.co/JF57gP8YFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday work on Suzie's back. The second swan we've done on her. Always fun to add the pieces of filigree when th… https://t.co/RW17ZDjV12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YumLemmingKebab @theroux_ @_alexd36 @Scarasyte @herebemonsterss @WhiteIsTheFury Don’t shoot the messenger. Wether… https://t.co/w00FLiBUN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimSmith87 Flirting with the line, isn't he?! Or is that Jay county that's right on the border?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArrowheadAddict Nope, let’s maintain character and a strong locker room, many changes anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is @JuliannaRWhite and I’m Derek Burgundy? Who put a question mark on the TelePrompTer?@WCCBNewsRising gets you… https://t.co/J4YGzBk8bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IfMyLifeWereAVideoGame: just press [https://t.co/wWpEImHcRm] to start a great new adventure. Adopt! https://t.co/fKa1PBmw4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelemorrow I’ll say this apex is the only battle royal that has reeled me in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Clockwork Orange by @blueearlbeer at @ryleighsoyster — https://t.co/RS3dAU2VK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golic and Wingo might be the worst sports radio show in the country. And that says a lot cause Midday 180 is terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandan told me the toothpaste I picked out for him was spicy like Cajun food...? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great times last night in Peterborough with an amazing team at @ShowplacePtbo #magician https://t.co/Ut2bCq2tbV]]></document></documents></author>