<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@buudgreen @RepSwalwell @harveyjkaye Corrupt??? What proof do you have?  I'll wait for your fake answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[funniness right? This Week’s Best of the Web, Featuring a Taylor Swift Meme and Video #web # projectinspired... https://t.co/VGsIWTbSb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shariknowsbest I missed it cuz our internet has been down or the cable company is jacked up. I’m pissed! Who was e… https://t.co/eaqDD7K836]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 Awe. You will find the right words — just say what is on your heart. I can’t imagine. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImpeachIlhanOmar #BanSharia #CreepingSharia for her racism against the American People]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to an AMAZING panel of brilliant, innovative educators at the @edmentum sales and services conference! Such a… https://t.co/jtX9JSefig]]></document><document><![CDATA[So stoked!!! Going back to Tahoe this weekend with thisismymtb !!! 😻 @ Franciscan Lakeside Lodge https://t.co/jN7V8YMvHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Girl don’t go away mad, just go away”  .... remember that? #ResignLisaMacLeod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve @pamfoundation  How you support the dictatorship Maduro, have you ever visited Venezuela? I invite you to… https://t.co/suRd3SG2KY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ impulsive decisions!! swipe ⏩ to see the before • • • • • #impulsivedecisions #redkenshadeseq #redkentribe… https://t.co/mjLfD7QveN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayygru Were you trying to part the red sea? Bc points for originality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might have a lil #Atlantaversary gathering the weekend that I move in.  Possibly. Maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Charter Schools USA? We're hiring in #Loxahatchee, FL! Click the link in our bio for details on thi… https://t.co/zv7EAHOTj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennPride365 @bewilliams11 @IHSAA1 This is awesome!!! Wish it could have happened sooner though, know a lot of EX… https://t.co/Dx3wiuu5yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald is a very big lier and the worst thing that ever happened to America Donald embarrasses the… https://t.co/H0Fq4Wowu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took Kaiser for a walk around the old hood. I probably should have stretched first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truethat #eatpraylove #momwifeboss #mood #vibes #wordsofwisdom #lifeofaninsuranceagent #realtalk #hustle #journey… https://t.co/TkBjRv815K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The absolute best rendition of one of my favorite songs. Lea Salonga - you are a treasure 💖  https://t.co/i4xvfspyfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleLataif Agreeeeeeee. Especially something cold which bothers the stomach. Hope you have energy today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m living my best life surrounded by people who love me, BITCH IM HAPPY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I guess #cabinfever will continue school closings already for Boston area my kids will drive me 🍌...🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night @TheToscars ! thrilled to be nominated! With @craigryoung and Richard Rennie. Thank you @GettyImages xx… https://t.co/ANswC13pOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear most these rappers and hip hop “artists” right now are just personalities with producers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie and the Chocolate Factory | 24 Adorably Geeky Wedding Invitations https://t.co/MxnbX1m2NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The construction industry ranks second worst in productivity, only to hunting. Technology and culture are the answe… https://t.co/0fTCjrWowd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @cfltorres Democrats  who believe they can accomplish anything that will stop our President Trump a… https://t.co/lzFSFXriGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[More and more I measure my life by the wealth of amazing women I am fortunate enough to call family, friends, and c… https://t.co/FWBHowlEBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low carb dieting is the hardest thing I’ve ever done. There are literally carbs in everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finalizing custom videos and scripts today. A trip to the gym and sine updating full day ahead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok then plz explain to me the ppl who stand up the second that the plane lands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @trump_enemy How many times has this spineless, ignorant idiot complained about @nbcsnl? Has he nothing… https://t.co/kfeM6pksma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nina_Soden Sounds wonderful. Good luck with your writing! God Bless :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar He does look like Lex Luther! The wall speech was so heartfelt. 🤢 Bless his little heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soIoucity @JNeiser17 Let me get in on some of that toasted ravioli … can you overnight it to Vegas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get yourself a man who knows just how to help calm your anxieties about your exams. https://t.co/iGCtU9JHsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Kasich is Wonk of the Year and as an Ohioian I've never laughed harder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radiohead - Weird Fishes MSG NYC 2018 https://t.co/bVMacGJtij via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[me:  has v bad anxiety about driving in bad conditions    also me:  has v bad anxiety about calling into work becau… https://t.co/vDufGwwv8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masturbate With zeana34g In Video Chat, Masturbation Fun With zeana34g Who Hates Been Alone https://t.co/jBljTSouqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Floriane Jochum for your excellent presentation #SMFM19 from the MEDIP cohort study. A new easy-to-… https://t.co/SvfOlpBrpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[who else came up on the wooden spoon?! 😩🇮🇹❤️ woke up with so much more love in my heart after @natashadiggs &amp;… https://t.co/TUbOfPdcAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on @nbc make my day even better and #RenewSVU21 @nbcsvu #RenewSVU21 give us our record breaking season #RenewSVU21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michaela_KD I honestly thought she was gonna eat shit that entire time]]></document><document><![CDATA[If these people would put half the energy into themselves as they do me and what I’m doing.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your grass is always greener where you water it ❤ @ Tyler, Texas https://t.co/GtdfGuDC1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else cant wait to hear the text of @jakequery bitching abt @Schultz975 ? https://t.co/jUjoZJTGr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattNBCBoston @DanielleWBZ4 I got you @MattNBCBoston ---it was Netflix betrayal. If my husband watches the upcomin… https://t.co/3QgGBvDPEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craving Disney now... what else is new. So I’ll just look through Disney photos and miss it more #DisneyIsHome and… https://t.co/5hqDMWjSaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drmikemurdock You are not alone.   It appears that the Dems have gone array or Crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came back to pin cart from my break and the girl who covered for my break said “I tried to keep the pin board nea… https://t.co/0T4loKcnvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 Creative Ways to Recycle Content by @BrennerMichael #pr #SOcialskills #seo https://t.co/ZB7ygDpxFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for showing a gal a good first time, NYC ✌🏻🏙 @ NYU Kimmel Center for University Life https://t.co/HRx4INOZAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Winter Storm by @HeavySeasBeer @ Andy Warhol's Grave — https://t.co/oXMqc9Isou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaabbott Beyond ready! Pugsatoni Phil totally got the Spring reading wrong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy el Gran Cañón cumple 100 años como parque nacional. Tengo la inmensa suerte de haber viajado bastante a lo larg… https://t.co/IvxvvBM9em]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the opportunity to chat with Shadi Abou-Zahra, the Accessibility Strategy and Technology Specialist at W3C, t… https://t.co/6wkcFbcGZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@915WRFT rockin it this morning with @FlashesWCC ! 🌏🌎🌍 https://t.co/0ZCpEM2iOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a dream come true!! #Equity and #ExcellentEducation for all kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’ve replaced most of my flower gardens with natives, the hummingbirds hardly visit the feeders- because t… https://t.co/cCJCHVnOYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men who love face masks &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Every58Hours @sundnce99 @NYPDnews @NYPD41Pct @BlueIrishAngel @GaryACarlo Basically, you have none]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul He could do with having his hamburger supply cut off by the look of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can mitigate it. By creating interactions that emphasize strengths, provide nurturing contexts, and by actively… https://t.co/M8b5B107bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a regular car and you manage to get pulled over by Mississippi DOT then you must have REALLY been fucking up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really have very specific online coping methods. When I need to laugh I watch @DavidSpade do anything. When I wan… https://t.co/8N8oJpmnxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 BTW, CL gives a person bad gas. Did you notice that? Ha-ya! 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caroline_Marie_ @KaceyMusgraves It’s such a beautiful, simple song which is what makes it so powerful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day kim.fish5 😘 @ Rogers Park, Chicago https://t.co/lKQ9mLzQ6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee with our early birdie☕️ #sundaymorning #earlyrisers #sadiesue #momlife @ Cambridge, Ontario https://t.co/CxAeZ5UG1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can go hours without talking to me, PLZ go a couple more🤷🏼‍♀️ #overit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjimblackman @LevineJonathan @AOC Then you might consider talking to her about rehab.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodimusprime @GrooveSDC @RabideauScott - ok I’m jealous- my sistas are fo real!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe you just need to cry bitch!! It’s ok!! Feel it and move forward!! You got this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have these people even been WATCHING the same show I’ve been seeing?!?  To people like this I have just one thing t… https://t.co/ZBtMNzPNRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkWalker Says a Trump sycophant? If you read the article you realize that this issue is much more complex tha… https://t.co/2Nqc8f1kR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are putting our ideas onto white boards and are beginning to start research! #PBL https://t.co/UXOrw1foKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of a perfect day🎈.... 'Happy 🎂 Birthday Jeremiah"❣  I pray that God covers you with his love for the rest o… https://t.co/Ccg3Z0roGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shannon99138495 @Lrihendry @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Talking about lining pockets. Lobbyists line the pockets of… https://t.co/4URXDetDAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen and heard this story many times and it still bewilders me. All the stories I’m aware of ended with fierce… https://t.co/XIu3g0fJWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLHade If you need someone to talk to or just hang out let me know girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Agreed but she is an adult and a congresswoman. Words matter, as they do with Trump and Steve King]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle Your colleague @chrislhayes  did an epic podcast on #with “Amazon’s Wish List” everyone should listen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Can we pretend that airplanes in the night skies are like shooting stars... I could really use a wish right now” 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dearadneris @CheeseburgerROH I'm hoping that once I get my hands on them, I  can translate them. All the pictures… https://t.co/RIzSTzvL9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElRigel_ @tonymarquezroon @AguedaBarojas @OmarCardenass @Pepe1807 @mikeleyva75 @germanamilcarsi @MarielaMtzL_MN… https://t.co/vlKt3nK70d]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this favors DT or Republicans, of course they won't! Does that mean all people who don't suppose righteous voter… https://t.co/9xVNO9RbHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STRONGMIND333 @realDonaldTrump You really cannot believe what you tweeted, can you? How many illegals and refugees are you housing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckaylarast I’m gunna be real with you. My IUD makes me want to die EVERY DAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Ardmore, OK job and click to apply: Sleep Medicine Technician II - https://t.co/87bqI9LyU2 #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always great to see your work besties outside of work @ L-Treyns Bar https://t.co/AQqt50aGH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[instagram is the worst app to be on rn if ur insecure and have low self esteem LOL save urselves!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portfolio 3.0: officially going into my 3rd co-op job search! Check out what I’ve been up to and my new projects on… https://t.co/86JnKtJA5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#drone #dronephotography #dronephotos #dronestagram #dji #djiphantom4pro #aerialphotography #cherrygrovebeach… https://t.co/c6uSHRn8n2]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing worse than a complete stranger telling you what you SHOULD be doing with YOUR child. It really sho… https://t.co/RJ5TB3lfaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dead Ass, If I can pay all of my debts (minus EMU) before the year is up. I’ll be happy asf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshhenderson I’m so sorry for your loss @joshhenderson   My prayers and comfort are with you and your family during this difficult time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertWelchNews Is that your kitty, Robert? He/she is adorable!!!! And likes to nap. Smart kitty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍸🍸🍸 (@ Universal CityWalk - @universalorl in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/edmqleN2w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave it so many chances and tried my best, but it’s time to move on. Distancing myself to avoid hurt seems like the best plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time we had a president who writes objectively intelligent, and positive tweets!]]></document></documents></author>