<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@scb81271 @DylanDreyerNBC She’s always cute. She’s the only reason I tune into the Today Show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jawley12 @mehdirhasan @IlhanMN No she didn't point out obvious truths. She created conspiracy theories about Israe… https://t.co/wkXypDq7hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZakkuRye This Comeback was disgusting didn't think I would win the first round (Yes I did win all 3 rounds) I'm sl… https://t.co/6Vo5BtjBrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya no dudo estoy seguro, cada tweet de este hombre es un reto para ver quien escribe la mejor Oda a aquel pequeño m… https://t.co/kEYaAdivVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamsjoe I call this a “cradle to grave” sandwich, but I’m terrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLOP SWEAT DESPERATION. COHEN WILL SWAT LIKE BABE RUTH, AND THE DRIVES WILL BE OUT OF THE PARK. AVOIDANCE IS UNAVOI… https://t.co/zenMbgrmXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a quote in a Stanford journal on Phone Girard (30+ year tenure there) helps to summarize: "Moreover, Girard bega… https://t.co/s4GJtqrOXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patzearfoss There is a web based tool. It's in my Twitter moment for 2019. I don't remember the name so I click on that link 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjambler @AlDula2 @PhunnyHaHa @F3Greensboro Very inclusive and accepting. No shorts = still served. #SarongStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino They are bringing on the “reset” quicker than we thought. Every society that devolved into the immoral pl… https://t.co/8QnrPKBQf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather Update: sleet in St. Michael/Albertville area - roads just wet right now @NWSTwinCities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Do you give a shit about the 1 in 5 and increasing number of coal miners with black lung, or are you… https://t.co/MQYKftMD6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PargaOrlando Trump les esta pasando el Rolo a todos a Todos ahora se ve y se siente el Dinero en este lado del Cha… https://t.co/Uk7WEyeFtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tequila really does cure a sore throat, I’m glad I’ve discovered this home remedy https://t.co/0u492Mr1tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumors are swirling about Apple's AirPower wireless charging again https://t.co/9Bi0iEPs5N via @mashable]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love to be groomed.  #mirandathelab  @makeupbymilo  #papimilo  @makeupbymilo  #sunrise  #florida #🥰 @ Sunrise, F… https://t.co/jm3WYlSmHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@absalon78 @matrixtwit1 Uuuuh ahora reventando 🤦🏼‍♂️ por un empate no puedes decir que es malo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyMazza @JamieMcGee_ @MariahTimms @natalie_allison https://t.co/0ItmQHhICo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsGAGirl @KAG4All @realDonaldTrump @GOP @DNC Globalist pressure and globalist money are driving the careers of… https://t.co/5x8QtioiSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many of us have dreamed of Han offering us this job? "Wouldn’t be nice to you! Doesn’t pay much!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I worked Michael Bublé at Amalie Arena. https://t.co/IRS0kONu29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@splcenter is great at combating those they don't like. Some are hateful, a lot just happen to hold different opini… https://t.co/4MOudqRAzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnson shot that foul shot and as soon as it left his hands he was like https://t.co/S4LKA5pMIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chreatonnn @autumnlane77 She was so cute as a puppy 😫😫 https://t.co/fZwNTq8RBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[As football loses luster, smaller teams take hold in Maine https://t.co/JLb763sWDu via @BostonGlobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 4 booths in the Trail Zone facing the front, Main Aisle remain at the Outside Experience.  You want to get you… https://t.co/KIM4DPujLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcmiceli1984 @LupeFiasco @Royceda59 @JColeNC @Logic301 @kendricklamar Ok they are cool!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I expect trump to continue his attacks while knowing they are inflammatory to his ignorant followers. He is despera… https://t.co/rTZVplmCsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Badger Baseball teams with wins over Gatesville. Varsity wins 8-2 and JV wins 11-0.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks FirstWarrior (firstwarrior)for the awesome swag bag! @ Columbia, South Carolina https://t.co/TnF2QmGsur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, there are pros to Planned Parenthood like free condoms and birth control, but it does not out weigh the amoun… https://t.co/TMRG3Djvs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laratablog Repítelo conmigo:  Gasolinazo = IEPS  Aumento inflacionario =/ Gasolinazo  Gracias 😊 de nada 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_wentz @ChildrensPhila You are truly one of Philly's phavorite son's! God bless you for caring so much  about these children 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quality group of ballers from the good ol’ days. #hawks #mnblackhawks #oldschoolcool @iammodelcitizen neumannc… https://t.co/vlVJVvmjeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty brew! #chicago - Drinking a Blood Orange Brew Free! or Die IPA by @21stAmendment @ Aberdeen Tap  — https://t.co/p2fepwCeVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieWGME @WGME @AmandaWGME @AaronWGME @JeffWGME @LaurenWGME @Liztorrey2017 @StevenBrasley @WGMEReynolds @LexieWGME https://t.co/09necK96Yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[One learns a lot about what people do, not what they say. https://t.co/8QwJgFQQp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_przybysz @Reflog_18 @Browns @bakermayfield @NickChubb21 @Kareemhunt7 @God_Son80 @AB84 @Primetime_jet… https://t.co/Ur2rFiiJFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Augustus Jones crossed 6.2. Time 00:54:06, pace 09:22 min/mile, est. finish 10:27 am https://t.co/LmyqYiICq9 #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller @AOC Oooooops.  Looks like Nancy Pelosi and Diane Feinstein has had enough of AOC's crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just happened to me.  Seems to be they want to put on the pressure. @codinghorror]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Harbour Island, The Bahamas https://t.co/uedH2jbfzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely day for ⚾️ Spring training stadium 4 This place is beautiful. Orioles vs Red Sox.  4 games in 5 days. Love i… https://t.co/rVcw5wErqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are rockin’ it here at the Seasons52 with Kelsea our server. Lobster Ravioli and hand rolled Lasagna.… https://t.co/HqsGH22lJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you believe in the 10,000 hour rule? Anders Ericsson: How to become an expert at anything https://t.co/H3GZcIgsKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercial de #howtotrainyourdragon3 con @jorgebernal en @lavozkids para @telemundo #director #dragoncoach… https://t.co/V5yBkWOzDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren If she is in danger, it is because ISIS has been defeated. If she is aloud to return, so will her ISIS politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKKollectorStev @DrDoggystyle @Peina81 for the kollectors in tonights reveal https://t.co/0RQ2TbBcMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudahLee while we’re all here.. I just wanted you to know that we share a birthday. Your new music/ and old has go… https://t.co/ggxzURsqVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Here is The Real Russian Collusion.... https://t.co/RZshSHzpGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snboxing @MonteroOnBoxing Tony Weeks was incompetent on that night, I agree, but I wouldn’t call him an all-around… https://t.co/e3gBrIqR9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IFCYipeS This game is so sick for when it came out, it had super jump juggle loops, dash cancels and OTG combos really early on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulZeise Offensively, they can hang around with a few of those teams. It all depends on if they upgrade their defense now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⛳️Lady Falcon golf team takes 1st 🥇in the Vega Tournament  🥈2nd individual Emmy Pitzer 🥉 3rd individual Kinsley Car… https://t.co/2KMlHSRlNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #MoreWomenInTheNFL on @tyltsports. More diversity is needed! https://t.co/aSeLW2PB6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have eaten many types of meat. And several of the same type of meat cooked slightly differently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: shhhhh go to sleep  Baby (through series of screams and grunts): yeah ok lmao  #parenting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Dear Gov. Newsom, this is not what you were elected for. The people of the state of California voted f… https://t.co/GXP8qNfX15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavtheRepublic @MAGAVoter @ToddGre94875758 @ElectWarren2020 If anyone is owed reparations it’s the indeginous peop… https://t.co/Mh1Vr7yvrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz Bill Griffith's graphic novel about his mother and 1950s suburbia; Wodehouse's Blandings books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub @Raiderdad63 Shouldn’t someone question the Mueller Investigation by now? Pretty much been a complete waste of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatrixTheHoes @Its_Just_TrevC Tyler Zellers uncoordinated ass smh. Naw Austyn rivers was real, can’t even hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComixBookGurl LOL I don’t recall seeing it but never really looked... If I would have thought this through yesterd… https://t.co/tUIi30rwRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaVinicky @wttw @capitolfax I love junk food, and I from South Carolina, but that was too much to watch in 5 minutes. I'm full!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @Dloading @EliasSports Russell is quickly turning into one of the better point guards in the NBA 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay. I've had my #IAmStorm fix in #AnthemGame. Time to actually try sleeping before work tomorrow... https://t.co/O0fKoDXf0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vbadillor @DeniseDresserG @SCJN Que antes las hacian cada año este las hace diario ahi esta el cambio eramos del t… https://t.co/ceDVaUlKtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leonardo DRS is hiring in #Dallas, TX! Read about our latest #SupplyChain job opening via the link in our bio: Buyer II]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedbauer2003 @JimCanto @nplusg @MrLexJay @kavita1010 @ScottOntiveroz @MattJ_O @joshmccormack @matageli… https://t.co/Hq2diWrC9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsherAngel i wish i had ya life always staying busy an meetings homework a good relationship with parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronBechtel @itzzdyl Shut up, you’re just mad he’s smarter than you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out walking with Tom Baker/Doctor Who #doctorwho #tombaker #dogwalking #tolucalake #losangeles #hollywood @ Los Ang… https://t.co/CoHiADCx3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @AnavidReyesKVUE the good things is I have the day off and I don’t have to be in the traffic today, am… https://t.co/WsMaS8hwCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_reliable1 The hate is real. We gotta hey you out if middle/coastal GA whew chile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @PeteButtigieg @jaketapper Too many think that guy people live in another kind of world, we don't,  we're j… https://t.co/ludEsTAiul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHemmer If she doesn’t understand the words she’s saying, she’s not smart enough to do her job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia's own #GreenNewDeal exposes what Dems really care about, and it's not the environment… https://t.co/KHUHD1yoRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @MaryOsb36485285 THE DEMS.CLOSE TO BRINGING CIVIL WAR NOW IN USA.WE HAVE SOMANYSICKFOLKS ONHILL.DESTORYING USA DAYBYDAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshly acquired from @greatlakesbeer is As Far Back As I Can Remember NEIPA with an impressive yet unobtrusive 6.4… https://t.co/i20Gihqlo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @shaunking It is an absolute shame that such an individual represents the most beautiful part of North Carolina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN LOL..  Bernie is nothing if not a consistent hypocrite.   He Let Hillary make him her bitch.  Now “I swear I w… https://t.co/8KUVCdV0ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Take your coward daddy down there. Show how America fights for humanity and freedom.  Oh wait, that… https://t.co/ONubyCR4sB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#greatfriends #greatbeer @ Barley Forge Brewing Co. https://t.co/9SLB2VeRMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump @VP One criminal Republican praising another criminal Republican.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, why i pick the mad early flights? (@ Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport in Arlington, VA)… https://t.co/jiLdDTLkT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apenitas, pero sí entró FG @adevaldes @pepesegarra @EnriqueBurak @kikegarciaadn @CarnerosUnidos https://t.co/OfJuzp6XAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ApexReyna You live in Texas and my first option is @Blackrosee_29 👀 lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey we all fall every once in awhile! 😂😆this was to funny not to share!  #snowboarding #goodtimes #redlodge #winter… https://t.co/5u1ZOxKW50]]></document><document><![CDATA[PinkAboutIt  ⭐ ⭐ ⭐ @Pink_About_it  5h5 hours ago A man sold his testicles to help pay for Bernie Sanders Campaign -… https://t.co/AlQ880B46n]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss @yankago The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVE… https://t.co/vOsEA0Up32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art being made right in front of me ☺️ shoutout to @Valstand916 for being part of the progress #music #sacgrown… https://t.co/slUWZMPX8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koedesu De acuerdo 👍, creo que somos zelderos  de ❤❤❤❤, Ahora solo falta esperar brother. https://t.co/ZXpaCKSgZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vinny_Giarmoleo @CraigCustance @RickCarpiniello Let me get this straight Dallas isn’t resigning zuc. Dallas isn’t… https://t.co/lXDyH4SO0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat Reading and writing are overrated. Also tell her ‘rgrgrgrgahagagahattsys’ 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trashcurryback @SportsHackCA @tev_bands don’t get me wrong, i WANT it, but it won’t destroy me like 2016... i crie… https://t.co/MgETir1ADJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had it on draft and in a can. Both super delicious. A lot more sediment in this one, obviously. - Drinking a WTF (W… https://t.co/ezchZ0jsWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning "brothers and Sisters" Represent with your head up high ...bring that  flavour amd hype to the RUGBY.… https://t.co/AO0vfycNYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer @AOC Do some research and learn something, Google Grand solar minimum, earth catastrophe cycle, without F… https://t.co/M489Zv0HGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurrenSy_Spitta x @wizkhalifa  🤙🏽x🤘🏽 #2009Tour https://t.co/ZfKvNPOXcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeCoinExpert @WanderingWare @RTB_Dutchy @GoodXrp @BobbiMarquez197 @kingblue_XRP @Hodor @research_omega… https://t.co/hjo7PInrem]]></document></documents></author>