<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@marybBamafan Followed you back!  Thanks, friend.  Have a safe weekend!  👮🏻‍♀️👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[what we're witnessing today is more voices getting to define what is and is not acceptable social behavior, and FOR… https://t.co/DNcF8Mvwrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last month my MIL let my dog out and she was missing for TWO hours but a nice neighbor got her. Tonight she let out… https://t.co/9QqfcmBJQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syndicalisation à la #SQDC : après les requêtes par succursale, les régionales | https://t.co/804vXTkJ5q #cannabis  https://t.co/zV0hQaQQgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/MuTIqmFYK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #AcademyAwards Show Sucked.  I felt awards were given to those not deserving, as not to offend anyone, and to t… https://t.co/cX5nUWui9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMIContent We have found that our website visitors spend 6x more minutes with our long-form multimedia storytellin… https://t.co/r2Q2Ubcj7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best show ever Fluffy thank you 💕will never forget the 16 shots of yager and one shot of tequila and the amber alerts 😂😂 @fluffyguy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told bae that I was gonna leak his nudes &amp; he said he was gonna call the police on me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest obsession:apple slices dipped in peanut butter. Living for our apple slicer 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo You are advertising the deadly poison ROUND UP on your site? How much are they paying you?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fordham University confirms Cohen Testimony that Trump threatened Legal Action to keep his Grades a Secret - https://t.co/gmjGRoL8jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay safe and warm today on this SNOW Day! ❄️☃️❄️ #crystalcouturebrides @ Crystal Couture Bridal Boutique https://t.co/sxNROWscHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPRmelissablock I’ve gotten “why don’t you just let dad do the cooking?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word to Cheyenne check on target then check on Cheyenne ughhhhhhhhhhhh moms do better for just jazzy so she can do… https://t.co/JyvYBpr51J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsD517 @muse For my #WIP, I have a lot of muse in my playlist, imagine dragons, avenged sevenfold, 21 pilots, bla… https://t.co/O56Os0FTGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serena_is_small You can have mine. It came today, full force like a bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenpollock20 @PaigeKeselowski Oh my gosh, the twins would love these ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[my last boy would tear me apart, but he’d never wanna split a ting with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseAnnDeMoro And it's important that this is mentioned.  Because we need to focus EARLY on the distractions throw… https://t.co/drFtdFLmyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[A glimpse of the future of Houston libraries https://t.co/9SmDiqooOw via @houstonchron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1truckerandy You got that right! I’m damn good (and proud) of it, too! 😉 @cliett_eric is one spoiled Daddy ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta leave in less than an hour for school and still have to read a chapter and write a thesis statement. Ahh! 😩🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scholarships aren’t just “something community Foundations do,” they are critical to our missions serving our commun… https://t.co/7PLuJizeIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I REALLY want to get a job for the summer that’s gonna pay $800+ idc how hard the labor might be. I really want a new car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorota_pytel @pigmalion55 najbardziej prawdziwego PRAWA i prawdziwej sprawiedliwości!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QimamFellowship تم التواصل معي عبر الجوال مع العلم أنني أدرس خارج المملكة ولا يمكنني معاودة الإتصال، هل يمكن التواصل عبر الإيميل؟ وشكراً]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bitred @OfficialJonZal As long as he keeps yapping it up to FOX don't you worry 💯✔🎯😎😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The line to venerate St. John Vianney’s incorrupt heart wraps around @olacathedral! Thanks @KofC for being this gif… https://t.co/VY9S3FsOZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate amaretto as much as I hate cilantro, so Nick got this. There is a subtle almond note initially but the sour/… https://t.co/bjf76oH8iV]]></document><document><![CDATA[... In my opinion, when it comes to truly breaking the continuous rule of the billionaires boy club machine that ha… https://t.co/AX9oLXyF4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow are my arms cashed today! Still sore from yesterday’s Chest/Triceps and today I added Back/Biceps along with th… https://t.co/qNkq7641DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[scholarship essays about the future are so bullshit lmao let’s talk about how bad I’m struggling right tf now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilkim1971 @alysa_apollonia @skipandpete @ann2156 @ki_native @quisqueyana1102 @benzie55 @Tia_Lunes @Sammy_Markle… https://t.co/Hby6cspLBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The notes Kenny G is playing spell out "I'M TRAPPED! PLEASE GO GET HELP I CAN'T MOVE!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather headlines: High wind warning tomorrow through the day #KDKA #KDKAwx @cbspittsburgh @ KDKA-TV | CBS Pittsbur… https://t.co/nmc8fs5qiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyBredeweg Im here and will be watching it when it aires for the West coast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealCamilleG I am sure meeting you made her day!!  You are such an inspiration ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed that I don't believe it’s true...  what a beauty dream... I AM AMONG THE FIVE BEST IN THE WORLD,  the be… https://t.co/U3wdv3cX1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico @ABlueTsunami And this is the major problem with TWITTER BULL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t silence her! She is accurately speaking for millions of minorities that fear for their lives on a daily basis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkolin If you drive a car around Central Florida, you aren’t surprised with this growing number. 🚗🚚🚛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I crave this simple dish as much as any meat one: smoked julienned bean curd in black bean sauce with punchy scalli… https://t.co/imP5mMJvvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeking examples of diet-related  myths from #health #nutrition world for upcoming public talks (myths and how to d… https://t.co/F6te1CHgIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarboo Happy #Caterday to my friend Kimbo and Sue 😸with love from Debbie and RIP Cinnomon!!❤️❤️You are one beautiful kitty Kimbo!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get the split! @fargoforce hosting @blckhawkshockey again tonight. Hoping for a home win for Sanford Children… https://t.co/rsMFepMrEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3IeNAuQlOi  @rodstewart  "Do Ya Think I'm Sexy?" 💖👄💖  #GlamSunday #glamrock  @CrisRefuse… https://t.co/CQxYmsadfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a great dinner! I am here to support the NFB of California San Fernando Valley chapter! (@ Chipotle Mexica… https://t.co/Cg4LWQkqb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL! @swimone visited Akron, OH (@IPROMISESchool) and I wasn’t there 😭  Shoutout to one of my lady-boss heroes fo… https://t.co/CXbe6reH4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBuckley There are no words to describe how blessed I feel to have worked with you.  You gave everything and t… https://t.co/jVL8medz6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not going is off the table @BBFan57 ! 😂 We decided on our way to KC to add a jaunt to St. Loius on the fly. Best ro… https://t.co/NwDmfXEPPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Lafferty crossed 5K. Time 00:30:35, pace 09:51 min/mile, est. finish 11:35 am https://t.co/Z2zdHBa7Bu #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the senior bishop of the ecclesiastical province must take charge of the proceedings against the archbishop. T… https://t.co/pPeTRJG2Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeauxRemy Nervous is an understatement, my body and voice were just shaking beyond my control]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really just wanted to get laid before I went home but someone was being a little bitch 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurplerainWendy @HavanaSims Excellent, I'm so happy for you. Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super, crazy grateful 🙌🏻🙏🏻☀️☕️ #wakeMEup #weekendmornings https://t.co/GDYHfp4b4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to be afraid or disrespect myself but underestimating what and who I am EVER again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ApacheTomcat @XGalmiche Quels abîmes d'imbécillité obtuse! Quelle crétinerie satisfaite d'elle-même! Inouï!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“At its core, much of spatial mismatch stems from residential and land-use patterns. A long-term strategy for addre… https://t.co/MYSH3D9lty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @realDonaldTrump @nickgillespie The Lord has blessed our nation!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@severson_j @DrGlendaHorner @TonyaDixon0221 @BDeporter @CyFairStaffDev Congrats!!! Those are some leaders I love!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this funny there's something wrong with you. #hilarity #tee-hee #grin #funny https://t.co/2iTtGz3Tcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m mesmerized in every way You keep me in a state of daze... Can you name this song? It’s one of my all time favor… https://t.co/88hrEbzKCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[LITERALLY SO PROUD OF MYSLEF JUST TAPPED THE ENTIRE SONG OF SICKO MODE 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZLive Raquel needs to shut up. She sounds so obnoxious especially when talking about the Tyga incident. Her mout… https://t.co/fWr14lnks3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Injustice in the so called land of the free https://t.co/ZE68P1uFLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three more keychains ready to list! #resin #resinmolds #resinart #resincasting #diy #witchy #keychain #ocean… https://t.co/20A8qYs4ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out all those YPs!! We ARE the Future of Water. @awwa @WEForg #futureofwater #WaterYPSummit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano But Alyssa you said you were going, so GO!  Go to work, oh that’s right you haven’t worked in a long… https://t.co/EGbNFUGIAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuganFOX46 @FOX46News Super disappointed in any local club owner who would let Mayweather in, much less promote a… https://t.co/iqyhQzx6jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink My daughter love all the Junior B Jones books,it’s about a young girl and school problems mostly and they are really funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE GREAT I AM Gospel Cycling class has ONE BIKE OPEN 7am @5StarrPilates #fitnessministry #greatiam #tgia #cycling… https://t.co/HTq9xCORCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the woman at Culver's thought I was insane. I just want cheese curds with BBQ sauce and don't ask quest… https://t.co/jYJC74fMpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Results are slowly trickling in @balloontowers @McMullanElem #MustangSTEM https://t.co/7LbOr98K4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Job Jenny Cha State Representative! #SISD https://t.co/jGcs8ewEzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people above me are truly loud 24/7, 365. They literally could not work or go to school. There’s no reason I sh… https://t.co/NtPuHl9HV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. Airstrikes Kill Hundreds in Somalia as Shadowy Conflict Ramps Up https://t.co/zYpvAQJQeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Undifferentiated-Androgynous. My scores are 56% masculine, 61% feminine. https://t.co/ktpIyCvRFA via @idr_labs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when Shamrock is feeling feisty and winks at me! This tends to happen when I have not run him quite enoug… https://t.co/SNesGpYQgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwornInChris This tweets only been up 16 minutes but I’m still surprised (and thankful) I’ve seen no let down memes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylornation13 @taylorswift13 @ELLEmagazine I’ve never been so excited to read something... I say every time I get… https://t.co/beEBfwUOM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitesow1 Ah, of course!  Laughed to myself as I read the Major McDonald episode last night, had forgotten he fell… https://t.co/Ge80OuYhPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello from the Castro 🏳️‍🌈   The LGBTQ+ people in my life have been some of the most influential, special ones to m… https://t.co/CJS9u93SJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on, spring! @ Armour Hills, Kansas City, Missouri https://t.co/fmjMKrQmLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I want more than just a Monday? 🗓 . . . ❣️Who are you crushing on this #mcm 😍😏 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/RuokmpLupc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro this whole time i thought i had work at 9 and i don’t start till 11 and I’m wide fucking awake 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grainfreekitchn Bobbi Brown works best for me! I can't find an eyeliner pencil that doesn't run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our government is in shambles, people are living without, and you’re on your phone bitching to @KevinLyman about th… https://t.co/6yp0zyD9Z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibbySaysSo I can promise you the town is a million times better than the book.  I am not a fan of the book, but I… https://t.co/PJwwq73mwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGinaP I agree with you about Jordan I would be fine if the character left but would that mean Donald would have… https://t.co/KMMZtjvGI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PilgramTraveler @Deshklok @religulous The Bible has some strong words about lying. Making such claims, having to l… https://t.co/QFjNJiXpIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will we ever get a more perfect scene? I just don’t know how 🥰💫🏹🕊🔥😍 #canem @erkencikusdizi https://t.co/CIUsQxvKi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanCohen24 @PadresGeekster @Theiconicpod @botemplin @jparis_sports Just listened!!! Awe Ryan! Hope to see more of you dancing! 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaileyMarkowski @AdamJarvis30 @INDIEWASHERE Interesting https://t.co/AMgx20UB6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me and del go see captain marvel*  *gets in car after after leaving theater*  *starts car*  Del: "Well, I wish was… https://t.co/o7xsVl2oOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Knockadoo I hope her family find answers a horrofice story...shocking...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choctaw_flag @kenzey_michelle Congratulations, @kenzey_michelle   So proud of all you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf am I such a sensitive bitch?!?!?! Like why can’t I just let things be!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @OmarHamada We need to pray this doesn’t happen. Life is a precious gift.]]></document></documents></author>