<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Has anyone asked Jared aboiut his meeting with the crown prince and his outcome of his peace mission in saydi]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯% agree!!! My former “unskilled labor” jobs have taught me just about everything I know now .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man .... at this point, I think I’m the delay voodoo queen or something lol OF COURSE the first flight of the day i… https://t.co/Tdck1REEGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this guy was black, Hispanic or Muslim it would be on all cable stations non stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing this amazing experience of a ride big time... 😭  #avatarsofpandora #pandora #animalkingdom #dak #wdw… https://t.co/s1NUOgx6C9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking out #oscar #gowns for the #redcarpet I’m hosting is #serious #business! Maybe you can help, #comment below… https://t.co/QoYvoUBUNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @IvankaTrump If they follow her "American values" we'll all be considered low-lifes! Class is someth… https://t.co/LTJFzBJQ13]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how much a song can sound like someone. It’s like Grandpa is sitting next to me❤️ https://t.co/eWeW8Gqja6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a scientific fact that actively trying to be quiet increases your actual sound output by 125%]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not know if there is a person on this Earth who is happier than Brady Tkachuk 🤣🤣 https://t.co/apzGhwfr9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegint aquestes opinions ratifiquen q anem pel bon camí. #JuntesSomMésFortes #JuntesPerCatalunya]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: *signing into tan at the gym*  Planet fitness employee: aRe YoU a BlAcK CaRd MeMbEr https://t.co/bWZBoE8TY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point all of my friends have tagged me in at least one Jonas Brothers reunion post and I have never felt mo… https://t.co/WNx7pHe8gA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure there are worse places to have a random, unprovoked anxiety attack, but having one at the top of a ladder… https://t.co/sjD4NHNF7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’m having major Nola fomo right now so I’m just gonna go cry in a corner]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an entire class of man who insists that what they want is a smart woman but what they're really after are… https://t.co/zOvartOjdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this equestrian ring stack. ✨ All rings available in my gallery, or via DM. The snaffle bit ring is on my webs… https://t.co/e6fjm0xj5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuretoneMusic Would it be possible for @the_nique, Georgia Tech's student newspaper, to be credentialed for a pres… https://t.co/9dxfXkxX0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruteVillain @DLoesch I have had my run in's with the law and unless you break one ain't nothing they can do.  And… https://t.co/6pZrUjyYJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try it.... it’s amazing!!!!! #lobster plus lobster design @ Racks Fish House + Oyster Bar https://t.co/KI8ZulcVCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vancitydan @ArthurAtkinson0 @DarleneArsenau1 @suepeac @KodeshPendragon @gtlem @Picard_Resists @Pepperfire… https://t.co/uQP44tTJt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy Step by Step Drawing Tutorial for Kids #humor #tee-hee #smirk #playful https://t.co/E5cNZT5Dhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One dead, 12 injured after Venezuelan soldiers open fire in clash over humanitarian aid delivery at Brazilian border https://t.co/ZlxzInFU9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justme10000000 @AuschwitzMuseum @haaretzcom @arielsobelle Gross is not a historian. He finished education as a soc… https://t.co/S1EBChNSF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek If we suffer another large scale terror attack it will be at the hands of Trump. If this reporting is cor… https://t.co/7iqEHFr1fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[u know u got a bad grade when your professor hands back your assignment folded hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Proof that Biden is too old to be president. I like Biden but he must be losing his mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my 3 year olds was telling me today, “MiMi went to heaven. She’s better now! Heavens so far away tho”  I almost cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great piece. Reminds me of the research we are doing in 2nd grade classrooms on civic perspective taking.… https://t.co/ybESyx1h2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay pissed as hell Anthony Hopkins (right?) just SCREAMED at Brad Pitt after like 20 minutes of people only whispe… https://t.co/UDM1MoW21E]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing that deserves to be my background other than Danny is the Jonas Brothers. They took the cake for now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allieleeperry @lisafischer72 @Skyhawk566 @charliekirk11 @IlhanMN Dear Alli, Qualification is no more matter  for e… https://t.co/pKWMOHmbwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve washed my face for like 5 days Straight why don’t I look like I have a $1,000 skin care routine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me smile! 😄 keithjhess #tlwnbmu #roadtrip @ Oklahoma https://t.co/1qtwvuVclF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookOut if I order a hamburger that means no cheese. This is the 5th time you have put cheese on my HAMBURGER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Target tries to capitalize on Victoria's Secret's struggles #Affordablebras https://t.co/oEzuO4TeUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my real captain @bdriscoll16 hope it’s a good one cap🎈🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaby_915 I regretted wearing makeup that day and I still can’t watch it without crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcolonna @Angels Good to know where the bad seats are, we're looking at catching Fridays game! I'll have to ma… https://t.co/WKeDes7SkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite daydream has a new story arc and I’d really appreciate it if nobody talked to me for a few days so I ca… https://t.co/joUOd7jkFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateZelaya ok this was like not a thing when I went there everyone said hi to each other !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMSISD_CTE @boswellhs @TCJLS I was so proud of the whole group and so happy I could be there to support them!… https://t.co/bo2nwopj2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. Albert Brooks is brilliant, hilarious and a genius. He elevates any film he stars in and I’m obsessed with all o… https://t.co/8kRM1vRmq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LearningIn206 @Hahne_Elyse At my 16 yr. olds conference his physics teacher thanked me for raising a kind and resp… https://t.co/Lbalgz1AD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarpad Yep but we here on the East Coast have 15 more minutes of SPN... #runpadsrun #SPNFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ARGUMENTS FOR MORE FOREIGN WORKERS: -"There aren't enough skilled Americans to take the skilled jo… https://t.co/rfeb4z68EG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsmeg Bitch same. Her voice is annoying and she comes off as bitchy. Well he does look like a punchable chipmunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix yall needa add more filipino movies im enjoying this way too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m deeply regretful that I missed the casting call to be #FakeMelania.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Hunter Padberg on making Honorable Mention All League!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad wanted to buy me some twist boots before my bday and there wasn’t any in my size and he’s so mad about it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[TALENT CALL: Attention Models, Designers, Artists, Performers! THE ART GALA PHILLY 2019 auditions will be held on M… https://t.co/fTSi628jKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_weinberg @SalesGravy @TheSalesHunter @iannarino You friggin’ rock and I love @SalesGravy for introducing us!  Thank you, @SalesGravy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost no #recycling @bushhoustoninternationalairport #yougottabekiddingme #wastemanagement #wakeup please @ Housto… https://t.co/fcYWQVk9Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe I was going to pick up my car at a lot after the show. The lot was closed. Just about the time I was… https://t.co/Q8adfEwsN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my back really hurts as if i’m a 91 year old woman. daang i’m only 19 i shouldn’t feel like this🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyyahlong I tried the whole “understanding” shit but these niggas forget who the fuck I am and what the fuck I br… https://t.co/XSGqqTmw9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME: Now that my health is better, nothing can stop me from flying to Buffalo on Thursday to see ⁦@arkellsmusic⁩ !… https://t.co/qRpFjh9P93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarieCallenders 1. Scrumptious flavors 2. Flakey crust 3. I don't have to make it .14 makes my tummy happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Nature is attempting to thwart my efforts no matter my location (Seattle, Los Angeles, Phoenix, etc.). Keepi… https://t.co/5Ifj1trUi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[SES...Grade 1 and 2. Book reviews are coming. Where can we share them?!? @21rncrossi @welvlucy @raeannelocke… https://t.co/Z3I5zbjh4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Wow Wow I pushed my button for @hannahkaymusic! #TheVoice https://t.co/a4qZj0Igxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[She pointed out that someone used a prop! She did not say the person’s name! DO NOT STRIKE FROM RECORD!  #CohenTestimony #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDeplorablegirl @elam_christie My three nephews are out there on the streets every day please pray for them! 💙💙💙🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simply_malcolm BITCH if I say I’m under the weather I’m under👏🏽the👏🏽weather👏🏽 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookreviews #bookboost #readme #circleofbooks #kindlebooks  Good morning. Another nasty and ICY day i… https://t.co/Bk9Fh9EkFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are Easter baskets at age 20 a thing??? Cause I want the @jamescharles palette and @JeffreeStar brush/sponge set in mine. 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never get my regrettable tattoo removed because if you also don’t feel regret when you see me naked then that… https://t.co/05hnSl587h]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But you, you're everything to me And I, I would die for you” 🎼🌺 https://t.co/9U8TtuxcMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole “I live where you vacation” thing is all fun and games until you try to see how much a flight home costs… https://t.co/BHbTXEXXKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[thriving rn bc my mom just trash talked my brother when an OU player missed a layup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Charlotte, NC? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Part Time CNA… https://t.co/2udBWCOuGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to go out tonight but I’m so tired and I still gotta go to Petco 😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[FULL All In with Chris Hayes has a rep from Democrats he told him that some republicans didn’t even show up for the… https://t.co/tWIg8uqpCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REPEALNFA1776 @cmonnnbri @canabienze @inihelene @iamcardib @DeannaRose614 https://t.co/um5TEqrb0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t have a Valentine how about donating a book to the program Riding to Read for Jaylen?!.....Ask me how? https://t.co/zMX7irlNcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the show on the strip. #notabaddayattheoffice @ The Mirage Hotel and Casino https://t.co/rQC0SyHQbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I observed groups of students demonstrating what they know about shapes, counting, sorting, categorizing, com… https://t.co/fTCsF2KsOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m actually gonna have to watch Frozen because y’all have added my favorite season into this next film.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWBChicago @JussieSmollett Good!  It’s about time they began recovering money on wasted investigations. This certainly isn’t the first!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get so offended when someone shazams my music instead of gassing me asking me what i got playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW so they really killed Clarice just like that??? As if she wasn’t the baddest bitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[THX FOR PROTESTING WITH ME THAT ONE TIME Amy Schumer and Emily Ratajkowski https://t.co/lF7ZCl9jYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to worship with the corporate body of Christ. @ Westover Church https://t.co/OCrSAfNue5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband right here 😆  Not literally, but literally 🙃 https://t.co/BDXn40Cw2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #ElSegundo, CA #Retail job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Associate Manager, Ma… https://t.co/ne5X58Vulv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to help you find the perfect place to call home!  Call me!  @URRealtorKendra @renrealtyok   #realtor®… https://t.co/e6xwhxCn0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floralfleet it definitely depends on what u wanna study but i know that my actual experience in business/fashion w… https://t.co/gUIovNthoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the wait? You better believe it! ❤️ I don’t want to JUST make love. I want to rub our souls against each othe… https://t.co/dPuXLOQ2ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a God who says we are enough. Just as we are. #michelecushatt #findrest #devotions https://t.co/urCbgR1C8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanamongeau stay strong beautiful. You’re a fucking queen. Remember that. Love you 🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO dan was a big ass nerd when he was little and he’s trying to tell me he was “popular” in elementary school. I… https://t.co/GIMLqR5hW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY mom wouldn't. It'd be ME.  My slogan would be, "Kick ass. Take names. Chew bubble gum. And I'm all out of bubble… https://t.co/h093CqfAAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i heard the dam is at flood level so i hope jason isbell is prepared for whatever happens when percy priest breaks open wide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that anyone needs another reason to appreciate @NateSilver538...but I found one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I look on the internet for the new GOT trailer and every day I am disappointed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t washed my hair in 3 days. Thought you guys would like to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor Dianne Feinstein responded to the housing shortage crisis by making it harder to build housing. She downzoned… https://t.co/d4Bl3jfBAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[eu sou mt burra pqp, fui inventar de fazer as unhas 4h da manhã, derrubei o esmalte todinho no chão]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m thankful for:  ✨ kids that are easy but fun to babysit  ✨ hugs and snuggles  ✨ generosity]]></document></documents></author>