<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[SO FUCKING CHAOTIC RIGHT NOW..  SHOULD OF LEFT THE WALL UP..... IDK WHO OR WHAT TO BELIEVE... 💔😢   WHOS GOING TO THE BAR TONIGHT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually it was a few million morons and an electoral college. Not HRC but instead voters or lack there of. Clearly… https://t.co/ZYO8v0IVuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson My breakfast....2 cups of coffee and an Aleve.  Every morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1sansnom Ok ! Alors pkoi donc inviter la censure ?  C’est vilain et aussi rétro que Moïse]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #OklahomaCity, OK, check out this job: https://t.co/omxN3VNX2Z #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having kids and being pregnant makes your bladder weak #idcwhatanyonesays #momsknow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notorious_exg Gurl you shouldn’t worry there. You’re a sassy blonde from Texas, intelligent, gorgeous, funny and g… https://t.co/6hGYa5X0MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes along with all the documented evidence he brought! Has got nothing to lie about at this point unless he wants M… https://t.co/1nMaxqYwhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[why did I draw Alas! when there were so many other f@tt birds to choose from!! I keep forgetting things exist until… https://t.co/JfgGZV8htl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#robertmapplethorpe #louisebourgeois #guggenheim à Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum https://t.co/HmU14J1l2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I say something? Trump is only looking for ways to expanded his interests. He's done it with other people's, ot… https://t.co/SFVZw7UwdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odyssey158 @GinaPustor123 @LHeraguemi @SonjaNi41294318 @Goddestofhunt @yolande0218 @LiseNilsson2 @ElenaFadeeva3… https://t.co/vSs2KKMMVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady I was adoring your hair and my 9 yr old daughter looked over my shoulder and yelled, "MAKE ME LOOK LIKE THAT RIGHT NOW."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also want to state that if our softball community doesn’t come together and work as one to grow the sport beyond… https://t.co/kyaUH8ITCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look how big the babies are getting and are getting the wingercizing down 🦅🦅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump IVANKA YOU SPENT THE LAST TWO YEARS WALKING AROUND THE WHITE HOUSE NOT DOING VERY LITTLE.  ALL YOU ARE… https://t.co/IML0FaxBFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[forever graced by the love of the best momma there ever was ❤️ https://t.co/ELfMgESqJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back from an intense and productive QA Conference with a renewed focus and drive!   Time to get on board or change… https://t.co/CADExMz5GC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Girl Power this International Women's Day♀️💪❤️. @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/HGKhbNFWHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow that performance by Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper was out of this world! #amazing #AcademyAwards2019 #AStarIsBornMovie #Shallow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun and inspiring event! #americanbirkebeiner #birkie #northwoods @ Hayward, Wisconsin https://t.co/acutKaPreu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @HillaryClinton No Ed, he doesn’t! Hillary colluded w the Russians.  Hillary SOLD 20% of the United Stat… https://t.co/G9Pq8Qcrwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sk8rb0i me when I was half naked and trying to get dressed while seducing ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be safe out there. The Senate took time to honor the courage and bravery of first responders. Thanks for keeping us… https://t.co/AlhkLzK26j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art is whatever and wherever you want to create. @ New York, New York https://t.co/A9od18OcEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to you straight from the shower .... @Jeremih https://t.co/iSoo7yepUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickhogan4real is the best at taking 7pm naps and then waiting for me to wake up with him from midnight - ??? 👀 bu… https://t.co/d9sZqMoQta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luutrn Yeah same here. I’m going to be at work and I’m asking my friends to help me but there’s no seating chart or info]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we celebrate the Firearms Training Center w/ @FairfaxCityPD @gmupolice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 9 is here!     - https://t.co/IY5fZW6bWu -   #songaweek2019 #saw19 #weeknine #create #evaporate #pop  To hear… https://t.co/V3bhZXX9bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family and I are on a diet and this is how it’s going... 🌚😭😅 #weeatingair2019 so we can look good #2020 @eazyfbby… https://t.co/85Xj46Tdb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tigerlilyg1rl She can go fuck herself. She’s not good enough for you b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made this piece with a touch of Swarovski for my customer!🤗 https://t.co/AmsaKH8ZCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where's Astrid? X•III•MMXIX #Duendes #DuendesDelValle2019 en Auditorio San Pedro https://t.co/U45HIGjVXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKJ65 @realDonaldTrump Cheetolini is the most hated person in America. He knows this. It makes him crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is Endometriosis Awareness Month!   Are you a lady that is in chronic debilitating pain? Go seek help from yo… https://t.co/Wl0MV7BZzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[instagram got @kyliejenner &amp; her @kyliecosmetics #💰#👌 #😉 - #Entrepreneurs #Kardashians #KylieJenner -… https://t.co/og2gDxnhSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Healthcare: being treated like a ping-pong ball being batted back and forth between a PCP and ER, but they… https://t.co/SUyMWRYFEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my babygirl and I can’t wait to meet her🥰 but I really wish she didn’t  choose 6 am to use my organs as punching bags.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Who is pulling your strings, lady? Whi is @SpeakerPelosi 's puppetmaster? Who is she afraid of? Is someone thr… https://t.co/fcrXZTUNVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#womancrushwednesday #humpdayhotness Repost from jessietfitness Sunshine and shadows ... ... Have a great day 🖤 ...… https://t.co/Kwi316wed1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a wrinkle forming across my forehead. #cryptkeeper #old #thisis35 #timeforbotox #howdidthishappen https://t.co/8u0iYwKF2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaKeats2 @TsetlinEugeniya We missed you too @JessicaKeats2!  But hey, Twitter tells me you're tweeting from G… https://t.co/HdnWBSOL3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandon Elder / Brewhouse Rome Georgia @ Tennessee https://t.co/UfjqMaFVcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t get any easier telling maleena bye everytime she has to go back to Missouri  😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracieHD4002 @DeeClark2718 @LaurelHappe @jennysonflower @DAVIDZ927 @BedfordLeslie Thank you Tracie, it was a great get together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah B went home so I’m no longer interested in watching @TheBachelorTV @colton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swmrs_arg @swmrs El 28 de marzo los veo en San Diego y les voy a regalar un mate 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to emphasize that this picture is  displayed in my abuelitos home for all to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregariousOtter I didnt even state my opinion, it was just assumed I was anti trans or adversely affecting them to… https://t.co/y3RI3kBpDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like now I’m wide awake but I’m about to go to sleep  because social media not getting it done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLERR_BEFF I’m gonna come with you and cut out all the pages form the magazines and put a million holes in my bedr… https://t.co/4McwySYwu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJenBlais @DECAInc @GRHS_Stallions @Decastallion @MrsGilchristVB @leslielehner @GreenRunHOA @GRC_PTSA… https://t.co/cmLmFEnGuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Warriors were fully engaged against the Kings. They were in full competition mode. Starters weren’t benched. Th… https://t.co/5XOLw3QBQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been sent links to buy mardi gras themed shirts from four organizations and if you think i’m going to buy all… https://t.co/ew9n4lTPUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIMAGA4EVER @ArizonaKayte Active duty military service is not a social experiment arena.ANYTHING that could negati… https://t.co/Gh1PZ7p1mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second bath in 24 hours. Finally getting the hang of actually using the self care items I buy instead of just hoard… https://t.co/kjCJS8adSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickiMalacyne12 @skywriter35 @maydaymindy9 No vote for trump no vote for Bernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_millander What article?? You do realize your tweet makes wanting to read the article more appealing?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Disney I could really use a movie on how Tinkerbell and Peter Pan met. Please and thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally after over 10 years in Utah made the short trip out to Midway to see the #icecastles and spend time with fa… https://t.co/WFNQ1LCW0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @brendonurie I’m a #blues musician and fan, but #panicatthedisco and #twentyonepilots are my fave current… https://t.co/JcGbDGXztp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP So captured was the wrong word, they rescued them after they tried to killed them and gave them back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarySue This needs to be a T-shirt....@RashidaTlaib @AyannaPressley @AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Pres.Obama agreed with Pres. Trump &amp; the need to 🛑 STOP illegal immigration NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team finished 2nd Place out of over 20 teams. Julia Garcia led the way with a 71, Kennedy Tidwell 79, Brooklyn Wink… https://t.co/z50O9MjXkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmatera @missmac100 @united008 @HeckAwesome @jloughlin23 @CoyoteRidge_ @tishrich @MrPowley @Gameboydrew… https://t.co/wp2B60D69i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part of the night is coming home and watching @MASTERCHEFonFOX while eating raisins cause you’re too lazy to cook. 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I’d like to know. This argument is going way beyond a Woman’s Choice. It’s really gross.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ollie_Cycles @NJSPBA @bikejc @StevenFulop I... wish she called the cops!? Oh I can’t w this. Mayor @StevenFulop pl… https://t.co/h2zzZ5Ut37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonInga @SGottliebFDA 12 yrs ago I was bed ridden, hooked to a J tube, and required home IV fluids for meds,as… https://t.co/tWdCpGruOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideEagleRock My car alarm went off too, along with a couple of neighbors. Any clue where it struck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[dotdiggler throwing down in 10 minutes! #breakslife #breaks #breaksalldayeveryday #breaksprincess #breakslyfe… https://t.co/6gQdA0j123]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lazy I keep water bottles on both sides of my bed so when I wake up in the middle of the night thirsty af I don’… https://t.co/pNgak6FIkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aUSAFVeteran @BostonJimmy67 Your desperation is showing. When Trump goes down, will you be foaming at the mouth? https://t.co/Ba4ucbm0dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGodOfDeathA1 @BOLDBATHSHEBA @JusticeOfTruth @HealThePoisons @RealGodOfThDead Ffs... When you reach the furthest to sound smart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some random guy in deep ellum literally just poked my friend saying "ey Ariana Grande" 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham National Day of Prayer..I will be praying in focused prayer with all of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZuluBall #ZuluSocialAidAndPleasureClub #Frands #Framily #CarnivalBalls #MARDIGRAS2019 @ NOLA Convention Center https://t.co/0L8uWFdjuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this humorous there's something wrong with you. It's the Final Crisis of Capitalism, Charlie Brow… https://t.co/QGZpbWI3ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapping up from Dr. Bakshi: not everyone is burnt out. Not everyone will be burnt out. But how do we harness the “… https://t.co/wm5VDb9hRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CindyBusby fans — get ready! Set your DVR now because @cindy_busby stars in an all-new @lifetimetv movie TOMORROW,… https://t.co/XS4rav00rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FLAYFORALL #pistachiomilkshake #BobbyBlueBaconBurger #LoadedFries https://t.co/SsESUgLYHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd Just putting this out there...trump wants a Nobel Peace prize and we all know why!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please he would leave. He knows that. You are spreading #propaganda  disgusting coming from you. @TheJuanWilliams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have to be the world's biggest idiot. https://t.co/lOWnWuPmfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I JUST READ THAT THE DEMOCRATS HAVE HIDDEN A PROVISION IN THIS BUDGET THAT PREVENTS YOU FROM BUILDING THE WALL@realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol You should have said yes to #PeterLemongello. Nothing wrong with his voice or style.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ledbettercarly Don't apologize I think it's awesome, we are losing contemporaries way to early gonna start making my own 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is a 6th @DieHard in the works? We are all dying really hard over here.   -asking for a few million friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @RepMattGaetz Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Bar Number is 48962. He violated 18… https://t.co/ZBivxf3Wi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting my #hairjourney back to #naturalhair #curls #sheamoisture #coconut #hibiscus #silkprotein #neemoil… https://t.co/kPSAUC61cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldreiling Happy work anniversary Lar. HPJ is lucky to have you. What a career!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great show tonight ❤️ wishing I could be there but I'll be there in spirit I know y'all are gonna slay it li… https://t.co/zsksOU1EAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #chicago - the sky is on 🔥 this am.  #getoutthere @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/0PVpd25hIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I probably won’t because ya girl is most@likely gonna be stuck here til like 5 or 7. 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The largest financial  transactions  ever will be in a new Space Economy - there is no enough money to do that. thi… https://t.co/K6XW2LqI5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly didn’t have time for that extra assignment which I why I’m now taking my lunch at 3 o’clock 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[This image from @GayleKing's interview with #RKelly is going viral. Will you be watching @CBSThisMorning? I know I… https://t.co/KkNcfiJ3PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[just remembered a weird part of my childhood where I was very into Jenny’s downfall on gossip girl and secretly lis… https://t.co/4JGBDppB07]]></document></documents></author>