<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired of people saying no politics just basketball. It’s forever gone be politics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathmckenna @Bill_Morneau @DiLebouthillier More importantly the carbon tax will “tackle climate change” by lowerin… https://t.co/8muP1RglTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[hahaha to the people that just witnessed me dancing with my headphones in, just know i was killin shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nault_T Just let players be able to hire agents. Let them make deals with the schools. Sell jerseys and what not t… https://t.co/v3RAenteb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covington High student's legal team sues Washington Post https://t.co/pazhDtTLML #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7Jarek @JackPosobiec @MSNBC @mitchellreports Does anybody really watch CNN and MSNBC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lonerider off the front about 55 seconds at turn 3 final turn on lap to. Pro12 race @TeamHincapie https://t.co/WvfpGGgq1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikRacer Right there with ya, Rob! I know it can still snow or get cold, but springing forward means we’ve almost… https://t.co/C0GlOKBzCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @Seahawks idk what y’all are doing but make this man an offer we need a dominate RB to give Russ who has develop… https://t.co/BZ4qX9KuOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The amount of eccentricity in a society has generally been proportional to the amount of genius, mental vigour, an… https://t.co/Sk2MrzH5jW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dirt_McGirts @CFBHome @SBNation Yo Tyler I was looking at this and said the exact same thing. The dude must've bee… https://t.co/AffF4gxN5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, end of watch everyone goes home, safe...🚒👍🙏 @ DFD Company 8 https://t.co/kZGPMoBdAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingLRG_ Im gonna leave this here cause this is a dank meme and will prob get mad love so heres my music https://t.co/0VqB88Q6NB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget vote Hampton Oaks. Go to WTOP search kids and vote #WTOPClickForKids @HamptonOaksElem @SCPSchools https://t.co/UHy8ENgUjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i havent gone a day without being intoxicated in some way for more than a month i dont even know if im depressed anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendalSheppard @johnnybananas The more you tweet about him 🙄 he’s a spineless slug]]></document><document><![CDATA[تم تغيير علم اليابان عام ١٩٩٩  القديم هو الذي بالجانب الأيسر والاختلافات ١-أن القرص الأحمر يميل لجهة اليسار بنسبة ١… https://t.co/dsqGua0MpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Room so fire bro, I’m glad he put   it on the album, especially after it’s been leaked for a couple months]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottMc85081322 @TheTweetOfGod I said the same thing when the original Ronaldo and Ronaldhino were killing it but… https://t.co/7jmAhIT644]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day in the life. I guess if would be worst if we had boys!  #noonedrinksnfromthetaporbrita #essentia #deerpark… https://t.co/W0ERzRTI7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s_dickk Omg my one cat does the same thing runs to the door when someone comes here, meow at the door when it want… https://t.co/pzdga3B7HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cesar9H @eedu_1180 @cristianchigre @FIFAntastic @Alkebar Mentira, los compro todos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Voyboy Never had an experience like this playing solo and I’m around level 40. Head up Voy. We all love you #itsthekid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtbauer Going Lawlor. Muting the filter so I don't see #spoilers until I can see it on Youtube tomorrow (we don… https://t.co/so3LrlsBJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeZone3 Truth stings don’t it y’all suck nobody in the SEC can remotely stand UT fans you a joke and you are too slow to know it 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FUNimation @NickRekieta @iTunes @vicmignogna Hey! This is great news!   Now how about the FMA delistings? #DoWeNeedToGoDownTheList]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annevclark @onlxn “Only You, Tucker” by William B. Turner https://t.co/iAUKlJRORg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @danpfeiffer Sorry but you and I don’t see eye to eye on this one.😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGBTQ rights: @JulianCastro says he's been a vocal ally since his days on the San Antonio City Council. Backed poli… https://t.co/MM9dsNqjj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicadean Jessica, love your show and think you do a great job. But pet peeve here. Gotta tell ya, there is no “… https://t.co/gawkVCNJco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Real_RobRossi And Malkin is?  Turnover at blue is his calling card along with offensive zone penalties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exhibit a) Bike share more popular than TNCs in Sacramento.  Exhibit b) @sfmta_muni cripples SF bike share through… https://t.co/42evY4BT09]]></document><document><![CDATA[LV Samus - this Metroid / Louis Vuitton mashup is still available on my website https://t.co/xrEzWL1CwQ   - - -… https://t.co/DcRkC4DSQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamsEra I think he must be a pats fan cause that’s the only place winning super bowls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAP and NBA Enroll Stat-Savvy NBA Fans into New Reality TV Show: GM School https://t.co/GdGzDBXyHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better one handful with tranquillity than two handfuls with toil and chasing after the wind. Ecclesiastes 4:6 NIV https://t.co/4YF743SE9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to know Eric Cogorno, #golf teaching pro and rising #YouTube personality. https://t.co/RzUt4AfDAm… https://t.co/wjWNwwIOgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[PIAA second-round sked Tuesday for D-10 teams 2A girls: West Middlesex vs. Juniata Valley 4A boys: Hickory vs. Hunt… https://t.co/Ap9fiq0RG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okayylita I see how you want to start your career!! Proud of you family!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinamcbride @FabFitFun Any help I can be let me know!! Bring this person down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finance Twitter: Is there a good place (other than Bloomberg Terminal) to find relatively up-to-date bond pricing (namely Mexico)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JM_NTSMG @GusVillegas 😂😂😂😂  Así se ven mejor, chairos. Cuándo ya muestran lo poco que saben dialogar, lo mucho que… https://t.co/RnJbQRLKgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas Golden Knights ready for the desert. #mint400 #goKnights @ Freemont Steet expierence https://t.co/k3Rpurtsi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the U.S and the effect it’s having on kids 😭this is so sad kids should not have to worry about crap like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaOfCowards @SaintsForecast @AndrewJuge @NOLA_Fredo If we ever get one, Gayle should for sure draft Bill Vinovich]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pliny the Elder by Russian River Brewing Company @ Clarkville — https://t.co/mC1qIFkedA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prooney07 @BrianHowell33 @CUBuffsMBB Andy Enfield is going to be looking for a new job by Wednesday night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[they cloned this man yo, no way in just 9 days, brah come out lookin all weird n shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REALDJPREMIER you're one of the G.O.A.T s my man R.I.P Guru #realhiphop #rockthebellsradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danhendo Dan, can I offer my services. I can do art work. See if you like my ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@persistmom @ahmad_iran88 @mamashab @obgenetics @goodbyehan @realDonaldTrump By being the ONLY President to ever go… https://t.co/2gEQflivoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPardeeORG @realDonaldTrump In 2017, though the numbers were down, the total was 310,531 a combined number over th… https://t.co/slmmGBd8dI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redmcgraw1 @CNN Amazon's temporary job program for Long Island City real estate agents is now busted.  #AmazonHQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackalac87 @the_Shildt_Show The NL is completely missing the element of a competent human hitting 9th though. It’s horrible to watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unique #ValentineGift! Giving a #pianotuning in Maquoketa, Iowa!  Consider a gift card promising it after… https://t.co/buIOsBkfGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSM_Leffen Leffen is really the villain of the Smash Community oml lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAJackson Oh I’m definitely getting one when they’re back in stock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilosophyMttrs AI can’t grasp the verity of contextual relevance’s of brute data. You need to have embodied momen… https://t.co/Ea5CavaeJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darksideofshoes Here's some more coffee to replace... https://t.co/dQmcokm7L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odessa High defeated EP Hanks, 19-3, to close out the day. OHS stats: Skylar Herrera: 4-5, 2 1B’s, 2B, HR, 5 RBIs.… https://t.co/lGPmWLNUTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani The GSP-CONDIT-DIAZ series of Primetimes were some of the greatest segments in the sport. Some of the… https://t.co/k5jKMxERZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportingKC @Arsenal @Pedrrroooaaarrr Injuries derailed his European career somewhat, but he’s an American kid, and… https://t.co/0cuHqchW4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allisonjanney_B @KenyonCollegeVB Reminded me of your breakout Kenyon Alumni Bulletin cover from my year ‘98! I gra… https://t.co/weR70NJzmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Peace @NACMANews I’ll see you there! You should stick around for NAATSO since I’m hosting a break out session again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the days where Gymshark was a niche, respectable fitness brand as now it’s completely devolved into an overl… https://t.co/IMc76r0PSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they said college would open doors for you: https://t.co/lsGSO3S0Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[High key jealous the homie @mona_haydar was kicking it with @SnoopDogg the other day... https://t.co/kQVoZBuBVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be looking at Alexandria Rojas, the director of Justice Democrats, into why they are backing all 3 , @IlhanMN… https://t.co/owayfu1f01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fave films:  "Chulas Fronteras"  "The Watermelon Woman"  "Los Olvidados"  "My Own Private Idaho"  "Hoop Dreams"   A… https://t.co/unhj2Hc5zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so upset. i was literally waiting til thursday to post this exact tweet. i’ll grab the rosé, if you get the cel… https://t.co/LZqmICp7Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @USAHipster The brazen and ridiculous action of @TheDemocrats and their allies is exposing their plan for… https://t.co/1wWIC35r1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alancornett Stupid statement. How about, Duke is not nearly a top 5 team without Zion, it showed in every game the… https://t.co/1kHCcDPFt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chhoffma I like him and Cheeks. And still don’t really know the others]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  Time to finish this monograph I’ve been ignoring for the last two weeks!… https://t.co/c7hQ7sGjNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks @BLEmmerth The Manafort sentence was wrong for so many reasons… he not only broke, but tried to chea… https://t.co/csdWcoZ4vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 RINOS are worse than liberals . The Republipussies are afraid of liberals. They suck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finebaum @KySportsRadio @CFBPlayoff The aggy are a perennial 7-5/8-4 program with 1 Top 10 finish to speak of in t… https://t.co/hXMl5nELzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I right to feel sad that #sxsw is turning into more of a tech/film fest than a music fest? Or is it a good thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me (to my esteemed 19 year old co-worker):   "There's a fine line between overachieving and doing too much, and you… https://t.co/5TWFSIQREd]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNC Coach Roy Williams being assisted from court after receiving medical help for vertigo#coxsportsbroadcasting https://t.co/eBAcO6pPfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be classes in high school to help people understand when a conversation has ended]]></document><document><![CDATA[we are #forgiven in #Christ, in #Jesus given new #life in the #power of His #name  we are forgiven of our sin, our… https://t.co/Q3XhuYISv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newenergyherald @robotic_hands @JesseJenkins @jgownder @mattyglesias @_cingraham Re the first point, it's Germany'… https://t.co/7rLJwjrAWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I want POTUS 46, maybe even 47! There is no reason we should be stuck on 45!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @marklevinshow @marklevinshow allso disagree with you NewYork Slimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @pattirod55 @OutlawedMind @Dannaja64Danny @JaackSchitt @nuwriter @caruso_ric @alllibertynews… https://t.co/hcVlkAQcqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shaun Howell's art colored by me. His b'day was yesterday but I wasn't ready till today! #digitalart https://t.co/8tyAdNA4PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all,  Last week was hot garbage. I fell asleep at 8pm last night and just woke up. Let’s try again next week. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaynesLeanne @SaintEunans @USSAA1967 @AthleticsNI @irishathletics Thanks Leanne and to Joseph too.. tell them both good luck from me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add me on snap chat!!! Need more friends @ Kingsville, Texas https://t.co/yX6XkY3nAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[EFC does a throwback to Motown. #doubledowndetroit @ Little Caesars Arena https://t.co/d4F0LHOsKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wealth taxes should be targeted to debt reduction and military deployments (war is usually funded with debt). If we… https://t.co/kSV5aFAIH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Of course not! Not will there be! This will allow time to find something else to revert the focus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refused the smallpox vaccine when more people were dying from the vaccine than the disease. But, I did my researc… https://t.co/Qx2JTyFobt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hush the fuck up clown. Getting names to back you won’t do anything. Especially some washed up scientist no one giv… https://t.co/xpfOkN2uyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepCommandr stop watching Power Rangers and start watching super sentai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good friends are hard to come by, but I’ve been blessed to be able to refer to these guys as “homies” for quite som… https://t.co/Q8aF7LJxtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umrvision I didn’t read that far. Told you, I can’t follow these Twitter threads. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do the prepackaged salad manufacturers make kale taste so much like bacon? There is no bacon in the bag. Miracles exist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journalism is Legal in the USA This is not Putin’s Russia, bud @realDonaldTrump #TrumpTargetsJournalists… https://t.co/9bdxYRKjYR]]></document></documents></author>