<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This has been such an amazing weekend. My brain might just explode because of everything. I literally had to go buy… https://t.co/zVDthrDc7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building background knowledge and expanding vocabulary 😃 #cannoli #specialty #delicacy #escargot #region… https://t.co/R93gXRFzou]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does @itsjameskennedy have an English accent when his mom has a Jersey one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[now to figure out why https://t.co/bbiI26baho rewrites to https://t.co/EC7QJBsRbO instead of using the proxy pass i… https://t.co/sghcBgF5B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few images from my visit to @bponzbro for the #soloflights #oneperson performance #bicycleface by hanvanscivvy an… https://t.co/nBuqx7STFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenbcameron Haha 🤯☺️ I can’t wait to talk more about this w y’all!👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Donut Stress the Writing Conference” 🍩 Finally finished up our conferencing today. The kiddos are set to revamp th… https://t.co/sHiYZgRZT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brooke_Kambel Just finished it. It was good, but one of the saddest. Prepare yourself. If I wasn’t so tired right… https://t.co/e6TLLrMwQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews @GayleKing @CBSThisMorning You know you are caught.  You look guilty, not that that matters but you… https://t.co/1W7MUdS1EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Gentry Jr. makes 1 of 2 at the line, then gets a steal and goes the length of the floor. Misses layup but Mar… https://t.co/rrbdqgn2QM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would anyone vote against this? @RepSamGraves @RepAnnWagner @RepJasonSmith @RepHartzler @RepBlaine @USRepLong A… https://t.co/Q044l5p4WN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scaming real estate in progress, are we going to allow the American war criminals to continue? I am Presidential en… https://t.co/GFlscMUvC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DucktheRoofer I love it too. I listen all day. But live music is best. I really thought Powerman 5000 is a great s… https://t.co/ScPDo1llzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this Nwot. Worn once. Women's Karen Scott Shoes for $20 on OfferUp https://t.co/Svce5xdFky]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will literally take any of the top 15 winning this race right now EXCEPT Kyle Busch. #Daytona500 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t beat this sunset after a afternoon of rain #sunset #bayarea @ California https://t.co/ND2HkLzyYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganBattalion @BernieSanders when I first saw this I thought this was Bernie/Julian Castro a difference without a distinction I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have such a bad memory, during the week days I’m usually busy w work and class and other stuff, I always have rem… https://t.co/8F4BjgW5cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re all working away on the 27th floor of this building and didn’t see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the one to have rigged your Administration  &amp; your tweets show you are very conflicted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyzachariah @DispatchAlerts My voice didn’t carry back to Biz sooooo @jimweiker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJonCryer Really not a good idea for Falwell to compare Trump to Cesar so close to the Ides of March...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NrinderWard3 @djnontario Got stopped here on my scooter on Victoria St. On Thursday. Notice in front of Medical bu… https://t.co/IoHqFLTdPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Foster_1981 @AnthemRespect @DebbieJ66015887 @DonaldJTrumpJr Good article]]></document><document><![CDATA[Response to my comment @ NYT from another solver: This synthetic element is still yet to truly be investigated so m… https://t.co/a7soI7GI07]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need a week off work with my boyfriend and my best friends on a beach somewhere... is that too much to ask?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It will take longer than you think, but not as long as you fear.  Just get started, so things can begin compounding in your favor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for spring break... not because I’m going somewhere but because i get to do nothing again🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never related to anything more in my life. It’s so frustrating. And don’t even get me started on denim shorts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I qgree...nothing sticks to this guy and his approval is at 46%. I dont think mueller found collusion, as that hasn… https://t.co/CRBzALsDbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 John 4:7-9 Beloved, let us love one another.. If love is at the center for everything you do, you will succeed. https://t.co/hYvDpWX8qC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Martes💫 Disney Skyliner💕 es un próximo sistema de telecabinas que conectará Pop Century Resort de Disney, Art… https://t.co/ngpPEpCJJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Where does it fit in? Made necessary by the left's obstruction  on securing the border and refusal to lis… https://t.co/YTSAx0voPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDemumbrum happy birthday bb!!!! I hope you have an amazing day love u 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RODEOHOUSTON World Championship BBQ Competition. Cherry Chipotle BBQ ribs #SCAP #HLSR #HLSR2019 #ribs #BBQ… https://t.co/g2zQJO9HVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiPiekos @r_czarnecki jesteś tak ciemny, ze nawet pisma "obrazkowego"nie jesteś wstanie zrozumiec...ale cóż? ciemn… https://t.co/eSQ9GqCkai]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say the best things happen with no reason, and you are by far my favorite accident ♥️ I could say thank you a… https://t.co/q9o9EW4aaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[While y’all here, check out my reverbnation 🙏🏻  https://t.co/nzVAFGtzKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein These men are despicable and are probably taking bribes from the NRA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @LoriLMarcus She's from the religion of peace, she's a terrorist sympathizer, she hates Jewish people… https://t.co/EPeVScDj6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadHigginsISIT Lmao y’all gotta put Mike’s Secret Stuff down and play fair!! 😂😂 https://t.co/2ti7q5g2mW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jabeale Two-years? More like decades. Whenever a Republican is in office, the media suddenly awaken!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great interview with @delaneytarr by @rachelkleah https://t.co/L3Z26viEKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toni Braxton this Saturday can’t wait taking my mom and my aunts with me 👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's right Republicans.  We are behind our President 100%  Stay Strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @SpeakerPelosi @GavinNewsom Also vegs the question, how did you begin your plan.  $, clothing, pack, etc.  G… https://t.co/KSXiBYktYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beekaykayisok @Alaskacryptogi1 @HillaryClinton Fuck u does that answer your question? Ass hole I have A Medical de… https://t.co/AFOV68Ys2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NannaInie I mean, I think it’s a great business model! I ticked the box for photos on the registration paperwork—I… https://t.co/8UVA9qU6h3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#onset today with @ryanbodiefilms and #director @delastarling #keymua #makeup #shortfilm makeupandhairbymonique… https://t.co/vXfZePYu8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought one Saturday. It’s one of the best pieces of merch I’ve never seen a wrestler sell. Don’t sleep on these!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codypooch @jayme_hess @akcdoglovers Attendees who are competing and planning to attend. Be aware China has no anim… https://t.co/fySjcGXC4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver dropped me off at the airport and said “have a nice flight” I replied “you too” I guess it’s time fo… https://t.co/SMphqQQebe]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a law against parents who pull they kids edges out due to mishandling. That’s baby sis hairline for… https://t.co/HOsHlO9yt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your #NASCAR forecast in  Phoniex,AZ for Friday  H: 66° 🌤 L: 50° ☁ #AZwx https://t.co/1u82u2zfYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday morning mood 🔥 @picturesqueband @halsey @yungblud https://t.co/5JxbuCbGGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[felt good to float~ thanks for the beautiful day @loganapeters 🌊 https://t.co/jakxHIpCRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[*James Charles films a video with anybody*  “Oh my God you guys, I just got done filming an ***ICONIC** collab.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Intelligence officials in the briefing responded that that was not consistent with any of the intelligence our gov… https://t.co/Nvhp4n5jvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NifMuhammad Ran cross country one year (poorly) and... I was a horse girl. I would love to be a horse woman but I… https://t.co/mUzBO7Im5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @NorthboroFire Department announcing the arrival of new lifesaving equipment purchased through a $252,000 feder… https://t.co/lEUjuuq8kM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But what made the short video so rich is that these activists were too young to know something important about old… https://t.co/OB6LnHy5Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLeonardKim You’re a writer...write her a love note every day for a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Freeman Engstrom calls for a “community of scholars” as we move forward in developing and reflecting upon AI… https://t.co/sikxLDUdqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never measured legislative success by number of bills passed. I have always measured it in shows of convicti… https://t.co/AjNAdGx1PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Luimelia #LuimeliaSquad #LuimeliaSinCensura #QueremosMásLuimelia #MarcelinoDudaLuimelia #AmarEsParaSiempre… https://t.co/dTqaDbN0J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chocolatekesh88 I enjoy you. I typed a bunch of other nonsense that was supposed to be empathic involving sandwich… https://t.co/bkdNYnsrB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time at NetCost 😍 (@ NetCost Market - @netcostphilly in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/PbohwTW7nP https://t.co/A9YrpyebPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know whether to cut my hair and go more blonde OR cut it and go back to dark https://t.co/YjVUaIhQcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people who get short mannered when you need help are the worst. They don't care enough to look deeper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieGeist Glad you survived @mikebarnicle “cuttting” comments this morning on @Morning_Joe We would miss you! 😉… https://t.co/Bi7SU0GpI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been told twice in the past month I look like her from princess diaries and I do not see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shorty just walked in the crib already yelling 😂😂🤦🏾‍♀️ I gotta grind harder I need to get out of here lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#satpreparation #satprep #satprepclass #sattestprep #satprepcourse #satpreparationclass #act #actprep #acttestprep… https://t.co/0kWXSZnnV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC well, I'd say that's a declaration against interest but not sure if all criteria have been met.  if so, except… https://t.co/gzzV9IpK8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gym date and Netflix Horror movies with @Wedlock92 🍿💪🏽🥰 #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the #illini basketball game Thursday. First time since graduation 13 years ago. Is there anything we shoul… https://t.co/7xgToSrdeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xyvzvx @dallasxsunny bo jest to plastikowa przykrywka i można tego użyć ponownie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing all these post about the beach makes me wanna go even more 😩🍍🌴☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC PEEPS!  Just a reminder—PBS TONIGHT at 9:00—@joshgroban Bridges in Concert from MSG!   PJs, slippers, and popco… https://t.co/Ye73n0EB1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jknoxville @NFL What’s that, 30 yds after first contact? He’s unstoppable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful &amp; blessed ❤️🙏🏻❤️ @ Our Lady of Perpetual Help https://t.co/ToVjsLD2xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Raiders WIN on the road! 1st Big 12 SWEEP in THREE years...super proud of this team! #TheMovement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried out a new winery in Hamilton County. It’s in the country. With chickens. And goats. My Texas heart is happy… https://t.co/f3UBHFPXfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Jacob Limon, Chief of Staff for Rep Meza, for taking time to discuss legislative priorities with us.… https://t.co/KplYkr4B1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlRojoVivo Es un ser humano unico y México lo ama #DesdeElAlmaTour #2aParte #Esooo #Seguimooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and Tea 🍵 (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/GgZUJ1OCew https://t.co/oMFziK1j16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. So sad for the ladies. I hope that they will get loving care. Put those bastards in jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, but red is actually my favorite color. You would never know that because I wear sooooo much Blac… https://t.co/PGKpnP19vV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biracial @DailyMailUK is too independent and too bright for this gutter press.  She does not bow down to them o… https://t.co/FEF0v2Z59d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the New Mexico Secretary of Energy, Minerals and Natural Resources, Sarah Cottrell Propst, Gail Cooke,… https://t.co/0XmaNpkuw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ESA Bubba needs your help! https://t.co/NG1XWCvhI3 Please retweet! @jarpad @mishacollins @JDMorgan… https://t.co/6rOyHdAB4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you imagine @norvina1 going on your page and your work not stand out for what she is looking for 😭😭😭😭😭 I need t… https://t.co/5JV4Y3q3JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s certainly a special power when someone you love laughs. It’s so pure and it fills my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes! Filming with @idmprogram Health Educator @natureboyrr today here in Denver!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherHomaXo If they’re on state roads, you can report them. That way if there’s any damage done to your vehicle,… https://t.co/M7qMNRdrMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always buy crazy colored shoes and never have anything to match them 😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Laure vs Ebon though. Could be the next Rondina vs Pons in terms of match up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moistywoisty @_samboxold I'll definitely keep that in mind. Thank you💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[when kacey musgraves said “I got a million things to do but I haven’t done a single one” I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriCityRD Where's Royal City Roller Derby?  Oh that's right, nobody wants to play a team of bullies.]]></document></documents></author>