<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@taddmike @Adam_Jacobi Will I get Mike's glass pun, it remains to be seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44Stretchisbest @hankschulman @iteptweets People are acting like Bryce would need a gofundme if he signed with the Giants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoinDeepRock Any idea when DRG could leave the @Xbox game preview program?]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a kid I did the “bang my head on the floor” version of this as well... a little too much perhaps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfs26 @KamalaHarris "On social media, people with political or ideological agendas fanned the flames. Presidential… https://t.co/7RNqsnrQvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Normsmusic Have you checked the firehouses and police stations? Just askin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blueface's flow is... different. I haven't been this excited about a rapper rapping offbeat since Silkk the Shocker. https://t.co/0Iqz6LB42d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Religion in government, what could possibly go wrong? For your victims, it may mean a beating and tortur… https://t.co/9HHpJQairA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este año en @ExpoTampico queremos ver a @RioRomamx 🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻  💕para Oír Amor💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clear When your own staff in #Atlanta are telling customers regular TSA Pre Check is faster your business model is… https://t.co/GCDB7oPPlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good To My Earhole, February 25. #desertmusic #mali #Mekons77 #folkmusic #angelbatdawid #musicjunkie #albumoftheday… https://t.co/2AcGSKkvuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizabethDrewOH @_ReaalAmerican_ @realDonaldTrump Roy Cohn told him to never admit defeat so there you go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@losprovocadores Zinedine Zidane regresa al Real Madrid C.F. Canción https://t.co/1B3ij4yfy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur Wow fact that @DrPaulGosar won CD4 against @DrDavidBrill by such a margin despite this and the sibling… https://t.co/yOa5d6Fw5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theswine15 @jeffpreston @NHL Feel the same way about Bergeron and Rask.  Much as I want to hate them because they’… https://t.co/QiNtLrndpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conklin_clayton @kenolin1 @TuckerCarlson @maddow @NicolleDWallace @SRuhle @Lawrence @chrislhayes @HardballChris Ye… https://t.co/Zi6Oj1GrjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @AdrienneLaw These MF's are ignorant. In todays age, and you KNOW  cameras are everywhere, C'mon mane.… https://t.co/rEMwYmofSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say "no" to you... KEEP GOING. You are worth more than you know and your time is coming. When people la… https://t.co/5rkRfnJPNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little snow tubing and beers with friends 🍻 @ Ski Ward https://t.co/oTRi5a4b77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo Chris. I’ve been a huge fan. But your show is getting way too preachy. A bit of constructive criticism… https://t.co/ngRdrHl4OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really think my #dog knows what he's doing some days to piss me off. He just looked down the hall to my room and… https://t.co/USLQkC64N3]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we’re waiting for spring, here’s the obligatory slo-mo snowfall pic.  It IS pretty if you don’t have to drive… https://t.co/pAfncb620G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkTreitel @sal_scott @marklevinshow "TRY' AGAIN MARK,,they tell facts not what "they want it to b" like bias  lying left//]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fawk wit a Legend! #BizzyBone #CarbonMonoxide @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/uET0Huuypo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a hard lesson to learn when you’re young. Never change yourself to gain acceptance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim Apple Tim A… https://t.co/nYDE05nEjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itz_gmoe335 Now use some common sense and tell me if dude looks like he’d be at 1.6% https://t.co/6cpaV6BXXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATTCares Now you send me a message saying you can’t find the account number after I gave it to you last week. Not… https://t.co/mEZ6tgLzqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe they're bout to pull off another big trade? Lol I'm assuming Dorsey has to be working something big.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cheeseburger Bobby's - @cbobbys in Norcross, GA https://t.co/FDUEl2CeXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your Sons Picture Portfolio this MONTH 🔥Link N Bio🔥  Haircut + Photoshoot Bookings Open on my Website 💥Link N… https://t.co/dpzToOgIy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essencefest “Naturally 7” would be an Excellent Choice to perform in between acts. All they need is microphones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DecodnLyfe @beaucoupbougee @Stephen_Dewayne @d0mocracy Speak for yourself... im JUST fine with going to work and c… https://t.co/rwOdMUHRZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Getting two Nigerians to help set up a hate crime hoax:  $3500. Bail for sniffling faker punk Jussie Smoll… https://t.co/N9qdt91ozc]]></document><document><![CDATA[tea: @lamelaysh is queen  @/deep_melancholy is fake but that’s just my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtanichthys @fountainscholar We’ve been using an Artec Spider for midsize specimens. Decent results.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cmon_JB If you switched lebron into that roster and took kobe out niggas would def say lebron carried nobodies to the finals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steph56Renee I love the quote from Alice in Wonderland, "It's rude to make personal remarks."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lightboi_ F that. I promised you an education. Plus a few others. We need to cultivate some taste to the nth degree. Also. Yes. Rebar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed TJ Hopkins’ three-run blast to give Carolina a 5-2 lead in the T2. @abc_columbia  https://t.co/cmcXj1QVJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas be afraid to moan....crazy, I be in my girl ear like: https://t.co/VqzB3R5XOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvptexas @DavidBalatHC @josephavellino @IP4PI @TPPF @AAPSonline @PPA_USA @IndDrs @DanCrenshawTX @chiproytx… https://t.co/sXOcMKnr1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InkonElbows @kaufmannGOP Kaufmann isn’t a legislator, why would he be drafting legislation? I’ll wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriRobitaille Been a Giants fan since 1963. The Giants last WS Championship before 2010 was in 1954.   Their first… https://t.co/Sy9DKwzpnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going more &amp; more in the right direction in regards to #RealEstate &amp; #SustainableDevelopmentGoals… https://t.co/4bmjn66xU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jblanier_ Ben- love you babe. I know how trying and frustrating these times can be. Here for you and standing with… https://t.co/LHd9LFKm2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FareedZakaria Boy are you off your rocker. You approve of killing babies, invasion of our country, government cont… https://t.co/SrLEgdMdJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheClosetedType @Criterion So did we ever figure out what this is from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEADS UP!! 4pm eastern time USA 5 spots open! These will start being done March 4th! Thanks! Direct Link: https://t.co/s3r2BelCtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Registered Nurse- Med Surg/Ortho - https://t.co/UbTSoYcw5C #hospitaljobs #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeekDuck @LeekDuck are the shiny stops same for every player? Or is it different for everyone like feebas day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchwartzLawME @GarySteTAAD Best out of state recruiters...in the MPA...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your car detailed today! https://t.co/YzD8CM8PgL Dm for pricing and availability today! #Wash #Wax #Sealant… https://t.co/Do5GXKIvdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hottest news to hit our industry in years, MH Advantage finance backed through Fannie Mae. Check out this home! @ F… https://t.co/22DGeDdsyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebteeiii @latimes I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOME Day1U… https://t.co/Bc5uzlbvN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re so full of shit. You have demonstrated nothing, but a willingness to overlook all of Morth… https://t.co/B1tTVzbKPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: Methane gas! *KICK* Polluted oceans! *KICK* Rising temperatures! *KICK*  #SDLive #WWEChamber… https://t.co/TYBWhHm5OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLadyFuchsia I would love to meet you some time just to have tea or lunch or a drink. Alas, I will not be visiti… https://t.co/gaTjJoxrZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @IUKWBB @IUKMGolf @IUKWGolf @IUKXC @IUKTennis @IUKVB @IUKSoccer join us in the Student Center tonight at 9 pm t… https://t.co/ZXxd4betlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JariahSensei @LetMeeBeGreat @bitchkream @luciamovilla_ She’s Gibraltar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessings upon blessings which of these two logos do you prefer? https://t.co/UzdwibhInS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday To My Sexy!Husband @cadej4686 . @cadej4686 @Badassgreaser @sodabitx @GreenLuffy26 https://t.co/A0qWna0YWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My past is what it is. I cannot change it, as much as I would like to some days. But I refuse to be defined by what… https://t.co/itrs94uC0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devon Lee the star for @Hbg_Sch_Dist his 30 points lead the  upset of @boys_wilson 63-61 and play for the… https://t.co/iL7gL453xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just cried while eating a CAN of chicken and stars and honestly i feel a lot better lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was his doctor with 7 degrees... I hope he was getting his head examined. He just left that part out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heh #MichaelCohen - how can you say President Trump never thought he would win when President Trump said over and o… https://t.co/3H9d2TzZHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardClaypo17 I understand I had had friends had them don earlier and late was best for them]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you’re helping row the boat, you won’t have time to rock the boat.”  —@darinsargent  @ThePointChurch midweek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gates_mcfadden Hi Doc. I lost my Mom back in 05, March 2005. And since then the episode of TNG I take the greatest… https://t.co/4xI7UsiFE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear: human trafficking is slavery. Let’s not confuse it with sex work. Human slavers put other people to… https://t.co/TCQ4CjuV9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhlblackhawks WIN ! 😎🙌🏻🤜🏻🤛🏻🏒🥅 #hockey #hockeyenespañol #hockeyisforeveryone #onegoal #chicagoblackhawks #blackhawks https://t.co/tKjdoDDqql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreh9205 Até bandeira LGBT, ELE COLOCOU NAS ESCOLAS. PRÓXIMA ELEIÇÃO, OS CONSERVADORES GANHAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[...So, who's ready for this new music video? 😏🚍🕺📺🎮📼🌐🎶🎥 @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/cebvllKQB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pizza perfect (at @GloriaPizzaNy in Forest Hills, NY) https://t.co/GZe54ZAHpw https://t.co/QrrfMxaD99]]></document><document><![CDATA[How NASCAR is using AR and 360-degree video https://t.co/XKx9meYxWy via @digiday GlassHouseSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC @andrewshermak2 Lol should have kicked his and your lying asses good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler6802 @chloecherryxxx omfg, @chloecherryxxx that's WAY more cocks than you had here... https://t.co/hgp2ZsIH98 u R HOT!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @HardballChris The problem is, if they start impeachment proceedings NOW or anytime down the line (before th… https://t.co/dIqffUJiIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am considering getting out of the Coast Guard then again I don’t want a job where I am required to be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronachng Lol idk generic skater hoodie, backwards hat and raggedy vans. Not the most normal walking through the front door at Apple lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinderteacher08 @DucksFanZone As long as he’s injured, get other stuff done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone on Twitter know where I can buy serrated truss head screws/bolts and and serrated flange nuts like is f… https://t.co/AOFogMijyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLPublicSchools #DLALC students lobbied the government in St. Paul today. Their powerful stories had a big impact… https://t.co/5yxqohumqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unbreakbroken @espn @TheUndefeated @WCCsports Is a Gael somebody who went to st Mary’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyPixar again disney owns the Oscar's too come on .... let it go.... and give Someone else a try this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[For pastors who are trying to shepherd your church but have wolves in the fold pushing against you...you may be rea… https://t.co/2XsVNP7Ny1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arabic_News if trump was  freandly  he would have shared this John 13:34-35 [34]A new commandment I give unto you,… https://t.co/lbX3MJZeCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@84Music1 @DrDenaGrayson @realDonaldTrump A President can be impeached, and after a Senate Trial can be removed fro… https://t.co/HRvz1oG1bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooo what's this? Well this is a nice thing to wake up to. Thanks @gayfuturepod https://t.co/eJ10W9OrhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MK_1997som @SKroatia @KTHopkins @suidlanders You genuinely know or you are one of them.. anyway for us is to only… https://t.co/CUclm4BHUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ur one these people who only collects P.E.’s or all exclusives, then you ain’t a sneaker head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettrg01 macieshaes  Why we dance ?  We’re the best workout in Dallas because it’s real-world based ...aka it’s… https://t.co/xBsGMG2cXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flannel February Day 20 it’s a Green Day so let’s get the green together to take the darkness of not knowing when s… https://t.co/2J9zkAxzxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Take solace that Dems have a strategy to lose 2020 election..Cultural wars seem sufficient for indigent w… https://t.co/OpM7nh2uJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutnumberedFNC I wonder how much more emboldened KJU became because of the seditious debacle that took place yeste… https://t.co/mZwWkkwSNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshwurster_ Gosh. It’s like you hate summer or something. https://t.co/fOIVdX0NFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy Which is why there has to be a Canadian Comedy Hall of Fame. Hopefu… https://t.co/Xhtb63l6OY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krek9 Siempre he creído que eres imparcial por eso me atreví a preguntarte y se que lo harás de una manera profesi… https://t.co/Dqi6i8Bfym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldboxATL @MitchMossRadio @paulyhoward I thought Mr C was definitely fading Follow The Money 5. How else would he… https://t.co/Xq2SDHh3f3]]></document></documents></author>