<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JeffCoMoSheriff Are you SURE she is the owner? How did someone get her dog?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makennaedissi_ Okay...if not a couch...how ‘bout a recliner at least? ..a tv?? FYI...Kenny is still playin..song r… https://t.co/YJlSbLesCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[New art work now available at Saatchi- Vivianna was inspired by nights at the gala, cocktails, fashion, and Vanity… https://t.co/V66nfmoo8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does no one ever talk about how fucked up the plot of Stuart Little is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst part was that i had commented on that person's polycount thread making suggestions for improvements https://t.co/EXkMaY5hj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett altho I didnt want it to be TRUE, I wanted to BELIEVE you.  😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just chewed garlic, minced some more, put it on a spoon with honey and swallowed it all.. fingers crossed I get better in 2 hours :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoArquette @Kellybolduc88 Good...cause we would have to kill them if they go after you💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Cohen u r not a liar! Trump is a pathological liar and so are his kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustCommonSens3 @SenClegg It seems he excelled in spite of public school:  "Einstein often felt out of place and v… https://t.co/rHGrc7DSBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyManCrushMonday and my #ManCrushEveryday @jordanknight 🥰. Even #AdLibs of the #Stingy opening are so beautiful… https://t.co/UiqiTW7HPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We should think about what is possible, not what is probable.” - @julianagyeman #justsustainabilities Thanks… https://t.co/uderzWtogE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomeOfUncleSam @ScotsFyre @PolitiBunny @RowdyRick73 @PerspicaciousXY @belle_lol_ @EvanSayet @APLMom @donf2528… https://t.co/1hDvOHMtp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Kona, our Operations Associate of the Month for February!! We appreciate you and your orange-blooded p… https://t.co/EUwIjUDvOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Barnes &amp; Noble - @bnbuzz in Rancho Cucamonga, CA w/ @elegantprojects https://t.co/9eddAjZpMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coles52620818 Wonder is right.  But I’m thankful for Judge Boyle protecting landowners in NC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokeyrobinson @WynnLasVegas You were awesome in Portland Oregon. I was in love with you as a little girl always l… https://t.co/KqBpwCFUU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nail his ass. @realDonaldTrump  @DonaldJTrumpJr  @IvankaTrump  @EricTrump  @FLOTUS  @jaredkushner  @LaraLeaTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[tmw when you’re mentally not ok and the one person you wanna talk to isn’t in your life anymore ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#513goonsquad #gooniesneversaydie #justiceforgabby #LLG #13strong #forever13strong #mentalhealtheducation… https://t.co/LAM3tfAQ0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night fundraising for @MagicMentors. #BigBrotherBigSister #IgniteMiami https://t.co/UYIQEAVFke]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Dr. Singh at work #healthcareforall #meharrymade #nashville #meharrymedicalcollege #mujeresenciencia @ Nashvil… https://t.co/5eblk1PjCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @satribesman @DavidHarris707 @SeptemberJulie @ArleneKowalczyk @CatholicPierogi @Jj051301 @carmelitequotes https://t.co/M3vvUwXVSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Sarah can say she’s going to die tonight but no one else can make a bad joke #DatingAround]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Georgetown University Law student is among the victims of the Ethiopian Airlines crash. Cedric Asiavugwa was know… https://t.co/p47oHNTZBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher Have you ever thought about a collaboration with Gaga? Your voices would blend beautifully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember my first tornado in Barton County — while I was freaking out, my neighbors were outside EXACTLY like thi… https://t.co/O6DlTPBjn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Hey girl...been through it. Can't imagine dealing with the world, too. Unfortunately you're forced… https://t.co/ocHWteqL3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeMacGirl6012 @JonathanRKnight That is so you Christina when you get excited 🤣😂🤣😂 #BHLove #BoysInTheBand #MixTapeTour #HanginTough30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok TRIVIA FANS!!!!! Pay attention. For Valentine’s Day we have something special for you.  We will hand out gift ba… https://t.co/zbOdAkzM08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just imagine what will happen to you for being a cheat, liar and thief? #TrumpFailAgain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter THIS from someone WHO speaks for amd and caters to Trumps MAFIOSO!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leeners66 @MrsContino So proud of you, Sebastian!!! Great thanks to the amazing ladies working hard with him every… https://t.co/ytF2nE1EIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaththeWineLady @FionaMorgan79 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @joneill55 @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt… https://t.co/aM2ix0Ayki]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . Scorsesean homages to the films he loves.  The characters are sharply conceived, the performances splendid.… https://t.co/bddyV92vEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting dumped in a foreign country seems like the worst. Unless you’ve brought my Mom there to fly home with me an… https://t.co/7srYMitMJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my favorite ladies on international women’s day! Love you all 😘 @ 24 North Hotel Key West https://t.co/eKIpXWmDIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TakeEDUCATIONByStorm #EducatorsRising #GSWSOE  Let’s celebrate our future Georgia Educators!! gswedrising… https://t.co/5b8TMiWlVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So why then do we commit murder, steal, adulery when we know it is wrong? At the bottom of all human actions is the… https://t.co/ooFhVyNNuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews I’m pretty sure @senatemajldr took some of those laundered Russian rubles that the @NRA was passing out… https://t.co/myfY2mnkZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD NEWS I will not be retiring🙌🏽 and even better news @IndianaMBB took home the dub against @BadgerMBB tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worship night with these girls ❤️🙏🙌 @ Experience Community https://t.co/imlXszIMmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or @chucktodd ! He loves Bernie... Trashed Biden last nite!...  All in for TRUMP! @MSNBC They'll do it again! Start… https://t.co/WjM9m77U8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for a Christening ✝️ #SundayFunday https://t.co/D8sFGldHAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKingCoIe @SamiRoske We are selling tickets to the gorilla show next week if you would like to pre-order]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSmithReads Memes don’t need to be animation. It’s just edited with music to covey a point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Compliance Consultant 4" at Wells Fargo? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. Yo… https://t.co/n5bbcy1qcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[💡Inspring A S.M.A.R.T. City with @Inspire305Miami 🏝🏙 https://t.co/5oL1te7foZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minn. press raises questions about Ilhan Omar's former marriage https://t.co/hWreZhKWdL via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers! My nephew had it done a couple of years ago and was released the same day. Hope your kiddo does just as we… https://t.co/PkujTAducp]]></document><document><![CDATA[let’s not act like half of y’all bashing khloe left y’all niggas the first time they cheated🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been out checking the roads, a big thanks to lots of people working hard to clear the roads We’re going to need to… https://t.co/KkViLLPgKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I’m showing a professor how important it is to expose his students to #IBMz and how easy it is to accomplish t… https://t.co/RDSRjhLkpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RucalTeam @LucasSeuren @sue_wilkinson @JonathanPotter6 @BoldenGalina @mandelbaum_js @songheepark11 @Kzhan66… https://t.co/Chiyqp7Iby]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little #koreatown with my Korean bestie #nyc #nyceats #barhop @ Empire State Building https://t.co/osOwV73xHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump you're such a snowflake and drama queen and a liar President Trump is fully within His… https://t.co/El57Af43t6]]></document><document><![CDATA[|| Been feeling like I’m on a mission from the higher power. I told myself and my family one day I’ll make you prou… https://t.co/37CLvncSwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AppreciatER @MeganMonnot @BIGBizDecker @emilywiper @BIGBizDecker https://t.co/0rMdkIob88]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @HowardKurtz, how are you going to spin today’s news contained in @NewYorker magazine re: the interactions of… https://t.co/XsoL44IPCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denisesaturn @Rosie My mom has Stage IV breast cancer. She has radiation 5x a week. If SHE can make it through 180… https://t.co/ZubZ7RVf4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll forever do whatever keeps me smiling, fuck whoever has anything to say 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Free Bed is always here for you. Happy Valentines Day. #askformary #valentinesday2019 🧡💚 @ Mary Free Bed Rehab… https://t.co/EIEumfgcuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToniiMagitt @JaymalGreen @chancetherapper I’m sorry y’all; Amara is wayyy more qualified than both of them. Please… https://t.co/SPfUmoKqnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst feeling in the world is feeling exhausted, alone, and helpless. What a bad combo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban in concert today. It was my first time hearing the Prisoner of Azkab… https://t.co/10UkoLieXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night Ty had a few buddies over drinking &amp; this one kid ate almost all of our big bag of pizza rolls &amp; it was a full bag 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCommonConsent In reference to a the tax revision bill. Which failed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffBezos we would very much like to invite you here to @cityoftoronto , see my community, meet our Mayor… https://t.co/Ta3Ab2gZJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkGrooove @SpeakerPelosi @cyndilauper @realDonaldTrump Nobody can force anybody he had a choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats @SpeakerPelosi PLEASE investigate this slanderous BS statement👇 #MarkMeadows + rest of #GOP must le… https://t.co/hGagGvCvCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu "Some infants are born with bilateral renal agenesis, where they have no kidneys, or anencephaly where th… https://t.co/TkvHvSpIIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #LoveYourPetDay even though I love you everyday, today is a day for you, my little bub. I love you. https://t.co/HM21kv81oU]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the old white men engage in yet another episode of “Whose Dick Is Bigger”, L7’s @DonitaSparks actually speaks to the issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloWrestling @NashedPotato_ You are our #LoudenSwain @NashedPotato_ Good Luck at the NCAA Division III Central Wre… https://t.co/10igpMEaOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long overdue. Hopefully things will begin happening now. Broadband is very limited, slow and not that reliable  whe… https://t.co/kBHhbz2XaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[He made an appointment @BroadlawnsMed. Step in the right direction and I can only hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why the Republicans can’t hold onto the Senate. They could stand together and accomplish things but they wo… https://t.co/TqbMXgkWQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am running in pure adrenaline rn damn I should not be THIS good at my job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavanahFinesse Hopefully they go on tour after I give birth!!! We getting wild 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burns principal and master teachers present during a district initiative to increase literacy! @Detroitk12… https://t.co/EOPARknKnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @KamalaHarris Don’t try to fool us with your Globalist baloney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normareeves @404girl @AdamMRagab @MarqRodgers @nc5835 @C_Hayes860 @jmedina930 @CardsHelena @Hampthechamp9… https://t.co/ZSSeiJPT2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday Repost from @hardfitness Early shoot with Crystal Cooper gofigure_24! Come see her today at our HardF… https://t.co/qGVD6KTguE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t believe it’s already March!” - something @H3MBR0  will say at some point today]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bJBdEqT7Vt #LincolnClub #AbrahamLicoln #PresidentsDay #Coffee https://t.co/f8P6q6dnVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, yes. Definitely this. “Did we talk about this in this section already?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josephsonofthe2 @juannisaac @AlcoholicsOf #Praise be to Grog!!! https://t.co/Qh8SWagzn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with my daughter Cheryl 's boyfriend James Kent (@ Kristina's Cafe in Saint Petersburg, FL)… https://t.co/jBnTsGsAmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CUANDO EMPEZARON CON EL AQUÍ HAY AMOR YO ESTABA COMO LA ESTUPIDA HACIENDO EL CORAZÓN EN MI CASA #VeneuelaAidLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new #AVFHome Bolt Vases. Available for pre-order now. Shipping on or soon after 4/30/19. #plexiglass #lucite… https://t.co/8GvhJZcr4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be going on and on about someone that’s been treating you like shit if you know you gonna run back to them 😂… https://t.co/Xqiy9WE5Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @RealMAGASteve He doesn’t even make sense: Republicans screwed around and did nothing about the wall w… https://t.co/yK0iR7SqPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭 😭 😭 @BeyondMeat BRING BACK THE REFRIGERATED ONES I USED TO FINISH IN THE CAR ON THE WAY HOME FROM THE STORE my li… https://t.co/kqXDRYLxAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump needs to be indicted without bail/bond for exthortion, rape, sexual abuse, destroying my breast and… https://t.co/X4koDfs938]]></document><document><![CDATA[When me and my mom moved too Lakewood to give ourselves a better place of living, my mom and I always watched the s… https://t.co/q22AaKSZTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t microwave relationships! Tayshia’s dad speaking truth! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[My home studio has been my happy place lately and I couldn’t be more at peace with it. Basically Puccini, Sondheim,… https://t.co/7G0K3yIGd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember when 3 Doors Down performed at Trump’s inauguration? I think that might be the most embarrassing thi… https://t.co/j6BvQHnSCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Accounts Payable Clerk" in #PlymouthCharterTownship, MI. Go on informational inte… https://t.co/CjE629zswg]]></document><document><![CDATA[today i knocked over a little kid at work and cut open two fingers but honestly what’s new]]></document></documents></author>