<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Franktmcveety @DonDegenhardt @nationalpost And thousand more now that China has put a trade stop on Canola....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @ursaluna I don't believe for a second that you've read it in it's entirety. And what a pompous ass y… https://t.co/BV88NkDDyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LocdUpProd @TheHeelJoshNeil @OhNoItsAlexx Do you not know what a paywall is or how micro transactions or the human… https://t.co/PoMNy4hPG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S-A FUNNY THING  UNDER ONE GOD=ALL THINK SPIRITUAL\IT CAN BE THE HUMANS WORKING AS ONE BODY ENJOYING THE SAME AM… https://t.co/T6FUTkY8QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Podrán criticar a #samsung por el celular ese nuevo que se transforma #fold y su ridículo precio de $40,000 pesos,… https://t.co/CM6uT9BM3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @realDonaldTrump Well, bless his ignorant little heart!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWehrls5 @OhVarsity Yeah if someone starts getting super negative, I either mute or unfollow. You’re not going t… https://t.co/YM1XbsCae7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re in Cleveland when... #it’savaluableprize #you’llshootyoureyeoutkid https://t.co/PCJ2VILyNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[+ so I happily got the heck out of the way so the fire fighters had room to move their truck in.  Amazing coffee ad… https://t.co/BwRLt0HMsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening up #927music #djrichsample #campatl @ Sky Restaurant Bar and Grill https://t.co/RKGjp7VjFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNAPCHAT SALE ROBBERY: Metro police have arrested the suspected getaway driver involved in an attack earlier this y… https://t.co/lDgj7kZSsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSpurrierUF you got that swag still I know @MichaelWaddell_ is happy we got to try to get a crowd out their man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonjwilde @TonyCartagena Do the @packers have an Assistant to the Traveling Secretary position? #DreamJob https://t.co/q2MUKhiATX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W2E4DAVID I didn’t miss it you just gotta show me more then some BS reference track that you can’t tell who wrote what]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge “thank you” to the tech support people at Site Ground. Thank you.  @SiteGround]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s a struggle man. #boxer #boxersofinstagram @ Tallahassee, Florida https://t.co/Mkj2xCqmrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigMoneyATL @Chiefs @TonyGonzalez88 Nah, we just have a better tight end that’s proud to play for #KansasCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flynn-backed plan to transfer nuclear tech to Saudis may have broken laws, whistleblowers say https://t.co/LGHPip08ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dragon_Age_Fans HoR is Strongholds.  Is it just in the regular (yellow) missions?  Freeplay? Legendary (purple) mi… https://t.co/IKMXQnq67S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @cdeseray17 for planning an amazing birthday weekend for me. I missed seeing my friends being wild. 💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattsunday @AB84 @DKPghSports @steelers @buffalobills Maybe we can take him to Duff’s or Anchor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbbevilacqua @jguaido Tienes toda la razón, eso fue lo que sucedió y mira el resultado. ¿Quién está en Miraflores?… https://t.co/jqlr688gU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 THIS WEEKEND: @Jeff_Sutorius returns to headline Saturday and #MarqueeMondays at the Nightclub, and local legen… https://t.co/Ri2jdDuOiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a time of reflection tonight.  We begin our Journey to the Cross. We will dive into Matt 4:1-11… https://t.co/p9yP7Pujq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Give teachers a voice. Be there to support each other. Build strong relationships. We must have a foundation to… https://t.co/e6jgPtAms4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diría mi primo l_e_s_inc "mira mi flow...mira mi pinta!" Te acuerdas @sjliberato JAJAJAJA!  #SuitedUp… https://t.co/MXLeO5a1po]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went and saw WILD WILD WEST at the theater when I was 11, and it was so empty that I laid down on multiple seats… https://t.co/SJxlIaFz1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarimeroWings tengo una pregunta muy buena, no se si ya has hablado de esto pero no crees que a Kyurem le falta un… https://t.co/NqKgSxNMig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never felt this much pressure to succeed in my life. I’m just glad I got my team w/ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why we dont use water to our advantage more tbh, its an unlimited mechanical power source]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coltcomics @Pups_n_Pompano I would really love to go to our 1st con this year, still on the fence tho! Still not c… https://t.co/tjaFgUEnZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could be that I just missed it before, but it feels like there’s been an intentional—welcome, overdue—shift in poli… https://t.co/zviwux69Uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinabaum @NatResources You got this! Praying for healing and a quick recovery!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallasnews @Rangers tell Woodward he is a liar and he has lost my respect. He wasn't even a great coach in LA anyh… https://t.co/B7EcitRCzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maayan_Techiya @NEJM @DeborahCohan African is a race that has subdivisions of ethnicities]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y me fui tras de ti persiguiendo mi instinto si quieres cambio verdadero pues, camina distinto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoSpandexReq @paparatti It links to a cad number that came up as Non Criminal Non Drug DOA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And is it a coincidence that the target of this bs is a black Islamic woman while white male GOP reps have gotten a… https://t.co/dd65YL63Y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some call it late nights. I call it early mornings. #NFLCombine starts now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bubblin🛁 . @AndersonPaak live @rebel_toronto (Feb 26th, 2019) . Photos by Mac Downey for @thecomeupshow https://t.co/VfxTRMQpAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Forgot to mention mid-terms... winter is coming mr trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last week off social media was a direct correlation to my mental struggle. The past week I was in a rut that I… https://t.co/M0MQbi2HGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥵Crunch Time Countdown 🥵  Set the timer for 5 minutes and see if you can complete the follow descending rep count s… https://t.co/7ImQSaK9Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioStateHoops was 12-1 @ one time and then something must’ve happened in the locker room because this isn’t the same team!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KFISH__ @SteaknShake It would have been less disappointing if they would have just been closed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌤Good Morning Vibes For You! 🌤  ☀️Director @chrispaynedupre  ☀️Choreographer @leomoctezuma ☀️Dancer… https://t.co/uPMiMp2iYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't faking an auction sale illegal?  I seem to remember that from when I was working auctions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpanyc Who are these people using so much bleach that it’s left behind after the rinse cycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanx for tuning in yesterday.  @ScrappyCoProd and I are getting great feedback and requests to Rant, Rave, and Rev… https://t.co/SMzcPVpaTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decree and declare that God is the mastermind working through me right now. #MorningDeclaration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Trump just refer to ISIS as “The Caliphate”? Way to reinforce ISIS propaganda Mr. President! 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️… https://t.co/Fjx5RNbqXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just played the most insanely cracked out League Play lobby, feeling hyped out w/ @DeviseGuhny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump doesn't mean anything Trump l is unfit to serve as president of the United States I… https://t.co/mobLavdbmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realSethMorton @realDonaldTrump McCabe should be in prison like a dog like Manafort]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/EW42cx2bG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also worth mentioning, this isn’t a Boeing 737-Max8. This is its much bigger brother, the Boeing 767. So much journ… https://t.co/L4C2UNJjbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing Pink concert. A Rockstar literally flying through the arena. From pure musical talent to physical strength… https://t.co/zDkjQOwfHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We tried to tell Trump supporters that The Tax Bill was a scam but none of them were having it at the time. Soon as… https://t.co/0wI7q80ucK]]></document><document><![CDATA[DLo and Julius Randle going off 👀 they’d look good in the purple and gold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eleanorstrouser @danehorvath Wow. I just Googled it and I already hate everyone in that town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxisnicee Playing ultimate whenever someone has a player with hof difficult shot. @ItsShake4ndbake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_kintner I sure will , I was getting ready to go down your twitter page to find some more of your music .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justina71893380 @JoeySalads @AOC Can you even spell correctly, small-time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojoclap_1 @Corey_Feldman I Agree. I’ve been saying the same. I think MJ was very calculated in his care of the celeb boys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[17th #UptownArtsStroll #WashingtonHeights #Inwood #WestHarlem May 29-June 30, 2019 #artists #submit #exhibits… https://t.co/M747LRAgPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel Well over 200 years since the 2nd Amendment was written, and Americans still can’t figure it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And why is Notre Dame even in this conversation? When will the elite media finally understands what the average col… https://t.co/lSDaW8pHC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKimCampbell @AOC @alyssa_jayne @girlscouts Fake Conservative... https://t.co/aypzcy9b74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Donald Trump Presidency is so bad for our Country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjamindcrosby The problem lies in the severing of confirmation from baptism. Water bath + hand laying + Holy Com… https://t.co/PmTNFbwr5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#geraldroberts #bgpradio #dcincentives   @applebees @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/J7cgk0yQ5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate my roommate so much like she ruins my sleep every night I’m sick of her ass honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Robert Special Counsel would release his report about Donald Criminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are not alone! If you, or if you worry about someone, are dealing with suicidal thoughts, depression, etc., cal… https://t.co/wdp804CJnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Would you help spread the word please? David Crockett High School robotics team from Jonesborough,… https://t.co/BfdIxwWve2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesnt blow my mind because he's using his whole forearm to throw the cap, it would be much more impressive if he o… https://t.co/DiNqGgkdvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @AOC I knew she sounded like an idiot every time she talked now I get it, she’s nothing but a street thug… https://t.co/aKZJ1Lxflw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ancientorigins Do they need a professional illustrator? I'd be happy to give archaeological illustration a try.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my two loves!!! @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/8bKZADnu1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[You bleach my clothes n shit and you might end up dead. Please don’t think you gone walk away untouched 🤞🏼🤞🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlquintanilla @CNBC @SquawkStreet @ErinBurnett Yup. Good man. I recall him as a local anchor in Providence RI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askck @Lalo_mago @FelipeCalderon La Zopilota que es la primera Lady Caracolitos de México...te dice toma tus...bel… https://t.co/BQjBbaC0e3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We riot if Monster doesn’t win #TheMaskedSinger https://t.co/3AKR7RfBG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I often feel. Especially when work is really slow https://t.co/yYwimqlmD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willsmithaf @unlobodelnorte @cenkuygur Your seem to imply that this belief translated into disdain for today's Jew… https://t.co/Z82h0XqBZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tower Mobile Home &amp; RV Park https://t.co/VxdIpp3jtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another good way to stop all the stuff that ends up in the ocean is to STOP DUMPING STUFF IN THE OCEAN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW IS THE TIME FOR ALL PATRIOTS TO STAND UP IN CONGRESS!   TRUMP IS SUBVERTING OUR CONSTITUTION!   THERE IS NO NAT… https://t.co/vgOfWoNOt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew_wiebe I havent seen anyone go down as fast with so little contact as Diego Rossi did since Kevin Nash got h… https://t.co/8ypj1vu1Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Atlanta to #Houston #RIP #DJScrew #ScrewedUpClick #SUC #DungeonFamily #DF #Outkast #GoodieMob https://t.co/osb9YLZIYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, I am stuck watching this. All of her points are valid. It's so hard when people pass laws that support one par… https://t.co/KCsdcjxknK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRapaport No one cares what a C level actor thinks about politics. It’s really narcissistic you think people… https://t.co/UhraqsynPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the great things about living in Portland is our proximity to so much natural beauty. Today: a chilly day at… https://t.co/p6F2NlgovX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Nova🐾 #husky #huskylove #huskyphotography #huskygirl @ Ringwood, New Jersey https://t.co/Duv57c2Fpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Israel is to the Moon!!! 🇺🇸🇮🇱🦁💪🏽💑https://t.co/KM5woYMKlQ https://t.co/6I4EHBzCry]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheBlacklist S6, Ep. 7 "General Shiro (No. 116)" Recap and Review #Blacklist  https://t.co/k6GeQcC241]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresidencialVen @NicolasMaduro @PresidencialVen TE QUEDA POCAS HORAS HIJOPUTA MAMAGUEVASO RATA 🐀 DICTADOR ASESINO… https://t.co/Vn30Bvqz1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGSportsNow @EdBouchette If the Steelers traded AB, could that same team turnaround and trade AB to a different team if they wanted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The SNC-Lavalin affair has continued to play out and evolve over the last week, here's https://t.co/uN9XQxyBKV’s co… https://t.co/Q8COzIJORb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up #BillsMafia? Long day!! Leave any questions you have on this thread and @RyanTalbotBills and I will discu… https://t.co/sxHGDgUbkd]]></document></documents></author>