<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Congratulations beautiful 👏🏾👏🏾🥳 Proud of you ! #BlackExcellence #BlackGirlMagic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing someone unintentionally hurted you &amp; continues to do so is the worst :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Guys for the Beautiful Birthday Messages , They really meant a lot to me , You guys are the best , Wearin… https://t.co/ApChE1CniK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is funny how it feel that winter seems to be dragging on and on but the RSP deadline came up out of nowhere! Fri… https://t.co/bVOeIH7OvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thing about that tweet is .. you’ll probably think you don’t feel anything about that person till something comes b… https://t.co/SySmhbPp9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again @PBS never fails. The “American Masters” piece on Sammy Davis Jr. was very enlightening. He believed in… https://t.co/yd88i0rwzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Mac Miller said, “She put me back together when I’m out of order” I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many good shows in April, I guess I’m celebrating my birthday all month long 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about Valentine’s Day is that tomorrow is the 15th, which means it’s pay day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have packed the hearing room and two overflow rooms for the first public hearing of HF1500 the house bill to res… https://t.co/VfcOlfvGhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence 👏👏👏 CONGRATULATIONS! You will represent ALL Americans with pride and honor. Saw you were in Nashville!… https://t.co/KfTwEWPLYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a 5 week old puppy is just like having a baby fr this waking up out my sleep to bottle feed him is getting m… https://t.co/VHuovIEqpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying my hand at gardening this year, even though my poor lettuce is already late to the game bc I apparently stil… https://t.co/u92eQKY0G4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like we’ve just been watching Giants owners apologize for doing horrible things. This isn’t ok. An official… https://t.co/oNas95Jzsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Warrior_Ready @TylerGehman1 @aaandrewwww @SecretarySonny @maggieNYT @POTUS Trump says he and Kim Jong Un "fell in… https://t.co/a5PKIBvPHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Não achava meu fone fazia 2 semanas já estava pensando “não tem problema, um novo é barato” hoje achei embaixo da cama]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please tell uncle snoop to come get me! I'm in row k seat 1 @SnoopDogg #smokeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 days until vacation and I’m starting pre-packing.   Yup...so ready to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iQuestionStuff Quite the clever play on words there. https://t.co/y9wjikw5IF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude left his keys in our car last night and now I’m stuck waiting for him to come pick em up 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great point from @EmoryUniversity’s Nancy Seideman - Don’t forget about @LinkedIn for building relationships and ma… https://t.co/eA9Tk0pWj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was an icon of my generation. RIP Luke Perry. 😔  https://t.co/vx23oZDg6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volunteer 🐾 https://t.co/lgDdHgi2vS https://t.co/uHDxK9OYa0 Donate 🐾 https://t.co/rEX66DcUVD Adopt 🐾… https://t.co/m44pdZgQ8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great connecting with @RashidaCrutch and @saragoldrickrab at @hope4college @AchieveTheDream #atd_Dream recep… https://t.co/8AEZPkwHws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy hump day or in Earper land we just  call it #FightForWynonna day! I have a feeling that every hump day will b… https://t.co/PYJSwdOa34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being rude and giving people attitude for no reason is NOT CUTE SWEETHEART]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @FortBendISD’s #ScienceFairExpo, I had the privilege of judging an @OCE_BlueJays’ student’s experiment. Not only… https://t.co/jIkRyGoAcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blueface is TRASH. If you think he’s raw then you clearly have no taste in real music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[how many times will Tom Wilson injur players before there are repercussions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao so lady just asked me how do I get out of this store 😂😂😂 telling ya the way they arranged target ugly asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JornalOGlobo Oh no! Aí falam no Brasil não tem furacão, tornado, tufão etc, mas chove e chove muito e a terra desl… https://t.co/kBSf9hWXJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsabellacloud @thelakeworthmo1 I just saw this omg but Nate has my number so wTF 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Kidding. I'm a freak too lol @ In My Bedroom https://t.co/yEZHKWaX7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Millennial Falcon IS BACK and looking fresh with a new paint job and interior! 🚁 Thanks @vincent_stahl for comi… https://t.co/fxxAhWJh0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully packed in an hour &amp; 15 minutes! This is a new record for me 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can they call anything a #political witch hunt when they call Democrats #BabyKillers ?!  Ridiculous inflammator… https://t.co/siNf0gB6Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Une raison de plus pour dévorer nos Cookies! 🍪🍫🍪 Jusqu’au 3 Mars, profitez d'un rabais de 15% sur nos boîtes de Coo… https://t.co/38A2ip9Z8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theonlyLissa @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump And thats on one of tRumps good days, most of the time he just babb… https://t.co/JBGosL5fbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing some finger lickin’ good tunes at @eatatpot tonight! 8-11pm. Nod your head while you nom down the tastiest… https://t.co/jUPPxLizUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/23/19, 10:30am, my apt...nothing new except that I finally left my apartment at 10am and got my mail downstairs.… https://t.co/B6tSRzLUtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @JordanSchachtel Call it what it is, Trump family will conspire with American's enemies for a buck.… https://t.co/6evuxeGJ33]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really appreciate @hadleyfaith and I feel like I don’t say it enough ❤️ https://t.co/KSUXprrpzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Natawryy yeah for sure :( I think it’s the worst when people lie about shopping too. It’s not “angles”!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took almost a year, and I almost missed the anniversary deadline for hitting it (by March 20th for some new cosm… https://t.co/nAVzjNJvt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con esta foto me despido! Mi Ciudad lo más bonito! #Repost mendozaciudad with get_repost #MendozaMaravilloza… https://t.co/vCGVWdrKqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra Pues nada mas vea quien es el gobernador, si nada mas le falta rebusnar, con todo respeto aesos bellos animales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lord sits enthroned over the flood; the Lord is enthroned as King forever. The Lord gives strength to his peopl… https://t.co/aqjFpDI0nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ll throw shade at you when they see you succeeding in life 💯 that’s something I’ll never understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Back in my day, I had to walk to work, uphill, in the Snowpocalypse of ‘19”  #WAwx #seattlesnowpocalypse2019… https://t.co/IeU4AWiFBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibiOfficial Discovered your channel not too long ago from your collab with @safiyajn and it’s honestly amazing fo… https://t.co/PGJN7PXhD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuciferSPN13 @KaterinaKestem1 @lovestheguys @LabelItKilljoys @Moondropz Good day Kay! Have a wonderful one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vrkimmel Don’t miss Maria! She’s a great teacher and her book is wonderful! @jeffreykubiak @hayhurst3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my son handed me flowers and a balloon I instantly got watery eyed he’s my heart ♥️ him and his daddy ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgive yourself for not knowing what you didn’t know before you learned it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRiggsWDRB @UofLWBB My pleasure, 👑Sterling  Have a blessed 🙏 day.   I'm tuning  in WDRB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @SenKamalaHarris @SpeakerPelosi this needs to stop. My wife and I are expecting in the summer and this comment… https://t.co/nMbCH5cYAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and join me and some other friends for a night of shopping.  There will be drinks and appetizers too and e… https://t.co/jQ9IEz749e]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to celebrate International Women’s Day than at BARTSCHLAND FOLLIES ❗️ 💋❤️💄#amandalepore  #showgirls… https://t.co/pWr2k07ZhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s time to sleep my wife is in my left arm, resting her head on my chest and my corgi son is in my right arm… https://t.co/aVHBfaWH3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was setting up my boyfriend to make fun of me and this is what I get 😂😂 https://t.co/s8PZSK06bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending our 3 year anniversary at the San Diego zoo🥰 https://t.co/hSsZNc24Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t we get these here in the states? There’s very few places to buy Vegemite in my area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whignewtons @NYCdisinterest Sarah, Albert Turner’s endorsement of Sessions carried about as much weight in the bla… https://t.co/66HPGUMG0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago one of the worst school shootings in history happened. Instead of picking political sides let’s work tog… https://t.co/1d3wddTEoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been so use to people treating me terribly in relationships that I just expect it and then it throws me way of… https://t.co/tPURGFxTPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Trump lies about size of crowds at appearances, lied Mexico would pay for the wall, lied he would show… https://t.co/jJKoSEwBQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walmart greeter with cerebral palsy may lose his job due to a policy change - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/BBWKQQK3gw via @.Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexconnorwrite @yuliashadesign @ChrisPopeWrites @KarlHolton @_rjardon @QUIRKIEBIRD_ @alleycat579 @gmontcuellar… https://t.co/VaTgI1RuQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME There is a better replacement: Dimash Kudaiburgen - the singer ET frm other planet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[brooklyn is absolutely superior when it comes to food.. roll n roaster, brennan and carr, L&amp;B like need i go on???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked around all day and night with my pants on inside out and none of my friends told me... #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vgunvalson Brianna looks like she did back in High school!  You go get it mama!  The 2 boys club is not for the weak!]]></document><document><![CDATA[devhynes you were/are incredible. @ Variety Playhouse https://t.co/m7bDYO36Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ManafortSentencing This is obscene!  Paul Manafort gets 47 months, less than 4 damn years. What?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your most important work in this lifetime may not be your job - it's a conviction within your soul, recognizable if… https://t.co/LDT9hbucGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgeOldRivalry @Patrick_Coffin Vix- The point is that you weren’t respectful. The interview was very well done and… https://t.co/BYfYBvKmYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[my work bf from Utah actually drew my name with waves and planes on his shoes cause he misses me and I’m crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucianobrazusa a pior q tem, MANDAR MSG kkkkkkkkkkkkkkk (rindo pra n chorar)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards The only victim of all these shenanigans is the poor dog that had to be with Dorit and her fam. 🙄… https://t.co/ZeP1s5zyZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @olgaNYC1211 She was very powerful. No wonder Trump and Pence attachedher. They cannot stand strong women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow I love dedicating my Friday night to doing homework but.. still.. not.. doing.. homework.. (:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GruvyGurl Yes we did!! If only some people would actually listen to us from time to time, they’d realize we DO kno… https://t.co/719BjlE9WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[They haven't been on the rise, there are a 1000 more police reporting them than before. They didn't report before t… https://t.co/QmuymTsPNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are coming back and I’ve never been more excited in my life. Long live Clare Jonas 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Local Blend - Cincinnati - Deeper Roots Coffee by @MadTreeBrewing at @MadTreeTaproom — https://t.co/5N3m3vyOHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big game today for @WindsorLancers @WindsorMHKY - This was photo from opening ceremonies - what an experience for t… https://t.co/PO608ggTn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFCArmyWifeMN @SheriffChody I totally agree with you! If you live here learn the language!😕🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @Iluvinspireu @ClockworkHamma @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @roads2 @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/LOjqgaZU5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why me and mine got a kitty and he sends me cute videos of him and her while I’m away ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only i went and did something different when i graduated i wouldnt be in this situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieFinucan @Arrowhead_Lib @vbkimani @LorrieVoshell @sarahpope0422 I saw your description and thought you might l… https://t.co/aNCGNdxuvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka She is ridiculous!!! And then some... how does her brain work nothing she said makes any sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Liars #liar #liar #DonaldTrump is a liar #60Minutes freedom of the press!]]></document><document><![CDATA[what the fuck? Newport is only a few miles away from me, this is pretty disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady just walked up to me in the club and told me that I’m so beautiful and to not settle for no basic nigga b… https://t.co/UIFnnnqX3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making a guest appearance at hooters today!! Come visit and eat some wings! I’ll be there allllllll day!! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has truly blessed me with the best of friends, and I can’t thank them enough for the love &amp; support they show me daily ❤️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, more dragon progress. @ Fridley, Minnesota https://t.co/53X4OasFXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to @RotaryCR meeting at Noon, as we hear from @JenniferDalyICR speak on the latest economic development new… https://t.co/3YM92lTKuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/W0rsZhSlcl]]></document></documents></author>