<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Today I tried the scaled version of #CrossFitOpen 19.2 and did not even get past the first 8 minutes.  I have to keep working and improving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOX NEWS PUTIN PROPAGANDA THE ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE DUMMING DOWN THE REPUBLICAN PARTY !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In him we have redemption through his blood, the forgiveness of our trespasses, according to the ric…… https://t.co/2B5QuIMUMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Right now, they’re playing with house money and nothing to lose and that’s dangerous for the rest of us” Norwalk h… https://t.co/AhHANQ3i7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyScurll @haoming_mask Is that the Villain aloha/Hawaiian shirt hanging behind you?? I'm still waiting for that… https://t.co/MY03bqNwHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolFGC @ProWrestlingPST @defyNW @3irishboyz @406Yeti @swerveconfident My favorite Serve moment was when he did the… https://t.co/oQA2ZwaBZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wearenorth99 why have I and a number of Liberal voices been removed from the Action Group? This is incredibly frei… https://t.co/h2DKkk0h62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@james_jordan_ks @stewartdantec Listen close now: IF YOU ARE A WHITE PERSON WHO HAS BENEFITED FROM A DISCRIMINATORY… https://t.co/7yE54jN7TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY TOLEDO, JOIN US THIS SUNDAY FOR A WONDERFUL BLACK HISTORY PROGRAM AND BUFFET AT THE HISTORIC CLUB 300!!!! https://t.co/OOCoDYqQ6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cause I think we can make it, in fact, I’m sure. And if you fall, stand tall and comeback for more” @ian_cade3 https://t.co/eq9faWW033]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great, especially at DTW. - Drinking a Norm's Raggedy Ass IPA by @griffinclaw @ Chili's  — https://t.co/VuagKPxfNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to catch the fam this season @idropcoldbucks 32 ball on Upstate tonight https://t.co/N5QUbhCIVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsjannings It is not 100% done, but there has been a steady train of kids working in this project. Eventually the… https://t.co/EJpJBtOoSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In-depth article on  @svvanguards - @GSSpartanSports boys hoops state playoff game by my main man @AndyBrackets… https://t.co/cgrLsoFj6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what @danielpuder and I  are working on yet but I can tell that it's going to leave a legacy!… https://t.co/Mdlp0q9rCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek @marcorubio @SecPompeo Puppet Rubio Posts Pic of Gaddafi's Murder as Puppet Pompeo Says Maduro's Days… https://t.co/cAgBnLDfW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doc Rivers stops Clippers game to give Dirk Nowitzi one final standing ovation!  https://t.co/rHlvAV8ktq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 70s show and How I Met Your Mother are the best shows of all time. Fight me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGD98 @NateSilver538 It seems totally insane even by GOP standards to open Pandora’s box over a stupid wall they k… https://t.co/QPP8Rz1zeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago!  Let’s give this amazing team some love tonight!  This film is BRILLIANT and very deserving of Oscar glory… https://t.co/wLytbUwDZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neyugnhannah I feel like volume 3 of Nursing is where you finally get to the good stuff https://t.co/UoTgbGiGda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was one of the worst turbulent flights I’ve been on. Where’s the doggy bag 🤢 https://t.co/N135qtyXXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the #Hawks lose to a team with a worse record than them...  #TrueToAtlanta https://t.co/ciVqtsyoCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nationalist4T @CoachMach @AFReport17 @KFerrugia @Dee4500Peter @Charisma_Fries @AppSame @AOC @IlhanMN That makes pr… https://t.co/p90exT6v4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One Impeach Trump &amp; prosecute, now! ☯️☮️💛💚💙! https://t.co/LVIrscPXKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertarianBlue @SebGorka Brave person!! Need both sides of the story!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GreenwoodBrews is one example of several ♀️-owned 🍻 in @downtownphoenix. @azcentral: "A number of other women hel… https://t.co/0FusIniNYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone player wearing Paul George shoes in Cameron indoor https://t.co/dfm9T7NyU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy You got that right today is anti-fascists are themselves fascist and they don't even know it I even… https://t.co/CfLrJE9xrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryBro77801894 @Lady_Red_2 @DaireFeeney @AnnaSemlyen1 @Alyssa_Milano I see your points. Maybe we can focus on the… https://t.co/X4UsufJSDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCPSKY @UofLFootball @LouisvilleLCARE @GoCards @JCPSSuper @JCPSRenee @JCPS_Attendance @tkonz @es_maupin… https://t.co/P3z6hvtSQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[DATA Sets and AI Applications..........What are the Bias Issues ? Impact of 5G Rollout and Application Utilizations… https://t.co/TY4fmOpdAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimWork13 @ScottKuffel Oh great...I’ll see what I can do and will try not to forget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Israel_Romm @carlos__alsina La verdad es que es un tipo mordaz, con un estilo muy peculiar......hace tiempo que la… https://t.co/39LISfH23R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats are trying to water down Ilhan Omar's anti-Semitic comments to include all anti comments/This is not abou… https://t.co/ieeEtULo8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I Think of The Wasted Time Taken Away From Honest Citizend of Chicago 2 Investigate This Manufactured Incident… https://t.co/fHxAgZBHT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be heading over to the CFSB Center this AM for the 1st Region Basketball Tournament draw. Things tip-off Monda… https://t.co/RwT5RWqI4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Sounds about par for the course for this out loud 🍊 ass-clown 🤡 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shows you how stupid he really is.  #JuanWilliams is @FoxNews answer to @CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[an election  judged fair by international observers. He may be  incompetent  economically but is not a dictator, Bu… https://t.co/OU61Pny33T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poetickate I once used a Blink 182 song as the basis of a sacrament talk. It was Josie and my friends laughed. Dad… https://t.co/cUAqQ9tocP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MxLambda I'm thinking about leave monad transformers out and explaining mtl classes in terms of concrete monads. E… https://t.co/dKnRnpCCwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @DrWhoisin @jan_cois @Debby_Villegas @SydneyDChase @robin_ked @anna_deardorff @Michael_Hudak… https://t.co/kyNwkDLyBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANOTHER new property to the market in Morris Twp. Great 3 bedroom and 2 bathroom close to town, hospital and easy c… https://t.co/JzM1zMdpRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang I’m sorry about Frank - he was the necessary punctuation. Good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Star Gratiot 21 - @amctheatres in Clinton Township, MI https://t.co/4kuHHCOSoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is a big bowl of noodles on a cold evening @ Pho VN Cuisine https://t.co/NYLOH0r6HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's early and chilly, but here I am #brea8k @ Brea, California https://t.co/9hWd0b27qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanNBCBoston Absolutely- A really special moment. are you able to grab the video off Twitter or do I need to send it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t root for this guy to have a long, impactful @MLS career with the #SJEarthquakes then I feel for ya.… https://t.co/kr5yVPohpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shticky Blonde Ale by @192brewingco @ 192 Brewing Tasting Room — https://t.co/eGhNpxjgHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoomPatrolDCU had puppets Nazis, and, amazingly, it wasn’t the weirdest thing in the episode. This show is amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToBeFrankIAm @TheGoodGodAbove @TheDemocrats @realDonaldTrump @IlhanMN She ain't an anti-Semit. Stuff the whinging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl ...law suits bankrupt him. And for every life he has ruined may he spend a day in living hell. #ImpeachTrumpNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLB needs to stand up to the players for the good of the game. It’s interesting because in the NFL and NBA, the own… https://t.co/hzoL5LzMNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HadleySheley They both needed the hair before plastic surgery https://t.co/WJJDwJ5f7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One !  https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo https://t.co/G36BGobsM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sayantan_b Season 3 was a huge let down for me but if season 4 bounces back they’re back in mix. Those other shows… https://t.co/eaWmMbm57O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling recharged and ready to take on another great week! @soulcycle let’s finish off February strong and push tha… https://t.co/vDv6VvCxEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueCollarFishn @XStreamFisher @Man_I_Fish @JacksLures @vjbanks58 @fishin4restofus @BHOAdventures @BamaOutdoors… https://t.co/mkoQYMCgsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’d like to start out Sunday with a Happy Belated 1st Birthday to the Duran Duran Litter!! 🐶 . . If you have been… https://t.co/9QnzEHq7gC]]></document><document><![CDATA[He spent the next three hours telling you every players hometown and junior team without pausing once...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CranfordChip Thanks Chip. Praise the God we serve my man! Appreciate your encouragement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm- wonder if Tiger’s people will now cut off ESPN for this veiled shot:) @riger1984 @bchapsports @MikeSullivan… https://t.co/3enC2n6MlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The American people are being held hostage by your admin. #PornStarPayment #NoWall #MuellerIsComing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promised some law enforcement a screenshot of my Google play music app so here it is.. I don't have much of a col… https://t.co/xdzYi3YXCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legeregraphics @OttawaPolice But can you remember to do that in the heat of the moment when your adrenaline is pum… https://t.co/zvJYtomxJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just waiting for that disappointing notification even tho I know he’s not signing with us 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[and grandpa simpson helped them get the house shortly before they put him in a retirement home]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who say retweet on social media sites that aren’t Twitter scare the shit out of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Why does any country follow America’s “sanctions” during the age of Trumpism. Russia/China, why do they c… https://t.co/s2FK2wLHj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSTwinCities put out some great stats today, among them is this one...if you don’t remember a March afternoon thi… https://t.co/GWRiQxcb9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsram311 @FikeMeeney My FIL passed away and my MIL came to live with us temporarily.  Temporary = 10 years on Planet InLaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineShannonDC And the Canadian in that news story should be put away for life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snidog All my best!!!   Your daughter is so valuable and I k ow that you will do your best to ensure that she unde… https://t.co/p2fGQopkGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinero hay para divertirse, si no esta la tarjeta 😊 https://t.co/djWyu65CWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone, Happy Friday!! I pray🙏🏽🙏🏽  you have a wonderful, productive, and relaxing day. To God be the glory!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💞 REPOST from @lgbt_history_ig “Beauty and the devil are the same thing.” – Robert Mapplethorpe . Picture: Robert M… https://t.co/ehkSG5Bu3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are these teachers in stories who tell kids, “you’ll never amount to anything?”  And where do they teach?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just began a running workout using #Endomondo. Peptalk me now @ https://t.co/oJqVm04nSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Darrin_Peschka and I interviewed Congresswoman Katie Hill after an event in Simi. She talked about everything fro… https://t.co/4cGZkVhHIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela, After Liberation: Justice    via @forbes https://t.co/PNsWjv8FYt my article for Venezuelan fooD day. In… https://t.co/utjntwGw6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[my other accounts: @wastelandjoon  @demondogz  project accounts: @friendsimfandub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@given_matt That’s not what you said. You said she didn’t want white males to see it, and that you were respecting… https://t.co/sCx68ZSVOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I published this 2 weeks ago. 75,000 readers in six continents later, I now realize why Buddy Holly's music will ne… https://t.co/PRUL6elJLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Leon has 15 points at the half for @OESJathletics, working a lot off of high pick-and-roll with Jack Brundage… https://t.co/wFMOLrU1RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: This city recognizes a BROTHER, and they're showing him ALL THE LOVE!  #RAW @WWERomanReigns… https://t.co/Rbt8jWL9xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to be in Atkins all night but hey MAY 11TH IM RUNNING ACROSS THAT STAGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @keithboykin People???????? This is all I have to say. There are no words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely love his gift of giving back! When we know better, doing the right thing comes natural! Congratulations… https://t.co/M26M09I4uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstrosOptimism2 I was on last year, but I don’t think I got to 130 ABs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamTimbur starts the rundown play and @weinert_lucas puts on the tag today for the Norse against Hagerstown, Maryl… https://t.co/7QCWsO2tFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImjustagirlJm @KarinSheets @DaddyBookins @UPS I have had some good service from FedEx. I think your experience had… https://t.co/O1giCY54GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little more accurate than #23andMe @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/Vz07NH4UxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now these three remain: faith, hope and love. But the greatest of these is love - 1 Corinthians 13:13 🙏🏼4our🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst service ever.  Manager said no to me when I asked for a “burger with no meat” because it wasn’t an option on… https://t.co/g2S1qzDVJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WajahatAli I am a white guy from central Texas...fairly thick accent...once, while in San Francisco, I overheard a… https://t.co/xrS5X00w1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WithOutHashTagGames my gif game wouldn't be on... https://t.co/DcwXqnQDTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[if text signatures came back what would yours be? mines  - whop won’t stop💢💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MRobFresh1 @imaladywith3 @thatgrapejuice FBI was still convinced MJ assaulted upto 24 victims.]]></document></documents></author>