<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tracinnasv I hope you can get the very best care and feel better soon. If I was any help I I’m so glad. Let me kno… https://t.co/lrj7QMiL8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of International Women's Day 2019: A big thank you goes out to each of these amazing women who were the fi… https://t.co/de3EtavgP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t agree with all of this—I thought the bird thing was adorable—but I like this piece. I find Sanders more lik… https://t.co/AZi4KbQCw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotivateU1 People are ignorant. Thank you Mo! Sending you love and blessings as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[☔️ When the rain messes up my hair ☔️ The salon opens at 9am.  Visit us at 6459 Hwy 42, Unit 14 in Rex, GA.  Call u… https://t.co/01hCCDvCdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ur ever looking for a giant dose of birth control, just go to a museum on a holiday weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaRed4 @debiowens There was no rationalizing with my sister.  She wouldn’t even listen.  I sent her some artic… https://t.co/MHpqSdKi42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #LittleMonsters. I don't think I'll be able to sleep with my foot out of the covers tonight.  @howiemandel #FredSavage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailBenzler @_drazzari @EatingBeagles @Oreo @boozychef There is actually a link where to find them for sale 😨 https://t.co/8EPjhq595h]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a red carpet was being rolled out for Kim Jong Un, the American press was being kicked out of the hotel they sha… https://t.co/AYHLSM4OpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell But he’s right, it would look phony for him to walk around the WH lawn with a dog because a) he does… https://t.co/YxEbincs1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frances_712 @consmover 🤣🤣🤣this is funny every time she opens her mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamYouTube Please check on your decision to ban @trnrtips and @MYSTIC7 from YouTube.  These young men are creatin… https://t.co/9chnIqy8LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmichprez This is AMAZING!!!  Lucky you!  I love @angiecthomas messages and her books, as do my students! #YANovels #FireUpChips]]></document><document><![CDATA[@updatewithinfo @DYShor @benshapiro @IlhanMN You can criticize Isreal without questioning the loyalty of those that… https://t.co/S25d3gDtGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Godbold @DontSilenceMe2 @Godbold @_jessicabarth_ @thekatkendall Yes we are - Sisters! 💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the awesome dunk show @continentaltire! #bucketsweepstakes https://t.co/TOTWOwEZCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uppitykiki @rkelly @LoveOnTheBlu How bout Wd chug your dry ass down!! Leave this woman alone and RKelly social med… https://t.co/G0DzLGbJ6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsledz_MRO @Jb5Jane @ArmchairExpPod You know it! It’s amazing how we can impact attitude with words. If only we co… https://t.co/8qqfovhljZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[at the @iiiPoints festival listening to @jamesblake, do i text my ex or nah? mad libra energy, will be gone in a.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Spirit Busses are full of Chrisman Bears and headed to @SECArenaKC to cheer on our @Chrisman_hoops team in the… https://t.co/4aesA8E8Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may have heard... Ummmm yes @Andy! We are still waiting for a secret mini series of this day! #housewivessuperbowl #BravoTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariaceciliafer Nopo. Fue Leloir y el nombre fue porque la mezcla la hizo en un club de golf 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the other hand there is not enough money for @pac12 in any sport but gymnastics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the females who got bills and can’t travel in time for this spring break where we going this summer ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@advocate_peace I feel like writing in these shows should be timeless. Ya know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @joe_warmington yeah about the same as y'all gave Justice Kavanaugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey no saben lo cansada que estoy, al chile no iría a la escuela pero tengo que ir 🥺🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyWho you are an angel and a breath of fresh air. I simply adore you!!!  Thank you for taking the time to chat… https://t.co/kPKpARW7K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robynsaghini @jay_riddle Probably rest them for Cincinatti then cause they’re weak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't fall for you, can't give my all to you I can't let you think that Imma let the game stall for you..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mermhart @martaduss It truly is a fantastic series and so nice when other thespians like yourself praise others for their work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustavoPuig5 @jgamorin @Tribiln2 @bugabea @oscarsito1956 @Cabrosa18 @Nai248 @MontevideoLatam @qkyfernandez59… https://t.co/saTjBcoxmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halseanderson @WritetoLearnMO It is gut wrenching pain. So sorry, I hope it’s gone and you are getting back to yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Celebrities have often donated time and talent and no one in either party has shamed them for it. It… https://t.co/irMvCcm822]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkroepke @heatfin1 @anothercc @buttons30 @Acarl1985 @eGolf63 @honeyburns @BrinsonEb @DocGiani @doodldoo @BxBabe717… https://t.co/oUJlaPDDCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenGaglian2 @Me_Bizarro @JustmeElc @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump Well said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should follow my brilliant &amp; funny &amp; smart AF cousin, @SarahHelenS  She recently got in the Twitter ⚡️⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very exciting day: we will soon be the proud parents of two guinea pigs. Some moments of early shopping. 1 month of… https://t.co/j0LY2STlVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseCruz12 @marcorubio @FelipeCalderon @NicolasMaduro Me pregunto?si tanto les gusta ese regimen,por qué no se van ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time at supercross!!! @SupercrossLIVE #SupercrossLIVE https://t.co/SrVxHGNzgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine anyone?!? Stop in at my OPEN HOUSE, Thursday evening 2/28, 5:30pm-7:30pm at 221 Twining Lane Wayne, PA. Stop b… https://t.co/pGLLqn3Vjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vwop I agree w/you. Simply curious, would you vote for Biden? He’s our guy. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blsamaddar @AnconaDanielle @dkmarie2216s @WriterSkyeMcD @teamechavarre @BB_Swann @evascalzo @LilyMichaels25… https://t.co/UtxZNCzDC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @manikchhabra for your commitment to address the #chronicpain needs of our #veterans within an innovative… https://t.co/htarSUUICm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why Mother Nature decided To drop the fucking bomb on me today  🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘cause its just another day in the life 👯‍♀️🎀📚 @ W Washington D.C. Hotel https://t.co/VqTnjAl7Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple Passion by DND, Sour Grapes by @lightelegancehq ! Link in bio to book! . . #nails #nailart #nailtech… https://t.co/QZSg6nz76r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Count on me to vote for the ham sandwich if nominated by the Democratic Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. House of Representatives: expel or remove rep Ilhan Omar from office for anti-Semitic statements - Sign the Pe… https://t.co/RtA9Q8cDvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok I will never make the mistake of missing ARTY when he comes to Atlanta ever AGAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonforeman, If only there were a way for me to work for @switchfoot remotely from Virginia! That would be stellar!! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[A-B Tech, county reach deal for sales tax advisory committee https://t.co/F78Knmistf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will QCHS make it in to school tomorrow Monday, March 4? @QCHSAthletics @QchsSection19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilovecucks2 @surreyleftie @DonaldJTrumpJr Watch You Tubers Jimmy Dore, The Young Turks, Secular Talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bourgeoisalien @JMooreBoston There will be a run on adult diapers-pants pooping time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[let’s do this!! #runaholics #rocknrolldchalfmarathon #itscold #pushyourself #noexcuses @ National Museum of America… https://t.co/6lx6kgWLYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss Wallows and I miss Braeden calling us Thai and jogging buddies and I miss Dylan laughing at us and I miss Coles jokes wow I’m big sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeyaSophia @MrRob_Educator @Malinda_Hodges @itsBTerrell Ahem—- Sophie Cunningham, Gabby Williams, Mizzou WBB, West… https://t.co/uOpgA9wb5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp Thanks for your reply, do you anticipate any chance of ever having more?]]></document><document><![CDATA[1000%. And thank god for friends who can help you see you're being gaslit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent and EASY request to fulfill.  Come on dog loving pals - let’s flood Emma’s mailbox!          @johncusack… https://t.co/9A2f9Jhm0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last semester I wouldn’t even try to go to the rec that was 20 steps outside of my dorm but I’ve gone 2 days in a r… https://t.co/ODX02cRM5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids Rule the School Day!! Principal, AP, and Counselor delivering treats to the teachers!! #teambce… https://t.co/XxGO7OSL50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @soph_35! Hope ya have a great day girl. Miss you bunches💕🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Whitaker eather your for our Country or your with Trump and Putin. IF YOU stand with them your a TRADER to our Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD bless BIG Lee - he paved the road and he did it his way! One of my favorites!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preschool Open House and Kindergarten Information night is on MONDAY! Please contact the elementary office of you h… https://t.co/jtGJBIW2OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman They have to make thier own country great from within. They have  thousands of people wanting to get… https://t.co/2pNjH770uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thecutlife #h#hederacreme #chicagostylist #stylesbyivy #hederafied #mohawk @ House of Hedera's/Hedera replenishing… https://t.co/d2oSt5SF5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went mia for a bit friends.. I’m sorry, but when In mourning it’s best to keep that energy to yourself..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0ryuge @DeeBrown1774 @thehill At trying to insult me for no reason other than being petulant. Trump is not in grea… https://t.co/WZgi9I1vXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an amazing group of educators finished up their 7 day math pd experience. Thank you for all of your hard work… https://t.co/13HkXciY9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[El cambio es un hecho ya no hay vuelta atrás, cada vez somos más visibles, más representativas y en mayor número de… https://t.co/Ev2FmEGJOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for the dart...#freezing #memoriesforalifetime @ Convention Center District, Dallas https://t.co/WZLwP6NHGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plant Your Roots: Picking Your Home Location https://t.co/GelPA0JSg4 Contact my if I can with any of Realestate needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sterlingalexis Bruh .... why did I get this bathsuit for spring break 💀 definitely not wearing it like this though 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @Illini_DaveK to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no review - just… https://t.co/XTgg2RhcpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwenners @ParkerMolloy It’s just a matter of time.  Give her a free minute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️ welcome back noah.rodriguez_ ⚾️ #jumpon1kid #way2smackit #gainsomemomentum #6 #trips @ Tesoro High School Baseba… https://t.co/gWcJBzrT4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mijo gave us flowers for V Day. Thanks mijo! @geerodreezy 😍😘 * * * * * #flowers #son #valentinesday #amosartphotos… https://t.co/nZLZlVTOSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[timhortons gave away a very generous prize tonight... Coffee for an entire year! Congrats Wendy! ☕️ @ Barrie Colts… https://t.co/obj7uLJDnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the bulk of my Twitter is mainly folks that I know from RL, but far and away the two people I most enjoy that I… https://t.co/VgPWEAE2Yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XTransCentral @SissyMelodyb @cute_natalieX @pinkmiua @TSVeronicaDark @NessaFSB @ts_arielle @Amandapink69TS… https://t.co/lnTf0GUGpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Friday night! #dirtymartinitime🍸🍸🍸 #bluecheesestuffedolives @ The Lakes, Spring Valley https://t.co/fMUy3QR8l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonjatMorgan I remember...its beautiful. Red is definitely your color lovely lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#21daychallenge #buildinghealtyhabits #teamwork @ The Learning Center Charter School https://t.co/Tu6S3H7DmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbendery @NRA How do we file a  class action lawsuit against the NRA.  They would have never done this if it was a… https://t.co/YiGnzd63FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all have a mother in law who isn’t a psychotic bitch, I’m so jealous of you. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princethomas @DrayFamous @Bharper3407 10/345 opt outs at 3 and 6 years https://t.co/63cptDQFNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it’s GREAT—All the Press Briefings Were Was A Blatant Hate Trump Hate Sarah Briefing—Who could be the NASTIEST… https://t.co/QHdVGTBAOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting song request to dance to &amp; that shit makes my heart melt fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollywoodmedium @tyhenrymedium @lizzo @howiemandel 👌🏼 &amp;.. the baby pictures of Howie is adorable..👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHAS11 Cowardly stunt to use 8 month old &amp; another child. Needs to see lots of years thru bars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing the wedding is almost 2 weeks away. Literally about to shit myself 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pineapple belongs on pizza Pineapple belongs on pizza Pineapple belongs on pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenisaCasement @NPOfriend There's no nonprofit in the world that can't take 30 seconds a day to snap a photo about… https://t.co/tsL2jfeZPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will I go to English class today ? Find out on the next episode of my college life]]></document><document><![CDATA[En verás  lo nunca visto, está  la clave. En la batalla de la luz contra la sombra. El Gran Inicio. Recuerdas estas… https://t.co/lhawHZRl5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindy_looloo511 I knew i had something similar to you but i couldn’t put my finger on it ♉️ https://t.co/IggnqWdjon]]></document></documents></author>