<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@amichaelswx @AmyFox43 My morning alarm is the radio, but since the wind knocked the station’s transmitter out, I w… https://t.co/C0YJDe8c7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @KellyannePolls Ahhh, so believable coming from the State Run Propaganda News Network and the White House mout… https://t.co/9EP8qMiktk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a grand time at DeafOpia Expo in Austin, Texas. Love you all! #superdeafy #johnmaucere #texasschoolforthedeaf… https://t.co/zICeaKy3cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m having arthroscopic knee surgery first thing Monday morning. It would be great to come out of anesthesia and… https://t.co/zKJgATzHK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my latest vid. Tribute to Dick Trickle https://t.co/nxyuKeAiqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briscaloosa @JordanLaPorta 1. Roll Call 2. End the fed chants 3. ????? 4. meeting adjourned   Did I get everything??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the Brockville tunnel opening again in the spring.  #brockville #canada #train #purple… https://t.co/krJWqe0fo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing better than laughing with your best friends until 5 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherry25793049 @Preacher_BF Is this America or Nazi Germany. I thought Josef Mengala was dead. They must still hav… https://t.co/Yji3S7PM5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKenzi73952465 @PistonsPlay @blakegriffin23 @LAClippers @DetroitPistons They need to trade him like we did with  Grant Hill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm @TPM Bet the nogoods aren’t Jewish. Probably Christians with MAGA hats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidbilly929 @CelliniNick I agree with you 100% Beau, but just to note... a torn Pectoral is MUCH different than a torn ACL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffsetYRN album is just so fire. I took a couple of my dogs on a lick 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief, thoughts and prayers to the family and you and your extended firefighting family we are here if you need us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Muir Woods Redwood Forest https://t.co/bKsHj6gJ6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantaanaRay @WORLDSTAR I guess you done already won then cause you never at work!🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @RonnieLouise2 🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🛑🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️… https://t.co/URRSWwiYE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OleMiss_Rebel83 @tiffinwildcat @karinasophia12 @plainwildcatfan She's a big girl dude ... we've bantered before. Stay in your lane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apaulbullock This movie breaks me... I love it but it turns me into a blubbery mess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InSessionFilm Yea I thought it was the right choice.   Although felt the opening action beat was poorly staged and… https://t.co/Q4QJoYnbXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[islamic babies become islamic men and women.  The islamics intend to conquer your country from the inside, if you a… https://t.co/Or7cS7LboC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesarienVamp I think it is easier for me to share my thoughts and emotions online as well. In-person has its advan… https://t.co/MPcBRy85wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rocnation #Pop #OnMyWay #NewMusic  #Africa  #Source #Hiphop #RandB #xxl #wshh #defjam  #Atlanta #Hollywood… https://t.co/lPF87ugGEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalAlbaneseNYC That may be a sort of “constituent service toward the will of the people” but if the cameras are ne… https://t.co/QUcGmyazXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fractured back, haven't competed in 18 months, but @AbbyPaulson is still a beam queen! #prouddad #lovethefight #NorthernLights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my guy @j_routte have a great day man! https://t.co/qi68XdtcC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smarty3385 he is good young prospect .... didn't get the time with Winnipeg who are deep .... even Lainie isn't ge… https://t.co/hMxJPuPdvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Obama took office we were losing almost 2,000,000 jobs a month. When he left office we were creating about 150… https://t.co/KDgQyXXk4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final home game of the season for @AlabamaWBB and one more opportunity to work with the best band leader in the lan… https://t.co/rErpSm2CDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be providing rides from the bus barn on 103rd if you all need transportation assistance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Proof he’s making an impact... truth to power. Your campaign will be as successful as your anti-Trump… https://t.co/emci8atFDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPMIndyCar @Ericsson_Marcus @Hinchtown Hey @SecondCityTO.  @Ericsson_Marcus and @Hinchtown may want to stop by dur… https://t.co/wWBRrmYwCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thugkotah @erin92_m It’s been this long I can almost guarantee he went to Mexico. Smh sad man and fuck them teo bi… https://t.co/4E1Ouc2L0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what #TastesBetterThanCake? Looking at adorable pet pics with clever captions. Check out @HoosierMamaTags’… https://t.co/kxqyWJrH55]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes. Jon Jones failed a couple more drug tests. Now it really is fight week. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[The older I get, the more I’m amazed the Allman’s Live at the Fillmore East was made by a bunch of dudes in their early 20s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like that I've changed my mind regarding All Star wknd as my alma mater gets to keep the 3point trophy won by… https://t.co/MTfAG9KZOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ultron just blacklisted Claire from the Breakfast Club &amp; this movie just kicked my fan fiction’s ass. https://t.co/Q7gijLLFnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[So instead they're going to create curriculum and encourage policies that they believe will mitigate the risk, leav… https://t.co/6vQwW4hVEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how people are mad at how people reacted with the clock..but are literally reacting the same way with the ki… https://t.co/nJKn86p6qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRebelOfDeath @BeckyLynchWWE @RondaRousey Oh Geebus NO...  (If Ronnie gets that reference, she may 🤯🤯 even more than she did earlier.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast 🍳 with my boys! Where’s that waffle emoji?! We need that (at @WaffleHouse in Reynoldsburg, OH) https://t.co/hj8QRocnEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattLoveless It's very interesting because on one hand your guaranteed money, on the other, think about what contr… https://t.co/4F7Se3od6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wall Street Journal: Startup Backed by SoftBank Pours Money Into a Bid to Reshape Construction. https://t.co/DjF9VoAldU  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leann Rimes - Purple Rain...I think this will end up being the most enduring song from the 80s... https://t.co/4K3vPCcDhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick_leitz That happens so often. Just don’t understand why anticipation fouls are called. Drives me crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyPitts_WSFA Hmm...If someone asks @realDonaldTrump to sign their Bible, should he say "no"?  "No one is 'good'… https://t.co/naKZqPQVkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my boo’s birthday. Happy Birthday @OVRFLWG  Party like a Rock star. Love you girl!!!!#HappyBirthday https://t.co/0wLRMrkcXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yummy😋😋 #foodporn #foodie #amicoolyet 😎😉👍👌😅 @ Two Rivers, Wisconsin https://t.co/wX6EWmgZ5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fitness - Increased work capacity across broad time and modal domains. ”Crossfit” #CrossFit #fitness #FitnessMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending Valentines Day learning more about the Chicago mayoral candidates while listening to Ennio Morricone don’t @ me]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I tend to believe in science, I though I swear I have found mistakes in books.  I have faith but I d… https://t.co/Prr5AJdpeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me today to get your act together before going out and looking at homes or condos - 843-683-7999 https://t.co/nP9t5dLNUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5 years @ShowdownGG 🎊🎮🕹 Here's another 5 more 🍻 https://t.co/KkjcM3yia1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christie1968ic1 @SpeakerPelosi Wish I could Afford to Leave mexifornia commifornia Back to the Good ol USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighlandL4ss Or she just wants you to think she's practically blind so she can get on the bed. Cats are shady as f***.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 year ❤️ (the thread ends but the relationship doesn’t 😉) hope you guys enjoyed my thread of this hottie https://t.co/bPHpXBQH0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home from #HIMSS19 gotta love @SouthwestAir offering free cocktails on Valentine’s Day. Luv you @SouthwestAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WmScottBlair @ClarkKe95563197 @CharlieD2749 @KentSailor @DoodlesTrks @janetshoemake @roosterpisces @Marizellell… https://t.co/5PLx0NjUV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenePark My car would’ve been all over that fish before I even started cutting it. He’d leap from the fridge ninja… https://t.co/E3j0tlA6LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmilelyLoriLynn @TheFive I agree he is absolutely destroying the Five Show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces me pregunto donde habías estado este tiempo, pero fue en el momento exacto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaceMCS Jac H, Dave Blaney, Bobby Davis Jr, Charlie Swartz and JW Hunt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great DNC move. Fox has become the Trump propaganda arm. No credibility. Hannity, Carlson and others leave a perman… https://t.co/frvW0EGYZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUMAN79 I have not been able to watch More than a couple minutes of a game in years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jw @jasonglaspey @mds @mds-ed my @Dropbox all day yesterday  Sparked so much joy 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic speakers coming to Glasgow on April 5th for Cardiac Marker Dialogues 2019 Meeting -  Allan Jaffe, Fred Ap… https://t.co/io35UJ19n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife bought me a Pixel 3 smartphone for my bday. I use a cell phone maybe twice a year, not to mention I detest… https://t.co/l6FBBmwiAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dillzilla99 @DonaldODaniels1 @Lainyy626 @fritchee @george_capen It has to do with your tweet that “nobody” voted f… https://t.co/7Bdr7ymF5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warriors shit stupid. Demarcus cousins hitting. 3s. It’s great for legit dub fans n ppl from the bay. But it’s awfu… https://t.co/JtSMqDcg1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yep, all we need now is a President that’s not batsh!t crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyBarnardFES @laroldan32 @TXLuisMartinez @AmberHaley1216 @BradDouglas0569 @569_Night_Ops Great Job J u d i t h… https://t.co/KAGXXSgnER]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have punched Valentine had I been sitting in Oscar's seats... brutal call. #Bearcats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawsen_Webb @RandallKraft @Larryputt @Mark4One @AndrewClarkman @BradfordCotton5 @Quin4Trump @KLHirst1… https://t.co/ldyqZFvpiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fondue night!! 🤤🤤🤤🤤🤤 Cheese and dessert #cookingclub #allthecheese @ Oakville, Ontario https://t.co/oJByb5S7RR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppStTailgate @appstatesports Definitely big donation. Doug has already teased that in an earlier tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadicalxEdward @CTaramore @Timcast So Kavanaugh can remember who was at one party on his calendar but can’t rememb… https://t.co/ILZBzjuNPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadenJake But it also think, conceptually, this isn’t the right way to think of a company’s capitalization and re-… https://t.co/Jy1wITsX2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, it really bugs me that I didn’t spell Connor correctly. Sometimes autocorrect can fail you. https://t.co/C4lQbSuQHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Félicitations aux gestionnaires de @LaCDPQ pour savoir naviguer dans ces marchés volatils .]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re an adult when you get excited for Dawn being on sale for $0.99! #serendipity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Change takes investment. Time, energy, effort, financial, etc. A lot of people don’t get the results they think the… https://t.co/uZpRtWrMU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is worse than seeing someone hurt and not being able to comfort them because your 800+ miles away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to spend some time with @coachtheronaych yesterday at Glazier Seattle.  Great insight into UofA offense and coa… https://t.co/w5G46DUeuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EditinKing Mayweather Promotions: where douchebags and clowns train at .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdufu @AOC @GirlsWhoCode @reshmasaujani Three idols. One picture. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TH0MASCHABOT @JHYellowknife @BonksMullet @Sens_Army_ @SensDivision @CudmoreColin @senstalk_ You might be the only one at the rink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwigbyg @Hesiod2k11 @DaisyButtercup @T4RIG @kraft_mike @DavidKlion I guess my main issue is the idea that all the… https://t.co/FJr6ZCMfs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was taught to never let an outfit go to waste 💪🏻 @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/aieBuuanjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nmenon777 @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump Don't  preach  to  me! I  make  60k  per  year  have  worked 2 job's  pu… https://t.co/IgbgS8sE0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinroseglass How would people like @aoc learn about law without bartending expertise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antasc1d82 @mwalsh11061965 @dkrwallace @IvankaTrump @WhiteHouseCEA I know you REALLY want Ivanka’s graph to be mor… https://t.co/nMOkP7roN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Founders Day! Celebrating Scouting at the Georgetown BP Banquet tonight! Thanks to all the Scouters, parents… https://t.co/sg3drGrMUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess this helps explain why drivers feel like they can do whatever they want in Greenpoint all these years. No w… https://t.co/SmAuWoRNnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatpetewoods I’d go to every convention I could since I was 17. Showing my pencil interiors. I would get rejected… https://t.co/QSQctvRoYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[oops typo. Meant:  Twitteratus (n.) = Twitter habitue / user / practitioner / wallah / etc.  [Based on Twitter + literatus]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realcindyhels @JacobAWohl yeah, well one time i saw on the news all people named Cindy sell human flesh as meat in… https://t.co/VF1QGgT4nA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Valentine's Day Spotlight To My Valentines, Mark  February 15, 2019 Repainting The Sky Chap… https://t.co/W7wR6pQFqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone has to find a clever way to study whether Giannis’ rise to superstardom leads Bucks fans to have a more fav… https://t.co/B04xqMKg3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicahBalz13 to Jordan Dwyer for the game winner! @HeirFootball #Pylon7on7 https://t.co/nx0SuHifSh]]></document></documents></author>