<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you @HawaiiDelilah for the tipoff to an extraordinarily calm and erudite article pleading for an American res… https://t.co/DV9YC2CjJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCCowboy @politico No Dem believes babies actually born can still be aborted. That's a disgusting lie and you shou… https://t.co/NqVMlGuOBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather @SpeakerPelosi Mr Trump will have no problem taking himself down. It’s just a matter of time so yes, it’s not worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chelsea Waterside Park Dog Run - @hudsonriverpark in New York, NY https://t.co/43oGv5vG9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dish_answers Nothing just a black screen so I switched to the SD  209 and it's black also]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shouldn't take long to clean up the mess.....the top shelves are still in place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote this when Steve Irwin died. Amazing guy. His methods were sometimes a bit strange, but the man was deeply d… https://t.co/acyZyAY5gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record...i believe the exact opposite.  I think he recovers his lost velocity and has a cy young year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shugheswrites @SaraTraceyTU @WillGordonAgain Peppermint patties are the best if you want a sort of mint taste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need the cowboys to sign Earl Thomas this free agency .. his price should be lower because of the injury last season]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could spoil the shit outta someone tomorrow. But I’m not. Im just going to keep doing my thing. Cause fuck it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Joel promote Alizas crafts is funny asf 😂😂 that shit hella girly.. You gotta do what you gotta do for your lady though 🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Krampus n #plaguedoctor in the house @wizardworld #cosplayer #cosplayers #comiccon #cleveland @ Huntington Convent… https://t.co/le1RJcsvuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benigma2017 @CNN @wolfblitzer Simply because They can. It's the trying to get away with it that's become a struggle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEAMWORK! OTD 1972, M*A*S*H debuted. For 11 yrs the War-Comedy-Drama showed how a diverse group of medical pros/sol… https://t.co/btYnggfF44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Action from @STMAGBB 70-48 road win over @BuffaloGBB. https://t.co/UnsFGJf38P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miiidnight_ No need to apologize. No excuse to drive impaired, especially nowadays with options like Uber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else remember this show? Because I used to watch it when I was little and the theme was LIT.   https://t.co/lJrNyinZvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have ran across a young lady with her eyebrows painted on, turns out that she was looking like The Rock the Wrasstl… https://t.co/pR9l2MIXpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get over it Rebels/Black Bears/Whateveryoucallyourselvesthesedays. You lost. Move on.   Ole Miss fans protest last-… https://t.co/48pHVLSiHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pizzas are here! @united you're team is amazing #sfo #unitedcares https://t.co/dXT23unoby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night at Mar-a-Lago with longtime friends @WinkMartindale and @jonvoight ! Great laughs and stories were abund… https://t.co/lhMbLvsIPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready to switch back to my gold shoes! 😩😩😩  wickedlyboosted https://t.co/aVslapfsEk limitlesscarcare @JDMFV sw… https://t.co/M1UB8TDAYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was invited to a marketing meeting with my University and I didn't doubt the total salary of the room probably ca… https://t.co/jaMQcfE38P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be on a panel of Mystery writers at the annual meeting of Florida Historical Society to discuss the role of hi… https://t.co/h02MR88O9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 2461 PEBBLE BEACH Drive #OaklandTwp #MI  #realestate https://t.co/mEJ3YKybGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me ofrezco a dar charlas en institutos para que los chavales no se dediquen luego a la prensa del videojuego. "Si n… https://t.co/VuRQ77d4yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenhildreth12 I sent it to my spam folder!! Hahahahaha jk jk I'll check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People spend more time in a week with Fishel than they do many of their friends and family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson You’re not worth the effort. You’re a poor journalist, but a very good propagandist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlottecoke You're amazing and doing great things!! I'm proud of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job big Fraizer!! But you got a while to go to if you want to catch me ‼️💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg is by far the most substantive and polished candidate at the #CNNTownHall. It’s not even close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe You are the way the truth, the life I believe You are the way, the truth, the life I believe You are the… https://t.co/7VoZ4luMTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoogleForEdu A1: @CentralNine continues to allow my crazy to take hold. The entire school is my laboratory and wit… https://t.co/9ox2w4lmkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long day, I came home to find a belated birthday gift had arrived from my good friend @marti0918 .    Die H… https://t.co/sIWoAbKFGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[DOT bans passenger airlines from carry... https://t.co/QXf0Igjwnt via @ATWOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @ReliableSources @maggieNYT @Acosta @oliverdarcy @shelbyholliday @BillKristol @Olivianuzzi… https://t.co/9IZM9Y3xWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNL announcer voice:  BE AMAZED AS THE BRIGHTEST MINDS IN COMEDY SUCK AMAZON'S DICK AND PRODUCE NOT ONE GRUNT WORTH… https://t.co/eYdJimFD0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage @leonys27martin Well done, TB.  LM...this city is like one big family!  Just don't piss us off!  God b… https://t.co/7fFhSBMm4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinsterna @mcuban @swish41 @luka7doncic @dallasmavs Where did you buy these doughnuts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScholarOfDecay @badbooksbadppl Going to give this book a read. Purchased a cheap Barnes &amp; Noble edition. Wish me luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfree23 Might be a little late driving through this blizzard in Rocky Point 🌨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKirkSBN I could beat James Franco, if he was stoned &amp; I snuck up on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While sitting on this planter, I managed to help @johnnybananas with the elevator and then ran into taylorlautner n… https://t.co/CNgKyXVh5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[No room at the top: The stark divide in black and white economic mobility https://t.co/Wa8TfMQ800 via @BrookingsInst]]></document><document><![CDATA[The goal of the #mnwild’s penalty kill should be to get the puck away from the other team 🙄. #MINvsDET #NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SeaWorld San Antonio - @seaworldtexas in San Antonio, TX https://t.co/XWhQivSayh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Millyy Yep, it seems mutual in those situations.  The woman I met had nothing but her dog and kitten both had plenty of food/water/toys]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who don't or never heard of Closes Caption (CC) before. https://t.co/McXHksezwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like getting kicked out of a house show because the host wrongfully accused @ndynmth for pissing on the nei… https://t.co/EYWwBcbZuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #Durham on Miami Blvd and Hwy 70 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm craaaazy stressed out and reached a breaking point yesterday buuut maybe theres a glimmer of hope in the fac… https://t.co/ATqoVTNf1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanHeld @BoggsTrey @BrandenSargent3 @Bradley_Atkins @marshall_noah #ClaimtoFame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle Actually all the corpses I’ve buried now have college degrees and jobs! They’ve worked their way throu… https://t.co/qhgOfGCpho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luv me some breakfast #disTimeOfDay.. come hang at @victorybargrill, now serving breakfast on Saturdays 8am...… https://t.co/incPyIrK3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcunningham3 Change? Yes. Fairness? Yes. Money to college athletes for aspects like likeness and jerseys and autog… https://t.co/BF5HQ4FCHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a live country singer performing in one of the bars! Never expected that in an airport.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@70sBaseball Just realized this exact scenario played out in Yankee Stadium during game 2 of the 1977 World Series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Don't blame Amazon, blame the stupid, cottonhead, good for nothing Rep.AOC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And thats a wrap for the trip, great weather and had a great time. Mahalo, Hawaii! Toronto Summer ‘19 here we come… https://t.co/X9r9sWf2YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sick since the beginning of January, we are almost in March and IM STILL SICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC ....THIS IS A JOKE!!! FIRST THE HIGH STICK AND NOW THE PLAY BLOWN DOWN!!!!! JUSTIFY THIS CRAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are abhorrent, Donald J Trump. #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbBanfieldRN @AllisonRBond @MichaelWardRN @MenInNursing @AAMN_Nursing @atx_nurse Because that moniker is usually… https://t.co/FJY151Kccl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Jack Henry &amp; Associates, Inc team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/33iMoD499Z #IT #Monett, MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tar Heels look to extend the nations longest home winning streak (26) and stay perfect on the season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP He is a Black Man defending his alleged illegal misbehavior, against charges brought by state/local governments… https://t.co/uQmzXlDIZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSpain we in #BucksTwitter got a whole list (see below)! key voices for opinions/fan vibe IMO are @fmaddenNBA… https://t.co/byVau6ad0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mariners middle relievers can’t hold a five-run lead in a 6-5 loss to the Indians https://t.co/ToNRpxMel4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 and I just realized Captain America is Jake from Not Another Teen Movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucydragonn @Cynthia9175583 @realDonaldTrump Have u heard of common sense ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk why i signed up for a 9am-noon accounting class on a friday https://t.co/SNTJEetNwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Mayor Wheeler moves ahead with the independent investigation of police contacts w/ Patriot Prayer, civil rights… https://t.co/TVu3xQYbMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES WE DO WANT TO KNOW,  THAT'S WHY THERE'S A INTERNATIONAL EMERGENCY SOUTH OF THE BORDER... EAT THAT CHUMP...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanKerr_math @AlexOverwijk @BreurBreur “Tracking” is maybe a more common term in the US]]></document><document><![CDATA[Link in my #mixcloud ☝️ #deejaystormnyc #1lyfeent #teamdramadjs   https://t.co/fv7hqwWV1a @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/Tls9udiZe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelFlatley I love old-movies more so than newer-ones. More colorful and more imaginative usually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥎@AuburnSoftball improves to 15-1 at JBM this season (21-4 overall) with 3-2 win vs. Michigan State.… https://t.co/3LBuUJ4gpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to ✈ head back home.   Happy #MardiGras2019 #NOLA  See you again for #JazzFest2109 https://t.co/axKQchFwbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdrhwke @noveryfakenews @GOCOAST @Kathalini @SouthTexasSalt @MichaelKnotts17 @DeniseF78650342 @BigBernieB1… https://t.co/i0hbw49O0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garrett_Wynn But we're gonna be better than the steelers that's for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, that was my first under the influence term...interesting experience nonetheless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TravisAvenue @Rawstv Shit I was living up there too back then. It was wild...but I didn’t lose anyone thankfully… https://t.co/49aASE87PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveBen52466738 @LaurentianNews Uhhh, methinks it is a satirical site which bases itself of the North Korean offic… https://t.co/ESEYoRbP1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[...d incesante muerte d nosotros mismos y d nuestros deseos egoístas,x q s solamente muriendo contigo q podremos contigo resucitar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more time I’m by myself in my room the more chaotic evil I’m becoming😥😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiranEC @vtimd @BobbyFantast1c It’s ok but I’m trying to understand the lyrics. Comb of various languages?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Large Kitchen Garbage Can. It was built from recycled Pine flooring. @ Pace, Florida https://t.co/LGeHLtbOCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody freaking out on #fakemelania but that not even my president 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ENRangerfootbal You got that right on time flying by, hard to believe I have one about to start college and the ot… https://t.co/bGhViBTAKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobNoriega7 @___rricco___ @_Marcoss3 @javiertoo_ Wonder why we still up 🤔 🦜 🦜🦜🦜🦜🦜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_petriello @SannyDamet I had no idea about this but I’m learning more about this techno everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP I’m pretty sure that comes after “preferred experience:” in Trump world job postings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seemyfriends last night performed by #davedavies of #thekinks on the #rocklegendscruise #ricklegendscruisevii 2019… https://t.co/XYTupdE5V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been blocked by some guy named Peter Kessler. He popped up on my feed when someone liked his tweet.   Who is t… https://t.co/FLcU996qP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We capped off our week of Building Construction with a friendly but competitive game of Jenga. Winner take all.… https://t.co/704aoRUSff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude, don't undersell yourself, they'll still want to interview you in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wZGskRptuh @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes FREE PRESS HAS BEEN REPLACED BY DEEPSTATE @cnni @cnnbrk… https://t.co/fZxWq6Em6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes it all work... #SASAudio #blinkinglights #iheartradioNYC @ 32 Avenue of the Americas https://t.co/6GHb3iXOji]]></document></documents></author>