<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Support womxn owned companies. #smokeladyjays #milkmakeup #pnw #oregonsmallbusiness @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/fz3C71GYiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night talks with your roomie are the best! Love you, @sarahmae1713 ❤️☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It must be nice to have somebody you can call on, without searching and scrolling all thru your call log 📲]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is is safe to say that Black History is in the making tonight? #redo #Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kletochkin was cited as saying by the RBC news website.  Human rights violations, activist says  Ivan Melnikov, a h… https://t.co/VNlDud3HHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying make me emotional! Should I have watched A Star is Born again on this flight? No, probably not! But here I a… https://t.co/z38fhc2HF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS I looked him up in the phone book, found his address and snuck in his (open) garage and left flowers and a thank… https://t.co/81dgsoWP2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Ms Warren. You have lied your entire career. You used the Indian tribe to become a millionaire, that money… https://t.co/jzTPyCwLZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Uuuhhh what about your taxes. You are such a moron(and that's being nice😳)only God will be your ju… https://t.co/7YEQUS0s4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I played volleyball tonight I can't feel my arms and I played awful. 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritza_darling @cinn_mendoza I already get horrible cramp pain idk if I’d be able to handle more 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResidentFOX Tell the writers, they are so Awesome..  and any season finales, I NEED 2 HOURS.... LOVED… https://t.co/ipSUh6aNcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The LPC using “her truths” acknowledges the differences, but that they have still limited her truth telling; they w… https://t.co/kTKQQiAI4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[They told me I’m fintastic but they don’t date tigers and are scared of intima-sea.🐠🌊 #fishkisses #suitors… https://t.co/lIP65w1B5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sé que estoy haciendo aquí 🤷🏻‍♀️👀 en La Horda Bar Arcade https://t.co/EaJM4XNSGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all alone, together. .  . . . . . . . . . . .SET TWO #music #pain #sunset #light #today _ #loss… https://t.co/fFOs69GKJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARCC @CCH_NU appreciates @DineeMD’s focus on community and looks forward to working with her on engagement in Chica… https://t.co/6H6twkt4R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black mold, rats and lead: Survey of military families paints slum-like picture of housing on U.S. bases https://t.co/4yRJlAzcli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sultan_of_stats @ByRobertMurray @AdamMcCalvy @Todd_Rosiak That’s EXACTLY what I was going to ask.  So...what kind… https://t.co/BeCmTUi4VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_J_N_G_ A very good episode but too emotional for me 💀  That’s the reason I started listening to the song again 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the drive in to work just now was any indication, the drive home should be an absolute treat. 😬🥶❄️ #kswx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megspptc @adamlambert @QueenWillRock Right??? I got goosebumps!!!!!!!! https://t.co/a0VAa9UDT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelAndJun They do it in Germany, too! I thought I was going to die my entire year there because they crank it s… https://t.co/igdmB2nCks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we ask and what is the meaning of this ?  . .  Well, Heal me in the verse means the following: Heal - and… https://t.co/0Xx16DH6GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKaminsky Can you please make @stephenasmith wallpapers? Please and thx.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any meal eaten 1 on 1 with a person under the age of 2 should be a write-off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teamechavarre Yup!! I’ll have normal hours and be back in Manhattan!! I left my current job fast! 😬 I feel bad abo… https://t.co/g9FwFDWqX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CECyTEC_SJS @franciscotobias @mrikelme @sary_tellez @matachine @Felix_Romo_sjs @CECyTECoahuila Saludos a sus estudiantes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever my coworkers leave I always seem to put on SiriusXM, and I just let my INDIE jump out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:50 in the morning and I'm browsing the internet for motivational and inspirational content to apply to my journey… https://t.co/3iXayO7aaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Because he started out lying for Donnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating a healthy society requires a strong culture and values. Look at #Pixar culture. Very few understand the… https://t.co/CRFdQyP4qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day seven of #marchmeetthemaker // the less glam side // here’s one not so shiny example of a hot mess. Some days y… https://t.co/nh928gkwIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a some kick ass wine and cheese for the first person to arrive at my door with some quality meats to round o… https://t.co/tMpigYP8Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @handsome_frank   Incredible animated Spike Lee portraits by our new signing @shyamagolden. How many of his… https://t.co/t70aGHReng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @JohnCornyn You should Ask Nancy, she has her wall around her house..she migjt know..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when someone made a poll asking if people would rather have a bunch of other superstar players like Gianni… https://t.co/ZnB7LtJEv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teenage Fanclub at The Fillmore!! ❤️ @TeenageFanclub @FillmoreSF #tfc #thefillmore #SanFrancisco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmpireShmempire @bourgeoisalien WOW!!! These all inclusive democrats sure know how to be inclusive alright. Funny… https://t.co/QCcR4pWWAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m going to have to talk to Spotify. I didn’t see you on their hottest singles list” is either the best or worst pickup line 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok i know it’s Sunday night and everything but like the fact that no one is awake rn is rlly rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bellas_Pets @NOWMG Can’t wait to have you back at #SMWL19 https://t.co/0XvcCJ46bF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Coup infers the overthrowing of a powerful entity. What this actually is, is referred to as a courtesy flush.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if classes are canceled tomorrow then it’s me, the couch, and New Girl alllll day and I can’t wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALarryRoss could never disown that little guy. He’s got the Ross genes. Hope he grows to be a great man like his G… https://t.co/gxqaYScMU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad Glenn Close didn’t win.  She’s an amazing actress, but “The Wife” was terrible.  I hope she gets honoured… https://t.co/xx1rchVWzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said, I'm pretty sure two other things that should be on that list are "play more" and "sleep more" both… https://t.co/8Hp4YXyFYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump allegedly sent ex-wife Ivana Trump to negotiate blackmail video with Russia https://t.co/DFkrVgIuxE via @PalmerReport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encouraging people to do more for there animal isnt elitist, its encouraging people to do more than the bare minimum for their pets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beezy_melt That’s the attitude! Thank you so much for bringing them, and I hope they thought it was at least a *little* fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonjaJorsen Hi! I'm a writer but want to engage more on Twitter...I find I struggle with how Twitter works some, but I'll get there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commuting on this Presidents Day? Most roads are snow covered and a bit sloppy. Leave with plenty of extra time, yo… https://t.co/Dfg7dq9Foc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to incline.  I meditate on Joseph  He was chosen.   God gave him a dream.  He talked about the dream. His… https://t.co/xvf7vasogb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This backstage look at @MyFairLadyBway by @petermarksdrama is filled with gorgeous detail and the excitement of mai… https://t.co/SCMq9x1NZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf has been gone since 6am for work and still not back I miss him thank god we live together miss him 😩♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irish Blessing Printables for St. Patrick's Day with https://t.co/7b4BEn1msA #funniness #laugh #smirk #merry https://t.co/4co0MysvO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaoooo never fuckin mind y’all tew much. Shout out to the 2 of y’all that pulled up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Flatbread. Goes great with some SAO Yellow Eyed Pea Hummus or that delicious Thai Lemongrass Coconut Cu… https://t.co/WJNsKObzQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t decide if I wanna go by the pool or sleep so I decided sleep by the pool 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarneyGellner you’re doing great. Ignore the negative comments. If you focus on the big picture so will listeners.… https://t.co/jBTqkk4GtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of birthdays to the craziest girl I know!! Love you @mckenzie_lempke  Don’t do anything I wouldn’t do toni… https://t.co/NqvwWjCEem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I don’t even think these Republicans would believe Jesus himself if he came to testify against President Tr… https://t.co/tjv3mTLMse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_iFrenchhInhale If they not gonna tax you all the way up it’s more or less 350 dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I have said before, as much as I hate how Michael is being disrespected, I'm glad he's in heaven, and doesn't kn… https://t.co/3MpPKFHWxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Suit And Jacket by @judahandthelion on @PandoraMusic   Ran into this on Pandora. You all are talented! 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandann_ Dude omg thank God you stopped!! Mine had me getting my period every other week!! 😒 and it made me bloa… https://t.co/T0kLM7r8px]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intactive @VioletVampire2 @CarterSteinhoff @zaaitir @eunice_pickett @Kommonsense7 As would less condescending dialogue. ✔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yipppeeeeee  A J White!!!!!! Score fast!!!!!!@Steelheads https://t.co/rJj6SmbKKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@algaulden Thank you, I love you and appreciate you more than you know! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookiee0758 @sianoresist beautiful! (I think we have very similar flooring)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy fuimos a revisar colchones Antonio y yo al Súper Colchones y la pregunta del señor que nos atendió fue: Como LE… https://t.co/dyYAp8uYdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not a schizophrenic.  I'm a female veteran a solid understanding of the human body and most of it's functions,… https://t.co/1NVfheImBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @GayleKing @rkelly It's called, Malignant Narcissistic Personality Disorder...and our douchebag @POTUS has it too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not heartless, all of the illegals with children knew what would happen when they reached the boarder. Preside… https://t.co/Eu9kUwtzsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to forecasted weather conditions, @MayorBowser has closed the DC Government for non-essential/non-emergency emp… https://t.co/Eiu7Cn71Zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetimtracker  and @TheJennTracker  I found your next puzzle.... https://t.co/LA5DCV5BwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton is such a pussy I can't believe this is the season that breaks my bachelor cherry I'm so annoyed https://t.co/LcUJbKs6RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It just hit me that I’m only 2 years away from being 10 YEARS in remission. God is good y’all ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/gR2Tv0HFcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorTwellman @OrlandoCitySC We seem to get a lot of the unlucky calls. 🤯🙄😔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instructions for building a LEGO tribute to Opportunity can be found here: https://t.co/IgS03LgCZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suck at twitter. The feeling I have when I see a dope poster and open up photoshop don't be the same as when I se… https://t.co/eci0fnAHfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FatNick I feel like telling ppl to stop drinking and doing drugs is just as obnoxious as bragging abt/glorifying… https://t.co/ejVlX6pcmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @ProfessorAMuse @realDonaldTrump @RepJerryNadler @SpeakerPelosi @HouseDemocrats I heard the Southern… https://t.co/nji9ftJLcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg When I was younger I got made fun of for being a fan. Today at 43, I still get made fun of for bein… https://t.co/P6KMr1kVTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unicorns and rainbows and mermaid sprinkles atop a chocolate ganache layer cake. All my favourite things for my own… https://t.co/ARLKy6yWff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyElves @DIXIEDOODLE12 Save the babies. We are created in the image of our creator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MedixKickOff @medixteam @camphometown so much love!!!! 💙💙💙💙 https://t.co/j42v7UIuTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @PeteButtigieg I do like what I have seen and heard as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6682family @JerradSymmes @shellytaylor442 @rockinrobinrock @SethPlumb @PerataKacie I am so proud of all of you. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest evolution for press advance: internet access b/c press need to send their work asap. Got to provide reliabl… https://t.co/dnmJRWAKfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi. We took in two new foster puppies today. I thought this was news you could use. https://t.co/gKMZa0UYmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandson Austin at 8 months. #Hearties  #smilingallthetime #ajaxontario https://t.co/G40EFmW0dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[GEORGE THOROGOOD "Bad To The Bone" https://t.co/zx00fOXdQ7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRehling @WhiteHouse Stop smoking the wacky tobacky!  There was very little racial problems until the Obamas got m… https://t.co/CbnPhJefTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading Choice Behavior!! Great things are happening at Bessie Coleman @NormanJonesCH  Kudos to instructors who ins… https://t.co/1ycodqyxlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[ooo I wanna do her some ponytails .. I be wanting to do some ponytails for the longest 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarris707 @SeptemberJulie @d_ast777 @Jj051301 @RosaDeliadelos1 @RosaryMysteries @ArleneKowalczyk… https://t.co/Ietc4ZBFU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad! 52 is way too young. Dylan was my favorite on “90210.” Prayers for his family and especially his kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roper364 But long enough to make them a wicked barrel horse seems unlikely. Cripple a mini real fast with a 150-275 lb rider]]></document></documents></author>