<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@chelsseasmiith @lys_jorgensenn This made my night so much better ❤️❤️😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oakland teachers strike continues after contract talks break down - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/cddQ903BUi 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 23rd St Metro Station - @metrolosangeles in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/SU6Iqw87gE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwest *Happy Tuesday* Hudson! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/J4U94RGWoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacJN22 @JudithDahmen @Hyper_RPG @joestarr187 @EmmaFyffe @Ninjanomics101 @zaceubank @kymcanon So glad you’re enjoy… https://t.co/EmAuF34UHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillySwanson you dont stand a chance gts wrestling is the better brand]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy had his first Junior Team Tennis match today. A mixed doubles victory!!!! So proud of his hard work!… https://t.co/NdgSoBtH3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[olivercpenn is serenading is for #unplugged at @discoverygreen @ Discovery Green https://t.co/aC6oDwbLfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtmoBlue @jeffborzello @MedcalfByESPN Have to remember we were a Mo Valley program a few years back. Look where th… https://t.co/t6WgeaHal1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another excuse to spend money, and add more waste to our already dirty ass world...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattyromero11 Últimamente los alcaldes y presidentes regionales, cuando terminan su período o se can presos o se fugan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should be able to celebrate that the person behind this crime has been caught. And should now be prosecute… https://t.co/IcRUfv9RQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Russian Imperial Stout by @TrinityBrew at @trinitybrew — https://t.co/aBnXONz0JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had farewell lunch w/Home Depot coworkers on my final day organizing shelves w/MET (Merchandise Execution Team), ba… https://t.co/00izyzKNfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkbro24 That https://t.co/6yKs5meSZe beautiful  , it drives me wild. https://t.co/sC2eXVXOWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannyman That was a phenomenal read. Thank you.  I couldn't put it down. Look at the time! I can now sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read about the new #GalaxysEdge info and opening dates, and it’s starting to look like for me that waiting a b… https://t.co/n9GcwigFPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROTEGIDO PELO SANGUE DE JESUS @FOL_ATLANTA hoje em Marietta e Dunwoody às 8pm!!! Teremos um momento especial orand… https://t.co/1KZSvTtyDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceLP4NV Because she has been accused. She runs the massage parlor where that millionaire baseball team owner wa… https://t.co/xTUfxXaEda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@max_holt14 @rn_kylo My focus wasn’t mainly because he was a 5th round pick as much as it was he didn’t even see a… https://t.co/WZsuggrTQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardOBryan I didn't see Christian. Are you Christian by the Grace of God]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfsparks @Bravewriting @eclecticbrotha Here is that poll! https://t.co/2VIjCWt2rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ear ye ..Ear ye.. we have an announcement to make. https://t.co/gzON3IrVRj https://t.co/MIwwKogziy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZekeDaHefe @alleyesnorth @NateFreemanNFL @PrimeCedi @BleacherReport He got an open look and a chance to get the ba… https://t.co/viLMxiM8Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NavygirlLaura Aleays nice to see a master chief chew someone else out  (wipes a tear) it’s beautiful...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to study the greats! Great job @TherealTaraji @willpackerprods iamjamesflopez  @willpowerpacker Where do I s… https://t.co/zbE9FRO98R]]></document><document><![CDATA[who wants to go watch a movie with me ? my boss gave me two free movie tickets 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeMoreForBmore What?? You mean they’re altering the comments from their community forums and incorporating the alt… https://t.co/qYrIwsLq8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherEric pretty fancy lines there..  is this the inversion? warmer at 4000' than 700' https://t.co/1gBnrIHPv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photobomb! Roserade still looks great!! Hi Smeargle! #pokemongo https://t.co/6rYm7RZhOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully in Christ they Will come to know Christi Persona perona(lly)🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that doesn’t make you proud to be a Hoosier then I don’t know what will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey Moron, I Can’t wait to see you eat your own words again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to @adasisraeldc's social action committee for prioritizing homelessness and inviting @streetsensedc ve… https://t.co/su7V2RwnF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherorourke7 Have a happy birthday Heather. I like your musicallys dress is like Ariana Grande has.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the first: North Tonawanda 14, @NWFalconsHoops 5.  Live look at the first quarter. @centercourt42… https://t.co/qlXmogBzId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nadine_Tweets @TheBandsVisit The Bands Visit is the best. I wonder if Katrina is going on tour?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azsweetheart013 @realDonaldTrump I’ll bet $5,000 he can’t tell which one is Silk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMBlackman Truman announced emergency seizure of steel mills April 8, 1952.  SCOTUS decided case June 2, 1952.… https://t.co/3oln3p8QlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help but feel #LaraLogan may have been inspired by #LauraLoomer @Lauren_Southern, @CassandraRules,… https://t.co/FGIJoPiMlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @MarthaRaddatz Senate finds no direct evidence of collusion between Trump campaign, Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskerWrestling @labriola138 Great  👍 job Mikey lets keep the train rolling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strom_annette @ChrisToTheW @ruthlesswench @esadah @CunningSq16 @MisleaderC @verocruz @Carlos_Can_Do @Barb81146… https://t.co/YkPMAant9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecoachvogt @slade248 @CoachShiffman @rdsmith86 @chowan6464 @dacoachmohuddle @bensonbuilt9 @CoachMckieJr… https://t.co/2qr6IkCchM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that you needed confirmation Tucker is a sleezeball. He confirmed it himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Peace I leave with you; my peace I give you. I do not give to you as the world gives. Do not let your hearts be tr… https://t.co/GWHqfTQzi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfrutando vacaciones... en Disney's Hollywood Studios https://t.co/DIVE8PeSrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Fun part about all this, @AOC ? Fellow that owns @amazon , also owns @TheDemocrats rag @washingtonpost .… https://t.co/yLF9oWf9U6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWVS #NEWYORK POSTED 📈 #X @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/lUifILgg8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#golf #golfinstructor #tompatri #tpgolf #tpgolftips #top25 #top100 #golfswing #golfing #balance #tempo #naples… https://t.co/gLNdNjrQTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Praying always with all prayer and supplication in the Spirit, and watching thereunto with all perseverance and su… https://t.co/6mPBhelQuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lumitrac @rockledgehiker @PamKeithFL I made the mistake of expecting a better debate from someone 1.5 times my age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magic &amp; Larry Fitzgerald are here, but so is former UK great &amp; Houston Rocket Chuck Hayes. https://t.co/R8luSlOXwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceBergenMP What the hell does that have to do with ANYTHING relevant here?? Personal attacks just aren't goin… https://t.co/vBS7wiWjwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atcleathalz24 White only Socialism worked here,it helped’m build wealth.The Head Right Program,Homestead Act,New D… https://t.co/xoKaJzZI44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely forgot tomorrow is Valentine’s Day until my kids asked me what kind of chocolate I liked 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[High rise and cloudy skies, don't let today's rain catch you by surprise.  Heavy rain will kick back into gear this… https://t.co/r83qiMlmJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vanilla, orange, mango.... Tasty stuff - Drinking a Johann Needs a Bigger Broat by @Aslin_BeerCo @ La La Land  — https://t.co/GFoPjANZyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Baby it's cold outside! But our workout of the week warmed our bones!  #legacybjj #legacylosangeles… https://t.co/WfziCESidl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think this news qualifies as breaking. I do like how they're attacking the cities first. Good strategy, tre… https://t.co/ao2ZEHOgKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four o'clock and all is well. #TheManWhoNeverSleepsInTheCityThatNeverSleeps #WaitThisAintNYC @ Bunker Hill, Los Ang… https://t.co/44tMJevsTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinhanson @tylercowen I suspect that relationship breaks down in places like San Francisco and New York City. Th… https://t.co/PbL83veMnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people:  "I wouldn't want to live in Buffalo either @AB84 "  Probably those same people: Answer the phone "WAZ… https://t.co/42YSEZIOTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s mf travis scott day (again) and i’m already concerned about my actions this evening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick of being forced to lower my thumbnail quality because YouTube won't update their 2007 platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revrrlewis @foxandfriends - the day will come when you all become wanna be has beens. There isn’t an iota of intel… https://t.co/onFFNGlj8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[They throwing dirt on my whole name only gets worse when she knows thangs she don’t see the perks of this whole thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celtwarrior715 @seantrcy @jri49msstate @vi99da @chimeracoder Because why would New York want more of a problem they already have?]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ybjLFN43LF How Verizon Customer service 1-855-431-6111 make sure that the Verizon wireless right for y… https://t.co/6u1T8TnDZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @SpaceX @ExploreSpaceKSC on the successful launch. Was a beautiful and excited moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APTNNews @BalochSami @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas Trudeau can not rule without trust. Trudeau can not buy trust. Trust… https://t.co/L258wo3BuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drakkordragon How round and lazy do you have to be to rely on self lacing shoes. now I want pants that pull thesel… https://t.co/FXVtr8uQtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cows 🐄 ☀️📷  #natchez #vidalia #cows #cowsofinstagram #mississippiriver #travelphotography #nikon #nikond7100… https://t.co/w6Qq9Ce90r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiff_Liao @tomi_adeyemi @MacKidsBooks @FierceReads And I hope you feel better soon. I assume you have tried chi en… https://t.co/VQoBR9MIK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to use night mode more but idk how y’all do this. My battery better appreciate my sacrifices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterGleick I think about this all the time. Our deltas need natural flow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers How does it help anything but your voter base? Just admit that is what you are after.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT to 1998, when both boys and girls programs won Region/Area Titles in the same season. Make sure to come suppor… https://t.co/wnUoSMBf5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreJBoulais @SourceCon @GoAppirio @Deandacosta @Fishdogs @ScottFadness @SourceConIndy @Jobvite @DisruptHRIndy… https://t.co/jpS5UyhlSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to testify at @toddkaminsky’s hearing on #ClimateChange today. New York State is showing true leadership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyhiser @newmusicbox @ashoncrawley @ShanaRedmond oops - theremin* lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawgNationDaily been waiting a week for u to get back on the air and all u can come up with is a gripe session? Co… https://t.co/MZl27LbwvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chad_Brewster @tallestCooper6 @Mathia26 @PFTCommenter Ouch. @OldTakesExposed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to rock at the Copper Rocket with some 80s themed Trivia! If you’re not here, GET HERE!  #SimonTimeTrivia… https://t.co/b2HlOHAzCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter The ONLY thing New is your Russia  narrative is dead (Mueller has Nada)! The new shtick? “Mounting  e… https://t.co/1AnXa83Grq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait... I’m sorry. But they said this man was walking outside his car, that was parked in the middle of the road, a… https://t.co/vvoRbdAJ5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day of hitting and resilient comeback in the 9th inning of game one. #Clawsup #Holysweat #Godsglory #GSAC… https://t.co/chnj2UNHWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my son @joshstowers7 , don’t be afraid to call home every once in a while https://t.co/SE9VSF7h3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruins made out really well in this. They solidified their third line center slot and Donato isn’t a huge loss with… https://t.co/10WSC5Lo4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSinger @NeerajKA @antoniogm @pt I love the PIVOT.  Maybe I'll use my remaining Crypto to hire @JimCameron to s… https://t.co/2MlQI0xR7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGParents Any leaders from PG County calling for her to resign.....nope😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karli_bonne @superyayadize Odd isn’t it how fast the sponsors of the anti Lynching bill supported the story!  Coincidence, really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend #VoiceBlinds she didn’t even hesitate! Great start tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read &amp; Study The Bible - Daily Verse, Scripture by Topic, Stories https://t.co/DExzt4A3Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think climate change is real, think about this... If the polar ice caps are really melting and the oceans ar… https://t.co/keHFnhnI0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a challenge understanding why my instincts and intuition demanded that I quit. Now I know why. It was a n… https://t.co/5t7aU1A7RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last sunset over the Pacific. @ Ocean Beach, San Diego https://t.co/2mh0mrHi8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Churby faces two batters and that’s it. Now in to pitch for Sac State is sophomore LHP Brady Rodriguez.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whstancil ...adding - the country has a LONG way to go before we get a balanced dialog on Israel.  https://t.co/tpTaXqrcon]]></document><document><![CDATA[To whom it may concern..... 😘✊🏿💪🏿👌🏿😁😀😂😂😂😂 #TearsFloweth #DailyLaugh #LMFAO #Funny #Comedy #Hilarious #Jokes… https://t.co/Y4EBzDM78x]]></document></documents></author>