<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Dyson product rant here. I live in a 1200 sq ft home, mostly wooden flrs. I have gone through 2 “stick” dysons in… https://t.co/8spBHgALCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be evil I'm still so obsessed with how wonderful @MichaelKeene made my catwoman look, and how perfect… https://t.co/4RKy30V3eU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLARIATO Spent all morning watching @ORIENTALWRESTL1 with @Linkhogthrob42. I get it now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika @JoeNBC I would have  loved to see @AOC have the opportunity to defend herself against all your critic… https://t.co/NzGZO4d5ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[“So when did you think it looked like Sir Kenneth Branagh?” 😩😩😩😂😂  @rickygervais  Jesus fucking Christ I’m dead #afterlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hhite62 @TCRWP @Lex1_Literacy @LiteracyJen @MrsBainsBrains We must have forgotten to snap that pic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ps: brownie points if you get the tacos from @torchystacos https://t.co/2z5e5piAtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to know why @AOC ??!! Because it was phony as hell! That’s why they didn’t vote for it- out of protest for… https://t.co/jq9fB3pAri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of our CA Cougars on getting the win tonight. Thank you to those who came out to cheer for this tremend… https://t.co/DUau2FRgzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinupchurch5 this looks like something in your class-♥️to hear if u try it!👍🏻@cloyacano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is giving &amp; receiving vaccinations #HappyValentinesDay #PublicHealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shakeshack - on 86th street, I just witnessed two employees go above and beyond to help out two women with babies.… https://t.co/Wub73uqqnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcsced #KarenCarpenter  #RichardCarpenter #Love  MISS THEM❣️ https://t.co/61eb1dl7ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no better feeling than waking up, pouring a cup of coffee, and then sitting down to enjoy it. Every other d… https://t.co/4YS0WaWVVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faeryxoxo @p3rseph0n3 @KevinLyman Ok that’s true tho, driving from Evansville was always at least 2-3 hours to get to Warped]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou My neighbor (a Trumper) told me yesterday that Democrats want to make it legal to kill a baby after it's… https://t.co/DoEweLfMZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s work together to help you achieve your real estate goals!  Owning a home is not out of reach...and I will hel… https://t.co/TSp0UwyNZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After some careful consideration, I’ve decided to clean up my feed with some respectable adult content!! Stay tuned… https://t.co/ftF1ggZAc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fangirlingjess wow blasphemy have you already forgotten kstew’s Totino’s commercial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro trump referred to NK dictator as his friend in his latest tweet!! can you imagine the freak out if obama had done this??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning fun hugo_official   #hugoboss #jeans #boss #mens #mensfashion #menstyle #menswear #chic #fashion… https://t.co/G4CNxQVL9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna put my phone on the charger during work tomorrow and just have #sucker playing on a continuous loop all day @jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running to win a cash prize of $100 from AT Player go for it😀 https://t.co/ZZ9lXX4eaC https://t.co/C0kbuQHHmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff If you endorse him then we know he's deep State and we standby the President and HIS decisions! We know what you are!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On international women’s day I’d like to give a huge thanks to @makersmark whisky for collaborating with us… https://t.co/DKqnXEEiJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashermaj @DonCheadle So, your saying that the once accurate acronym has now been transformed to a slur by more big… https://t.co/caHkwFn2eV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s Run Series❤️ Run like a butterfly🦋🦋🦋#run #cardio #race #halfmarathon #10k @ Steam Pump Ranch, 10901 N. Orac… https://t.co/LAwY7GKt73]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is ludicrous. Safety First Complilation | Click the link to view full image and description : ) #hilarity… https://t.co/apPSsoE0Bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder And it's just a coincidence that the man who got Epstein a slap on the wrist ended up in Trump's cabinet. H… https://t.co/f3kw0Pqw4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcruz2418 Still looking for this guy.  Everyone here is.  Everyone everywhere needs to be!  👮🏻‍♀️👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennberthume @thefloridakeys @PalmBeachesFL Great photo! #RoadTripChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[New ink 🐻🌲⛰💜* * * #inlove #tattoo #tattoosofinstagram neri_ramirez @AdornmentStudio @ Adornment Piercing and Privat… https://t.co/YPi0cXlksk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake @NicolleDWallace Where did she think she was going?  To the beach!!  She should have had this info with her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of the best food-themed love songs of our time tbh https://t.co/lmU21SaGg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How far you will make it depends on how bad you want it. I want it bad so I’m about to have to put in a lot of work… https://t.co/ney07yw4kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tug my heart along You know how to make me sing Got me wrapped around your finger Like a puppet on a string]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and Shine. It’s business Monday again and I’m ready for ☕️☕️. Have a wonderful day. #MondayVibes… https://t.co/dbuJDLcymq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t sleep and i have the disneyland “get your ears on” song stuck in my head ):]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onlyindreams730 Seriously. I gave up and we’re paying someone to do or taxes for the first time this year (well, m… https://t.co/9VG4uyyteO]]></document><document><![CDATA[HappyFriday! Elizabeth Taylor makes up her Eyes. https://t.co/gEnIpqxmLn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days all you want to wear are pearls... they make my heart, soul and skin glow... what do you love wearing tha… https://t.co/5YDILTznR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thank #God most of all. The black line is how large my wound used to be...18 weeks later,, #voila https://t.co/S0OaN14CJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Did anyo9ne even see her lips move when she said just fine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlgitw1 @PsychoResist @JeffJustice83 @EdKrassen @SpeakerPelosi Ah, and “Nobody is perfect.” 🇺🇸👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[// NEW BLOG POST //  ft. some #ValentinesDay outfit inspiration 😏  —— 💕 What are your plans tonight? 💋   . . .… https://t.co/kRlewqbkr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaRedCaracol no se puede recomendar a nadie porque el premio del Desafío termina,empieza el otro y aun no le pagan al ganador]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 10th birthday Bailey. You are still my baby even though you are double digits. #LivePDNaiton @PascoSheriff https://t.co/rvp2NOhB4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahVH Nope. I still have flashbacks to some roads similar to this in Ecuador.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 What are your goals this week? ✍️ Personal or business, doesn't matter - they're important! 🎯 Are you pushing thr… https://t.co/bvk7HQSrUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA['Absolutely' prepared to sue administration if #Mueller report not public: Top Dem - #ABC News https://t.co/A6A1LulHTK (via @ABC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so happy when I realized I got out of the shower before midnight because that meant I could still snack on so… https://t.co/7ndjeFo3Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mermaid... 22” life.. 😉🙌  Click my bio for appointment today ♥️  #khandtiedextensions @KimJette  . . .… https://t.co/vpYE8Mr3Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PubWest speaking as the short one on the panel, I really enjoyed the discussion about how publishers can better ed… https://t.co/so6UEqsBf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @IlhanMN The rest of congress should just admit if other lobby groups paid more they would have as m… https://t.co/9pbAldZVJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is merry. #hilarity #laugh #grin #absurd https://t.co/Oe44Zd9C9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@needaprez @revianzap @HillReporter @realDonaldTrump That’s because he gave up on Trump understanding what he said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those 6 strings are asking for new songs from me. https://t.co/JqTI7zxRVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be gassing my friends on IG like I ain’t see these same pics in the GM before they was posted 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sea_of_shoes Our malamute puppy literally steals from all our neighbors. She has a sorting pile and then a keep pi… https://t.co/2rqYErSWN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous about tomorrow 🙏🏽 this will be the longest plane ride I’ve ever been on 😩😩 I just hope I don’t get sick, if… https://t.co/F0HvxFcU3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate your job? It’s important to do something every day to relieve the feeling that you’re stuck in a never-ending… https://t.co/10oWqF7TWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, the push against terrorist CAIR begins what about @Cubs @Arkansasgov @ArkansasEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSBRVOTES @ShellyS63206798 @Harry_Styles #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hello_darling13 Me and @LaurenDanaeMc tonight when we went to Homegoods 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting 🤓 #DaylightSavingTime #espresso needed today! @Dictionarycom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jellis942 @LunaLuvgood2020 @Rey_Sistance @lfkraus @TrinityResists @B52Malmet @TrisResists @DebbieDoesTwitt… https://t.co/UXuZB7MGx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now in LJs! Arson speakers hosted by @MaryvilleForen1 @MaryvilleU #CareerTalks https://t.co/5yZYlp2cEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will this period be the one that takes me out and makes me bleed to death? Find out on this week’s episode of “I’m… https://t.co/X4aMNUXiS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ew literally wants me to work for the dick?!??)! Are u fucking kidding me right now?!??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more gorgeous #superbloom pic before I continue home. @ Borrego Springs, California https://t.co/EVpnMBRNxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Patchogue.  Two women dead, in house fire.  Suffolk officer injured rescuing resident.  Cause unknown.  Not c… https://t.co/V8hPoSVZhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[currently thanking myself for choosing not to compete next weekend cause I really enjoy this QT in my bed with no c… https://t.co/IsqW0oK9WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been a few days; life and weather has gotten in the way but I am back! I'm not stopping yet! #nicolesandra… https://t.co/p6cj9ecYHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarMachine2013 Wonder if we could do espnwatch. Not seeing there either?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tutty352 @laxidaisy @LakesStiles @teresa_knox @thisismenic70 @theirishego @LansdellMum @AshtonBadLad @Lals1002… https://t.co/tvvJfvBw45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bert_gilfoyle @SpicyFiles @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump These are the games I am so tired of. Why is that toddler wasting our time?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outerbanker1 @BlaineStewart @JessicaNLarche @ericagreenway @MHendersonWTKR @samantha_german @AnthonyWTKR @WTKR3 We… https://t.co/Iv412NFagM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twin_blue_eyes @SarahPalinUSA @NaturegirlRaine Never had them when I was in school.  That's why American's are spo… https://t.co/418FSeTKxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withamorxfaith roll your eyes constantly and then leave, also, visit Denton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Britain's Tudor Treasure: A Night At Hampton Court (Full Documentary) https://t.co/nDC1X4HhcW on YouTube. I f… https://t.co/gZTXIOZK1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women's History Month! Something not to celebrate: Women's rights are walking backward, say @HelenClarkNZ… https://t.co/E0P5HsEk9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Christian women she is, Christ wouldn’t like her believe as of Democrats and i guess she believes in abortio… https://t.co/4hDImGmbNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allybauerr happy birthday beautiful! I miss you sm and hope we can play some vball soon 😉 https://t.co/N1VPjFaKF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler How about the facts you are facing in court regarding your complicity @OSU . Facts are… https://t.co/QQjTmZLFWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrisco @lopezobrador_ Aquí voy, seré breve: *prejuiciosa *ultra-conservadora *homofóbica *hazmereír de expresión o… https://t.co/qqKIiHAMOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my cats don’t get me wrong, they kept me sain in Alabama while @riahhhhhhhhhh was at work. BUT I can’t wait… https://t.co/aDHrBUzgWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg...people that put read receipts on every email. https://t.co/uWHgAC0C7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to have my son home from Baker Lake, Nunavut where he was working as a heavy equipment apprentice for his c… https://t.co/LjrxMqsTPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a protest sign that should go viral. @bunkybun @KittyBhagat @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @lilith2u… https://t.co/5cZRnwbrjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music is my life. Takes the bad days away and I've been singing since I could talk. I was in both jazz choir and co… https://t.co/PWbR3IugCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters fox gets its news from CNN.. then lies a nd distorts it to meet their agenda to make trump look good.  NEV… https://t.co/B7OEQaFyM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever thought somebody was fine asf but they see you as one of the “bros” MAN FUCK YOU 😭😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to the Durango Film Festival! Snow, Ski, Film and Friends ❤️❤️❤️ #Durango #Colorado]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think spring!  Time to find your blooms! @ South Carolina https://t.co/CAvySqiB6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I caught a performance at the Melody Inn in Indy by fellow Harmony alum Austin Lucas, who is promoting his FANTASTI… https://t.co/YrNlwkSCWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissajean07 💁🏼‍♀️thanks girl! My life goal is to up the sass to be more like @GillianWithaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cathy47204163 It was wonderful to hear you on this week's @timcorrimal show. You did a fabulous job.  😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finished the Beauty Marks Bible reading plan from @YouVersion! Check it out here: https://t.co/RUyOBUozqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the longest time I had no idea there was a season 6 of KND. I thought it ended after Operation ZERO, and I didn… https://t.co/3H8TvhJKRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potus has chance to prove Hire AMERICA, #AmericaFirst is real. IF signs Congress #INDIA giveaway program it's over.]]></document></documents></author>