<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥Great tip !! #gyms #germs 7 Places Germs Hide at Your Gym @SparkPeople https://t.co/j832D1PzCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pajama Day 🙄👎 She could've picked some REAL pajamas tho. Ugh ❤️ #Alicia #DieHardFan @ Park ViewElementary https://t.co/cYzVqcN01u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was amazing you guys!! I had such a great time connecting with doTERRA leaders and teaching about using your… https://t.co/YHMBdEInK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coyotesarchive What part of "cast out" his seventh daughter sounds warm and fuzzy to you? Not one bit of it. Pssst… https://t.co/qGPpDXlzF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls has a lot of damn nerve! @DonaldTrump being lyin since day1 now all of a sudden her Pelican lookin… https://t.co/9hilsQNuMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t there something anti-Christian about worshipping Donald Trump?  #MorningJoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life hack: less friends means less funerals when your older. Plan ahead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol @The_Fool_Monty @Shawn172510 @GTA_Redhead @DollyVol @madsatan6969 @beers300 @Bubba_Henson @HippieVol… https://t.co/V3QEwE7pc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re getting hype for March Madness: Poetry edition here in our LA department! 🎤📚 Thanks to @KellyGToGo for the id… https://t.co/1j6FDiw4Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGDAverk @mostcurious2 @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @darker_dearie @AlliCamAllison @tweetNorvena @VillainPeterPan… https://t.co/wWWbh0dPYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatLos 😉😉💗💗 it’s the 8 years of spanish class in catholic school hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ex would fuck anyone in a doc marten... prob even a doc marten itself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielleradford @JimmyNewstetter And periscoping everything! And taking hilarious shame shots of shoeless people at Starbucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand How dare you tell anyone what they can charge for a service! Anyone that is ok with this should have… https://t.co/I9HfQN8OJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then you would get back from Summer Break and people would ask what you did and how it was and you’d be required to… https://t.co/X2MYls3Z8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCrean @UGABasketball @GatorsMBK #GoDawgs Always great to beat the Gators!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This house is so cute, but as much as I love pink, I’d go insane having to see this everyday lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The destroyer of Moab and his cities has come up, and the choicest of his young men have gone down to slaughter, de… https://t.co/xjcg9Fd7U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Boston City Council should remain a seat for two years. Let’s just take the BS out of this and not make this a seat for life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet my brother 5 bucks if he made the plastic ball in the indoor hoop we have ide pay him 5 but he didn’t have to… https://t.co/4M1Nk8MSVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Diva's Headquarters in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/yFfvWYf6Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby shower is tomorrow 😁😁😁😁😁😁😁 I'm so excited 💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃 #TwinsOnTheWay #BoyAndGirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, uh, turns out I like to travel a lot more than my bank account likes me to travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my dumbass gets off work at 4:30pm and I literally clocked out at 4:00pm thinking It was already 4:30, nope I di… https://t.co/uAw1q4hi3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS My mom always told me to be careful who I called my Friends and that who I hung out with was who I was.  So.… https://t.co/Ev8n3KByGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[nbd but i get to meet one of my favorite people from my childhood today]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Who Writing The proposal we gotta Do it now cuz we. Kno our HBCU can run On CP time @TXSUSGA1 @AfricanMalcolm  👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobconrad4 @nytimes Prove it I bet my dog can catch 6 tennis balls in a row before you can prove just one of the 8… https://t.co/fUx1JK8bSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new butterfinger is gross🤢 @Butterfinger poor move no longer my fav candy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @RebeccaLHerbst The best wedding on day time!!!! Awesome couple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had the time and the money, I would go on a vacation all by myself. It sounds so lovely right now 🌴🌼☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing like waking up to the smell of roses... at 2 am when your fiancé gets home from work and you’re sle… https://t.co/aru3hRl7dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get ready for all that spring cleaning!  #Thieves #ThievesEverywhere #sofresh #soclean @ Plano, Texas https://t.co/3NJ7GVm3L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sweet young boy was our PAWFECT student yesterday!  He’s sweet, kind, hardworking, and a whole lotta silly!  ❤️❤️❤️ #rhes19]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite spots; love twodudesseafood and Ferrari Carano by the glass doesn’t suck either! #beachtown… https://t.co/RTVHCQjwEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NWO Orthopedics &amp; Sports Medicine in Findlay, OH https://t.co/OgysWYQGZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Activewear Lavendar Tutu Dress supplier Manufacturers In USA, Canada and Australia https://t.co/5CyuXOYP8k… https://t.co/oXYwJAzCjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc7marc I want to make you some chicken soup, bring you some slippers and a comforter to help you feel better. Yo… https://t.co/WguRyZBT2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC your in a pipe dream... we are your bosses and tour the damn employee]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW NAME CHANGE... #ClubUnforbiddenFruits 🍎💋 #BusinessOwner #Catering #EventPlanning #MobileBartending #Bartender… https://t.co/LFLvURDKBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my!!!! Kinda looks familiar- ya think??? #CheapShot... #ThisIsSportsCenter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise from @radiojoecicero in Florida! He is back tomorrow! Just a little Monday gift for you 🌄 #sunrise #florida… https://t.co/e5HmzYek9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this so hard?  Turn to teachers and treat is like professionals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emma and all the survivors we have you in our prayers, especially today. Fight on. You are our future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_m_munoz @LasPalmasStaff @LasPalmasElem I took a middle school group a few years ago and it was so much fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to make some compromises, but progress is slow and ongoing. The men that are involved in the project have all… https://t.co/SdUcZU2ilT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dloscarawards I only watch the red carpet. Or if Jimmy Kimmel is hosting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iSavage_PI @GibbonsOnRye @GrampaMorris1 @RepPressley Come on now. So don’t 7 year olds when they take their fairy… https://t.co/DdidwPeqob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I thought they took an oath to protect Americans not illegals?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a reason why I always gravitate back to @contranyc. The food is simply amazing. What is also equally as am… https://t.co/rjb0oiuL0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I should’ve stuck thru it and taken up the space at the bash that I am allowed. But also: No. I don’t w… https://t.co/QVJyVB4SZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at N. 163rd Ave. and W. Jomax Rd. in Surprise, AZ https://t.co/B2Ef2hAqPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chidinma_xo @sonnislove I’m more concerned that a guy asked other random dudes to drop dick print pick in his thread 🧵]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope all our friends in education will help us out! I work very hard @MadingES to ensure our learners have all th… https://t.co/okLKaLFrVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland “People say they’ve been together years but really they have maybe an hour before work and then they s… https://t.co/KCu9uV2v9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainBadger79 Good morning! Have an awesome day! #SaveScorpion 💜 https://t.co/vBoff3QWp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Valentine’s Day, here are my favorite romance novels I’ve read this past year: One Day in December, The… https://t.co/MgS043YC5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgfair Yes good question!  I know she’s run sweat shops overseas and that doesn’t seem anything to brag about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of March. Year is flying by. Make it an awesome month. Primer día de marzo. Que sea un mes buenísimo. El… https://t.co/UK7yvSxt4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are struggling with depression or know someone who is, this episode of the 4:13 Podcast is for you.… https://t.co/AiKc0pOjKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theJagmeetSingh Her being a woman or indigenous has nothing to do with being the AG. It was her qualifications for… https://t.co/snIp5DyMkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tis the season.  Here we go with regionals.  Spending our day in Bellevue playing basketball. @ Ensworth School https://t.co/yqoJhC6Yre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukebasketball @espn @Nike @ZionW32 This shoe quality blows my mind. I thought these guys would get "the top of th… https://t.co/7Bx1SIHXmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a fucking FIELD DAY with these past exams. *rubs hands together evilly*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines! Swing by and treat your sweetheart to a Chocolate Covered Strawberry Mocha, some yummy food, Amy’… https://t.co/8ogPVYkZhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never have been a Harvick fan but I have a little more respect for him after his comments on Jimmie. Jimmie has b… https://t.co/gAlVXdgAYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most annoying thing about how bad my vision is, is the fact that I ah e to wear contacts to TAKE A SHOWER becau… https://t.co/HfHYNC44dB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m interviewing @PaulDBoyer on a new bill he introduced.   He says parents should know #vaccine ingredients before… https://t.co/mIBtqieyoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @Charvettebey Liars of the Trump family and entourage will be wondering from now on about the possibility o… https://t.co/YuETOB23aG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsearian @emilyjorgs u need some with ur 5am Snapchats, @MahaParacha needs them with a selfie of her and Amit an… https://t.co/y91Z1uyd7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perks of the job getting to go to warm places...loved hanging out with our FCA staff Steve Young from Tampa… https://t.co/J4CgQy4mmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey beautiful souls, you feel like forever! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/MyEDI4O0ap]]></document><document><![CDATA[He sided with The Saudi prince over the killing of a journalist.  He also said he believed Kim Jung Un when he said… https://t.co/kLcX3kPXNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[today....and the only FACT IS MBAPPE PERFORMANCE TODAY...nobody cares about 5 or 10 years from now...Mbappe today a… https://t.co/GL6AfYnUZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RVvJEip1NA use promo code NOVA10 for a 10% discount on your purchases! 🔥🔥🔥 #fitness gear online!… https://t.co/RccJRAmnI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSteynOnline @DennisDMZ Love listening to you on Tucker’s show. You are the highlight of the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anxiously waiting for Georgia All State Chorus performance to begin! Can't wait to hear our 4 #rtmswolves in the Mi… https://t.co/GgfNzLe5Zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This months newsletter includes feeding tips/resources and some ways to connect w/your kids😍 Plus, join us on 3/5 f… https://t.co/NnZX3ywR4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyPolcha Ha I'm not one of em. Doing well. Been going back between the 1/2 2/3 and 2/5 just trying to find the… https://t.co/JojV5uYKRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀 gpsgreekkitchen  #gpsgreekkitchen #pork #zucchini #redpotatoes #lemon  #porkskewers #greekfood #eat_authentic… https://t.co/ubVVn429YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spy some of my coworkers on site at today’s #PoweredByBreakfast event, raising awareness for the mission of… https://t.co/VE0RaslOoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 4 spots left for my fun event! Email me marcy@stampinwithmarcy.com  to find out more and reserve your spot!… https://t.co/onj4vcrl3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well my Dad bailed on me and my sister didn’t answer me so @OG_Rojo for the sub . @Lakers game here we come .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber @TheBeatWithAri It seems like forever. We will be lucky to get this country back to normal I fear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YPqXqkr2o6 Learning2lean on Jesus...having more power than we've ever dreamed...He holds the future an… https://t.co/YGCarvJGiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hennaJo Monsieur dort sur le dos....ça fait pas très chic dans mon lit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little bags of gratitude. @ South Charleston, West Virginia https://t.co/P0QVsoQcMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelenMcCready Alright let’s do this   I even have my TSA PreCheck ready!!!! https://t.co/5is33Zy7st]]></document><document><![CDATA[Touchdown @mandarinflag and the W in the @Jaguars  #PreSeason Girls Flag Football 🏈 @DuvalSchools https://t.co/XplO8tFp1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[We partied all day and rock and rolled all night. Or vice versa 🤷🏼‍♀️ @ Van Andel Arena https://t.co/qbuQ0WXtIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResurrectedPan Yeah or Bingo if that O was getting a little boring. 🙄😉🙃💚 #LeviathanAnn https://t.co/qhjtx9T011]]></document><document><![CDATA[purdue ppl: selling a young the giant ticket (floor seats) for $10. hmu 🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be @WilkowMajority for a day. I already have several camo hats to choose from!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlrs___ that is the CUTEST sh!t when will she be signing pawtographs???]]></document><document><![CDATA[It'll be cool if I can get to the point in my career where I don't have to work every Saturday. I'd be down for lik… https://t.co/ZbWSvNuaFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra You have got to be kidding me @LeaderHoyer @SpeakerPelosi @HouseDemocrats WTF are you running????… https://t.co/U6fAx556sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO here is more of my story. I have a horrible sugar addiction and I alwaysfail by taking that 1 deadly bite. Keto… https://t.co/eioH02l9Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @SUPERGOCHOo @VictoriaD6363 @malekalby @marinavibu609g @PatGrant7777 @AAvallones @EliLeonarda… https://t.co/naVJjpFl7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BongioviBrand Omg 😂 I was hysterical It's my Show ... She's to much lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onetwogee @verizonfios We left Verizon and went with @optimum our WiFi speed has been really good! Compared to Ver… https://t.co/sCAaDotQnr]]></document></documents></author>