<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks Arkells for a great chat about songwriting and letting us stick around for soundcheck! #arkells… https://t.co/jIcGzL3OHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flights resume after a disabled aircraft halted traffic at Newark airport  https://t.co/C37zKuJjBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came home last night to this....must be a sign Pheasant Fest is only a few days away!!! @pheasants4ever @quail4ever… https://t.co/nPcNzyxWsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders History will remember you as a huge failure. Stop spreading absurd failed ideas to Americans. Thus land is for the brave work]]></document><document><![CDATA[so grateful to umbrella academy for proving to me once and for all that istanbul (not constantinople) was not just… https://t.co/uUw9h5LK6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiComo Jed lowrie, ninnies, next! It’s already starting less than a week into camp! Nothing serious they sa… https://t.co/JH560gg2xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but why is my ex requesting me on all of my social media’s again lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salen once, entran once de Timbers. #SEAvPOR el empate a uno continúa al minuto 61.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember all those dumb deals we just for out of 100 million for Marcel, stupid money for Charles Clay]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruh. this is fuckin insane, so if i dont ascribe to this definition of "biologically" am i suddenly transphobic? i… https://t.co/4bq7YcTm5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_fan9 @AnezSez @ESPN580Nick That dude ain't playing anytime soon! Just hope he gets on the court next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxkonnorxxx @livingout02 Now it time to wake up..lol..look down in tell him to get the fuck up..it play time again..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay @ChrisCashman @AngelaRussellTV @TVsJordanSteele @KaciAitchison @MichelleLiTV happy… https://t.co/XSCdY930oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreasuryMog @WashoeLibrary @GovSisolak After all , @TreasuryMog , Gladstone,  that's how Boogie won the election l… https://t.co/QXNn0Y3R1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean the walls aren't padded now? This would explain quite a bit. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benwritesthings Not to give him all the credit, but this seems to be a happy hallmark of Yuval Sharon productions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing back another one! 🏇 @ Chester Springs, Pennsylvania https://t.co/c70QiJeAaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyFairfax @zoe_samuel So, did the beaver cause his half to be spared from the fire, or did he cause the other h… https://t.co/gGw3zCzjUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @susygofficial @_MichelleThorne @Abella_Danger @MandyMuse69 @Misty_Lovelace @charitycrawxxx… https://t.co/QKNolUiAbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gentleman from Starbucks never answere , did they pay the rent on that store ? President Trump was asking the o… https://t.co/2Xkmla7VuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are less then a month away from @peronicus sharing the stage with @DangordonraeRae, @DomInationCDN and… https://t.co/pgySqaDgVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jerome Iginla was a hell of a hockey player. Fighter, goal scorer, leader. One of my all time favourites #12legend https://t.co/bmGdQFIHT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShoffnerMedia I agree 100. If your coach gonna risk it all to defend the squad then that better light a fire under… https://t.co/pbm1TpAtot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cadet Bone Spurs has some nerve talking about ANYONE who has served in the Armed Forces, let alone someone who serv… https://t.co/YlUe775ayo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cashier at the mercado in gview was cute... https://t.co/WByaZw9eVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: How I Met Your Mother is better than Friends  fight me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calendar is here! #utah #beutahful #wasatch #Sundial #Wilderness @ Sundial Peak https://t.co/IXWpnvFWB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyMeierFox9 May not have a choice. You are in charge if I don't make it back by tomorrow. Remember to keep… https://t.co/IiOCQfxiuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #dad don’t spend too much time working your way up the corporate ladder. You may miss the moments that matter t… https://t.co/AcRt7aH59K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachHinesCHS Servant Leadership in its truest form.  Great message coach!  @careacter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currency social media price sentiment = bullish, without extreme much hypium yet, which looks hopefuly to me. Do with that what you will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyEmber I wonder if people purposely lock them for any reason?  They’re such a nuisance, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJTimes13 @TheMikeSnyder @Hermann22 Have you watched it all? That’s addressed. And let’s face it, he slept w child… https://t.co/v692x7zImz]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Demon's wanting children to de killed even up to birth is a pure evil way to make money by selling body parts… https://t.co/rf1bGT26Ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the definition of sleep.. tell me because I don’t know what sleep is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor coming onto tumblr tonight to say hi knowing she didn’t post anything  https://t.co/7heAc3ouH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shouldn’t have to use a plugin to have a user-friendly experience! There should be a toggle for classic mode buil… https://t.co/b0AQaZKzFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally, there’s no socialism happening here 🤦🏼‍♂️   Cillizza’s headlines drive me nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnthisDate in 2006, I lost my father to #PancreaticCancer, Mom is still with us but has also missed him dearly eve… https://t.co/GYmluUQqH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global Vibes Saturday's @bigcitytap Music by resident DJs mwelwamusambacine &amp; #djcoreybless #reggae #dancehall… https://t.co/X7Gts9jDxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The responses to the Panthers tweet? Roughly 40% of dudes asking if she’s single, and this knuckle dragger saying i… https://t.co/uWut5vo1IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nach meinem gestrigen Besuch im botanischen Garten die Kakteennadeln sogar noch in den Socken gefunden 😮 https://t.co/jGS8pcfg4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morocha44 @CwMcculloughjr @DeanObeidallah @HuffPostPol What do the Jewish people do thats horrible?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoardingArea @OneMileataTime I wonder if the old SPG Amex card will switch over automatically?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avery Liliko'i Kepolo cans now available. https://t.co/uWyb7MOTAI @AveryBrewingCo #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 15 Minutes the show will start https://t.co/pCZXb9ryoz 2019 @USLChampionship Preview Show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisjjlane @thefull40 @ReferSadness Man...I really really need JQ to step up and beat out Collin for that job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odhetx3 Damn that sucks lol I actually might make a trip to Vegas for the night Bc my boy is there on the 16h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made the terrible decision of watching Blue Mountain State for the first time this semester. Not only do I have s… https://t.co/dpP368BOQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot when I took this but....A wet day in #Chelsea, not too long ago. #nyc #manhattan @ Chelsea, Manhattan https://t.co/t4tY22p6V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgenJulie @MTaylorNDP I’m with you Julie, but she is on the right side of THIS issue, and I remain grateful to have her in our corner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously folks, you have to read Section 600.9. William BaRr ONLY HAS TO NOTIFY CONGRESS THAT HE RECEIVED A REPORT… https://t.co/s71lA0cclB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how bad this tweet makes Laker brass on all levels look???  "After hours of dedicated study we decided a b… https://t.co/pGMIjnHl2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeoliberalFed In any case, young folks are always super smart (think infant language acquisition). I've looked int… https://t.co/w4dcXsvZmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slotkinletter @glennsumi Fantastic! They are a superb company and it’s lots of fun to see the differences in the a… https://t.co/hkmvEMXhNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGiardi @JimBowdenGM Was my first thought too. And, what that means?🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @agbm96 &amp; @rsig_ Happy to see new and important work for #LGBT health in #PuertoRico. 🏳️‍🌈🇵🇷 #UPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO HAD THIS? Well my ENTIRE Middle School L’Anse Creuse South sure did. 😉— 6th Grade year 1986-1987. Released Nove… https://t.co/9ELjnlipbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiggiNiad @ewarren not that i need to explain to You but i am a thoughtful #american #citizen .. seek asylum… https://t.co/uYOTQ61202]]></document><document><![CDATA[For You (Beat By #AnnoDomination) by PhillyBlunt2000 https://t.co/2nMKOWeHfM @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Belie… https://t.co/qhO1N0o9ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@literallyhank @HotlineLing_ Okay so we add shot attempts fg% and shot attempts into the conversation. He’s a stat… https://t.co/Rt9TXCBCbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vulfyuta in Grands for Doubles at Munkaid, Wish us luck in grands! Im happy that ive shown my sheik is good (Atleast in Teams lol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year is going by slow, God wants me to accomplish all of my goals 🤘🏾❤️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a nine-point game. #LadyVols cut South Carolina’s lead to 60-51 entering the fourth quarter. Tennessee has onl… https://t.co/CiibHRzhO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaParesky @AlisonGopnik What a great story!  Thanks for putting this out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakesTakes @captainmarvel And again, aren't SHAZAM and Captain Marvel the same character?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfGodAndMan @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Jesus your word is Gospel!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love all of Illinois. The work ethic in this state is like something I’ve never seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really proud of my girls this morning. Played awesome on Saturday despite extenuating circumstances. We are startin… https://t.co/uz6E8IeaYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResearchSoft The quote by @ctitusbrown completely legitimizes this endeavor: https://t.co/vYWRbPy5Bk @_inundata ar… https://t.co/nEmRdo0Hw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allison + Ian's Georgia Wedding  https://t.co/OLAZZE9gNq  #roostmke #roostweddings #holymatrimaney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfectly executed surprise weekend amandamozier @ High Point, North Carolina https://t.co/EZDKnwVH7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13swift1989 Virginia’s a very cool state, I should know, I’m a virgin. (but seriously I live here and I love it lol) 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fc_adventures Hahaha I'm good with either service! Thanks! (Low priority since I still have 2h15m left on this movie lolol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers coming back together is great and all,  but if their shit don’t slap like this did, I don’t want… https://t.co/CzMwoigcmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeylogano Hey, just wanted to say it was nice meeting you and your adorable son this morning at the Dunkin in Cor… https://t.co/VlgaeOfXR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got this rather large (4ft. x 3ft.) original print on brushed metal panel mounted. We get to enjoy it for a few wee… https://t.co/JZshFbIq4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just discovered @Bishop_RuPaul, and until today was certainly living less than my best life! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LmlLmt @JuliaMorales @MattClark60 @HOUPetsAlive I was making a joke as she is about to go to spring training with… https://t.co/X8XWUoIA9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltmjason @AtTheBarr Thank you dude! Just made it to Lawrence. Roads were awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello, @PGATOUR @PGATOURRules I would like to lodge a conplaint. It has to do with dropping your ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Let’s get the second half underway.’ ——————— I bet day three with be incREDible. #SETC #setc2019 @ Candlewood Suit… https://t.co/2o2CONdVlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[We added 2 more guys who can generate their own buckets and Brett still sends Ben out there with no plan to get the… https://t.co/38EI2HQHbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoadrieneyo @morningmika Agreed on both counts.    Sending thoughts to Mrs. Scarborough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly unbelievable how many people are stagnant or complacent with power moves that are right in front of them.. #MakeEachSecondCount]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did your mom live when she was pregnant with you? Did doctors feel they need to give you heart surgery? Famil… https://t.co/C9N8LAxmXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCYB_Heather @WCYB_Ricky @WCYB_Quon @AllisonBrooke21 Everyone loves a chocolate cookie, but the best part of an Or… https://t.co/ily0qedK12]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a new fan @GNote_Official ! You killed it opening for @umphreysmcgee. Thank you for Five Funky Nights on t… https://t.co/TzBB8x81q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @getinwego for the tickets to the @atlhawks play the @spurs. It was a good game but poor execution in t… https://t.co/VZpzHidZlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #IWD2019 where we celebrate the accomplishments, successes, struggles and challenges of the women in our live… https://t.co/mRn2PolpKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise is coming! 🌇🌞🌅 Also I froze my butt of for this photo, so there better be likes. @ Iwo Jima Monument https://t.co/zXNpk6Kn9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it wrong to buy Easter candy right now, even if you have no intention on keeping until then? Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clay says he is waking up at 6 and wants to be in the cafe by 7. He still isn’t awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson @benshapiro Thank God she’s not just like crooked Hillary isn’t the president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanWade24 @Tomahawknation Ha ha ha, insurance, he is a good dude, had some big wins for W, but had a lot of help… https://t.co/aNoGNB911d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are few #action #pictures of Nikkolette from this weekend’s #softball #tournament at #NISD #EastCentral… https://t.co/ZKKkUUX7zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSpecktator @BillySpeckman @moonpie69 @tinaborcher Have you ever fell asleep on the toilet? *raises hand sheepishly *]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beverly Hills BMW 5070 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036 (877) 794-4678 https://t.co/bP3aRGQh45]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all on this journey through space and time @ The Mann Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/0WVWqfxCrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods An arrogant idiot that is a Communist and a member of Congress.]]></document></documents></author>