<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mtravis63 @EvilTwinBrewing @ManvsAle @ephoustonbill @RodJBeerVenture @jwags48_jack @CATbrew13 @wrayzors… https://t.co/FIFhszEzcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stats from yesterday's @DDPYoga workout. OH FUCK YEAH!!!   #Unstoppable #PositivelyUnstoppable… https://t.co/kWKRGZYZCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup 100% !!! Then the industry participants would have to work toward keeping everyone HEALTHY! Clean food, air,  a… https://t.co/5KjaqsV9eO]]></document><document><![CDATA[College Game Day!! #BBN #GoCats @ Memorial Coliseum https://t.co/WDJAHNBY2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[This must give you pause. This guy is guilty as hell. #McStay put Merritt on the stand 😂😂😂😂. Won’t happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKBlakely @teerhardy @itsmejjwarren @gracelavinia_ I agree. Most youth workers I know are also young and ofte… https://t.co/WgLAHmLO1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateLevenson of @DMG presents on ways to save $ with rightsizing. @JFrancis5 co-presents at #NCE19 https://t.co/MFMam1irtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Holy Scan Remains on My Head/Mind. You can Hear U.S. Govs Speak on Satellite as That Unique. P… https://t.co/Ib5WtQZpkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, that was such a wonderful dream. I don’t think I’ve ever had a actual good dream until now. Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broke tired and can’t find a f***ng #dietdrpepper and we have to fly with 60mph winds!! #stilllivingourbestlives @… https://t.co/Z4y7bxQzLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break out the beads and indulge in some fresh tracks. It’s #fattuesday in #aspen! @ Aspen/Snowmass Ski Resort https://t.co/KgjbQOSxAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to bash my idol @taylorswift13 please unfollow me I will defend her no matter what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlamLifeGuru If someone left a trail of glitter, you would follow it, like The Yellow Brick Road!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been doing so good and now it feels like someone came and pushed me right back down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MopedTN @Shawn172510 @Legallaw1 Every woman’s problem too but most wont admit it 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iPhone X 📱is on sale for a limited time at @tmobile stop by your local store and get yours TODAY!! #NERules… https://t.co/s1oEbdPsWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind a day...I've accepted the challenge to post posters of seven movies I enjoy, one per day. No explanations, n… https://t.co/irbI1RB8Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mean to get all political, but I could not care less about my microbiome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who have the opportunity to travel often have so much distain for people that can't travel/don't like to tra… https://t.co/hierl3JnUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al the bottle girls have spoken, Any SoundCloud rappers wanna voice their opinion? 🎙 https://t.co/jlvyHTRyvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Sunday, time to catchup with pop culture. SNL, done. Up next: #SparkShorts — Smash and Grab | Pixar SparkShort… https://t.co/kQs3nmCowY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s Monday and you wish you had a twin. One to go to work 💼, and one to stay in bed 😴 #monday #mondaymood… https://t.co/xzaV4pHWrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RollingLoud Me since the first day i bought it knowing it gonna take a while https://t.co/sT1bkr75fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebakingnanna1 @CadburyUK @DrOetkerBakes @Rob_C_Allen @sweetiehour @tweetmasterone @mylegoman @Claire_Clark Awesomeeeee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spiderlinge That’s fucked up. You have every right to be upset. Sounds like the system made a huge error. Your ang… https://t.co/h0265sRZdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ixisav They annoy me everyday and time they open their mouth. They can deal with me annoying them back and waking them up for once lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta love the hilarity #laughter #tee-hee #smirk #hilarious https://t.co/5O0Llfefop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wreckitralph @movies_anywhere I need this movie to come out on DVD sooner, I can't wait!!! 😖💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump SDNY will be ‘waiting with cuffs’ when Trump leaves the Oval Office: MSNBC legal analyst https://t.co/bNJ84Iebkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to giggle. OMG - so true. My husband loves to do this to give me a heart attack..and... https://t.co/pDTTOs4a4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiking fun at Faust Park! The dogs had so much fun tonight. They’ve been cooped up too long with this single digit… https://t.co/nrReuH3lCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a read by  @chriselliotts   This family lost luggage containing food and medicine for a #nutallergy child-   I… https://t.co/HCcpEYB5p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day of lightwave_led, @rezenerate &amp; @beautigenix beauty. A WINNING COMBO! #agelater @ Lincoln Square Skin Care https://t.co/58pSP40loM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite thing ever is coming home from work and talking to my parents for about 30 min each night 💕💕💕💕💕😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram should ask you if you are single or in a relationship on Valentine’s Day, and then filter the pictures you see according to that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackCDLee @proturnedexvax @Dreadpirate42 @4everleather1 @Flwrgirl66x @Charbrevolution @CplBart @boglethemind… https://t.co/ETdtOs85co]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe that what God is doing for you.... I hope you realize your mistake... https://t.co/n9yvMQJ9xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harry Nilsson - Gotta Get Up [Russian Doll Soundtrack] S1 E1 https://t.co/eaGob6tjC2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @Almagro_OEA2015 @IvanDuque Intervención Internacional ya!!!!! No más muertes!! No más heridos !!! Necesit… https://t.co/GPc2ndLsFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weepers And Warriors Vesta Mangun BOTT 2005 https://t.co/Ie0Jw6sZcU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA Mandy Moore is not "piling on" with her experiences about abuse.  POOR choice or wording in your report just now]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got out of my appointment with my counselor &amp; my hard work is paying off!! i’ll be receiving my bachelors this fall 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a good thing we don’t really have neighbors! They probably wouldn’t be thrilled with the 6am jam sessions that… https://t.co/T16gV1u1mG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adoptedwoman @adopteeson @haleyradke Listen while you drive, walk, ride the bus, clean your house, drink your coff… https://t.co/VEUee0BY6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ve que viejo más loco que se cree el Rey de inglaterra que alguien le diga que no es rey que es el presidents de El… https://t.co/6kC2PhSDAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉🎭Happy Mardi Gras🎭🎉  We had the BEST time at the OOC ball tonight.💜💛💚 #Wetumpkastrong @ Wetumpka Civic Center https://t.co/PWPQlSF3VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[must be nice for the people who can walk into target, get one thing, and leave...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The path we are taking is a shot in the dark more than a moon shot.” Jim Townsend #nmpol #nmleg #nmgov #toofar #notmynewmexico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieMcgonagle @joeymcintyre @WaitressMusical Awesome!  Should be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyLevi I just watched your latest IG story. I hope that you have a good workout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbalbuena_4 Double or nothing!!! Steelers don't go to playoffs in 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people shuffle through my piles of paper on my desk! https://t.co/LvkxaDEFgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Thank you, Mr.President. America is standing with the Venezuelan people &amp; PRAYING for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga I am so happy for you!!!!! I cried when I saw the picture of u and Madonna. The smile on ur face is price… https://t.co/9a9hxD3KCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m not forcing you to lay down, I’m just heavily contesting to you sitting up.” @CoryShea5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyMntnMike @MalcolmNance #MSNBC Is that legal money was appropriated by Congress! So now #Thug45 has line item… https://t.co/mxg2EI0YHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[not rlly sure why... but why is pizza always better at 2 am than any other time of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeDeaner @HazelTedStella Sorry I had to look it’s Fresh Step the type is great. No need to scoop all the time a… https://t.co/BLB5ndnLbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justlissa007 @seraphicpetal I'm sure you're gorgeous and everyone notices 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @kmele 2) Get some inspiration from brave, confident, secular and straightforward EU medias. They are… https://t.co/XmvfJUgkZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes @aninick4n6 screenshots things i put on my story or things i send to him but then he never does anything… https://t.co/zYrR51XZQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what needs to be fixed Now. All voter rolls purged and only citizens on the registration.  Spot check state… https://t.co/WOm69NHxO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I HATE that I always tell myself I’m going to wake up super early to get things done before work but I don… https://t.co/UGURKPoVKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon #MyBadLuck I got a red light ticket on my way to rush and try to meet Troye Sivan but he already left… https://t.co/QScDryGip2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler I’ve started highlighting on assessments and excluding grades. Grade in grade book, not on top of pape… https://t.co/BfBtQwwn83]]></document><document><![CDATA[might inspire us with awe for these monumental figures of salvation history, it is in the unpolished picture in Gen… https://t.co/r5wgehbA0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaSmi16083663 These men are genuine.   #60Minutes #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough https://t.co/8KSXsL7xWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Why are u shouting Komrade, does Putin like that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Bull. Trump is no Reagan. Never will be. The problem in Venezuela is corruption a… https://t.co/CT8M6C4Mrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ViewFromMyPerch #BlessedInBmore #GoodMorningBmoreBuds #KeepHopeInYourHeart #FederalHill #InnerHarbor @ Christ Chur… https://t.co/40tBuxGRCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflecting on my day today : I promise you you’ve never dealt with rejection as much as Real Estate agents do 😭😭😂… https://t.co/WdlfAq994Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don this makes no sense.  get off the drugs.  go to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marie5253 Truly cringeworthy and disgusting, and Mitch was right there with him. #sisterwives]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just hanging with the “Boley Crew” tonight, testing out our awesome new Botley coding robots! I’m super pumped to u… https://t.co/SyankSaRcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philliesfan1000 @Goldengal301 @Claire_1224 @bcmom5 @BRNRGAL @LGiaPeace Loved the sun pillar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler is reading The Knife of Never Letting Go! #dyslit 😂 @tpolk8 https://t.co/Rj5HmEwa5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimash_fr1 @dimash_usa @WorldsBestCBS @dimash_official Dimash should sing some relaxing song. No need to show off… https://t.co/J0rE4wVLyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you have the best weekend market when you stop by on a whim and there is a whole concert happening. Nice!… https://t.co/ag1jGCwjQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[bc guys i just wanna warm you, it is coming to this if it hasn’t already. gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do y’all care about ur ex...I could care less tbh 🤷🏻‍♀️ I got a man who is all about me and treats me right..so… https://t.co/I0oCynjgP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to the twilight saga: new moon album to purposefully make myself sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[when are you people going to accept that frozen was a good movie and had a good message]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family!  Celebrating our Lil Cousins promotion to Assistant Deputy Warden! We are so proud of you for your patience… https://t.co/fw4VBKhqG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien @MalcolmNance The Trumps have been corrupt for decades.  Their concept of “class” is gaudy gold everythi… https://t.co/x6mIUsHmSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma gonna keep posting until we are sold out!! #lundigrasdayparty #bbbsswla https://t.co/vFNlQ3DLcg. 🤷‍♀️🙋‍♀️💋 @ M… https://t.co/ZDLQJ4S9DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[crashone WIP for @LisaProjectNYC on Christie @ Broome, 2.5.19 My contribution to this month’s @soldmag Staff Shots!… https://t.co/FnTXh8Bbal]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to add a “pay me or die” clause to my invoices, because it turns out people don’t care about their first born as much as I thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m to the point where Im over social media, why do I need to keep up with peoples lives that arent in my life ? Ho… https://t.co/BoNgex1ChD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when mfs tell you to save they number like no , I choose if I save your number or not like goodbye 👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly tho that’s the only reason we believe it without hard evidence. 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once this next shipment of uniqlo turtlenecks and jeans arrives I'm going to run campus]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think so fondly of the acting teacher who destroyed my self esteem for a year by often remarking what a shame it… https://t.co/i5ZwRx5ir7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC until you walk the walk instead of just talking the talk, you have no credibility. Do your part first then may… https://t.co/Qa6TVmKicw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very very disappointed. Again no concrete action. ONLY PROMISES AND WORDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn__Daniels 😂 😂😂 I was laughing at being humbled while posting a verse on humility]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is to you, the new Bachelorette #WomenTellAll https://t.co/eVPmsz9m75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DysonDoll And on like the fourth call, my Dad was like:   🗣THE RACE AINT GIVEN TO THE SWIFT, TIFFANY!   And then m… https://t.co/0ykNKefSmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC Survival ... one of my kids I grew on lemonade and fried chicken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanieIDean @provdcrumblover @gorillastyle @alta247 @MAGATrumpster @naturelover3333 @MrCharl79533255… https://t.co/gILEBQ5iVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwyatt23 @ELGLSconnie @1stLadyOfWater @neorsd Don’t forget @ZachNavin was also a @CSU_LevinCPNM #elglinspire speak… https://t.co/F5cv9wQuzH]]></document></documents></author>