<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey Jimmy you like to make fun at the Spanish guy in your show right but that's not racist ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillibean557 Democrats promote the killing of babies and now they what to provide Americans with Healthcare ... 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NachoRgz Nacho. Aqui sube tambien solo que aqui nadien aceprotestas si a estado subiendo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotFrmPaulding @KillahCam__ They keep dancing all the way to the bench and eventually join track and field as a walk on]]></document><document><![CDATA[ima say it again, i’m looking forward to seeing Solange live... the visuals are gonna be amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump You know Lindsey if this was the 80's or 90's you might be right? How… https://t.co/R0NvIPMCYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcrehabexpert @drphilpage Glad I missed the anti-ice movement and my rehab pendulum seems to be on point 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y aquí me escucho en silencio, la habitación vacía. Papel, pluma y una oleada de recuerdos que anotar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's @MarkToro talking value of #bumprate #collisionrate   at@midtownatl ATL Annual Meeting @thefoxtheatre… https://t.co/oMFJVkXdR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh.. hai.. I can joinz the winez tastingz? @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/sRs9o54lQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHermanCain All the dem will vote for it. Because they know that it won't pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notvlove87 Was going to tell you if you have Blue Cross they have a thing called Fitness Blue that gives a discoun… https://t.co/bLsUVKoPXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[_taylorbennettmusic live tonight @rippysnashville #concertphotography #nashville #chrisstapleton #tennesseewhiskey… https://t.co/uL6aA2NjfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momma made some good tips on the first day back from vacation. Flirting really does help, even if it’s with straight men.✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hoodletown Munich Dunkel by Hoodletown Brewery @ Hoodletown Brewery — https://t.co/CgbkM5AEPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with like minded people - people that inspire you on a daily basis - people that unintentionally… https://t.co/sSGqkbbFez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMHQ @kellycass  @ReynoldsWolf #sunrise from Milwaukee! https://t.co/Xdgp7b0zrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half: Buffalo 27, Rogers 24.  Willert with 10.  Thomas Glad 9 for Royals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not going no fucking where tonight bitch staying my sick ass in the house as I should]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing a beanie for the next 2 weeks because I tried out a new barber shop 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[photo by @davidnietophoto | what’s on your mind? 😌 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/OwGJ0QKZq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franklinleonard There’s something wrong with her. Don’t know what it is, but it’s there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or do your 20s kind of suck? Like will I feel this way when I’m 30 flirty and thriving? Asking for a friend of course]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished Iron Man and The Incredible Hulk. The former definitely better than the latter. Hulk served its purpose in progressing the story..]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIME FOR THE FINAL PUSH WE CAN DO THIS!!! @TaReefKnockOut @NoleGameday @usnikefootball @FSUFootball… https://t.co/k9f5IxfSZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorEntertainr Amazing Mike! Blew away my expectations. Congrats, sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dakota_stogner is my favorite , told him I needed some money and he sent me some I love you bud ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gotta be the Blueface Effect if I’ve ever seen it. He definitely was/is, he’s just been progressing. Still Swe… https://t.co/SLy8l5GbkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[After church #lattèthirty (@ Elora Café in Centre Wellington, ON) https://t.co/ALiuUkewhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was good seeing @zreese11, @Ztrotman4 , Garrett Wilson, and Teddy Bleuger all putting in an awesome performance… https://t.co/438WWnOppg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cheers - Drinking a Flight of the Rooster by @RaviniaBrewing at @millerspub  — https://t.co/wfXWqtkm7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHofferCBus Its not a conversation I can have on Twitter but I definitely have some thoughts on how badly creators… https://t.co/V8eHgyq35K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonifacemwangi @UKenyatta @NPSOfficial_KE @KenyaAirports @KenyaAirways @wmnjoya @gathara @TeamCourageKE… https://t.co/Q8bAp3HAlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Obviously there were huge consistency errors too, like Rey learning how to use the force like it was nothing. But… https://t.co/6wLDECd8PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at North Star Tavern - @n_star_tavern in East Aurora, NY https://t.co/G4S4Fd7cUU https://t.co/sHw9l1mNiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we still allowed to play Ignition-Remix or are all R.Kelly songs canceled now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve met some awesome people on this spring break. This was my first ever real spring break and was def the best ev… https://t.co/xyfbYpbWCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seamarshmetrosb @BridgetPhetasy And we have a winner. Give this man a Kewpie doll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAC Boys Volleyball Tournament tonight starting at 4:15 at Sidney Central School. Let’s go UV! #livethestorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just announced by @USLChampionship:  "Powered by sellout crowds at the four USL Championship expansion clubs hostin… https://t.co/3yJnZbMMm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't embarrass God because He blesses you by forgetting Who blessed you in the first place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGregoryRoseDDS You mean people who (finish college) who are going to make 2-5 million dollars in their life time,… https://t.co/81wfyLnAfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyeaglesfa1 @100PercFEDUP Demonrats be like https://t.co/vBMrji3VTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hil_81 @HowlMagazineNY @BBakhshandeh @MichaelAvenatti I'm sure my kid's wouldn't think anything like this is ok to… https://t.co/A1pBSOViE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writerguydell @AnnCoulter If you don’t like Trump it means you like the Demons, therefore, you’re an idiot or just… https://t.co/Z8qBLUlc60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 2XIPA by @stbcbeer at @dinosaur_bbq — https://t.co/v2GWUj4iPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerWeather @WOWK13News Thx for the reports. We hoisted an advisory to cover the squalls. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catheri48080862 @thebestof2018s @GracieLovesUSA @McginnKeven @AMBAMERICA @Quin4Trump @DrummondJeff @CraigChermside… https://t.co/IfIhDh80FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umm, where is the pro-life outrage?  Joint Statement from ICE and CBP on stillbirth in custody https://t.co/xGOJX1WxDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedLeitner Being from OH, living in FL, listening to you on XM for many years now, does feel like baseball family.… https://t.co/67HUReT1JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another for the list of why privatization of public education does not work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Screwdriver by @clubtails @ Koch's High Gravity — https://t.co/APSRdSsbMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I find a girl who is proud to be with me, a little “he’s mine” headass... I’m marrying her y’all can get on]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOMORROW NIGHT @lyrichyperion 6:30pm Slangin’ this new 🎤🔥 on the #letsbehonest #improv show hosted by my guy… https://t.co/H17rUFtGwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefBetter bruh i’m sorry, but you’re picking a game where he played 47 minutes. yes lebron is incredible when it… https://t.co/EYkQXIIpP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m continuing Metal Gear Solid tonight on my stream, upcoming events will include Psycho Mantis fight, Sniper Wolf… https://t.co/5kUJiV8w8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews @sjwdebates @JussieSmollett Yup. Anyone who was looking for a reason to ignore or deny all claims of ha… https://t.co/ZcqptUSrMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse of the day - 3/7/19 #mysoulthirstsforGodforthelivingGod #whenshallicomeandappearbeforeGod #psalms42v2 @ Sunse… https://t.co/82IjT9RhkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wayne_horman @WKOW @GovEvers You made a pretty uninformed vote, if you didn’t think this would be part of his twisted agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Browns coach Freddie Kitchens: Nick Chubb’s our running back. ... He’s not gonna back down... that’s what makes him… https://t.co/QsS0NI3u0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we pry our minds away from our problems, we can focus on God and His plan for today. He is our shepherd, so ther… https://t.co/SPD9oCLhrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquikap They put ph in place of a V one time? This whole thing is bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can no longer support President Trump with his refusal to veto the MS-13 Protection Act then was… https://t.co/f1zCcQXXMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drone vid from a couple years ago in Cinque Terre https://t.co/WPHfW12V6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camp season will be here soon! Registration is now open! https://t.co/zAGFK2swhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowstorm or not, we'll be poking @SchellsBrewery #bock with our friends @jlbeersgf until 8! https://t.co/nJymJtz9ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbrogan I’m simultaneously appreciative we live in the land of farmers markets and sad/upset for everyone who… https://t.co/KSyI0wxmil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts? The proven facts are worse than the accused crimes. #MyPresident #PresidentsDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandy25dandy Yes...  Netflix will probably have a special with him as the subject and Barack Obama will make a cam… https://t.co/2rQDuJYy0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LobeLog Surely Cohen recorded an  incriminating conversation or two on this BA§tµrD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump ordered Top Secret Clearance for Jared Kushner, Overruling Top Officials-Trump almost Out the door]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m not one to brag, but I made chocolate chip cookies for a bake sale for charity at @CBSNews today and… https://t.co/RzjKcX0epd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrangTNelson Wait can you actually use this as an excuse not to come to work?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ingostoll Ich würde das #Bully Whiteboard genauso nehmen wie das Vorbild, das wie gerade am liebsten gleich mitgen… https://t.co/vhHbiycPQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Days 38-40 in shorts was coffee drive to school , couch surfing 🏄‍♀️ with the 🐰 and 3 hours of pickleball...  now t… https://t.co/xEkv1lymMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeca_912 Nah we called and everything had to get it, but found out the total once it all got charged https://t.co/X1uXzreYSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTVBTerhune Is there a reason you guys aren’t capitalizing the  L in Lyombelo? Not just once but throughout the whole article]]></document><document><![CDATA[Korean #beef BBQ from a @Cargill meal starter kit at #MeatConference #retail #grocery #mealsolutions @MeatInstitute… https://t.co/Sc2Durzs8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[My niece just called me  on my sisters phone and asked me to come over and play ❤️ like how could I say no to that? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jazz closing lineup should have been: Donovan, Royce, Joe, Favors, Gobert.   Maybe you sub Jae in situationally for… https://t.co/BCfnyeDLnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The longer you put life insurance off, the more likely your health will change. That makes premium higher, or even… https://t.co/HQW9hkvJ9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This way to the carnival #chicago #ice #lakemichigan  #navypier @ Navy Pier https://t.co/aJJfVkauPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your heart aches for this team right now and what they’re going through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackarriere @BasebaIlKing Agreed I like saying Votto is like fine wine he gets better as he ages, love this guy us… https://t.co/NEQStTP89n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AiWalker77 @peta what’s the big oof, we’ve been eating animals since caveman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanzberg @landonjburke @JEKranzberg Oh, so this is who I have to punch when I get to CoMo in a few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, this same juge #JugeEllis didn't bother "following the law" in the Manafort case, sentenced to 47 months when… https://t.co/DqCqOrtvjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @realDonaldTrump In 2016 the United States was between 86% and 91% self sufficient in total energy consump… https://t.co/KeRu1Gdn9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandon Ingram is the first name that pops up when I search for famous Brandon's.  He's tall but slight, a stiff wi… https://t.co/DOcwrMSnMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SenateDems Why don't you mention all climate change scientists are funded… https://t.co/Gzwvf8PaVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnny Manziel screwed up again? The least shocking statement of the day!! Ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao my bf loves 2 get smart but when it’s the other way around he can’t handle it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge Soviet 'mind control' radar hidden in forest  https://t.co/VThhs7mwaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cimarcos @IlhanMN Dems eating their own because she calls out isreal accurately. Dems are acting islamaphobic. Dem… https://t.co/0QzegD2swN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right out of the playbook. Nothing new  .. why surprised?If you ever expect anything normal or non biased your not… https://t.co/mdXJBa7VGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuniorBraves65 Can’t wait to see you guys again! (And hassle you for book 3)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u didn’t vot CUTE on my IG story last night first if al fuck you???? Second of all it’s still live so go vote n make me feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is undeniably ridiculous that a project of this size and length can be dropped on your plate without a moments notice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReggieBush @konner_b23 I can’t get over this video. So much hatred going on today. So much cruelty. Kids need bett… https://t.co/OQguAIIjrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatwestboxing @UnkhanciousAmir There’s many white people, Italians, Irish, German, whatever that embrace their roo… https://t.co/LTaAYRVKun]]></document></documents></author>