<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[With a bottle of water ready for you because I know the thirst is real. 💦 @ Stereo Live Houston https://t.co/DwOIcmeZ69]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think my body would be used to a hang over but every morning I act surprised when I feel like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all those men who want to abolish abortions. I hope that means y’all gonna be ready for those babies to get drop… https://t.co/f1piDWhgSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a full day with my man; this is the best part! @ Cooper's Seafood House https://t.co/vWXgGXBt4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's criminal enterprise is under Mueller's and the SDNY's microscope.  I bet there is lots of juicy corruption… https://t.co/tdPy6iJ0h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stg I remember I had this ex whose mom call me and the 4 other people he was fw daughter 🙄😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc Oh yes, he was a fox!!!! 😀😀😀 &amp; he always came across as so nice. NOT like the so-called "stars" of today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @JoeBiden I'll be totally honest. I just want someone who can #Kick #ShittyPantsAss. I think you can take… https://t.co/mUulWxdh7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@folha Está apenas começando. Tem muita limpeza a ser feita ainda. Até o final do governo, muito jornalista vai entrar em colapso nervoso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already know it’s going to be a long restless night with Lilah not feeling good 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotLithVAian @shanehardy58 Then more then 1/2 of America should be called in2 Mueller's office 4 review 4 calling… https://t.co/XOTWWtfmCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chazzy_Cee I only take responsibility for the one obvious shoe print 😂 but I am sorry 😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vmochama It's pap. Bradley peeing his pants on stage was far more engaging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss Maybe Fidel Castro in his day. But even at that I’m not sure. Donald Trump, in his own words, is a total disaster!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevaevaevans @Jeremyf55928489 @CNN Doubt the parents are going to enjoy the part where the multi million dollar co… https://t.co/GYrxZbebt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[An absolutely radiant practice! This is gearing up to be an awesome musical! Come see Once Upon a Mattress this wee… https://t.co/qyY7bB3J64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, My...@realDonaldTrump. If you declare a fake #NationalEmergency in order to appease a few knuckleheads by worki… https://t.co/8yElVXD5Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @ClemsonWBB hangs on to beat Louisville, Coach Butler should be the National Coach of the Year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendi_c_thomas It’s a main focus of Michelle Obama’s retrospect of her Chicago neighborhood in the ‘Becoming’ memo… https://t.co/IDtQXFmprT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigsnack24 @EzzyboyOYH but let me be clear, i think a woman should get the time a man was gonna get (or vise versa… https://t.co/67BJ3ydNuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody He's dreaming of chasing and catching a record number of bad guys! #goAxelgo #bluepawsmatter #beautysleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not just now finally asking yourself this $64,000 question, are you???? 😉😂😉😂😉😂😉😂😉😂😉😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mister_Jericoco i lost my fuckin’ vape on friday when i blacked out LMAO 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimZarins @FW_Medieval No, a human romance - future husband, so totally worth it, though my German never improved much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created the heavens and the earth. https://t.co/3zGPlyJ7a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink Zebra is perfect for baby shower favors and gender reveals!  So many ways to spread sprinkles and smiles!… https://t.co/HJHVYVd5Bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Shame on you Nancy @SpeakerPelosi.  You have lost your way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so peaceful seeing people around you be happy, but knowing you are not even close to that kills you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broken_medic Interesting... I'll have to pass along your info.  Hope you're not in too much pain after your walk!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I side with the ancient gods #OldGods. Now the choice is up to you ... #AmericanGods]]></document><document><![CDATA[en Segunda Sesión Pública Solemne de Cabildo Del Ayuntamiento de Los Cabos @cmendozadavis  gobernador donde hizo en… https://t.co/IbeLgpm1dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Before Tomorrow Comes (feat. The Parallax Orchestra) (Live) by @alterbridge on @PandoraMusic… https://t.co/CO1As60Ihp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed listening to @SenGillibrand explain how she "will win the presidential election". Also proudly announced sh… https://t.co/IbcYzb5is0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day ❤️ @dakota28diehl #HappyValentineDay #ValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/dueaCeUxmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, let’s make it more difficult for students who are struggling to learn by cutting lunch funding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your an ahole!!  U confirmed him last time senate was overwhelmingly in favor. Anything against @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Disick is an idiot... talking about if Black Chyna marries rob “her name will be Black Kardashian”  No. Her f… https://t.co/z5E9oku0L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash CNN is so anti-American &amp; + their so called false uncreditable analyst is only there 4 Fame &amp; Fortune $$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauriemeyers @politicalelle @xan_desanctis She doesn’t have to imagine the half a brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadSain @smbizrevolution It's your kids fault. I couldn't resist him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoDresbach @fabiola_pizana @RobeEmpire_1 @lunalover25 @rockromanfan @kaikaisonic @diamond_shonna @HandyRed… https://t.co/GIbWtEhJm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fell asleep but dreamt of these potato chips I had left and here we are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm... The West Virginia woman who grabbed national headlines in 2016 for calling Michelle Obama an "ape" has plea… https://t.co/raPYRe0t9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @andylassner @Trump @GOP @GOPChairwoman @FBI Where's FLOTUS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell your child that some kids play differently. They may or may not understand your games. They may or may enjoy b… https://t.co/KWSXa7rBik]]></document><document><![CDATA[people go nuts over the bachelor as if the relationships actually work out after the show ends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second half underway. Rudder leads Montgomery  Lake Creek 36-13 in a 5A Bi-District match up. https://t.co/SlvxzugqZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachEMcCracken @verdouxkai @GCPNation For sure! I definitely need to get new shoes! Possibly two pairs so I can ke… https://t.co/uHY1IvjpmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happiest_Gurl @MrErnestOwens @OffMuteRKelly And their parents shouldn’t take them there either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a meeting with a member of the board of a major climate change activist group member.  One of the fundraising… https://t.co/HpGgH5cAtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this so much. The feeling of having your loved one come home after a deployment is amazing and indescribable… https://t.co/MT0LlJxiF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of a serf-based system of labor, workers were increasingly employed as part of a broader and expanding mone… https://t.co/Htvhuq6hO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whosssss readddddyyyyyy 4 municipalllllssssssssss!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/juCNXmYqwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said they pay $10,000 a month to keep them out? What? I love how the young woman said she will not generalize a… https://t.co/7M3I5r6hhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgad I was just thinking that I can’t wait for the weekend but then I remembered Venezuela will escalate tomorr… https://t.co/CW0VGFc0su]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are my #StarWars fans? I'd rather watch this than football! #iamup https://t.co/yxo5XGt4Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[(another thing I said today is "i love my new pen bc i can make my writing even smaller" my coworker called me evil 🤣🤣🤣)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I thought that you were not going to touch Medicare and Social Security.  You Obviously were not b… https://t.co/MH65JiOaRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @MeghanMcCain I've been saying this for a while this women need psychological help.  I think the dea… https://t.co/sWlM9dC7Tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to think my unicorn of a therapist played a role in that... https://t.co/HPLj2FCJM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astumpf My dad now turns of his favorite news station because “Paula doesn’t like it.” Understatement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[She pioneered how we work and early federal jobs programs. She couldn’t be an economist because of racism and gende… https://t.co/2G58vA9t6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindyMeans @ThomasRhett @dustinlynch @russelled @RhettAkins Yes! Pick a city!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a good day!! #hiking #la #california #wisdomtree #live #love #life #laugh @ Behind the Hollywood Sign, Lo… https://t.co/hw0eYCULp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 6️⃣ Dox Aitken is currently tied for No. 6️⃣ all-time among UVA midfielders in both career goals and points!… https://t.co/gpwNg0EWlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wineworldnews @pietrosd @NJWineandBeer @TheBuyer11 @SteveKubota @winewankers @JMiquelWine @TweetaDean… https://t.co/yoIWSpHP71]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re sore when you’re still laying in bed but already in pain.   I did leg day yesterday but it feels li… https://t.co/wbFDBOTI6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i rly need someone to slap me in the face and tell me to lighten the fuck up and stop worrying about STUPID SHIT  ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need help completing the FAFSA? We will answer all of your questions on College Goal Sunday. Call 812-265-2580 for… https://t.co/GZsEY0F4it]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole “shield” and 3 rejects crap that they are pushing is not what I want to see. AT ALL. Out of all this, I feel bad for Drew #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #IWD2019 I've been reflecting on the music that shaped me throughout my life and led me to where I am today. Th… https://t.co/dkimY7xOZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyo_es_sy Dahil nga senior si boi. Sya ang phenomenal. His mindset. Ilang bdays ba ni meng na ang greetings nya is… https://t.co/HTfasOdMx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“tell the truth through the lens of your part has been because that’s the only part you can change and the only par… https://t.co/UOVHorxUTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao what noise . When it comes to codes.. CLEAR THEM HOES . What problem ? What codes ? If you can’t see them . Th… https://t.co/0CZY3fzEg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweeties imma bout to be all about Parisian flapper girl looks WAIT ON IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of these cool toys to play with and he still prefers his hand, lol. bradfenton33 #4months #skiphop @ Zionsville… https://t.co/SX8ygtgohG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp Enough already, teddie you will never be on the same level or have the following Lisa VP has. You… https://t.co/RgT8gTlNKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Data_Sue_ATX Right?? It's so insidious. And infuriating that the impact is so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using this FBI tool is absolutely incredible. Searching by name and reading the unclassified FBI documents and corr… https://t.co/gaASw5P0vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nurse, #KrystalKenney says she left patches of blood in #KelseyBerreth’s home as evidence, hoping investigators… https://t.co/8hreJwMDzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mxbubba Bro he damn near lost it before the finish line jump but he had it pinned and just went with it, then that… https://t.co/kaAkczWEg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beersrinna i had a guy ask if it was in once and i literally said i dont know, i be sparing no ones feelings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mathgarden @SXSWEDU @LeBlancPeter @LucGoudreault @TobiaBrooke You were amazing. Feel so lucky to have seen the bea… https://t.co/MJ2G3Y92h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque I don’t know who my candidate is yet, but I want this same investigative reporting down about every s… https://t.co/k0ArfhhML2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago today, I flew out to California to begin a 9 day adventure around a city I’ve been dreaming about going… https://t.co/osbipQo3Jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry was also a nice guy.  Had the pleasure of chatting with him when I worked at a Fox affiliate during the… https://t.co/TfpL9nwpxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got this #WIP at 26k what what! How’s everyone doing today? #amwritingscifi #amwriting #dailygrind #writingcommunity https://t.co/IgMiwr5oPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie is not dangerous. He’s unelectable. What did he ever get done in Congress?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drfishman @DryEyeZone @DryEyeCoach @DrHovanesian @DryEyeDiva @ClarkChangOD @DarrellWhite @Healio_OSN @RCOphth The E of the #mgd BEISTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I’ve rekindled my love with @CodySimpson after seeing him on broadway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many voices all at once.   I’m going to face this in a huge social gathering March 31st, at a LivePD Meet and G… https://t.co/msSePTYajv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find your PASSION! Find your PURPOSE! Make it your PROMISE!Thanks @DrBaronDavis for inspiring our future leaders at… https://t.co/lUfosAt58R]]></document><document><![CDATA[“XENA” is the answer to a clue in the @nytimes #crossword today. I should just stop while I’m ahead. #nytimes #xena #xenawarriorprincess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Redid my sign. One of my favorite quotes for this time of year! @mrs_angell4 @lmelbourn @LeslieRussell16… https://t.co/RdVrllZFH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's entertainment. #hilarity #giggle #smile #clever https://t.co/d3hcvbuDEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EventeurChi @pjstorms Thank you!!! You too, to you two. https://t.co/zj6AitTP4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @lldubs Oh, yeah, Monica #CourtneyCox has her vein...#lldubs has the 🙄.  Beware⚠️ of both of them,… https://t.co/p6Qz7HceJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for new music, any suggestions? I really like EDM, hip hop, r&amp;b, and indie pop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEFTIST WAKE-UP CALL!!  Mexico is ALREADY  Paying For The Wall - Now Go ... https://t.co/nhjKpUwAw3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindness coffee and snack cart being delivered with a smile! https://t.co/WeaGmIlg4l]]></document></documents></author>