<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Coach_Willett and his squad on their back to back 15th District Titles! @thebigjamesmac @steve_coachk  @GlasgowDogPound]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever learn to crochet, this will be my 1st project 🙂 https://t.co/b4f6Pgxq2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkPelfrey All minus Reid so we will be fine next week when he is back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freddie Kitchens: A lot of work for Kareem Hunt to do before second chance comes https://t.co/C4kVgOL9Oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shahselbe I know the feeling! My sympathies and congratulations, in that order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church doesn’t exist for people to come and have their ears tickled. Church exists to declare how great God is and… https://t.co/GZOAsmZZw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSoGu @RadiologyChicks @ACRYPS @ACRRFS We look forward to having you! Thank you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the 2 dudes who are liking all my pictures,...my dms are open so slide in 🤭👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[My labor went from 0-100 reaalllll quick with that. 10/10 do not recommend getting induced unless necessary bc it m… https://t.co/EGFeY47qv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I was in war before 21. If Malia wants some wine before 21, I toast her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatfamilyTrivia @TheAnimatedBat @JuliaKato Such a great episode. I loved the way it showed Bruce’s cunning strateg… https://t.co/mrzDZljXPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustSumNiceGuy @BrendanSchaub @RondaRousey Bigger douch is Edmond who has no business in MMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Baltimore County, Maryland https://t.co/Av4QMm56nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #Buffalo #Bills from 1965 0n.  https://t.co/TfjD7LO2dB … … … https://t.co/HRoPQil69g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that Bernie is a member of the Silent Generation is meaningful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing as it’s 5am, do I even bother trying to fall asleep at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justifiable homicide! Revenge or self defense its justified. I would save judgement of this woman unless you walked… https://t.co/RQaZuuzo6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @_Danejah_ to post 7 covers of books I’ve read - no explanations - no review - just… https://t.co/Tm2GbWDO2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m bringing it to the runway again in NYFW and I can honestly say that through words, actions and life,… https://t.co/wGAueAvtpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never seen a team create such strong bonds to a city before they even played a game.   The Vegas hockey team d… https://t.co/vbcxzgBw5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lewis Marriott started the Cowtown Weekend MARATHON! https://t.co/twDj8HJSH8 #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A HUGE block by @decaturheritage Will Jones takes this game into OT....   47 all  at the @AHSAA_hoops   #Ball4ItAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quietfanatic I guess this would completely depend on the individual intelligence, but I appreciate the optimism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦍🦍- one of the few people I actually miss from high school 😂 real recognize real and you always gon have my trust big bruh 💯👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Contractor In Woodland Hills, CA | 855-456-6835  https://t.co/Wn3XqiMP3S  -Premium Service -Low Prices -Qua… https://t.co/aWFW4ywHhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[INTENSE Army Battles, Firefights And Helicopter Battles  (RAW FOOTAGE) F... https://t.co/FQ9YaOMRdK via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @ReaperKat I guess I never realized how poorly @FLOTUS speaks English. Too bad she ruins her message on not… https://t.co/n1Yf3KsUBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lakia_Holmes @TaylorRooks Yes!!!!!! I’m inspired with how you keep chasing your dreams. @BYUComms is lucky to have you as an alumnus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited about delivering 160 handwritten kindness grams out to @APS_Finance We have been collecting letters all… https://t.co/vmpSqxJ23H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellis Island NJ Sat Mar 9th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Sleet Lo 35 SUNDAY Rain Hi 45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felderk @FairParkRising @edgray1906 @Wylie_H_Dallas @KenKalthoffNBC5 Councilman Felder at Dallas City Council Plan… https://t.co/oGL4tJFBDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JettyMind @MarkDice @AOC Aerospace and software engineer here, nice try. Liberal grasps of science is typically re… https://t.co/RkXmppEf0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itscarneezyy Fair enough Chief, I still think my boy Mob BIG saucy out here though you feel me? Look how glorious… https://t.co/j7XQL87lxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Though men's hearts were as hard as rocks, the Word is a hammer which can break them! ~ Edward Reynolds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listens to Alex Jones on @joerogan and my head is literally swimming https://t.co/ZwBcq9hg1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @NBAonTNT These guys are absolutely awesome. Man that’s funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dubbayoo @xanister @Bellaira @LinkinPhoenix @davidwhittam Keep a lookout for the Eric Cartman themed Go Kings Go v… https://t.co/W7rk7xva8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Better Question: "Given trump's divisiveness, why would anyone ask him to throw out the first pitch?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀 Halftime at UCSD: @CBadGirlsBBall 33 - @GrossmontBBall 23.  Alexa Miskeska has a game-high, 18 points, including… https://t.co/JtFTC3GWmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerTylatch Idk bro if ur late everyday It makes me feel like ur disrespectful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL @AMG_305 @brickleysbrowns Thoughts on Cards puitting out all this smoke for Murray at one to run up t… https://t.co/hSgs6bGTns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @secretRicky007 @AOC and they are good at leaking and also making up stories]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_hippiequeen @RoundRockTim @Aarcraft9 See now this is some bullshit because even if I counter that I have, it’s… https://t.co/7rlFcOYehA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strnglss @ErnstPauli88 @Pope1849 So I think most of these suggestions are 💩, but I could definitely see a Michael… https://t.co/vOqx6B9XY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking up to security at SJC, I realized I had a can of guarana in my carryon. I drained it in the 3 minute queue.… https://t.co/IyMI7oMZiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmayn Bernie needs to put his ideas into a pamphlet or a Powerpoint or something and just hand it off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeelStCloud LMAO!!! Valid point, major fucked up but valid nonetheless. Oh my gawd is this some fucked up shit...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillNye @AOC No Bill. You support liberals, you support legalized infanticide. Then you support socialism, the end… https://t.co/hhaifIlgKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday @SecPompeo Good answer @SecPompeo when CW tried to “stear” u or YOUR REACTIVE REACTION to the “big”… https://t.co/1ihMjn6kAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr In other words he is part of the swamp and will what DEMS tell him. DEMS are running DC while our cou… https://t.co/vSceWPoY7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 gold medal 4 all star mvp 1 mvp league 3 all time list score you whant more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit feel like I am: 1.) going to throw up  2.) pass out  Should not have ate before coming to the gym!! 🤦🏾‍♂️ hey… https://t.co/2l2XRfOWuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This race is so pointless . . . thank god Supercross is on in a hour ! #BoydGaming300]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scout_Finch Democrats do support killing babies that survive https://t.co/hVSsYbejLa can make up all the crap you… https://t.co/ujjKOgbJVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Brian you need to be investigated you probably on welfare assistance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHIEFGILBERT1 @OHFCSO @FCSO_S6 @fcsok92 @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation Though chief my car would look like a Christ… https://t.co/rrlvST1zv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joabaldwin @britbury21 this honestly sounds like Migos, prove me wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICYMI: Watch @GayleKing’s  unbelievable interview with @rkelly on @CBSThisMorning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people thought about ways the Patriots dynasty might come to an end I’m not sure this was a scenario most people thought of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out for Ricochet - our new double IPA! 💥  Big, bold, and hugely aromatic with unbridled hop character and an… https://t.co/zjFqfYCPYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny+Teenager+Posts | tagged funny hilarious teenager posts teenagers tumblr #hilarity #laugh #grin #laughable https://t.co/c6CGJ5W4Wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpjeno @zachleat @RebeccaStavick Well I was sort of kidding. More along the lines of "Startup Sis".]]></document><document><![CDATA[More to the point, since when did revolutionary socialists get squeamish about violence? We're all libs now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two minutes into this Oscars pre-show and I’m already uncomfortable. #OscarRedCarpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I signed up for a soccer league at work.. I dont know the rules or really how to play. But you can bet you ass I… https://t.co/6Rf693Y9t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldKutney @jkenney The whole point is the collective actions of many, from me, from you, from regional governme… https://t.co/XExvSPJ0NV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyO Wouldn't you like to know what was in Mueller's written questions for Trump?  I would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump and @LaraLeaTrump just normal people flying commercial on travel day. Very nice/respectful guy 💁🏼‍♂️… https://t.co/G3oDND4NXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ojay_MojoSoDope @TheMattGrimes @zaytheprophet_ @afuentessss You all look good, but you’re not the OG 1506. Just re… https://t.co/7B657aYNC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFlynn20 Trump has hurt hog prices too much or we would have foot the bill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLong_Bailey I don’t think they’re exactly intrinsically evil, but the @Conservatives and the @GOP were evil, I’m… https://t.co/tlzdA20fYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So which one of my dawgs gonna drop a jit wit me so our kids can be lit ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Does the sun undertake to do the work of the rain?” - Marcus Aurelius  When we live in accordance with nature, we… https://t.co/xsQdlMo7sB]]></document><document><![CDATA[realist thing we will read, and some of us will forever take them for granted.. your mom is the realest person you’… https://t.co/j08W24Pyh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[These most magnificent and intelligent #pachyderms must be fought for, not eaten! #Boycott #Botswana!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attorney representing Caitlin Clavette’s family released these photos of the manhole cover that flew up and killed… https://t.co/WekUKPfTSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 23:11 Make me a servant, is today's posted devotional at https://t.co/Mew4SEYFvw &amp; https://t.co/Km0JAdJPzA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamrank I like pro wrestling too, but how about you drop @RicFlairNatrBoy of this list and add a real wrestler li… https://t.co/hG0ORa1H47]]></document><document><![CDATA[So y’all are telling me that you couldn’t get a 1st round pick from a team that has 3 in exchange for the best rece… https://t.co/Y1JnP20gqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm actually sad and equally kinda weirdly happy that Teheran may start opening day again...just...yeah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poster artwork I created to commemorate The Original Harlem Globetrotters at the Pechanga Arena San Diego on Februa… https://t.co/OEmIV7qMNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[proof that azealia can’t stand to see other female rappers be more successful than her. as I said before, you are c… https://t.co/50jrcGtLxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[DV’s Blake Gearhart scores last eight points of 1st quarter to give Warriors 10-9 lead after 1. #winorgohome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Helloeats_ HQ in Orem, UT https://t.co/FyRZ2GPbLM https://t.co/KZcudBKTjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganPatin photographed and filmed in the Garden District of New Orleans the day before Mardi Gras 2019… https://t.co/SWL06gUbVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karasoth @WinslowHomie @AdamLanceGarcia I also agree with the terrible pacing, storyline and emotional disconnect,… https://t.co/zAumh9F4a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Cumberland, North Carolina https://t.co/REXFk5eAE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #random #landscape #landscapephotography #winter #cold #lightroom #samsung  #galaxys9 #galaxys9plus… https://t.co/uTvvhiksAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSymmesESPN @colepearn Yeah it will he’s always been a great plate racer and drafter, not the wins to show for it,… https://t.co/B9mHH3TLvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akkingon how on earth do you know where you're at with those conditions?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitePac2 @670TheScore @JulieDiCaro What if, you listen first then add a criticism. 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nephew: “How good of an athlete were you in high school?”  Me: https://t.co/yN9EUQwy7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Troyw4242 Damn Troy, they’re up there too. But Boys Who Cry was on another level. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marl1405 @LeDevoir Thanks for the local color. Were u involved in the planning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why’d I think Tyler Posey was taking a photo with Diego Sans https://t.co/3pwnrVAEuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloBowling He will feel that tomorrow but what adds fuel to the fire is that his pride was shot to hell. PRIDE all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaAKehoe @ethannaluz @StartupGrindPhx @therealAniRavi Not the same without you in the director crew this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frosties for the Avs in #Smashville! Right @lmg8? @PredsNHL @Avalanche #COLvsNSH #GoAvsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a case of religious beliefs trying to negate civil law. Those people will never let it go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilHecken @UniWatch Michael Thomas wearing an OSU shirt under his Saints jersey vs Cincinnati this past season.]]></document></documents></author>