<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MikaelaShiffrin I’m gonna leave this right here - you are a role model for young women on what it takes to win. Congratulations!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live for nights like this one ✌🏻 Happy Friday kiddos! Let’s make some blurry memories 🥴 . . . . . . . . #friday… https://t.co/wJhh3Y5bRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Gold Fly.....😮  Crazy!!!  I guess Global Warming is affecting everything....🌞  It even has Green Eyes....🤢 @ The… https://t.co/YCItL8r8lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldnt say that #coffee solves my problems, but it certainly prevents me from creating new ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YelpLA @Yelp Thank you for making things right @YelpLA @Yelp https://t.co/cK3sG27Uug]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random advice for incoming college students: save atleast 4,000 dollars before going to college. I swear it’s easy… https://t.co/Uk3BejtRbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So bc I am at home with my son, while my husband tries to take care of things, and I try to be better, while I take… https://t.co/kAMVNyjczv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great morning presenting about @BrightBytes Early Insights Suite with @Crystal_Aker telling how Springfield City Sc… https://t.co/uroiFzh1UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course hackers would steal money from me on a 3-day weekend bc I can't go get a new card until tomorrow 🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[The census citizenship question is specifically designed to harm immigrant communities. I just made my comment to p… https://t.co/o7g5aoHxPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence Why am I always SMH at these lies.  I can’t understand how anyone could believe this BS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bailé el baile prohibido (Lambada) en tercero de primaria y sobreviví. #AvancemosJuntasEnConvoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everythingloria Where you had the courage to be straight with him, he did not have the courage to hold himself acc… https://t.co/R0VNSWKAKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Double_L22 LOLOL and that was before I went to campus today only to find out classes were cancelled 🙃😭😭😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTRUMPERLAND @LaunaSallai @Jillibean557 @RubyRockstar333 @FL3WBuZ @KINGof1611 @INTJutsu @speakrofhouse… https://t.co/TePz9R6k6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raiklin @Patrici15767099 @w_terrence Yes I do happy your feeling a little bit better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Willow wanted to participate in Tabata Tuesday this morning, although her version was slightly different....Tabata… https://t.co/ml5mD8EkjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[your long branches are like arms of comfort, shade and a sense of family-our roots.    📷 @xraydj  Charleston SC @ C… https://t.co/RtCdrTj84Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nasty indeed! Shoulders are crying after this “Shoulder 6-Ways” from @MitchHeaslip    😩🔥 #fitness #fitfam #gym.… https://t.co/EIShevJPZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikelisovitskiy @MariaARIS3 @ruby_zd @Ruby_Rising @nursrose3  @demon_heart_spn @GailZMartin @yui_aya_miu… https://t.co/YPTuYjZ1tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition Ok have information what are you doing abt this information?  Are you sharing it or just providing infornatiin]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @jonasbrothers have started a trend and I think all Disney artists from the late 2000s need to take notes 🙌🏼🙌🏼… https://t.co/poyr3jcge1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit, I forgot to add that @charlottelawr is in here because she claimed it’s her dads best show and I want to believe her]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I started selling drugs, who’s gonna buy some from me because that’s exactly where I am in life 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay rate my #mediumrare steak 🥩 #ididntcookit #shoeleather https://t.co/6kCivRJUXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdManOfAustin @GQMagazine Was he looking in the mirror when he made that statement? I'm sure he couldn't be referring to my President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellemare_jesse Beautiful! Bobbi does such amazing work. I’ve had a few new species illustrated by ear, and her bo… https://t.co/pCf7MFWWYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES. PLEASE. Solar beats other sources of energy almost every time. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #Solar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MexicoYaaj Bueno yo no entiendo hoy en dia todo es open maind y mas faciles para uds lis jovenes.y aun se estan qu… https://t.co/zfHZVG5mSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm always in awe when I see recent grads announcing their great new jobs right out of college. Thank god Twitter d… https://t.co/HYQsMoJXaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk K A L E I D O S C O P E: a collection of free analog creative sanctuaries dedicated to the refusion of a… https://t.co/uIc2zptcUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[comme j'etais sûre de pouvoir atteindre le résultat souhaité ,j ai confié mon fils à ma mère et j'ai commencé à étu… https://t.co/kykSTqYPab]]></document><document><![CDATA[This from the idiot freshman who sailed she couldn't afford an apartment in DC. You are such a tool. Can't wait to… https://t.co/t8WyIcNN5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIGBANG - YG On Air ▶ LOVE DUST(사랑먼지) https://t.co/FRUUXpmaJa via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put up some snazzy posters to help promote computer science in the halls today for #DLDay #DigitalLearningDay We’re… https://t.co/xqvk4TvTnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all are strong, smart, beautiful, kind and compassionate women around the World 🌎 Happy Women’s Day 💖🌷 @ Toront… https://t.co/eZXYBPbfpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[kanebrown_music  last night was amazing, he wore a Texans Deshaun Watson Jersey , put on a hell of a show, and to t… https://t.co/izcCvWdIlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoJATOE No for Dee I got a few friends to pull together and maybe do a little raffle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily reminder: I most likely would have been able to afford SAG’s dues by now if my cell phone carrier had not bee… https://t.co/NZ88m8ap7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donlemon @purpleforora Don Lemon, you are the real raciest jerk! Even when the jerk  is probably guilty you still… https://t.co/Lefjcr9wSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my girl hitting her 1st High School  “Outta The Park” HomeRun!!! Love my girl🥎❤️ #1stofmany #mygirl… https://t.co/gF3kGWIZ5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r9miles Causal research is hard when tackling something as complex and abstract as reading process. With very conc… https://t.co/OEben0izE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our newest photo backdrop/ceremony structure for just about any occasion!  Double paned for extra depth and an opti… https://t.co/vvsZ8r4Wak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsightTaxLaw @thedailybeast Sorry. What is the con now? The fact that two queer boys were arrested, and put to de… https://t.co/AishkZKXsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Listed in #Charlotte #NC. 11812 Shoemaker Court 2283! Please retweet!  https://t.co/3E1RWQlFnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKlave What trailer did she fall out of? "Sheriff" my ass. Now when I watch Nye County on "Live PD" I'm going to s… https://t.co/OeNhnGURB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only good thing that happened to me today is seeing a service dog at the bookstore 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many questions? The baby? Him peeing his pants? Why is Bernie so tall??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rejection is perspective....  It can mean nothing or it can mean everything.  It can cause you to question who yo… https://t.co/wyi3IIvicr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You failed Don.  You told a different story from Kim as to the failure. The buck stops with you. You failed US. Again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 Something tells me it’s Valentines Day! Happy valentines to all. ❤️🥰😍💋💐💗💘 @ Bellingham, Washington https://t.co/hFV30GbzoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[help. I will never understand you bleeding heart liberals falling all over yourselves to protect murderers then tur… https://t.co/NlyhRAJn3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[He doesn't know what facetious means, do you? What you see is Acting.  He feels nothing, says whatever comes into h… https://t.co/CkCdboRcFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bringing my coworkers donuts and coffee tomorrow, they don’t know but they’re all about to be my valentines ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know I complain about lousy customer service a LOT, but today!! Huge kudos to @BankofAmerica for catching a f… https://t.co/pxwS8AzLjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine with this. Hopefully it’s humbling and exposed weaknesses they need to work on. Vols will be just fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just screenshotted the snap Kevin sent me of 2 boxes of girl scout cookies some lovely gentleman at his work sold… https://t.co/brVUiVYoSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a couple ideas:  1.   How about if the men who       DROP their pants, use       contraceptives‼️OR;  2.  Unm… https://t.co/GtkosCZTLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Denier Is Spearheading Trump's Climate Panel - @colbertlateshow https://t.co/qo5vaxrghj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brothers 7th birthday and the only friend who was there for him was baby Cel and Lina :( MY FREAKING HEART 😭😭😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBedellWHIO @MHartsockWHIO @DaytonFootball @DaytonMBB This is great! Maybe we need to invest in some bubble wrap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚Proverbs3:21-26 We live in a stressful world.  We are bombarded by negativity from many quarters.  In six short ve… https://t.co/RRjrnsqpLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly praying to the heavens i don’t run into any kids i teach this weekend in rocky point  👀😂 cause I’m not ms.… https://t.co/oU1fqae8Xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Go ahead...no one cares about your debates....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerrickMoore88 I will haunt you until I am your #1 favorite character. #motherofdeath #SLAP #insidiouschapter2… https://t.co/6HsCbk8NaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember in 6th grade my best friend and I didn’t want to run the mile at school so we tried breaking each other’… https://t.co/HVzem8KiBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Republican controlled Senate wont do shit about trump paying off stormy daniels while he was president. At this… https://t.co/tgPOJ8NHqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NADOHE19: “I’m tired of building buildings. I want to build people and community.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen How desperate &amp; sad that he went to that place... he did an injustice to so many causes.... sucks all around...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole mood when we sweep Alabama and then remember  Saturday is the last time @Bwb_2 and @horace_spencer0 will p… https://t.co/v91Hspxy4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[J’ai toujours ce que je veux... ça devient effrayant mais je ne me plains pas]]></document><document><![CDATA[We studied Question-Answer-Relationships relating to DOK levels then the students applied this knowledge when const… https://t.co/elhUAXJp7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many people grieving this week for the loss of loved ones...family, friends, neighbors. So instead of… https://t.co/IiuO7xLkai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister tRump is a Traitor and a coward #NotMyPresident #ImpeachTheBiggestDangerToAmericaTrump        #ImpeachTrumpNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been CACKLING for 10 minutes now because I was watching the barista make my drink and I remembered this meme: https://t.co/a1U86HY2ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerezHilton @KimKardashian @khloekardashian Mess with her baby sister, the claws come out]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom making me choose a historical figure whenever i had to do a biography project in elementary school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts @Jeopardy @GMA Good grief. Of all the things that make me feel old this tweet really hit. I was on th… https://t.co/hzposjwMEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pretty confident I am the only one from Rapid City, SD that hasn’t taken pictures in front of Mount Rushmore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1pissedPolack Your family has a right to mourn any way you see fit! God Bless!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day of the Week: Wednesday  Deity: Ganesha, Remover of Obstacles 🐘 Mantra: OM Shri Maha Ganapatye Namaha (Ohm Shree… https://t.co/CuDcQScpWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’d think the older the female the higher the class...I guess...that’s...untrue. Damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricet2568 @shadowstar30 @sweet___ash Aww thank you so much Tony! What a sweet compliment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeaGig139 @PatriciaAHenso1 @Yve8699 @linda1974a @MyLove4Fassy @LovesWaterViews Happy Valentine's Day, De'a et al!… https://t.co/BPa3JFJnEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shutupmadelynn Apparently it means she’s posting something but sending it to a specific person??? There was a tweet explaining it but idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's getting harder and harder for people who actually need painkillers to get them. And they say it's because of o… https://t.co/3KTmq0n9kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A thing I keep thinking about—centering being a consumer at the heart of your identity is pretty toxic. And consump… https://t.co/4Bn0cFLbHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi anyone going to singular tour Philly can we all take a Philly girls group picture.... please and thanks mwah!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In love!🥰😍                         #masonjames #milavictoria @moparedes @ Newmarket, New Hampshire https://t.co/d2YZNhWiFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this is finally happen. For the first time, gun-control groups out expended the NRA. Sad to think that as a… https://t.co/QlGbX6u0AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetMariaS But you could come visit me and we could go to the beach and to Disney 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTobstersMom @LibColleen Oooh- exciting! So far i have only made scarves and hats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSNSteve Yep another one bites the dust #hardtobeasensfan you guys have a hard act to follow after @TSN1200Bunda @creecher1200 what a night]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant believe this is my life LMAO so much has happened since i napped]]></document><document><![CDATA[This type of behavior from a President of USA will sully our democracy for too long!  I pray this can be bleached w… https://t.co/dq53i0cl5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así es...todos los días es el día de esa creación perfecta! #FelizDiaDelasMujeres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @CBSNews , why would you even do that to those poor parents, they have asked police to help them for two years see their daughters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnvmoore @eclecticbrotha My first thought was Cubs victory rally and parade. Maybe that wasn’t a celebration sin… https://t.co/8fekjPMSUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents are going to kill me when they find out utc sent me to the hospital by ambulance instead of with securit… https://t.co/9hi4EscEvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debralcamp @Jennifer_Hogan @HillMrispo @SteeleThoughts @drneilgupta @SarahSajohnson @OroAnnM @AllysonApsey… https://t.co/xPLvJfB7qp]]></document></documents></author>