<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@comicsexplained NO,NO,NO,NO! Physical copies are best! You can't SMELL the age of a digital comic! You can't feel… https://t.co/rEbfZ5PzJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youraveragejo Seriously just had a dream this morning that my mother-in-law was driving us on a road like this in… https://t.co/O5cS9zevlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beliebers! It’s time to rock the vote! Make sure you Tweet and RT to vote for #Beliebers for @tacobell #BestFanArmy… https://t.co/9umEKyqqHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we are talking. Every airport in America should look like this 21 st century all the way. https://t.co/nZWI5Tdsza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah! So awesome and I’m so happy for @TimGettys and @GiaTapHarris! Love this! 😄🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter: Republicans Opposing National Emergency at Southern Border Are Not Principled at All https://t.co/Lq9XLutIid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiraichaengie I will never buy a Huawei phone  https://t.co/gsIMF3ZuDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[v.1.0 - you begin to preempt and predict outcomes of situations, aligning your heart for the next season BEFORE any… https://t.co/gZKWpH652Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle aged man pets a horse. @ Norco Farms, Norco, California https://t.co/aDdpbGfkea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, actually, the "If Congress won't act I will" guy is no longer in office.  The new guy hasn't been that bad so… https://t.co/2V7uU3pTX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjayerrday Man there still an hour left bro why u start the stream already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brownsWAVE I’m much more interested in the likes of ravens Zadarius Smith washington Preston Smith lions Kerry Hyd… https://t.co/TeJf4d6DXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LoveLike_JESUS We should keep what we just switched to. More light at the end of the day. No more switching back… https://t.co/bWPi1MzCtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[As my brother @opdlla said, “this is what ABD looks like.” It’s been almost five years since I officially started w… https://t.co/FBKSSWeTgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigten @B1GWrestling “Wrestling is too important not to cover the entire tournament on the @BigTenNetwork “.  Wres… https://t.co/BMBGtvAYv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlcusa1 It's all choreographed they're intentionally upping the American hate index before ((((they)))) collapse t… https://t.co/Odn5GpKqrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars may be putting people to sleep but this gotta be first year everyone was right on majority of winners. ✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s called training, Donald. The payback comes when it must be applied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little 🐻 loves Disney just as much as his Momma! What have I done?!?! @ Disneyland https://t.co/fmGV92Exfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmoren @danielpunkass Ordered.  Happy to support a local (and enjoying your first book as well).  Good luck on the launch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m as big of a D Rose fan as anyone but this is revisionist history lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poor flag has seen and gone through a lot of crap in over 200 years, but never has it been humped by a Russian… https://t.co/moT05JCmm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexis Lemire a nice lob pass to Erica Warren for layup. @PlainLocal 40, @AHSLadyHoops 24. #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re lookin at the best blackjack dealer in the tri-state (me) ♠️💰 @ Park Ridge, New Jersey https://t.co/QWWl2anfkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for all the LOVE Hawk Nation. Hope to see you tomorrow. Be Loud, Be Proud!!!🏀🏀🏀🏆🏆🏆 @NISDHarlan @HarlanCheer… https://t.co/VJKXHbZfjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattcolville Back of the shirt suggestion "It's Asmodeus, quick start a book club!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JstnMchl retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donley-2. Cashap… https://t.co/qdu1tueICT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in Twitter time out so won’t be able to follow back for a couple of days. We've temporarily limited some of you… https://t.co/g9gIiv0sdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmadsen See this for now about credential exchange. https://t.co/Pc4SIMIJ4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[CANT WAIT until @Giannis_An34 meets my boy @kawhileonard in the playoffs y’all gonna see when you have a guy who ca… https://t.co/nRaZ67qNC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSHQ @KaceyMusgraves @Harry_Styles You better release a studio version of this wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @realDonaldTrump Get a clean CR Bill and declared emergency. Don’t sign something you don’t read. If it’s confuse veto it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquiUK @BrexitYorkshire @DavidJoBrexit The problem there as in many other places is the PEOPLE have done nothing… https://t.co/pzjwPInsuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a chance to catch up with an old friend with years of wisdom and racing experience last night after we got done… https://t.co/x7HflwN61m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly bro, sooo much music has dropped in the past 2 years, we shouldn’t ask for anymore for a loooong time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird Hey, So how is 666 5th doing? has he sold som som to get bailed out yet? He has his hand in every… https://t.co/hrsJZuKPII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting with Hampton City Schools Transportation Dept. this morning.  Looking for opportunities for our Auto Tech s… https://t.co/POdOIRB1ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith really said the young core has to step up! Lmfao..... the vets have been letting down the #Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento How bout just getting the title for my car that's been paid off for 3 months now. How hard is that.… https://t.co/imdyN3J2Ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawkdaddyjason1 @TrapperTackle Lolol 👊👊 Thanks Jason...really glad you like them]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020’ Class is Strong 💪 @CoachModkins @COACHMALONE @Doug_Belk @evancooper2 @Co_Jackson21 @coachcanales… https://t.co/VnoL9SIoYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I did a gofundme to travel the world to hug every single cat, would y’all donate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[IKE ELLIS- Nothing Like Today https://t.co/P03K9srLMu one time for the first video we ever done....evolution among us ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leandroruschel Você esperava que um jornalista, hoje, seria capaz de fazer estudo comparado da obra dele e de cara… https://t.co/KO0rgJGPOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabbgrat Hasn’t it been on since like the first season of True Blood and that ended 6 years ago skskskks]]></document><document><![CDATA[It don’t matter you win 33% of the finals you play in. Playoff LeBron ain’t scaring shit @KingJames]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penal bien marcado a favor de @Chivas, @alanpulido lo cambia por gol.  Chivas 1-1 San Luis]]></document><document><![CDATA[That #rhonj preview on #WWHL was AMAZING. @MargaretJosephs with that epic comeback to sleezy Beverly. Can’t wait to… https://t.co/6eFMuYUvbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TezlynFigaro Dont just limit it to the left media, all of America waiting to hear what most of us already knew]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 1St Choice Healthcare in Walnut Ridge, AR https://t.co/ABsiIZOLlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We added tire flips to Sam's workout last week for the first time. 30 total flips and it was a killer workout! 👍👍💪💪… https://t.co/hVD6qD5Zbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaLaw employs a law professor pushing @IlhanMN #antisemitic dual loyalty charge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This heifer deserved to have her ass beat! Props to the lady that she assaulted for keeping her cool more than I wo… https://t.co/03m8f2JFqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What as if these guys and Russia turn up under every single rock we turn over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAGirlsmom @we_r_Psymese @machalo0712 @806_sharon @ColbaltGooGal @Seahawksgal81 @naughty1loveb @MissHannahMelia… https://t.co/idEWDcSHVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hiraeth123 @JussieSmollett $1800.00  "I will destroy the wisdom of the wise, and bring to nought the prudence of t… https://t.co/GzDstDMDyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryansuddith Bro you’re just down the road from some jammin #BBQ @OinkADoodleMoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dstebs02 @_carolynlee @SantacruzDaveed See, these old folks just took what you said the wrong way😁. They're so old… https://t.co/3HYMjrVqE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty solid.   Hops hang on to hold it from higher score, but very good. - Drinking a Space Dust IPA by… https://t.co/ClucBxBbRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at little miss blondie. I like to rip her to shreds. She thinks her tail is real atomic. Well, it just makes me wanna vomit. - Smooch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimi Hendrix jimihendrix by Kazuhiro Tsuji @kazustudios #KazuhiroTsuji #JimiHendrix #RockandRoll #Guitar @ Los Ange… https://t.co/2GMdwhk9mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's Goooooooo! Goooooooooaaaaalllllll Orlando City!  2-2  #MLSisBack  #ORLvNYC  #VamosOrlando]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s now March 2019. After the congressional hearing w/ Cohen, Impeachment hearings and/or the 25th Amendment will… https://t.co/9jocZfXOHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[VOY seemed to get “tweaked” a lot over the 7 seasons, with character changes, shifting antagonist to the borg, lots… https://t.co/UehfjJ4yWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanIsABrave @JDunnah This feels hurtful. I just came here to have a good time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ajohnso50141696 @kjblackhawk @RepMarkMeadows Sweet burn. I've never heard that before. 99% of the time it's said b… https://t.co/gzB4TVezbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorRooks Marvin’s was the best!! That wasn’t good by Anthony though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlband777 @KurtSchlichter Just so you can see I'm consistent, here's my Tweet about the House resolution in the… https://t.co/cj8Po8Mh3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalVegas Vegas: The Show was a pleasant surprise and is a hidden gem. I recommend it to a lot of people...  ... after Absinthe of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheyWereStolen @viaSimonRomero @jennymedina Written by my good friend #GeoffreyDunn of Santa Cruz!✊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a deep breath, open your mind, read up on the subject and take some common sense medication.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Le Pirt by @knottybrewing at @knottybarrel — https://t.co/DChVOMXAAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McConaughey so let's get out in front of this...who will be the new mens head basketball coach at the university of texas next year...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ancestors #Warriors #ChampsNoChumps @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/3XigBRy2rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[These days I try not to be too high or too low. I stay in my lane and keep my eyes on the prize. @ Beaumont, Texas https://t.co/6IulPGODfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDunc_ @YNWMelly Boy I know we heard the same song 😂😂 and the buhl TURNED HIMSELF IN P 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoynsie Why? He can't play the outfield or play first better than Santana and Bauer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miguelApalta @ParquesColombia Eso sí es Proteger el medio ambiente, empezar con invasiones y después de eso el est… https://t.co/u62Dl8lYvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treat your girl this nice everyday ya bitches. Why do it big for 1 day out of the 365?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acela not like commuter rail. Left on time and the door shuts hard on my hand. Should have pushed the brats with ro… https://t.co/1J08m8fKK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Par-cooking is the same thing as partially cooking, except you only par-say it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canonlawyered But you also quoted an unnamed source that no one in the court room could have found him guilty. Eve… https://t.co/5P9o9GBQT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Care about who has access to @SFBART?   The city of #Pinole is hosting a transportation town hall with… https://t.co/gLoR9gBulw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoP_Editor Interesting, is this based on what those with #CysticFibrosis have been told to do or what they do. All… https://t.co/AhBo6qAYwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chelseagigz I’m hearing that it might be our tickets coming in early haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyH812 @OHLIceDogs How did @JamieMaxdelaney get in the centre ? #TheBear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inez_javier @FirstTake @ScottiePippen @Jrent2018 he called LeBron the goat last year 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just run over someone’s cat &amp; im gonna be pissed if it dented my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hockey fans would not survive an NBA or NFL game. People standing and walking around all the time.  No grumpy old f… https://t.co/yqMhBqMNou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting at a bar alone is one of my favorite things to do on planet earth. https://t.co/9OOKKR3cgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[C-Shift ARFF Truck Orientation @ Brooksville–Tampa Bay Regional Airport https://t.co/pU1swKWCJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We closed theyear our relatively strong and was glad to finally have our music accessible to everyone and not just… https://t.co/zR3AIj3XAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zdroberts @washingtonpost @NationofChange Thanks for your courage in documenting this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharaCarbone We won’t repeat it’s hard to saying it now. It’ll be a shock to the world but we will still be a great team!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angels receive: Mickey Moniak, Alex Bohm, Scott Kingsley, Odubel Herrera  Phillies receive: Mike Trout  Who says no… https://t.co/zhCyHofgsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buvox @KrangTNelson @William89936537 My bad I miss interpreted it I apologize]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @Uber what am I to do I orderes a uber. It said the uber was a min away l. I have been sitting here for 10 al… https://t.co/YE9DFMYWjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chavis_coriana Lmaoooo go ahead and take Bennet out your bio you don’t have a school anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done Moe! This man is work rate personified. Your journey is just beginning young man, keep getting after it.… https://t.co/PQ2SNj2S5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broccoli. Cauliflower rice. Pesto salmon. @ Wakandan Embassy https://t.co/SGtfUKKqzy]]></document></documents></author>