<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There was a time when I wondered whether we should streamline our topics to focus on only a handful per year—but I’… https://t.co/IPjKQsiGbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adeline esta enfermera pero no lo suficiente para dejar de jalarme el pelo y patearme]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess Hannah G for Bachelorette by process of elimination. Only gal who hasn’t been catty or dramatic]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just music...some of y’all act like country music poisoned your well and burned your crops]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's merry. #mirth #giggle #grin #hilarious https://t.co/wzS87IpgUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food for Thought: “If a cow is starving, we tend to feed it instead of weigh it.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Will she ever accept an election result? She’s really turned crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/K4ckNZuKbn  #offshore #offshoresoftwaredevelopment #offshoredeveloper #hireoffshoredeveloper #LivePD… https://t.co/COjq7Ygst7]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we have come full circle. Dave's book in the Times next to the word verminfluencer. "In their 2013 anthology of… https://t.co/2Rwa1VuEv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch as the Philippine ambassadors to Japan  @bernardokath and @imdanielpadilla tour the different places and tour… https://t.co/sdQ0e4yRw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueJays @Daytime_Baller I did not know that. Rooting for him to make the team this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man when I tell yall I found some wild pictures that I forgot about.... maaaannnn this some straight incriminating ish 😭😭💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get to stop traffic to give someone you haven't seen in a while a high five...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dicen que en mi casa hay fantasmitas pero nadie de los que la habitamos ha visto nada, y pos ni quiero ver, good vibes ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PineyElem highlights from last week in the #STEAM lab featuring general student awesomeness facilitated this week… https://t.co/ofrUhbeHR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way To Go Ms. Schnabel 😊🎉🐾We’ve always known how fantastic you are but now the NASA Family is gonna know too!… https://t.co/7Nr5mehUgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 Things You Can Do to Care for the Planet https://t.co/ksMGn0LQOQ #PublicHealthHaiku We have power to change - Our… https://t.co/xYIt2DyNRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/O6Z1UUWjl7 #satpreparation #satprep #satprepclass #sattestprep #satprepcourse #satpreparationclass… https://t.co/lG4FqD3qVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarheelchaplain In a blink of the eye our lives can be devastated - that poor family]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Look around, look around at how lucky we are to be alive right now!” - - - - - I’ve waited 1095 days to finally be… https://t.co/LrhZufQv5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsadDaDrummer @LewisBlum @AxTheBevTax @ZionBaptPhilly @mediamancomm @PhillyDailyNews @phillygaynews… https://t.co/ErPsr1cDYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib Were u standing with the Jews when u crossed out the nation of Israel on your map in your office? The… https://t.co/8d7F5fdIGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @JoshNBCNews @TIME Depending on your eyesight Joe Biden just might look like he’s got a bob haircut😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump OMG OMG!! “Major” fireworks AND a clown (PLEASE please tell me you make balloon animals!!) my kids… https://t.co/l7qmv7pPBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been sharing my nonsense with the world for 10 years  #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/KncVWvxKYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I was at BU the two years McAvoy was, this meant we lived in the same building and I didn't know it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PenskeRed3 @ScottyMcCreery I know he is seen him many times . I will enjoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reminder on this #IWD19 that there is still a long way to go.  #addwomenchangetheworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two week countdown till my favorite event of the year with the #concertcrew  diffadallastx Is going futuristic this… https://t.co/Jc0Xoh2RJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am in #Virginia today. Folks are patrolling my home. Visually now. (For 22 years since my elections I had oversig… https://t.co/ka4XHeoujE]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to those who Love us when we are not even likable ‼️ Honestly y’all are the REAL MVP’s ♥️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkbossychick Lmaoooo same like I’m always thinking “omg this will get back to my mom somehow” lol 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solitary walks on early mornings. #reset #peaceofmind #sundaymorning #sunrise #letgo @ Portsmouth, Rhode Island https://t.co/lzxJcXKM4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎄Con Sue Photography and Design🎄  🎄Like our photos...Follow our IG 🎄  🎄This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/CVeSyijoRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I seriously question what is going on in this party. The far left has hijacked Nancy and her well s… https://t.co/98gkoRdAYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stand in awe at witnessing Gods glorious deeds. I praise Him for working through me and into the people I love. #Heissovereign]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve made too many sacrifices and adjustments for other people.. it’s time to focus on me now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washing my babyboy newborn  clothes has me so excited for him to be born 😍💙👶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mel0ba you should really think about the Men's feelings before you post something so emo like y u so inconsiderate moo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_p34 @ubathletics #ubhornsup🤘 @ Alumni Arena https://t.co/4j6K58snfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wonko_the_sane_ @benshapiro I am Jewish and I find the comparison an abomination.  I am pro choice.  I wonder what… https://t.co/UQ1LFNt4ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasssieC @comcast @comcastcares No- maybe I should have them contact all of our clients and explain this to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How We Win When We Fail Big on Purpose https://t.co/64GKHgYt3H via @shinetext]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone want to send me $20 so i can get the thank you next vinyl 💕💕 https://t.co/VpYuVee85C]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to give State officer retiring address for @doorneweerdc  #nationalFFAweek 💙💛 #Throwback #ffajustone… https://t.co/voymZaAh5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Well at least she is honest...has an issue with reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett is a distraction! What is trump doing?!!! @EdKrassen @DrDenaGrayson @mama2fluffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realized the last 5 minutes of my lunch I should’ve taken a nap instead of be on my phone 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump plans to bypass Congress, announcing a national emergency to get more funding for his border wall… https://t.co/zqdydegoPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple months ago I accidentally told my nieces that the tooth fairy wasn’t real and today I heard my niece tell… https://t.co/Nkrkp12K1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hOjj6SsluB   #herbalifenutrition #herbalifesnack #cloty_coach #reto30dias https://t.co/UirjHHOd1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning🌞 Twitter friends. My first graders study life cycles through raising chickens in the spring and need s… https://t.co/fbhgMe1PCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have given up on tumblr COMPLETELY there’s no way i will ever get a notice :’( taylor swift come on twitter challenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolute bullshit move to  allow the kidnapper/abuser in the room  during the interview with these two young women… https://t.co/ttIqhJWNXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Women Control the Money, Female Founders Get Funded https://t.co/9StXUcJ5YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomUprise @SaraCarterDC I imagine other doctors gave up bicycling...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this bar playing “how to save a life” I’m about to cry Derekkkkkkkkkkkkkk 😭 @GreysABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!!! Anyone who’s knows me know that is my favorite pastime to destress!!! lol. Love General Hospital.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianacristal21 can you use astigmatism to not work at night? bc if that's the case then im using that mf as an excuse lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear to god if it gets to the year 3000 and we still don’t live under water]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think about it, the thought of a school lunch is disgusting but when I was in school I had some good lunches]]></document><document><![CDATA[This energy will only build you up.  In this Awakening, in this Divine Light, it is only going to give you the chan… https://t.co/U2rErsWWFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been so exhausted and sleep deprived lately that I passed out when I got home today at 5pm. Thought I’d sleep throu… https://t.co/lKwmzAFmiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unrestricted gifts tend to be higher in places that have a lot of public broadcasting activity. (Did I mention it’s pledge week?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karaoke @ the Unicorn 🦄 in Seattle w @TessaMero and she grabbed a pic of me doing the offspring’s self esteem 😄 https://t.co/OX2bJ5AJUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonytechies @jbderoma1 I was just about to say I like my poppers with buttermilk ranch! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Savemefreddie i usually don’t wear foundation unless i’m going out or my skin looks WAY bad like yesterday but mos… https://t.co/gYgsORg7Or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @ItsJimJohnson at #suncitytx #Rotary talk about how the @G_TChamber supports #localbusiness .… https://t.co/hFA2WFQtvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of my little poems! They are getting so big! https://t.co/1Fsxkmc84h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do u ever see the sun reflecting off your mirrors while driving and think ur being pulled over? No? Just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading @beckershr Why this Chicago hospital treats homelessness as a health issue https://t.co/neIfRrIFnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBr83143864 @ASimplePatriot Just as Trump trying to tell American's what to think and how to feel.  Fake Ass People!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Queen Emily!!  😍 Earpers are FAMILY We are here and We stay! @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to… https://t.co/cBn8Pk9fpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday honcho!! @AmirRabah32 💼❤️ i love you, stay humble https://t.co/8OMsreZMXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom is currently telling her recent love life story to a complete stranger at brunch lmao me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleHCherry @QuinnCherry__ Way to go Quinn! I was cheering for you here in Houston!! Called Jordens dad right away and told him . 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madea! Hilarious (at @Cinemark - Louis Joliet Mall in Joliet, IL) https://t.co/CUDCyL24Qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[KINK Abbey Leather Night ‍ ValentinesDay https://t.co/u5mSVNTspd https://t.co/Oc64wkg270]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really shows the maturity level between @jordynwoods and @khloekardashian because jordyn isn’t posting drama on twi… https://t.co/2mvSequ7Po]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mᴀɴ Cᴿᴜsʜ Mᴏɴᴅᴀʏ ʙᴇ ʟɪᴋᴇ...ᴅᴏɴ’ᴛ ʟᴏᴏᴋ ᴅᴏᴡɴ!   #DIPLOMAᴛICAғ @ New York, New York https://t.co/PMg1wFKGcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Starks sent some love to my firsties! We got a stuffed hedgie (the class named him Valentine) and some hedgie b… https://t.co/BdaboE0HwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I (somewhat jokingly) signed my boyfriend and I up for next seasons  Temptation Island and got a call back lmao what do I doooo 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait!  I’ll be getting my ticket next week.  Great conference/great venue!  @InnEdCO #WeAreInnEdCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmac100 Thanks. I'm going to instant pot my own chicken soup. Unlike yesterday I can at least stand today. Can'… https://t.co/LEMkq7347N]]></document><document><![CDATA[CIF Central Section Wrestling Masters Championship update: Aliana Lefotu has advanced to the finals. #BulldogSTRONG… https://t.co/FjQlROljLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Imma depress my foot in yo ass if that kitchen not clean before you go to bed”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retracing my steps, as a kid I had: -A set schedule -Breakfast made for me beforehand And quite a lot of time to "e… https://t.co/5XdOCEKiL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotelsdotcom Well Holy He## F×cling yeehaw more fuc=ing snow in the forecast today #WinterSwearJar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting this month, I am giving myself 6 months to turn the following around:  • spiritual wellness  • health  • s… https://t.co/RXA0zcSPOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih Shirley Chisholm. Mahalia Jackson. Maxine Waters. Alicia Keys. Nina Simone.Aretha Franklin. Mary Finger. Zazzette Scott.]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning happy Monday im neck deep in @chrissyteigen hamster content now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benediction:  May you find a hamlet (IRL! Digital!)  that gives you  the warmth and  community of #TCMParty   [No g… https://t.co/BO4TqJw2WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to go to the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame 2019 Induction Ceremony! https://t.co/RWWGTohnKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP you are a shame not us  you gerrymeanders and liars and fraud children beaters and prevs]]></document><document><![CDATA[o boy came up to my table talkin ab buying drinks and flexin so i said ayye pay for my tab AS A JOKE tell me why he… https://t.co/NY5Th0f9HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lisabug74 Chloe in the foreground where she lives and belongs. https://t.co/BIi4r3CbrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have enough respect for yourself to do the right thing when no-one is watching.  ~ Pst. Martin Froelich]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only does my mom use my room as storage now that I moved out but now also took over my closet?... I’m hurt 🥺lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allmydads OCEAN MAN: ORIGINS!! Okay ya I have that’s lichrally all I’ve heard I gotta shift into ween mode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePostWest @DanielPipes @BernieSanders @fshakir @amprog Sanders also reflects a rapidly growing segment of Jews w… https://t.co/rABFA1t6lL]]></document></documents></author>