<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[How the Mad Ants will recuperate from Saturday’s loss. https://t.co/p5XQ5N4sNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - The Hive:    Rupert Murdoch vs. A.O.C.;      Michael Cohen Goes Back to Congress to Crush Trump… https://t.co/dT4hilD3kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noodletreetx we were going to take our food to go, but we loved the vibe in your space. Glad we stayed. Great rame… https://t.co/H5QdchgA8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marquette’s utter collapse is really giving the Parkey’s double doink a run for its money on my personal list of mo… https://t.co/HgFTxQDu43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibbsMshairgrl @GinaTrammell4 @GaylordFanClub @LaurenDuski Shannon you are the Best!!❤️❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsingLV @abc7Richard I will say 6000+ acres seems rather large. And this is just solar right, no other forms of al… https://t.co/zqfZPAUCFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rangers fall to Northfield 31-32 to end the team portion of State. Individual Tournament starts on Friday. #RangerPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench @RichLowry People should be held responsible for the things they do and say. Starting with Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wisdom #truth #today #profound #thismoment  #jeffreybyron   THE ONLY THING THAT'S CERTAIN IS TODAY! 🙏 @ Century Ci… https://t.co/MqGAHz4lMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bob20390518 @tombrady_NFL THIS ACE DAVIS AT 10 YEARS OLD IS A VERY SMART KID.. HIS PARENTS ARE VERY SMART TO TEACH… https://t.co/sM0XWU5977]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so humbled to have been able to play #OldMartin in the powerful and impactful encore production of the… https://t.co/s4XlJ7aAD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im not tryna promote being an alcoholic, nor am i tryna promote being a stoner. But when you work 40+ hours a week… https://t.co/iHTzm63NLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ra_MicroSci @FrontMicrobiol Deleting rRNA openings is NOT easy, I know all too well. Making these careful measurem… https://t.co/3ujwFz3MPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyFerr3 @CommittoVote @greg_doucette @fsckemall @brycherrera1 Spot on. That’s the mantra- rather than “my first… https://t.co/IBqdVy4SCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineNoelTV Great story, thanks for sharing! Glad that you joined the TV news.. though your journey took you away from Den]]></document><document><![CDATA[...figura d voluntarios para "facilitar" esa ayuda cuando n verdad lo q van s a entorpecer a quienes c encarguen d… https://t.co/IuMJCBuZP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #HillsboroughNC #hyperlocal experience in 18hrs hitting up: PM - Volume, Hillsborough Wine (@CHWineCo),… https://t.co/fwh0dKE60F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Owencroberts17 @_mamadeb @lukobe @BlondieFivehead @Wonko_the_sane_ @benshapiro you are ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffhilimire @geoffreydgraham I agree...it works 95% of the time. I just don't have a choice. The 5% is a casualty… https://t.co/t8swxTuxGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yummy! - Drinking a Game On! by @levelbeer at @elephantsdeli  — https://t.co/hsnEc1c09E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can somebody tell me why we even ask Offensive Linemen to run the 40 at the combine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey is more routine in the ring than @HulkHogan.... at least HH made it look good. WWE just isn’t right fo… https://t.co/aar2KVaVe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omaha Westside leading off Sportscenter. That’s got to be a #nebpreps first.  #bestthing @notthefakeSVP @nsaahome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the Joseph A. Floreano Rochester Riverside Convention Center Tonight for the 2019 Rochester International… https://t.co/tmQxHxZO3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @harjo111 @el_latinpete @MMchiara @Michael_me @DLindsey2 @winbabywinwin @dejean76 @rvplace14… https://t.co/Tuy1G8qxkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@htcbro did you know that the German word "Hell" means both "bright" and "Lager Beer"? https://t.co/19NFz9DCse]]></document><document><![CDATA[05:56 Temp. 45.9°F, Hum. 90%, Dewp. 42.3°F, Bar. 30.06 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 109° 1.6 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @dccc @GOP People who start out tweets with "Dear..." 5th grade JV cheerleaders Prepubesc… https://t.co/5ui6uuia2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limited menu at Moon Tower means anything good that is tapped is gone in a minute. This was the best I could muster… https://t.co/VpB4iHgW6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@che_rollins @justinvondoom I’m gonna have a little 420 time while I tickle your butthole hun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure if this was before or after purchases elsewhere, but #Venezuela’s oil exports have reportedly dropped 40%… https://t.co/OQDDfC3PaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanFilmLover TBH I haven't seen John Carter, but I will defend Mortal Engines as I think it's legitimately good,… https://t.co/qEbwb9TDnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Andy Isabella so far ahead of #1 that he didn’t even make the list?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicksonright @DLoesch @hammerandnigel @tonykatz If it’s illegal for us to lie to Congress, Why isn’t it illegal for Congress to lie to us?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein When many things like this really happens the right says nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peace_as @averiehatton @EBONYMag Not minimizing who’s black enough but the narrative was “Is Harris” black enough… https://t.co/f5iJFqbj12]]></document><document><![CDATA[3-0 @McCallieSoccer over CPA 38’. Jake Tremain on the backside running blast off another big corner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 I've Got To See You Again by @NorahJones on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/RJVm3cA1G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Job @TrentonamoBae!  You are extremely talented and we are appreciative of your incredible performance tonigh… https://t.co/kE3FA5mN0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what I built all by my lonesome. #proud @ Live for a Living https://t.co/awAtqxjQv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I describe Kenny to anyone I use the words "Best Wrestler in the World" now u may find out why...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandicarlile and @JenniferNettles could y’all PLEASE do a collab together?!? That would be an eargasm for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh @settlemlCFB got me so mad that I don’t wanna watch #RAW tonight. Hell, even Mania. 😡😡😡🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also: If you are going to have HP and the Deathly Hallows Part 1, please also carry Part 2. I need all the HP I can… https://t.co/9uBK8a8HfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and the GOP gang are massive (bigly) deficit creators with no benefits going to create a better quality of li… https://t.co/t5SAvtwdBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pastorhodge @CNNPolitics I have no idea how that dude got that job and keeps that job. Literally no one respects him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YangXiaoSlxt Yeah, pretty strange…well is this strange https://t.co/kxKFK7wm9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Painting with this hottie porkchopkay    She’s the master piece ;) @ Agincourt, Toronto https://t.co/DRCZenXDmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[since being in houston i honestly don’t have anyone i can call my “friend” and i think that’s good. 🤷🏽‍♂️  especial… https://t.co/JepMLPIDJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekbauman Could start by banning and removing slip ramps at existing street intersections. See Victory and Madison for example.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi es ! Eviten las vulgaridades y hablar desde el odio! Discutir ideas no se trata de llegar al salón sin haber re… https://t.co/VC3hGgr4v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taxes are done, so it’s beer-o-clock! - Drinking a M-43 N.E. India Pale Ale  by @Oldnationbrew @ Clear Creek  — https://t.co/nwCBjAMBqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy no tocaba entrnamiento... pero lo aplicamos para evitar tener pensamientos babosos jaja 💪🏽🐻 #gymdone✔️… https://t.co/uOakDCQuxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The choice to use more steady cam tonight at the #Oscars was absolutely brilliant. It’s giving a personal view that was absolutely needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2.17.19 #Drawing: A lifeguard station on South Beach, in Miami! https://t.co/M9fvIZzopK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Must-See Acts This Week: Indie folk Gregory Alan Isakov (with John Craigie) 8 p.m., Thursday, Feb. 14 and (wi… https://t.co/eo1fg4dwVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shandershow @jelynchjr Unless it’s Clifford, he’s going to have that problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoOnionsUK @KTHopkins Thanks. My friend is writing a novel about the fall of England.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning WorldWide! Happy Monday full of blessings, and amazing seconds of your life. Not the best selfie, hey… https://t.co/apq9fiANCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bioreus #PicturePerfectClear A Biore Exclusive with the one and only @kristinaschulman 🥇 https://t.co/rgkcyd2Gn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel @realDonaldTrump Democrats aka baby killers and those who have no God but themselves are a cancer… https://t.co/FrYaqJbTX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the coolest @Powtoon videos one of my students has ever made. She’s gotten over 8,000 views. She has a brigh… https://t.co/Wjpi1k0gLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIGHLIGHTS: @TCAmericans can't solve Dustin Wolf tonight, falling 3-0. Let's talk about Beck Warm. 33 save night, p… https://t.co/zgQi5aVP74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump i find it so humorous that the guy the dems are beliving us a convicted liar, and that they find h… https://t.co/9alKuK60N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t imagine what they’re going through now knowing they’ll have to spend a 2nd night there.  Hoping help arrives… https://t.co/oXY5Kb4j5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tight I gotta miss another @CupsNConvos  Gamenight cause I work Saturday nights   Anyone need a ticket?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jckluge @bigtimcavanaugh @akstanwyck @JohnDukeWayne @tcm That’s how Matt Damon always comes across. That’s just Ma… https://t.co/vCTiVokdER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV Hey DICK ! Call for immediate action against Bill Self ! You sre a Hypocrite DICK !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Food 5 ⭐️ Ask for Guba #thankmelater milkmoneybar @ Milk Money Bar https://t.co/nRrqEFqk8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your discussion and theorizing of God and Adam and Eve etc are wastes of breathes]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Ustedes advierten que se cierne sobre el país una suerte de Apocalipsis en pocos días? Recomiendo confesarse de ur… https://t.co/OpnB8sQECo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great take by @AdamSchein - thank you, (from a die hard @buffalobills fan!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[El País no se trata de quien quiere gobernar.   Si no,. Aquien NECESITA EL PAIS , para que lo gobierne.@temomontas https://t.co/fVL1QSg8nM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m stunned and speechless. One of the most beautiful things I’ve ever seen. https://t.co/CWmbqzJnyj @RubberLegzIP @MosesSumney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what else is funny? C- we have a layered brain.  I swear when I am stressed and angry my lizard brain takes over… https://t.co/qqcazh1DZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhorell14 Sharpay and Ryan are siblings and Kelsey is the one who writes music and dates Ryan in the second movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today wasn’t very good day.   But hey, tomorrow is just a couple of hours away. #staypositive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #NGLA2019 attendees! Are your chapter meetings unorganized? Mike is speaking today on Parliamentary Pr… https://t.co/xAbhgvG0YZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningNorth doing a little research.  Some say coy wolves do not exist.. others say it is a hybrid better known a… https://t.co/DjN6XeeGGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:36.0°F WchillLow:27.1°F Wind:5 mph Dir:W Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:77% UV:0.0 @ 02:00 03/11/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[get your money right, pay your own bills, and take care of ya damn self... a lot of y’all are too comfortable🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a good article. If you can help me understand an opposing view, I would greatly appreciate it.  For decades… https://t.co/uEk10IfM8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I have a suggestion about the Democratic primary process. Let them tear each other apart. Stay out… https://t.co/h3i58B5Elc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbook37 He put them up there because he’s impressed by Michigan’s innovative uptempo air raid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I’m cardboard cutout(artificial)swayed by #SweatShopSusie! https://t.co/Q68AG9yHUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 4314 Frontier Trail #Norman #OK  #realestate https://t.co/cUYakUgdSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @littlesexbuddha @milanamaylove @missjojokiss @AbbyCrossXXX @ScarlettSageX @akaDaniDaniels… https://t.co/QaEsIyuLAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . . . #photoshoot #stylish #fordmodels #model #fashion #style #topmodels #modellife #photographer #malemodels… https://t.co/ZHTduujGE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffanylynn314 @pinch_a_bobozo @thecheerdadlife I’m in Wylie sooooo 🤷🏻‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️ lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donfazool @john_fowler_jd I tried some after your tweet. Definite home run!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt this. If y'all think I'm awkward now you should've known me pre-2012. I admit I'm still really bad at some t… https://t.co/5acSwGVFqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I decided to participate in Dance Marathon by fundraising a $400 minimum and dancing for 30 hours straight, I'… https://t.co/90Ug1yLWCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePME @fantasynational Hard to believe you won when the two top golfers (JT Woodland)in your lineup for your ende… https://t.co/eldtT8SPDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get off and stay off! What happens when you get off Facebook for four weeks? Stanford researchers found out. https://t.co/VknPV0AIgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sour Inc: Sour Stout With Cherries by @NewHollandBrew @ New Holland - The Knickerbocker — https://t.co/GaAXYTSer7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiru_tiru09 Thank you for making such an amazing ass on Kris. Like damn that's a nice ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobinmag No democracy is the best system on earth!  Capitalism only benefits corporations and the wealthy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC The question is why did he lie about it?!? @realDonaldTrump The answer is he lies all the time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@storyboardlife @tableau @bibleviz Awesome! Thanks for tagging him Peter....let's hear it, Robert!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seth_abrutyn Agree. That and the fact that you can't get Pappy even if you were willing to pay for it. Have you se… https://t.co/mpnqKEKYHk]]></document></documents></author>