<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Can we all just agree that she's insane, and needs help? Like I wouldn't even give her a ride to the… https://t.co/ksFaCJ8Y8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#survivorspeaks  FBI closed the Las Vegas Massive shooting  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 6… https://t.co/Mi4f7Bunyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last of the #cocoafest2019 was the Samoa hot chocolate, and it was a true delight. @theshopfoxpoint when do we… https://t.co/dOydmD4DU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMH_FZ Thank you. These are sad days. But I believe The Lord can heal our Land. https://t.co/wDBlDthtQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sirveaux1066 @kkcorby14 @ashnotatree @gsmooth89 @uren_marc Watched that for the first time during October last yea… https://t.co/74DPLyqlud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southercandy @grumpcrusader @Valma_Bunce @Pigface0  @MikeJMele @MyMJJisLife @AlexaRenee1 Happy Saturday😁 https://t.co/icyeYcz6GC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Expertise transcends experience and experience always comes with time.” X https://t.co/vwdAd8fStd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Flyers lead #RedWings 1-0 with 9:55 left in the 1st. Shots 6-5 Philly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[California Parents Sue to Block ‘Inclusivity’ Instruction in Schools https://t.co/eqp1jVNFyj via @epochtimes  Onlin… https://t.co/f3kgUriOiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fckin_roo NVM the coke that was left in there from LAST week's shenanigans 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I’ve seen in each video posted each student simply wanted answers and for some reason a simple question made Alc… https://t.co/mFBze3NpfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic “one pager” theme reviews from #ToKillAMockingbird #onepager #HDHSPride https://t.co/rzjgnhoaRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraPerlongo @JamieStelter I have a 15 month old boy and I always buy gender neutral clothing. I hate how all boy… https://t.co/qR3uGJBqtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in bed before 11pm and it feels weird I don’t know how to be WELL RESTED]]></document><document><![CDATA[When coffee is life, a regular coffee cup just doesn’t cut it. You MUST have one the size of your face!… https://t.co/v8JsdWyqgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScienceOMFG @mims Agree, that’s just fine as we’re all revolutionaries; it is the child labor and mountain choppin… https://t.co/L6izXuThRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[28 kids taken to hospitals after eating Valentine's  Day candy at middle school: https://t.co/4NEG2iGXKG https://t.co/OgwqSG8cQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lane_newsom_ i yelled i love you too but i don’t think you heard me from OK :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[The miracle did not happen so now this is a memorial fund. 😔#stevenadamscare #gofundme https://t.co/h3erMIHMT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote an awesome letter of recommendation so my for it to get corrupted and unsalvageable... https://t.co/pKHHtxzZSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @LillyHiatt1 for IG story of last night’s show in Nashvegas! #NewMusic #NewToMe 🎼🔥 https://t.co/Ksya6f3QYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This afternoon I tried my new #cuisinart #breadmaker 🍞 #breadmachine I think I’ll use this for my French Toast tomo… https://t.co/1BMm9T6yl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet @DeMar_DeRozan We miss you @DeMar_DeRozan thank you for everything 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_bauer @RyanDeal_DR @MikeHenriksen I can’t find my keys most days, but I clearly remember this game NOT being… https://t.co/hTDpiU8eF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, I have 1,000 followers! Thank you. Think I’ll make it to 10,000? Follow me I'll follow you back ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get very aggressive and irritable when I’m stressed. I don’t want to revisit that version of me for a minute..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smilon713 What is going on in this country, how can they let these things happen, they have no heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SouthwestAir what is going on with all the flights from PHX to DEN tonight.  Three in a row, all delayed?  #conspiracytheory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having some fun at Politics &amp; Eggs this morning! 🥚 #NHPolitics #FITN https://t.co/iotjuZfSTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShariGateley @teacherman82 @KristinAtchley Also while we are all here has anyone watched “Free Solo” which won bes… https://t.co/zplgGfMmsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get yourself a best friend whose stepdad even yells your name from downstairs on the couch.   Thanks for always let… https://t.co/zuOgH9SRtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 Why does Snowden think people trust the word of  stinking traitor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know many women r angry with me i am not vociferously going cray re these women.. they have to show me more meat… https://t.co/gwJS66HY4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi New York!!! 🇺🇸💃🏼🤤 @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/n3IbMbLWai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a lesson. We want our children to be great right? Right. So let's intentionally surround them with greatness… https://t.co/xThqs9GFvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so impressive that time travelling developers more than 100 years from the future are still developing for nod… https://t.co/i76bo5ES3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support A rep sent me the same old bullshit you guys been sending me for the last 2 weeks. That it takes 3 to… https://t.co/JgTjxlfg38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JULIA3VEGAS @DaphneBarreto You forgot the part where you don’t answer calls after you don’t show up  haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter @ladygaga @GwynneShotwell #GwynneShotwell @SpaceX 🚀♥️  https://t.co/3QjyIRwCp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I would’ve known that we were going to have such a bad storm- I would’ve covered my hyacinths💔😪🌾]]></document><document><![CDATA[COMPLETELY betrayed. Your predecessor was a crook and apparently you are too. You are to represent the PEOPLE of Al… https://t.co/LhT8FDhJRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lived here 24 years-first time I’ve seen SNOW on Boney Mountain!😳❄️ @ Newbury Park https://t.co/WHzY2126XZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really care for Valentine’s Day, but seeing his reaction is what I live for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wirewiseguys hi,how are you ?i sell fiber optic patch cord,drop cable,splice enclosure]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite past time is crying about being poor and then buying new bikinis]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY watching A Star Is Born. I can fuck with a rock star Bradley Cooper. 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoradoChaos Good luck to all the boys! Definitely going to miss this... what good memories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts and prayers @GeorgeForeman to you and your family during this time.🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remhq - Man On The Moon (Official Music Video) https://t.co/Aw1dCwiTrJ via @NASA @NASCAR @NASCARONFOX @NASCARonNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou I think Russian interference was the greater contributor, the media may have been influenced by that and… https://t.co/Yg6E3XZcax]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case of emergency... raise glasses 🍸 #impromptuhappyhour #friends @ Bourbon &amp; Bones Chophouse and Bar https://t.co/xheyItrswQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/IcsqnF8aNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my “husband” haha. Seriously though so happy for you!!❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[End up getting a small apology before I walked away. But this is the thing, folks. If you’re BIPOC you’re either fo… https://t.co/CkbkUFfpN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh let me tell y’all the cloud macchiato tastes like fucking ass its not good]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one I've never seen like this before ! Oh my God.  I have to share this one.  To be that water ..  damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been miserable for two days and I’m pretty sure all I needed is dick but my boyfriend thinks it’s cool to see… https://t.co/S9b4grBSRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is insanely unpredictable. Love others and put God first at ALL TIMES.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys my dogs were about to attack eachother because my girl wow wow squashed my boy one ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews @9NEWS @wdmlg I couldn’t find the video from the other angle like I did on Facebook. But this is so… https://t.co/ltVOseHZrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W7VOA (Reuters) - Shares of @BookingHoldings Inc fell more than 10 percent in early trading last Thursday, after t… https://t.co/OhSnkLvqHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PsychologyBravo @joegorga is smart enough not to get into that kinda " situation" so @Teresa_Giudice can suck a di… https://t.co/MQvC2zKvTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump No he didn't. Just like most Trump supporters you twist what you hear. Americans aren'… https://t.co/KrKUQ5Ov72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting to meet people like Mary Wilcox inspires me so much and makes me appreciate what I get to do every day! Mar… https://t.co/tXF32ch2AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Madelyn  I was born in a good way  My age is not really bad  I like to give you guys some good news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Aldean Memphis is so adorable!!  Excited that a new album is in the works!  🎼🎸🎧🎸🎤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson I’m there with you.  I’ve been sick since Tuesday and have no voice now.  I hope you feel better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPAIN Congratulations on winning #TheMaskedSinger - I was very surprised at the big reveal. You have an amazing gi… https://t.co/VXXk8ALRkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Anything coming from Breitbart or you for that matter I would find greatly suspect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only I had been as smart as the car behind me that left after 15 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolineneva Those were my moms exact words to me when I told her I wanted to go on BC lmao. Then she pulled out the Bible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have now reached 20 followers. Thanks everyone who wants to read the zaniness I post :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EntheosShines Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE… https://t.co/PudMC36CA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[life hack: if you want to curl your hair but don’t have a lot of time; put your hair in a ponytail, curl the ponyta… https://t.co/RpCEPwLFS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio As much as Tennessee fans love Rick Barnes and them Boyz. #GoVols]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HirachetaNos @brado04 Yeah, for work I completely understand that but if you’re dressing up then follow the ruuuuules. ☝🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't sleep ... I didn't want a crappy yesterday to ruin an awesome today ✌  Thanks again for all the kindness an… https://t.co/0i8t6SuIou]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re high as fuck watching planet earth 2 and Sean goes: yo this island is fucking sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was in church at my nephews baptism...it took a lot of self control to not run through the church]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icelandic_rkwon @kodakfatuglyass @kari_mcewen I gotcha if you need it. I’m not blocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to raise $10,000 for #wigsforcancer  Via a donation of a gown originally worn by #raquelwelch  Courtesy of… https://t.co/hZe52iIyeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommyofCharles3 I’m tryna see. Lol. I’ll have to come tomorrow night but it’ll be too dark for me to bring Jonathan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LINDAMA17521827 Don’t let things like this get you down it’s the other person that have problems 😉👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been watching Its Always Sunny bloopers for like 50+ min now and I guess this is what my life is lately cause idk what else to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes my IUD may have been free but now i will be spending 2.5 million dollars a year on tampons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanadams @BBCRadio2 That is wonderful news. I would tune in but can’t from the USA #shinealight]]></document><document><![CDATA[101 days and I’ll be a collage graduate with my AAS! I honestly am so proud of myself, I’ve came a long way!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The atmosphere of expectancy is the breeding ground for your miracle.#PastorRodParsley]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know what to do if your toddler begins choking? I do. The simple knowledge of how to react saved my sons’ li… https://t.co/dDaA9HNTJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every struggle you had in your life shaped you into the person you are today. Be thankful for the hard times they can only make you stronger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BazersCarol @NightlyPolitics But he’s Rupert’s spokes model (head liar).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliemozer @Hobie_Baden I can say, I have 100% gone along with it and it definitely helps😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And let the peace of God rule in your hearts, to which also you were called in one body; and be t…… https://t.co/J5rRZKhgcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett Who? Never heard of Smollett until all this publicity started. #notsmart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myserenity69 @AnnCoulter We democrats need to stop eating OUR own.  We are allowing one attack after another on vi… https://t.co/b4CLGmIvsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEShop casually waiting for the shipment tracking number of my last order, Ordered an USO penitentiary shirt and… https://t.co/FauFfJkhd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPS @USPSHelp I would like to call you out on your BS once again that my delivery location was open until 11PM, y… https://t.co/KzLkUvlPr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook always has the best videos!!! 👏🏼😂 “I just wanted to tell you I’m home” https://t.co/SjopTW1ZdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulinasplace @ABC Our history is far beyond slavery. And is so systematic that it is almost the most disgusting t… https://t.co/2vVWQZYpOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holly_evamarie This is the most Holly thing to ever happen.   P.S. Gazunteight]]></document></documents></author>