<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I told my Grandma the only thing I want for my birthday this year is to meet @RobertDowneyJr  because I bet he give… https://t.co/YUFo8eoyYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorCarlDay No. It’s just easy to figure out in some cases. So say somebody follows you but never watches your s… https://t.co/5ii3jg4H5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, he shall come up and fly as the eagle, and spread his wings over Bozrah: and at that day shall the heart of… https://t.co/KELkXNOJx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 new videos up now on my YouTube channel! Reaction to The Shield getting back together 🤗 🤜🏼👊🏼🤛🏼 *LINK ON BIO*… https://t.co/vtGD5Es4At]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElEddiePV If it's the one on king u not getting that till the summer lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Wholeeeeeee Bunch Of Baldheaded Hoe Shit Ot Happening Tomorrow And I Condone To It 🤫🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr4liberty @JulianGroveMD @Surgeon_General @CatoInstitute As a pain patient of 2 decades, I can't imagine a world… https://t.co/XmT3iC1eko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Da Vinci Day Fun! Working in groups to plan, design, construct and test bear traps. #DaVinci19 @LoeweCheryl… https://t.co/Rx5IZHLk5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Solo is (sadly) not a documentary about the movement to get Han released from carbonite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyramsey9404 Well I'd say Minx but otherwise Zoomy wins the prize. 🏆😻👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY @graceslick77 Poor baby! It takes a few days for people to transition their bio clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mizzeyheart13 @iamritu @DrMarthaGulati @DrQuinnCapers4 @fitmslax @pulsecardiac @bes502 @becballa @VietHeartPA… https://t.co/4WDKYHFXh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna be in the presence of miss Stevie Nicks tonight no big deal ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahUko @GDLA @FOXLA You look great girl! The morning shift seems to suit you well! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@only2galaxy @heiltsukvoice No? Oh. Then I guess this journalist at the Star got it wrong: https://t.co/w2ccPGoz4B… https://t.co/4Np2YZnXKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @GovernorLittle for joining us today. The kids loved it! #idedu #earlylearning… https://t.co/M5YEYAYOti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABRLive @GStevens_jockey @KentuckyDerby That race was phenomenal!  I stupidly left Code of Honor off my tickets an… https://t.co/2Fglxt44fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up in a snow globe again.  Shoveled round one. The driveway was white before I finished.  School is cancelled.… https://t.co/aNwKbi9Kmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please shoot me... I’m highly considering going back to school ughhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dispute use of the term "foot soldier of the civil rights mvmt" because the Mvmt is not over and BS ain't marchin… https://t.co/hizYaigMM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdHenry A lot of old people say you use to be a serious journalist. I find that hard to believe with your time at… https://t.co/wDQy5FBTQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump of course he has your endorsement - he's been sucking up to you since day 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever see a photo and just wonder what lengths did this photographer go to in order to get this shot? Amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the therapist tells them they have to get rid of some books.  😬😩 #hoarders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of the time I get “you look 17” but when I take my almost 6 year old nephew somewhere I get “aw your son is so… https://t.co/bC4zMPqbtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have only read 90 pages of #Whenbreathbecomesair - as my chest was heavy and tears filled my eyes.  It was an imm… https://t.co/JX61w43zB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmac708 It would be great to see a script about how each element of the movie-making process is choreographed b… https://t.co/ybbdmL4evl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half sleep gettin it in tho lol this shit ain’t pretty March Madness baby day 5 @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/ckXzFb0bRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debating if I should pay for TSA PreCheck or be cheap and suffer through the security “random” checks...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheila Jackson Lee is trying to make the border a problem about children as if the democrats were not the party of… https://t.co/3a23PK9d2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update I’m DRUNK. &amp; k is putting cold stuff on my feet to cool me down bc I’m hot. Omg. Wow. Blessed. Wow. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flash_Katie237 @p_machor @kara_querl @EverAshleigh @Emmanuelle_TLSE @Enherman27 @RobertF39646589 @deezel21… https://t.co/icfYWEpD1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we have any hintaroonies on tomorrow’s vid please!!? @GraysonDolan @EthanDolan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenholden72 Loved the show last night. You guys were all great as usual! Looking forward to seeing you again tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Kiss by Prince on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/KSzYUjLrgE https://t.co/CtURjQ8Q7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved attending Azmeena's #Nikkah ceremony!!! #Bhi2Khan https://t.co/kiXYvy6Bgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heck out "THE HERO CONCEPT" preview by cosplayer Julian Jaye aka Trunks IRL.  https://t.co/etGMLom4ZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeriah Horne has a dozen points and five rebounds in the second half and Tulsa leads East Carolina 71-55 with nine minutes left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Oreo Day!!! 🐶  Our sweet Oreo got to go to the office today to celebrate Her special day 🎉  (what do I do… https://t.co/ZXY2T5xFUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You people on here will say anything for clout I can’t fuck with Oakwood twitter cuz none of y’all have the same en… https://t.co/BlsTB3hVbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickwtyler @SRuhle @MSNBC Ooo maybe most of the hour! Good stuff to talk about!😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine believing you, as a human being with religion, philosophy, music, art, science and an immortal soul, are in… https://t.co/Rav906mDCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told myself I’m not going to any concerts this year and I’m already going to 3 🙄🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can show you, better then I can tell you.  Have an amazing day! @ Coral Springs, Florida https://t.co/7zQ1v7OEIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Amazon! Have you thought about some kind of reusable shipping container that could easily be delivered and pic… https://t.co/NfvY7Tjt7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdknapp3 @RoKhanna @BernieSanders So if I said POC were pushing it before him that means that they did it before h… https://t.co/RJrv93sYhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @terveza We the people support you Donald Trump!🇺🇸Trump 2020!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bachelor dropping a song with my favorite ‘00s boy band is everything I didn’t know I needed.  Well done… https://t.co/eqh4B5F3x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please. Would some lawmaker with  a set of balls bring this bitch to justice?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got another fricking cold and the amount of stuff that comes out of my sinus cavities is insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disn3yw0rld Is it good???? Which products do you have bc I really liked what I saw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving cousin time @sxsw! What a great reunion with @jacobmotz- highlight was definitely introducing him to his sec… https://t.co/n3X8wSGOwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#27forever #letsgoducks #nhlducks @ Anaheim Ducks https://t.co/UL1MhWs7KA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blondehair #balayage #ombre #elixirsalon @ Elixir Gallery Salon https://t.co/btXRciospZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a highly productive and exhausting ideation day with my team, I left wondering: Is decision-making fatigue a thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can TELL that this writer is asian bc he (even in a The Onion-esque parody article) actually distinguishes the… https://t.co/IrW4JvCDoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[God didn’t create you to be weak. He created you to be Victorious no matter what situation you’re in. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Licensed Practical Nurse I - Nights - https://t.co/xCQHA95INi #Nursing #Waldron, AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make ye him drunken: for he magnified himself against the LORD: Moab also shall wallow in his vomit, and he also sh… https://t.co/xXBzvyFJ5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahmduckett @sunrisemvmt My favorite book to recommend in these times !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilpump You had better learn how to spell it before you go there. It's HARVARD. Don't you have auto-correct on you… https://t.co/F8KAtQVGA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@provdcrumblover @Aliciastarr001 Total disgrace. He made a huge mistake in marrying her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[His eyes are blue, just like the ocean His heart is a river free Now and then he gets the notion And he finds his w… https://t.co/9OYmqW1gbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don't think it's OK that @sxsw offered a credential for a rate of over $600. They said doing this will incr… https://t.co/UX2mkFhRMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[guys in college are confusing. guys in general are confusing. i’m not here for any of it🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump When do we get to call in the military to remove him from office?  And the spineless Repubs with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinsean @mathematize4all @CAMathCouncil Awesome! See you at #NCTMSD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump or maybe even some beautiful 8 layer chocolate cake! https://t.co/qKaB2zJKJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going out makes me feel incredibly insecure. I'm just going to stick to concerts with the love of my life who makes… https://t.co/ctwkNwcK8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Young Sibling Family Loses Both Parents. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/QvmMRZwaUR via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Little Creek Casino Resort https://t.co/DThzsMe58h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoJASMlNE Thank you again 😂 people picking sides like no y’all both fucked up and both of y’all ain’t shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glover_ceo Don't be discouraged, three words for you. Amy. Berman. Jackson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words don’t have to explain this image 🙏🏽 1 Corn 10 “I appeal to you, brothers and sisters, in the name of our Lord… https://t.co/6mR7giDQv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verdadwines Love this wine of yours!  It’s so well balanced, elegant and silky!   #verdadwines #PineHawkVineyard #CertifiedBiodynamic]]></document><document><![CDATA[tryna be that cool girl watching ‘thor’ but just all, ‘sorry but this is inaccurate to norse mythology...’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen cheesy chicken Milanese #husbandapproved https://t.co/d2Vinrs13J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanvasPirate @nitrocosm @Rayearth49 @AOutsiders1 @YellowFlashGuy @_Hero_Hei_ @TheQuartering I'll be civil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace School students graduate not only academically prepared to succeed in rigorous academic environments but eage… https://t.co/qIPFZtI5cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thinking of deleting my other nsfw account and just post wherever on this one... what do y’all think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reporter. "Secret Agent Man" Live at the Red Creek 1986 https://t.co/WoUglr0a9s via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayla didn’t even look twice at the tackle. #onlythereforinjuredathletes 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelNorman86 @carrieunderwood She has a great voice. But, I just have to get it off my chest once that she annoy… https://t.co/FgWwaKIKug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Believer037 @enolatonlori @EstVallChorale @PoeticPastries @MMcLaughlinsong @fourcornersfld @julie_dibble @Lead1225… https://t.co/JIbdjkQOCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever wonder what's on the scanner on a Saturday morning? Well, today it was DNR conservation officers (@mndnr) talk… https://t.co/bDr7ctgSD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devoneylooser @asuEnglish @ASUTheCollege @CAWPTeachers @WesternMassWP Right back at ya ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petersagal Maybe not greatest, but watching a bit of Casablanca last night I was struck by how effortlessly good a… https://t.co/P8zq1HfS4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[He drops me off and I get straight in bed, this boy puts my ass to sleep 🤤😂 https://t.co/G8d3JEH3TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I get on twitter and all I see is the whole TL dragging the Kardashians 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortuneMagazine Oh no, don't get me started! 1. Menstruating females, want to be clean, how else can they do this?… https://t.co/esdq1zpDYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[raise your hand if this is the most beautiful thing you’ve ever heard 🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crupi_1 So stupid. So so so stupid that I care about children getting murdered by something that could easily be p… https://t.co/d3n99v8K5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[[NEW] #NBA legends arrive in Charlotte ahead of All-Star Game. #AllStarWeekend #clt @FOX46News https://t.co/5TctYiIwKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCPappy I hope you find him and prosecute him to the full extent of the law. I also hope the Officer injured will recover quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU ARE TELLING ME. @MiniWheats. IS NOT HIGHER? Like NUMBER ONE? I demand a recount. And free wheats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how the @NY1 election magic happens. Tune in tonight at 9 for graphic genius by @msabedi https://t.co/82VxlfDezA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Only A Test by @VaShawnMitchell on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Ddwv7MHao8 https://t.co/uL6odfdf0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sternshow Fred makes the show.  His mostly perfect timing just amazes me!! That and Howard’s parents.  Too funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of that time Kenny Chesney married Renee Zellweger 🤷🤦.  Only, I don't know who this guy is.… https://t.co/e9gFEqvysL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pet birds have a few angry things to say about being woken up an hour early.]]></document></documents></author>