<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Irish_Outcast @Razorsmack1 @pjbowles4 @my3monkees @_IamAnita_D @OMARRSHABAZZ @MarleneKeener @MikeinKansas17… https://t.co/43RykvVUaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 Actionable SEO Tips to Increase Organic Traffic https://t.co/Mab3bI0pwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenDeHoney @BryanWinsAgain @BrianELogan I love Joe, but he should have run last time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some serious star power at #Sketchfest tonight. @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/2L7vWdmjeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve dated someone who’s mother hated me and it’s not worth it. Find a mother who loves you as her own, it’s health… https://t.co/jUozRv1aGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnFi31399406 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Most Trump supporters stay quiet or lie to liberals. Cause you phys… https://t.co/4tzBzYK6lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can @ a lot of you but y’all could never own up to your shit so mejor me quedo callada 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Give it to them #TuckerCarlson!! The left continues grasping at straws, and they always will!! 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are boys (with a few girls sprinkled in) scores from today’s basketball postseason action across the twin stat… https://t.co/nlPSr1MLLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meal Prep Sunday😋🍆🥒🍠🥦🥕🌶 #mealprep #sunday #tucsonpersonaltrainer #topphysiquepersonaltraining #mealprepsunday @ Tuc… https://t.co/r9xDbS9j6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four years is the shortest prison sentence I've ever heard of. Good to know that the justice system can show compas… https://t.co/Pqh262wYCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna “It’s not my fawwwwwlt!  It’s nevah my fawwwlt!”  Hahahahaha💀 💀 💀 https://t.co/uaMXtz6oqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[she bought her a new fish 😭and this nigga jerry asked “does it look like the one she killed?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive through worker at chick fil a almost told me “you’re welcome” instead of “my pleasure” and I FELT the fear https://t.co/6gLCufWczD]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s unfortunate. Jussie Smollett is under arrest, Chicago Police say  https://t.co/TqcZ3U1Q5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY PENDANT HAS BEEN FOUND!!!! Because I was tearing things up, George got out of bed to help me look, and he found… https://t.co/HOhOtN2OeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was saying yesterday i wasnt drinking again till spring break, but here i am enjoying a vodka soda 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahRightmire I love that John doesn’t have a six pack and he’s still hot! He’s a teddy bear... a sweet little teddy bear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctsinclair Will there be an escape room again this year?  Orlando has a 2 hour one now  😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beagle, she protec #shenotattac @ Swepsonville, North Carolina https://t.co/cFQq45Ppso]]></document><document><![CDATA[lauren: someone: *takes lauren’s donut* lauren: https://t.co/V13Guf3TV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nationalpost because he got caught ...   if you're gonna sign up to play the Political Coercion game,  exercise ex… https://t.co/iXWJhghtXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ojalá!! Pero igual NO SABEN MI FELICIDATTTT. MEJOR DÍA EVER woohoo bye https://t.co/9hDTejgJGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globovision Al bobalicon @jaarreaza la desgracias que vive el pueblo venezolano es culpa de la… https://t.co/z2MnzdIVHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am producing this inspirational show that runs next Saturday and Sunday  at Hatbox Theatre in Concord.  Three dif… https://t.co/q2GpHgJZWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuuTakeNotice drains another 3!   @raptors905 58-48 at the half! @ Raptors905 https://t.co/djvHnDfPFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two bands that reminded me so of a boy that I loved painful and poetic are touring together this summer! @bushofficial and #Live]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RElGNSSECTION @Americareform Got the Roman shirt coming in Monday, the bracelets by Thursday and just ordered the Shield shirt today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Sanders crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 01:47:45, pace 08:43 min/mile, est. finish 9:09 am https://t.co/B3MPxhveoy #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaMichelle I have watched the seventies and the 2000s series. still need to watch the eighties and nineties.… https://t.co/XCFrgul1Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually daydreaming about the sandwich I’m gonna make when I go home. My lab could not go by any faster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family is going to be in Atlanta all weekend for Emmah’s cheer comp &amp; I’m sad I can’t go :(((]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything about appointments give me anxiety. Making them, going to them, everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JennBailey @alicia_amoroso @brndncoleman @ScotOrlowski First capture of Jenn in the wild! Excited to see more! I’… https://t.co/eRHLYoPW9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ Today at The Poem Farm, a work of art from Kindergarten Artist Ava in @WymansWonders's class...and a poem I wrot… https://t.co/1fWVsmBFI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday evening. Curled up on this couch paging through a book filled with Jim Brandenburg’s amazing work and a Chop… https://t.co/M5was096CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A si es pero los políticos no quieren pedir la intervención militar extranjera el pueblo no puede solo como sacan a… https://t.co/N2UUsOQC1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @RhondaBur1501 for hosting  the virtual meeting with @hildebranroyals and @bcpshuskies in your room!… https://t.co/wzJmhiLEdb]]></document><document><![CDATA['The Benefits of Fast and Slow Yoga' via @MyFitnessPal - https://t.co/cbrlnQqFaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpbtheactor JC has an album and hes in a straight jacket just saying 🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[The well to do people will flee, leaving the government to “print $” and end up like Venezuela. Be aware and BEWARE… https://t.co/G1jsYoq3tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swipe to see the before 😳😳😳 .  Itip Extensions and color transformation.  Hair by @YahairaKolb Wigs @yahairakolb… https://t.co/UBDi5t154u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see Cristian EVERYDAY, but my ass misses him like crazy when he isnt around 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_blues25 @TrumpStudents Sad- to see the female population reduced to sniveling, rude, physical, vulgar humans.… https://t.co/Y5WqFoht2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPLC Action Fund statement on divisive Georgia bill that would protect Confederate monuments - Southern Poverty Law… https://t.co/WdCLuMCk4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay You are the future Loki Rose!! You will accomplish great things!!… https://t.co/hFKQMgqN1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Socialism: they are wealthy, you are not. Do you understand how this works? Trump: inherited the ec… https://t.co/pd1khFmxAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body on Brighton Rock - a fun spook flick at #sxsw @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/EOjx7FtG9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody still have a @BronyCon 2017 pin?! If you do, can I buy it off of you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pugchat a3 - I'm a man of routine in the morn (6 am walk followed by food then 10 am dog park to see my friends).… https://t.co/5hn4BD9Qvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today this woman told me Michael and I wouldn’t make it because we were doing long distance and “that never works out”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out! Enter for your chance to win the 'NYC Launch' Sweepstakes.  Prize includes roundtrip tickets to NYC,… https://t.co/oGd5naOPqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaLL_RoZaY The bar I’m at has a live bad playing #forgetyou and I’m thinking of you and @Crys25stal at zodiac. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I’ve read @MichaelCohen212 pre-statement before hearing is already overwhelming for me about crooked @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaKKatz @KamalaHarris @courtni_pugh Great news &amp; perfect choice! congrats @courtni_pugh !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booking hotel rooms... looking at apartments... working...???? it’s almost like I’m...... *gulps*..... an adult....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my kids never end up going through half the shit I went through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the thing that sucks about missing deja is hearing all my friends talk about how much fun they had while I was stuck in cold ass Michigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Witness #4, a police officer with EPPD is called to the stand.   She was the last officer to arrive at the… https://t.co/HLZTrfJU7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to stop by the @PotawatomiZoo while it’s closed for the season?  You can on Saturday! It’s their last Winter D… https://t.co/9r2MiY25Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future of Oakland’s Pacific Boychoir Academy is in jeopardy after  what they thought was a generous donation of… https://t.co/J4B950S6eL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lap dog Scout. Happy husky. @ Second Guess Farm, Rescue, and Brewery https://t.co/VXfMDVI9ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski I'll be crying, watching Top Chef, and chasing the day away with a lovely Bordeaux. JK, I won't be crying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dazzlecarol @cas_33 @allyemmerson @lucretialive @lusciousvixen @jaguarlogdrum @Jetemetet @feromoon Morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[So calm y’all lil weak “Why you so mean? Why you gotta be like that?” asses up, thank you. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m laying in bed chilling and I just thought of the time when I was like 9 years old when I stayed with my grandma… https://t.co/7ioRgfEHOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never having watched #CriticalRole post your favorite GIF and I will try and figure out what is going on.… https://t.co/M8zszvL7s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SweetN0Vember If it is a hoax, I just don’t understand what he could have gained from it...this makes no sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billymflynn @YouTube @extratv Oh No Chad, your leaving😭 Oh that is it. I will definitely quit watching now. Your t… https://t.co/d7suvlaJTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hauntedmuseum @Zak_Bagans we have some feedback for you on your awesome museum but don’t want to give away details… https://t.co/3BtqE5dj6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The desert is a natural extension of the inner silence of the body.  Jean Baudrillard  ____________________________… https://t.co/QyZFKGY4de]]></document><document><![CDATA[#4thofJuly  Love this idea.  Let's celebrate America! https://t.co/EUeqqIs6Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[N O B Y S T A N D E R S  #airmax97 #nikeshoes #ootd #nikela #losangeles #astroworldmerch #hypebae #teddycoat… https://t.co/veS2y8glTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDPhillips Will do my research. Thanks again for your attention. Rock on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueinmo @realitychuck Maybe I do have what you had.  A full breathing treatment in the ER did noting to stop the… https://t.co/QdKQ44POrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad on insta-  Texts me that my picture is cute but does not double tap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resting Hospital Face In AZ St Joseph's hospital. @ St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center https://t.co/7ZiHUCXzoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Attitude like what you looking at, my face look like I don’t wanna chat”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocketgirl3914 @dariusrucker hopefully tomorrow we will get more answers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an amazing talent of being absolutely invisible to most people.  #sundaysong https://t.co/247ugg0y3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickRandall @catizme @ReneeFiredup @UROCKlive1 MAGA trumpubllicans are a cult. I block instantly.. there's no r… https://t.co/s1FBYSvAhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[😳😳. No .@BernieSanders - that’s the Democrats. That’s you.  You know “Identity Politics”.  Remember when you hate t… https://t.co/YDZfoROgPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Tinsman I have a girlfriend who would give her first born for a flip razor! WTH?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTaylorSkinner He had some valid points, he deserves to know if she is real or doing it to just have a man on her… https://t.co/KAs7uVmdTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOLA here we come ・・・ 📧vivianVguerra@gmail.com  📱305.609.2301  💻https://t.co/kpfuo8oP3X ・・・ #kwfr2019… https://t.co/TB12zEjwOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I laughed too hard at this. 😂 but really, don’t disrespect Led Zeppelin like this ☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyHockey @sevenohthree Now now.... I have nothing but respect for Czech guys https://t.co/N6t9EQmk2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove from Champaign to Chicago today. Burning question: Why do semi trucks drive in winds like this?? It was cra… https://t.co/II5QUvcvqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedilleyshow pandering loser horizontal Harris . We see you for what you really are!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! This would be amazing! We vote Yaaaas @SouthwestAir ! #gayvegasguide #gayislandguide]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gonna be a good day 😎 Rock it out there, kids!   #jamiemazerealestategroup #realtorlife #realestate… https://t.co/bZAFLZGPbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me to the part of Florida where the scammers and the Zoe’s at period 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date Night AND Study Break combined‼️😍 #collegestation  #grantnkelsey #lovemyfamily @ College Station, Texas https://t.co/UGQZdxTyoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My post yesterday about my little sis got me a little nostalgic for MUCH simpler times in that relationship. So… https://t.co/QijZOFXLLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Wells Fargo Cedar Point in West Des Moines, IA https://t.co/1Y6AXpV444]]></document><document><![CDATA[What reality is this lowlife living in? Wonder why he holds these opinions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a degree and I can date a man without one 🤷🏽‍♀️ long as he got a decent job the degree don’t matter to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes Friday night distractions come in the form of impromptu music tribe shenanigans around dinner...just what… https://t.co/x8vEWUF5zF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I was in pijamas by 8:30pm and asleep by 9pm. It’s been a long winter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CulturedRuffian Let's find out where to get this!!!🤗🤗🤗☕🍩 https://t.co/tZT9XPmajC]]></document></documents></author>