<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@DougJones do you agree with your fellow Democrats that mothers should have the option of killing the infant once… https://t.co/ib0Sb4jJbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@april492018 @SaraCarterDC omar and tlaib should not be allowed to hold office in our country! They took the oath o… https://t.co/nmexPpSr29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews Pretty girl with a good job and bright future. Threw it all away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shane temporarily turned into a bog dog for the afternoon https://t.co/DKSZfKLP9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y es que no sabes mentir, no sabes engañar, se te nota en la carita si no dices la verdad @danielrangell8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonWTennis Hope it's been a happy and great birthday for you, Allison ! Thank you and all the tennis ladies and… https://t.co/bBsrWnsNEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllOutShow @SIRIUSXM @rude_jude @RickRockbeats @Shade45 https://t.co/sUBCsDXy4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joyeux jour de la famille Ottawa! Joignez-vous à moi et plusieurs autres entre 11h-14h à hôtel de ville patiner sur… https://t.co/mTKcKpxD3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoloTv84 yo peep this out from the Jubilee blind date thingy https://t.co/qyDtlLalte]]></document><document><![CDATA[10th Street &amp; Then Some #TomJoycePix #downtownlincolnton  #lincolnnebraska  #downtownsnow https://t.co/GBRRirO1xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellsFargo opens 1000s of fraudulant accounts &amp; makes a "best big banks" list? Would love to know how much… https://t.co/qYlG80NA8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marissanadler setting a deep, pensive vibe tonight @zebulonla - 3/1/19 - 🖤💜💙 - sacredbones #marissanadler #zebulon… https://t.co/3TEOQQ0ras]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lazulioness @seapipe @DonaldJTrumpJr Except for this one last time.https://t.co/h6Iiy4uTWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh what a surprise was it a foursome with that young gentleman who was compensated $400,000 taxpayers money, come o… https://t.co/c682tFpxgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1NASAAN @Roxi_Didi Nasaan _u probably don't know me but I'm the God Son of your father proof DeShaun Holton I'm Em… https://t.co/UrbhG9MAsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 Nadie , careta sola@por el hambre la miseria y las mentiras ! Solo dale@tiempo !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesoccerdon @Enquirer @fccincinnati @MLS @FS1 It’s taken decades for the Enquirer to even recognize the sport.  B… https://t.co/cv2q4n2q9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaponRoss Which is right? Pledging allegiance to a foreign country or condemning a foreign country. She pledges al… https://t.co/4YfUjvKpFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Fidelity Investments? We're hiring in #Westlake, TX! Click the link in our bio for details on this… https://t.co/gP2BTgGltn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien Well they told me I was black I even got a black membership card in the mail https://t.co/RZP3z9hIaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Does your dog listen to you ......Unless... Or ...But not when there is a ....Learn how to become the… https://t.co/TI4swNVNbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orin was born in November. Yall be safe out there around this time 😂😂😂 #valentinesday2018 #KingMDot #FonzieBePraised https://t.co/NVkUJdOwkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIP To actress Katherine Helmond better known as "Mona" from "Who's the boss" who died today at the age of 89 https://t.co/0BWnVGFgAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Tickets on sale for third annual Clusterfest - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/lkIMuYifkZ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left is for justice like it’s for blacks, women and gays—as long as they think the way they do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited that announce that this picture I donated to the Community Support Centre Haldimand  Norfolk called “Ol… https://t.co/8YR8IewAGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you rot in Jail for the Rest of your Life McCabe!   President slams Andrew McCabe's account as 'so many lies… https://t.co/AmkZKUUqyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattZygaj We have a constant struggle with defensemen. Tahts a fact. Dahlin is our future star number one defensem… https://t.co/nznedPSlrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Bible Verses  He Spoke in Parables https://t.co/HAgz05lIjQ #arcamax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, Ryan. Are you mad at a college kid for making basketballs go through hoops? https://t.co/eKJVM7joy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Also like I’m having an unsalvageably bad anxiety night so that may be part of it idk idc)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp @Secupp , From the beginning of this, the left absolutely grilled Trump supporters as being responsible for… https://t.co/wgc2p1SIYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[$40 for 10gb or $56 for unlimited talk/data for 30 days #MVPSummit https://t.co/wbskkaKW4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoAccountThomas He’s definitly old enough to be a part of the band now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @LynnePatton Just another sell-out.... https://t.co/4XB6L351zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsaSmith @6News That’s music to President Trump’s ears. Bernie is the Ross Perot of the Democratic Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all the FFA State Officer “Car Curse” is real. Our team has destroyed, broken, been crashed into this year more t… https://t.co/8YbaNogPAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobo103nyc @RoyHarter @Flutesy @EastSideDave @TheESDS Bopes you forgot @jjimblackman you know he needs attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Wouldn't be worth it. I'd have to spend all the money on therapy. And new underwear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaRaeCOS3917 @MayraGmoreno25 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/v1yQN0Dwm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible run for Billy Begley and his team. 13-3 since the new year, capped off with a state championship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling my clothes! All my #tall people and size 11-13s come holla! #depop @depop #taylormoon #taylormoonpies… https://t.co/dHuHizTlIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans I am, I'm calling you guys out that your show is fake, prove me wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avs and Jets each have 3 guys in the Penalty box. Game is getting pretty chippy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenKelsey___ @colton I actually did. Had to leave with 15 minutes left in the show 🤦🏽‍♂️ lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wish incarceration on anyone but gotta admit if Wifisfuneral got arrested it’d be kinda funny cause we’d scream “Free WiFi”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal Some truly sickening shit here, just the whole image is a catastrophe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this Leaving Neverland documentary got me fucked up. I used to be such an MJ stan but he is fully cancelled not… https://t.co/DbuY8mIjoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Duwamish call Beacon Hill "Greenish-Yellow Spine" (Lushootseed: qWátSéécH, pronounced QWAH-tseech) due to decid… https://t.co/HvuBvUDzd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shit you not i just witnessed an elderly couple race eachother in they're electric wheelchairs across the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #EarnedNotGiven on @tyltsports. Hiring should be merit based! https://t.co/laBDhGF18V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blackhole #astrophysics goodness courtesy @PBSDS https://t.co/AiwtnJagEo via @thephysicsgirl happy… https://t.co/CVoYtBkf2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *plays Mr. Highway by ADTR almost perfectly on drums for my dad* My dad: “Play me something I would know.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennisferg4isu @franfraschilla Using the Wooden standard, UCLA is not the program it once was. Record since our la… https://t.co/pBCXglumte]]></document><document><![CDATA[L̵̢̲̬͚͕̖͆̑̊̂͐̓̚͜ͅȨ̸̥̫̩̗͕͓̤̀͑̀̆͛̔͗T̷̗̀͂̈̐̄͝ͅ’̴̟̘͉̰̌̑́̍͝S̴͎͍̬̰̻̜̆̆͒̀ ̴̪̙̥̥̥̦͐͒̽͛̉̇G̶̲̼̻͍̮̬̺̫̈́Ë̸̖̤̬̪͙̪̊͌͛́͌̀̀͘… https://t.co/jFYKFUDn73]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a betting account on bovada, &amp; Lucas made me bet for like 10 games almost I only hit 1 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just getting off. Time to make that journey. #GoodMorningWorld #FloridaSerengeti @ Weston, Florida https://t.co/BVjHWw9d5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnythegiant I sure hope so because this tweet gives me that chicken skin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUTIN'S PLAN : To weaken us, cause divisions, create chaos and generally screw-up our democracy. His plan? Get Donald Trump elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fauxHoiberg How about those of us were at the game?  Are we allowed to tweet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prairiehauler @FabionPicheco @edgar224u All I'm hearing is your rate better be large to be able to be profitable w… https://t.co/8awHX5YF67]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TonyStewart shows up at Milton, FL's #SouthernRaceway. He seems to be struggling a bit, at the moment, but this is… https://t.co/T3yMiWt6Kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[all the rappers used to fw jhonnie blaze tough.. but shorty couldn’t keep her mouth closed. sad case, drake would’ve blessed her game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniforTheUnion @JerryPDias @boborrunifor @Lanampayne @NaureenRizvi1 @joiewarnock @ScottDUnifor @THDM02 I think it’… https://t.co/kcgLobJOoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Just another tweet from you and others like @realDonaldTrump to appease the public. Nothing gets done… https://t.co/yxdeHXvI5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fly_clinton the country is in civil war again because of the same racist and hatred that led to the civil. Sadly,… https://t.co/IZAjXTd1fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brumwell_r45 @CoachTJSuper Stop trying to take credit for what you know was Taliek’s doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only reaction to the Bundy tapes is astonishment that anybody ever got caught committing crimes before like 1984.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjStephens31 congrats to you! good to get recognized for all your hard work and great results on and off the court!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calli Carver on Murray’s fourth-consecutive First Region title. https://t.co/DkyjNYSu5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Musuchi_F1 @chunter16 @LucasdiGrassi Haha “whatabautism” the best Russians got? Please! Russia is the cancer of th… https://t.co/cQhHROQk7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can go ahead and pump allllllll the breaks on this. The man hit below .250 last year. He’s lucky $300M was on t… https://t.co/CpR7WyRw8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillRatner Happy Birthday Mr.Ratner. Thank you for all the wonderful years of my childhood as my favorite action f… https://t.co/69Fqa6kFfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catdame And you just have Trump and Russia hashtagged in your profile. Just curious if you knew any good Russian conspiracies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beltrandelrio buen día Pascal escuchandote en la fila de la autopista Saltillo_Monterrey no hay pasó saludos https://t.co/ey179kwOPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome job Danette👍 Danette was able to refer a customer to the Rental department for a duhumidifier from the Gard… https://t.co/w84c4SBW2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Plutarian_Vibes @blackqueenofTU @her Nooooo I just pointed out the blooper 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! Not the best, but I love this hobby so much. Buen dia #ghostin #arianagrandefans #thankyounextalbulm… https://t.co/4b3eWx98Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tharidgeman Hope you and yours are all doing well. Sending positive thoughts your way. xo #FingersCrossed #Tornados]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funtimeseddie Not that I know of. Hey it doesn’t bother me what so ever I just always wonder if I did something wr… https://t.co/NgEWvzxQOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘The pope ignored them’: Alleged abuse of deaf children on two continents points to Vatican failings https://t.co/PqUmYTa46L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VonniMediaMogul @Brockaganda @IdleOats @thisisendlesss @g_mojgan @AOC She "filtered" it through co-sponsors, in Co… https://t.co/SSXhOXG8JE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kapanen gods glove high on 9/10 breakaways and scores almost all of them #sniper #LeafsNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmeans80 @dstaples I hear you. But not even close to NHL speed. And not even close to NHL level competition, whic… https://t.co/8XkmrUTsZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me informan que Estados Unidos deportó 400 haitianos hacia la RD, sin ser estos ciudadano o residente dominicano me… https://t.co/xRPAWoBu4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop @LuvMultimedia We have to !! 🎼🎶🎶 "We've to get out of this place, if it's the last thing we ever do.… https://t.co/LQdaMsapWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few weeks back; Trump said he was going to pull all our Troops out of Syria.  Two of his Generals quit - - dubbing… https://t.co/skqxaI64Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @DemWrite If trump didn’t have anything to hide he wouldn’t have anything to say!! His start as pr… https://t.co/vaKpSk22l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia Tech coach Josh Pastner on #UVA: "They're good. Good enough to win the national championship. And maybe the… https://t.co/tIHWj6eoA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jahimes says J.R. Romano is using the actions of one deranged individual to demonize all immigrants #ctpolitics… https://t.co/rxI6tf3Ht3]]></document><document><![CDATA[3521 Wilshire Blvd 3521 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90010 https://t.co/GjVcqXRfTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgebarr Yes!  I found my 3rd great grandmother was from the Isle of Man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Del Mar: light rain, 45°F 93% humidity, wind 4mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no. Have I somehow made being “down to earth” a negative and undesirable quality??? I mean, I’m so down to earth… https://t.co/DaRRnMtxTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi más sentido pésame  Fuerza mi hermano Es duro Más ya tienes un ángel que te cuida y siempre estará a tu lado Ben… https://t.co/ZAJUFN4XrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[There has been a @iamcardib @BrunoMars collab for THREE FULL DAYS and none of ya'll told me?!?! 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames @DwyaneWade Seriously tho' - respect your game, both of y'all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJBeekirArtTwit @ansible I hear you. I had to use YAML to build a parser for exported rekordbox media databases us… https://t.co/InFBlXcqS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorealisCanada @ThatsMrNeil The CAJ was never established to be a regulatory body for the media. It has, for the p… https://t.co/1sCMOmBwZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheresaLubowitz @PeteButtigieg I really like him Theresa I wish I could vote for him]]></document></documents></author>