<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MelissaNordWx @wusa9 @hbwx @TenaciousTopper Topper not painting a pretty picture on air]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite guitarist/composer just told me one of my scores looks hard ahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Lo que trata es de esconderse en el nuevo disfraz par a qu e nadie lo señale ni lo reconozca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech Laws across the whole country need changed with more education]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is beyond unbelievable.  DeBlassio should be charged as an accessory to the murder of a police officer . NOW 😰… https://t.co/E3iBo3aUzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Junior cOlivia McCauley received a GOLD medal at ISSMA State Vocal Solo and Ensemble Contest in Indy yesterday!  Sh… https://t.co/gOySqiCLn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @Twitter @TwitterSupport please have someone contact @AronEisenberg so he can be @verified thanks its 2/28/19 already]]></document><document><![CDATA[Performing a new song I wrote called “Claudette Colvin” for an amazing woman of the Civil Rights Movement who deser… https://t.co/koCVnBt4FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Manufacturing Engineering Manager - https://t.co/gVwVVZxDPH #Engineering #Bothell, WA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alright team, we need to get some of the actors out of their contracts, any suggestions?” *15 minutes pass* “What… https://t.co/MEGxQDGQPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @Varneyco @FoxBusiness @realDonaldTrump @PressSec Good for you!! Next time you're in the cargo hol… https://t.co/5aPQKNNonB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revivalist Heathens understand that the Gods are more than Archetypes. Humanity has a way of naming our Gods and gi… https://t.co/m0yNXhSStr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrinKerr @michaelmorley11 I’d submit this is feature of the development of the law via case-by-case adjudication, not a bug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the darkside @AntonioBrown  ☠️⚔️😎👌 #Raidernation @ Chester County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/qN7wWERyjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entourage: Ari "Fuck You The Most!" https://t.co/1TveKzR9xV via @YouTube AKA Me when I’m drunk! #bottletomyself https://t.co/vcY3vskNdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legit just delivered to an old woman who had 10 catbowls outside filled with water and food for the outside cats… https://t.co/uHRqr88u0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger McNamee calling for a national debate going into 2020 on whether it should be legal to do commerce with our p… https://t.co/CwiVt35JUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derek_adesso Let's try this Derek.. Gotta work..😁 https://t.co/ihkuCu8oWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thunder_Up13 Remember last year when y’all lost to an electrician? https://t.co/tNeYhMYaWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatonequeen @trixiemattel @manilaluzon She didn't work with this format 🤷‍♂️ #loveShangela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doritos_Xtreme @keithlaw It’s a cycle that starts with wealth, yes. Also a cycle that one could argue is a continu… https://t.co/cbRQIDCHYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my friend and former co-anchor Sarah Jennings @brandikingwhp! I hope you have a great day!  Miss… https://t.co/DzYmBD8RGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks at (or coming to) the Capitol: @BradTabke is leading a Diaper Drive in honor of a @ShakopeePD employee who pa… https://t.co/Z4RPmCspBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact that I just found out tonight. A Colorado Burrito is a California Burrito but it has chicken in it instead of steak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleCiderRadio @DonaldJTrumpJr You idiots will understand the “truth” when that knife is at your throats. I’ve se… https://t.co/lP3Ab6Q25Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 22nd 2019. A cold -7C morning in Dorval @ Dorval, Quebec https://t.co/EP94eFYHJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Exhibit 32,478 that all trump has ever cared about in any of this is himself and his business interests. #GOPwasduped]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Barrett 82A1 50 BMG Rifle from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $9000! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/pYSIYhp7J9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr Hong Han presenting at the @iBESTResearch seminar series her work on high throughput platforms to investigate ge… https://t.co/Lbks55jNMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaKidGowie @icecube @llcoolj Cube and LL are as good as they come. It will be incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off loud! - Drinking a Wether by @thebruery at @WildSideBrewCo  — https://t.co/EIlB387inC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPHL #Premier Division has some of the most under developed officials officiating games. That I have ever seen. T… https://t.co/S1h3ZNvIus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye fersho ¿en donde puedo conseguir ese Box Set de AC/DC aquí en Monterrey?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worm2126 @GirlGolfs ‘Wonderland’ parents have nothing on the ‘Abducted in Plain Sight’ parents 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluedress1959 Right lol it ridiculous like so many of his contemporaries were better, he knew it and told anyone w… https://t.co/W71t98WRt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colleges are teaching courses on romance. Yes, there will be a quiz, and it may include this question: How long doe… https://t.co/QCmECzL3C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wingmanusn @jgeltzer @MrScottLads @CNNOpinion Nonsense. People don’t go to prison only because you don’t like them… https://t.co/mRTZwZ9wi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@72_leeann @kharypayton Ah just shoot her if it were real but wouldnt be good for a tv story line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunnyrjuneja There wasn’t a page. It was at the bottom of home page. 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spec3806homede2 @DavidLoescher22 @LSchigel @leceeonn @HDKristofer Thanks Brian great leadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteSnoopy2020 @ReneeLibby2 I feel your pain. My birthday is April 20.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention, all: @timbhealey is signing an autograph https://t.co/tqQyS84EIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you know how everyone stay talking about how Sprite hits different from McDonalds??... lemme tell you... that Ha… https://t.co/HZH6MDN1z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Don’t you have a law called ethics law?? Then why the bleep are we Preskett in these media… https://t.co/JeBxh5vyo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill hey sissy schiff "I've learned that the greater a person's sense of guilt, the greater his or her need to cast blame on others. "]]></document><document><![CDATA[REINA DEL 266 ANIVERSARIO DE LA FUNDACIÓN DE LA  HEROICA CD. MIER TAMAULIPAS   Dania Dayana I 👑❤💕 https://t.co/lxIBjN3tQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wH7QFgwJ31 @bladingfortruth @djstames @ACCoolDown @SteamtownStunna  #PrivateWhiteyReportingForDuty #RAW #BuyersRemorse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanguardComic @TKOpresents @cannonhillcomic @RECKLESS_IMBER @AlfieGallagher You're a gent, Dan, no matter what all… https://t.co/Jzjg9t7VGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot for officialtriumph by @EASPHOTO @ New York, New York https://t.co/SCOXHvBa74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bufe00 Don’t even have the number saved.  Savage.  Also, I text you this morning and didn’t make the feed :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_miss_kim @POTUS @Acosta It’s a shame the POTUS has to deal with these idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Exile_not_Expat @waltshaub I guess that’s my personal opinion. When I am sad and depressed and don’t work out then… https://t.co/a6S2JwNTmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @philip_prebble @Corp125Vet @davidSraw1892 @rexcrown777 @ZeeInTheMoment @Luckydawg @MistyMa45875193… https://t.co/Y0SqgYEK4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trae Young. Last 16 gms (since 1/26): 25.5 pts, 9.4 ast, 4.1 reb in 34.5 mins. 43.4% on 7.6 threes.  Next 21 gms (1… https://t.co/POlPnljB2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a good day for the Lindstrom swimmers!  Both swam there way to MRC cuts, in multiple events, and both… https://t.co/Tm1zH7Oprl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Carpenter @THEJordonBrown Aaron, please sign it on a bible #presidential]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 68 of the One Year Audio Bible Experience. God sets laws and punishments for sexual sin. Jesus is arrested by t… https://t.co/0wcMGfORcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[K. So does like everyone else in baseball... that’s what happens after you win the World Series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Schwartz To clarify. I’ve never booed a team off the ice/field/court]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puppy Gets A Prosthesis Hand #funniness #laugh #grin #laughable https://t.co/LEKeinzU07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javiertoo_ @luissacost @Normsdr__ @illumivate Javi you ain’t sending shit 🧢🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOLY FORKING SHIRTBALLS!!!!!  YOU GUYS!!!  WE WON!!!!!!!!  By over $86,000!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  I haven’t had such a happ… https://t.co/0tNenO441E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBeastYT Still asking to eat pizza at my wedding to save some of that munny. How do I convince her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evveriichardson I’m so sorry honey I hope that if your reported it they actually take it down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice chocolatey stout without being heavy 👍 - Drinking a Brigadeiro by @springdalebeer @ The Barley House  — https://t.co/xpqtrQB6Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @12crazysworn You can stop this if you want to  stand up and fight the Democrats Release all Documents… https://t.co/WJW7PB9J0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chic011518368 @TheAmericanVets @CaraMariatea3 @iammikeyp @kailah_casillas if you feel like a moron , I am sorry th… https://t.co/8VoK3H5hWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanPatrick @statesman Teachers need raises, but you also need to fund public education. Texas needs to do its share.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aewallace8 @michelle_ott @Snapchat My guy has @OhioState gear on in the one pic.  Love that! #GoBucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AskMNGov ask the #hibbinghighgraduate to translate my tweet please; or are you only answering #softball questions?… https://t.co/dRgAHYkQAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[These women inspire me! I can’t wait for election #2020 @IlhanMN @AyannaPressley @RashidaTlaib @AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking my day with a seven hour @delta delay and a resulting missed funeral couldn’t get worse - then the guy who… https://t.co/GWoKIQWr0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[A U Call It Thursday:   - Your favorite cereal?  - Why the combine should be scrapped - U know you’re in Arizona wh… https://t.co/KTh80PEYTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz Nice trailer for the new movie, Apollo 11:   https://t.co/EDNYlHnHLi  Our #book chapter on the Apollo… https://t.co/dKud28E7VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay whoever is making big drama about me and someone needs to stop saying we ducked like bitch stfu 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic Games has announced the first details of the Fortnite World Cup featuring $100 Million in prize money, includi… https://t.co/F2jcDZVsgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand your G-Dless idolatry, is not going to make anything better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets #SceneStealer is our #SweatShopSusie! https://t.co/8sYcgQtRIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the fourth, it’s anyone’s game. Keenan holds a 50-49 edge after a @anneleroy30 hoop/foul makes it a one-po… https://t.co/Gggk0unZGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[these are my people, these are my friends•  @gabriella7613 @jcverhague @Hockeytim08 https://t.co/ohObnn2O8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @uhbroncofan @Eddieonfox @raider_rob24 I'm on the case...in search of Randy as I will be delivering in N… https://t.co/YzjIJaoEKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADelgadoT51 @OEA_oficial @Telemundo51 @FernandoG_T51 B I E N   H E C H O !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN You have tweeted that the reason the U.S. is loyal to #Israel is because of a proIsrael PAC buying favor i… https://t.co/YBWB9oRmEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LemonnLimee Lol, I barely understood any of these words or acronyms https://t.co/PyBEMqwOwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyyLe We need to go ahead and close the transfer portal then @NCAA shut it down boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtlalonde @ut_pez @doobshmoob But if any one wants to lose in NHL on PS4 I got you]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny really, here’s @AOC sharing her utterly valueless opinion on a subject that she could not possibly be qu… https://t.co/hCOY1SxSpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[At halftime in Edwardsville, Alton leads West 27-25 in a tight contest. @DonovanClay11 leads all scorers with 14 pt… https://t.co/yyayYXdSVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to 33” in the last six days, it was an epic week of surfing the forest of Blue Sky Basin. #Vail, #Colorado.… https://t.co/ihmYCB1Xnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marriott: the last six hotels I've stayed in have had flat sheets that don't extend to the foot of the bed and bec… https://t.co/LRX76gElkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliDeplorable @kaymarierob @JoinTravisAllen @GOP @POTUS Rooting for a revived California GOP! U can do it again, Reagan country!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Sheahen @jus10castelli Go get 'em, Brian. Excited to see what comes next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now @DeerLakesAth is in the PIAA playoffs thanks to North Catholic’s win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHDavisNewYork @davidhogg111 @MomsDemand @Everytown @shannonrwatts Soon we’ll have to start a dining Zupcode to keep them straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out now on all digital platforms!!!  Spotify iTunes iheartradio tidal  #VastAire. #scienceninjateam records #HipHop… https://t.co/G8SdILs5X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews .@LastWeekTonight but what about Russell Crowe's 'costumes' in Alaska?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein They Republican Lynch Rope is Fraying! Perhaps they may one day join the rest of the human race and A… https://t.co/mrHAzWBcPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took this walking Kona and trying not to use a flash to wake the neighbors. Came out like a mosaic Owl pic.… https://t.co/y4v725PEI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hehe winner winner. I’m no fan of her but I do find her attractive 😍 .  #maga 🇺🇸🦅🇺🇸🦅🇺🇸 @ Prince's Bay, Staten Island https://t.co/mAUN188iGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Heinz Field was a domed stadium so that AMA Supercross  could possibly come here. I would love to see that in person one day.]]></document></documents></author>