<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Listen to Don't Let Me Down (3LAU Remix) by 3LAU #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/5ekrrB4G79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_G33 I’m not sure I agree with that. Your going to be great in the NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s a true #tragedy that Revolver is such an underrated Beatles album by anyone other than Boomers]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hope Street taught me how to grow and provides an environment for that to happen. I got my life back here and in t… https://t.co/vvBKQVq77w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I choked on gum earlier, and haven’t been able to breathe correctly or stop coughing since. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr  So how many coincidences do you think a jury will believe Little boy? https://t.co/iS0SuIR2SZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lex_gonzales188 Right!!! I have always cooked it in the meatloaf but I can’t put anything on top now because Trevor eat it with gravy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWBDimash #WorldsBest  @WorldsBestCBS   CBS , when can we see the whole performance ...Very disappointed with edit… https://t.co/5sHeRxzETG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally think I saw my future husband today and I have no idea who he is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird He already has they are waiting for the next phase God help us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers can do this ALL DAY LONG! We have been fighting our entire lives!! We are here &amp; we stay WE ARE FAMILY!… https://t.co/ntdgRRdaUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_defender @realDonaldTrump You actually put in your bio “retweeted by Trump”? That’s just pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I see an image in a comic book or a graphic novel that’s so interesting I can’t help but wonder what must… https://t.co/wN2qzTGBdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter If men stopped raping this conversation would be happening. Why don’t you focus on getting your half to do better Kurt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow When you tweet send it to her @SenFeinstein Tell her we haven't forgot. Do people really believe a… https://t.co/CnnqPWvvCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaisedOnGH He should come back n hire a big name for her Mom @gyver_23 #Eileen Davidson #susanlucci #kimdelaney.… https://t.co/9Pn5BEqDVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookboost #kindlebooks #circleofbooks #bookreviews  A nice warm week expected. Going somewhere? Here'… https://t.co/QnuU5zLAzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My newest listing coming to the market in April!!! #finalefarm #newhopepa #adayinthelifeofcarynblack #sothebys… https://t.co/LDavC1ZHUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm excited to share the BURST brush with you - the best and last toothbrush you will ever need #BURSTAmbassador… https://t.co/GSu6o9nPMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @NoHookerNoPeace Not a real one...My guess is he will have one made with his name on it...Like The P… https://t.co/4NFi3ghWvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beatleswift @MyNameIsAlex107 @LuF1602 @TheAcademy @KaceyMusgraves https://t.co/Y7AiTOOsKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Hannah B. Meeting Colton’s family already!! That’s suppose to be saved for the final 2 women!! Wtf is this! 😱 #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m chosen, I’m covered in gold✨ @trvisXX #ASTROWORLDTour https://t.co/J6fJCTiSx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump What part of illegal do you not understand? All they have to do is come in the legal way...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to self - don’t angrily put away dishes. Another note to self - order more plates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrMarkRyan @AtownDioceseEDU @notredamegp @Becahi_Hawks Thank you, Father Searles! We appreciate your good wishes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaKacmar @machinegunkelly @comethazine117 @trippieredd @LilSkies @JuiceWorlddd @YBNNahmir @Lilpeep @lilmosey… https://t.co/MFOTte1UGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Women's Caucus Feb 25 meeting, Rep. Teresa Tanzi (right), sponsor of the Presidential Tax Return Bill, shows off… https://t.co/Bw6fu0DI6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving Weezer’s Teal Album.   I really like their covers, not bad guys!  SN: Rivers Cuomo still makes my heart skip… https://t.co/0RC7lHIrER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cookiewallace77 @kimisanauthor37 Yes it does. Love is beautiful and to come full circle... #itswhatmakesmefearless… https://t.co/I1CDHgXIBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry be happy 🌞 @ Lake Buena Vista, Florida https://t.co/7gCKgKZ0y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I basked in 19th-century leisure, feeling my nerves softening and my attention span stretching back out. I read boo… https://t.co/9o4C0xjrad]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GOPLeader: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is crazy  breakfast for 2 after a Workout Damn! https://t.co/vBLLgIjAl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol #MickysWeHo #fhercho_2121 WATCH: https://t.co/C3UapVLyQM https://t.co/zIEM8klWta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eddie Vedder covering Cat Power's Good Woman... https://t.co/yG1JyufxSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I completely forgot to snap a pic with my awesome freshmen yesterday 🤦🏻‍♀️ but I still wanted to make sure it’s kno… https://t.co/paW4eku7vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GDX1776 @davidhogg111 Dude. Go smoke some weed GDX. Oh wait. Big government Republicans don't want that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJAC33 THANK THE GODS! 🙏  Also, I too am hoping for some Brienne/Jaime action before the end 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tutu15346383 He deserves everything he got. He's playing up his health problems, gout, while painful, is not a dis… https://t.co/pyVPrTI3BH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Wanted - @SecretaryAcosta - do you stand behind the DOL Labor Certs?  #releasethevisas #savesmallbusiness… https://t.co/TNAaUt5q8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the Branagh version of Hamlet is awesome ... the “To Be or Not To Be” monologue in front of that mirror… https://t.co/0zCb6z78oD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HempBombs @HempBombs @Kimberl38218406 y’all please thank you 😊 good luck 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50cent Y’all better leave 50 alone, now!!!! Get the mf strap, shine it up, now what time are my office hours??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've always had my taxes before V-Day until the Donald got in office... Uhhhh 🤷🙅🤦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lefty_Les @McAllisterDen The problem with that statement is as the things we see publicly get more and more libera… https://t.co/QPzGJA3gxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenattyreb @jaylexjess I actually cancelled Apple Music because I use it the most. You do you boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Officer_Stabler Century Schoolbook is a serif font as well and not accessible to those with visual impairments tha… https://t.co/bzcYUQZDLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/fWcDOMLEHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colleague asks if they’re supposed to be in on this meeting. Explains they’re just trying to learn every little thi… https://t.co/8Zw46dVp3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s totally worth how mad my parents are 🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/t4IMXQXbaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this to appreciate the hatchet job that was done on Amy Klobuchar.  https://t.co/n9SmrhEJMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out spring break plans don’t go too well when you and your friends make plans while unknowingly having COMPLE… https://t.co/baJIVfC8jY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dead don’t eat nothing that’s on brunch menu but today might be that day]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Show what you’re grateful for” Lenten Challenge Day 2: My husband. We are like ships passing in the night half the… https://t.co/YDOZMxILuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilvaRecord @g_knapp @TTSAcademy Gimbal? Bob Lazar described how they can navigate in his latest documentary.  Are… https://t.co/1lTAfFG5ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glenn_Macias @Wetnwildlv @PapiElGuapo @wolffremont @EddieG702 @VitalGermaine @garyvee @kylesaidthis @lmorris1908… https://t.co/zi6w5AjAre]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: After one in Fort Wayne, @LourdesWBB trails Indiana Tech 26-11. Jefferson - 8 points on 4-of-6 shooting]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Charlotte, NC #HR job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: TALENT MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT at Compass Group USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARAISXSEAVEYY @jonnybrenns Im trying to find out the date his audition aired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espnmma @espn @ElizeuCapoeira @CurtiousCurtis This is some barbaric crap. How anyone enjoys watching it is just mind-boggling to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least we FINALLY know that Colton jumps the fence next week!!! #TheBachlor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFDSullivan @TheScottCharles @PPDPaulGuercio @PhilaHomicide @AGirlInPhilly @DeniseNakanoTV Omg @PFDSullivan your a… https://t.co/jsOeLeo6NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Bay I'm commin back for ya! #edgepss #upsstrong #peglegtrainer #upspreloadsupervisor #boxesinthetruck https://t.co/8DVKJjZkX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to be a beautiful person  - Don't ever stop giving a fuck - and don't worry about those who have]]></document><document><![CDATA[The never-ending love &amp; support. | 14 Things About Your Family Your Phone Has Made Worse... https://t.co/Igx308j20p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Second Sight by @blackravenbrew @ The Woodlands Pizza — https://t.co/DiQQ0TTfYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/CrJ5JsRtlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetickster73 My fave.  Tried the toffee ones today. They weren’t awesome 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aprilp2a @goodreads Haven’t yet seen Crazy Rich Asians, but read the trilogy. I think maybe the film works. I’ll w… https://t.co/jYOmNJgFSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @realDonaldTrump Peace on Earth.  I have read that wars makes certain manufacturers of war weapons lots a… https://t.co/krcDc5ixHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BritFitzpatrick @BlackGirlsCode @HowardU Ahhhhh Bison power! 🙌🏾 SO glad to have you. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our dog was learning to use his nose to open our trash can and get into it. So we got an automatic one and he learn… https://t.co/HUSujOSUpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact https://t.co/RUPqTge3Ou to book a training/ consultation. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/1d3L7V8kJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend called me today to tell me that I needed to listen to this guy @KolbyCooper_ I just laughed.. I ALREADY KNOW ALL HIS SONGS 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Charlotte, NC? https://t.co/MA9cfyoyl3 #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl in the rags lab is giving me death eyes bc i just printed out 50 pages from a free online textbook heehee… https://t.co/2oH1OIfYDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, Ms. Perkins' name can be seen on the @USDOL building on Constitution Ave, and she is memorialized at the… https://t.co/nK40KVHMBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qk59M7tmtr.ToAPM!  #Apm2019 #MeetingsMatter #ConferenceDirect  #CDMeansBusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a huge challenge in #ChathamNC, as you know. Thank for your focus on this basic economic development need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to rise and shine get in some Planet Fitness! Have a great day everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a contrived hearing that was. 10 hours of coaching by Schiff and his staff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully this hidden Mickey means Disneyland because if luck would have I might meet @bucketlistfam on my vacation… https://t.co/7VzAe8pk1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revdarko @PeterDavid_PAD Disqualified on the grounds that Spidey shouldn't be the straight man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá me contó que hay una chica en la colonia que tiene 2 hijos de uno y dos de otro, trabaja como enfermera. Di… https://t.co/m27nJCxalJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The health benefits alone from lowered emissions are huge. Alternative energy from California. #GrowSolarCalifornia… https://t.co/nZ7adKF1ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karnythia @upulie Completely and utterly true. She’s awash in easily wounded entitlement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @NYGovCuomo @AOC She makes Sarah Palin look like an absolute genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh lord I tweeted about a podcast once and now I keep getting tweeted at with links to other podcasts. How am I eve… https://t.co/mYvgBFetfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jumped out of bed, got dressed and read a BOOK to the 6th grade class at @MissionDAcademy! The school is celebratin… https://t.co/NtwnhOwQtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling blessed to announce I will be continuing my academic and athletic career at Lindsey Wilson College! Thank y… https://t.co/o2W17XvZ4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @billmaher I live in PA a Red State, I love Chef Boyardee and not Chef Wolfgang Puck. I like the fact that I l… https://t.co/EnjvSYQlQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! I’m Lucy Gray, co-founder of @globaledcon and ed tech director at @NSCDS! If I could go anywhere right now, I’d… https://t.co/inLzLxw6vH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhudeboyavenue @madflavor That was the other day. The police have since confirmed it was all lies! The Nigerian ge… https://t.co/BZzm6L4kaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now my heart is broken and everything I thought about love is now shattered into a million pieces and if they can’t… https://t.co/i7rd2SbVL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I am so lame for having watched all of the first decade’s worth of episodes too many times to count and realiz… https://t.co/Wr900CLflG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir @senatemajldr @GOP With all the newly-minted GOP felons, you’d think they’d be more supportive of HR-1… https://t.co/8eJkxzRneM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHookfox10 @DaRealGrizzle @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Obama destroyed this country. Epic failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MMViverito Get you and your 8% polling self outta here #byemelissa #PublicAdvocate #NYCVotes https://t.co/75Fz8FjtOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win a box full of yummy and seasonal Japanese treats from @tokyotreat ! https://t.co/XQ7RsyZ1PC]]></document></documents></author>