<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@StarCityTam If they have videos of him molesting underage girls, that’s gonna be the end of his argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is Rocket Science!☺️ SpaceX's Crew Dragon is safely back on Earth. Now it's the astronauts' turn  #NASA #SpaceX… https://t.co/UIm9wW27yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtesywave @LastStandHats Ordered my hat earlier today https://t.co/RRvVcD05qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueFulton12 @ManInTheHoody I was thinking the housecat figured out how to sous vide some lamb shanks, but your thing's more realistic. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickyBibs11 These are just in lex. Like I said definitely a great district. Consistently a top 5 district but woul… https://t.co/YBbEQeIMxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this group! One more to go tomorrow for the Class 7A ship!! #CHSBulldogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmelOdiesOG @ErikHansLarson Hard to find people to actually discuss issues with on here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sh_irredeemable @KamalaHarris has already been anointed by Media. #KamalaHarris2020 is their pick. The rest are wi… https://t.co/Ow701e27tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you get mad when your favorite athlete makes a mistake on the field?  The severity of your anger is directly pro… https://t.co/21qXnEzLDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back40bham @districtbrews @ Back Forty Beer Company Birmingham https://t.co/Tnd5RXceV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[From today at Washington w/ Literacy Coaches....  🎯 Activities need to be productive to move kids.   🎯 Learning rou… https://t.co/aQ5kaneArm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maj_Jim_Miles Thanks Jim, there was a little bit of fog by that point, but thankfully not too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celtics I’m glad y’all are killing it tonight. Use this as a jumping off point for the rest of the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When did politics become such an all or nothing venture? I always learned that #government was the art of compromis… https://t.co/ElYKyLNaOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ThinpleTrumoskin picking another fight to distract from Paul Manafort trial Russian interference A… https://t.co/WcnXBG1l5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w4acutie is inside on the YACHT net so Myla has come outside with me to try to work a linear satellite 😊🛰 https://t.co/ORSSwdrBbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @apple i just sneezed on my laptop screen whats the best way to clean this off?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spicypantalonez @D3SanJose Bro...you making me blush https://t.co/3yqqpRrvpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have entered the time of year when I get triggered by people still putting EST, PST, etc instead of EDT, PDT, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishaSpeaks71 @THD_Jen @HDTilton Boom!!! That’s what I’m talking about!! Great Job Kevin!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@packbrewfan1 @StarryEyedMelis Well, I mean... Green Book is clearly a movie that INTENDED to have a message. It so… https://t.co/VK80JzeCFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[vro my life is actually pretty good tho no bs i’m literally just taking one little thing and blowing it out of proportion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmalt @latimes The King has a Twitter. I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Pres… https://t.co/7clE6CY41j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Hermosillo, Sonora https://t.co/o2xwCfAd9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s too cold for California. I didn’t sign up for this cold ass climate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/QdWOcrvlxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Directional sound -&gt; Leadership 2.0 Cc @HarvardBiz   See the INVISIBLE  Before Others see the VISIBLE   Hear...  Smell...  Taste...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sissi23__ How do you think I feel being the only one with green/blue eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[So going into tonight’s #TheMaskedSinger finale, the standings are:  @WCYB_Heather 7.5 out of 9.  Ryan 7 out of 9.   Big night tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russ_carpe @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/rjnnOlXSD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Softball: After 2 BB to open B2 @taliahannappel gets next 3 w/ 2Ks. Headed to T3 Edison 3 @OVHSSoftball 0… https://t.co/WreuMwd930]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember, it’s been worse. One congressman killed another &amp; didn’t even get a rebuke from the House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly! Hard to win when you turn the ball over 7 more times than your opponent and shoot 25% from the field.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjCalderon @markhoppus @VansWarpedTour @blink182 @311 @adtr @Thrice @TBSOfficial @ReelBigFish @goldfingermusic totally real]]></document><document><![CDATA[This game is staring to look like it’s between the 2008 Canadian WNT and the 1996 Norway WNT, both as managed by Ev… https://t.co/b8Kv4Vcbzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not just cars that fill up at the Irving. Lovely to see this Amish gentlemen feeding his horses while his fami… https://t.co/AGge3zlATY]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those not familiar with the work I'm talking about, here is a link to my website. https://t.co/64mk0r8cPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[On rainy days, who is your snuggle buddy? - @LaryssaRose21 photos by @HarryLHGFX - #happyhumpday #humpday… https://t.co/NMy7ceOhVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicgame He expected his partner to understand. https://t.co/Lczu4Sbzhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to share this one when I got it a while back. https://t.co/5LJCHugmPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woodshed_1914 @Nykterryandtray @OotyMac @2ForgetUs @PreZnyc621 @BklynGM @RisKOutlawS @knickanator @Chuck1one… https://t.co/4Y6fRDgW4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBI @SecretService How about Prosecuting Liars of your own Administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one should need to be reminded of this. Especially this time of year - but I see this all the time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried #SunsetOverdrive for the first time this week. Not really either terribly impressed or disappointed with it -… https://t.co/bmkFxbVimm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelFiffe Here's me trying to be Joe Mad, back then, not traced. https://t.co/ycJURFlsGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRae48 you can also blame Harris for the lack of Blue Jay world championships.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to back bangers from @PWXwrestling #BattlefieldX this Tag match is solid as hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mhoni Y Sus Cartas Del #Tarot #Sismos #Clima #Deportes #Venezuela #MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni @magdaproducer ✨📺🔮🎬🎥… https://t.co/OTnP8tGZbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Windows on the left and the right, so cool #wintersunrise #sundog @ Strawberry Point, Iowa https://t.co/lV5yRXelbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkepticalPet There are a number of Jews who have come to accept Jesus as their Messiah. Ariel ministries, Messiani… https://t.co/7Xk8vLflRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[For our lives to be fully devoted to God, Pray the Scriptures https://t.co/wDKyEgHaGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Dear Diamond &amp; Silk...we love you and glad you're on this great President's side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkdiamonds @dbongino Kim Jong Un knows he’s happy being in the nuclear club, not in the no WMD Saddam/Gaddafi cl… https://t.co/wEVHgvfWfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias a @CinepolisKLIC en medio de la cena romántica eh podido ver el partido]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump What a pathetically desperate and whiny attempt at a whiny excuse.  No wonder TPUSA… https://t.co/WpPmAFcCAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kangaroos are both cool and CRAZY. Have you ever watched one hop around?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It even in Little Rock 12 hours, and the tornado 🌪 sirens 🚨 going off. 😳😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ando congestionado con una CASI GRIPE y encontré esta MASCARA DESCONGESTIVA en el bolso de mi novia. Me automedico?… https://t.co/8uewtfw4Zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Every word that comes out of any of their mouths are unconditionally supported by the entire party. If yo… https://t.co/VaEFL7FraQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did not want to leave here this morning. That fluffy new @endy duvet might have something to do with it. ❤️… https://t.co/21ZdtEc0Tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFPeeblesChamp Sleep is for the weak.  For real? Let fantasy football hang. Theres really no need to be fully up t… https://t.co/O0sYNcIMvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randy BoBandy and Julian from Trailer Park Boys in the 80s 🤯🤯🤯 https://t.co/D5RfZcGc2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slowdown begins in durham county and continues into wake county in #WakeCounty on I-40 EB between I-540 - Exit 28... https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CageyBee33 @N_Fatale @ericswalwell @AOC Third grade me would be very upset with you.   Dare you to break down the… https://t.co/ruGIqpBdQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been you all night. Dogs kept needing to go outside. So, I said, fuck it; nade coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in St. Martin only for @SpiritAirlines to delay the flight and sat four hours which made me the connecting fl… https://t.co/WQ1WvODurj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Just drive straight to the house, I’ll pick up chicken nuggets” I’m married fuck y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how good of an album #EVOL is. Back in rotation and my vibe feels balanced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about he concentrate on HIS health rather than the dwindling health of the ratings?! I think you can eliminate… https://t.co/oS8H2hSc8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 65 of 365, cleaning out the house of Waterline Square. A new owner cashed its chips in.. came all the way from… https://t.co/AnE1eRcvMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unger2Unger @Jeff_Sharon @UCF_Banneret April 18-22 is when American Conference Men and Women Tennis Championships… https://t.co/K3fNSRJEmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say I love you all the time. But it’s until you can’t say it to someone that you realize how much you really mean it..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder do they hate me because I taught them to fear. This could be the fact that a group of people ride and carr… https://t.co/fhZCD6YgOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DESPISE when people drive with dogs on their lap... that should be a fucking ticket. #Smfh #CatsBetta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre https://t.co/bWm19JHOhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmkillustration I'm just annoyed that lazy white savior narratives are still being made at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pitbull on my birthday... lookin good #PitbullHoroscope https://t.co/f2kJ5aIPO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamecockBasebll @DRMorgan19 Great Day for Gamecock Baseball. Keep it going!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NievesNieves63 @NASCARONFOX Every time he cashes them checks after winning races.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarciaMentor @jcorippo @marvelousmcc @alicekeeler @MrVaudrey @robertkaplinsky @KevinMonsma @mavenofmath Agreed! I… https://t.co/GDUeivzkHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those two things. I don't care who you are . You will be the next @BillGates or Mark Zuckerberg or @EricGilbreath d… https://t.co/ytOvKpVNDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the first hit smack you and you realize you still smoking @ArtByTcustoms @Mardieg24 https://t.co/OPxQhBTxE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assigment: Photographer of the Model #BeachVolleyball Tournament 2019 (Day01) Photographer: @Hsinack Location: Sout… https://t.co/YuZy12YX0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFTimes_sports Every Christmas, there is a massive debate about that song. https://t.co/3M174S8F82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME President Trump’s former political adviser Roger Stone may have violated a federal judge’s gag order by publi… https://t.co/qTCKUSRKwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevMSlaughter really enjoyed hearing your sermon at COR. Thank you for sharing #byourlove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great, then stay there, where they love you. I suspect within a couple weeks, once they know you,… https://t.co/ug2s5tA27z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big money question will be answered soon! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides! I cou… https://t.co/Bn5gzSNwDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think its so funny when a customer asks me where something is i always say idk and their face looks so sad lol or… https://t.co/HVXYBmyLHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsedi205 @MashiRafael La Krullen, te recuerdo que el lugar de residencia d un individuo, no deternida su visión po… https://t.co/4QzpImELhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Métro feet. 25/02/2019 #commute #montreal #goawaywinter @ Berri-UQAM station https://t.co/qS4K07UFwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the first leg of the trip home! It’s cold and snowing outside, but we should be departing on time! Hopeful… https://t.co/UwspDfTK62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dj_gswizzle @TheScottWegener I never said you don't care about poor people. Stop projecting on me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times #rollerskating today @ North London Optimist Community Centre https://t.co/p45rVHXUVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steven_Travale @JustinTrudeau I think Freeland has leadership aspirations.  Notice: I'm not saying there's only on… https://t.co/W5kJ0gVsYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting… https://t.co/cSZ3LsT3MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Lc situation is exactly why you can’t fault any guys from holding out. Here is a guy that went to 3 pro bowls… https://t.co/j88CECFX4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[A model looked at the potential financial and genetic gains from a range of AI and IVF combinations. Ultimately it… https://t.co/wR3IHJWdcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras tanto en algun lugar del planeta tierra. https://t.co/J0h1CJgGwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom 🌞🌞🌞@PCHdotcom_01 if won just send will not gove on line banking info over phone https://t.co/49vi8j3NER]]></document></documents></author>