<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Charles Lee if That’s my Child and Deacon Hermon Thornton lead a prayer outside of Lee High School after parents go… https://t.co/GAh66J8GQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuluBowen1 @snikolao @MattWalshBlog Hey anyone talking to me about Irish, let me tell you my last name is Hogan. O… https://t.co/P2NZgtrJXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first time in my life that I've liked a cardigan! @hicusick   #ThePassage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller I’m beginning to think our government is uneducated and have no common sense!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[18 miles to the LA Marathon and on the way I stop at my favourite watering hole the Four Seasons LA, in my Nike’s.… https://t.co/LMLsKnQr0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DunnRandi @hoggtylerisd @TISDELAR612 Man y’all just keep running, don’t you! #jkr way to show up and be the change!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m a nice person for no reason so due to personal reasons don’t fuck with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigwalrath571 Can you throw in kavanaugh and the other judges shithead#45 insisted be on the supreme bench? Jeee… https://t.co/OF2OceUAxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I need help. Am I wrong for expecting a friend to listen and simply chuckle or just “that’s crazy” without telli… https://t.co/0bxbiwLQDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickcarter Happy Valentine’s Day to you and @Lauren_Kitt enjoy your guys dinner tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Every 11 minutes someone in the USA dies from Fentanyl Drug overdose.  And the Democrats don’t see a… https://t.co/CbnNnnQNcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well down goes your previous #1 team in all the land @Vol_Hoops . I tried to tell people that there are Coaches tha… https://t.co/mMAAd118RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe be like put some respeck on my name...why you ain’t even respeck yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NowakRo @hlc48 @ashlyntucker_ed @Syskakj_edu @jordyn_pistilli @Simply_RJD @smgaillard @TaraMartinEDU @tamaraletter… https://t.co/zgxJjpy9Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitter cold- stay home #newyorkcity #PolarVortex #cold #newyorkcity  @weatherchannel @NY1weather @JaniceHuff4ny… https://t.co/ivc1cjh0xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Child’s play. I found out I got cheated on the night my baby dad got locked up. I was out the door empty apartment… https://t.co/FxHV1W5vEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theastropath What if I am? What's it to ya? Wanna have a vampire fight? Bleh bleh bleh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming down to Queen Street, the lake was a beautiful color. #lakeside #toronto #queenstreet  #beach #winter @ The… https://t.co/FCDv89D9GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar dudebros are too much of a snob to admit that black panther is a genuinely beautifully written and filmed mov… https://t.co/wZRQtH0w4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 Trump knows exactly what he is doing. The Dems must now refer to him as King Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kireau @JenGRodgers I think what was meant is, they aren't supposed to be done in a personal capacity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to go to bed early tonight but here I am looking at memes at 3am again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadian_quiet @MaximeBernier @peoplespca Frustrating as hell. I'll never stop supporting Max but my effort seems… https://t.co/awUjhs6jWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t get over how amazing this show was last week. @PanicAtTheDisco put on the best concert I’ve ever been to https://t.co/k7uM9gsw8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experts Agree, Trump’s “National Emergency”  Undermines National Security https://t.co/D9mfLf1YDi via @AmericasVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[A: Columbia University Catherine McQuerry, University of New Mexico  #theNSLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoratiousPowell @CrystalBeebe3 @Madonna @dubstarr73 @MEDUSAS_BROTHER @Sheena_655321 @YantisaJ @JamesTConleyII… https://t.co/jjAD7VUBhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaamodt12 @alexissporterr @JYoko14 Yea the beat is unreal. And back in 2017 I DID play that song on the jukebox at… https://t.co/k8XV2w8n6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time again! #kickass #cocktailhour @ Emory Winship Cancer Center https://t.co/swjSOKt0xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[They keep saying Roman Savosin and I keep hearing Roman Sadovsky and reminding myself “WRONG ROMAN”]]></document><document><![CDATA[showing this to my dad so he’ll have exactly 6 months to look for a mariachi 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pray ✅ #Gratitude✅ #Covfefe ✅ #Ketosis ✅ #IntermittentFasting ✅ #FollowYourBliss⚽️✅ #Crackyourselfuponceaday✅✅✅… https://t.co/yJouud8vL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sisters Striving For Excellence, Inc. is holding a Sister 2 Sister mentoring interest meeting on February 20th, 201… https://t.co/7ooNesb4Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL I WATCHED THIS ENTIRE SERIES TODAY AND LEMME TELL U IT IS A M A Z I N G https://t.co/4WPdKJUnwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My CNAs be like I need a break.... 15 minutes, 30 minutes, here I am working 14 hrs, 1 admission... for the past 2… https://t.co/pnv4Ktb8wP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jptrib1 @AmerMilNews Russia is not; never has been, never will be, our friend. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hold on just for now, you’ve got this whole thing turned around “ @KevinOGarrett 〰️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son’s marching band is in need of new snare drums. Please help if you can. Thank you! :  https://t.co/Ah6tif4dig via @donorschoose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Google: stop the fake ads intended to defame me. You have enough legal problems without professional Registered Nu… https://t.co/reKabthRuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my mom still doesn’t know about the tattoo I got a year ago and I really want to get another one soon but I would get killed 😂😂😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should read this. Our new Congresswoman does not like answering questions about living and office arrangem… https://t.co/XSwrWkjMHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chopNscrewme RIGHT. But they hear it in music or they don’t have the representation they want in entertainment so… https://t.co/mC8nO6czWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aag2805 @AbdulElSayed College is a choice. I happily acquired a quarter of a mil in student loan debt, which I’m s… https://t.co/3gA42URqXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[done putting up with this crap! Please disregard (her) offensive language and inappropriate choice of topics.… https://t.co/QD4pgyrrjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so speedy that I ran by before you got out there! Thanks for being there to support me and for making me fast… https://t.co/dnmdjsn8LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterDK @RedwoodGirl And when they have 'Progress' in their name, it's (IMHO) fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last time!!! 🥍🥍#GAMEDAY #seniorszn @ Morrisville, New York https://t.co/h1yl1jSInD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retire dogs, cats &amp; monkeys from U.S. government labs! #GIVETHEMBACK - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/I360mZml7W via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I thought I lost me, you knew where I left me- you reintroduced me to your love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato @PressSec 🤦‍♀️does she think the entire world swallows her bullshit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[collin told me he tells people anything spicy at chickfila isnt spicy so the buy it 😭 &amp; hes never actually had any of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaSportsHall @CityofAlexLA @Alexlaconnects @4SeasonsBowl @BOMest1903 My costume is ready @Bevdower !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NokkiNatter Noting that! Sharing is the best way to go about it all haha. My sister and I would do the same when w… https://t.co/t8kAyvGLJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fairy on Seahorse 8" Ceramic glaze finish $30.99 plus shipping. #fairygarden #fairydecor #seahorse… https://t.co/ozm5aBNAFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbchamberlain @Crosscut @Weinbergrrrrr Yes! Thank you @Weinbergrrrrr! 🚲🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when I have happy clients!  #annarborhair #annarborhairstylist  #annarborsalon  #annarbor… https://t.co/omSxxmVTO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankieB_knowin Btw I used to have a crush on Steve Austin &amp; I have a theory that might be why I found Jose attractive lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieCnh12 Me neither. Its fur is offensive.  My grandma used to cook it all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you HH for having me at Teacher Appreciation Night! https://t.co/MdUd211vPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two 💞 are headed to see kanebrown_music in concert tonight. #AbiNate #WhatIfs @ Shreveport, Louisiana https://t.co/Tb2DUyX9PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[That episode when Rory turns down Logan’s marriage proposal gets me emotional every time. After the sixth time watc… https://t.co/DqCBE9atIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: making progress Also me: *says something* Oh wow I just went backwards again with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already have our tickets! Can’t to see @robert_markus put on the blue polo! 👕 #DEHToronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been hours since my friend opened up a candy bar and a tiny piece of chocolate flew into my eye but it’s still… https://t.co/Mdb0Ssqoiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly Schitt’s Creek would be so much better if they did away with Moira]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Boys ... Matt 2015 &amp; Kyle 2019 ... My ❤  #ProudandLuckymom https://t.co/54hfYoarlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIGAlliance @GWSportMngt @GWtweets @catherineordway @EmanuelGsc @EQLeague See you there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pleasure74 @MisleaderC @SafiMaasai @Barb81146 @DeepInTheHills @chefrocky413 @NancyNoseYou @IgoddessResist… https://t.co/xsqN8qOb3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be required reading in every college teacher training program, HR office, seminary, medical school and… https://t.co/IHHgM483ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much #MWHSpride celebrating this wonderful group of k-12 #WestonkArts students at the Youth Art Month Exhibit Re… https://t.co/r8ca46Sdns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleKraska @AAFFleet Will you be giving away tickets again for another home game by chance? I have several chronic… https://t.co/Jwa6qB7GUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[El alumno a superado al maestro, mi esposo en #Miercoles y con pedita de tequila!]]></document><document><![CDATA[me any time i listen to the seventh stranger, land, or my antarctica https://t.co/DAO2XAtt2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[son i b overthinking like shit. if iont talk to my nigga 2+ hours my mind b like ok sum aint right w us cus..... wyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enews #DAILYPOP Eminem came for R Kelly’s ass . Just twisted some lines from killshot . #notalike]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevlyons @GermanDoner_UK @ScottJKyle1 One question...were you wearing your kilt?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will always have a part of my heart and be in my life. That will never change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessDuck Yes the Avs do play dirty. At least we won, I hate walking out of HC when we lose. Blackhawk fans wer… https://t.co/xkGPae1l4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsbenngreat Hang in there ❤️ I know the feeling both of my favorite teams don't come back to AZ until next season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dollbaby312000 @MLB2MLR @HeatherR120508 I know the feeling. ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/ya3tWQ8im5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s incredibly exciting to see a candidate prioritizing the climate crisis, giving it the attention it demands of… https://t.co/Qr40JoOmOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @KamalaHarris this coming frm a Dem that voted against passing background checks on illegals trying t… https://t.co/GSj4stRkKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Weimer_ Case closed you filthy trash. Where is murderers news..where r rapists muslims news???? Where is Clin… https://t.co/wDoqokzpl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took some wrong turns in Tamworth, NH and ended up here! #Scenic @ Tamworth, New Hampshire https://t.co/YtGbpkW2GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 4:02 still havent gone back to bed. Looks like im rolling up and taking a shower 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rates are back to where they were this time last year, (boring!) while the real estate market continues it's march… https://t.co/mWO9vOqE7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AineMcAuleyCros @YouTube @HeidiMessenger @Drniallmc @freyaohoro @_TheMusicDoctor @BookHubPublish @AuthorTherapist… https://t.co/KWcibRXg90]]></document><document><![CDATA[My reaction to emotions...  Sad: cry Mad: cry Happy: cry  If only tears were good for your skin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh to have the energy represented here. #PhDLife #ParentLife #2019InPictures @ UNT Wooten Hall https://t.co/eHIA7rfYEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet sweet girl 😍 Lydia cuddles are truly the best! Besides of course, her mommas 🥰 https://t.co/AnSzweLHed]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Valentine for me 😔 he👉🏾@usher acting stupid😒 @ Backstage Night Club &amp; Lounge https://t.co/NiajPmfNsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was one of the most beautiful days with blissful light , bountiful creativity , and  serendipitous moment… https://t.co/crnBs44xSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump COMPLETE THE WALL !!  Pelosi wants ILLEGALS to VOTE. , unbelievable. They are Desperate  for VOTER… https://t.co/6WBX5aic0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you never had to use a bathroom stall that didn’t lock so you had to physically hold it closed while you pee, and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElDestrinador Si. Bueno tiene casa en la misma cuadra donde yo vivo. Lo hemos visto llegar en varias ocasiones com… https://t.co/SfXG4GObD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hadip @60Minutes @codeorg @ayahbdeir We’ve spoken about this several times before privately. But even as an Irania… https://t.co/MRs6AvVg5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianarowland not to mention that using the microphone means that questions could make it into recordings of the se… https://t.co/Awszl2fNI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyTumbleweeds That is how American's do.  We don't nip things in the bud but instead get angry when things are out of control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boozychef @Coravin @DemiCassiani @_drazzari @jflorez @RealWineGuru @TheWineStalker @wineworldnews @SteveKubota… https://t.co/OW1Z8QSSJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the first night of #daylightsaving @ Carson City, Nevada https://t.co/MI153M3imT]]></document></documents></author>