<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LadyTeig I don't get to see my family a lot and hearing how a lot of them defend Trump makes me not care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $1,667.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/JcCvrLXbEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBusch @SNICKERS #SendIt @KyleBusch #RowdyNation is ready to cheer you on in your @JoeGibbsRacing @ToyotaRacing… https://t.co/goXNzWukTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicklockwood Painting with a rather broad brush, aren’t you?  Is it possible that you make the same mistake about… https://t.co/vSOs7WdHTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris When a woman makes the Choice to have un protected sex and gets pregnant.  That's her choice, nobody… https://t.co/zD1ElUB0rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whipsmart13 @tscirrotto @WillieAtFLO @MysteryFiction @CenzoJoseph @wrestlingnomad Threw*]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you find inspiration? When you just don't feel like it.. what do you do?! Comment below and share your metho… https://t.co/lSnfLoOQwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Week Tonight spent most of the show discussing Brexit.  No solution except for Parliament to grow a pair and s… https://t.co/ERIQywaD2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[My story’s ending has yet to be created. It has some very juicy parts before the ending though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎮 Enter #MySillyLittleGang Spring Nintendo Switch #Giveaway ; U Could #Win A #NintendoSwitch w/ Neon Blue; Neon Red… https://t.co/1vwgEN0SNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julia19640309 @gmlsrnfma24 U are extremely beautiful I love your sexy hot body]]></document><document><![CDATA[I respect a girl with drive. I wanted to lay down and watch a movie but she had a paper she was stressed about. So… https://t.co/6tFV64jAjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve really gotta sick baby moms smh. Keeping your child away from their daddy selfishly is just downright sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaLewinsky @racheld @girlscouts No, thin mints. Every sane cookie eater knows that. It's thin mints. End of discussion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't hear all them sophomores talking on the tl no more🤫🤷🏽‍♂️ @MmhsRampage https://t.co/5mEUAqSNXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream car went for 200,https://t.co/pGdb4P2rOI condition only. 8miles on it plastic covers still on seats...wow!… https://t.co/czr8ykRn8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOSER...ADAME ,, GO HOME..SHUT YOUR PIE HOLE...U HAVE NOTHING TO OFFER AMERICANS THAT IS POSITIVE AND GOOD 4 THE PE… https://t.co/giS59d0yNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAZ0RFIST Similar situation to MJ. Convicted due to "weirdness".  When it is the fucking mob that are the real weirdos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the next summit or in his next love letter, @realDonaldTrump should ask Kim if he had anything to do with killin… https://t.co/5rQv3AMpXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anamariecox Sweet lady Callie has slept through the whole thing! (She murmurs: #InsteadOfSheepICount happy homes.… https://t.co/SbBxiKdfsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pntrack Freelap start cone location? Or are you using the start button?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cast my Heisman ballot for #SaquonBarkley! Click the player you think deserves the @NissanUSA #HeismanHouse vote! https://t.co/Hl9J3wMuwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport My eyes are always on me which I guess makes me a narcissist. @lifesafeast @heyjacqui_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Denuclearization? While you sell classified nuclear info to the Saudis? Go back to the omelette ba… https://t.co/pi423x1t85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathrynMaga @EdKrassen @BarackObama @HillaryClinton Why do you keep writing. Ivanka said it I really don't care do you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson We are a 4th world 2 Banana Republic thanks to a criminal in the Oval Office and on… https://t.co/WgYMWFSGzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollishamilton @SCsolarguy @normangirl2 @KyleKashuv There were all kinds of reports. To authorities. Can’t help if you don’t like facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow i still haven’t been to the beach and i’ve lived in SoCal for 1.5 years now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar lookalikes. (Only one was in a good movie.) #Oscars #Oscars2019 https://t.co/EKcHZbwBbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having #NationalNappingDay on a day when I can't take a nap is just plain wrong... https://t.co/HZZZC8YtYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitOnLion Work, Spartans, Drinks, and more work. Getting ready to travel with my @Lions this fall.… https://t.co/4crDDMVxCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyDoreShow  Marco Rubio tweeted that an electric generator in Bolivar state had exploded in Venezuela.  He said… https://t.co/ptHIkwKc6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavenly Father, I Thank You for allowing Eve to be Deceived by The Devil, So Man can look pleasing unto woman and… https://t.co/pcz16xdIey]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Iyanla talks about pathological trauma and behavior this brings me to Kris and OJ back in the day... sips tea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnKennedy You still 100% support Trump and believe he has never lied, weighs 235 pounds, hasn’t had sexual wi… https://t.co/G371S0wTCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelmickeyMouse Strangely, this was an absolute page turner of Thomistic analysis:  Occult Phenomena in Light of Th… https://t.co/shIHYRekJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for the difficult people in my life. They have challenged me to be better and stretched my character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrestan a policía que denunció abusos - Vía @elnorte https://t.co/YFA5dbVkQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @senrobportman and @senatemajldr McConnell would do well to follow to follow Sen. Paul's exampke and to d… https://t.co/aubyu46jQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final box. @USFCooBBall slip to 4th in #nsicmbb South https://t.co/FG5ufPnbaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShariWiltrout @adriancumming @Kimbrulea @amyklobuchar Being registered only does one thing, they still have to mak… https://t.co/4c7Zi8bWZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHForte @notcapnamerica These rich guys always find a way to skate out of doing time.  He defrauded the government… https://t.co/5Nd8iYU6SN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugliness that you see in others is a Mirror reflection of what’s in you. #ExamineYourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends and family pulled me back to reality... I cannot forgive them for this though. For a business centered o… https://t.co/KcaBqNcd5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 15 KU tops No. 16 K-State 64-49 to maintain Big 12 hopes  https://t.co/mWeToY9vJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump could never get away with his own little army to protect his bastion. The Secret Service, would take him down… https://t.co/1Hrl5AgvQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @DannyGradio @raider_rob24 Hey dummies "Mr Sandman" is the song that was used f… https://t.co/sDMFQqh9O5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipPulley @MrNunesteach @heARTISTatWORK @kat_goyette @KatieJMcNamara @KarlyMoura @ShakeUpLearning @gcouros… https://t.co/rNYdWAC1WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @CoryBooker @BeefUSA You.Are.A.Huge.Idiot. https://t.co/cN3I07VASQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Scrapb👀kSaturday 💋🧚🏻‍♀️🙌 #Movies #StayBlessed #kisses🍰 https://t.co/i0zG7tAq3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patt_Brown Probably by names alone but mid season nah I don't think so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mvtty I already took multiple@dabs ate gummies and hit the bowl before bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undisputed @MichaelRapaport This should be on your next episode @undisputed !!!!! https://t.co/KDTr7LHUOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/jos9yZ1K3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you!! Who’s subscribed to What the Fashion on Snapchat Discover and seen our Oscars rundown and VERY special… https://t.co/KxqaKwARdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmyrossum @realDonaldTrump Well the dams are completely doing Satan's work lives are out there using KY to get it… https://t.co/0iHnPYMtVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patricia_maben @CampusSonar They better be! Lots of chatter almost as soon as that injury occured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insureblog @Hiveaway @MedicalQuack @chrissyfarr With a “counting room” in the middle...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am getting a monster truck #monsterjam #monsterjam2019 #monsterjamworldfinals @clintus chlo_bug @chrissybevo broo… https://t.co/hfu99DrUL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Translate gave me that Chinese version, which seemed reasonable. Microsoft Translate turns it back to "Allow… https://t.co/OWaGMEzAlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen’s testimony Wednesday to Democratic  #OversightCommittee is a shotgun blast of embarrassment to #Democrats fo… https://t.co/kFlj4GIEif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin Angelica is a precious child of God she doesn't deserve to be treated like a piece of meat. She's my BFF… https://t.co/aOcY34UQxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We believe in the future of #journalism too,  Hilde. That’s why you’ll feel right at home here at @Cronkite_ASU, an… https://t.co/lc7RbVZWV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Rock &amp; Roll” will never die. 🎸 @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/CASmA2HYQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the family @rokinonlenses Happy and excited for the new possibilities. @sonyelectronics #picture #lens… https://t.co/Au6pPn0zxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_60s_at_50 - I am working on completing the sixties. Have 1960, 64, 65, 66, and 67 already up. Will fill in the next few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate oat milk chia seed pudding topped with blueberries and almonds is the shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS your Tax cut is now costing the middle… https://t.co/z0jUut6taP]]></document><document><![CDATA[About time to trek over and wait in the cold until they let us in. 😒 #MidwinterChicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sundance_kid13 @KKEC_ Mr. Anonymous needs some tips. This is all wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clara_Resists @joncoopertweets Agree! They have been lying to a whole segment of America, it would be wise to open… https://t.co/JWc4GNob82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section 4AA Boys Basketball Tournament begins TONIGHT at HOME!  #11 NLA Eagles vs. #14 St. Paul Washington Tech Eag… https://t.co/moO1Eswyyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[AR is so much more exciting than VR right now. Wonder if Oculus and Vive will start hedging their bets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZionW32 better tell your little freshmen buddies, that their dumbasses just showed why your asses will be out of t… https://t.co/Re27PrwAtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The discerning sets his face toward wisdom, but the eyes of a fool are on the ends of the earth.”   - Proverbs 17:24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí te va una canción para ti… En Peligro de Extinción de La Adictiva Banda San José de Mesillas https://t.co/lIi1g31owX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullshitMike90 We are a small team and we look out for each other. Even the annoying guy that will talk your ear off about asinine stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the government that is already not clearly in control of it’s own agenda on day 2 of spring session. How do… https://t.co/RiwBEAcy62]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I need is one big company to give me a shot at running their Twitter, then I can finally drop out of school]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Gameday. #LetsGoStickmasters @ Polar Ice House at The Factory https://t.co/4UgjLeIkLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanImmergluck @HistoryLivesDet From Stars to the Marvelous local music fans of Detroit,there was always a great ti… https://t.co/lKXQoYEzbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/pHKSTnYBJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertwickens @itsKarliWoods Good stuff lad! All the best for the rest of your recovery]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennajameson I said it on FB. I've been to that area of DT Chicago.. Not a snowball's chance in hell some dudes 80… https://t.co/LcJ6Fbf16d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting! What do United Methodists really believe? | United Methodist News Service https://t.co/V7QUOHSDsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great game tonight, came down to the wire. @MooseHeadsHC remain undefeated in the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Allow them to join and make them all meet up at a disclosed area and call the cops so they’re all off the streets]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think you’re reading it closely enough @RepPressley https://t.co/74LfMNdfyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenJackd1 @TexaLonestar I wonder about the 380,000 men that died freeing slaves, did they mean anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t nobody wanna see two successful black men go at it over a misunderstanding 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_little_laura @farmer_wayt Inflation makes things more expensive not higher wages. You can't survive on a minimum… https://t.co/FcLtMko3bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glicoro 牡羊、火のエネルギーから牡牛、地のエネルギーに替わります。象徴が天災みたいなモノから人災とか、金融不況・金融革命とかそっちにシフトするかと。変化の境目が一番ヤバイとも言われています…]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is how idiot democrats win - they act unethically, some republicans act “honorably”  - Americans lose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr PRESIDENT.. I need help.. The grants pass Water District is trying to take my LAND... J j https://t.co/2Lh4ZrbG5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome show tonight @daronmalakian @scarsonbroadway 🇦🇲🇦🇲🇦🇲 🤘🤘🤘 https://t.co/a2lHZsupRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daylonc2sont @Zrowable Hahha sorry I’m always shitting on people’s shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth cannot aid us until we become participators in it. We only possess what we experience.  ... Here is a simple… https://t.co/e2JoXN2lZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: all crackheads deserve what they get. does anybody deserve death wishes? no. but they deserve ev… https://t.co/oj041VBmiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday, February 23, 2013 - 6 years ago today was the big Pinewood Derby; I've been a part of it since the 2004 a… https://t.co/BNSKUi6buf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dan_sauceda_ Ohhh to be a Twitter god... if only for a fleeting moment]]></document></documents></author>