<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@vroberts9 @MissytheB @lynda3035 @sharon_cantley @GordonHarmony @BloomNight2 @marisbellamy1 @DonnaLeeThomps8 Saturd… https://t.co/HQ4Jol6dn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doskey64 @Union_Jacky @Disorganised1 @jessix @LilyLilyMaynard Or trans woman. Trans women are also adult human fem… https://t.co/pdc84nsoz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remain with us the whole day, Lord, — let your grace be a sun that never sets. Remain with us, Lord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosinaAnderson I have never loved an Oscar look more than Billy Porter. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that, Ladies &amp; Gentlemen, is what Republican leadership accomplishments.  Opposite of what socialism brings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@culturaobscura @wandercrystal Thank you ☺️ for suggestions. I have work shop today and nice dinner with family 💚🍀💙🌎😊☀️❤️🎈💝💕🕊❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealEnglishMatt @bitstripObama @KevinJacksonTBS @AOC https://t.co/tPmf4t5u3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on Mercari! REROCK EXPRESS BOOT … https://t.co/7ToeGG4bZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coats1234 No. Were used to seeing him as a Mayan. Would've been really cool to see @EmilioRivera48 as a son though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmckenz44559503 @maydaymindy9 While it's kid gloves for his favorite cast of liars...Corsi, Nunberg, Stone etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling into work with a ruptured ovarian cyst like.... https://t.co/27N4kogoi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are going to prison Traitor Trump -- if you are lucky!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man last night's game was so much fun @TorontoRockLax https://t.co/lT72g0ZFlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petjonvil @KrisKatJam @BusyPhilipps If you take a marketing course, the general public spends money to feel better… https://t.co/NJPs0gNTzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great, informational, multigenerational and #active event!! #CoActiveLeadership #BeYou MGN Day part 2! 💪🏽💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @CNNEE @cnni @CNN Nicolas Maduro is not Venezuela’s president. Venezuela’s interim president is @jguaido. Plea… https://t.co/nTtNdDknOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travismillrr I was literally there. Look at my snapchat story if you don’t believe me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me and I forget, teach me and I may remember, involve me and I learn. - Benjamin Franklin #oneCCPS #edpsych]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMJoyner @VincentRK @MayoClinic @ScottWrightMD Thank you for sharing. There’s not enough recognition for the many… https://t.co/bW6qdc7IAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday John! Miss you more and more everyday! Have a good one🤘🏼 https://t.co/tdxsoYp1Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debivort @superkash @caprastro Please advise on how to steal and raise this baby goat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching broadchurch season 2, very distressed about these courtroom scenes. NONE of this would fly in an american courtroom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[busco pessoas q queiram dormir cmg de conchinha pois n sei dormir sozinha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏍Con Sue Photography and Design🏍  🏍Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏍  🏍These designs were created by: Connie Wheele… https://t.co/cYOWieH0eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 41% Off Hair Services at Paul Mitchell the School https://t.co/YbVmf3TwgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is the first president to keep promises to America n people ! Has done more good in two years than Obama in 8… https://t.co/pb8m5SSTrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went from 100 to anxious crying in like .95 seconds and i dont know why]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump He does not...is that a trump poll or a fox poll?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; @joel_owen are ready for round two on Thursday!!! 🤪🤪 @NJOMZA https://t.co/rqqh93nQFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cocoa_Bean10 They should leave if they think it would be better in another country.   We don't want these morons h… https://t.co/P3X8GAsMTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing the first art market I’ve signed up for in years is in a couple weeks! https://t.co/ZTcpftQjQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsAmy47 @Cmm09672 @CheriJacobus @sutori Nope Melania is his handler. The big cover up with how they met, her citi… https://t.co/gwCZC6IJWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The squirrel you kill in jest dies in earnest. “ ~ Henry David Thoreau  😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cleansing Fire of God LIKE IT OR NOT‼️  Be filled, tried-transformed into gold....OUR GOD IS A CONSUMING FIRE!!… https://t.co/O8l2frkeHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Downtown San Francisco in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/Bht5ninjYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ppAIl4A51T She absolutely wanted that letter made public. She has to 1. Keep Meghan the name in every… https://t.co/DWvC6xJBbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best 2019 Soft Hand Towels in Bulk USA, CA, TX https://t.co/Y6gIfC0PBu #handtowelsinbulk #towel #manufacturing https://t.co/UVdWgyoB7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beatles vs Stones 2/7/19 🎶♥️🎶 #tributebands #beatles #stones #houseofblues #anaheim #thankful #love #latergram… https://t.co/QUEAKNo0CG]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S THAT TIME OF DAY BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE!! YES WE ARE OPEN TODAY! 10a-8p So stop on by❤ - - #CreamOfSpinach -… https://t.co/Vvmpqa5LZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelleyElwood I eat most my meals at home so that’s probably the answer but it still seems so totally nuts and I ♥️ TONGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol smh I’ll be one of those babymama’s who still let their baby daddy smash 🤷🏾‍♀️ don’t judge me..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No sir, the enemy of the people is you. #Unfit #25thAmendment #2545]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids are being indoctrinated and find steam don't give a damn how about you she's been doing this for 30 years… https://t.co/uFQ6PRqiXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove to the lake to run it but it’s so cold I’m sitting in my car listening to @Akon instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From “Once Upon a Time” to “Manifest”...@JoshDallas is the best! @OnceABC @NBCManifest #Oncers #Manifesters… https://t.co/PIlQgSiNC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh I too have gone down this road a dozen times now. One of my greatest badges of honor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Press thru....reach up and get your miracle!  just like the woman who grabbed her healing...God's healing is availa… https://t.co/DaYhfcgKxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[So how can we ever expect to achieve greatness, to become successful, if we sow seeds of negativity? How do we expe… https://t.co/KzN0XH5sS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momness1 @cspanwj Morning Jan...It's not just Friday, but it is 45* outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CInsidious @ZackMorris82 @Pirates Again, I was being sarcastic with that tweet. I liked the Dickerson trade so I’m… https://t.co/zVZaajmSKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleLauraaa Me Zooming into the crowd to make sure I don’t talk to any of those ppl https://t.co/kRWn5hUAym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some pretty heavy rain 🌧 fall in the BP (Baldwin Park) area flooded streets and all #ABC7LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day fun in a Milestones! ❤️ #BEWES #HappyValentinesDay @MilfordSchools @WoodlandMilford https://t.co/eFvy7EvCn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt @_TJWatt You guys are hysterical...we love it!!! Bringing it always being for real frfr😁tytytyJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never really were friends with that person if you’re fine with dating their ex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 24 years of proudly presenting world class LGBTQIA cinema, the North Carolina Gay + Lesbian Film Festival (NC… https://t.co/K8hkm7h1Uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janesa_xo welp then he gonna hurt his own feelings and i really don’t give a shit anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[A laughed so hard at this. Watch the whole thing, the second half is the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I would be so happy to wake up to the sound of rain 😌 There's something soothing about it, don't you… https://t.co/W7pXfXu3UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been challenged by @AC_Schafer and @KLawsonBelonwu to post pics of my favorite books for 7 days. Each day I'll… https://t.co/ej5NRrkySv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And judges kept saying Destiny's Child, when the Lion kept saying her parents were Hollywood royalty. 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love cooking for @theadrianpoot because he thinks everything I make is so bomb. 99.9%  time I’m experimenting and… https://t.co/SCm1bpRjMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirectionersRok @itsavarose_ @Complex 1st off Jewish people were only 6 million Hitler killed 10 million so there.… https://t.co/oQv1bMLmrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiminssi_mx @BTS_twt Mis manos miden lo mismo que las de el, but siento que mis meñiques son mas largos xD sorry jiminssi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my state (Washington State, U.S.) switched to no-fault divorce, the divorce rate went up, yes, but the best th… https://t.co/oz2o7O7eWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom just got me in trouble for being on my phone she said I’m addicted 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sardonicIeftist @Queen050780 @XCleXo Sure, and a year earlier as mayor it was this: https://t.co/1YWnrByRYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms.Otis’s 1st graders working hard solving numbers to make groups of ten with multiple strategies, sharing and disc… https://t.co/MnLYFgL3yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland "several reports of wires, transformers and telephone poles on fire."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHS_Admiralsbse There’s still time, Deputy Cubs, just sayin’ 🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/icSsTbUk3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Image Result for https://t.co/JOyOeMch6s #comedy #tee-hee #smile #comic https://t.co/yKFkfQmStb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yes_that_dolly @HeepDouse @RidgewayGirl01 @amalgamary @CEB1980 @Michael_F_Page @RadFemme74 @ClearlyShe… https://t.co/ygFGcqrh47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCole_301 @MeghanDonnelly5 Not defending anyone. I want to hear more from some other victims and those close to hi… https://t.co/jJTTElkT7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[These leeks wintered over beautifully @ Long Beach, Washington https://t.co/2uXFuiOuMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMStateBaseball @Jdehn55 @Ltrell234 @Head_HunJoe8 @Nick_Gonzales13 What’s up with the live stream?  No sound.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#martigras #fattuesday Let the good times roll! @ Sunnyland, Illinois https://t.co/JMIE4Km0Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bill_preston @Distra67 @kare11 I use it medically for chronic pain, and I wish we had a broader spectrum to choose… https://t.co/Yax3K5mGxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[lets be honest, there's absolutely nothing about lullaby that i wouldn't like. strong rapping, versions in many lan… https://t.co/ZdhASb01T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveMyCatShadow @Tracy143DC Because they are cowards...I appreciate you (: 💜🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traci_tousant @donalynbooks Ooh! This looks interesting... https://t.co/PNHZmPEByv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Arethatribute These people are on here "sanging" their hearts out! 👏👏 @tylerperry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cumberanston @OhShitShinoda @mikeshinoda @goodguychady Can you imagine how much music all those Mikes could make????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me at CycleBar and get your first ride free!!  https://t.co/Pd0heupg2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonDingle If you asked my husband (who jokes about this) Cold Hearted Snake by Paula Abdul. He says this becau… https://t.co/x4r6bKWSLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it was her feet and interveined so you can walk  https://t.co/3Di6iSdxkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Somebody had better look into this! Who allowed this creepy billionaire to be involved in our electi… https://t.co/PLK471kEEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelywright This is awesome. @blanketboat is my new favorite follow. Good looking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Privilege: Still being out on bail after publishing an image of a federal judge in crosshairs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Kate Flowers, her letter to her students about the purpose of annotation is spot on! #CWPatCATE… https://t.co/Qv64OkePav]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t tell if everytime i watch episodes of chuck and blair together i just get sadder or happier]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Raising_Canes Chicken Fingers in North Canton, OH https://t.co/VxLclWvHWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like our teacher leadership initiative at my school. I am so blessed to be part of something so rewarding.… https://t.co/MtT0hzQQuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylalahowell @bbrryynnnn @GoldenKnights I see the potential for some Fortnite dances during pregame warmups now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #win for #twitter.  Making a break for it.  I need to be back in my #inlandempire. @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/hfVZvMonIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcaaron @Oprah Husband, daughter who claimed woman was killed after helping Baltimore panhandler are now charged.… https://t.co/lGNMrGqms3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thania__galvan @_deysigaribay Ustedes no necesitan maquillaje si ya están hermosas mis hermanas 🤤🤤🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachcav7 @lyan118 @JonBershad @realDonaldTrump Sadly, we learned about researching I'm 4th/5th grade??? Don't you… https://t.co/OYh1IiUxRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a kid that’s super bad, I’m sorry when he cusses I just find it hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love an omelet to start the day ❣️ #ProteinPower #happygymrat https://t.co/nzKcgg7Y21]]></document><document><![CDATA[lovely day today perfect day to open up to you &lt;3 https://t.co/Lo7T0hQk0e]]></document></documents></author>