<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sambassartist RIP to one of NASACARS biggest hearts! https://t.co/8hSlxg3ltQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[just found out there’s not a Lighthouse Pizza in Lincoln, like what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90yehafnairb You do realize it’s Presidents’ Day not president’s day which means it honors PAST presidents too, ri… https://t.co/vfJ0vdMRyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This student. | Community Post: 14 Cards Against Humanity Players Who Win At Life #comedy #lol #smile #comic https://t.co/p8V8f596gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hourlyFox @KevinGFox A fox  carrying a feather must be a sign of good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump David Zublick from “The Truth Unsealed” states that the Clinton’s doctor testified recently that s… https://t.co/prKItVZ8VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinycarebot LOOKING FIR WATER THAT IS MY FAVIRITE SONG. THANK YOU STICK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMavel has the most awesome sauce #heroines ever #BrieLarson #LashanaLynch #AkiraAkbar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peek at one of our new menu items available tomorrow! Summer Cabana Salad🥗 Mixed greens, candied pecans, stra… https://t.co/tDx4iZeONd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @MIWband and @atreyuofficial are touring together is some of the best news I’ve gotten. You bet I will be at this tour!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight has been a night. First 4 hrs of my shift was literally nothing but dealing with beeping IV pumps and occlu… https://t.co/Z75qTf67ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk where i get my money management skillls but i’m jus glad i got them. even tho sometimes i do spend like 200 a week lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t shaved my legs since New Year’s Day when I left for Portland, this bath I’m about to take will be more of a shearing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMiers @JReinerMD @scruffage @jaketapper @peterbakernyt Sorry, I got a note to translate tweet. Cardiovascular… https://t.co/vcTA3c4uVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGates @melindagates. @gatesfoundation. One of the uses of toothpaste in this article is to stop itch of mosqui… https://t.co/5zh7cohpfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @nancycordes That money is for a real emergency, not for a President acting like a spoiled child!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDawsonWrites @BDawsonWrites The fan who started the altercation gave an interview very much proclaiming himself i… https://t.co/FtCfuQBOgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannemcd Recently heard "between you and me...." and the 30 people in the area]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to all the presenters at #TDSBDLL today! I learned a lot about @TDSB_AT assistive tech,… https://t.co/getXP01uYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜💘💘💘 Ends 7/31/19 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure the people you keep around will still be there through your downfalls and not just your successes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burrr, it’s still winter everywhere and cold. Keep your stuff warm in this Dior vintage leather and shearling fligh… https://t.co/EuYYvu77Pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Someone explain to me how other countries have OUR constitutional rights and privilages??  If that w… https://t.co/TaJ42by3YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSmith4WA @WolfPAChq @AOC @BrandNew535 @justicedems Did I stop a heart attack? I’ve been very stressed, yester… https://t.co/uT50Bejb7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleismyna2 @HildurArnar1 @DebbieRumsey1 @BravoHWFanClub Yikes! Darn Michelle, very mature of you. I don’t lik… https://t.co/kVC3n3sCkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hiked in *joshua tree* and stayed in *joshua tree* there were so many *joshua trees*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never skipped a practice and always played to the last minute #losangeles #marcquiblvck #shinin @ Los Angeles, Cali… https://t.co/GLVnbFtvpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryancartoons I used to make it every Sunday night when the kids were home. It was their favorite dinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @sabine_durden I’ve seen her walls, check out her new gait. Those heels are getting higher! 💩 getting deep💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Genius Hack You Can Use to Get Fresh Eggs at McDonald’s  https://t.co/O0ohO2v2hX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow Then they have to be charged as an adult. Can't have it both ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first dog together passed away today. Our hearts are heavy. RIP Cabo💕 12 years went by too fast. https://t.co/KXMHuHGBNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SachelleD @southwestcolts @NatalieOstrand2 Oh yea 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 two awesome ladies...I know it’s gonna be fabulous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earth_to_sammie Plus if people aren’t gonna give you a chance just cause ‘you look mean’ then that’s their loss ca… https://t.co/n46zF3sUNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the best compliment I’ve ever gotten was “I’ve never seen you with a pimple”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog Placing more of his Buds too protect him! How will this country ever recuperate after this Regime Of TH… https://t.co/m9gccGI9o5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nynfa711 @AstrosAtoZ @DollyDwyer10 @somosLosAstros @sillylilmom @WBaygents @astros @MadSadAstrosFan @HtownWiggy… https://t.co/txHdLGw5SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @gabeschoenfeld @BulwarkOnline Of course I want the Democratic candidate to win the presidency in 202… https://t.co/tRDb08Dfrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all didn’t grow up with unlimited minutes past 9pm and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 American traitor: Kushner  #2 American traitor: Prince https://t.co/EfWzgrv6M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelGarofola Please @TheBachelorTV DO NOT PICK Cassie for the Bachelorette!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amriana @unovana @deadheadsticker @MailOnline Pretty sure sharing amongst resisters is not advertising rather shar… https://t.co/7hUsMgZkN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The State Board of Education voted not to renew a school’s charter.  Students at Charlotte Learning Academy tell us… https://t.co/ctfHp3DAk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT The public has no sympathy to The MSM Respect given is respect earned.Respect our POTUS! #NomoreFAKENEWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empire actor Jussie Smollett staged attack because he was 'dissatisfied' with his salary, police say.… https://t.co/KsfZV29uQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RookytheRook I noticed ravens seem to travel in pairs and the crows are in larger groups. For some unknown reason… https://t.co/szZflXqYOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t go out anymore these hangovers are not worth it https://t.co/fOYbGOeujK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Chris walked into my room yesterday and was like “Soooooo you like to read?” And I’m just like 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos con derechos 🎶 Yo no te pido que te enamores ,seamos eternos está noche , yo no te pido que seamos novios si… https://t.co/5YorbDEtBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a fall during the Polar Plunge today! Ouch!!! #GonnaFeelThatInTheMorning  But that's ok... I had a great time… https://t.co/gDtteB2Mnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHAHAH let it be known that I tweeted the picture of @FunPapaya and @colesprouse with a piece of bread in his pock… https://t.co/pEqShN2wR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhovianLeap "Okay, where's Bob? Was he up all night reading #DoctorWho fan fiction... Again?"  🤨 https://t.co/vKR3kUL7zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @Iamproudamerica Just a phase? Here is a woman who at 17 goes to the middle east to marry an ISIS terrori… https://t.co/TETHR3h6Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, for some reason I keep thinking about Tony Stark addressing Ebony Maw as Squidward and smiling. Just struck m… https://t.co/090Hx1zyaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmo32978761 @theDamorela You ain’t never lie it’s beautiful honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great lunch great price.  Give it a try!!! @ Waynebrook Inn https://t.co/O5PzigGMMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smobrien24 @hicusick Right? They did an amazing and believable acting job. My heart broke with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff4877 @LayneScherer Education for employees (e.g. GA/TA/RA) about How To Use their health insurance. We are not… https://t.co/oScFNzqQGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What triggered the biggest increase in house buying power?? 🏡# FirstAmericanTitle https://t.co/pH75iNm9F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cracker32259 @eilishp @Holyniwa @poohsbrana @BernieSanders @JusticeGinsburg @Skirball_LA Would you mind including… https://t.co/geh54laSJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG. (@ Milk Bar LA in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/0kIDHRdwtN https://t.co/soamybZhcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhhh my son’s last High School musical playing “Sky” (the fiancé) in “Mama Mia” beyond proud, it’s hitting me in f… https://t.co/4OhXTnHK7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[But this situation im dealing with though and this other situation tho, 😤😤😤😤 sheesh ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illegal Alien Accused of Beating Newborn Son to Potential Death https://t.co/xE0DWLooHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliStokols @maddow I can’t help think if he would be friends with Hitler or even Osama bin Laden and why not throw in Saddam Hussein]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday to one of the best friends I’ve ever had! Even though I didn’t get to spend much time with you… https://t.co/ryLmzNfQHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[and yes I'm only saying this because wasteland, baby is making me emotional https://t.co/AD1Dxy8C2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolat @noasbobs @sarahlalondee @MrIanFischer @allison_fuisz @YKrawiecki @ErinPelhamDoak @VivantaVie @RebelGeo I'll… https://t.co/iLefeQkEDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking about The Voice, my mom def just said, “John, you know, @chrissyteigen’s husband.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[These folks out here on the parade route smell like beer, ass and bad decisions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuburnU @UofAlabama @SouthernUnionSC is this the type of behavior you guys condone? Hold them accountable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas brothers are coming back and my inner 13 year old doesn’t know what to with itself]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #PrinceFrederick, MD! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Wireless - Retail Sa… https://t.co/aYoF2kKnCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicForLife @RosaDeliadelos1 @satribesman @d_ast777 @DavidHarris707 @CatholicPierogi @carmelitequotes @aryservant @ArleneKowalczyk 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeesoul And the person recording this has a #rifle or dart gun something to kill the bear if the bear gets out… https://t.co/JB2L32p3qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polirealm Ok. But what has Biden said or done to make you believe he wouldn’t take climate action as a serious, existential imperative?]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 days til I’m back in Vancouver 🇨🇦🎉 one of my favorite cities ever and lots of...sightseeing to do 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambertests Since I’m not a mother, I was speaking from the place of being childless and her devaluing my existance… https://t.co/WDX1qW1ud3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX @TheRue I knew it!  I think she denied it because the public guessed her so quickly!  Easy!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day later than originally planned but excited for our home opener on Saturday!!!🌲🤓⚾️❤️ https://t.co/sszssHCBpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasemonkey @NeeNeeCreative I love this, @jasemonkey and @NeeNeeCreative! 😘💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelagallippi @normsworld FYI, my son is on the spectrum, too, but he's "high" on it, functioning in normal class… https://t.co/A16CUycs6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCLASemelFriend do not tell me i need therapy because what i need is the last ten years back.  I am not going to d… https://t.co/ghu5nW3QWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hell_HasCome @OleVetUSAF @amvetsupport @Jusretscpo Animals would NEVER act like this!  STOP USING THIS DESCRIPTION… https://t.co/eKpXG3cK2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Shelby were just talking about if we were on death row what our last meal would be and stuff and she’s goes… https://t.co/pkDOfcXASf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly speaking, social media has a lot of us fucked up in the head...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did two raunchy, very R-rated comedies starring kids/teens each use "Nobody Speak" in each of their trailers?! #GoodBoys #Booksmart]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was on FaceTime with my grandma and she asked my mom to get her “the green cucumber pot to plant stuff in” and my… https://t.co/7Nns2rNQvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karobinson47_3 @KevinLBedfordSr I’m sure POC we’re outraged at a genetic level (our pathology runs deep). But beca… https://t.co/pf1LIZjJK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jediabetic1 @mblock29 @NickiNicholsMS @MTL613 @lollydaggle @DiabetesSocMed @diabetesalish “Where all paths cross.”… https://t.co/KyCCGwXm6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally spending the weekend back in my favorite city giggling and seeing fabulous shows with my bestie and I… https://t.co/GZInaMYUsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parasailed, hot air ballooned, sky dived... but I don’t know how to swim. Don’t @ me. 😩🙏🏼 Just thanking god I’m alive...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored FAC ⁦@jfkphd⁩ with @APA President ⁦@TigerBingham⁩ and GR Associate Director Doug Walter ⁦@APAPractice⁩… https://t.co/hrqCHKlF5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, love Mom. 😄 @ Cowichan Bay, British Columbia https://t.co/ojGgg628sC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Far as I can tell..... I believe that you have covered just about everyone of them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I was in her Special Education class because of my speech impediment, back and leg braces and walker... thi… https://t.co/vDtvQCEBlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cops &amp; no counselors: how the lack of school mental health staff is harming our students... https://t.co/JC9Y8W5SMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #satchat friends and @TheBradCurrie @ScottRRocco  and @wkrakower for the awesome chat this morning! Have… https://t.co/XoCouA40Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hungary Faces a 'Worrying Course' on Women's and Refugee Rights, Expert Says https://t.co/lye2G5B3jr #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allkpop I think she should marry Kim Jong Un. They look cute together.]]></document></documents></author>