<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thx 🙏🏾 very kind! Presently at the lobby Hilton restaurant ... night is young. Weather conducive to watching colleg… https://t.co/GPyWDMUaOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEAGUE PLAY GRIND WITH @daiptixx NEW MIC AND ALERTS TOO!!! https://t.co/2Fut898YdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GettingCooked @edgar224u I’m blocked by all three most days. https://t.co/hdHm5qcSYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna hear from the Trump children saying they know what regular Americans want. You were born with a Silve… https://t.co/4Jlj0jCsCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is such a bitch...it’s so long and you’re so antsy for spring but can go from 65 and sunny to 6-12” of snow in 2 days]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tokyo related dreams are increasing with only 23 days until I'm back there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHOOTER_989 @RickShielsPGA Come on over anytime. The deals keep presenting themselves. Sometimes hard to pass them up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shaved off my beard this week, it painstakingly grows back. The bar looks more fun then it really is right now. https://t.co/c9FcX79cby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who just booked his first pro wraslin video gig... TCW  https://t.co/cgSDVb5Jxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone that missed the highlights of the @NYIslanders absolutely owning @91Tavares and the @MapleLeafs on his r… https://t.co/6snMj3hVai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StructuralBCN @RodrigoEstvez1 @rafasadaba Problem there is the surgeon oversized the valve. This is a known proble… https://t.co/k7KGwyJ8rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to go visit the Calabasas fam and honestly I’ve been putting it off! 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything worse than @Marc_Bertrand laughing at the crazy hijinx that is @ZoandBertrand ? No #idiotic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markanderson65 How do you get a tax break in one day?? Get traded @vegas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheConqui5tador Both are terrific. Based on last performance, it’s an easy call.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My talented wife, D’Lytha, instructing Fort Worth Actors Studio Tuesday students.  #powwow #actingforcamera… https://t.co/UUHQSALAVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my goal here is to see, basically, how many GOOD TWEETS I can generate in ONE REGULATION LENGTH NYC WEEKEND - th… https://t.co/1t6oZBwPmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[These situations occur all the time and are constantly covered up by NYS and our government please help raise aware… https://t.co/Zmt7BmeCgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The passing of @Dodgers legend #DonNewcombe reminds me about a book that changed my life as a kid. "Boys Of Summer"… https://t.co/Ot9RaWDfbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Greenfield, MA, check out this job: https://t.co/Uz3sj2LXlT #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andybaskin5 @CLETalkingHeads @923TheFan  Signing of Hanley isnt significant. Phelps still owes pizza. The indians… https://t.co/WrXpN95lXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafstallions @TheAAF @WillieD_effect 4 turnovers and still within one score. Nice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRothstein This is the pac 12 basically saying they dont want to compete for viewers. It's why football start times suck as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasta Limerick No. 24: . My son tried to draw a quick doodle  of a chef baking crisp Apple strudel, but I'm sorry t… https://t.co/fqWsl3wWjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Lady Gaga, for your encouraging words to those of us who walk a differnt career path from most.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sang Run MD Sun Mar 3rd AM Forecast: REST OF TODAY Snow Hi 29 TONIGHT Snow Lo 18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike Please get some consistency with your shoe sizes. One shoe I’m size 11, another I’m 10.5. When you do limited… https://t.co/Ml1JbFmQvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Festejando el triunfo contra el chivas miado salud banda y buenas noches a todos los Rayados de ❤️🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺🍺 https://t.co/ALihQ7elRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#burbanknoonrotary #karaoke burbanknoonrotary 2nd Annual Karaoke Fundraiser Dave the date Sat May 11th 5-10PM… https://t.co/65sCNmVIdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s Daddy/Daughter excursion... @ Cracker Barrel Old Country Store https://t.co/1IYROHcBT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t help but wonder if Sondra Locke’s exclusion from the “in memoriam” segment of the Oscars wasn’t because she o… https://t.co/grAyin5g4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk "It is not that every decision you make is the right one that makes you a good leader.  It is whether or… https://t.co/eVNX1HbGSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHast89 @ChirpinParaKeat @CarBombBoom13 He had his head down!?!?! Lol wtf are you watching]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump You are disgusting. We remember your 19 brothers that hijacked 4 planes and brought down the twin towers on 9/11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever wanna bawl your eyes out to a song? Just listen to “Alyssa lies” by Jason Micheal Carroll. The saddest song ever 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ebzo Clearly, this is why we still have a problem today with mental health awareness. Get your heads out of your a… https://t.co/D8aNATHHXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicLombardi Is and has been one of the best in the entire game for a long time. Wish you all the success for the rest of your career!]]></document><document><![CDATA[such a fun way to end a long week of hard work in the lab @BeerWildHeaven! and we finally got an “official”… https://t.co/6fYYjziWLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlyonne As good as that film is, I would like to see Leigh Brackett’s original script, which Altman pretty much th… https://t.co/DGxe7KLRah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NextAlberta @ConcernedPah You need connections to the @fordnation crime family, or be able to grease his palm with at least $1250]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow will be my last day in a house I’ve lived in for 23 years. It’s a little weird to think about. But I’m rea… https://t.co/02japAY2h1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eulokodoreality pq tem 3 anos desde a season 1 kkkk the oa tava esquecida no churrasco real]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I see the Nationals are offering Craig Kimbrel https://t.co/hVtoP4TADE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganRobertsMR @Topnotchmilfs @SEX_Overlord @TheAmateurArmy @kymsw12 @Lox_21 @thesexpedition @heinz_spack… https://t.co/gbCuCXhjt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I say that we must learn to realize love as a currency people think I'm talking about prostitution. I hate that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrissyBalls @TheSopranosClub @DEADLINE @immatureAMRCN (In Henry Hill voice): “Jimmy and Paulie weren’t happy with… https://t.co/gnlQUiSGJW]]></document><document><![CDATA['Cause I'm a ghost in training, Because my heart's been waning Because of all the shit I've been eating, I know one… https://t.co/b4jizgc86q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williechunderan I am a public school teacher but have nothing against homeschooling.  I have tutored many homescho… https://t.co/nuuIkm9VX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d do anything and everything for my family and friends that became family. Know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Old Smokehouse by @millstreambrew @ Lark Brewing — https://t.co/sEbClClUYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at One World Trade Center - @onewtc in New York, NY https://t.co/r7H3ssHrZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrStephenCQuinn @GoldenKnights It's only like 525600 minutes till the next game 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d0mocracy Lmfaooooo I never seen so many ppl get ON BOTH sides. Soooooo many ppl pulled up to agree lol and so many to defend it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @MarshallCohen Yes and this country is in shambles due to their treason. You can bet if this was the… https://t.co/7xIvYKQvv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just waking up to hear about the #EthiopianAirlines #PlaneCrash. So sad. :( #Travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t gone to see Captain Marvel you need to get your butt off the couch and watch it! Wow above and beyon… https://t.co/hiA85SjL7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, how did I not see this 🤯 #CaptainMavel https://t.co/GrqHlzqzVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing it all the way back to high school. Mr. Trusheim brought me in to do a sketch with him to entertain at a t… https://t.co/ByaoGEMhUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is my neighborhood just stopped me and asked if I’m a realtor because they saw my flyer #realtorlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a lot to cover today   Let's start off with the   Pledge of Allegiance 🇺🇸  Jim:  You want to start us off… https://t.co/Ec6nxXjEHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, my dad discovered that he can send me gifs through texts. It makes our conversations that much better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyearofelan We’re just trying to keep the “x” from feeling left out....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuluagajorge @mauroh06 @sampal66 @CalleCrispy Ahí usan unos pesos, que si entendí bien miden la habilidad y estima… https://t.co/P2JOeqtNnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalms 25:4-5: - Make your ways known to me, Lord ; teach me your paths.  Guide me in your truth and teach me, for… https://t.co/4JfbUGB8K9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @paladique for sharing the awesome URL:  vim​.dev   ... that apparently has everything and yet nothing to… https://t.co/mSC6VGf0Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my girls had our first date. We went to the Daddy Daughter Dance in Lawnside NJ last night. We really enjoye… https://t.co/8vobAVv6q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand And you allow New York City to be the most segregated schools in the country. You justify it saying… https://t.co/VwzSKIMAKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPetrides_ @naval Shifting your wants from status building to wealth generating 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise here folks. This has never been about evidence of a conspiracy. It's all about harrasment. This has bee… https://t.co/lEnvtqX3qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEADLINE Wow he got up and just left.. holy S! Well, he didn’t do the right thing after all did he? 🤬🤬😂😂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SCOTUS justices won't hear plea by Cosby accuser Catherine McKee to reinstate libel suit against imprisoned rapist… https://t.co/8Q69DWnyTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraviTroo won a free year of Creative Cloud at Flourish! #flourishmobile19 https://t.co/JLXsmXkalU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itspawlina it’s not a bad thing, you want someone you can enjoy looking at of course but it’s easy to be overlooke… https://t.co/gZ0AsTdxDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertAbooey @salgovernale Well Hello-Hello, Sal is fine, no need for a visit to HR.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillCallison Sounds like the United Methodist International conference this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX They make it sound like "gunfire" magically did this... moreover, the NRA caused ot to happen. So illogical it funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson WELL DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT . And then we can talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive Affirmation of the Day Today I am loyal and I express my loyalty in word and deed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s controversial move over border wall came after months of frustration https://t.co/uXdZa1porW via @BostonGlobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-dawn workouts and practices are counter-productive and can lead to injuries and poor performance in the short a… https://t.co/V2CMGOIbVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillWVNN She committed treason.  May God have mercy on her soul because Bama boys won’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cloudy Background☁️. en Facultad de Ciencias de la Comunicacion UANL https://t.co/18Vl8vtbOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haseebarien @Queeenash_ And if you want the membership for LA Fitness for the low low let me know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Met_CindyFitz Happy Meteorological Spring, Cindy! (Although winter isn't ready to give up without a fight). Stoneh… https://t.co/VGXxoBJFZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsteeze You should just explain the joke to her. I know a joke isn't funny after being explained, but it's been… https://t.co/TN4zqsYziy]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:45am - Hearing the rain outside is NOT helping my motivation today.  However, it being Friday IS my motivation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so much goodness-sign me up for that diabetes - Drinking an Imperial German Chocolate Cupcake Stout by… https://t.co/1AwPOjqciH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBStats @Braves @SFGiants @Pirates @Yankees @Reds @RedSox Roberto Clemente]]></document><document><![CDATA[recently started dabbling with making highlight videos, here's one for my maniac of a pal @kodyrice13 🍔🍟 https://t.co/tYN6jqZckZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew @LuckyChewy Lichtenberger Leads $200k GTD $5k 8-Max With 11 Remaining  https://t.co/OPCpFQcI1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[My two expressions while watching Abducted in Plain Sight https://t.co/G56MpproTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heydjnash Tonight’s show was absolutely incredible. Maggie and Gary are the most perfect couple on the program. Ma… https://t.co/gSz2xNUIaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it stills considered a sunset- When the streetlights have kicked on? ‘Better start kicking rocks home ASAP’  One… https://t.co/gUHHtByVVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between the @PotholesOfIndy and the traffic, I consider myself BLESSED to live AND work north of 96th street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo........ next election make sure you vote for James Miller for mayor!   HUGE changes coming your way! #IGotYall]]></document><document><![CDATA[My former colleague just asked me to be his best man. Wow, cheers that that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[pointandsalvage takes some awesome pictures.  This is @lesserglow from genosportland in December.  Come see us at… https://t.co/3EbbI3DtAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunnersResolve Yeah, either I’m a chess champion or 100 years old. Whatever! 🤪👊 Thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed that one I was there the year before with Winston Bennett. #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Ontario attorney general weighs in on SNC-Lavalin  affair https://t.co/mUUe3W3try via @YouTube]]></document></documents></author>