<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Erika: there’s a ran over cheetah here on the road. Me: a cheetah? In Forest Park? You sure?  Erika: yes!  Me: THAT CHEETAH PRINT SHIRT???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrbromwich Christine Ford imagined her crime, ergo no evidence, but ruin a man's character. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi you are losing control of the House.  They will run you out of the Speaker position.  Omar is a jihadis, loo… https://t.co/ac3JumCkKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 11 National Days Johnny Appleseed Worship of Tools Oatmeal Nut Waffles Promposal Funeral Director and Mortici… https://t.co/DmXvLUhWmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg Thank you, Mayor Bloomberg. Good luck in your endeavors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting things happening tomorrow @iamcardib @BrunoMars blessing us with the Please Me video at 10:05am   After th… https://t.co/7RvJFY1t9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for the sunset and watching dolphins 🐬❤️ @ Naples Fishing Pier https://t.co/glccNbJ3Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most precious acceptance speech I’ve ever heard. Genuinely so happy for her. #TheOscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BolsonaroSP @realDonaldTrump @jairbolsonaro Cachorro vira lata perebento e cheio de pulgas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldsun123 @NickielynnG @PaulLeeTicks @realDonaldTrump @RollingStone Tag teaming I see🥚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @LindseyGrahamSC Only a fool would go to a signing of a resolution and not have a clue what is offe… https://t.co/dt3nqI6AAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WC_Lions_Sports @DubCLions This is so unfair @AKSportsInfo should be ashamed of themselves calling the state and t… https://t.co/7YkoJZ3iG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Outnumber manafoert sentencing guidline were because of not going with mullers narative lack of cooperation not of… https://t.co/MDAfcKCLdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past month or two has caused so much anxiety in terms of my health and taking care of everyone. There’s a const… https://t.co/ZQuETnoVv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In matters of style, swim with the current; in matters of principle, stand like a rock. - Thomas Jefferson #missysquoteoftheday]]></document><document><![CDATA[IKEA’s “be the morning person you are not” ad campaign is ingenious  I want to be that N I want to do that via Scan… https://t.co/xWxwTpdihN]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd place out of 32 teams , super proud of all of us.💛💚#M3 https://t.co/S455cDzZd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lock Him Up!  You are a despicable person.  Shame on you!  #MakeAmericaGreatAgain]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sweethometdc #kellynamazesme! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ @ AmericasMart Atlanta https://t.co/ePCubUL75l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop watching this...  @Boii567 block, @DrewPember7 long quick pass and THEN @quesglover NASTY DUNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You people spent $40 million of my money on investigating Pres. Trump?! I want that money back, I wa… https://t.co/xfLRCROp8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WanderingwithAl @tajjackson3 @killerthrillerr @marigold1154 Oh the truth will bubble up about it if @tajjackson3 h… https://t.co/NS8TkqeWVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Willie700WLW Such a POWERFUL conversation @Willie700WLW.   Reminds me of the days of Marcus Feisel's horrific murd… https://t.co/bnbh9An4Ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiGi11317 @krishudsonwx @CampusTrailsMSU It is not annexed in and is in the County. The county has the funding but… https://t.co/uO9fTJnY3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there anyone who is NOT running for president on the democratic 2020 ticket?! 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danielle’s face... HORRIBLE. Yikes. #RHONJreunion #RHONJ #BRAVO https://t.co/J6xLO7Jczb]]></document><document><![CDATA[After having my friends edit one of my papers, I’m pretty sure I’m the only person who prefers Arial vs Times New Roman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teach_marietta @UnivWestGa The Lyons are two #UWG grads who #teachmarietta! 🎓💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[See?! I should delete this its stupid. I am and always will be dumb oblivious Scotty from Boogie Nights, 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis padres están viendo carros para comprar y ya yo estoy haciendo planes para irme de roadtrip con el carro nuevo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Rell have been binge watching Gotham every night 😂 never thought I’d get into it like that but it’s one of the top shows I’ve watched]]></document><document><![CDATA[And FRANKLY PAUL GOSAR, U R DOING A LOUSY JOB! We don’t need a wall! Go down to the Border or LINE, as u call it do… https://t.co/horE9QiC9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @JustFireDem @Tex_Ghost @RightOnT @USAFVet18 @cali_curmudgeon @grannyanon1969 @Intelligencia76… https://t.co/U0gFFBVe1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Postmates is actually garbage..my order is never right and I never get help afterwards even when the restaurant ag… https://t.co/hOrljm17rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[GoodEvening @DonnieWahlberg Can u please say a prayer for Mississippi,been through floodings and now a tornado last… https://t.co/FaccH14TQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think i’m the only person you know who will go to impulse while it’s snowing and eat shit on the balcony 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTorelli @BillSchulz @JoNosuchinsky @CompoundAmerica How fn adorable do these two look in this pic. It’s like… https://t.co/5GAlwTYMxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErnieBPhoto93 @westpointtbred Hes your main Derby horse? Theres been whispers that Gunny cant get the distance???]]></document><document><![CDATA[First.. the string is hilarious.. second, the photo and article are from 2015!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreygamer @wes_chu Russian doll was awesome too! I really binged that show, right through. 24 hours and it was done 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this Photo in so many ways ! Cheers to Flappers and Rainbows! #happy #love #funny @ Burbank, California https://t.co/fEsilhxFwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Oh he's definitely straight up psychiatrically incapacitated. He is nuts, no ifs, ands, or buts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That ass whooping gone hit different because she thought I forgot🤣😭🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe next time we stay at one of the tipis @VenturaRanchKOA @GoRVing #GoRVing #GRVingsponsored #FindYourWay… https://t.co/gqAz6m76Lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aIIhallows Of course I’m talking myself out of a vitamix but I think the nutrininja looks great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff is doing his due diligence and investigating where the leads take him. We elected 4… https://t.co/c8xCFaamMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Aurora: snow, 17°F 66% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1018mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechnyGal @kmani22 @DeManeDavis @maureenbonfante @kate_hammer @riaro @wise_browneyes @digitalcloudgal Happy #Galentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickChibbles @peterwarren That doesn't always work. Ideally you have guy fucking girl till last minute, pull out,… https://t.co/xZPs7XOFnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devin_J_Wallace He smacked the shit out of her and chased her out of the bathroom and then came and sat on my lap smug as shit. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder we’re open all week in Kensington, come check out our new space! #newcafe #phillybrunch #kensington… https://t.co/YhBdMmBpES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con las guapas Delyse Braun y La More el pasado Jueves✔️ @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/Y2fTVE2YxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This why me and her have a hard ass time being friends ... having male friends are better]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have said these things to you, that in me you may have peace. https://t.co/QK6y1E2GBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Knoxville School is closed for 2/20/19.  Get out and shovel and do some extra studying! https://t.co/aoDXlvoZ6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to tweet at the Construction Law Reception last night! But thank you to our sponsors of the event… https://t.co/atL5Vtzqn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best conversations with the sister.  #Goodtimes https://t.co/IahMBLAqLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For reals, my heart is just broken today. I try to be cognizant that I didn't know this person, not the real person… https://t.co/AuN0m6eJFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My LSDT Performers are amazing. Cool Aid: Another section. Coming to A Light Mix April 13th at CHAW! lightswitchdan… https://t.co/hzRgVVlYeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[LSU finally has a team since the 80’s that I really want to beat their ass. They are good. Don’t care if they win tonight. They can play]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im in the mood for buffalo chicken dip, sausage gravy and biscuits.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWF @yaledailynews Just report criminal behavior to the police. Dont make dossiers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brogantatexo Kudos to you! It’s a great accomplishment. I love your channel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally went to sleep at 3:40 and i’m back awake now. normal sleep schedule? never heard of her. 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad needed his very own UK wreath! #gocats💙 @ West Paducah, Kentucky https://t.co/VuPJX5wKuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationsFounder @finkrya @RealPitino @DukeMBB @UVAMensHoops “Engaging students through international travel opportu… https://t.co/WYusIUS8nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalinghausD It was so much fun. Really brought everyone together! Thank you Mr Fouard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a SPC is such a brown noser and continuously sucks up to every 1LT known to man. Bro shush]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like being woken up at 3 am by footsteps on your roof.. my 16 year old sister and I go to my living room to… https://t.co/lVCraLeGIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[VA Gov Ralph Northam is threatening the lives of newborns saying it would be up to the doctor and mother if that ch… https://t.co/x6XRKpyp3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[The UN human rights chief has warned of the threat posed by growing global inequality over income, wealth and acces… https://t.co/e4zJjcaf8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Kamala, you are such a fake!  Give up the grandstanding, chest beating, call-to-arms "do gooder" rout… https://t.co/z5Q0y6OdiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where's Emily Mills? It's getting crowded at the sold out #howshehustles event. #IWD2019 #toronto #Diversewomen… https://t.co/Z0aNrnKk2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hide nothing from the American People. This is what it is. Real life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fauldsca @OntariosDoctors @OntarioCollege I still don't understand what this means.  Can you clarify or provide an… https://t.co/POvTzqm4Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bless your heart! You are clueless! You have really shrank the Republican party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to my buddy High Pitch Erik for wearing one of the shirts I designed. ❤️ “I do it LIVE!” shirts are availabl… https://t.co/MuU8FzQesk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz That is more @DonnyDeutsch coaching #sigh. Biggest mistake made by Cohen was hiring the relentless cabl… https://t.co/btcfwIxuZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The groomsmen gasp at Seans new wedding ring at this virginia tech themed wedding!......thats cute would... #comedy… https://t.co/qCLFKYH3qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philosophrob @MikaSpencer Through the dollars to rubles exchange program?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how nice Klobuchar is or how she eats, because I’m pretty sure that the current POTUS has her beat in… https://t.co/7ZOJ0yq67V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimzolciak she does Kim want to have those huge lips. They aren’t very becoming on her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day to celebrate your birthday!  You’ve changed the culture of Adena and WE thank you! #wearelakota… https://t.co/iHWvSUkqVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Happy Thursday Day 21 of the #FebruaryChallenge to do my #Daily #Pullups everyday #JoinTheMovement to… https://t.co/GCawLxrA2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[i loooove love love reading the newspaper. does that qualify me for AARP?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Izzymabelll Yaaay I’m proud of us! I just bought my car straight cash so fuck it 🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna say I love going to work when I can see, but I can’t see cause it’s so foggy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonus #rainbow this afternoon. I’ve seen 4 rainbows in a day, but not all end to end like the 2 today. #lucky… https://t.co/3UfRGqxaBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasEDMFamily anyone wanna buy a boombox cartel ticket for tomorrow in Austin? Giving it away for 30$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dj_khardi .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different kinds… https://t.co/TDiqImq5VD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolomonRachel #SheInspiresMe You are a bad a$$ girl boss &amp; inspire me on the daily 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingkongus22 @NYIslanders Agree but Hickey can’t get back into the lineup unless someone goes.  Sbisa can go to Br… https://t.co/5dQRvnTfLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[omfg i hope i never have to take my nipple rings out again, it honestly took me 7 hours of failed try’s to get them bitches back in. FML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support the Hispanic Heritage Council of WNY, Inc. by coming to our annual breakfast fundraiser. 7th Annual… https://t.co/LZwzB3Jrbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[one day I’ll stop diving into taylor swift theories regarding her 7th album but that day is certainly not today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ken_kremer @BBCBreakfast @SpaceX @BBCNews @i24NEWS_EN @trtworld @TODAYshow @NASA You're Absolutely #Galactic my fr… https://t.co/E2ijSanUJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that you don’t but if I ask you if you love me I hope you lie to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @marybeth_evans1 may your day be as sweet as you are❤Thanks for always being such an inspiration to… https://t.co/8hkQAM1UNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinkPetro @randizuckerberg Loving this book! Thanks @randizuckerberg for sharing your motto. I’m ready try “this l… https://t.co/oo5u1fk6ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseAlexander Bro I saw this and was gonna tag you in it..why can I see you doing this to a kid😂]]></document></documents></author>