<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When you meet someone with challenges who doesn’t take one single day for granted and uses his energy to stay healt… https://t.co/ESLGIWFIkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okok I admit, #aries are territorial ass bitches . Don’t want to say jealous bc that’s just a different meaning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Just got home from a University of Tennessee baseball win! Locked up and watching North Woods Law! #9PMRoutine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stomp and Read at North Creek! @NorthCreekElem #MarchisReadingMonth https://t.co/zQrqWeMhuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMightyWeasel @frankassubc timely for your discussion tmr on #flexGC !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually have a co worker who thinks ...”they deserve it!”   Left me stunned and speechless.  What the hell are t… https://t.co/belU2GzCmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GitLitHit While we do absolutely nothing!! Really you must not watch new laws coming out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Heart Day! The greatest LOVE you can give is to yourself! Be kind and gentle to yourself today!… https://t.co/wA2q8c2c56]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to remind myself that it’s OK to miss the memory of who you used to be as long as I know that’s not who you are anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulineGraphics @HoarseWisperer Woo hoo! Love hockey! Been watching my hubby #RickTheGoalie play since, we’ll neve… https://t.co/BKZw4f1TGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of one-week book cover challenge by @ThomasJaxTampa: Post a cover a day of a book meaningful to me. No commen… https://t.co/5egeVNZ2h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hauntedmuseum watching artifacts.  Dang some of these the emotions hit you bad.  Love the show but some wow are hard to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so Bri and I are at the theater watching Captain Marvel and the movie ended and Bri started to get up to leave... I… https://t.co/72TfYZhM4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working Saturday Checklist: 1️⃣ Harry Potter playing 2️⃣ Halsted cuddles 3️⃣ Coffee brewed {and delicious} 4️⃣ Logg… https://t.co/pPUsHXF4ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the Jonas brothers are reunited.. Can One Direction stop playing and also reunite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BJ_Hodg All day. Ever day. Live and breath by this statement: Marlowe before Blooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#slatt🐍🐍 #slatttt #slime #ImHim #IBeenThat #PoDilly #slatt🔥 talk dat fake slat shit... If y'all want to... I'mma be… https://t.co/Gdt71MDy9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTARadioSports @CoachGerlich @utasbea Made them special for @CoachGerlich and i didn’t even know it! 🤷🏻‍♀️👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @Wendys likes this I will finish the laundry, take a shower and go to bed early.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParadisoPresent @TroyThompson23 @Carol_Cole @cbellwall @DaniKimble2 Thanks have a great one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @HuffPostPol So inhumane. Just despicable, Trump and his heartless minions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The goals of #livingwealthy workshop started with Jeff Tomasulo, Steven Sitkowski and while waiting the famous shar… https://t.co/E5vv12GwES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Period. End of Sentence., a film about the stigma around periods in India, won the best short documentary Oscar. ”I… https://t.co/SYtCbbPH8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximusupinNYc @EmpireStateBldg @Barbie @Mattel @nycgov @nycgo @nycfeelings @brooklynheights 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scitch8 @CardinalDolan Read the Bible study in a book or cell just read n compare Jesus words w “ do not call anyo… https://t.co/RTOqVshT78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is around the corner! Buds on the blueberry bush!  #pnw #vanwa #inmygarden #blueberries #bluesky https://t.co/GtaeNtY1ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only do you have to be as amazing as me, but now you have to be as cute and talented as Brendon Urie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be so focused on the plan, that you lose sight of the purpose! - Dr. Cheryl Smith (@drcrsmith)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The research is out there, teachers! We need to advocate for #Bilingualism and educate those who continue living un… https://t.co/MvPOWkB2vT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGT Congrats Shin Lim! Hope you will have the same lasting success as past BGT winners Collabro, with 4 CDs, and s… https://t.co/jmCBHMzkmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarinaDiamandis will I ever be able to listen to lonely hearts club via Spotify or iTunes?  Also soy excited for the new music 💕💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman Andrea Colavito scores her first career goal, and Liberty leads 11-1 with 8:32 left in the opening half!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody What a beautiful blessing to have a beloved dog as part of your family! Enjoy every day you have with him!🐕🐕🐶🐶💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight!!!!!! @AmericanIdol @LukeBryanOnline #AmericanIdol #LukeBryan https://t.co/EMTL6CdKii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escape the ordinary!! 🦋 🦋  **Come join us at @aileyextension for BellydanceBURN at 6:30pm THURSDAY!  No prior dance… https://t.co/ofgNaDBxc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snifflesnack At this point in recovery you should be hitting a meeting every day. In my first 90 days I often went… https://t.co/KGfYyHO8k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryknews @janamakesgames @kchironis @chrissyteigen Tried this too, still working on figuring out if it's my "thin… https://t.co/IjwYiET20i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@risquerebecca I’m so sorry that someone completely disregard your experience. I hope you’re okay ♥️ I’m sorry that… https://t.co/xY0QCinnT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Former KKK leader praises #TraitorTrump  1 of many https://t.co/jiSx8AP50e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Classact1979 @doritkemsley1 @lisarinna Just ask other people who Rinna has eviscerated while trying to take them d… https://t.co/xMtJIPr1rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaMKenny3 No! I hadn't heard. If those countries fall for it, money in his pocket.  But it sounds like he is t… https://t.co/etz5iNNgE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off #WomensHistoryMonth by visiting #MaryChurchTerrell (the @ObieLib traveling exhibition) at the College o… https://t.co/avP9IGePj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, obviously, after you order enough fried chicken for four people, you order #tresleches #buttercake because… https://t.co/vzldRBopp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last request is... Help us get One Day At a Time renewed!  This show will helps a lot of people.  If you can, wa… https://t.co/V9Vn4F0jLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn: because i had you is not on the set list  Fans: “We’re leaving”             “I’m offended”  Me: should i sel… https://t.co/d6PCoXyAuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌇 Sunsets 🌅 The lives that have passed through over the years - inside these buildings🏙, their stories and our stor… https://t.co/TZE6eOIOJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the cancel signs not work on top of literally any other emoji besides the rainbow flag though I’m-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iammarkobabic @LazicMilorad There you go -- quintessential. Hvala puno!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magicalmsmurphy @edutopia Really awesome idea!!!  Thanks for sharing ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody all aboard! #everydayadventureswithcillian #myloves❤️ #mommyslove❤️… https://t.co/nRVfUSH7lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that people are still supporting this fool is mind blowing, nauseating almost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my best bitcccchhh🤪 love you so much, hope you have a great day 💛 https://t.co/9zFri7KCop]]></document><document><![CDATA[When rules are fair and consistent.....You wouldn’t have to ask a child, if they think they can do anything....Chil… https://t.co/erKE0duOPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisbwright K A L E I D O S C O P E: offering free analog creative sanctuaries dedicated to the refusion of a fr… https://t.co/o43nx9Lk0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I couldn’t feel any more strongly about this than I already did.  But now that I’m a faculty member, the… https://t.co/L28S29JFAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dreams and reality are opposites. Action synthesizes them.” -Assata Shakur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Hillary they are thinking that voters will just vote for any dems candidates because everyone hates pres trump… https://t.co/RcVr86AAQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#URGENTE Presidente encargado Juan Guaidó @jguaido es recibido en Cúcuta 🇨🇴 por presidente Iván Duque.… https://t.co/5G4eco4UpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland People choosing not to vaccinate have become a global health threat in 2019, the World Health Organization reported.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might sound rude AF but I’m tired of people asking me how my job is going 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[NHCD presentation @ 2/12 #ATXCouncil Housing Committee: In New/Expanded Programs/Services section I noticed contrac… https://t.co/qHYZI3368l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyThriller69 Do you think Democrats care? At least Trump is opening jobs for minority. That's a step forward. It… https://t.co/OPo1hZ28qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golds gym yogis thank you for making weird shapes with me for almost 5 years. My last class will be March 19th whic… https://t.co/y4PlM4qhxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @TheIncredibles2 for the first time (yes, the first time, don’t judge me I’m a busy lady) but I just h… https://t.co/ghkujWTl2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone recommend me a new show or movie to watch pls https://t.co/7hjBp4l4FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamondslil @79Aspen Ok thanx so much!!! I'll be attending either the one in Ohio for which I live in or the one in Michigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmexreece woodstock 50 is in watkins glen, ny (actual location is unannounced) and the cultural festival is at th… https://t.co/z7ugCBhAkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try again, @Ally 😡  https://t.co/VQWBpC0E4G by @MatPatGT #Theft #CorporateGreed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AlaskaAir. I get weather cancellations r no skin off your nose but seriously? U can't b bothered 2 get us on a… https://t.co/dTttTiAMTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddSte76200730 No, I don't post everything. Honestly, a lot of it only makes sense in context and the money slides are dated every year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It happens WAY too often that spotify doesn't have the album I'm looking for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful resort for conference and birthday weekend. https://t.co/tQbKqZKtK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurasgoldman @KellieAnn_W @Televerde We’ve been around since 1995. 3,000 women have been through our program. 6%… https://t.co/XRsLKs3VSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if you wear the wrong T-shirt? | The 35 Hardest Things About Taking A Picture... https://t.co/U4Dwz2xXvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#T3Learns with @pwharris being more efficient than the algorithm... https://t.co/1AQddCL4ZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for the @TexasBaseball home opener! #HookEm #FormerSIDstudents #CamoKoozies 🤘 https://t.co/5cIiIaxjbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to share that our friend Paige is 💯% cancer free!!! Best news ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#crabtrap #somerspoint #oceancitybridge #oceancity across the waterway. Fresh #seafood #lobstertail… https://t.co/sovgR8E6Ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expansive places grant the most room for boundless, open thought. Surely Death Valley is where Writer’s Block comes to die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByJasonGonzales Those people are not allowed in my house. https://t.co/aCbWiRoo4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 had his whole life ruined because of @POTUS.  I hope the rest of us fair better, but it’s not looking good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄WINTER CLEARANCE!❄ I don't know if it will ever be warm again, but I do know that all yellow dotted winter shoes a… https://t.co/MIHWhNydjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the sun came up yesterday morning   #moonsetting #moon #moonset #carlsbad #carlsbadcliffs #calm #california… https://t.co/VwrGZMxBEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to joining #APSA2019 tomorrow, speaking on the importance of advocating for international humanitar… https://t.co/2H9J4P8COn]]></document><document><![CDATA[RECORD LABEL 56 IS AN UNDERGROUND RECORDING LABEL THAT PRODUCES HATE MUSIC WHICH NEEDS TO BE BANNED FROM RECORDING… https://t.co/KjGvHO99gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyStancil No, we don't have access. I did see the big orange cables being installed across the street. Who know… https://t.co/NjBhbT998w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dicledach @fperaza @rogerwaters Please seat to study the last 20 years of history in Venezuela.. and then you will edit your tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gerald Butts about to testify before the Justice Committee and hopefully shed light on the missing half of the stor… https://t.co/MCIOoUHG7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardSaiz4 @brirodriguez29 @morales0212alex @BriOlvera ^ real nigga speaking facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those in the @GOP and over at @foxandfriends who continue to bash @AOC because she’s “only” 29 and used to be a… https://t.co/rvCQU5ppAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pitchatpalace Young entrepreneurs in Bahrain don't miss your shot to shine...complete your app today!!!!  And good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Just A Bread Win.... you get it @ Broward Estates, Lauderhill, Florida https://t.co/OjpfxJb6se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinGunderman @SenatorFlowers I am a fan now too.  This woman cares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writerchickmc I had this at Eataly a few years back and since I’ve adapted healthier eating habits I wanted to try… https://t.co/ooHAAABMmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @jlheelan Let’s not forget HARD LABOR at a Penitentiary of The People’s Choice.  I’ll most assuredly vo… https://t.co/XB4CXXNz4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah. @AOC brings out one of the ~most awkward and unrecorded~ moments of the shutdown. It was pure tension on the fl… https://t.co/8FFVJ0048v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other presidents even found it funny. Is it possibly because you have to be emotionally mature and mentally stable… https://t.co/QCybZNKltf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeannine_3 @maydaymindy9 No, the other one on Pt. Washington. I guess it’s long gone now. We used to go to the one… https://t.co/u7VDTWYRBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay ranting: You turn out queer in hs, then have(absence) of balls to terrorize me? - No thank you I am not angry,… https://t.co/CucuFuIgqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Somebunny” visited a Kindergarten classroom at Jim Darcy today. Luckily the snow drift was high enough and the vis… https://t.co/DaiX7uqlBH]]></document></documents></author>