<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@randyebert @PaulMcCartney @ringostarrmusic @TheMickyDolenz1 @thebeatles @TheMonkees Supergroup opportunity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaissieLevy Does this apply to non equity as well because I am seeing one tomorrow? Will there be buckets there? Hmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny how liberals are the ones called snowflakes when republicans throw a temper tantrum bc of what happened at pe… https://t.co/q8MRiH5YgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im sorry if you not watching Mob Psycho 100 you really lacking as a anime fan right now because this anime is ONLY… https://t.co/4E3AAUkkv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheresaLarkin9 @ECHOtheCALL @DeborahODell6 Oops should have known, just seen what she said and I lost control 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio Hey Amy! I'm with you when it comes to most mint food products but I do make an exception when it comes… https://t.co/LZn1ETrHZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neither rain or wind or floods deter these redesign focused educators from looking at many options to do things dif… https://t.co/vhkIukjdUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zekNcashe To the leg?!?!?? 😂 love moms but she gone have to take the bullet https://t.co/y5xnMfCbpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@402meg Are they from out of town? I was kinda hoping Omahans would be smart enough to vaccinate their children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram… https://t.co/VMhxss47oD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenafrumes @TMobile It is. I was on all 7 continents this year and @TMobile crushed @WorldMarathon77 @JohnLegere]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m calling it... fasten your seatbelts for #DubCon3 @JoeFortenbaugh https://t.co/Q95WrudJyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthem just locked up on me again. I hope this wont be a common occurance that I'll deal with everytime I play the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pulse1000 I said the same shit. Everyone be geeked To get their luggage after a flight and dip if I saw this coming out I’d be deadddd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump WTF She is in charge of Americans future ?You are all fucked over there if this is true]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help get this movie’s distribution funded. Got to meet the two amazing people behind it last night.… https://t.co/hbmcackhh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What I don't understand is why they drill down into your life and why they don't drill down into… https://t.co/283ilmdt6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEARKDaniel @WEARLauraHussey @wxkaitlin @WEARJared @weartv So good to see you all!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusWasARebel2 @HtownDood Bullshit response to a bullshit response. The oligarchy is STILL sitting on the profits… https://t.co/ulfXsDSYKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pastordhughes w a great word this wknd on 1 Peter 2:9 about your definition and your destiny! Catch the 6:30 servi… https://t.co/j1hY2gmMNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOXRoundtable Bring Dennis Miller back mnf is already a joke might as well throw a comedian in there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenCohan Love Whiskey Cavalier. Both you and Scott Foley are great. I’ve gone ahead and set my TV to record the… https://t.co/qrKmxHaF91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I drink fancy cocktails in the Vault... @ Vault https://t.co/QKWQR5Wjy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need a name for ourselves.  If they call us Socialists - which they always will.  Then what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence A great idea. Easier to get volunteers at polling places.  Frees up people to assist others to vote.   #electiondayholiday]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Power of a Story with Susan Fowler #sxsw (@ ACC - Ballroom D in Austin, TX) https://t.co/wLpocGm3tM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actionhankbeard Lolol sounds good to me. I’ll hunt one down ☺️ Thanks for the lead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then people tried to say he looked like me. That was a stressful time https://t.co/CWJf5mlfWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event Photography @allswagga #KennyBeanPhotography #Photography #Nikon #ATLANTAMODEL #PhotoShoot #NewYorkModels… https://t.co/7ERe170J3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the red stretch I marked.  The west side of Eau Claire is being paralyzed by this blizzard. https://t.co/XZlRgZs2as]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tannerguzy Where's my leather bomber jacket and stone-washed jeans?! My country needs me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[had an awesome day of networking!! #ScrippsPRSSAtoCHI https://t.co/1tr8l9MI2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbcrosscountry @MattDValenti @ccicanine Their mainstream. Their paratransit arm, so far as I’ve experienced is jus… https://t.co/8YE2BLI3Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be so great if I was a sociopath. Just focused on me and that’s it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually kinda like this one guy but then I just don’t know cause like they’re always so wild when it comes to me👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed @karaswisher and @profgalloway's live podcast yesterday at #SXSW. Especially the interaction with th… https://t.co/R0qbpB5sGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter Don’t worry, he’ll make it all back in endorsements in NYC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's surprising that Schiff is in office, who vote 4 this guy? He must have campaigned - most likely a lot of money… https://t.co/DZNAHTSWo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xiggy89x Plan is to develop from within. Fill in holes and re-sign your own players. Free-agency comes only in addition to that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbdsoundsystem Michelle I have a theory that you deliberately use the iPad to tweet so you can type slower and the… https://t.co/0KP68vOmzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Running against females is the only way he could ever win...loser all the way around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeyBees_ @devarsh_8 @jeskeets LeBron lacks finesse when he dunks, he's more of a power guy. Not good for today's contests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this a “woke” moment?  I could poke more fun here, but instead I’ll just say I’m happy she tweeted this and that… https://t.co/BWSZyjrmMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The over-analytic shithead believers on this app and in general are the worst...the worst in every which way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, but every night. @ Manhattan Beach, California https://t.co/XNdegBdTS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WinterJam360 was an awesome experience! But the best performance by far was my 5 year old daughter singing “What A… https://t.co/o2AYyoNzEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks, @BestWestern, for the helpful bed in the "handicapped accessible" room my friend booked https://t.co/hYlBi9ayB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Competencia de habilidades🤪🤪🤪 en Lawrence, Massachusetts https://t.co/dqv4fuBnk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ravens might as well keep cleaning house and send Harbaugh and Tucker somewhere. Maybe start with decosta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Don’t govern, take your orders from Soros instead. Worthless 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fuck Ornstein and Smough were tough. Only lucked out cuz I used my humanity for healing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga @VanityFair So proud of you and the blessing your music from this movie has been!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoorHardwareLux @ShiCooks @NantucketGal @lawyer1mom @Rubybeets @brendaslynn @Seaglass67 @amosedale @dempsterbeach… https://t.co/SnnJdQ9PDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's an opening suggestion: Remove any and all family members from the board of directors if they're directly inv… https://t.co/wetWEBZmNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradSibole @HawleyMO @USSenate Didn't learn anything from the #GOPTaxScam either]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DumpSquad waiting for my Sub from JettsMachine like... https://t.co/7uTB1pgNFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley clinging on to 53-51 lead with 31.9 seconds left. Darrell Brown called for a traveling violation in previou… https://t.co/b8SsbzjS6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonTexans @CFL_PR @CEYHomelessness @JCITexas @jcidublin @HomeDepotRetool @OFIDnews @irishhockey @NotreDameSWD… https://t.co/021PdbFOpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody wants to go to a restaurant where a server acts like that. Period. Any respectable GM would want to know tha… https://t.co/FeaZzQ3Rla]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eBikeThoughts Surly launches its first #eBike: The Big Easy. I agree with the article that being priced $2850 over… https://t.co/6QnT98BAgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th Match Prediction: @WWEDanielBryan retains the #WWEHempTitle #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[I plan to be at the Canton Memorial Civic Center to see @BoysTallmadge in the Canton Division II district final Sat… https://t.co/zYcPThErqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My apologies for the above tweet. Coach's answer started about Monday night's game but then altered into incomplete… https://t.co/JkFNUTT6Nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulTBiondich @tfcacademy @BMO @Breaking_Lines @VictorSatei @terry_dunfield @MarcoCasa7 Well desvered bud..this is… https://t.co/17N44tc9FR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HackswithHaggs Kane means the punch from behind was no big deal 🤷🏻‍♂️ ....And btw they’ll fight again. When do the… https://t.co/JJnK7XnJMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteOfTheMoment @AdamSchefter The better comment is that he would have a ring by now if he had a QB after Warner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamEdwards @theblaze Joe’s Kansas City Barbeque. (Out of a gas station)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to preach 3 English services at @gracecov (for obvious reasons Ps @FullerLifeToday did not sked me at Spanish &amp; Korean services)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahCRothman Overpopulation myth historically is about lack of resources.The overpopulation issue clashes with cli… https://t.co/bf7pJBZgK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @rrheisler for sharing your story and your loss too. May your son’s memory continue to be for a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell this account is run by a girl cause it keeps bringing up old shit..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lake county commissioners voting today on if Treasure Island Range meets county zoning regulations and should stay… https://t.co/2FNvztMgco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought things couldn’t get sillier, @folioweekly proves me wrong. Again. #jaxpol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich @benshapiro Maybe our only hope is a Designated Survivor scenario.  These ads clowns only serve themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mental toughness doesn’t form over night. To callus the mind, you must endure pain and fatigue. When things are dem… https://t.co/DW3G5Oezel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump FAKE NEWS!!!!  HES BEEN ON THE JOB FOR 5 DAYS JACKASS.    BUILD THAT WALL!!! https://t.co/pZ1jafm8Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joegooding @Trump454545 @donlemon @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @PatriotJenn @IamMonicaRae @ChristieC733 @jjauthor… https://t.co/YjvwhoHRkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bandit 6, Scout 6....contact, dismounts and PCs, North, engaging, out” - me, for a while, as we head over the berm… https://t.co/48IHevHI69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_woods15 FYI- they still have JG Pageau. The turnover has been fast and furious of late]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, I LOVE my waltdisneyworld. Especially the #MagicKingdom, but Disneyland’s version of #PiratesOfTheCaribbean is… https://t.co/hCK9GgkgmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sedaalyn It's a good thing because my paycheck from my job is PHAT plus my income tax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday #sunrise from Coconut Grove in beautiful @MiamiandBeaches #FoundinMiami https://t.co/p565Ghr160]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @MichaelCohen212 @RepAdamSchiff INVESTIGATE THE INVESTIGATORS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is better that the Watergate hearing Michael Cohen Testifies Before House Oversight Committee Michael Cohen, P… https://t.co/ConG2Gl5mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite being legal, I just can’t imagine either my Mother or hers, if they were alive today, cooking with… https://t.co/mMcWIs74mG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andresills373 I’ll break the legs of the suckers who poke some eyes out! 👊🏾😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think your environment is your problem, you won’t esteem grace, but once you admit that you’re your biggest… https://t.co/D58wyF8LhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/LOUFI8mz67]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't want to start thinking about myself. IN A GAME FOR $100,000, YOU DON'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT YOURSELF?????… https://t.co/EH7GKnJOSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is within your power, and your power is within you.... https://t.co/bMH6LWPFX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[take time to smirk. pon and zi | pon and zi (66) | claudiaciuta #comedy #giggle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/bsQNcbxxXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFSculpts Also this obviously isn’t the original lineup from the cartoon but I had a fun story idea that involves… https://t.co/55eEgL82r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave__Ocean @andyholloway Lmao it's part of his job to talk about it. Why are you so angry? Miss one too many hugs… https://t.co/rx4KAht2DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoked his last L with me before he left the ville 4 years ago, never forget that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Tell them to pay the tax payers back that could be used for more border protection and security dr… https://t.co/j0o97CET43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just found an H-1 engine from the Saturn  just laying around in a junkyard. https://t.co/YBrhHs5y8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I had to bring my daughter to the ER cause she hurt her wrist , the PA’s name is Dragon 😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flexibledragnet @AlbertaNuclear @EnergyJvd @mtaylor_nz Nuclear capacity factor -90% Solar capacity  factor -25%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe and @morningmika Why do y’all avoid mentioning #Palestine and #Israel? The Palestinians are being just… https://t.co/C2CycuVc1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Factsssss but once u use a legit solid indoor hoop you’re wetter than steph curry]]></document></documents></author>