<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dumpstercryptid @NOBLEjerky @TheGoose50 @consciousmuscle (It’s a vegan jerky company)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nzamora86 @MikeChambers Ah perfect. Thanks everyone. I've been posting to that podcast and seeing the cover art was driving me crazy. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAndyHarrisMD Trump is abusing power again and @RepAndyHarrisMD is helping, by condoning grabbing money from our… https://t.co/LmMf7sFDaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures of adoptable cats at Heartland Humane Society today (2/23/2019), an animal shelter in Corvallis, OR! @ Hea… https://t.co/Ix8rMxfgVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGViews Always are Us this way is 1 happy song I like to see you happy makes me happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💕 ¡A quererse todo el mundo! @pinatafactory_ @leonardovans_ https://t.co/TaeKgdjwSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion @JedediahSPurdy Dems have the legislative agenda right but do not have political power to get it done u… https://t.co/vQjAbJFBlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AubreyWright3 @mrjdub23 I hope that was the finish if not it would have been lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greyfaguette Silky also called that Sara woman a racist so there is a clear disconnect lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WYEP @elks339 I've had enough by The Who off of quadrophenia. The song that made me fall in love with banjo. (Subs… https://t.co/Ob5hYiGPD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será prudente empezar a gritar?? Aplica para el municipio, estado y país]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gnight peeps! #skyscrapernationalpark @ Bryant Park https://t.co/MA1PEkoXDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REPUTAYYYY13 @taylorswift13 I think you will look great either way so do what makes you feel happy 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajaja se están pasando de pendejos. Lo digo por los signos de exclamación mal empleados jajajaja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely a good squad but let’s neglect that soon-to-be bare system. Still, money is nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cgodoysalfatte @BoseOfficial Todo segun sea dictado por el Pais en el Norte del continente, es como se perciben la… https://t.co/55dJjOz7hV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malbeckford So you’re calling me out for calling out a liar who manipulated and betrayed your trust?🤔 I hope you’r… https://t.co/ntEvFYRtX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaplinOfficial @PhilharmonieLux @CarlDavisMusic @CityLuxembourg I don’t have a problem with this, but the Chaplin… https://t.co/BuXvZTd91U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @DelPercioS @DonnyDeutsch Ever since Reagan, 1980’s, the country has shifted right—to finally bring us… https://t.co/OiBs0LJ5Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correcting Your Grammar is a digital print from The Artwork Factory that celebrates a small dose... #comedy #tee-he… https://t.co/Y2kztIRxih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the best we could get from a so called President on #PresidentsDay How lower can he go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Falk free agency, the draft, and training camp has me on Twitter 24/7]]></document><document><![CDATA[open this up to you all. Thanks again for all of your support these 2 full years. Looking forward to your thoughts and questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @Someone71927696 @chucksart3 @luluHru @RPowell2011 @Lexa_Merica @CentsMy3 @Sissy4Trump @yoakumgirl923… https://t.co/0IU7sD98hK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shalfanonzo you should be able to upgrade your laptops RAM, there should be a slot on the very bottom (if it's not an older laptop)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Porter Ranch Town Center in Porter Ranch, CA https://t.co/F5twCWZjza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodywatley My first acting job in LA, was “ Most Of All” video!  You were VERY SWEET!   I’ll never forget how down to earth you were.😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllVape3 @Raymosaki @cannaworldsite @Bklynbby @Smokette_ @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @james_bong13 @_jena4n… https://t.co/w2HqdaY1Qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my last tweet before the election in  2020. watch who wins. ...James Woods can't vote in Florida nor can Ch… https://t.co/SkSxpquNkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[There has never been and there never will be a bug free countdown timer for use on websites.   I swear if you know… https://t.co/rL3gZbDeEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not always have enough free time, but when I do . . . I might be thinking about; Industry Study: Nanotechnolog… https://t.co/xtVD6Osb9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[But yet your posting about how you use to post about your feelings??? Hmmm 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #EdenPrairie, MN job and click to apply: Sr Business Systems Analyst (Oracle Finance) - https://t.co/fBNiBEsOPE #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda of want to watch the Kakuzu and Hidan arc in Naruto again. Just to watch Shikamaru go through all of it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomson72419298 Don't Think you'll Find a SERIOUS Relationship Here? But, Join this REVIVAL of the ROTARYWING! Finally a GREEN Version!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mc_Driver @ISMRaceway “Had to get my ass dropped by Suarez through traffic” doesn’t have the same ring to it, I’ll admit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time something goes upside down for Trump - i.e. finding himself and Republicans lining up with a spa owner..… https://t.co/EP6HnV26Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen y'all I have no shame talking about this boy I'll say just about anything but his name lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[INE piece more...  #catherineclassic #gaming #gamestagram  #gallery #gamingsetup en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/MT7izflB8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniCal1f0rn1a @awonderland We are a little obsessed I think. It’s cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe what you want😖 Most morons do. Doesn’t matter if your right or wrong.  Have you heard about “The Sermon on… https://t.co/G35yhyzZw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masonda94886873 @DeplorableChoir Love those ladies. I believe that this person - who posted the picture - has crea… https://t.co/KtyF6v4yEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the students (and parents) from @FairwoodExplore for stopping by the Capitol to chat, and for your GREAT… https://t.co/wS1yXF2Xvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a lying piece of shit and nothing but a Muslim trader troublemaker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actually your peeps are not very smart. They continue to lose money,civil rights,healthcare and a good education.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorite bits from today's #MardiGras parade. @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/dKvoDUrlk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last day on the hill. Friday morning Lifeaholik Gondola report. Y'all better get that Lifeaholik Yoga in your l… https://t.co/MezN616yXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CecileLavas @bgirl0001 @LisaMar91564392 @JustinTrudeau More questions in the coming weeks, and we know how he hate… https://t.co/IywLjttKPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hallofchristian @X929 Not much of a better system than here. Well, still better than here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryzo_0451 @GailSimone Bono has glaucoma. It’s why he has to wear dark sunglasses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to hold local governments liable. Why do they get federal funding for this hatred? SEE SOMETHING, SAY SOM… https://t.co/O3LEsXKcbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this praise for a white dude but when Wayne did it for Nicki y’all was silent.... okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcflanery @ryanstruyk @jaketapper @CNN @DMRegister Lost 1984, 1988, 2008.... https://t.co/a1tFd4V6Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[if yall support dat nba whiteboy kid yall might as well unfollow me yall show me more n more this all jus a joke to… https://t.co/0Ab7PisiTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeeToThe Drinking too much Tampico is the reason why I can gargle peanut butter lmao. I’m not new to this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I agree. You must be a verified American citizen to vote in our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realandrewblock @sebastianbach @OfficialSkidRow @sNAKEsABO @rbolanbass @ScottiHill Yep. That’s what I said. You’re… https://t.co/rJ1s34b2iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraborondo @quimicefa @Narbiz "Pepperidge Farm SE ACUERDA" https://t.co/dqyYNkLI2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triscoe @MikeKoppens Hmm, glad that's not in the song.... https://t.co/u8AL2whzfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karen_hair Hombre... No tenemos cambios emocionales cada hora jajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. Who gives a shit about Robert kraft getting a handy.                   IOWA FIRED DOLPH!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein You fool. You’re saying that this has gone on for DECADES!  After that many years of illegal crossing… https://t.co/Cuyb3BjDFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeMillerTech @stickermule LOVE the peanut butter one! lol https://t.co/aGAIRF2oy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our demons got things to do. But that’s okay, take it, reverse it, and then make them work for you.”  Conversations // @judahandthelion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunAlex87 Amazingly, “Chinese food” is one type a food that is different in every country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the performance of Lamar Jackson, I’m really not surprised Baltimore will be trading Joe Flacco to Denver. #Ravens #Broncos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dee_levingston4 @Peter_ToshJR @air_hardy1 @humblefaitfocus @AlmightySmoove 🙅🏾‍♂️🤐 https://t.co/E8nGXDt6Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustincary @MonsterJam I am not. Needed a break. Last weekend was crazy busy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past and future don't affect me because I'm focused on the present.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PagePhysics @MissStrunk I used to teach such free-wheeling physics through to the end of the 1990s. Then we were d… https://t.co/smf5Gq63xH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in okc is there a Chick Fil A and a strip club right next to each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fired for having integrity, and telling the truth. This is extremely troubling. #onpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collinc32 @ChrisClarkNFL Thank you I could not remember the name their show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiversCuomo I’d have to fly there, or take a very long drive. Might be fun though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see @CodyZeller succeed. The thing is, he is an even better person than he is a b-ball player. @rick_bonnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeanwyllys_real Ouvi dizer q seu cuspe tem cheiro de candida (agua sanitária)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BreitbartNews The Dems have a problem.  Yes Republicans took money but they weren't committing stupid… https://t.co/MkS1hd9KpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImabitcSumtimes @Manuel39503599 @CaliRN619 @Sequencer16 @GeanineC @OutOfRegister @Tombstone1954 @CensoredC1… https://t.co/z0D0NmgBtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sorting continues, making will resume sometime this week! #art #artlife #maker #makerlife #studio #cleaning… https://t.co/F83AFNBPo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenleeKali @rachelslathar Heck yeah, had a job offer there 2 weeks ago welding 🤙🏼🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton @DineshDSouza So you want the Democrats to keep lies and cheat to get in power what's new they been che… https://t.co/ttlrAvop9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a peak inside our war room where our amazing students and fearless leader, @UCApresdavis are calling to thank… https://t.co/QW2WORP194]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to tell you are short-----&gt;when 3/4 pants are full length on you lmao @ La Fitness https://t.co/C0qZif8tCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheRicciAdventure Part 2✨ Y así, de repente, cumples el sueño que llevas esperando realizar toda tu vida: conocer… https://t.co/xCvGcvBzaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WindingDot Mine is like 15 years old (cbj fan) who followed me so I guess it’s not surprising]]></document><document><![CDATA[CORRECTION: Quarterfinal game between Canjo and Hoosick Falls. Little bit scatterbrained tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicj9311 @toknow420 @thehill Brother I know exactly what you mean. I hate Trump so much more each day it hurts. I… https://t.co/0zr1kFhYKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myself and coach @SpencerW15 were literally just talking about this guy and his actions this morning. Then we go on… https://t.co/L7apzLeXwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me vine a leer las cartas y que según voy a empezar una relación pronto con una mujer blanca pero va a haber riesgo… https://t.co/xDsBu7zPh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvarezMaynez @gigiowifi Ese ejército será adoctrinado o comprada su conciencia para en el futuro darte palo #Mexico]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otto. #doctoroctopus #marvelart #MARVELFANSUNITED https://t.co/oSI5JdeODo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetsyyyXo I would argue that’s a good thing. Right now the ONLY reason we are not being fully challenged by other… https://t.co/3EWYc0hgCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeMeetsCars @GribWrites They haven’t met since they created The Fellowship of The Rims!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtNeverest @Buick They legit are no longer old people cars... As someone with some GM exposure growing up, the Bui… https://t.co/DlIxp9jNl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fitz’s annual Gala: A Night at the Fair, May 4 https://t.co/5qTEwFdIlB https://t.co/o9OdeWSdTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenKts11 Thanks, today hasn't started off overly promising and knowing what I have to get done today means off t… https://t.co/2Xfp2AjVL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps you'll think before you say that God is dead and gone Open your eyes, just realize that he's the one The on… https://t.co/vz9xSRwD1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@relisberg I read this batshit crazy lady’s comments and being batshit crazy, she blames the Girl Scouts for the ba… https://t.co/aF7SlGDA5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodguys #loyalgirls #bedroom #joedamico #thehostoflasvegas @ Spanish Trail Country Club https://t.co/sDuB3Gx9cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[( yellow cake double layer / vanilla icing between layers , chocolate icing with reese's mini p nut and white choco… https://t.co/AbPBkEKIoY]]></document></documents></author>