<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Have a great week #livepdnation!    See you next week!!!!!   #livepd #misfits]]></document><document><![CDATA[At some point these people that are intentionally doing this to these strong women NEED their licenses revoked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hazier than hazy. Dry as the dessert. Running out of metaphors. - Drinking a Hyper Scream by @drekkerbrewing at… https://t.co/ncvkjMI8iH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The server's lipstick is bright blue. It is hard to look at her. And she needs a #sammich]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at my outdoor friends 🦌😯 @ Canfield, Ohio https://t.co/yN9hN6srMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann @wilderpone Obama. You are a hated person. A target for the Dems to silence you. Watch your back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___Leland You and me only contribute if we attend any of his games or buy paraphernalia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a tease this morning from @Royal_Farms 😭😭  #1StinkingPoint https://t.co/7fYqHB3Ne0]]></document><document><![CDATA[In some ways, the biggest takeaway from yesterday is that (with a few exceptions) the national political media oppo… https://t.co/an93DFHB6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an exhausting fuck of a week in which every negative interaction was balanced out by a dozen great ones, and… https://t.co/RxYBFHDh3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Belch_4021 @organicbrelan @JohnHillbery @SBNation The discussion isn’t the Heat I know they aren’t going anywhere… https://t.co/qq8UdUVwso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NichterUC_DoB @uofcincy @TUCBIDG @StuAffUC @GoBEARCATS @anitaney1 Congratulations Anita! Thank you for representing the #Bearcats well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think cutting costs would be a welcome sign in the community, personally. Dangerous? Good thing we have licensed… https://t.co/IFZdhzqVby]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man who’s not my man wants me to get into Mariah Carey’s music so guess who’s getting into Mariah Carey’s music, this guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorCalStoolie @nbcbayarea @USGS I was in Napa for the 6.0 quake in 2014 and I can assure you that it didn’t feel like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mroy62 Fucking corrupt FBI .. liberal fake news can’t cover this shit up 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme x The North Face Expedition Backpack Sulphur https://t.co/QE3mRjjA87]]></document><document><![CDATA[K.C. Clark went to my daughter's Kinaaldá and actually participated. Left an impression on me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgedavilaCNNE CNN NO SE HA ENTERADO QUE EL GOBIERNO DE MADURO MANDO A QUEMAR 3 CAMIONES CON AYUDA HUMANITARIA O… https://t.co/dSMNFgJ9ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSaunderson @NorbertElekes Not at all! Sara Blakely is amazing. Such a cool story of how she built @Spanx from t… https://t.co/8b4Am9BMES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Amazon was going to pay about $70 per hour to people in your district, you dolt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilaaron911 Every fucking time in 7/11 and i think u know what  Maybe monsters not that bad ill get it  It actuall… https://t.co/0v1T6oRXAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCalmighty69 @hankschulman I love old pocket schedules you get at liquor stores. https://t.co/sUDjtmK9tJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhopp79 @coachhersom @Sean23Roberts @RossPeterson_ @TravisCreates @ChrisMWilliams Unfortunately, you have been sus… https://t.co/8fTML88MV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a night privilege. @andrewschulz is a 👑 🎤 🙌 https://t.co/NgF3Js51xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really really suck at Smash Brothers Ultimate. I never played any of the other ones. Watched some online videos t… https://t.co/K3QTfnCbaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Manzzz @jennduarte58 @_roxeen @jflosnonsense I’m with it! Hopefully we don’t end up at the function again. Like last week🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#babyKai #beach day with #daddy. @ Jacksonville Beach Pier https://t.co/08dd4QHVQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NachoRgz @tatclouthier Nunca entenderás las implicaciones de la militarización; tu fanatismo por el lider, te impi… https://t.co/40HBUb5YnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do not be anxious about anything, but in every situation, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasJoe94 @Back2Stepover @MVPDakota He APPARENTLY brought something to the game they were lacking, bcos the end… https://t.co/G9QDpk3mMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_rostron So what? There is a lot to be demeaned in the totalitarian, Socialist, baby-killing Left and the Dee… https://t.co/fh1PP8NJxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashWizards @Troy_Brown33 @CapitalCityGoGo #FireErnie #FireScottBrooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump And you have to be so, 'Far Out There'!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to playing the 100k gtd on @PlayNowCasino today. Gl @edog007 @AlexBPoker @Stuicide420 @CanadianG223… https://t.co/2PxQvqySM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s easy to focus on new taxes or tolls today, but there’s also a lot of wonky stuff that’s hard to explain but co… https://t.co/yTW7AftZJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exacto este maldito traidor está simplemente enseñando de que pata cojea pues ya nos traiciono antes y no se detend… https://t.co/lfAzDJuQAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a honor to spend time with the men and women who paved the way for people who look like me in this industry.… https://t.co/VNzmGkZq8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodfellowes @LadyBloof Thanks 🙏🏾 had a great cosplayer to fill the frame]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Book on Amazon! The Collectors: Death is Easy, Life is Hard - Fiction Kindle Version: $3.99 @… https://t.co/GvSwD0pe2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the love for cinema? Got a new post up on https://t.co/S1qXNv3XRG. Check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will the roof open and the players float down in a balloon a la The Fish That Saved Pittsburgh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electricvoilet @MonstersOfRock @MHFOfficial @Metalmike3 @RockTheseTweets @RushFamTourneys @Metallica The Thing That Should Not Be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is the night!!! @chloeholland13  ... Show some love for this young lady!! Inside.... Hulkamania is running… https://t.co/cbYK5pYQ0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are people losing their shit about jason witten coming back ? that boy is washed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekintheCity @beanerita @OneDayAtATime @GitcRadio I already cried over the no-makeup abuelita.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunNGun8 @chuckiefick You know it’s funny, he might be watching somebody but in reality that’s just his swing. I’v… https://t.co/q9ciARCbDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leafsreallygood @draglikepull @51Leafs Kuch is grossly underpaid and has the Florida tax shield. Everyone knows it… https://t.co/TLxom2kiFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic @malibujonfanti @SenFeinstein ‘s hubby, Dicky Blum’s construction company, received $986Million for “… https://t.co/FXo8EQL7ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstFloris That's great reminds me of a young Casey and Candice Neistat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@equitationgirl @allsportsfan24 @ScottyPick6 @LosPonies Sal's early pk4  R1. 2,3,4 R2. 2,5 R3. 3,5 R4. 2,5 $24 Sal'… https://t.co/8E0QDm22FW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 16-17 of the #21DayCkChallenge . Finishing up the Lambda pre-course work. Also, diving into @w3develops site. I… https://t.co/QRFLaMZsap]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 better be the year Catherine O’Hara gets an Emmy nom for Schitt’s Creek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to officially announced my candidacy for Big Ten commissioner in 2020. #BazB1GBoss]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN IN THE FUCK DID I SAY THEY SHOULD FREE MY BROTHER???? MY BROTHER BELONGS BEHIND BARS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCostantino @ScottGrimes @markjacksonacts I’m hoping for “Issac’s Gone” in part two of this episode. https://t.co/cMw0NC1hRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedMitchell_15 I think the TSSAA streams the video on their site. There might be a fee though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Did you complain when Obama circumvented the Constitution. If not then you're just another liberal hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cleen_Rock_One @hallublin I met The Rock checking into a Red Roof Inn, but I'd be just as thrilled to meet you. Yo… https://t.co/BmWISMfPZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing @BigTurnRedWing today! Gonna hang all day and see all u friends, @GBandTheWiz plays at midnight to close th… https://t.co/2Ag2zPhPAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having to spend #219Day in Ohio due to a @BallStateMBB road trip, but do not fear, I have informed everyone in this… https://t.co/xBsNAfmfrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec I almost feel sorry for her. It’s going to be a long fall when she doesn’t get reelected. Going to be… https://t.co/EzNibM6qvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain @wowsuperheroes the main event will be havok vs tessa blanchard on the season finale plus the 1 tag… https://t.co/7VxpZczywv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaP @kelleydeal In the Lollapalooza days, I chose to forego Holes set, so I could see Moby on the second st… https://t.co/3qSSzjPNrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the movies with friends. Watching that film The Room. Lol. ☺️💕🎶 @ Landmark's Clay Theatre https://t.co/0A3TcUDehm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta I’ve been around at least 3 cows and I have yet to have a complex social conversation with one of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t buy the conceit of the Dragons Love Tacos book. Not being able to handle any kind of spice means you could never love tacos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typingelbow @saracsalinas WHERE ARE YOU ON VACATION??? THE HUNGER GAMES???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anauburntiger Answer. I really haven’t done a thing except collect a government paycheck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Attention, taken to its highest degree, is the same thing as prayer.”-Simone Weil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakes_Jamie13 BAKES!  This is an amazing piece by @KatieJStrang. Thank you for your honesty, and I look forward to… https://t.co/H3SIkc0dHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fredericton Police in action!!!  VERY brave souls!!!! https://t.co/ZRMW7wEI8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of them at the @NigBarAssoc are useless people,let me first remind the alleged rogue President of the NBA that… https://t.co/zAjkOFcn5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Aaron Schock —  where are they now? He’s training with “models” to uhmm be a better Former Congress pers… https://t.co/XvV1D6Kmg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me voy a volver priista nada más para escuchar la comedia que pone este señor... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElieNYC @sarahkendzior @amjoyshow That spot needs to go viral with Sarah!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed_perezP @opti_mistico @CescWolff10 @pochodiaz @LORENT_SALEH @MariaFdaCabal @PoliciaColombia @CGR_Colombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMummyToo Hi Emily, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we w… https://t.co/mcOb9pVCvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. @DebLavender gaveled down and mic cut off for speaking on Medicaid in the context of abortion, whilst a freshm… https://t.co/MS1LAjaaIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. I’ve never seen so much body shaming bullshit in my life went through comments and everywhere I go it’s crack… https://t.co/6YeX0K6ngO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberDawnGlover Warm jammies with socks. Cozy blankets and warm liquids. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnieman @RobertGarciaLB Thanks- hope all well with you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOM OF 10YR OLD KID FACING 5 YEARS IN JAIL OUT ON PROBATION COURT ORDERED TO TREATMENT WITH ANKLE MONITOR ON THRE… https://t.co/dp8qMLiw5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ainslieann Link doesn’t work. My daughter plays in weekend tournaments there great place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @Breaking_NewsTN I feel as though I just watched Rainman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClearwaterPlaza What’s the Name of the Song that plays during your Commercials???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raiderjoe_FO @North2North @BigRed_STL @EMac22NYJ Thanks for tweeting this—I will make sure he sees these.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A haircut will make your girl act right pt. 3  Credit: @iamdevale   #sharpstatus #staysharp #devaleellis #freshcut… https://t.co/D8dnFJvUOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hump day. Sssph. I might get lucky &amp; have a dog hump my leg or something. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@incarceratedbob @KyrieIrving Heard L&amp;B Spumoni Gardens in Brooklyn has the best...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J__Velasquez @AOC It’s given the opportunity to over 1 MILLION immigrants to obtain an #AB60 driver’s license in t… https://t.co/c643Fz8Htb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden @BernieSanders He’s only a Democrat when it’s convenient for him. For this reason, and others, I do no… https://t.co/6PPFXCKvMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nostrafartface Perhaps to one treading the thin, treacherous ice of misogyny...(sigh)😬😬😬🍸]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had been at that Brandy concert I’d have walked out and gotten my money back. A mess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shleybraker Now I’m worried if I “celebrated” National Chocolate Mint Day properly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indiana has one option and you let him drive for a layup plus missed free throws and so many missed bunnies. Top 4… https://t.co/UAJOD09XRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchlafon Detroit Rock City all day every day. Spirit of Radio is a great song though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wafcstudios I think the animated short format could work for Zelda too. Different episodes for different dungeons… https://t.co/kTAazCfguD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What a fucking joke, she flops more then a fish in a pan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssrewind I love the ending music for episode 105! It got me laughing pretty hard!]]></document></documents></author>