<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@terrancelgreen @utexascoe @UTAustin What a blessing! Congrats, Dr.  Green.  Keep up the great work!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oman  Expat numbers drop as Omanisation kicks in https://t.co/FfamB8YvRy Times of Oman-Feb 26, 2019  “There has bee… https://t.co/8SjW2tmtVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[New wax melter for my apartment. Fits me very well since I love the city life so much. https://t.co/vR7m8ugs34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father and son 👶🏻🧔🏻❤️ @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/t28JVxhuNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget how nice it is to cook with a crockpot. Dinner is already done by the time I get home 😊😊 plus it always smells amazing!! 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socialmedia2day @JenniferBakerCo Kudos! I am generally a Hootsuite fan. Wondering what kind of reporting do you ha… https://t.co/wGe3gnUtwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Everybody loves Anne. But I like Emily. She’s dark.” I have never felt more seen. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaustiniMary Old dogs..children n watermelon wine. Any body alone? Grandkids don't call...useless lonely hours? Here's your cure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isletsoflngrhns @IngrahamAngle @JussieSmollett He was the worst President in history!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would give anything to be able to see and talk to you one last time 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone commented on one of my tweets but i cant see it cause they are private and i dont follow them 🙃 i so love that @Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaughtySassyHez @0SleeptilDawn @binestom @mandra40 @Lothiriel_1 @wcugrad_09 @jjwinters_child @marianavbelisa… https://t.co/WfoNLyA0Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite thing is when someone uses a phrase i’m notorious for and then acts like they’ve been using it “forever… https://t.co/4gIda0Uf4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanlemond @JaredLorenzen22 Happy Birthday Jared!!!! Hope it was a great one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beck is a conman, with serious recurring bi-polar and addiction issues, all about💲and fame, no surprise here. #ETTD https://t.co/VBtqlb0a55]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this Lent Bible study on the Bible app. The first devotional put it brilliantly - Is your Lent a sacrifice of… https://t.co/TEgZEWEjd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have to leave Twitter I become angry when I scroll. I'm not an angry person. #WTFMoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to see Shirley Hilton's story in the @WR_Record #BalanceforBetter #IWD2019 @GKWCC @WRPSToday  https://t.co/dbjcKPsYIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[jess told me to say this to my uber eats driver https://t.co/qR5gbLzT6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Oh - please let her back in- and then put her in a hole so deep she will regret coming back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[24°? Meh. #realminnesotan @ South Como, Saint Paul, Minnesota https://t.co/lIffyUmTqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[La #SuperLuna está en todo su esplendor y yo sin poder contemplarla ☹️😢😢 ☁️ ☁️☁️☁️ por que tenían que aparecer hoy… https://t.co/6ZLo2Bv72p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urLIFEwillBLOOM @RobinStroup @abcnews @CBSNews @CNN @NBCNews @nytimes @washingtonpost Ty‼️👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I only tweet on Fridays lmao, oh well wassup Friday again less do dissss🤘🥳🤑☕️💨🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please note that the Gr. 5 bus left Vorlage at 4:30pm. Gr. 6 is scheduled to leave at 5pm. I will update when we ar… https://t.co/ERi8AnDHai]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’m thankful for today  That real life housing is not like UD housing. The “point” system is in no way a measu… https://t.co/BocKXXPbMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad, but certainly not a surprise! Thats what happens often...reality check @HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats hello]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thomas sticking his tongue out at his daddy! What a little ham! lol. #Days]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are hopping to their new home in Mississippi! I think they will love it down there!  🐸 🐝 🌼… https://t.co/Lm5Ip7wkIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the most alexis ass tweet if ive ever seen one 😂   @lexforrestier]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then @SpeakerPelosi needs to create a mandatory freshman representative orientation educational model for non discr… https://t.co/rtTlpwoaZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agalanis17 Siempre hay nuevas oportunidades, los tiempos de Dios son perfectos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one event that has happened in your life recently was going to take you out, I doubt it would be the excessive T… https://t.co/dFCKdSIIcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever makes the Wings at 240 must have went through ALOT in life. Ain’t no regular person just making wings that good bruh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found it nicotine can be good for my autoimmune disease idk how but now I feel less bad about juuling!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThinkingGirl5 He will never own this. He still maintains he is the wronged party. Narcissistic, perpetual victim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakedhamisbaked @elizaminnelli_ wow the shared urban studies experience. can i get a shout out for anyone who had to take 110 w stout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPHOUSTON59 @Freedom92946574 @Bubbas49 @RepAdamSchiff Wait... your talking Botox nancy who wished people a happy t… https://t.co/lQjZ2Uhaaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The glorification of apathy is one of the most dangerous yet overlooked social norms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before we can shape a future, we must share a reality. #bailey2019 @juniatacollege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup it’s def softball season when your whole left hand hurts from taking balls at first from @kerialexis1 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait- what’s the point of groomsmen and bridesmaids?!   What’s the point? Someone please explain]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true! EVERY KID NEEDS A CHAMPION! This never gets old! https://t.co/E8lj4lB8e6]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday kay💓 ily and miss you sm! party hard for me!😙 https://t.co/80pB9RycIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annaclaire1478 You’re exactly what you should be and that’s always enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Digital_Vix3n this really hit the nail on the head for me tatjana LOL couldn’t explain it better myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family and I visited one of the largest Buddhist temples in the Western Hemisphere this weekend for their… https://t.co/vQqUbIz9v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell them to drop dead. THESE two collude with terrorist organizations AND they are looking to impeach THE PRESIDEN… https://t.co/8aJSiXozX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[*never discussed Masada/Watkins sr business. My mind was halfway out the door I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a pre pre red carpet for the oscars &amp; genuinely wishing I was there 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally the voice we need for Hamilton Mountain!  Hamilton's Bruno Uggenti is our Liberal Candidate and can get us… https://t.co/cGMyqEy4L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 9am, I’ve been awake for 10 minutes and I’m emotional. https://t.co/oIJoFEiK4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhunnn! I dare not! How arab men play with their pets😁 @ Landover, Maryland https://t.co/LtQxu3DA05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Representative David Gregory for being our Champion of Direct Consumer Access to PT, HCS HB 410!… https://t.co/4ZQn1QfVxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all peep my dorky brothers first vid on his YouTube channel. Dis dude out here vintage shopping like no other. Pe… https://t.co/MPUNdudEk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristencherry26 @LarissaSherrod @A_Klein09 @DinwiddieUNC @jeffreykubiak @PrincipalTrots @KristenWitt13… https://t.co/1taTctH7nI]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Pakistan says it shot down two Indian aircraft that entered its airspace”  https://t.co/a8soNSZGoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure all the baby clothes I just washed have shrunk https://t.co/paedS9Kn7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have had trouble sleeping and having horrible nightmares. Ralph wakes me up and tells me, I am trembling and mumbling!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobRobbEdwards How sad and a Deplorable act it was,just sick to my stomach hearing about this horrible act,pisses me off big time!!🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Matt9Duchene I’ll be in jersey for the game tomorrow - diehard sens fan - would love to come up to the press b… https://t.co/JWCyueH3SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our State Troopers don’t often have chicken-related news, but when they do, it’s a good story!  (State Troopers are… https://t.co/spdNbWMTks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew @LaurenWern “The evidence will show clear violation of the#EmolumentsClause Article 1 section 9 of the… https://t.co/z2QmEHntI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/Ypl0j9qxoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las paletas de maple, no tienen comparación 🍁❤️ https://t.co/id9sTQIEzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TiffanyDash Fr. I was trying to give her the benefit of the doubt but I truly feel like she’s not getting back to… https://t.co/q9xqPNl7Gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kastia I think that's why I'm still intimidated to draw them to this day. HOW DOES THEIR HAIR WORK????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethanphillips_1 @sydneybrothers she’s right and i’m agreeing with her on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAHOO ... She is on her way!   Hosanna Rubio is #CaliforniaBound from #NorthCarolina for her #vacation https://t.co/uXJ9xAcQq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcx_steph I know you’re sleeping, so I hope you’re having pleasant dreams and have a great day mañana 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikadallimore @Moonface1975 @sumace @anyaruns @MrsAJFrance @goreckidawn @louise_gw @leggylinda1 @Cadders68… https://t.co/gosxdx6mR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#micromanagment #jobs #buildateam #raisethemup #trust #education #believe  Micromanagement will push the.good quali… https://t.co/MIxoyBGhjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[*You’re in dallas and your parents are driving you to school. You turn on the radio*  “ITS KIDD KRADDICK IN THE MOR… https://t.co/1BbJdZ7OFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl I know at my school just flew to Paris to hang out with post Malone??? I’m pissed???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got that Right Felila! Take your team to Hockey East Tourney Championship! Go Warriors!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fotd sometimes when i sleep over and have no spare clothes for that extra day i gotta mix what i had previously https://t.co/NnCWPw61Sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello! Tune in to @CBCHereandNow at 4:07 pm to hear me speak about this week’s cover story on the relationship betw… https://t.co/mLk2Kkbkj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy presidents day!!! It's day 39 of my #rigside #mealselections .. phew what a nice long well  #foodjournal… https://t.co/R7oCAViOWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude...the few times I went on air that early I was afraid I might fall back asleep ;) I’ll DVR it 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memphis QB Zack Mettenberger discusses his pass intercepted by Atlanta’s Tyson Graham Jr. @CrushSportsTalk https://t.co/fMt5f9tdfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just parked in the wrong parking structure and had to pay $45 to get out  Get a car they said It would be fun they said]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to remind ppl of the time where Justin put his wants above the law..there are many of them.  Each case Justin… https://t.co/oagFumRiQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[To every fan who thinks they can look some information on me up on the internet it’s incorrect baby sorry wrong gir… https://t.co/BLIAuF5fgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaMillin @ResistanceRed1 @LUCIAGO19276424 @WendyTruong3 @ResistanceGold1 @WHurensohn @Gram247 @kysgabbygirl… https://t.co/dkZrugUNks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glorious day here today! At #universalcitywalk.  #orlando #florida #sunny #warm #instaspamming @ Universal Citywalk https://t.co/OkopOamQeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spookybrit79 ngl you’re beautiful but ur probably taken so i dont gotta shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s becoming obvious in addition to placing Manafort in Trump’s campaign to lift sanctions,change policy toward Uk… https://t.co/ab9raQEMGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️💙💚Buby @theSB 🍣🐟🐙#sushibuby💗🧡💜 #HappyValentinesDay💘2gether https://t.co/nrcLbjPVu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@editorialunilit Las siete amistades que destruyen» brinda recursos para superar el dolor del rompimiento de una re… https://t.co/Q5JsK62URi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we like to play dress up #allusiatogo &amp; #barbiesaddiction #jasonkingphoto #BeachesWeHo… https://t.co/b8jV8V7VV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Sonyabb I’m surprised my mom is drowning everyone with pictures at work 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroSchools Read Me Week got off to an amazing start today at @Churchwell_Elem! Shout out to @MNPSDirector,… https://t.co/iUcWt0bCTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hubs gets homemade cards for vday... he is always in for a treat. He loves me just for my humor. 😂 #valentines https://t.co/HFA5qTnSTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Zahn crossed 20M. Time 03:51:07, pace 11:50 min/mile, est. finish 12:06 pm https://t.co/Q4leAOv29O #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How will this be stopped? He’s simply going to go through with this. Unbelievable. We all know he works for Russia… https://t.co/pRKzgCrS6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[76% of investors who have a financial advisor report having a positive sense of well being. @Doug_Owens - I think t… https://t.co/R4lkJ26JkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idkmaddie oh gosh thank you so much 😭 i was a lil too embarrassed to go out and actually see people but thank you… https://t.co/MvoalRvplx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonjames I crochet, I can make nets.  Alternately--I can crochet hats that we can put on the dinosaurs so they fe… https://t.co/rpjLgFCMvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se me olvidaba que no tenían clases los de la UAS, perdón por querer convivir con ustedes pensando que estaban en cln amiguitos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking #YQG #WindsorEssex connections with @MichaelTibollo #MinisterTourismCultureSport @GordonOrr66… https://t.co/zW3rTaoqB5]]></document></documents></author>