<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kindyllynn can carry me up 3 flights of stairs and he can’t even make it to the room..🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thewarburton2019 #songwritersnight #sjcrh @ JW Marriott Desert Springs Palm Desert https://t.co/pPmeF1PmEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driver doesn’t call/message or follow the delivery instructions and (even though I explained it in my claim) order… https://t.co/g11qsgpun3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews HRC won every debate. To this day you haven’t prepared for anything. DISGRACE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuraInBrooklyn Next winter I think we will drive Ziggy up to nyc to see the Balto statue ❄️❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiomonroe Hey Howard! How have you been? It's Julie Steinmetz.  We've been out of touch for almost 20 years. Wow… https://t.co/CGB9ghgfho]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕#WonderfulWeek @realkimgosselin @bonnie_hake @JamesNorth01 @cynthiakahn @viragshah4 @earlshelpdesk]]></document><document><![CDATA[chris young wasn’t lying when he said the skies in cheyenne, wyoming are just about as blue as it gets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_meat_lady Amen!  I wear a lot of Duluth clothing. Expensive but wears like iron. Cabela’s has the warmest oute… https://t.co/CesTxVfzwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studying for children’s lit and honestly Perrault’s Cinderella is some bull. You’re tellin me those stepsisters tre… https://t.co/RbdjNCdjc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mxnews I'm a WNC writer and I just won a trip to Portland in an international novel-writing contest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveGigilo9 Yes, so I can listen while I'm driving. Trying to use my home hours for my own writing. But the plus i… https://t.co/bjcAuJBM4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swetTEAaddpeach Not sure how’s that’s a solution... at all. If anything, would make the problem worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Huge, unbelievable, President needs to sign EO, for free speech on college campuses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something green is about to happen. Cleaner air us in our future! Stay tuned! @AcadAcademy @ACCHilt_Inst… https://t.co/QNVMWJdVci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub @JenniferAydin @daniellestaub @DoloresCatania @Teresa_Giudice I love, love, love Delores!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjkeegs @marty_walsh @BostonCares Amazing and well deserved, @pjkeegs! Thank you for all you've done for #service in Boston!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost fell in love with a thotty 🙅🏾‍♀️ My dawg said you got too many body’s 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I rope an unsuspecting date into seeing THEY SHALL NOT GROW OLD with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganHumphres @realityxash Supposedly they might drop a new song on March 1 I’m dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @Twitter Wow. Coming from you and what you just tweeted about Cohen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MsDrake_SEP for and Awesome #celebrateMonday STEM challenge! #SEPolk https://t.co/DNcPjD4QmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Erie, PA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/UVNCCvQpaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day two of #birthdayboyweekend coincidently is also #nationaliwantyoutobehappyday!! Kicking off the afternoon with… https://t.co/eA9A40ysBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are the Democrats!  They are the Party of homelessness/open borders/liars/hate/illegal aliens/crime infestatio… https://t.co/A9kt9LO3m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This soup is as delicious as it is beautiful. Curry carrot soup with lentils at @cerberusbrewing for lunch. @ Cerbe… https://t.co/6OIAK8d149]]></document><document><![CDATA[As with *any* physical problem, I should have known better than to google my strange abdominal pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showcase is tomorrow DON’T MISS OUT! Bring your friends! #txst #txst #txst #texasstateuniversity #txstgreek https://t.co/MUAJFhkMtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Let me put it this way most of us could care less about whats happening over there. Take it how ever yo… https://t.co/LzyHhfdfRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitts_jason @FGBvsEveryone A lot of High School Coaches are faiIing. I guess they are leaving it up to the Travel Ball Coaches. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS.   IT SNOWED.   I AM SO EXCITED.   I AM ALSO FROM FLORIDA SO I AM VERY COLD. https://t.co/I1oi2dhMzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time Eugene Melnyk needed a liver and the Sens Army saved his life? 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRobRoberts @adrinktothepast Hey might as well take advantage of the points when you have em! :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaLibrarian @ChadLindberg You can NEVER go wrong with the original Star Wars trilogy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is absurd. Sometimes I Take Baths Because It's Hard To Drink Wine In The Shower Wood Sign 12x12... https://t.co/l8BZBzklOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi nivel de alcoholismo es: abrir una botella de vino y acabarmela en esa misma noche]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Your sense of humor is so refreshing” so do you want me to start sending depression memes now or later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @sxdoc @realDonaldTrump The demon rats are the ones who are violent I haven’t seen one true case of a… https://t.co/XwY7w8SUb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smartclean_app Bull shit, all you have To do is delete all the crap you saved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bccraving @SVanchough @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Nothing to do with HRC. I'm not anti GOP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rscottjones @AmericaHikes @goldbutte 5 hours 56 minutes from PHX to Mesquite exit in to Gold Butte!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryl38885180 @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @RealJamesWoods @LindseyGrahamSC Fake news. She didn't even marry… https://t.co/WCJu9Lh0PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WrestlingUncensored ep. 430 tonight on @TSN690 after #habs postgame Batista, KO, Hardyz, and Roman Reigns return a… https://t.co/aBa4dJZSfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your hips get wider the older you get. Some of y’all should’ve waited before getting that surgery! Lol ok I’m done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braydon: *looks at me* *cries* The musical is over, we’re old. https://t.co/MmOeMsptk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RL9631 @realCalebLawson @nancy_hamm1 @SealeyGerald @RazorPack65 @GodFirstGina @Maga4Justice @gopoundsand1234… https://t.co/jfnnOrkva0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sad James goes to talk to Big Ed. #TwinPeaksDay https://t.co/tNRzBe79hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @mattchap6 for signing my gold glove. Hopefully I can get @mattolson21 to sign it tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what it’s like to not wake up deathly hung over after a night of drinking. Must be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuidicottiJr @Th3Re4lMackyG @Honeybadger1978 @JosephNSanberg Have you ever been to Scandinavia? Have you studied t… https://t.co/ITxVvPAL23]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Red Carpet for the launch event of @movikarma !! Thanks @escarcegasteve for all the AMAZING pictures! 🙌🙏… https://t.co/CFnlQIBxz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOVIE TIME!! 🎬🔥🎬  Check out the fun here: https://t.co/AH1YMhN1MA   #KCFF19 #itsallhappening https://t.co/KmhK5AGOiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn’t having the best of days and I was venting to one of my sorority sisters and she told me“It’s okay, it’s ju… https://t.co/KuWgSjnQAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsStewart757 @VBCPSengagement @TESSeagulls @cziggy1 @JoshRingling Love that this has continued! You rock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Women dressed in their best. Looking Gorgeous. Strutting w/confidence. Black Men dressed to the nines. Hard b… https://t.co/9hlcyzfwfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My chapbook PHANTOMS is now available for purchase from dancing girl press. Found objects, abandoned spaces, haunte… https://t.co/PW91FWn3Cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lead "social media in the misinformation age" for @DanceNYC on Sat, Feb 23rd, 1-2pm, @huntercollege, Rm 407  We’l… https://t.co/R6Jmenp8wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Club at Hammock Beach Resort https://t.co/qUqqpWZqOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow No, unless you can prove that the kid is up to no good, otherwise the kid could have a medical problem. Parents need to step up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblackdetour My mom had to do that when I was born...57 years ago. She got dissed for it right until she passed… https://t.co/QB9H2lwebU]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are perks to being the girl team member who snores... I get my own room!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmdallas @TelemundoNI @TelemundoCT Gracias Tony! Hoping you come to visit soon! Saludos desde Boston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queria apenas falar que pular na neve no Canadá é uma delícia. 🙏🏻❤️ #brasileirosnocanada https://t.co/rQdDBmU7i3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hivwomen2019 Lighter moments. Channelling my youth. Lesson 1: Learning how to arch-tutor @SitholeNyasha https://t.co/lYhcTBeWV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeesAndBaking @AnthGeek What is this faux fur extraness in JULY https://t.co/cALGl9kKpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby is in his crib tonight 😩 I’m not ready to give up co sleeping at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VintageEliz If anyone can clean up this mess, I have my hopes in this Pope. He’s got his work cut out for him though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erin_Embleu There literally is no way to do it, and if you figure out how to, you’re probably a sociopath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me on Bev Cart: “y’all need anything?” Guy playing golf: “a new golf game” https://t.co/loS6gOHrNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes For a City thats supposed to be so advanced our School system is one of a Third rate Nation. How is it our… https://t.co/Vt45k9e3Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herlifeinruins I don’t know what to look for specifically, but post photos of anything super cool you find!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiiilyf 😂😂😂 Nevermind then. My hair and 90% chance of rain don't work together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s my goal? “Empowering women to monetize with their authentic voices, regardless of background.“ Blogging make… https://t.co/9YuT456HWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the Senate floor to Summerville Country Club: @CoryBooker and @SherrodBrown hug as Booker wraps up his speech… https://t.co/c4PMZuBYrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few looks from last night!  #carmensandiego #captainmarvel #warbird #binary #msmarvel #caroldanvers #cosplay… https://t.co/APZDyrpnSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Why don’t these stupid “ moms” give the newborn to a hospital E.R. Then leave. Better than murdering a newborn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charles_gaba Open Enrollment also contributes to that, no? Making sure peeps don’t sign up when they need it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWIMCvolunteers @ionnalee @alliex I feel like I am stoked to see her live ❤🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[But i aint gonna fuck em cause I’m scared of that disease, passing out that dick like government cheese. But not me… https://t.co/J66yRhe6NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day here in heaven #amwriting @ Cayuga Lake https://t.co/HeRDariV16]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol when Michael Cohen has grounds to say “shame on you” to someone, you know that person is really doing a terrible job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump Your red duncecap says it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. I don’t think I’ve spent more hours on a game than this it’s not one do the oldest memories of video games but i… https://t.co/yKbewYJn2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[And how does your Friday get better? Seeing that your rockstar “I wish I had her as my personal mentor” favorite au… https://t.co/LjpLRnefqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DurvidImel @superscientific @UrAvgConsumer @booredatwork @theMrMobile @lora_krystal @macmixing @ZacksJerryRig… https://t.co/tWsfnjZHd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pelea de Leonel empieza temprano, Sin Maquillaje, enero 28, 2019 https://t.co/0gWaG3mr3c vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEP My mom @louisemarcus. She’s been my role model since day 1 - between beating breast cancer, raising a son with… https://t.co/Wp8T5VP5k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jc4p @gortok That’s the same ones I found, plus Best Buy. George literally search the brand you want 1TB or 1TTB d… https://t.co/vAWKxFnHLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[on top of it all i can’t charge my phone and listen to music bc iphones r fucking stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gatekeeping is way more of a recent phenomenon for me. Where men, don’t believe I’m the Star Wars fan, comic c… https://t.co/ocz9bzO8eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIP: work around your self-care schedule instead of trying to work it IN. have a set-schedule for your #selfcare an… https://t.co/siKQy0hOYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG NEWS!!!! @ScottRogowsky @seanseaevans GIVE ME THOSE HOT QUESTIONS!!! https://t.co/3woLkRqfTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @TracieAfifi and coauthors on your award of Article of the Year and for moving the field forward in unders… https://t.co/zzWLxJsDiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL kids CAN . Let’s focus on the possABILITY and help all kids be their best! Morgan’s Wonderland is a great place… https://t.co/1SEctv0BY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJoshHopkins Can you give us a brief synopsis of the plot line?? I’ll be recording it for sure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night my dad was telling me how he just wants his kids to accomplish what he couldn’t and more.. I don’t deser… https://t.co/YYtTOrlxK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like this pale Irish Princess knows how to cook for her handsome Mexican Prince.  Salsa, refried beans, chili… https://t.co/2TXjue4zwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[my very talented friend @Ellevarela wrote about the greasy magic of fast food and now I want a burger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @jeremymbarr On the plus side. Melissa McCarthy will be back at SNL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katielawll NO LIE HE WAS LIKE TALKING ABOUT MY BROTHERS SHITTY LIFESTYLE SITUATION THEN CALLED ME A GROUPIE]]></document></documents></author>