<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KathrynJ1092 I told them going in that I’d be looking to cut as much as a third of the manuscript. They want to se… https://t.co/RTRA3NlcQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a concept about if your dating a transgender you can perceive as a man you can presive her as a women its… https://t.co/FriOd0SOu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealtorKingwood @BadLionGold Wow. Is this how you rep Keller Williams?  I’ve asked them if this how they do busine… https://t.co/kMYEWckY7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessiStone @steelyonsports @AndrewGilmanOK @Eddie_Rado @FranchiseOK The NBA players wives play against each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trendchasernews Complete waste of time with no ending.  DO NOT WASTE YOUR TIME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait! This Thursday our new addition comes home 😋🐶 #puppylove #dogdads https://t.co/AxBDcIMiOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mexicoseries #yoamoelbeis @lasmayores mlbmexico @mlb rockies @dbacks mlb.atbat en Estadio de Béisbol Monterrey https://t.co/yS8iDbHNFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck dude I’m sooooo stressed I have like 7281628728 assignments due and on top of that I need to study for these midterms haha yay 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did Spike Lee hurt your non existent feelings Lord Farquaad? You are a #Fraud in every way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quisiera una foto con la Hermosa de @NaileaVidrio espero conocerte pronto. Saludos Bonita ❤️ https://t.co/TWpNnvqezq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey gym Hump Day CHEST! @MikeOHearn PB @HeathEvans44 @JDBuffone @turbittabc27  @AMANDAbolic @DemetriaObilor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stuart_zechman I hate this band and yet have never listened to any song of theirs all the way through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing gifts 👀from friends at #Pensacon 2019 - Day2 starts TODAY #TheFlash #DawsonsCreek #TeenWolf https://t.co/hUtx5U1lIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only other national emergency besides the border are the mentally sick people in office!!! Like Pelosi and many… https://t.co/M5RKtJOsKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@httpnewscatcom @Incatnito1 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Guess they were reporting the facts regarding Benghazi and U… https://t.co/sONtYIVuZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Workeh must decline this posting of him to head UNO Officein Nairobi for the sake of region. The new Manchurian… https://t.co/ly03UobMbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec Please POTUS do not sign this piece of trash Bill that is nothing but liberal open border trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauralynne103 @boi_twarty @iamericwhite @eleeburns @Kingkeraun @KingJames @BET They actually shoot more white peop… https://t.co/sKu6eYnQDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretaryAcosta @jkbjournalist @POTUS When your message gets lost in your baggage ... #PerversionOfJustice Read th… https://t.co/Hj7NrFfHIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with Brian Durbin @ Cube Night Club @ Rivers Casino https://t.co/xk8dCYP3qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Price gets first @UHVBaseball win first game of twinbill, Jaguars on wrong side of record-breaking performanc… https://t.co/y02EoBOcHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the idea of NCAA hockey at USF.  I just don’t think it’s feasible.  https://t.co/qGkfTaWHuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a new end of the world and it’s 99.9% of instagram-sponsored musicians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan Was Air Force One grounded during the shutdown? No. Stop lying. Trump upgraded the simulator that Oba… https://t.co/JgKXKJfRLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GREATMEMORIES #GREATTIMES #THEBESTOFTHEBEST #ICONIC @ Icon Entertainment Branding &amp; Marketing, Inc. https://t.co/en8M9j4Y8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPIALBasketball tonight with @HSSports01 @hsuniontown and @rvburch at @Edinboro for first round of the @PIAASports… https://t.co/U3Yh0z2tx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starts off sweet and malty... With a hoppy dry bitter finish... Easy drinking... - Drinking a Nugget Nectar by… https://t.co/z4CBgfxwyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Ways to Protect Yourself from #cybersecurity Threats | FinSMEs https://t.co/zpQmRNebL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guaidó refutó órdenes directas de Maduro con su primer decreto presidencial https://t.co/19xtrN9toB vía @@caraotadigital]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think so. He's like all of the other leftists hates white people. Specifically white straight males]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniescribes days, nights left to burn on the pile out back wasted hours in the bondfire we stand nearby glow on our faces hiding our tears]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wkend come on out to the grand opening of remedysouthbend  #EatLocal #Art #GrandOpening #DjBlackFoot… https://t.co/S0n6bljcwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinpahuja @VenetianPoker I would expect open seating for most of the day. I’m sure at some point there will be alternates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words mean everything... That is why we have them... a killer and a murderer have both killed people... but the kil… https://t.co/SQoPdTm0o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diegonoticia @pilarvelasquezv Otro jugador q no llegó con grandes condiciones fue: Jhon Edison Castaño, Alex Cortá… https://t.co/zMZXQo8Iue]]></document><document><![CDATA[v.1.0 - understanding and practicing Biblical principles (getting things right) with the right heart, right people,… https://t.co/sbHLM9cP4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[p.s. Let us all look forward to the day when we all have equal access to healthcare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliciaStella love the new episode, is the music you use at the beginning the area music from port of entry ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmachado59 @khanfar60 @ADL @tcwittes Jordan and Syria attacked Israel.  Israel launched a preemptive strike agains… https://t.co/TWmSyTBpkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambezzyy I throw them away or give it to homeless person If I see one 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Piscataqua River Bridge in Portsmouth, NH https://t.co/JdQvnJltCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PurpleReign 💜💜 @natalieevamarie for #AmericasFavHG #BBCeleb https://t.co/xfHVhyxtZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[/7 Small Modular Reactors (SMRs) were found to be economically viable in hydrogen production, aluminum smelting, wa… https://t.co/XS5qiXijqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have A Great Weekend Fam! @seand67 @boaplazaatl 😎📸🌇🔥🌥 #friday #tgif #atlanta #nikon #photography #shutterstock… https://t.co/vwIYuzSPUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magic Sword or Magic Swords? Also @destryur to kick it off. @magicswordmusic #magicsword #destryur @ Saint Vitus Bar https://t.co/hcsEyu3ugu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Your diction and thought process speak volume of the type of person y… https://t.co/uEGTIYtTPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love our new 2nd location thewtrainingfacilityoc and our new family @medterracbd TEAMWOC #iwanttowineverything… https://t.co/BIVR8Es6IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everything Trump does on the world stage benefit Russia the most? It sure fits the story doesn't it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Herrera Esteli Toro seems to be the mildest of all their cigars in have enjoyed. Great morning or early daytim… https://t.co/CFMxmMPGjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews maybe this is a story you should follow, not Beto dropping an f' bomb!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, if that 125-foot bank pass by Crosby to Guentzel would have worked ... #dkps #penguins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissAuroraSnow You're a hard worker!!! And a great mom you need love time for yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to believe all you peoples jobs involve you using excel🤔🤔🤔 How much do jobs require people using Microsoft office 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grant_D_Taylor @AaronOKelley @h_a_thomas Sure - I’m talking modernism here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis ya parecen a otros show , pura música , necesitas producción o que]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaraNotTahra The big problem is it is overpriced by at least 50K. It needs some serious work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be live from Allen Street in just a few minutes I’m @WGRZ #Daybreak to tell you exactly what you can expect to… https://t.co/Ybcad1amd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAO https://t.co/mP5NOkjSU5 explains how to solve world hunger without huge investments. Allowing people to take c… https://t.co/2t3L8suCyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AP Because of you and the changes you want to make to the Democratic Party I will be changing parties. I hope… https://t.co/e3LGhygIHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggsag @NIRSonline Sure. Here's one https://t.co/oCEcYz92K0. And this https://t.co/s9xsI2pJ5f. But I'll be fair a… https://t.co/ksulnO0Jwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its game time #UNCvsDuke   Greatest rivalry in sports 🏀🏀🏀 https://t.co/MAhGVBM7cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tobat02 @theauntysharon @laffbro @SemiloooreAkoni @Real_kingAde @Bc_blackchrome @_valkiing @iamvictor__… https://t.co/Q3a5tNGKNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atNickVega @Geoff_LW @EJayZarett Good is relative. It’s a touch artificial. But the beer is cheap, clean and refreshing. I’m not mad at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anonMom5000 @JackPosobiec @DroneGoth Who's "their"? Only Tucker's words were used. I don't know what more creepy then defending teen rape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfzombienation @fodorstravel @RoughGuides @lonelyplanet @Frommers @TripAdvisor @nytimestravel @LondonBreed You are… https://t.co/K6ZpgmiqN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME IRL drinking coffee,tea, soda #DetectivePikachu https://t.co/wz8JtRzJ1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drawing is the fastest, most effective way to learn, according to new research @ebtrylevelrebel https://t.co/g3zxlWgmZM via @Inc #drawing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also while we are freaking out about the Cohen testimony. The Missouri house perfected and passed an abortion ban s… https://t.co/2tQWjU8rr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the same time as Approps. is working on the budget, the Finance, Revenue, and Bonding (commonly referred to as F… https://t.co/gSUqol9S02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when cell phone commercials weren't music videos and they could just come on screen and say "YOU CAN CALL… https://t.co/xHUCIaV4yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like or dislike, on MSNBC said advertisement noted in below article was aired this evening:  (So, once again: “Thos… https://t.co/NhssMlRqrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask yourself how many shorties u been wit that give u unsolicited info on other niggas? That happening to u too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come down with a cold and won’t be going to the Wolves game tonight. Does anyone want some tickets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megker10 Stfu. Thanks for coming around every blue moon to chirp. Duke got those recruits cause of sustained succe… https://t.co/lE4QU0VmzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cc: @RDubThree @1053SS At first I was on Shan's side but after this tape idk 🤷🏾‍♂️   https://t.co/MwuZpAjpNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@needyforbesson @JonahMarais @ImZachHerron @SeaveyDaniel @whydontwemusic @corbynbesson @jackaverymusic z@SeaveyDaniel @ImZachHerron]]></document><document><![CDATA[yesterday i handwrote a check today i drove myself to the mall and bought a present for someone i may be stuck in a ‘90s VR simulation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyDCross You’re commended someone for birthing 16 children! I suggest a different word! Irresponsible]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m off to the trainer today @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/EtaT9kIVCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyTopBucs @EmptySeatsPics @geoff_calkins Hey, let’s just cool this out. We know who we are and don’t worry abou… https://t.co/ZRWSisOeUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized God is a woman yep took a long time but its the truth AMEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona Department of Transportation sign above Interstate 10 in Phoenix. "Caution Ahead: Stubborn Belly Fat causes roll over "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elilehrerdc @NickZaiac read your article on the CO 2 person train crew bill. Clearly, you have not done the job no… https://t.co/5dAJ6Fntph]]></document><document><![CDATA[GHOSTFACE KILLAH #STANCESOCKS stancesocks #PEACESOULDENIM #BILLYJEANS #BJ97 @ Billy Jeans Denim Workshop https://t.co/cv6TGbVMFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnmilrad @TTrogdon That will do it with SSW at surface. https://t.co/hvZwArhKO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't the new Republican party. Racism and misogyny has been spewing out of this party for a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMCPresident @StateofColorado @CityOfTrinidad @Nature_Colorado @tpl_org @COParksWildlife @GreatOutdoorsCO Thank yo… https://t.co/lJaoh6oxin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a few can understand @ayednicole @ItsKweenKay_  friendship 🤣🤣 they have came a long way from 2013 https://t.co/ShhTiKdsZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerrancejames I hear ya. For most of the year it's actually been fairly straightforward. Struggling between Fla, B… https://t.co/x5Zk3IgQDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[من أهم إكتشافاتي اللي أنا فخور فيها إني طحت على لبن في أمريكا، لبن بمواصفات خليجية.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbuxman Hey bub. If you’re around tomorrow would love to find a time to catch up before you bounce out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katkelly14 @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Agreed.... https://t.co/Kb5AnzUmLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A proud #lion 🦁  I #LoveLions I saw this art piece at the State Fair this past 2018 #Art #Artwork @ Arizona State F… https://t.co/6CxpdCC4Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Private label #clothingbrand always has fresh new stocks according to the change of seasons. Here are the important… https://t.co/R5N9BLNiyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruno is 5’5” Cardio is 5’6”  I’ve got money on Bruno standing on a box to look taller. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrinkallCoach @MichalettiKWU @MountainDew @HendricksonKWU @Myers_KWU @Webb_KWU @CoachSallayCSC @Fleming_Coach… https://t.co/fVLZFAkonq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bluengold34 @jeremym480 @Crazzyintheusa Where I'm from, that's a proper hello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWahlenNBA The fact that a fan would even engage with a player shows a complete lack of maturity and yes his tweets are disappointing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuteFairy Funny how that shit works. Everybody got they own vices. Shit I’ve seen alcoholic motherfuckas. Worse off then dope fiends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might have to give that show....the cut-ins from thst beast present the most unsettling vibe...like from that night...why go through that.]]></document></documents></author>