<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Such a fun lunch catching up with great friends ggtdllord41 ❤️❤️❤️ @lanceesimmons #greatfriends #friendsforlife… https://t.co/yEJjLAIWBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teenwolfgray72 @YouTube @BrianHullsVoice @evynnehollens @PeterHollens ABSOLUTELY AMAZING !!!!!! as always… https://t.co/HGxPtgsWOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desiree_bastos @Niih54118223 @mayconn28 @PassareliCibele @dilmabr @zehdeabreu @mariadorosario PresidAAAAAntaaaaaaaaa..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We can only hope that after your demise those who eulogize speak just as kindly ad you have. Perha… https://t.co/Zg0K5HOArI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always is a good time for our Churrasco Argentino: grilled outside skirt steak, accompanied by our famous chimichur… https://t.co/t5L73TCuL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Ghost White Stout by @OronoBrewingCo @ Orono Brewing Company - Bangor — https://t.co/IALB3UkOlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did my best and my best is good enough! - from the Oscars tonight! https://t.co/IpK6D34QCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjohag @GovMikeHuckabee You got that wrong..no rep has been charged and impeached for screwing on the White House… https://t.co/ioxoMvOffI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight savings is this Saturday and TBH, this might be one of the best things I’ve heard all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite days #olympicnationalpark @ Olympic National Park, Hoh Rainforest https://t.co/QJVzjYCOIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, going to Whole Foods at any time of day in LA is an extreme sport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I was spending today with my best friend @laurenmh11 and these tacos :( love and miss you SOOOO MUCH 😭❤️ https://t.co/15MZQOlezq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatherineDines @elle_dee_see @AlgonquinColleg Yes Katherine, your daughter is doing some amazing work!! I remember… https://t.co/tmiotpGVmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Got rid of all those job losing Obama Regulations  #MAGA not counting ALL the others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValentinoAndy77 @penguin_promo @robcharles1969 Happy Valentine's Day Bro! I hope your day is awesome!! https://t.co/SmO9iBgBsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 7 and i’m about to take my first nap of the day... goodnight/morning everyone (,: 🏐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to pair up my birds. Figuring out which birds go best with which birds for #accbaltimore #hoopart… https://t.co/6XAPh1NIGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt Sure. And Mitch McConnell a vote on the GND because he wants to support… https://t.co/EadUkgyKGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[GirlsBB: 6A Area (14) Beaumont United 39 Pearland 40 F-OT Shewolves inaugural season ends at (35-1) #409Sports… https://t.co/xoZtksSnR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee Absolutely,  AOC, at 29, is incredibly brazen and arrogant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday @polaspilates came to rehearsal and during lunch she healed my body and strengthened my spirit. #grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just keep thinking about how I worked really hard to have a rockin summer bod.. lost 33 lbs... then got knocked up. Maybe next year 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Ponch's Porter by @denizensbrewing at @brasstapfitz — https://t.co/TlcRAPjnqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great discussion about music, screenwriting, big wave surfing and activism. I’m inspired by Bianca Valenti, Victori… https://t.co/Cna6j2aSFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @wackyvorlon haha. I like the completely unplanned nature of this project already]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are you coming back?   We want you Well but you are definitely missed. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Destroyed by Hippie Powers” deserves to always be played in arenas!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @tomreardon3 @JohnLaMaster @TICalculators #T3IC2019 #winners]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @Drake and @rihanna get on another single together? The airwaves need you both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Uh, if you live in NYC and there is a billboard in Times Square how can it not be for the locals? So a Nike bi… https://t.co/8D3YeJZxqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyParton   Jan Drake Bakke  @007hotmail  Mar 7 ""Enter the Light" radio show" hosted by Sacred Embers on Thursd… https://t.co/Iy8tqXXgmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElegoMall I think the blue is nice but the brown is my favorite!! @philbh77 , @Mivele70, @ @mstephens156 ,@irwansyah_vape]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MsHanReads to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Each… https://t.co/8Z3OirjK7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently Valentine’s Day is the day uber drivers want to complain about their significant others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganCotton Yeah it was so rude I was like omg why would someone do that....]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone checking the syllabus to see how much of their grade they just lost on that engr exam https://t.co/Xl7DY2WWgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganKidgerPM I’m so glad you liked it! Any beautiful lines worth recording?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarALardass is trending. What a time to be alive 😂 https://t.co/rMffS6fT10]]></document><document><![CDATA[tuesday’s are always my favorite day of the week because a. i’m not at work and b. it’s @GoodTrouble night! #GoodTrouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdixon1234 Yup! Fully "professional"! Me, my best work peeps, sun, sand, and a whole lotta mathematicians... Paradise...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my Lyft driver I’m so sorry for having you take me to the hood this early.💀 he said “ehhhhh it’s all good. We all gotta die some day”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t think I would ever miss my college friends this much but fuck I wanna break down and cry I miss them so much. Idk what to do💔😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish i could’ve been born with a talent so my life would be a little bit easier]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 2️⃣3️⃣ , This Saturday 🗣 Official Black History Parade Afterparty 🎭🔥🖤 Hattiesburg MS at Club Empire ‼️ Juk… https://t.co/jf6VcEaAyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 @AOC @errollouis Aoc ! Doesn’t respond because she can’t ! Sad us congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, I needed a few minutes to recover. But I am still #reading Record of a Spaceborn Few. The alien sections, the I… https://t.co/EGS4rqLzUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ve watched this a hundred times... I absolutely love this guy 💙💛💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[....and then I arrive home and find this on my computer...😘❤️💌💐😍.  Thank you wyguy_2.0 !  You made my day!😘😘 .… https://t.co/qoBmFgYJdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the dog while y’all are sitting at this bar? This is irresponsible. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Luimelia  #AmarEsParaSiempre  #luimeliaeh #loveiskind #loveisunderstanding #luimeliaEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 That’s why AOC went for a list of other witnesses and set it up to go for his taxes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoomPrevails @BDisgusting You know what? I totally read this as favorite 90’s movies and not favorite 90’s HORROR movies. You’re correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekpiquette dont be so quick to let them cut on you!   I have some therapy that can help!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It wasn’t a “hearing,” it was a taxpayer funded pep rally, and it was totally devoid of facts. The DC voucher progr… https://t.co/xWkHYBeez5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Mom and Dad! Happy Valentines Day! #bestparentsever #flowers @crstwdflowers @ Crossroads, Kansas City https://t.co/gF6k6X9kHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#massive #snow in #snowmass #forreal 😵🤡😜#snowday2019 https://t.co/3gRuoCC0Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[KR is sending Tatiana picture from the ✈️. He is flying commercial.. 👍. Thinking about her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Thank you for being a strong voice. Like many others I look forward to your tweets. Hateful violent… https://t.co/BmfAtKclk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun with my Tatum! #yayatime #yaya #tatum #granddaughter 💜 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/Tm3xLNdOUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyCar @robertwickens @itsKarliWoods So happy for you @robertwickens !!!!😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes Could you focus on the Russia part. I think you are missing the bigger issue here. Focus sir, focus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to start IVs and repping my favorite team. 💉🤘🏼@astros https://t.co/NZes2EasVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan maybe wasn't paying attention to all the hearings because he was too busy teying to cover up Trumps cri… https://t.co/YCmGBFHnuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIVA VENEZUELA - MADURO SE VA!! TODA EUROPA SE UNE EN SU C0NTRA - COMPAR... https://t.co/1OPwAGdzsd via @YouTube#vivavenezuelalibre]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is from my friend, Brittany Scott. This was also me at one time. Thinking it was too expensive. I always tell… https://t.co/iAF2WGjmfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bebesexy09 @blairfan4life @lldubs @MauriceBenard I think so too. and yes whatever happens Mdoubs will rock this SL… https://t.co/3JbQP5aaMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovin’ Cali. Honestly, girls in Ohio have been either disinterested or hostile and not respectful.  So sorry 🤷🏻‍♀️ not my fault]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riverdale is the worst show on television that I cannot stop watching. They just tried to get me to fear a guy call… https://t.co/K1rLfH9A4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is allowed to read my mind because all my thoughts are definitely in Comic Sans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe  I am sorry for your Mother’s passing. My Mom had Alzheimer’s dementia for too many years. Nothing is… https://t.co/0zeNGDKoue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberUveges She was an older lady at the nursing home we do hair at so I wasn’t offended 😂 she normally neverrrr s… https://t.co/P8qOPYDTrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nextbigcarthing @NBCNewsTHINK @AOC @kurtbardella What proof of that?  That sounds like a Fox hyperbole thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMG24resist @funder @TXHiker @realDonaldTrump Here let me help you. TRUMP:  "Michael Cohen is a liar.  This is a w… https://t.co/UInXNiTUm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that girl In your city &amp; she don’t come see you ...she somebody else girl  stop wasting ya time ⌛️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scalzi I would just like to say that I only moved to Arizona from Georgia 5.5 yrs ago, so...well crap. I guess I h… https://t.co/jnHMxzuOAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you P!nk! #beautifultrauma #BeautifulTraumaTour #pink https://t.co/j0Cr7Dg651]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apartamentos disponibles para rentar de 1, 2 y 3 habitaciones.  Con seis planos de planta diferentes entre los que… https://t.co/UwI88LiE1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadams276 literally does this &amp; this kind of sums up how I feel about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cronica @NatachaJaitt Porque nadie le dio bola cuando la violaron?La maldad de la gente no discrimina,a todos nos… https://t.co/mmBKg4YctT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids nowadays would never feel the pain of the constant roasting you would get if you wore Champion back in middle school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftyPVBFL @bubbagump324 Considering everything else being so damn depressing right now, I live for pics of those precious critters!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“#geneediting allows researchers to develop better genetics for #crops much more quickly to fight off disease.” -… https://t.co/wQmbkNY0rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Christmas Day in #Cincinnati when I got my FIRST of many guitars. I thank the Creator for my mom who bought me… https://t.co/rudWsKPUrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suficiente con ver tus fotos para ver de qué lado estás. Lastima que no me di cuenta antes “amiga”. https://t.co/QrGnnzmwUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekPlease This! Every song P!nk sings sounds the same to me. That’s why she’s always a skip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeThePlan I'm reading "The Great Awakening" on Scribd. Check it out: https://t.co/sp1ihz2Ns8 Q book.  read free for 30 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our very own sunshine @DominiqueP_C is in first.  Let's help keep her there.  100 votes a day at… https://t.co/PpWLvJqt4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenT_BSNRN @LeffingwellDan The fact that his hat gets launched off at the end is ridiculous! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBudden Good morning Joe! My name is Raven I’m a visual artist based in LA. I’d love an opportunity to shoot 📸 y… https://t.co/v3W90xjoed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a man who will sing sugar ray at a restaurant with you @ShardNet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump He looks like he just exited the latrine with his pants still around his ankles! 😆😆😆😆😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little two face for #sacfashionweek yesterday. I love showing my creative side with my fancy brushes. Can’t wait… https://t.co/Hk5mi8xSvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always fun to see your Legislation &amp; Regulation professor in the news!  @BYULawSchool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenMcSallyAZ for sharing your story and speaking your truth.   And thank you @SenGillibrand for your lon… https://t.co/anxaWQQ4lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahsyndergaard @captainmarvel @Marvel @brielarson Don't ever cut that hair Thor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta love the hilarity hockey mom quotes - Google Search #mirth #snicker #grin #funny https://t.co/NbYsiD3d6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @TFtakeaction @southernwayjim @Tweets4MAGA @DanCovfefe1 @TrumpOrBust2020 @VFL2013 @DaRealGrizzle… https://t.co/V8oM0NDjSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19… https://t.co/0Q2HSLdYwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason I love lo-fi so much is because the hats and snare are slightly out of sync with the beat. The first tim… https://t.co/8fqunIURo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetgrubes this Kanye track will always remind me of the 2010 ALCS. I'm sad YouTube took down that video otherwis… https://t.co/0VAu1MK4aE]]></document></documents></author>