<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Tell me he doesn’t look like EVERY NAZI in every movie you’ve ever seen !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay @CNN @JohnAvlon If the report was released and he says there is zero Russian involvement the left will only… https://t.co/r8RCMzYNAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[tmelikian leading his first staff meeting for mauryhills Columbia. Seeking to answer the most pivotal question of a… https://t.co/PnOKBpxU9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonMaly @SenatorBaldwin @SenRonJohnson @RepRonKind @repmarkpocan @OPENPhysEd @WHPEOffice @USGamesSE Those smil… https://t.co/2PCV2IkIuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstelleGoodwin Eh......., you know, Estelle, I never was a cure fan. What about you? What's your level of fandom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me on Instagram! Username: vonwolf9 https://t.co/usbAeFJGTT https://t.co/nkAIR672um]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrandHustleGang checkout a snippet of this artist new ALL NIGHT LONG #tonydamico317 #reigngangornothing #newtalent… https://t.co/XHZoFqur6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me exchanging football for baseball after hearing that Bryce Harper just signed a $330 million dollar deal🤯 https://t.co/316CQxNP0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT It is now in… https://t.co/6tzJ2ftCow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_1791 @WashTimes So, in profiling traffic stops now ,one must determine a certain kind of erratic driving? Wi… https://t.co/kLbQNULskK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NetflixIsAJoke "I could but it's garbage night and I want to get all your garbage."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa The whole thing is so stupid and #redneck, I had to give #JussieSmollett a mullet in Photoshop. https://t.co/P1lQPB2Vb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[As many years as I’ve been in this business.. This is actually my first real Blue Blazer.  #mixology #blueblazer… https://t.co/I2Rn3S6TLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RishardDensmor1 @CoachFagan_5 @__CoachMaye @Rivalsfbcamps Congrats on ur Air Force offer 🦅✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartYasso @MichaelCollin @bostonmarathon @runmeb @JordanHasay @ShalaneFlanagan @karagoucher We got to look 👀 out for each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now #TXLege has competing TCUP Expand bills by @StephanieKlick and @DonnaCampbellTX. Both medical professionals… https://t.co/B9ZWJ1q1hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athlete’s Sunday’s  9pm : Let me get some homework done  9:01pm : *remembering you have 6am practice* https://t.co/k3cLCUtdLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for the meme sections in the museums when we’re all chillin at like 85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersForDays If they land a superstar because of hin then their job is done. Done real well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelockhart 😂😂🤣In all the excitement I had forgotten about..... hey.... you don’t think it could be....🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyFilosa As i told u these games lost there fun with 8 innings of A ball players. Ppl where buying tickets to… https://t.co/s5jUxY6ZKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am shocked and offended by the New York Times’ comments on “ghostin’”... ARE YOU DEAF?! https://t.co/vvWnQxMjTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, we got a RE2 remaster and now we’re getting a remaster of #LinksAwakening for Switch?   What Hyperborean god of… https://t.co/3Wei2WSJpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonAndDeb dude don’t forget actor, I saw Fred Durst play a bartender on House once.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyHeyItsConrad @tonyschiavone24 @WHWMonday would love to have you guys watch inyh Mind games. https://t.co/m70WCHFqVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megmmag I’m a big Kinkaid guy , but he KILLED his trade value in the last 2 months he has some of the worst goalte… https://t.co/9ew5UJeha8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary DeCarlo (Steam) -  Na Na Hey Hey Kiss Him Goodbye https://t.co/5qA62fJGC9 via @YouTube Gary DeCarlo had a great voice !]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must resist the insistence to have the last word. #HolstonConvo19 Jerry Russell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StoolGreenie I’m starting to think the best realistic scenario is 4 seed vs Indiana and I’m ok with that. The Pace… https://t.co/vavQoVzxQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW &amp; UNFILTERED: An honest review of the #gayapps 😈 https://t.co/0xN7Hkw1XW https://t.co/KgNObT5eSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate 🍫 lady or vanilla lady??? let I answer first chocolate 🍫 1 of i flavor 👌💯 HIT THE LINK in bio.… https://t.co/Qm7fK9GQku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlegriaFox Good morning, Michelle, and Happy Taco Tuesday! Nice red dress! I hope you have yourself a nice day at… https://t.co/R1P5YQisEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello My Queen @MsCharlotteWWE I found u and look like a true princess of the WWE lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decent peanut better flavor, light, smooth - Drinking a Cloak of Feathers by Home Brewing Co. @ Home Brewing Co.  — https://t.co/YvD33zHd0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks kind of funny, worth checking out 👍🏾  Spy series #WhiskeyCavalier is slick, silly and nothing new https://t.co/PxGwDxWP9W via @nypost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you please go find something to do and stop bothering folks? @AOC I’ve never seen anybody wear out their welcom… https://t.co/75FIMCFstO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Nancy Pelosi thinks she’s the boss she needs to get off her high horse , Their are 1.7 million illegals… https://t.co/UTvs5Qd7v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doug_nagel I’m amazed all my friends are either married or engaged what a night mare the dating world is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleWBZ4 @MattNBCBoston @Met_CindyFitz @clamberton7 @ShiriSpear @NWSBoston @WX1BOX 4”  17°  Hopkinton 15-252]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakey50_ I’m just gonna assume you’re a fat piece of shit because you don’t have your picture as your avi. Fuck of… https://t.co/93n74SOG1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been squeezing a stress ball all day.  Today just isn't my day,  better luck tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woahlyssa @AmericanIdol @ABCNetwork @katyperry @LukeBryan @LionelRichie @RyanSeacrest @mrBobbyBones Thank you! I’ll keep singing🎙😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBowmanDC I think you keep posting the same videos...Or Claire plays against Arlington every week. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have seriously had this on repeat for the past like 2 years forever grateful for sodown saw him live and didnt even… https://t.co/QBlMcvqv9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeriesBooks @DrNealHouston @tedcruz @benshapiro Thats not true at all...Republicans and conservatives alike are ag… https://t.co/fbPZpky2Dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Authoroux I keep having the opposite problem, get new game wind up back in Destiny. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fashion Mall just seemed like multiple malls that just fused together and annexed more stores over the years...… https://t.co/SoJqXsF7FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newspapereditor That would be so cool. Maxwell Smart is due for a hipster revival.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuddhistEthics Shambhala is not a cult. I participated in their programs at some length over a period of years, th… https://t.co/ua9Nv6YdJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalelle Seems-it is awful, it’s a fabrication, it’s just a flat out lie, lie upon lie, a lie that he paid for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom this about nailed it. the GOP  has failed in it's duty to defend, the Constitution, the office and in… https://t.co/RwNmwjlwU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leftfieldmike with all of the snow on the ground this made me think of this video, I don’t know why this is so fun… https://t.co/mxDa04Dtb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpenceTillman Depends on what I’m guilty of. Example...If I’m guilty of speeding, I’ll take being rich!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmachlan @peterdaou @SpeakerPelosi She doesn’t want impeachment because she’s realizing Mueller’s investigation is… https://t.co/UUbz8XumG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can't forget that Planned Parenthood was founded by Margaret Sanger, an avowed eugenicist (q.v.) and virulent ra… https://t.co/B7qKHvugC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDPomp @937theFan @JoeStarkey1 I don’t even have the volume on and I can hear the whezzzing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bokamotoESPN Seeing as an interim title is literally meaningless, why would Tony take that fight? He should get Kh… https://t.co/Nd1LeQ834s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have the right to remain silent... https://t.co/yE0hm95q2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Coconut Key Lime Pie Imperial Cream Ale by Hydrosaurus Brewing @ The Citrus Blossom — https://t.co/uXnaa5Q7iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UN_PGA @UN @paularisikko @JuttaUrpilainen @sauerka @FinlandUN @FinGovernment nulTI laTer al Izn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive and moving keynote by @kmorrisjr yesterday morning. It’s always great to see and hear about the continue… https://t.co/lZPMkf8v4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Compop7 @BartAllenImpuls Just because there may be some tokens in there, doesn’t mean it’s not a hate group. Try a… https://t.co/CZMUSRwgCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrong Cono.  get your facts straight. some of these blue states are bankrupt bc of dem control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trailandultra A2: Nope. I can barely plan what I’m going to have for lunch tomorrow. #ultrachat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or we could stop glorifying mass murderers. Back before we had 3 cable news channels and social media this stuff wa… https://t.co/dW0CcWekoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiburonJaro8 @TwitterSupport @TwitterSeguro @TwitterMexico Queeeee https://t.co/jqK2E5ff68]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD SAYS BE CHEERFUL NO MATTER WHAT PRAY ALL THE TIME THANK GOD NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A grand #IPA to finish a #Sunday in #Colorado - Drinking a Conspiracy IIPA by @bluesprucebrew @ Blue Spruce Brewing… https://t.co/v5MGIbF7YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuscularDevelop #LSCSports TO ALL  #WorkOutWarriors #GettinAfterIt #LetsGetIt  #BodyBuilders #PowerLifters… https://t.co/epOj9NEy7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[While attending an event this weekend I told an elected official from #Westpointms  “it’s good to see you” he repli… https://t.co/8eJpn7A2Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IreneSDavis Hi Irene, I’d love to join the list. My email is physio.jho@gmail.com Looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edmonds_tim @joeyedmonds5 @WyomingSports Congratulations Coach Edmonds, Joey, and the entire Edmonds family.  This… https://t.co/mptvc1y6co]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to vote out republicans in 2020. If we want to fix America. Republicans are no longer responsible. https://t.co/LcND6ombbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling like I’m cool if the Dolphins signed Trey Flowers and cool if we don’t. We’re gonna have space for the… https://t.co/8KJPFNtWnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamfgoldberg Atkins never kidnapped Alex Lifeson https://t.co/QbAWSauzmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best sleep I’ve ever gotten is when I have the rain sounds on! Don’t knock it until you try it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I would love JD Clowney on the Falcons, the money could be too much to make sense. If only the cap didn’… https://t.co/deWnsp04W4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMilesLuna Oh damn I missed that. I was too busy looking at the Machamp crossing guard. https://t.co/pu1YorXNSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marybeth_Gay You are the best! Those kiddos are lucky to have you in their lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want our money, add value to our lives. Don’t try to steal value from our lives @WavesAudioLtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met Robert Rodriguez on his way to direct a film in Mexico https://t.co/IAbF8fpAwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prayer for today. It’s not about me.  . . . #crucifiedwithchrist #truth #itsnotaboutme #myprayerfortoday @ Weymo… https://t.co/5LWyIHIgzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I associate myself with a weird bread of people lol I love it though if anyone life makes no sense it is mine 😂 but I'm still here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaEinDC Democrats going to have an interesting convention with Corbynites ascendant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittenRescuer LOL. Lies. It's not interesting at all. For any reason :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDiffley7 @marcdemaco69 The chips and salsa is one the things going for them. And the salmon topped with that mang… https://t.co/tGuS9ByLKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_sxls if by superior you mean not better than May babies then you’re absolutely correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Youngwood crossed 15K. Time 02:12:04, pace 11:33 min/mile, est. finish 8:49 am https://t.co/xtMroUsd6R #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/CrhricEFiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most expensive car ever sold. Bet you could buy several cars with the insurance payment.  "Take a look at the world… https://t.co/e3eWxoLRzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlayZeKyriarchy If you don't know about "cloc", it counts lines of code and lines of comments in a bunch of differ… https://t.co/ibzJa4f4zC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I walked away from the edge of that roof and somehow survived all the homophobic things I saw and heard in society,… https://t.co/DfFU1e9BAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyMarlow51 I wore my satchel into Walmart and felt so liberated. You're a true icon. @Taylor_Kinzler https://t.co/GDWQHI6Rfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope we don’t have to call in the army #djgimports #nofiltertshirtco #sportit #lifesnotfair #coachinglife… https://t.co/QPkiLtepMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[03.01.2019 ........ the madness is coming!  🏀🏀🏀 #marchmadness @ Towne Lake Hills Golf Club https://t.co/iq4t9uPnww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwrGolfer @RobertLusetich His history cause lets face it he did not become cheap overnight,so word gets around...p… https://t.co/Qq2a8dckcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump She joined The enemy she became the enemy too. That alone gets her citizenship, born here or not, revoked. Good riddance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fejimanz I’m praying for you and yours tonight brother. I’m so sorry for your loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Shoulders and Arms”  Giant Set: 1. DB Shoulder Press (4x12) 2. DB Alternating Upright Row (4x12 ea) 3. DB Bicep Cu… https://t.co/xqUEKGVocF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradPeel3 Proud of you ! I was delivered from alcohol nearly ten year ago it is a true blessing !]]></document></documents></author>