<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i always wanted to JUST so i could ride the elevator in elementary school .. then the summer going into middle scho… https://t.co/jodWFGkx2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitsy on her way to her new home in Florida @vianneygriffins @dtraina17 @jpicha1 https://t.co/b68XhtyAxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Look up testosterone and it’s affects on the human body!  #science]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaKingHR @lakendradavis @AdrianDJohnson2 @LL2573 @AshleyBSiller @krburton2007 Thank you @ShaKingHR You make my da… https://t.co/kzUCWOiqfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1 Homework is fine tuning what you learned at school. As a parent, the homework I appreciate is when my 16 yr old… https://t.co/vHpDoIKiqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are very lucky in NH. Anyone can get their photo taken with the possible next president. The 2020 candidates are… https://t.co/RkDEJREakZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man attacked a gay man waiting for a cab downtown last night, if you have any info on him please contact SLC p… https://t.co/2ynM4ToMBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Wings Zadina on the ice earlier today in preparation for his second NHL game. The team takes on the Canadiens toni… https://t.co/lvfebltB35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Bernie Sanders did not vote for Russian sanctions, did not vote for Magnitsky Act.  So I have conclu… https://t.co/ClLjc3dUQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basnatural My dear it was a pleasure meeting you finally and just having a grand time. I miss you already but I kn… https://t.co/kWRbrfOAr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha! Right!?! Propose already Jesse! @ArenBuchholz @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV #Hearties]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for my forever valentine💗 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/HATtoCisSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHarveyFM @SteveTVShow @moworldwide This is a true friendship God Bless you both love y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there a hotel search tool that will track ALL of the potential discounts you might qualify for (AAA, various hot… https://t.co/cYOkdtZITj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Weekend! Check out our unique and beautiful Cascada earrings at https://t.co/dPJYvy5bV4 they are 3 inches lon… https://t.co/hkaeO8OYF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a wet breezy Wednesday watch @WPLGLocal10 onair and online https://t.co/HvsZMzlYcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I wonder if they practice the timing of the "thaz right" affirmations that they give to one another before they go on air...]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I strongly dislike about school is that all of my tests are given right before spring break but aren’t gr… https://t.co/LsskiluZLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pooramor try finding at places that have veggie/vegan options!! meat is always cooked w/ dinner at home so i do my… https://t.co/Z5ftjgsJwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t be a chaser. be the one who gets chased. you are the tequila, not the lime🥃😚 https://t.co/jeLzbWhBAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Dude if you do the chord in Cb I’ll do the one in D  Hannah: wow that’s so generous of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not emotionally spiritually mentally financially or physically prepared for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fendermanjazz @robcharles1969 @MadisRaeOfHope Sure, do you have the link?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another warm run.... and I do NOT miss the snow.  🤷‍♂️😎🏃 #run #trailrun https://t.co/nmhZV0StG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[SURPRISE POPUP!!!  I’ll be spicegirlin at 6:30pm thespicesuite w/beadsbywoo  ❤️ @ Spice Suite https://t.co/h6ajo8SfWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opens tomorrow!!!  Come out and support the arts! @InGhostSide @fauquierhs @johannahuberr @fabulyssa09… https://t.co/l4NyIANXzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADFRNTBooklist @OBHistory @BsamCanada @ADBCC777 @orbitbooks @imbobswaget @miguelsanv1 https://t.co/KcplQfwLj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missdarma I figured he'd get this story because there's no Carl on the show..I wonder how the fandom would feel if it was Carl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do makeup artist make money for real unless they charge dumb money and have clients daily? Who is paying for th… https://t.co/S1WuIyMPSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Heyzeus by @melvinbrewing at @TheWineSpotCH — https://t.co/LlVBEOrw9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm got emotional bc this the last match #TheShield will be together @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins #DeanAmbrose https://t.co/4yoX1Pe6d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!!! 🤗💥 ... jackornely opened escrow on her pocket listing! ... #andrewsoasis is back up and running aft… https://t.co/yylt5fx73j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just4BeerLovers @GLBC_Cleveland @badhopper @JohanBBT @cellmavin @beerguypdx @ManvsAle @lhtetrick @Paul_TheBeerGuy… https://t.co/9YiIEybWhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myvillage @themacdallas with #alfarrow #thewhitehouse #wrathandreverence #elysepignolet #sandowbirk… https://t.co/RPze1d3Fjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Molson Canadian by @molsoncoors @ Waterdown Legion — https://t.co/Af3WIjHbCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[En mis tiempos de paramédico PPP significaba otra cosa, ahora es una canción pegagoshaaaa💃🔥.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brace yourselves. The crowds at the bars tonight are about to be OC🤧 ...  ...but I’ll see y’all there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading Mr Hills book #fivepresidents . A resident of mine was also in the SS . Ooh the stories… https://t.co/P0uWN5c9Nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION OWES THE AMERICAN PEOPLE RESTITUTION ⚖️ @SpeakerPelosi  @RandPaul  @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #friyay Shipmates! Have a fun and safe weekend...remember your safety brief and #glowbelt! 😂 @SandboxUS… https://t.co/XtpCfeuvys]]></document><document><![CDATA[This breaks my heart! Clean up after yourself at the beach and everywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody tell Smack to set up Jakkboy vs Saga, it’s gotta be on Banned though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If events right now call the word "apocalyptic" to mind, recall that the word comes from Greek apokalyptein: "uncov… https://t.co/AalZVBzzkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@novelastime @Venusdenko @horadlanovela @telenovelo @NubiaArizaga @El_Buen_RogerMx Y porq hay que decir lo mismo tú… https://t.co/tP8jt8H2Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Florida Strawberry Festival https://t.co/UbmKu3KP5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Can’t wait to see @Trevornoah from @TheDailyShow tonight! I used to live in Table View. Excited to hear some lekker jokes. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha!  Worked like a charm!!  She didn’t even notice a difference except maybe that it was even more delicious than u… https://t.co/ZaOENk6vMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncusack @BernieSanders I’ve wished you would run. I’ve prayed for someone to defeat Trump. But I’m sorry, it’s… https://t.co/sma7Ib3ee1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just enjoy life. Driving in a different  #Lane. I own the #Gifted  🔑☝️😇📝✍️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such an awesome week with @BryanMRussell working our teachers in PLC. Every student can succeed and the tools t… https://t.co/NZE3C570on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YiippyTweets Hey, please follow me  back. I've reached my limit right now. So I can't follow you back right now. T… https://t.co/PXk1eNPcrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porlagoma @JorgeGestoso por cierto @jorgegestoso empleado de telesur no es un periodista, es solo parte del aparat… https://t.co/JxHCQ6ZA5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to have had the @FoothillTrojans join me in studio today and even better, we got to have a little dance party… https://t.co/9pvByqZdF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump do you not care about the families whose love ones these murdering dictators have killed or is res… https://t.co/ex3wqIJani]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magueyes floreando en el Cañón de La Carbonera en Arteaga, Coahuila. https://t.co/GMr1Fci61M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullet3600 @LivePdFans @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation @LivePDPundit @warwickripd @officer_jill @K9Viking1 Love the names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanMig98525616 @CassidyTorres_ @kasensmommasav there’s more formaldehyde found naturally in our bodies than in va… https://t.co/hoWghcWKlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jent103 @divergent_ai I think this is a really insightful and often overlooked at view of the trap of experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please just get me every gif of this video? Please. #PleaseMeVideo @BrunoMars @iamcardib]]></document><document><![CDATA[•Went to @gwatsky concert in Pittsburgh. ✔️ •Listen to my favorite music ever✔️ •Hold the man him self, GEORGE WATS… https://t.co/ER7cH5TbH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Dare he mention killing healthy babies??😡 Just wants to benefit the rich??😳 God is NOT HAPPY!! Repent GOVERNOR!!!🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Change is coming to your morning.” I don’t like the sound of that. What does that even mean @K945]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are really mad at John Wayne for an interview from 1971 in playboy???  Really?  That’s how good your lives a… https://t.co/HRG7ly14JL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremy_wightman @NikkiHaley @CondoleezzaRice @JohnBrennan @NBAAllStar @NBA You know she was a never trumper....why… https://t.co/omWQtz6CGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathieeGee @ThatProduceBoy @beckylynnperez @wednesdysociety @0hMyGoff https://t.co/01z7geaz50]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my children will be like this little girl. This. Is. Me. https://t.co/FIOvgxzLhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh.... I lost it at "Jamie Madea Dailey" 😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣  https://t.co/Dl3tuPwuYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisalfonsom @IngrahamAngle Give me a break he stays in the USA and it’s his house]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t agree w his reasoning but Jim Jordan is going TF OFF! #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga is looking BEAUTIFUL tonight.  Girl has it going on tonight😊❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[La semana pasada no fui ningún día a la escuela y hoy me dan el justificante de toda la semana! Gracias Ues]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely moment ..peaceful early morning ..catch and lease fishing...happy fisherman and unique moment ! Have a great day...Bonne journée !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving in my house this week 👏🏼😭🙏🏼 renovations nearly complete and I couldn’t be more proud 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of shots I had to take last night was rigged and you’ll never convince me otherwise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another chance to win tomorrow morning at 6:05 with the #3CrazyHeadlines @991KGGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished 1h:15m:00s of doing martial arts with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/sDzVsRGHoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mi me gusta los chupones pero algo que no puedo es trabajar con niños teniendo unos chupones no se no se me hace moral]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told txt this man and told him I wanted fries ....do yall know this man came from damn near Camilla to Slappey br… https://t.co/xICQTM5lta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Myers and Dana Carvey are the BEST! @TheAcademy #waynesworld #BohemianRhapsody⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mind people talking shit about my toxic habit of going out or drinking bc it’s verrry much true but don’t l… https://t.co/ftfJhKS7au]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aggieteach03 is left handed. #SPRINGBREAK #SJHTEACHERSCAVENGERHUNT #FANTHEFLAME https://t.co/OeTrMm6zwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an Indigenous journalist working among non-Indigenous mainstream media counterparts, some of whom I look to for… https://t.co/bDZyog4POw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never shared this, but look how amazing my go-to @Airbnb in COMO is🤩 https://t.co/zMNd3OL2u0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esp1371 Hopefully she can sleep for a few hours on her 24. By my math, I would estimate she could get up to six comfortably??]]></document><document><![CDATA[~ Her harmony came not through the complete absence of chaos. But in realizing that she was resilient enough to com… https://t.co/Lj9vYfwxs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren Buffett discusses ‘disaster’ contributing to Bay Area exodus in CNBC interview https://t.co/qi2jascDMD via @SFBusinessTimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVNancy @Jamierodr10 @RepGwenMoore They are so jealous of our President...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobotReese Currently im rotating between Mixed Chics and Shea Moisture]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love you, Professor Harold Hill!!  🎼🎭🥁🥳 Fantastic show by all! ❤️❤️❤️ @ Apex, North Carolina https://t.co/cpY00Mj6rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateOtter @FruitKace The Bush Crime family was a baby crime family compared to what's squatting in our WH now… https://t.co/hNNMoz3cnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AftertheArcher @juanluzardom @DiegoFalconVE @IlhanMN Yeah right https://t.co/csk3WpLtCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#uptownvibes #tampa @jahova33604 we out chea #goodmorning @ Centro Cantina Ybor https://t.co/AFceJxG3Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did we go from the positive self-love messaging that is "thank u next" to the complete opposite that is "break… https://t.co/Ny8bGkn1gN]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching A Star is Born yesterday, 2 things became apparent: both Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga should have wo… https://t.co/zQsm8zA5Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of educators ready to learn and hone their craft early on a Saturday morning. #EdCampNKY2019 https://t.co/tFffPq446N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely meta and awesome. The opportunity to hear @JasonReynolds83 and @KielyBrendan in conversation is a though… https://t.co/dsPeViFfbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MONAKatOILS I think we need to let @AnnCoulter in on this.  Trust you @POTUS you have not let us… https://t.co/2n5bpo6vmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly fuck being a woman idgi why so I deserve to be in this much pain to the point where I can't go to work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GroyperSpace @UPS EVERYBODY knows my dog.  She's big and noisy but a total pushover.  The delivery people love her… https://t.co/ybzxDRfi6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a full week of meetings and learning, had the chance to enjoy nature and recharge a bit. This is the Las Vega… https://t.co/PGCWdN9QyQ]]></document></documents></author>