<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Chasing Max Kerman around this massive @arkellsmusic stage trying to take photos is probably the best workout I've had in awhile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I was feeling on our last day in Palm Springs yesterday... 😭 https://t.co/1B3GYHYXAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dolphins are in good position to get a 3rd round comp pick in 2020 for losing Ja’Wuan James depending on how they a… https://t.co/IaOpKWVmXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rememeber I was hella hyped to see you a while back, now you just a bitch nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9NEWS End of our country as we know it. Thanks Polis for signing this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC Sports Streaming channel is the only streaming app that gives me issues! Constantly buffers. I do t think I’ve… https://t.co/DcyNSiNhqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i have kids in the future in prepubescents (when they actin all rebellious) when they try and come for me and… https://t.co/IcTqWjtJTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta start off with my boy. The twunk. The coolest fighting game character ever.   Guilty Gear's resident pool hus… https://t.co/sLzr7CPd7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Montrezl Harrell is easy one of my favorite players in the NBA. Dude out works everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargaretOrr @wdsu What is the critical river level at the bonnet carre?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the top 3 hottest chicks now in the @ExOnTheBeach house is @00Hitsdiidii, @angelababicz and @NicolexoRamos.… https://t.co/kG0akT42uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[future: “Dirty soda spike lee, white girl -“ me: RUN THAT SHIT BACK!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's day dinner! (@ The Nantucket in Crockett, CA) https://t.co/H4VqwmMJyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDietzen @CallawayGolf Have you been to the Pro-Am in Pebble Beach?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WmScottBlair @KentSailor @roosterpisces @janetshoemake @Marizellell @CharlieD2749 @DoodlesTrks @azredhen @yrwol7… https://t.co/kwAuaFwZuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this mean we’ve made it? When you start getting these? 😂😂😂😅😅😅 https://t.co/3tKpAg62NX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sneakzs I’ll be gone until the end of the month latest beginning of April]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Plantmore1 @SeeDotRun We could roll with that. https://t.co/mpO9aavE04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iona Preps Isaac Gonzalez opens the 2Q with a 3ball to make it 15-13 @MSM_basketball! Update... @AidanAidanh hits f… https://t.co/xzayY3Xqld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy and Jay getting much better. Someone loves his mommy!!#adoringeyes#BestValentineEver❤️❤️❤️💪💪💪 https://t.co/Vl9gZZJvM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have all misunderstood. I genuinely do not understand in what manner to eat them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunching (at @BumbleLosaltos in Los Altos, CA w/ @mbrianaepler) https://t.co/oKYlRsq6hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually laugh off conspiracy theories but am legit starting to believe #fakemelania might be a thing.   👀👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberalism is a mental disorder a fact proven by the lunacy necessary to believe either of these women rank anywher… https://t.co/oRllCmPHzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, my mom will be there. She’s way funnier and a lot cooler than me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or maybe their decades of over fishing is taking its toll. “Climate change is endangering fish worldwide, shrinking… https://t.co/FyleQL7oO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmack1966 That just isn't true. Divorce courts aren't the leading reason for homelessness. Mental illness &amp; drug addiction are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deskrabbit Unicorn vampire doing the walk of shame. Bursted into flames because it was sunrise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reports of a possible murder suicide being investigated by Oakland County Sheriffs in Commerce Township. @WWJ950… https://t.co/BZFFoLjWVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t celebrate my life when I’m gone. Let’s pop Champagne now. Gday 2/23 I love you Self @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/oZt3r3JsQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best practices professional development #interiordesign #Steelcase #iida #iidaclc #iidanorcal #iidanc weekend discu… https://t.co/Sb4hhJVY8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black &amp; Blau by @oxbowbeer at @novareresbiercf — https://t.co/TOUZcnruTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USTFCCCA @WakeTrack @NCAATrackField So you’re saying he just has to finish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ozzbalddd @dretre91 @adrianh100 Yeah i retired with honors. I was there for 200 Como La Flor’s and 300 Mr. Brightside’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDJIceberg @djplugg Yoo iceberg Mercury The Rain THANKS FOR HOKKIN ME UP ON THE NEW SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding out trinity believes trans queens shouldn’t be on RPDR really should have ruined her but it didn’t because… https://t.co/TgmIOpMFHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So like that Momo figure is legit one of the scariest looking things I’ve seen for a while. I have a fear of humanoid objects as it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATX_fight_club @yogi_lv If you can charge 110, bring in someone who can dig under the fence and install an under g… https://t.co/XnrhGJxyie]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Birthday Spotlight Celebrating The Birthday of Germind 20 Day Birthday Party: March 11 - Ma… https://t.co/XRHoNwDbwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kofi getting to the top 3 is a good sign. Here’s hoping they do give him that program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webertom1 I agree. More voices is a good thing. Unfortunately the bad ones cause a lot of harm and that's  the opp… https://t.co/DhN8C2n5VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Dan, thanks to you, Sean and Mark I’ve been scared as hell for a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiriamLeitaoCom Quando a senhora assaltava banco, fazia reféns e apontava arma pra cabeça das vítimas gostava de… https://t.co/KN9wyEilGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kentuckats1 @hayes_williemze @810BorderPatrol More than 5, less than Zion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wgomezjr inspired a sticky in more than one way. #pun #puns #punny #wordplay #stickymoments #comicstrip #doodle… https://t.co/draE9qNhOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol This would be a classic false binary because Trump fuckin owns you guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea everything a librarian does for a school, then I married one....wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGavrich @Back9Ben @LinksGems @AnthonyPioppi @RichardZokol @TPCSawgrass @PGATOUR @PGAVillage Actually you don’t… https://t.co/Kh6uY1zqjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All good except for one thing, you severely underestimated the power of the people, the real power, not your ignorant base]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Ramblings – Funny Friday https://t.co/rL01Ak22QV https://t.co/VMUDbs5dRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “game is evolving beyond enforcers” crowd isn’t asking for fewer Jarome Iginlas. Many of us still love the true… https://t.co/9EnZbBpr4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations way to play @Mfrauenheim2 #dancing #MarchMadness19 @d3hoops @PtBeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[Age of the autosexual: the people sexually attracted to themselves https://t.co/rglBlJcC6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[PHOTO GALLERY Putnam loses to Bloomfield 59-40 in CIAC Class S second round girls basketball… https://t.co/oG9nWYyRT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why hasn't any car manufacturer used Babyface's "Whip Appeal" in a commercial yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ Good luck on getting healthcare facilities and physicians here in the U.S. to agree to the extremely low… https://t.co/8eeAQdUD9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a Johnny Orr tweet earlier, Johnny would have lost by 20 K-State and beat Baylor by 10. So, I guess, I dunno man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Country roads take me home to Norman!   Gritty road win for this group of freshmen and sophomores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No dejo de pensar en mi novia hermosa y que la otra semana tendremos otro viaje🥰🥰 #minivacaciones @marielrdz92]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are jordyn’s fake lashes disconnected from her real ones or am I just blind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workout done now back to the studio. Join me at the top of the hour for the best of the 60’s, 70’s and more.… https://t.co/wXB8gZOtHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamrath23 @dkess @LeByrne6 Nba guys say he’s top 10 and they make a hell of a lot more than I do to say that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful. - Drinking a Permanent Marker Pen Disguises by @hoofheartedbrew @ DrewHQ  — https://t.co/nycwJvSO0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all give this women too much power over y’all lives and all she did was give head on camera]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_LetsGetIt_ Told @landorosario we have to start getting busy. Need to get on your level!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've decided watching someone I know perform is like my brother watching me take flying lessons. Scary but exciting. #nervesofsteel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Getem_Cool @therealllsnow Nigga don’t spin on the front tho 🤫 nigga be shooting poor lil thomas to pieces]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahck55 Your Murray reference shows lack of depth...he played 13 games that season....thats keeping him fresh? No… https://t.co/kkpGpt6Tv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jana’s soundcheck with the 7-8 Grade State Jazz Honor Band.  Come check it out 10:30am at the Minneapolis Conventio… https://t.co/W40pP2GQhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Sean, unlike some radio hosts, truly understands Mr. Trump.  (I won’t mention any names.....like any F… https://t.co/46MxHry3Rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SohrabAhmari @benshapiro Yep blame others for your chosen mental illness lol  have a tantrum and burn down your house good rebuttal 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @JebBush @StateDept LETS PASS an immigration law we CAN live with for the next 50 yrs... And SUNSET it ev… https://t.co/BBNKefceNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM SO PROUD of my @RedhawksW!! @LMC_RedHawks @LakeMichCollege #ConferenceChampions #njcaawbb #Redhawks… https://t.co/X7IFQUoQug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump Yes you are a milk toast! We are making America Great Again! You must not be keep… https://t.co/o0nH23ZqKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRhodes9 Yeah man I have a deer in the headlights look every time I step in that water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's inside myself that I must create someone who will understand. -Clarice Lispector #Rufskin #ruflife #menswear… https://t.co/12zK0JOlmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mantruths #lifeEmpowerment #TODAY #Todayisagoodday #MakeyourownHappy https://t.co/yI6OxqJl37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaaaaaaaaaaaH_Q @SchulmanShari @politico Look what they do to babies during abortion. https://t.co/KeUkDtyctL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad you didn’t ask @todpalmer that question but we did bring it up on the #4thAnd1 podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaijeChill @Giannis_An34 @TeamJuJu @deshaunwatson @JohnWall @88PKane @JonnyBones @JEFFHARDYBRAND I just copied and pasted bro my bad 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peytonlohaus SO BLESSED TO HAVE MET U !!!!! ps ur skinnie  Glad to see that ur doing well hope it only gets better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Respect for All in Every Room!  Signage should be posted prominently in health care settings. Thanks for the guidan… https://t.co/CNLPF49jR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah well when your boobs are as big as your heart no bra is not the wave]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moon and stained glass II #moon #stainedglass #unionmemorialunitedmethodistchurch #stl #stlouis #handheld @ UMW of… https://t.co/ZNnE1YENoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mentally ill person with Dictator understanding only no hope for America or citizens Allies or any… https://t.co/2P79lrZKaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire @conservmillen @RealSaavedra Didn't take her long to fit right in, did it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Opa_opa_yall @seanhannity Renegotiating NAFTA, the worst trade deal in American history, more than paid for it. He… https://t.co/ozicmCLxQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slim_hillbilly @hogsrul @RyanAFournier Oh buddy he’s your president!! Guaranteed]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it all went downhill after this picture @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/5oB0jYsCAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Cloud Training in Phoenix #GoogleCloudOnBoard #phoenix #Kubernetes https://t.co/x5mf2QHjRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would’ve thought a 2 star would be considered one of the best going into the draft? @JoshAllen41_ is a monster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett So they’re almost as stupid as you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just have noticed how far I've come  radio wise, but that came with weekly airchecks, constant notes.    I just b… https://t.co/bgQRaB0LbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dale Kozel did this, I’ll never forget the look on our lesbian science teachers face... only because he did it to g… https://t.co/xib9Iyo1YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovemyyorkie14 @whatznextfolks @MAGAGwen @joegooding @Boyd_2650 @darhar981 @ChrisRowland9 @Lady_Vi_2U @Maggieb1B… https://t.co/zy7NPzopkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending a busy ass shift with a bowl and breakfast burritos w/ my wife is probably my favorite thing now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview may be aired today and tomorrow on KHOU-TV. @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/d45W1q3YcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searching all the world for one thing. @ San Pedro Garza García https://t.co/izKZl1zsVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GYC_Mark Did you notice "Goldbergs" Cuda the odometer was at 0000.0 and the numbers were at half mast. Does your d… https://t.co/Hb3WY9aAEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria, Nutrition Julia Medina, Social Work, Charles Ozzoude Nursing at Jack Layton School https://t.co/S7NRzvvXK3]]></document></documents></author>