<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[how do we cancel a dead actor?  rapper punchlines? remake his movies with an all-black cast? get someone to dress u… https://t.co/xOk6rliMXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawgatAuburn @dennisdoddcbs Yeah I think if Mullen would’ve stayed that’s close to a playoff contender with that roster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The student that didn’t do his homework or read a chapter might have a good reason.  Don’t assume it’s apathy. Don’… https://t.co/fpoELLHFfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffries Hmmm guess you were pissed out during state of union speech, he covered school thst.  This was about b… https://t.co/FllJfbNSKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago He said he DID forget them. He went back the following day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spadeaudry @rcallimachi @c_mcandrews Though ISIS has been degraded in Syria and Iraq , it still has a presence in… https://t.co/jUhSrSjmr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your family had one of those machines that would rewind the VHS for you really fast you’re upper middle class https://t.co/w5vH1EECoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnVassNascar @JasonandBarney @TruckerS63 That's common for maximum braking effort.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AirBnb booked for @thejmblya with my homie @jayreyes2323 LETSSSSSSS GET ITTTTTTT😤😝😝😝 https://t.co/U24ZhN5ilU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RageQuitGirl @Craven665 I have astro a40s. Not sure what you are running for audio. But it comes with mixer amp. W… https://t.co/faTV1J3F7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FOX4News: #RowlettPD responds to more than a thousand motorist assist calls along a dangerous 3.5mile stretch of I… https://t.co/kO0SMhYMFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Censor keep your head up dude, wishing the best to your family, you have a lot of people that support you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berner415 My submission! Actually Froze up, attachment must be too large. Stays sending!????]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a guy on my train snoring like a flu-ridden water buffalo, and we haven’t even gotten to Newark-Broad St. yet. FML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the conversation has pivoted to whether that aspect of law is actually, currently applied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #DonTheCon.  Proved lying 70%... every time he opens his hole. He's got all the best lies.… https://t.co/9nrhbXsQbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomanReynebeau @OfficialHARIBO and now they are building a plant in Kenosha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s scary when my savings account has more money in it than my checking account. Almost twice as much. Granted com… https://t.co/ohbkBQGt46]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a broker system. Still in awe athletes haven't fully revolted. #gopro #nba.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDLHughley @shawnsapp @Living @get_repost That’s a real fucken teacher!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnny rocks......x skipper of the Nebraska Sluggers the good old days.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino That's why they are after President Trump 24/7. He may not have drained the swamp but he damn sure did expose it. Big time.🇺🇸MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Are you still get paid to do this? If so whoever is cutting the checks must be deaf/dumb/blind. Yo… https://t.co/IjI8bHj95A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aj0kee Surajah you are drinking beer? Meanwhile why is that guy in white shirt looking at your leg in the second picture 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give my mother’s legacy new life by buying yourself your copy!  #writing #mothers #fictionwriting #bookings… https://t.co/mjBdfU7p2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMTigersMBB thank you for the thoughts and kind words....best of luck to our boys and girls 🏀 🏀 🏀 in the next roun… https://t.co/75ZzHwyWAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shared the same air with Adam Sandler last night, and for that, I am grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni Hanoi,Vietnam How to do: IN GOD WE TRUST? at least an effort trying to be made How can our trademarks join to… https://t.co/DXYWhg9stp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s about being strategic in your career path, to get to the place you love.” -@kmin   Play your cards right! #theNSLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone use @LawnGuru_co ? Well let me set u straight. Don’t do it. I’ve been waiting 48 hours for the plow. Three c… https://t.co/aSGxQ70H32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on the 3-peat Coach Vic and the basketball team!!  #2019 Battle for the Ages https://t.co/PD96fIPwwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate This is terribly written. Will you please include the part where @BarackObama says he opposes reparations, a… https://t.co/34hhhdWJAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chefferie du PQ offerte à Véronique Hivon : «Est-ce que ç’aurait changé quelque chose?» https://t.co/TQJRcqM8Gw https://t.co/8OIimeRllc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ibaka got mad for nothing. it was offensive pass interference if anything with his push off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuneMyThang13 @EricLevitsky @Danie1607 @dullman_nonnie @Libtardsmasher @youlosenordys @PhillipDenton @DonsAudrey… https://t.co/o42xu1Cc5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrabsMatt @SecVBBasketball @McQuaidJesuit @PrimetimeBall_ @_AnthonyIglesia Kid looks solid in black and purple https://t.co/S19wGFaBsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisamagnusson Alla arméer har kockar och chaufförer, så ock den svenska armén där det finns ungefär ett fordon på… https://t.co/43FEq1ENVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSmithShow @cesarhfutbol @cmzizzo @JordanCarruth Some guy named Jordan, I think]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianRSobrino @nativecult Yea but that’s still years away, plus AI still need humans to program them so people will still rule]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snoringelbow is in the house!!!! I’d like to share a pizza with you good sir! #PWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slack2thefuture There's no need to whisper. The intended response is loud and clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raging_Red @LisaMei62 @55true4u @michaelbeatty3 @seanhannity @SaraCarterDC @jsolomonReports Red or yellow interest… https://t.co/FqnKpf7a7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsBrownAP @eposthuma Without getting into the specifics of Erica’s situation, I want ‘compliance’ to be part of the way I assess kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente I do want it to be known that I’m a fan of yours Dave... but.... https://t.co/5G94ScIs3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Hales Corner's fire captain's job hangs in the balance as the village continues to investigate why a fire engine… https://t.co/ZahgYyR1i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it more normal for a Hispanic woman or man, to live with their mother from the ages 18-25.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT Monday begins… https://t.co/JbDZrg5VZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dustinsmom89 @RealCandaceO Lord. I hope someone protects the women your proudly Neanderthals encounter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KYL_C343 @ParadojaNFL @Canderslice @SharpFootball @mikefreas1706 They extended obj because he’s a great player, wh… https://t.co/oKpOyVFqAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a terrible Hulu watcher.  Right at the moment I begin to re-engage in the show, it breaks back into 2-3 adverti… https://t.co/3c9bAmUDmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eck43 Great. The first Tweet sounded like 85 games total. Love when you're on the broadcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There comes a point in some Uber drives when you realize your driver just isn’t going to shut up. At that point, I… https://t.co/edngddukAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta Braves vs Philadelphia Phillies spring training game ⚾️ https://t.co/DHB8bWehFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really excited for the Hicks extension. 7/$70m is a great deal for the Yankees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great so so night for the #cornerman #juanjeremy @juanjeremy100 once again cheated out of a victory but this time… https://t.co/yNa0BHYwyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[He responded, " I'll let you know in 20 years." He knew that his greatest victories as a coach of young people had… https://t.co/qMJdD72vsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjammingh @mjg59 It depends on how much time or money you're interested in investing in AmigaOS-compatible Power… https://t.co/6qptQbq1LG]]></document><document><![CDATA[stacys is launching its third collection of limited-edition bags that feature original artwork designed by female a… https://t.co/IoF61I2z0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless @ShannonSharpe @undisputed Is? Will? Lebron be activated??? 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT Good Morning… https://t.co/RnUh84CWqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipcoffey At least he's not declaring A national emergency over it. I'll bet you support that though right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khaliya I dunno I can drive on weed them 5 grams the other day took me down a rabbit hole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave4FtMyers @hmarie52 @MMwiley204 @Arkyhog @jmksd Old Elizabeth is a sick person,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing. I’m sooo happy your embracing yourself for who you are now. You are a strong, beautiful, ind… https://t.co/K7IVhR3Zp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D1Overson @MLBRBI @MLB_YA @ABQTopes @DukeSOFTBALL @WorldSeries @BushElearning @HSUAthletics @HSUBSM @NMSUCatholic… https://t.co/EubllgOiht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senategopfloor No votes ) Sanders (I-VT) Schatz (D-HI) Sinema (D-AZ) Smith (D-MN) Stabenow (D-MI) Tester (D-MT) Ud… https://t.co/kEAFjwJNOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The deadly truth about a world built for men – from stab vests to car crashes: Data Bias based on Gender… https://t.co/zcNsUjhvPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Obstructing our sovereignty is lawless .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Indy I’m headed your way ! Start date May 7th. Learn more email tpatri@mindspring.com #golf #golfinstructor… https://t.co/A971HfD4MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[After x 25 after listening to Fast Car in the past two days I’ve decided I’m packing everything I own and moving away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love your debunking of all this cr@p. Hate it when actual science gets in the way. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last event of #SWW19 for @gsc is the Reseller Awards Dinner. A good meal and entertainment among 800 friends fr… https://t.co/4VNZZtA2rZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz You are NEVER gonna be our voice, you self serving prick]]></document><document><![CDATA[TE analysis and results from the 2019 NFL Scouting Combine.  Including thoughts on Noah Fant, T.J. Hockenson, Kahal… https://t.co/lfzYBgWsa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching WWE Fastlane on the @WWENetwork for only $9.99 a month!!! #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really not that hard just take @SonyaDevilleWWE Goofy persona from Damandyz and apply it to her gimmick]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MisterRogers’ #ethics messages also healed scarred and hurting post-#WWII parents and other adults. For my toddler… https://t.co/b8Msx3xHTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will argue this til the day I die. Those ‘96 All-Star jerseys are one of San Antonio’s Top 10 contributions to ci… https://t.co/IagNV7BH89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah @Charlie33312 3) But...this is exactly what I am looking for out of all of us; If we see "our side" do s… https://t.co/s5rvpQkWNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CineplexMovies I still haven’t seen this movie, I purchased tickets for me and my kids way in advance for opening… https://t.co/yMG4ZlfuiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickGurney Sorry to hear you’ve been having issues. Did you have to get another HD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance What is the most innocent interpretation of the presence of the crosshairs of a rifle scope?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hokie_Hoops @kjblack15 @accmbb Great job!  Inspiring!  Meeting the Challenge!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbsacks According to Bohemian Rhapsody, Freddie Mercury seems to have contracted AIDS by hanging out at truc… https://t.co/bwKuQ6fXpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/MqJszzp5Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an absolute blast with our first @PlayHearthstone #FiresideGathering! Thanks to everyone for coming! More are o… https://t.co/hL4gvzXhnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's merry. Old TV Show  Home Improvement. https://t.co/mM1JsXAzyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE! 🔴😎🎮📺🧨🔫 @DiGiorno #Fortnite #BattleRoyale #XboxOne #TwitchAffiliate https://t.co/sw0p2kGWQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sberrios5171 @Elex_Michaelson I’m not a trump supporter tho. We can do better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP @realDonaldTrump You would think after 2 yrs it would be time to hang it up Mueller....]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poll explains a lot about why ResetERA finds so many games boring. If it's boring, skip it]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. loved this film giantlittleones #directed by keith starring #joshwiggins @josh_wiggins2 @realdarrenmann… https://t.co/BSzQPJ7WWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you hotboxing 4 deep and you don’t take the headrest off the front seats you are doing it all wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanGill317 @LustyNorsemen @Ebron85 We knew nothing about them until Ray J and Kim releases the sex tape.  Hell p… https://t.co/ZpwWMibuA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #DAYTONA500 so far. Happy for @mattdracing they deserve the good run they're having. Still anyone's race though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GardnerKatyg8 I have no recent point of reference for a rebutle.  Other than chocolate....🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defender stumbled off the court sobbing, “Mommy, he’s picking on me.” #TresRules]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand somewhat why people who come from cold climates are the way they are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emersizzle @PrincipalFrench @PrincipalKap @posickj @sheehyrw @mccall_kelley @AllysonApsey @kasnelson… https://t.co/Wl2MtioaCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @AOC Big talk from someone who's committed FEC violations.  #whatatwit]]></document></documents></author>