<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Loved watching. Living storyline. Looking forward to seeing @DougDavidsonYR as well @YandR_CBS #fromthebegining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiildthangggxo Tell me it wasn’t you who air dropped this to me at pink parrot 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waraujo64 @paololuers Este vejestorio piensa con el@dedo chiquito del pie 🦶🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Manners says she feels too young to get a “Legend Award”, but 20 years in a row with sales ranking her in the… https://t.co/0OHmmu7Ajn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHSsoftball @JessAdamssss @Jacque11Adams @briannrenee_ i see you lady vikes!💪keep working! #hardworkpaysoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YorkiesRPeople2 @collinsp1960 @46_still @KKay7777 @AlisonWarren6 @LadyTi88 @ksage10 @LadyTeapots @DebbieRumsey1… https://t.co/88bP63xpSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeWithoutDiet Must be— Have you *seen* the fashion from then? Surely had there been tv, no one would have worn that stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a face wash made for sensitive skin makes your face red and swollen ... 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such sad news for Maine music community.  This band is so loved by many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshGamesAcct @Wh0v1an_4_L1fe Now these are the type of normal healthy debates that AMERICANS should have with each… https://t.co/1nR7MLNlLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior Day!!  @BeaverWBB let’s get this win!! #GoBeavs https://t.co/5rFA5gT0PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersCanes305 @WPLGLocal10 A little warm 😎but will take it right 👍 have a great day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm tempted to get Division 1 since a friend wants to play it. I see it's on sale on PSN. $10 for standard and $18… https://t.co/BafOgY2y60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful I work so close to home that I can enjoy a nice quiet walk before going in https://t.co/lZ3X3FRKwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My skin is feeling and looking the best it’s ever had. Thank you skin gods 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatBirder27 Excellent! I wonder how I did not know that. I remember my Dad laughing so hard army King Tut he almos… https://t.co/wMtcuIM7jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a killer team!! Photoshoot for @HairByRRojas  with the beautiful @touriyahaoud!!  •Photograher by… https://t.co/iZwFUvczze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to my skin just when we are good for a few days but then it starts with me https://t.co/KnjizSLmsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would the need would talk about how completely racist Spike Lee was with his comments about interracial couples… https://t.co/5runMedOTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 @takavl That’s the best argument against impeachment. We need to get rid of everyone in the trump admin… https://t.co/tnLpCAuFei]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fit in 30 Studio Battle Creek, LLC in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/OTkAQ4oZB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did this actually happen?  No. She's Crazy.  ....🙃 https://t.co/QUElf9SPI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People look at us as if we have given the sins of the fathers. To say you do not see disability is like saying you… https://t.co/v5e1u8IWOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’m sleeping over at my boyfriend’s house and I just got hungry if I go get a snack in the middle of the nigh… https://t.co/aWJzncL7nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choupete450 @AnnelaTannante Bon je quitte bientôt pour aller fêter chez Choupete merci d’avance tenue casual?😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget! You have until 5.30pm (local time) tomorrow to submit your applications to the Emigrant Support Progr… https://t.co/XKUmk2ZrF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colinpeery @leavetotrench Well great finally something that idiot has done right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[De estos delincuentes, todo se espera a prepararse contra las acciones de los malandros]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting to that point in the quarter where I praise myself just for showing up for class. Never mind the fact t… https://t.co/gozjkotRrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[And people wont vote for him because he’s a socialist 🤦🏾‍♀️ but trump is running in my opinion a democracy and it’s… https://t.co/tnWEPD62Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitedsWife Can I have your body? In like a none serial killer kinda way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a good idea to watch scary movies when I have the house to myself right..😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryKayH188 @k_pastorkova @marykk196051 @LeviSharonrose @RustyVillagers @mary @DariaX55 @joannes02439842 @DMJ36509084 I agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momaha_owh @LAPainter @MolCav @Mywritesdntbite @Jenni_DeWitt @HaHasforHooHas @LeiaBaez @jenlivlaughlove https://t.co/QM44dtydGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CncBhDdubminion @chrissylynn7837 @MarciNkotb79 @nkotbgirl25 @Jonsfriend4ever @DDUBGIRL69 @cassie04061983… https://t.co/osOcE2XMqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE watching movies . I’ve seen Alita like 3x at the movies and I stay watching movies on Redbox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just read the article of a groomer breaking a German Shepard’s tail &amp; hitting her head with the nozzle &amp; im furious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's wonderful when your colleagues are also your good friends. https://t.co/hesji5QUMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my second favorite movie. I just want to be picked up and placed in it. I can feel the love through the scr… https://t.co/hvSZGkU1D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATRboxinguk I’ll probably get sooo hyped that I’ll hit her foreal foreal 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only @SilencedHippie was live streaming to help me try this new Superman X strain and to christen this new piece... 😚💨🍁 *SIGH* 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TRUMP OWNS URBANDIC: E=#TRUMP I=#JAREDKUSHNER U=#MICHELLELROBINSON Pandoa=#IVANKATHRMPKUSHNER GOOGLE=#TRUMP https://t.co/6hs2HwC790]]></document><document><![CDATA[Male White Grievance, Inc., has something to say. You talk quite a lot but I’m not observing any listening. 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did it. After at least a dozen Southwest flights, I finally remembered to actually check in right at 24 hours bef… https://t.co/e9swhdYE3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritesJodi Mirra would probably jump on a ship and get as far away from the capital as possible.  She might head t… https://t.co/VlYsSnQTJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMHotFlash @mommamia1217 @GOP Somehow I think you could delete the word "Texas" from that and it would be every bit as correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Steeeeeeph Let’s go, after geo gets out of school? To the one you go too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/9SDdN2xe3V https://t.co/tOWJRl6tMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@face_de_gras Tsé déjà le fait de pouvoir sortir de chez moi sans planification et prendre des décisions spontanées… https://t.co/ECKOm6STFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PettyVlad @Twitter @VladLokshin How did his happen? You are Vlad Lokshin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does facebook keep suggesting me to add my tinder matches... The FBI works hard but Tinder works harder sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @mgohagon to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Each ti… https://t.co/yKLXD6WCvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atmosphere selfies are the best! What a great night in Aspen! It was well worth the drive! Thank you Slug! 😊😉🙂 https://t.co/krFjHJq884]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: here’s my #shelfie with my next TBR #book #propertyofarebellibrarian  @allisonvarnes As a #librarian I’m thi… https://t.co/fSGuRnYEKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[As seniors become more food insecure, they also become more likely to develop diseases and illness that could cut t… https://t.co/r1hlV0xp5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work this weekend so I should be editing my video but I’ve been so lazy I keep putting it off😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino That lady needs to be put away she is bad for the USA she is a hater of the worst kind!!! She’s beginning… https://t.co/gqHcTUv1jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport Step back.. Alabama also was on the national stage for going grass roots n electing Sen. Doug Jones.… https://t.co/Iwn4pYReQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got done making my boys teachers chocolate covered strawberries and both classes goodie bags.. kind of feeling like a badass momma.❤️🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[he 1) never let her finish speaking and 2) equated divorce to disloyalty and lies. he deserves to be single and i h… https://t.co/ilrFN8Thh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know what I’ve never overcome? How fitness trainers want to ask you some chit chat questions and think I can simult… https://t.co/bxmofqZiqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my #1 supporter, motivator, best friend, and love of my life, Happy Birthday! The kids and I love you soo much!!… https://t.co/RMU3ZeU3Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/i3hWwiBO2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyTheStampede when i had abs (college days) ...i’d bite off both ends and use them as straws for my bottles of orange crush]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my birthday, it’s the first day of Pisces season, and we have a full super moon tonight.... I feel so fucking ALIVE.  ♓️🌚✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just so you know #HannahG, we’ve been waiting for someone to say something to #Colton and we’re so glad it’s you!!! https://t.co/Pqqq5UGoic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mishonh @k9_retired @workingdogmag I empathize with you.  It would be difficult for. Me, too.  We get so attached.… https://t.co/38czlmsSrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookewinkWX @GulfCoastHumane Brooke, it is terrific that you volunteer! Perhaps you can do a segment to promote f… https://t.co/6jcqnxfBSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m pretty much certain i could get the pirates to sign me to a minor league deal at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstiQueTee *sees the Futuristics and synth pop* YES *sees mumble rap* NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este es el mes de la mujer, la guerrera, la luchadora, la soñadora, la madre, la mujer es un ser único, valorate am… https://t.co/BzoRwecyPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdeloryn @acheung219 @Starbucks @salesforce @LeylaSeka @josiec211 @amandalnelson Love ii!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen @ColMorrisDavis @palmettocheese @Target At its most basic, pimento cheese is 1c each grated sharp ch… https://t.co/AqukrOYmt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Valentine’s Day &amp; I still can’t get your full attention. Lmao #ByeFelicia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I use the p-word and call him a pig? I hope he doesn't have daughters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Store Manager @LucSCTOM leading his team in the Home Depot cheer ...exciting and awesome experience https://t.co/21egUjgZra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Hell, I gained 15 pounds over the holidays. Tell me about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[smooches💋 for the best man a woman could ever hope for🙏🏻 &amp; love 🥰 #mylove #handsome #husband #smooch… https://t.co/lAo13HVdWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evoespueblo EVO EL GRAN IDIOTA, c..o de tu madre, porque no te callas ?🤬🤬🤬😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Church on Sunday #PuffPuffThink 🌬 Tarot and Oracle Cards ♦️ Peace Pipe ✌🏾 https://t.co/sh3pxXtQXQ @davidbanner… https://t.co/i0qVZHFcza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Вчера были на Ки-Уэсте (самая южная точка США) и зашли в дом Хемингуэя, где он жил в 30х годах. Замечательная жизнь… https://t.co/ycl5gGdfs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strom_annette @MisleaderC @esadah @Barb81146 @ChrisToTheW @pleasure74 @Momof2in1year @CunningSq16 @GrandmaVeteran… https://t.co/4WaVcjNjhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy voy a caminar pensando mucho en Luke Perry ❤️ https://t.co/RDWpU3T9I4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmcenta I'm reading How Emotions are Made by Lisa Feldman Barrett...wondering if others are including her theory o… https://t.co/XviycDmo1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[im in a coyote ugly bar rn and cannot figure out what is happening around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I do not need to open this app at work. Its too much going on up here. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought Republicans would throw away everything they stand 4 for Donald Trump. There will B a time after Tr… https://t.co/noJyUfUyHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be a hard day for me.  My favorite boys will have there last match today.  I will be there cheerin… https://t.co/o6767HQ9fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertoampuero Con el debido respeto q le tengo Sr. @robertoampuero, no soy abogado, soy una venezolana q tiene 20… https://t.co/VodQWLq84o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealityTVBliss Allegedly a large pay cut.  Sure the same with the rest of the cast no Raises]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ireland is and will always be in my heart and my second home. I miss you and cannot wait to be back there soon. ❤🇨🇮… https://t.co/esokcCD2KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I vote for 'Woman Like Me' by @LittleMix for British Video at The #BRITs 2019! #BRITVIDLITTLEMIX  https://t.co/B8sECV6EhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialCBC is there a White Caucus? How can we tell our kids we’re all the same when the government shows them th… https://t.co/XCJ2eNqpQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I got my aligners and needless to say these bitches hurt and I sound like Miley Cyrus with a lisp https://t.co/T9gkmraZMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a people who matter. Yes, it's true.  Now go show the world what people who matter can do.  GO SHOW THE W… https://t.co/0JDZFjsFVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[please tip your tattoo artists especially the ones who are your friends!! I don’t care if it’s a single extra dolla… https://t.co/pCpPm3SwA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @vanessahysell to post one book I love each day for 7 days and invite one person eac… https://t.co/IY0JhSFBOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol Rachel is here! #bunsisters @ South Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/CqkgEQWiU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill  great job yesterday’s during the hearing. You are a credit to your constituents, the House, and all… https://t.co/JTZPKHQ42L]]></document><document><![CDATA[- band / marching band  - the fact that it was free  - i wasn’t as stressed in high school]]></document></documents></author>