<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I think one of my former co-workers looks like Yeji from ITZY (well, she's a few years older than Yeji lol)  Asked… https://t.co/s6ILTXtNqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gythrigdon Awesome voice. Best of luck. #TheVoice https://t.co/mxGHjSEtW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ten minutes before sunrise.  It's chilly in Scottsdale but not enough to be a baby about it.  #winter #Arizona… https://t.co/l7XrajdI6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[RACIST?!?! from you?!?  Man fuck you! You’re a complete embarrassment to HUMANITY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbykleeK @shboogies @DayDaVonne_ @MTV_AMANDAG theo and kyle.  Theo actually helped day clean up amanda afterward… https://t.co/flqlZdLXLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenifa_0_Jenny @TrueGodImmortal @_JEANIUS_ U stuck on a movie, 3 sides to a story we wont ever know who telling that truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Featured Item:  2015 #Hamm H71 #compactor  #JeffMartinAuctioneers Early Spring Public #Auction, Mar 7-9, Brooklyn,… https://t.co/OrcUsvH7B6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KWagumz11 @F3_Wegmans @F3theFort @F3_ablock @Funhouse_F3 @F3_Royale @F3Dirty @RPesanka @F3_Chicken_Hawk… https://t.co/QTmcPZ1lvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[when @BrianPotato and I both know that it’s time to get coffee https://t.co/X3lgDTD405]]></document><document><![CDATA[Copper Pyrite w/ 925 Silver. Only few left 💪🏼 ✖️ WEAR GREGORIO NEW YORK ✖️ https://t.co/164f6AXx60 #bracelet… https://t.co/rb1m8r9tse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cory_B_Mason @DCHSAPHarvey @BoilerBall This is an IU/Purdue conversation though...Kentucky can say that to just ab… https://t.co/uyRZFgJklf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buggazing @1210WPHT @ChrisStigall @ChrisButlerFMU Buggy's alive &amp; atop my TL what an evening! ❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice citrus flavor up front clean crispy hop finish - Drinking an Experimental Session #1 by @FatHeadsBeer @ Fat He… https://t.co/TktoYuWRQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll not defend the fairness of these side rolls (especially from Baby Bell D20s) - but they're better than nothing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is he gonna have a rap career 🙄😭   "Anonymous dropping some heat on Tuesday from an undisclosed location"]]></document><document><![CDATA[why niggas care about awards shows anyway why we care what white people think about rap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIB_JADE I used to but got injured (knee) and couldn't walk well; no insurance :(. Pay was too small and I needed… https://t.co/R7QlfBr5gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JarrettRenshaw Heaven forbid anyone feed yeast sugar to produce alcohol. Wait...🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta es una captura de pantalla con Spanglish   This is a screen capture with Spanglish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delusional !  Maybe the beginning of an insanity defense !  McCabe: ‘It’s Possible’ Trump Could Be a Russian Asset https://t.co/JKnqyLjsgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaThomson2 @sg_thomson That’s just a lot of goodness wrapped up into one package]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating 100 years today. Happy Birthday Dr. Davis! @Phoebe_Putney #birthday https://t.co/iclKgK8zwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper, I’m really happy for you Imma let you sing, but Kanye had the best Sunday perfor… https://t.co/O6teezzHGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out @DrNowzaradan is on Twitter and he’s putting out GOLD like this. #DayMade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DominicScelzi41 @RothMotorsports  at Keller Auto Speedway Feb. 23, 2019 https://t.co/wpCNZ1JyzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encantado, my new crush!!! 😂  #happiness #torobrands #toroenterprise #Toro #maryland #virginia #dc #dmv #love… https://t.co/5IRAkbLHM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RedSox we would love to have the team join us in Orlando #march4tbi https://t.co/sJA1MtKIIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheRidesABike @NoSpandexReq @kptrease 👍  Timeline? Is there a budget?  We should probably take this to DMs or emai… https://t.co/qDybsqjCQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilton Manors FL Fri Mar 1st PM Forecast: TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 70 SATURDAY Sunny Hi 81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yusefroach It’s the best feeling in the world to listen to your girlfriend like tell a joke or talk about shit you… https://t.co/NuEYqM5p1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like @RobertDowneyJr hit the gym hard before Endgame. Can’t take a second L😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el noticiero de @CarlosLoret consiguen enlazar una llamada con @alfonsocuaron y en lugar de hablar de #ROMA le p… https://t.co/Kt5VoUpPUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All you have seen her in is sweatpants and a bad attitude” @ERichardson99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storme Cooper gets hit by a pitch and we’ve got bases-loaded with noneout and Fred Franklin at the plate #USM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris gives awkward response when asked about Jussie Smollett claims  https://t.co/SY84VxYDvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only February and God has turned many tables... many🙏🏽🌹 #iamfavored]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHS_Chiefs @craceman2001 @jsc_120 Can’t wait to see what he does in college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angry_Polak @JamieKerstetter The oddest but funniest commercial to me is the puppy monkey baby commercial when the… https://t.co/DMqOYVqzdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WelbornAmber said "I don't really care about UAB or Auburn, we're here for two things: my friend and the fights."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocotillo(Fouquieria splendens) can live for hundreds of years. Though for most of the year it’s essentially an  oct… https://t.co/hVjmBEEazZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelTrue @ValerieComplex Omg she is only 4 years older than me 😱😱... I swear I thought she was upper 50's lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishrygirl I have two identical twin cousins. One is gay, one isn't. I always wondered myself. If you get an answ… https://t.co/svrnla1MtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court off Prospect. I need to make sure I've got plenty of weed and weed related accessories for the big "Roger Sto… https://t.co/7QdrkB4Lq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarqMerks @MarqSlays League play is 60 but customs arent i tested it. Just wanna see how its worded to make sure im right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattFredenburg @NFL_DovKleiman @AdamSchefter I know right.  This guy is kinda weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[@windgineering @HaiLi86976724 @DianaOlick @CNBC @MBAMortgage So much hatred on Valentines day- shame on you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Centazzo @chrissparling We need a sequel.  As long as I can pick up Steve Brito from Crew parking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Saturday  morning  have a great day @ Camp Taylor, Louisville https://t.co/O6M2BXA32c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got shitted on in madden lol. Time for that apex grind. Come chill with me #twitch #streamer #newstreamer… https://t.co/RpalIneVq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariahCarey @CaesarsPalace Mariah is a beautiful, classy, powerful woman with the ability to attract beauty into a… https://t.co/jiIrV8oAZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @TimODee16 Wonder if she (I Van Ka) ever had to go to the clinic because of her dad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDBerryMD Well as kids get even bigger they will just double down on it and blame video games or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[iPhone X - 3/6/19 - “Sunsets in Carlsbad” . . . #sunset #skies #sun #carlsbad #chrisallen #evening #timechange… https://t.co/FJECDHqOqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gerald Walker - #Time (Official Video) https://t.co/xt7hxJ7oDI https://t.co/iArMDASoLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senyorreporter @washingtonpost I think there isn’t a comprehensive focus at all. The reporter here says that all t… https://t.co/LpGlxGHI0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[the crisis in the white house literally we have a mentally challenged president a psychopath literally kissing russ… https://t.co/wejQqtn0dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was showing my gf some of my fave beauty gurus and i showed her @jackieaina and she goes “what’s her header???” and oh my god we DIED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSmithNFL @pillagejust4fun It’s hard to be a logical raiderfsns some times.  This is perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After months of hard work, Anh-Thu finally got to enjoy the fruits of her labor (and I’m the lucky +1) #grammys… https://t.co/aSPKbODgoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live in LA...good vibes...😚😚 #ethankalixa #dj #music #live #radio #mix #techno #minimal #hitmaker #beatmaker… https://t.co/eQDCuirEiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @SeemaCMS @IvankaTrump Hey...Good Afternoon! Thanks for sharing. Prayers you and your family have a wo… https://t.co/nFc5Fd5W3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Bring Amazon HC to the greatest city in the world, Long Beach, California. We won’t complain ;) @GavinNewsom]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact I cheer on @jmcnamee_18 in NHL 2018, like it’s a real game is unreal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerdyWorld79 I used to be like that and my family always told me to try It and I’ve been a fan ever since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my3monkees @Jayhawker4Trump @Derameth @heyitsCarolyn @andrsngirls @Rbigzs @ShellyCov @nancy_hamm1 @007jorgeEnrique… https://t.co/UnS6JV472M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROOTS Ordered a bunch of stuff online for the free backpack, but I didn’t get the backpack. Too bad. Guess I’ll ha… https://t.co/Lj73LRKIXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you're walking back to catch the train and realize that your zipper has suffered a catastrophic failure… https://t.co/TR2TbEQ6Sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan You deserve them since you think that they are so great Y don't you move to either place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidplaysSTUf Agreed. It’s not a plan for smaller trees. Redwood and sequoias for survival!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawtybeanie @nhsCFwarriormum @VertexPharma @MattHancock @ChrisMRiches You mean the meds that took $4b and 15 plus… https://t.co/rHAwTapB0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A State Department spokesperson confirmed that the visa application denials were a result of full implementation of… https://t.co/Nn34K3sMbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never knew Frank played with Grand Funk. What a guest list on this beauty. https://t.co/wweJqKiKKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Braum's Ice Cream and Dairy Store in Midwest City, OK https://t.co/SUMqQGd2fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video of @KroqChip Practicing her hockey skills @thekevinryder @kevinandbean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@god...give him a spot up there.. He celebrated 25 birthdays by himself, with no one in that planet... and still di… https://t.co/CsSiKUnx5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fiancé rocks... Literally. Surprising me with front row to @RockOfAges. 🤘🏻🎸🎤. Beyond amped. https://t.co/BxXXwL5Xcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNBC: As fallout over pedophilia content on YouTube continues, AT&amp;T and Hasbro pull all advertisements.… https://t.co/r9gLF7IgQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @mingo_1 Hay MIEDO MUCHO MIEDO. VAMOS BIEN MUY PERO MUY BIEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWE Hall Of Fame 2006 - full speech for Eddie Guerrero of Benoit, Chavo,... https://t.co/Ht1WPxWUMZ via @YouTube @WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARCANDERSONNWO @AOC What's AOC got to do with it? SHE didn't unfollow @PoorMeMarc. And look at everybody, all san… https://t.co/3OwZwkWUAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick03907 @EMC_Maine @Flroach @JohnBechard Storm?  Heading just your way this time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇸🇪👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Jessica Edström! The White RACE Swedish BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beauti… https://t.co/1Jwa6iZDhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaBugle @robjh1 @SpeakerPelosi Shut up Nancy https://t.co/zIKxvY3PoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northern Iowa was back. Then Bradley realized it was 2019 not 2015 apparently. That was a really well played 2nd ha… https://t.co/tR4yoLFVc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[right here is why even though I love Tre he's not as good as Tyus in a spot like this Tyus would step up offensively]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Play the Democrats continue to switch the words or should I say the word play, because come 2020 Donal… https://t.co/hnQlfOTYSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shesatornado Yeah, I’m working so why the hell am I up lol  Hope your Sunday goes good 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work hard . Play hard. #uralmotorcycles #sidecar #scelife #3wheelin @ SCE Event Group https://t.co/vJLJW56L86]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught him. This is the punk that sucker-punched the conservative student on the U.C. Berkeley Campus. He needs ser… https://t.co/OEd6CARfYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le Vrai du Faux  Durant 3 semaines, des expositions d’artistes locaux et internationaux et des activités de médiati… https://t.co/9h9h3kORK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m told the meeting with the group that’s traveled the country offering ways to handle violence was set months ago… https://t.co/gooE3ofJbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[die lit is a literal masterpiece and one of the best works of art made in the past 2 decades]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is in spirit of our team and seeing our coaches support us like that meant the world to us. You don’t deserve… https://t.co/ambZlJaDs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you not know? Have you not heard? The Lord is the everlasting God, the Creator of the ends of … https://t.co/fY9G4XHVrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molratty @pipandbaby @El__Bohemio @Gormogons @TonkaSly Literally, Me2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddawson87 when you are at home listening to the Lady Hawks on @ABE937Radio  and the lchs band plays our fight song… https://t.co/mBEvQoflkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ardentLESS You know me. I believe like no other. We’re 14-5 in our last 19 matches. Obviously 0-2 since Dortmund.… https://t.co/xDTLAvnZRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[MPA New Engalnd Qualifier at Oxford Hills Comprehensive High School. The top four finishers in Class A and Class B… https://t.co/tj8iZAV0Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytmike @nytimes @maggieNYT @benprotess Another opportunity to mske money for Trump sell pardons. TRUMP SORROUNDS… https://t.co/xjdMAvnPSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[just made an art account bc this account really just turned into a total spam account😂  you can find ONLY my art an… https://t.co/LNqzhp6W7Q]]></document></documents></author>