<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Grateful to have a part in welcoming Governor @henrymcmaster to @KershawCountySC today. We have the most ready mega… https://t.co/RHX2SW9Ktf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could not be more demeaning to black people on black history month if you tried..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Dave Meltzer dig deeper into being AEW's lil' lapdog continues to be super funny.   I get they're your lit… https://t.co/7Fug4jJ3fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO I saw what that douchebag said to you earlier and as one of your biggest fans set to appear on one… https://t.co/LdblTOlKu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woodley has fallen in love with that right hand...needs uppercuts and combos...this is a mauling right now....props to Usman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Jessica Biel, born March 3rd, 1982 in Ely, Minnesota. https://t.co/DYOtg78gjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, we are really going to do this fucking thing? Alright. #CBJ https://t.co/quvFgMeDsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @AOC She is also pointing out the curruption in government that people don't want anyone to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Wander @F3Columbia @F3LexSC @F3LakeMurray @F3LMRucking @F3RichmondHill @evan_plankey @F3EvansGA @BOSTAPLES @F3KenDoll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely #nofilter to capture this glorious #sunrise in Coconut Grove @MiamiandBeaches #FoundInMiami https://t.co/G3QCje3nb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m mad af, I was just thinking about how I’m gonna leave work and go home and play fifa and battlefront online the… https://t.co/U1pfcibuaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalter Omg, when did Sportsnet turn to the Oilers network?  These guys doing play by play are the worst in hockey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEddChina @DRIVETRIBE @YouTube Big fan of both you and mike. I honestly wish you guys wouldnt air the dirty laun… https://t.co/7QMXjVMkd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHSTrojans working on a story about National FFA Week. Does anyone have any video/pics of students driving their f… https://t.co/0pH144J3b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been told this since I was a child.  Your environment plays a major role into the person you are; whether it i… https://t.co/9UMMgYmMiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topherjaims Curious how this would differ from college athletes in general?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mount Baker and British Columbia peaks from Issaquah Highlands, Issaquah Washington. https://t.co/wS5n4iJVVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mickey Beignet  #waltdisneyworld #food #yummy #tasty #dessert #brunch #treat #wdw #travel #explore #photooftheday… https://t.co/gljQPNXvRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever made the snickerdoodle brownies for Lewis County’s hospitality room is my hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KainCyril @realDonaldTrump Yeah, clearly not consistent with everything else we know about the man. Trying to rewa… https://t.co/v40If0zqT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlastairMacaul3 Typically smooth work from the @nytimes tech department.  First two videos in your informative and… https://t.co/NEnGJMimLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RcsSports The push. Anything you or anyone else can do will be greatly appreciated because he can and wants to pla… https://t.co/U3BpabY9Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders running for President once again. Gonna be a long campaign year hearing about his stupid ideas for socialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel is given a 6/10. The film was certainly action packed and had comedic elements in the dialogue. The… https://t.co/1s0DAIKobp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oklahoma Joe’s for Lunch before the Daytona 500! https://t.co/iMuspo8KYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪 Working those shoulders today with team Eagle Claw! (Aka: French it_me_teapot and wanginat0r )! 4 rounds of push-… https://t.co/qaRxtDo3hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuvTuri @_pbIII @MattMtz13 @KeithF_88 Wow what a hater lol next time I see you 👊🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PitBarrelCooker I hear that every time I make it for someone. “Best chicken I’ve ever had!” @PitBarrelCooker makes… https://t.co/ZhZTjNC6sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UHCougarMBK @g_robinson1 @UHouston A young John Legend!! Congrats @g_robinson1 !! From Lovett Elem to March Madness! Enjoy the ride!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlquintanilla And anyone with a brain who believed that doesn’t understand the economy of this country. We don’t… https://t.co/ZyruHhXRH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how sappy be on twitter knowing she still hasn’t texted me back !! @Sappyyy_]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:17 left in 1st: Hillsboro 13, MWC 2. Four different Hillsboro starters have already hit a 3pt. #pjspreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cschlebe @KalamazooWings @ESPNAssignDesk @Buccigross @sorney9 The Tan Man Can!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGodfatherMoody  @SiriusXMNASCAR what did we learn from the clash?? That cold weather plate racing stinks 😂 have a good day Dave]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepxpert 100% cotton and not by a real brand = it’s going to fit like shit, fade fast and shrink like hell and l… https://t.co/UoWqrBNlP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Caregiver/Home Health Aide" at ResCare by asking for referrals. It's a great way to… https://t.co/wzxykSO9Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yu Darvish and his new approach to 2019 next on Inside the Clubhouse @670TheScore . @MattSpiegel670 and I breakdown… https://t.co/Ay0K1KXOE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A frozen gym Hump Day ARMS!  Let’s do this! #fit60 #fitfam @MikeOHearn @HeathEvans44 @JDBuffone @AMANDAbolic @DemetriaObilor @turbittabc27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landon Collins has been my favorite player on the giants the past four years, he played tough and through injury ma… https://t.co/xi1CqDbzxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No thieves, no traitors, no interventionists! This time the revolution is for real! Fidel Castro]]></document><document><![CDATA[And some of us enjoyed Disney After Hours at Hollywood Studios which was awesome! https://t.co/vCv4lcXnxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So please, hurry, leave me, I can't breathe Please don't say you love me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get some fucking jobs and maybe you bums could pay for your own. You 4 are gonna get eaten up real nice in prison 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks for this awesome piece by peter_t_wilm  Check out his work online and on the wall at @truestorybrew… https://t.co/vRT1IW1HBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairbankOBX @D1scourse Some will say shot clock era is partially responsible. I think its the talent pool has expl… https://t.co/7SvfDTdbcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISPPutnamville @AbbyKirkWTHI Hope it goes well hon. Have a good day. https://t.co/nKiR1NjzUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pikachu with MiLKYWAY at Idol Revolution ♡ Moe Moe Chu! https://t.co/0SCTiNWa9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[📌 This Contemporary version of Venus de Milo looks #amazing like this, and  you can appreciate this #Beautiful… https://t.co/RkG2abjrlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD1 $40,000 is available for 4 people who retweet within 28,000 split into sums of $10,000). Paypal only.… https://t.co/Im1ZmcrB2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveatfirstsite @NEWSCYCLE_News @infomakernews https://t.co/guha2jo0fR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you’ve literally put it so out in the open that you’re a virgin and then on the women’s tell all you comple… https://t.co/2Ifsx5EsFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are employees really going to read 500 page manuals.......😴😴😴 #MondayMotivation #MondayThoughts #work #manuals… https://t.co/64T7yYpvUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delayed Valentine’s Day date with my valentine @wholenchelleada #eaglewindterritory @ Winter Park Resort https://t.co/pJj3ytCpKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshmen (1-0) defeat Corner’s JV 8-6 in 9 innings to start the season! Kellen Mashburn hit a solo bomb. J. Tatum p… https://t.co/aO0x2lEaEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six Airplane Facts to Cure Your Fear of Flying&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; https://t.co/akeSZWq4ST via @lifehacker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 I've always heard Milwaukee has plenty enough hotel rooms for Summer conventions, it's just that the… https://t.co/MyqbXH12TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[MI @GovWhitmer “The decisions via Twitter are dumb whether it is on trade, or tariffs or immigration. These are inc… https://t.co/Wf6XNytL3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[If being alone on Valentine’s Day makes you sad, I can’t imagine how much the other 364 days suck too HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC This is the kind of information that even people such as myself who follow politics and the goings on in Wash… https://t.co/w6me1X03DK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently witnessing man discover fire in the studio with @GideonAL 🔥🤘🏻 https://t.co/lgrUdZgIff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenajalikhan @school Thank you for your kind words. It was great interviewing with you.  Thanks for making a difference.  All the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping the #EMR cluster busy this afternoon... https://t.co/PgymYU9Ayz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conspiracy theory: wife is intentionally shrinking my clothes, therefore growing her own wardrobe. If I go missing, this is why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FancyPantsWTVD @425suzanne Twitter used to be a place where your chicken fries were safe but sadly not nowadays. A… https://t.co/dHpgV8Q0T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes You’re right Geraldo she is you at 26 an asshole just like you wore today only today you’re a bigger asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StadiumSeries they're walking up stairs so they can go down decorative steps from Rocky.    And lite brite Gritty will be in my nightmares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLinWood Did ‘drummer boy’ meet the threshold for assault in D.C. on Mr. Sandmann?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would highly recommend this! Great deal for the greatest park on the planet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lntinytorch @LonesomeLook @surrealtc @TheCryptograph @qsanaq @SatoshiChela Are we up to 22? If so see below   lnbc… https://t.co/BbthmYg7sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strotherMason they found out about our massive plot to critique this movie so hard is bombs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GmurphNBCS @TMacPhils @JClarkNBCS @CSeidmanNBCS @rickybottalico how excited are u that Bryce Haper is a Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorSteele Luckily it was in his chambers during the motion in limine argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see @hectormolinajr for the central Texas Catholic men’s conference.  Amazing passion. https://t.co/pLE55IJ91z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars2019 parties in #Hollywood. #Fabulous #Flirty #Funny &amp; #Foxy #actress breshawebb shining with her… https://t.co/gm39hHHtwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KICKTHEFED @CAndricsak @glo4itnow @patriotdb @dianeh15285 @whiteguy3275 @DereckWyatt @MarkEasterday8 @gaming_grump… https://t.co/MZZxiJtgvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always want to help people improve their shooting but I never want to give unsolicited advice because nobody likes that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN  Mr. Trump sorry can't say Mr. President but you are always complaining about fake news what about fake trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone is having a great Sunday. Try not blowing away with the stong winds 🌬🌪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really about to upgrade my car insurance now that I’m back in Miami because these people down here can’t drive bruh 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson look at the time.  I have to eat.  I forget and don't eat a second meal some times.  I have 2 snacks… https://t.co/o9Od5QLAq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravosNLD @BlanquiGol @LigaTDP @TerceraM @RNDeportes1 @NoresteMX @liderweb_mx @danielsalazarTD @Gob_NuevoLaredo… https://t.co/WDCY1PSmME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdelacruz_IoT @Ceo_Branding @SDGS4GOOD @sarbjeetjohal @JBarbosaPR @cybersecboardrm @kashthefuturist @TmanSpeaks… https://t.co/uxexBT5yqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We now have space directive 4 which is going to be the 6th branch of the armed forces. Marines were initiated to be… https://t.co/3CHlrgw86q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dreg_Society @Happy19111 @BertJ4411 @martydemic @ZeeInTheMoment @Lucille77316971 @rghtwngextrmst @surfnutsc2… https://t.co/k5rDYjENJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acezwild21 @MAL___ Tf he got the ball dribbled toke a step and went up you high nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimhightower7 @TweetJDUB2017 @TrvlPrst @maziehirono Ummmmm yeah🤔You were saying? 🤷🏼‍♂️🤦🏼‍♂️ https://t.co/bjcFMgdXrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecampaignbook You should change/delete one letter a day till it says “that’s what she said”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacquicollins_ It also means that if she’s buying GS Cookies, she will actively not buy Thin Mints. https://t.co/2XilhbHMfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[lamb hashwi #salem #bostonfoodies #opussalem @ Opus https://t.co/RcTdkixPGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say @CarmellaWWE didn't earn it but Ronda did is like saying @MichaelCole 1 @WrestleMania win tops The Undertaker streak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @jeffrosenstock how many retweets will it take for you to go to prom with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emlaughsallot88 @YellowVestsCA You don’t know real tyranny. Pump your brakes. #CDNPoli #ABPoli #ONPoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vTRouter delivering on his promise to build a wall and have Mexico pay for it o wait 🧐 these people are insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything you need is inside you. #TBT #LAArtShow #LAArt #OliviaSteele #AnthonyJames @ Downtown Los Angeles https://t.co/mF76Dh82ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joaquingarzafox It takes 4+ months to order them custom :/ couldn’t do it in time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkyogaclub718 is looking for volunteers! Please see details and if interested, holler!!! #bkyogaclub @ BK Yoga Club https://t.co/ribBZ5dfD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer was great but @MsAmberPRiley did something amazing to this song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StLouisBlues please have Jon Hamm call some games, his call of @Barbashev2295’s goal last night was brilliant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝🍭🔥😍😘@latina https://t.co/gNEJLj3qLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I routinely eat jelly beans too fast and get them stuck at the back of my throat. I’d say I have to hack up at leas… https://t.co/mffoulDmjQ]]></document></documents></author>