<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@grahamjennifer2 @sandy_forand @BillBlackRI @perryprincipal It was all data, all day yesterday! You 3 are making stuff happen. 📊📈📉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, just as soon as you Confederate history and statue loving/South will rise again/ gun loving ammunition hoarding… https://t.co/1IJ2WC05M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewDillner @JRMotorsports Chicken nuggets!!!!! https://t.co/1JvTh3WjAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinityResists @MDHaddad17 WA was among one of the states not havked because we have mail in verifiable ballots. H… https://t.co/3xQUmf5FUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had to live vicariously through my dads snapchats of the Kiss concert he went to last night so that’s neat. #jealous]]></document><document><![CDATA[friday is gonna be good i’m spending quality time w my friends and the first new foals album comes out 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@countingpulses Nope. There is help if you need it. Don't wait for your GP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC New York dodged a bullet with Amazon.  Amazon has trashed Seattle. Why do they NEED more tax breaks?  Their em… https://t.co/bE7h44w7VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PegahJafari00 @JustinTrudeau @DomAnglade C’est pas juste de détruire tous nos rêves.   #Quebec_immigration_injustice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aleeex_6546 I feel like I keep clicking the refresh page but the internet is down so it just freezes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarris707 @d_ast777 @SeptemberJulie @Jj051301 @RosaDeliadelos1 @RosaryMysteries @ArleneKowalczyk… https://t.co/ebUcKVJieg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyinNYC In the 80s, I literally attended funerals every week - sometimes more than one/week, including my best… https://t.co/lEaHsC9pCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Airborne Toxic Event - Sometime Around Midnight https://t.co/Ga2amL67M7 via @YouTube Thank you @Airborne_Toxic for this piece of life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don Mills (던밀스) - Ye I Need (Feat 넉살, ODEE) MV https://t.co/cJic8LyZ5o via @YouTube Hey Daddy I have my Car n Job N… https://t.co/GyW1dtjaXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity #Time to keep listing all the aspects of sharia law so that people know what it is @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/ppG7kBgfzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biorph Open to interpretation. I count summers working on the family farm as "chores" rather than job since I wasn't paid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #WakeUp11 sleep study: #1 @WHAS11Hasch you look great #2 kids don't let you make up sleep on the wknds anyway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMNHL @StellickSimmer @GordStellick @simmerpuck @Rupper17 @ice_chip @HunterBros @JamieMacoun @UMDWHockey… https://t.co/mro7Hz6z7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the nations the LORD destroyed before you, so you will be destroyed for not obeying the LORD your God. https://t.co/49EFrcwFMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The regents will vote on whether to approve Coach Tyson Helton’s contract. @wkuherald]]></document><document><![CDATA[“everybody in the kkk should be dead... and you can quote me on that” -brooke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to catch an early morning flight with two rambunctious toddlers is just like herding cats #oyvey   Where's m… https://t.co/bs8NSYI4RB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got it all fixed up it took 7 stitches to close it up it wouldn't stop bleeding but she did a good job closing it😭😭… https://t.co/9XRWFmVbWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i look at the staaaaars [ + when i’m with @switchfoot ], i feel like myself ⭐️ this one goes out to… https://t.co/Fogor7y8XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I helped out in a Kindergarten class where students were exploring and documenting how cars roll on different… https://t.co/IbL80zVmfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@365DaysOfDisney @CharMagicTravel Lordie...bless your soul!!have you really gotten to actually eat a meal recently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaJoyNoTrump @Bfree33 @PrisonPlanet Smh delusional! I am an independent but voted for the Democratic candidate i… https://t.co/DPokQOMaz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/dwp3Lbvem7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“this life will be good and beautiful. But not without heartbreak. In death comes peace. But pain is the cost of li… https://t.co/mda3VFUYt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BreenBernal  for the the lock screen https://t.co/kVZqvtqyAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagniFieri @newyorklady1234 @RollingStone Can’t wait till she’s arrested along with Hillary and Obama!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shits mad real. All my life i thought he was just a punchline and someone to make jokes about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @VP @MunSecConf Evangelical bullshit. They want to push their beliefs on a nation that knows the people tha… https://t.co/vKlagtO3e2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoppin’ our way into your news feeds and TVs this morning!  Happy Wednesday ☺️ https://t.co/AdfHpfEQso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilbertobm @atajoslargos @tayreyes La vaina es tan grave, que se podría decir que eres afortunado. Yo no se nada d… https://t.co/VhWH840bcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for using my photo, @VIVAMASFOOD !  That bulldog was super yummers and I need more in my life!!… https://t.co/6Q9EJFIAtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como me encanta esa sonrisa.. 😍😍 #TwitterBestFandom  #TeamBTS  #soompiawards  #LatamxBTSTour  @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeepsGreen @agocs_jodi @Legendary1941 @TopJeepers @KrawlAmerica @THEJeepMafia 🙌🏼🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t you have vanillla anymore @panerabread, seems ridiculous since that’s the most popular flavor..... https://t.co/yZmAWmp0f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an alarm for 7:20 because my doctors appointment is at 9:15 and I didn’t want to miss it lol 😩 so um yes I want to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am loving the results that I am seeing from this F45 challenge, I am absolutely amazed my transformation and it’s… https://t.co/BmtnZSF0hZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenact4 @BlueJays @BuffaloBisons Going to Jays opener, hard pass on Buffalo in April.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BR officially cancelled 2/ 20.  Of course I’m here🙄 https://t.co/IE6qrFGtVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyft’s New App Creates Positive Change for Passengers and Cities https://t.co/0W9AIBlb9o via @lyft]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG I can’t tell you how much having @AuthorCCPayne visit my students meant to me! They LOVED her and her inspiring… https://t.co/DPRii0ncF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’ve been on twitter for 10 years! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/va6vf65viX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaddiieM My worst best habit is over applying chapstick to keep my lips hydrated while nodding my head in an agree… https://t.co/QhkIDHnsVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stranded snowbound man survived on Taco Bell sauce packets for five days  https://t.co/e5bPd5jYX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamramey It IS a bit STRANGE‼️ Good Song❣️  (thought this calculator was a cute prop as a security system to open… https://t.co/YaKvkxaEVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a relaxing Sunday, regroup and recharge for next week 🌊 ☀️ #aimeedoesdisney @ Disney's Typhoon Lagoon https://t.co/0l4mCl9hbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[this just in: @TPAIN is an environmental legend, using paper straws only for his guests drinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MossyWill66 @Patriotress @bbusa617 @TiffanyATrump @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @KamalaHarris @SenKamalaHarris… https://t.co/1SS1e3Qev6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad I came across @est8her @serenarenaaa they seriously keep me sane 😙💓 I appreciate y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyberNetPortal @EricTrump @realDonaldTrump @HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP What about the Republican Party that has befo… https://t.co/QplnO4CHD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland National Weather Service data.  That's a vast improvement since 1990, when the national lead time was 5 five  minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM PISSED TF OFF! They did this bullshit to Glenn Close again! They could have at least given it to Melissa, if a… https://t.co/2Z975CwRy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ma1nick02 @Lexa_Merica @tenaciousKansas @Probinson640 @MaggieakaM @TeighJay @cmc8083 @johansson_derek @TimOrmsby… https://t.co/lTSyQDuJcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My young Gunnas playing in a Big Elimination game tonight . Let’s see what we made of #BILOXIHIGH #09Champs 💍chasing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sourcederived It's offensive and I would also hit myself all the time on it. It's taking up counter space.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDCPS be on the look out @1pEST your students from WR Thomas Middle will be presenting their #STEM project on the… https://t.co/JN47rPG8y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichM413 bought me a 57oz bottle of @HVRanch for my birthday and if that’s not love then I don’t know what is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/pNH9aFetrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my fully vaccinated but asthmatic kid who caught whooping cough at school will not be allowed to travel to New Y… https://t.co/TS60PHVmcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smgaillard Definitely a groovy song 🔥 Thanks for sharing the Sunday music inspiration! #ThePepperEffect]]></document><document><![CDATA[plan strives to reduce the country’s dependence on expatriate manpower by substituting Omani nationals for foreign… https://t.co/tamxhI734p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg Teddy's at 30 weeks. 19 weeks have already passed since this season started. #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royals Go Royals!!!  Another great spring training game!!!  Woo hoo!  🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷👏👏👏💙⚾️🌈❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[He kick her out of the car and drove off so fast  with them twins #teenmom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamWestcott For real, Court is THE BEST @BravoTV real house husband ever!! His eye rolls and general suspicion of… https://t.co/GbZU2DK6JG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsvu Oof, I have a rare Thu night off &amp; it happens to be my birthday as well March 7th and wouldn't you know, SVU is on hiatus. 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day!! 💙💙Come in or stop by to place your order!! 💙💙 #spencesflowers #loveday #flowers #fresh… https://t.co/w7I2Zzn0Xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm off enjoying my time away with my granddaughter and I've seen the best group shirts and personalized travel mug… https://t.co/qyfzgYPvBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEST OF BOTH OFFICES: LUDACRIS TALKS OPRAH FIASCO https://t.co/tdo7Lm5KF9 via @YouTube: Public Relations disaster.… https://t.co/n7eEr7XncY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting on the porch of a brunch cafe in Siesta Key surrounded by friends, but missing my love @justinpstrong so ve… https://t.co/4T2kZ1Ov3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longhorndave @drew_fox Just getting that smell out of my hair takes at least two washes. Plus, being around smoke… https://t.co/gm4iIzOoe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlkSantaX @MrsblksantaX @agooding58 @NewmannMichael @7brdgesroad @Aussiegirl126 @EllasaysMs @justheragain… https://t.co/t6glNX1IZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well collusion has been proven. We are waiting for reports to come to see what else there is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanyodarouse 🙁yep.  We have gotta unite so we can win this in 2020.  This kind of crap makes me nervous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like my Milano cookies with #hotchocolate @milanocookies #AwardSeason #SaveSomething4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends abortions should only be given when the fetus is not viable, has some terrible deformities or endang… https://t.co/UTAzkkqEg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite thing to do in my free time  is to watch animal planet videos on dogs getting adopted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get it twisted I still miss you like crazy and think about you daily, I just don’t think we could ever be together again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jwoww gave her 3 options! 1.) stay and get your ass beat 2.) stay and get your ass beat 3.) stay and get your ass b… https://t.co/nQVyAJfPbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalGrammarDay to my fellow editors. https://t.co/srQBOiAGp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @Centristchowdah @cspanwj @RepDarrenSoto If I want to search through the web perhaps.. but I'm not… https://t.co/aNTzIJXICe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woodley/Askren is the combo I never thought I needed. Askren makes Woodley seem not so corny. #ufc235 #openworkouts… https://t.co/exbCEz3OcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Sweetwater #TN  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/HV7UhFFieG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neither Sarah nor you, Ms. ROMNEY McDaniel, know your ass from a hole in the ground!   There's CONSPIRACY in plain… https://t.co/MUiqs9NrKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[BROWN...PENN...WASHINGTON STATE...have also offered Alexandra Z‼️ https://t.co/qywZa0Wbth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SydneyJamesson @BrownAngelEyes_ @BettyrvRivera @RandomCran @JDT19 @SusieSteinle @sylvainreynard @pamlangworthy… https://t.co/q0g66a2AVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good point:  Kelly McParland: Justin Trudeau would fail his government's workplace tests https://t.co/4yzQSu2bjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maluma - HP (Official Video) https://t.co/djFRZVAUDG vía @YouTube vamos con todo HP @maluma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Imagine my surprise when I found out that he took on Palm Beach because they wouldn't allow Jewish p… https://t.co/aV6ZwQSjBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the the “implications for students with dyslexia” section in the attached article! Yes, using picture clu… https://t.co/oG5UJneRCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rashe_ii its not addiction I could stop at any time, I just dont want to]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @arkellsmusic was once again one of the best concerts I've ever been too 😍😍🤘🤘🤘 https://t.co/WewkGYzrJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all better send me some fuckin money. I’m not playing with y’all!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin might be a little excited to go see Weezer. Memphis here we come. #roadtrip #Weezer @ Gallatin, Tennessee https://t.co/kowyKaHpOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiceGuyBCommMBA @CJVAttard That's lowered the danger of over-dosage for children with chronic diseases like epilepsy and asthma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @RealCandaceO You man, RUN FOR YOUR LIFE. She's a shape-shifter!!!!!!!]]></document></documents></author>