<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lloyd Boner will still be your champ at the end of the night. #WWEChamber • #Theplanetschampion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not paid and I haven’t hit any of these subscription limits. Is there some sort of loophole?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerwillow One more... because it’s not all about Mal... https://t.co/8nWMUPwo8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes 180 shots to take out 1 bad guy Wow lucky more people were not killed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_StephenKLP @rogerstv @Steve_Dangle @sickkids @SickKidsNews @Marner93 @LeafsPR @NHL @Sportsnet @RossChambers54… https://t.co/FxhX1AumLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cost_a_lot If Cool Runnings played in a Power 5 conference, she would have made it]]></document><document><![CDATA[When New Yorkers unite against Amazon. #nyc #ny #NewYorkers #NewYork #facts https://t.co/pGnwSh1svG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concerned about "lawless presidents?" Cool. In what way does #impeachment with a Senate acquittal stop future lawless presidents?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune into the WR workouts at the combine today and check out Antonio Brown’s replacement 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday February 18 - Your Morning Five:    White House indicates Trump to veto disapproval of emergency;     The st… https://t.co/lPHBj4VWqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANKS BARACK 👏👏👏ALWAYS PUTTING AMERICA DOWN AND LIFTING YOUR MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD UP 😡😡😡 https://t.co/QdbuUxxh3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamagedBttm Defeated? No. After all you've been through? You're a survivor. But yeah, all that **** would exhaust… https://t.co/bQp99PX7tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing group of athletes and coaches. Looking forward to next weekend. #StateMeet]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are colorful critters in my Etsy shop! https://t.co/xDsHFz1GWF #animals #etsy #etsyshop #artprint… https://t.co/CG5r1EQrLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_TrumpIN You mean his testimony that was instructed by a piece of Schiff &amp; coerced by Mueller the traitor in getting a plea deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[PEOPLE n AMERICA we must come together and demand the impeachment of TRUMP now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueDetective thought this season was the best among the 3, so now gonna rewatch the 1st 2 to double check 😎🤓🐢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Faitelson_ESPN “desatado” fue el madrazo que te dio el Santo patrono de Tepico el 8 de Marzo del 2003]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harvest Bible Chapel (@harvestbible1) Dropping Defamation Suit Against Critics - the church brought a lawsuit again… https://t.co/CJdAHqH3MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank goodness to know that after HOURS and HOURS of stress and time and dedication i’ve put into to something and… https://t.co/rxeQyVhEig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei It’s worse than that. He’s not that stupid, but he thinks his cultists are. And he’s happy to exploit… https://t.co/O5oi7RJkn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrinkmanCheryl and @MattHaneySF thank you for your serious, outcome-driven support. What can we do to extend this… https://t.co/lLhrDnrTkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @AOC will ya read thy story as ya know us boys live our pig n cow meet here in Wisconsin n down yonder… https://t.co/gtfQZOyrGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re so dedicated to the gym. More than you were to our relationship. - me to my ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just went to go see @arnezjcomedy at @zaniesnashville with the wife. Had a great time and we laughed so fuckin hard… https://t.co/wQhKt5PWqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The readings for today. https://t.co/wkxiQha370 https://t.co/iTWICQhSCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Electivirus I would say this photo is   Of the sexiest man of all time 😁😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgriffin_kmov Haha!! So not fair! You still have an hour of vacation to use. #LastHourLunch when you return! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidforOCASIO @LaraLeaTrump @IvankaTrump 11.) SO THANK GOD FOR OUR @POTUS'S DAD WHO INSTILLED WORK ETHIC AS HAS B… https://t.co/y2gRMpnyeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba @PSOE Infórmate imbecil , ya tus esclavistas te dieron derecho a internet, claro controlada , tú sabes , tú sabessssss!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renataxduran We save minutia like that and the Great Emu War for college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hombredeltiempo Gracias, Visto con TIME- LAPSE RATE GOES16 Producto: Color Natural se ve un TRANSVASE de tick Cirr… https://t.co/53cPriMZ8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nibroc @iajanus @GeoffreyHuntley It can. But if it doesn’t, silence. I can’t wait till the GA to decide to build a… https://t.co/fzYTRiKYW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorWFPod @ZackRyder @TheCurtHawkins @Walmart I went to my local @Walmart and I was very disappointmed in the fig… https://t.co/j3FlATlzEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jredding 2/ I doubt that this risk is unique to Supermicro, other than it coincidentally being the vendor IBM sele… https://t.co/5XOe1ehk8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I pray every night for somebody who’s no longer in my life. Idk how you’re doing but just know I hope you’re yo… https://t.co/CMaO8YxlFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wolverines offer 2020 CB from Trotwood-Madison. https://t.co/3Ukb79jqFd @BriceMarich @TremendousUM @SamWebb77]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of people who leave the bathroom without washing their hands boggles my mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please just donate the rest of the 800$ bc I’m tired of my ribs cracking and not being able to enjoy da… https://t.co/pUkRpC0nyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always blame the coach for lack of leadership but I think it’s pretty clear where that lack came from. Pels… https://t.co/ASObUYIc9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buck Grunts (0:00:26) while eating Deer Candy on Cajuns Live Deer Cam Wed. Feb. 27th 2019 - In Memory of my Dad -… https://t.co/m6zFRYWGAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see Senator Ted Cruz is still being annoying. #SwordArtOnline https://t.co/YQgfcVm3Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmbutt @Richard_Florida Good news, there are some UT Profs in another part of this thread. I bet they can tell you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very interesting take on FF and EJ by Denny. Haven’t thought of it that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_u2 Asi debe de ser vecina , muy buenos días y feliz sábado saludos cordiales y cuídate,!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matphilly @BeyondWland @discoveryprjct @insomniacevents @ExchangeLA @academy__la @BassmntSD Best of luck man! Hope… https://t.co/JcJRHFkSfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "4th Annual G.O.L.F.3:16 Charity Tournament" https://t.co/v8glsJuTKX @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tripp_trippn Yes bruh going crazy, I’m pulling up to a game with my jersey 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rec. League by @harpoonbrewery @ H &amp; M's — https://t.co/iciFvZ15LP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lemonsand @itsa_talia My lawn will vouch that I've been trying to kill it for 20 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing If #potus45 really cared even a little about making America better for working folk he wound Stop hav… https://t.co/3p48akwC5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major breakthrough at summit in Vietnam. Kim asked for economic sanctions relief and led with @peta exports citing… https://t.co/5KjCKYQQmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo... inflating your net worth for "brand value" only "might" be a crime? I mean... if there is some gray area the… https://t.co/aY4yOhNPX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davepreme @RealKentMurphy I didn't catch that. After looking closer at the video, I now see that the 1B was lookin… https://t.co/A8VFr9rPTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickinerino Also me, and I have a library e-book ON THE GEE DEE PHONE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCRonline It has its roots in a disease and the abdication of the laity in dealing with the disease. The more ende… https://t.co/itxZsIs7CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo WORKS FOR ME! Yawl!!😝😝😝!! https://t.co/8zHYMAGBcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikmace Individual players getting off to hot starts is way more important imo than the final score when the doubl… https://t.co/2w3IYx5tHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[No cap. I said this would happen my life changed over night. @ Lafayette, Louisiana https://t.co/meZqUnbiP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janemarielynch I’ve seen this a few times and it never gets old. What an amazing man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your mask if your career WAR is 4.3 higher than Bryce Harper. https://t.co/DqzgsKQuPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#texas on fire 🔥!!! #sunset #elpaso #elpasotx #mountains #orange #friday #landscapephotography #landscape #nature… https://t.co/KqJlwpW7hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Npumford @OaklandWBBall How does Lane already look older than @marcnorton59?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @melaniejoly Protecting Pensioners? FFS! Does she not know how pension funding works? Christ is she dumb! #snclavalin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight everyone this handsome devil is calling it a night,  I am still single and available looking for a seriou… https://t.co/zRvapWrUbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey princess, I've been sittin here all night tryin to figure what I'd say...here's some pictures instead! 👌👈    💝 https://t.co/6kuXEhjQim]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am one of five people that get to say this in the world, but my dad is the guy at the FT line getting ready to sh… https://t.co/Oq7vNfIdUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#espinim_fotografia definitivamente me encanta la fotografía nocturna...#newyork en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/cpWKK04XJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folsom in transition once again, Rose makes it 42-35. Timeout Riordan, 1:36 left in the third.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As good as Jesus was even HE had people that didn’t like HIM (so much so they crucified HIM) Not everyone is going… https://t.co/p2ILczcSIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all want to be in better shape, make more money, have stronger relationships and improve many aspects of our liv… https://t.co/Koc4I7Y8lG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeAnte_Gray20 wasn't happy with his performance even in a win with @WyomingSports so the first thing he does this… https://t.co/E3o9an8bzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[paying maintainers via charity or donations is the wrong approach for long term sustainability, also shorts maintai… https://t.co/uGZdaUgEr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga was cut from her high school show choir, was told “you’ll never write a hit song about a ‘disco stick’”,… https://t.co/kcYS0KyCHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No pues a Rafa Puente nada mas no lo ayudan los jugadores... será que tienen semanas tendiéndole la cama?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JByrd74_ @amheide_84 @Ebron85 @Lions My ego is so big it doesn't even fit on Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything sadder than a brunch DJ? Sorry, DJ Woody B. https://t.co/xylvOdcfHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you. I would vote for anything by @tayari or @KieseLaymon as well, but especially their latest works!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics The best propaganda is that which, as it were, works invisibly, penetrates the whole of life without t… https://t.co/pNP61UPqqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @Madison420Ivy @felicityxfeline  @thekiranoir @AnnaBellPeaksXX @Siciliamodel @LilyLaBeau… https://t.co/r4fWQum6L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tailandia #Filipinas #ContibenteAsiatico #Oscars #HappyMonday #Oscar2019 https://t.co/AI0muiZf1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Show them what Keene High Hockey is all about!  Play hard, play smart, have fun! #BlackbirdPride… https://t.co/o1At70bjvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at North Village Yellow House in Kissimmee, FL https://t.co/QXvQswfbOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's gonna make me become an alcoholic tonight. @ Energy 92.1 Myrtle Beach https://t.co/cTjD8PYO5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn New York, really? #tesla #teslamotors #teslaowner #teslamodel3 #model3 #elonmusk #teslalife #electriccar… https://t.co/3NUkDEEzkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I just spent 3 minutes at -300 degrees below zero in a liquid nitrogen@CryoChamber. It was cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beaux_Banks I need you to get booked in El Paso si I can finally meet you 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on over to Edgeley Country Club today from 10:30-2:15 for hot coffee, lunch, and cold beer after Dicamba train… https://t.co/ffxQkX6b9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFeinsteinBooks Have you read this.  Great article.  https://t.co/jOR5EzYXif]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you looked at the credits he was the writer of more than a few episodes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linzbinian @Trulieve It's worse than some, yeah.  But you aren't suggesting what should be in place so kinda hard… https://t.co/iap3JcNLlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to spend more time logging in to things and less time actually doing things.  Oh, wait. Not possible.... I… https://t.co/txpARUdtUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/PpSjl1x3q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_wintergirl93 @RealJamesWoods @IndyaMoore Wonder if he’s smart enough to set the timer on an automatic coffee make… https://t.co/wTAXgAFQEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALFABOT2000RBLX @nerdfighterliv I literally get a twitch if I see anything frozen 😂😂 it annoys me so much. I want… https://t.co/y9KTeWby11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @isabenfica51 @awkward_1110 @koushikdas47 @PPourgourides @PawsLost @CyntWhite @MoishesMom @SamLitzinger… https://t.co/DLlRegMK0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tal parece que el Vaticano también controla ya la polaka de Nuevo León.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want a shamrock shake and some crazy bread. And no I’m not pregnant]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my captures from an #engagement series taken last year. _________ #thekccreatives #portraits… https://t.co/CVd0Ac5xiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAMARSHALLSMC @Robbiezombie @spreaker @camarshallshow It was from the end of the 70's to mid 80's Gritty, grimey,… https://t.co/m1OQuQSVQz]]></document></documents></author>