<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Efrain_Pina25 @CMonteroOficial Eso es lo más importante, aunque no pensemos igual . Aceptar el pensamiento del otr… https://t.co/TZe0F4qqD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man, charged with murder in a 1993 cold case, is fighting extradition back to Alaska.  @WGME   https://t.co/7ozgJmsq7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL drop some self empowering songs below!!! i need a self worth boost HAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spread a little Pride and Joy every day!  Happy Pride Hearts now in my @Etsy shop. https://t.co/TChlCjWMXv  #LGBTQ… https://t.co/tCEGBDJPQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s talk about punching people,” Lopez said. Lopez said a basic fight stance said legs open, knees need bent, fo… https://t.co/HOUU8Bdxrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/FbGIfetmoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sugar Ray Charles "Ray" Leonard (born May 17, 1956) is an American former professional boxer, motivational speaker,… https://t.co/gEzF0XzDta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I can’t believe he is still the president! He is friends w our worse Enemies! Who knows what he has g… https://t.co/CShRLzxMd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh!! Norman Tischler @toddmeany that is soooooo sad RIP...he wasn't very old was he?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm always sharpening my craft n keeping in condition - "Chet Da' Jet" multi-master Boxing Champion #traingcamp @ M… https://t.co/aZxXJv2bv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter! #Pokemon #PokemonGO #PokemonLetsGo #WednesdayMotivation #wednesdaymood https://t.co/LiWLG4vZ3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @Razorsmack1 @AnthonyGuidera @ThePsycholitics Awesome. Congratulations.🇺🇸🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mouseketia i love you more. you are the most important person in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPDLTOetter @OmahaFireDept You would miss all the attention.... https://t.co/bpH2crmAFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTweetsOfMP This has to be a secret between you, me and the Internet. My paternal grandfather was an accountant.… https://t.co/efRPoG8ELu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the proper etiquette for a chino pant, do you fold it on a shelf in your closet or do you hang it on a hanger? #SundayMorning 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do people find it okay to cut off a 40 ton truck? w the roads being as bad as they are right now wtf is wrong w you]]></document><document><![CDATA[EEUU no cesa en el asedio contra Venezuela, Departamento del Tesoro ahora arremete contra los encargados del Servic… https://t.co/OwpTj8vx7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[anybody else have zero thoughts when they look at homework? like I can read it but I’m not even thinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the pot calling the kettle black .... a liar a cheat and a thief !]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATL it’s been too long! Can’t wait to visit next month for @420fest with this great @everyoneorchestra crew! Get yo… https://t.co/qV1pVTh4f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unconditional Love..... Eventhough the struggle is real at times. 😥 #Mantra #MondayMotivation https://t.co/60cPgdzRxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuSteve_504 I like mine with grilled onions and vegan cheese...hold the pickles lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @We_AreAlert She is anti-Semetic, anti-Christian, and anti-American. She is Muslim and her total alle… https://t.co/s2dTTkmLS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of hate groups in the U.S. is at a record high  https://t.co/Mn7AEGzsQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh well ending tonight w a positive tweet, i love isaiah w my whole heart. i got really good chocolate today. goodnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjmingo22 @SenKamalaHarris Women that think like that they are worse than animals. Even animals protect their babi… https://t.co/nMza9MgI86]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buying cool old stuff on ebay is kind of cheating--part of collecting old stuff is the thrill of the hunt, and typi… https://t.co/koYz2sJ0oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#prettyinpinkphotography #photographer #photography #outdoorphotography #flowers🌸 #cherryblossom #cherryblossoms… https://t.co/j8hQn6SDsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MisterHudelson  to post covers of seven books I love: no explanations, no reviews.… https://t.co/AIFUFMKwTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pleasure74 @MisleaderC @esadah @Barb81146 @MelissaFunGurl @strom_annette @CunningSq16 @ChrisToTheW @GrandmaVeteran… https://t.co/EiNeoh46Ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YRInsider @CBSDaytime Please let JT be alive!! Send him to therapy, if he's too busy to be a regular on the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF MAKE YOUR WAY!!! . #Repost @laterrazany ・・・ Monday To Friday Happy Hour From 4:00pm to 8:00pm 💥💥 2 X 1 💥💥 • ma… https://t.co/KnC9lTZNuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Praying for you and your precious mom. May God give you and your family peace and strength during this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t checked out my blog, you totally should. https://t.co/xMSgvVreb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kind_Red_Soul I don’t know how I made it this far but I’m taking breaks here and there to process. It’s been a lon… https://t.co/PZfmVkz5sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresOfCourse Well they changed over from Time Warner cable to Spectrum, but the TWC WiFi went to the bedroom bu… https://t.co/QkzvrXeQar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally have school again and my students couldn’t play outside because someone decided to smash glass bottles in t… https://t.co/8wKCeKfzbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to trust that You are near Trust Your grace can be seen In both triumph and tragedy I have this hope In the… https://t.co/QYMsjBq2LZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juicyjonjones Well you obviously feel an emotional way if you spend time to open a new twitter account dedicated t… https://t.co/cq5ieCdDeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see how he came from out of nowhere!!! @IAmTheNightTNT #iamthenight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DC4Hope @notcapnamerica Yes, and that is all it takes to produce misery for all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodLovesUgly22 Getting fired by "Hollywood elitists?" Marriage to a RWNJ? 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I’m at the point where I’m waiting for someone to pop out with a camera crew and be like “YOUVE BEEN PRANK… https://t.co/2MW4Z6cJRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioKristin Hell yes!  And honestly, a bunch of people who thing #BestsByDre are quality studio cans... eh. #alreadyLost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh this makes me sooooo happy ♥️♥️♥️ can’t wait to get my Sophie on Saturday. She will be 9 weeks old ♥️♥️♥️… https://t.co/mbMos42G8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[80 Day Obsession is literally the best thing to ever exist 😍 I’ve almost completed my entire week of it. I said 201… https://t.co/nzlHHuNcgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look at this English Hobnail crimped Rose Bowl. Looks totally like Westmoreland!  Well you can buy this gorgeous… https://t.co/PSVb2dLwpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @JakeCsiz_28 and @OlivetBaseball1 on the big win today!! Way to go Comets! ❤️⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigMama @boomama listening to y’all talk about RHOBH has given me soo much joy! Thank you for your ministry. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this farcical. Funny Pictures Of The Day – 81 Pics...@Sophia Thomas Thomas Thomas Thomas your dogs??? #mirth… https://t.co/xWLDW6fyzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My office mate worked extra hard today! #whoiscleaningthisup https://t.co/tN9cXYZnL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedOQ @QueenOfTheMM These are all so beautiful!  I haven’t read these stories yet but the mood boards give me a… https://t.co/Del5PTiCNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aDramaticPaws @RealCandaceO @therealroseanne @prageru Sounded like they were coming together to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers need more WayHaught! Earpers are FAMILY @SYFY @IDWPublishing Put our cast and crew back to work… https://t.co/BIEzlrNVqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joethomas73 Absolutely. Takes skill and love. Ray Charles is a musician? Correct..]]></document><document><![CDATA[One question: why would Uncle Aaron's Prowler outfit not be bulletproof?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maramcewin Meantime he transferred to UPenn with these grades! Unclear if this is real transcript?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children Do #NOT Belong in Cages...   They #Belong with Their Families!  https://t.co/FNwnlBXk9W via @lirsorg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin McCarthy reacts to Ilhan Omar controversy  https://t.co/YeTt86kxaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackYatesHoops @Esther188rod  GLAD YOU ALL LIKED THE PICTURES THEY ARE REAL CUTE TO PEP YOU'LL I THINK YOU ALL ARE… https://t.co/wgWRjLoZiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ParticleDecay @stormcrowmanor Hahaha no need to apologize! From what I understand they open boosters and just put… https://t.co/IBYpqlM6Tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolinaE1962 @helenprejean I pray so. The powers that Be need this brought to their attention ASAP!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These babies are dissected like frogs! FROGS! HUMAN children! #humanity #heartbreaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[God. Cody is just the WORST. When is her storyline DONE?! #BatesRevisited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelheldevans @BethMooreLPM Fact. ‘83 🙋🏻‍♀️  • days btw responses = you have a life too! It’s rarely about me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjdeluca @sereneksingh @CUBoulder Proud that she's part of @CUBoulderCMCI!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍖 🍖🍖 Final meat of the month from @GraceWong630 at @chicagotribune @ChiTribFood: Grandma's pork belly at Ghin Kao E… https://t.co/0De4MumF0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[It snowed in LA today and people are freaking out! Tune in tonight at 10 @FOXLA for the latest! ~ Snow reported aro… https://t.co/sSEpAXIumV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilysatdell I am presenting on Monday and then attending the roadshow on Tuesday. Leaving Wednesday morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_WarriPikin No but honestly! Everyday I imagine what it would be like if colonization never happened because this is beyond me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy for Joe! He will be moving to week nights... I can’t wait to get back to my girl @KarliRitter and the rest of… https://t.co/R1Mqrulbhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/tEubCaQFH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone told me today that I had a good voice for TV and I didn’t have a southern accent so I guess I’ve yee’d my last haw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I don't like to talk about this often but I want to share some nitty gritty truth. 2 years ago I donated m… https://t.co/b4QhG1zV9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick lunch break then back to paddleing! #doublestampday #FLStateParks #everystampisastory https://t.co/1p3rNkkIG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just funny. Hilarious meme from the house of funny  Click on the picture to see hundreds more!... https://t.co/rwjRGhvvsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eloc070707 @VarshPrakash @sunrisemvmt It’s worse — @SenFeinstein plan is far superior   https://t.co/RvJAqT8W2P…… https://t.co/jMvoB4cZlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[communication is everything but i get tired of telling people how i feel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the chat is out here rusting me while i was at work 😤lmaoo https://t.co/MJwadyh5Vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi Let’s run a polygraph check on you Murderer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been this nervous since my phone interview for the DCP and that was YEARS ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful out there. Someone tried sucking on my ass the minute I stepped out the door. It’s a scary time. Protect yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard for people to believe republicans can commit crimes?but boy when s democrats or someone associate… https://t.co/TY3eb0BzDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happily_7 Me too . I was watching the Red Carpet and thinking he'd be such a beautiful class act there. What a frenzy he would create.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go team @StMarysGSB! Good luck in Round 3. 🍀🍀🍀 #NIBS2019 👍👏👊 #RattlerPride #WeMeanBusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen... I present to you the most expensive new car ever made. The price tag? $19 million!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iceland is going to kill 2,000 whales. Stop them. - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/qnKYiNH0Mt via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digital Learning Day occurs EVERYDAY at Brentwood! https://t.co/leUwNayWJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC @ckubeNBC @carolelee And why again did they terminate the Iran deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Maryland City Plaza in Laurel, MD https://t.co/oZR99EyNtW https://t.co/BRBS2lRGNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC ..seriously Alex....you are making a fool of yourself.  You aren’t going to get people to give up instant e… https://t.co/0VYWbRNyYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!🌅 Tap and share 😍 @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/jWxpC3hAJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s our day off of school.... and I’ve been awake since 5am. 😡😡😡 #teacherlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food prep for weekend meals. #homemadefood #freshmushrooms @ Southwest Waterfront https://t.co/3rLEaz1Wzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#engagedallas2019 @ The Music Hall at Fair Park https://t.co/cjXvHYDMC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister I live on the coast of NC and have only seen a trump 2020 shirt on a man. Lots of bumper stickers- butno hats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @magicbeagle Stop insulting clowns.  Why do people have to copy/paste their insults?  #GetCreative]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CliffShep @HillaryClinton And checking out your profile, I appreciate your military service. What I can’t wrap my… https://t.co/vRbFugbpes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @AnnCoulter There is an easy way to solve this problem if you think it is a problem: America is a melti… https://t.co/ik0OA3a0Pu]]></document></documents></author>