<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Our bestest friend ever! Nothing compares to the love we have for this dog! #goldenretriever #pure #love… https://t.co/FjjIZXp5dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows You have blind loyalty to trump just like he did and look where that got him.And alot of other people .PRISON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfoulks Those are just my original predictions by game, if they win out they still total to my original 12-8 guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @GayleellisLydia I'm with you there girl I don't talk about it much but I was raped at 13 it destroye… https://t.co/LHnVDSIu0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch Stupid woman Someone was reporting on family connection...any truth to that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin to make it happen. See, this is the kind of stuff that just cracks me up, even though I know... https://t.co/wnuQlme3x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 months + 2 weeks: Sitting down on her own, showing her first little tooth, saying “mama”, biting #7 sign and gett… https://t.co/ixVGomi8sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We call our home the "treehouse" for many reasons. For starters, we live a few stories high with the most mesmerizi… https://t.co/6f77SKaSzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always tag Dennis as Bretman Rock on IG that this one guy I went to high school with actually thought Dennis was Bretman 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, working a double after coming back from vacay wasn’t the smartest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting about the addition of a city-wide Flag Football program to your programs this year .  Ages 5-15.   #ottawa… https://t.co/PE3SrWifi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asap_rickey @Indigostarr777 Love this!!! This should have been released as a single]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 He’s not married. Otherwise it’s a good tweet. Agree with the sentiment, but it’s inapplicable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoBobbo @WPXIMikeHolden NOOOOO!!! I’m tired of being cold and being sick and having sick kids and having gross flo… https://t.co/YPfdct3s6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @FakeNews_CNN_ @KamalaHarris The right thing to do is get the garbage man of Venezuela out of offic… https://t.co/7AzRbUt5Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baggiepr @shuchig @whaleygeek @scratch Will live tweet the highlights for you @Baggiepr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/aAnbZ14Mrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a week! How quickly life can change in an instant. Joe is holding on; he has a relentless, excruciating h… https://t.co/58PhwdjIjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MakeItHappenMondays  What a great program loganuchicago sponsors called the Young Arts Critics Program. Year 2 as… https://t.co/9sTXHAlKu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedacult @angmichaud @GrowingupinSCN @MikeRinder Purification rundown-Type deaths, or what? Feel free to point… https://t.co/Z8jAd5xguT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New nickname alert? "I saw little shifty Schiff yesterday," @realDonaldTrump says at #CPAC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great mtg @USRepLong last night.  Enjoyed conversation abt building bipartisan collegial  civility on  #CaptiolHill… https://t.co/WjlkkYc5io]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil_Lewis_ Bruh he better stop 😭😭😭🤦🏾‍♀️ don’t be mad everyone kno ur a racist now 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert oasis #mexico #oasis #travel #trees @ El Golfo De Santa Clara, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/daVU3J0uVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just4BeerLovers @AngryOrchard @badhopper @JohanBBT @ephoustonbill @beerguypdx @15jjc @qblacklock @RJellyman… https://t.co/SUfrN7BVQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have hidden your word in my heart that I might not sin against You. -Psalm 119:11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattiBrookd @Paul72717 @Gege58519609 @jorge06218084 @ZEYNAZERDA @olaerciosilva @pilarmartinprie @heroldbarton… https://t.co/1ZLdr8Tiak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent analysis by @rgranat of stifling new TN regulation of automated document software publishers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful gallery opening at argentumstudios with @ajayjhaveri laceman34 celebrating the beautiful artwork o… https://t.co/By8WIztbgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly can’t wait for next week. I’m ready to start a new chapter in my life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_Shalott @mikandynothem @robjh1 @SpeakerPelosi @DineshDSouza @DonnaWR8 @KatTheHammer1 @LeahR77 @DaRealGrizzle… https://t.co/cZZLyPRldq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realized I forgot to send out the studio view for the night. Here is your Zen moment.... @ Ravenfish Studios https://t.co/y1klZjLU77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airmit106 @dir1957 @johnrobertsFox @realDonaldTrump You left out the attacker was a Trump supporter, wearing a MAGA hat.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very proud of my very serious 🤣little Civil Air Patrol cadet! Cannot wait for him to learn survival skills as pa… https://t.co/UhTdn1Vp3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodNetwork There's Alot of protein.....I'd love to cook with any of it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg_4949 @Roberts19681 @RTR_BAMA_FAN When my youngest was 4, he used to pretend he was the drummer — he would tuc… https://t.co/O1n3vdaBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveGrandMusic Hello Steve I enjoyed your show in Sacramento this year do you plan on making any appearances at a… https://t.co/AxWnsNYLn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are looking for tips and stories on how to be successful in a non-academic WITH your PhD, check out… https://t.co/IF9oVPB3te]]></document><document><![CDATA[La importancia de la correcta puntuación. #DíaDeLaMujer https://t.co/ybFtZtL871]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitwit08270216 @dahlakhyper I am not worried about your reparations at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrissAnn Awe haha thank youuuu! I know plenty of people which is what helps me hah! It’s also nice to know some in the league]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merciful and gracious is the LORD, slow to anger, abounding in mercy. He will not always accuse, and nurses no last… https://t.co/3LbHmLZuBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok ppl who are sexually active + have animals: do y'all have sex when your animals are in the room?? Does that freak you out? I need answers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPruitt3876 @UTKnoxville Exactly!! We don't get a pass bc we are black. Students like you are a prime example of h… https://t.co/rswNBHX691]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wallajay I wish I did read a lot more but I can't stay focus... Music and long drives are my thing. So I think I will do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In class again on Twitter, and again here comes the porn 🤦🏾‍♀️  Put it in ya bookmarks and keep it moving lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much siskphoto for sending me files of your amazing pics from the @jasonblaine Night with the Stars and G… https://t.co/IZJDxBnXAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyStoneAuthor Passionate about cooking authentic Caribbean Cuisine #cooklikeatrini #cooklikeahboss… https://t.co/b5vx4Pk3Tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching all-day game shows (retro and modern) with my parents, everyone is dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandalozanor @asap_machu Alch parece mocosillo de secundaria haciéndola de pedo por que le copiaron jajajajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iouisavontrapp has quality content on her twitter and sometimes I just scroll through her feed to ready that content 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of our @GenoaJaguars students at today's NHD regional contest. Many are moving on to the state competiti… https://t.co/7P10RXz25h]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids were going to say a little thing about how influential MC Hammer was, and talk about all the awards he won… https://t.co/klUn2AEUW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not look good in orange. I do not look good in orange. #teenagers #backtalk #momlife #aintnohoodlikemotherhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm buzzed, I hope I don't completely fuck this tweet up. I just tried to start a sentence with a preposition and God dang it feels gangsta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all know her as Solange Knowles, popular indie pop artist, but me? I know her as Camille, cheer captain at Crenshaw Heights. 😌😜😌😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching @MarthaRaddatz walk in to my neighborhood Sbux to pick up a mobile order https://t.co/wpEYrkrcPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏘️🏠🏡  This gorgeous 6 bedroom #CooperCity home re-priced at $995,000.  🏡🏠🏘️ Something you just must see!!  Give Ron… https://t.co/oItD1epS5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom hasn’t given everyone her new number so she just walks around with two phones. Tell me why she’s on one phon… https://t.co/exBCC7E2KS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made pecan “breaded” chicken and roasted radish “potatoes” for dinner and I’m actually so proud of myself because… https://t.co/vRSqFDEC2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like have a real conversation with women. Talk about life and what you want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JalenReeves_10 @Pomm_Mom @natti_p07 @Runn4UrLives @RunningtoResist @sloopydeb @bostonpeanut @Copy_Beethoven… https://t.co/bpPBkQg2RD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cary Dental Rejuvenation - @dr_bikramsingh in Cary, NC https://t.co/HLAAokGwNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[entire suitcase for spring break = textbooks and LSAT prep books 😪😩 #breakrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel last night was very good and for sure will be seeing it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julie_espo Whatever we have a whole week of togetherness soon https://t.co/i1DUlRcxU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just paid over $163 on my dog to get a check up b/c she’s limping and there’s nothing wrong with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: we were on our way and she fell asleep //: let’s try again tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfroStateOfMind @claycane @karenhunter Lurie, I always love listening to you.  I think you'd be an amazing president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The drug is rapidly acting, so it starts working faster than other antidepressants, according to Janssen. It works… https://t.co/3gSPwmYpKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#8M porque todo lo que hagamos será poco para lograr una mejor situación de la mujer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an incredible opportunity presenting at GSHP about establishing clinical services in outpatient pediatric prim… https://t.co/I2F38gUXJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powered past being tired to get some personal work done and now it’s way past my bed time and I’m deciding what fon… https://t.co/lxYg1iHlX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robber shot 8 times.  Officer shot in leg.  Detective killed by a shot  to the chest.   The only live rounds belong… https://t.co/duYXfxujqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beadweaver1L An aging sumo wrestler with balding head covered in corkscrew curls. #sisterwives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowcountry1Girl @Nationalist_KAG @POTUS God Bless RIP thanks for serving]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s officially #WomensHistoryMonth so my Twitter now has an editorial line :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Americans from all states ought to provide financial support Mitch’s opponent in the next election. W… https://t.co/QAU8fHdahM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geezus_christtt No you are not allowed. You blew up everyone’s feed daily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellCare_Health I want to say Thank you to Avelene who is my Ins case Worker ..She is amazing and caring and she g… https://t.co/4uITfGXhgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP “I’m proud to lie to the American people.”  I don’t even care if you wrote optEd, you should be ashamed of your… https://t.co/6jbdpnCA5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NCAA1958.  Just saw #ToddCounty's own Mr. Harold Ross as part of the #Fiddlin'Five on CBS.  We love our Mr Ross! https://t.co/Qq4EzqvbCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PelleCreepy @SaiThanos @SuperWinterGirl @SnyderSpartan @WeirdNPissdOff I always liked his line about "As long as i… https://t.co/DIHowur5c2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA #BEATLA… https://t.co/5Yp0MsFvpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Samaritans Help Save Overdosing Woman In Westlake https://t.co/RErbCo3ufd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltraVerified Sorry, the bernie ship sailed in 2016. Kamala for President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If every American used the White House physician we could solve the obesity crisis immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hottie! This place is really cool. Love these big chairs lol. @ Grand Bohemian Hotel Asheville, Autograph Collec… https://t.co/YsvdZdaNCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 years ago we started walking side by side. Luis you are my biggest blessing 💖 We've been together over half of o… https://t.co/z6gs4hqz0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to my favorite pair of glasses. They’ve been missing for a month now and I don’t think I’ll ever see them again! 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wanted sympathy growing up you were not going to get it from her.  If I had a dime for every time I heard he… https://t.co/iYTMVDg5PX]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has great credentials and we have to give someone a chance to lead this organization in the right direction!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidYoungTBLA @SouthwestAir @flyLAXairport @jtimberlake Very sweet tweet .. happy weekend!💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home and Sam is walking around letting me take pictures of him. Homebound till my car gets cleaned and it… https://t.co/2xj956E1QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyAller @alloutofforks @OutofConTxts @Singleshot25 @wakullawriter @Ealanbrock @bsweatt60 @Andrew_Miller36… https://t.co/QYNpgq67HU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a peek at yesterday's shoot from our photographer collierphoto This is just breathtaking. I almost can't bel… https://t.co/mRGIdvl7RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨It’s a magical Seussical kind of day at Edneyville School! 🌟 @WeAreEdneyville @HCPSNC #WeAreEdneyville https://t.co/SZihDd1tkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[has (@ Orangetheory Fitness Greenwood in Greenwood, IN) https://t.co/rF9EkYgEbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @simplysallyh @GailBenzler @CaththeWineLady @DivaVinophile… https://t.co/O7ScxIHWa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela people have suffered greatly, it is time to get rid of this horror show called the Maduro govt.]]></document></documents></author>