<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I don't see my gladiators getting good wins until goats is no longer the bread and butter. At least that's what thi… https://t.co/rTmKJ8XNVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birsic @nicomeo @JigarShahDC @renewables4life @SolarInMASS @croselund @EnergyBinCom @Adam_S_James @SolarFred Actua… https://t.co/phAVhyoZcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early week winter. #bostonwinter #bostoncommon @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/PoNKtpMbdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pauliieC @ABN58 @marcelobeyliss @Chaposoto @YouleeGuzman @kioscomayor @Samvalor @CecyDuran @vagoner35 @elchiltepin… https://t.co/mV27GQC0fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyRossSwing To be GOAT it’s more than a numbers game. You gotta take in attitude and character. Lebron doesn’t… https://t.co/K2XGlg1wKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s KUTE 49.1 FM “Raw radio 📻 for 🍊Orange County” @RoseParade snapshot 📸 of the day brought to you by Creative… https://t.co/6OLtLxV04e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase And I'm gonna guess they're all super dangerous if you get bit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#oscars when they are reading off the nominees for best original song https://t.co/2AitBFGSm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Castigar a los opresores de la libertad es clemencia, perdonarlos es barbarie.”   Maximilien Robespierre]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday @OnTheMetra we have broken trains and delays on the BNSF.  Schedules we don’t need no stink’n schedules.  #Metrafail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachburke82 @SilveyESP I'm hearing 4.39 is the expectation from people close to the situation. Based on previous tedting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold as eff. Get me out of here with the @Hotelsdotcom #WinterSwearJar. https://t.co/7ClXiZx42Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romyreiner No, I don't think they should be making fruit cake either. I've been giving the same one to my friend's… https://t.co/tuHqMI9B0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff , you should run for the presidency. I think you will be a great candidate!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Frontier Communications Call Center in New Haven, CT https://t.co/0N3rHsG2Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pornosawa @JC_Moody_86 @Tycho_fan @MrKaytos No me acuerdo de su nombre real, solo del apodo que tenía: JOSEGA. XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more the Democrats embrace  their left`wing ideology the more I  look forward to political activism in the comi… https://t.co/JfgbIS8fyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Ways To Disrupt Your Call Center Using Technology and Best Practices by @tlaird_expivia https://t.co/B2AyrRtBx2… https://t.co/tpm6MS5dtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rianbroseph @acorns I have a business management degree but I’ve been looking into tech sales and sales in general… https://t.co/pN2j8gnWfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyndablooms Smollett to you too. (Black men make up 13% of the population but commit 52% of the murders.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Participants charged a fee for participating or for room and board, and can be remanded for custody if they fail to… https://t.co/2soTieB5R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaghiB_27 @RE_Games @CapcomUSA_ Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box… https://t.co/qZi5kyBX2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frjamesram I won't DM you, but thanks for the follow. I am a children's and family pastor, married and have 3 sons… https://t.co/dRA7QhuH8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came into the office this morning with system issues again lol #wonderful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate all the great articles throughout the season for Del Oro! Huge thanks to @Leniespictures]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time in Portland today seeing my friend travis.biglow who is up from LA. God graced us with overlapping… https://t.co/mJwYalFMz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to Japan from America Good morning America to the whole world good morning to everybody just want to s… https://t.co/fjp6WVi5nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorbar @RandPaul @realDonaldTrump @GOP I totally agree with you Dor Bar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great view of the summit we got today... @ Mount Bachelor https://t.co/qS6Ocr9ZO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timothy_burden @POTUS The democrats really have thrown away any chance of winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beach 🏖 Day w the Buchsters 🌴☀️🌊😎... . . . . . . . . . . #boca #bocaraton #beach #sun #sand #ocean #seagulls… https://t.co/bjq41NbhS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do dogs feel the need to jump on your clean clothes you’re wearing right after they get out the mud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio No exaggeration, people have been blowing by Hagans the same way they would as if Bead was in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much of an iPhone fanatic that I have been for the past 10+ years, I’d like to give the Androids a chance. 😁… https://t.co/jqVk50Jn7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bobbi Brown Cosmetics experiments with Facebook AR ads https://t.co/zwMhLcwFxz #]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bartender is obviously fucking this server but they insist in calling each other bro 🤢 come on guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ARHoops I have noticed its thrown his timing off. Still, you have to try something new to shake off this losing streak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the white man Dr. Naysmith is the GOAT for creating such a sport that people will pay hundreds of dollars t… https://t.co/dceO8zRYKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_corraliza @rolinhocpc 5:40 de la madrugada y un jet lag de caballo, no me pidas mucho más]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickiringer @Bakari_Sellers This guy: “You know, if you have something really important, write it out and have it… https://t.co/SFACj29XSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habermetrics If only there were two wingers in our farm system with proven success this year 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaders around the world have learned that they can do as they wish without the U.S. calling them out.  The Trump M… https://t.co/BKJJKSRlql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jellybnbonanza As long as he stuck it with adhesives, I'm cool with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJTorrance With that reaction, now I have to go on a date with you. LOL! I love your taste in libations. 🍸🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter daily for a chance to win a brand new Apple Watch! https://t.co/aC9sYdcVcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When #Raiders sign @LeVeonBell is Raiders fans going to shut down twitter with massive traffic @AB84 @derekcarrqb @Raiders]]></document><document><![CDATA[After living on the lovely #elizabethstreetnyc  I can really appreciate this fascinating and insightful article (ch… https://t.co/SN2lTxaCeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only things that I will miss from traveling to the south is Bojangles and Zaxby’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t waste your time hating on those who talk about you behind your back or those who try to keep you down. They a… https://t.co/kO6lugfse9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomaPete @MetOpera @tomkonieczny Yep just a few noises at the beginning - otherwise fairly quiet, though from up i… https://t.co/NnQzZDGIC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woodley's back is red from Usman having him against the cage and mat so much. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night we saw Cats, the musical. Everyone's first time except for Sabrina. We all loved it and laughed and sang… https://t.co/k3Dg8sMxfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3rdPeriodSuits imagine caring about hockey players lmao  I just sit here during games and type “the leaf’s” after every goal and tv timeout]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Faith Church - @faithefc in Allentown, PA https://t.co/yWXEAbA0Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenToomey We are anxiously awaiting your answer and for you to be a leader.   We have not heard from you since the… https://t.co/VwQvYhTpTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I join a 5th mission for the evening and the game crashes on my Xbox one x. I’ve had fun the past few nights,… https://t.co/bDL9XiEjIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monacharenEPPC We either negotiate with him or go to war with him. Which do you choose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#s2000 #honda #hondaboi #rockstargarage #hondas2000 #s2k #jdm #tuner #hardtop #sunset #sunsetshots #cars #japanesecars #thecarculture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is running out to take advantage of our new membership opportunity! During the month of February, anyone who s… https://t.co/wuJPIfn9bD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielrmorrison First, have them listen to Alanis Morissette's "You Learn" and recognize that learning comes throu… https://t.co/6EL317oO0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 It all goes back to Castro.  Take it from someone who used to live in West Palm Beach.  Here is their… https://t.co/YOgbadMqoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grgbkr37 @1ClickBiz You’re an embarrassment Biden, stay the hell in Europe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Twitter is a window to the world. Snapchat is a window the self. Ok, now I’m just saying things.” - @Cameron_Stirner]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UNCP don't miss out on your chance to shoot the #MoonShot at halftime tonight for your chance to win $1000 towards… https://t.co/nZHFruq2pU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@startrekcbs @actordougjones Is there a reason that many videos appear to not be available in Canada?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost getfittrainingoaklawn ・・・ 💦💦Water CHALLENGE💦💦... •Rules of the 30 day water challenge seem simple: • ⚡️You… https://t.co/MjjUKRJefX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BreakingNews Jussie Smollett is going to share a cell with Jared Fogle. It’s a #subway thing. #smollett https://t.co/SHmNR2ViDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying something local - Drinking a Family Trip Belgian Tripel by @bittersisters at @zolisnypizza  — https://t.co/uQ7YX6EUPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCGridiron @TonyPauline @wiltfongjr Terrible to even consider it. It would be Kevin White short-light.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jbrackets1 Have I missed something?  You have the LSU coach profanely talking about paying money for recruits on a… https://t.co/rGwtUiDjV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SenateDems @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Senator Chuck Schumer ought to know a fraud when he sees one.… https://t.co/TwHHXR263v]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Of course I wanna be the best version of me. I want to be healthy and in shape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ I’m taking the challenge... ・・・ #Repost #AndyFrisella with make_repost ・・・ What is #75HARD? . 5 simple daily ta… https://t.co/N9hYuwpJtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt Cinnabunnnz: “Oh, he gets to “choose” a jersey. What happened to the other one?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxiqt You could come baaaack and follow da hedgie! https://t.co/tfYmEC6suu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Load your #geojson directly into #esrijs in 2d or 3d! Treat it like a featurelayer with client side capabilities an… https://t.co/Caz96VLyRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally forgot about this Incredible Hulk parody moment. Except this Incredible Hulk’s weaknesses are sausage lin… https://t.co/Fy4cgHunNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to road conditions and snow accumulation, today (Thursday) has been moved to a full #Snowday. Your homework - b… https://t.co/6hcx0oQnxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple amendments are on the board for the conceal and carry bill, SB 150. Up to this point all the amendments ha… https://t.co/cISX63NNsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexAltenhof We’re suppose to be trash. And we’ll see about that March 12th buddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I just ordered Taco Bell, but I can cancel and come watch Pump Rules, you just let me know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[$190/260 million bitches! (@ Honey Bee Lotto in Staten Island, NY) https://t.co/MRWUGlsmUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoAddedSugar in the new @ClifBar line, #WholeLotta + 10g of #PlantBased Protein (love the Tart Cherry Almond Flavo… https://t.co/8BNksE40i7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostOtto @realDonaldTrump Keep resisting, organize for 2020. Please follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked to speak to a manager and the hung up on me. Mind you aim a gold medallion previously a platinum medallion for the last two years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @AlanDersh No, it did not. What other mistakes have you pronounced latley? Everyone os entitled to a vigo… https://t.co/aZlKp7JUhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daytona 500 2019: Key information for the NASCAR Cup Series season-opener #Daytona500 #NASCAR @DISupdates.… https://t.co/rfvElGJdm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoldbergsABC Best line of the series: “I’ve planned out our next 12 decades.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @NBATV @KDTrey5  #KevinDurant (31 PTS, 6 3PM 7 REB) dominated to lead #TeamLeBron⁠⁠ to a win in Charlotte!… https://t.co/fIweEqkQys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our new shirts are now available. Come on out during round 8 and get yourself some #MPW swag.  #MarioPartyWars… https://t.co/cQdZXlajbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Kingston Fyah Dub by New Kingston, from #SoundHound https://t.co/ZbMqDyhch3]]></document><document><![CDATA[G Web +8, top play UNCW +10.5, Iowa +1, Houston +2.5 Good Luck @ Cleveland, Ohio https://t.co/Diwk1iuFmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanditchphoto Grandma the cat loves when @ciaraspillane23 turns on that back pain heating pad thing so she can sleep on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready for time travel Drivetimers! Today’s themes for Thursday, March 7 are: 1979, 1989, 1999!  Does anyone hav… https://t.co/2IL6qehEvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinicorreiacs This one is from Amazon, you might have an easier time looking there, at least it might have the style name]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 run HR by Angel Rodriguez, @REL_Baseball takes a 3-0 lead over Lindale in the bottom of the 3rd. @RELRedRaiders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton What a beautiful wall.  #DonaldTrump https://t.co/C0h1cgW2AA]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARCADIA on Broadway Adult Small Red T-shirt Theater Theatre NYC New York City NY https://t.co/Prg2oTYUPK via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa...nice February for "Anthem"  @anthemgame #AnthemGame  "PlayStation Store Sales Charts: ANTHEM Is Top of the P… https://t.co/2AQczhIQzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[6/ Whenever Trump does something crazy and authoritarian, who puts it in context? Historians like @KevinMKruse: https://t.co/L2IhHeZVZq]]></document></documents></author>