<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Koji262 To be honest,this is only what I have heard,he is not good about keeping details of love life confidential Allegedly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta Eat every last bag of shitty rotten dicks in hell, you absolute monsters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to save cash without thinking about it? It just rounds up your daily spending and saves it. Check out… https://t.co/XBJNevDWWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elisegraham @samanthanoami So so good, right? @KevinTPorter is a genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyVirtualVaca @HaagenDazs_US @always5star @MadHattersNYC @SideHustleWino @TonyOnFood @FoodTravelist @DivaVinophile… https://t.co/HCALS3Yh5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children work for shorter hours. The really good actors that are in this age group can do their scripts in good tim… https://t.co/86LepSij3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[My knees are so fucking bruised and my entire body is sore in case anyone was wondering how you feel TWO days after playing civil war.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The proposal to #BoycottAmazon for its role in tracking immigrants for I.C.E. will get a few more months for vettin… https://t.co/ZHVK5iYEO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather be fat and happy than skinny and miserable. Today. I eat the cake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a fricking fantastic day- Friday, Matt Duchene, renewed #CBJ season tickets!! Mom and Dad are smiling from above 😊🙌🏼🎉👍🏼🤜🏼🤛🏼👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaAHarwood @SNHU Oh my goodness you just made my whole week! Thank you for being a supportive and kind colleag… https://t.co/QeR7zvPJGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah that's what it feels like too its not right what I've seen and heard either I'm sorry for privacy policy is be… https://t.co/qDGhtTa0ET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @suyingeorge There are so many ties between Democrats and Russia, the biggest is that Russia NEEDS… https://t.co/F59kgFyKMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealMrNixon I have a Moose!!! Its in her Genes too look hungover at all times... https://t.co/78NFIInHC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[a migraine will fuck up your whole day FRFR 😭 haven’t done a damn thing I planned to do today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing writing that we are proud of 😊#GrowPositive  #JSVJags https://t.co/epurJikX69]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SnowboundPlaylist The weather outside is frightful...the money 💰 is so delightful... the plow trucks go and go...… https://t.co/kLh8V1kiSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialist trying to divide our country even more! She needs to be put in her "junior" place. @aoc  Ocasio-Cortez wa… https://t.co/yUqY6qBal0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo hoo! We love Biscotti lovers!! #biscottilovers #crunch #lovewhatwedo #biscotti #awesomereviews #etsy @ The Art… https://t.co/i0hcbkagfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAGED HOMES • Staged To SELL • • • • #stagedhomes #stagedhome #styledhome #stagedesign #staged #homestaging… https://t.co/7z3KEcTEZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[For me, nothing is as important as the education of our children - they're our future! I am so proud to support the… https://t.co/TqrD32qm29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caitlin &amp;amp; John's Wedding at the Knowlton Mansion, Philadelphia, PA  https://t.co/tEEE2vZYPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition for @jonasbrothers to do a secret show in NASHVILLE @1075theriver @i1067fm ❤️🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fisk_lab @jillbrooks85 @jillbrooks85 do we have the same necklace??? https://t.co/uLPI6vT0Wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks amazing—-and stressful. I’ll still see it but my fingernails may fall victim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaTKorb @KingsIslandPR YAY but thats still a long time i miss The Beast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @DonorsChoose is offer 1.5 matches on all donations. Yes, $20 becomes $30! We only need $180 to be fully fund… https://t.co/eMttU8JmsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely not. I wouldn't wish it on anyone. "I had to suffer through it" is not a reason/justification to push it… https://t.co/PAePoqx3Nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope you had the sweetest 16th caitlyn brook, i absolutely loved getting to surprise you on your day. i love you… https://t.co/Hg7gHiDiGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have had years of hearings on the emails and Benghazi and have found nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS And we're supposed to respect you? But look who your married to @realDonaldTrump. https://t.co/YNTRXZVjPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch with the Harringtons today! LS had on magical red shoes and was a hungry girl today! @ The Mousetrap https://t.co/6ZzfakOMD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VICE I’ve always viewed comedy as a means of sharing culture and creating empathy between people. Why? Because it… https://t.co/C6YACcfaXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[gab: i think i’m about to have a stroke lexi: that sounds serious but woooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iveyjanette_207 @missberra Well I’m back in the hospital for surgery on my OTHER foot. Dayum. Terra’s dad is commu… https://t.co/Ynadj3bcEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my favorite thing is when someone comes back in because they THINK their order is wrong and I show them it’… https://t.co/GAgsKu367k]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a morning of inspiration  @AshokaU’s #aux2019 in San Diego with opening panel “Expanding Changemakers” thanks… https://t.co/WHO5ekbcqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Rotary is like a buffet; it is up to you what you want to take from it.” Ravishankar Dakoju #Serviceaboveself @Rotary]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get pushed far enough. YOU WILLL BREAK the rules.  You will go beyond your borders to get what you need.… https://t.co/NVfFh6Pdyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[winning best emo at an emo themed party is my greatest accomplishment, luv my fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Capricorn and that’s why y’all got me too haha I was gonna say I love ya 💀🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[checking guests into the dorms during mardi gras is the single worst thing i’ve ever had to deal with]]></document><document><![CDATA[KWAZY #CUPCAKES by the girl who was Saturday night 😉 https://t.co/fNEmy43REI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This multi-national corporation I work for just sent out a toolkit on ethical decision making. 🙄  On the second pag… https://t.co/abgFW4C61s]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S TIME! Go Blue Streaks! ❤️💙⚡️ @LHS_SwimDive @Lake_Athletics https://t.co/HRDWETaBWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the coffee doesn’t wake you up this AM, one step outside will! Feels like -5 in Portland right now🥶#wakeMEup… https://t.co/n5qtOusdPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revelation 22:5 KJV And there shall be no night there; and they need no candle, neither light of the sun; for the...https://t.co/9fr8QjoXdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithawynn Walking into work before 7am and seeing the sunrise on the horizon is magical.  Tea in hand!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day. A former student at UCLA Extension Writer's Program wrote a book! She was a chroni… https://t.co/RSi84aGkiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianejcarter @lugree @tedlieu That won't teach them anything. They will harbor more anger them unleash it on some innocent victim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not BEG for someone to be in my life, you either in or out and that’s how it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I do is go to work, school, and go home.. lmfao I need friends.  Wasup? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurting my Progress!! Negative Thoughts #psalms139v17 #negativethoughts #hurtingmyprogress @ Persevering Word Church https://t.co/Bw3odkcm5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro people are wild on the shit they complain in my classes. Like bitch, it’s college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy and blessed to have a fantastic day on my birthday 🎂 🥂✨Thanks to all family and friends for all your calls, m… https://t.co/jDR45AI536]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xan_desanctis @ScottsOriole Who is responsible, for this?  The woman who is given the choice?  The man who impregn… https://t.co/Y6hdSS7ITi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democracy in action 🙌🏼👏🏼 Thank you to everyone who made calls‼️ Also thanks to @SenatorLeyva @AsmPatODonnell and… https://t.co/5oGpxwEAg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @nbcchicago for coming out to  @LaraAcademy to cover our school’s #Pozolada. Thank you also to… https://t.co/M6upqpXaTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emilyxvn Hehe. Deadass I know what’s bound to happen but it hasn’t happened lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwaNYNY Also, I have found that I no longer follow certain people that I knew I didn't unfollow, like Michelle Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Sunny  ya viene en camino desde Ohio me acaba de avisar la Chiqui !! viaja solita x Delta 7:30 pm llega a Las… https://t.co/XfWG47mbo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The best color in the whole world is the one that looks good on you.” - CoCo Chanel   https://t.co/9lSYitlJI4… https://t.co/fXsYHozwcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolters_ann @johndavidstl @FrankLuntz Proves that if your white, there are two systems of justice. There I fixed it for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[she like them boys with the big ol' chains ride around town in a big ol' range]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayTookYaGirl @SQUIRREL_G5 @RockstarGames They on some other shit fr cuz I’m at $0 now and like,, I’m not trippin… https://t.co/ETB0a4QlBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really want to stop the numbing normalizing of gun violence then cover ever mass shooting — I challenge 1… https://t.co/GMyVziv81s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “All the strong bases just have OH in them” Kirsten: “basically” 🤣☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badassassassin I imagine his sisters just dog piling on him cuz he’s so cuddly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royalsreview Went twice. 1st year, I was the bookkeeper at the radio station. Not as cool as DJ, but everyone had… https://t.co/eVg5aJ3fGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has been so good to me these last couple months, im just waiting on my lil boy to be here 💙👶🏻 then my world will be complete]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS MY BABY GIRL, PINKY. I LOVE HER SO MUCH! GREAT GAURD DOG! https://t.co/OfIHX5Fh7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra The #BIBLE says that NO ONE knows the time or day of His Son’s (Jesus Christ) return. It shares that… https://t.co/VBOgKITaYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP you know, it’s not totally unheard of for a same party challenger to run against a sitting president in a prim… https://t.co/ofXGaPJCCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely did not miss having an upstairs neighbor &amp; of course he’s your typical frat boy😒🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s about entertaining the possibility that you may be wrong and being open to learning from the experience of ot… https://t.co/7wfAk9eoXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to some free online posters and time today to pull books, Women’s History Month display is up @HolmesMS_FCPS… https://t.co/kH11dMN6gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew He is a National Security Risk and he is using his position for personal gain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While it absolutely sucks the streak came to an end, it’s not the end of the world. Streaks end, it’s inevitable. I… https://t.co/KGWKi1GO97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ontario Superior Court dismisses bid to save basic income pilot project: https://t.co/Qh5wR8QKJZ via @torontostar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC you need to out law cabs as thay pollute and you have subways practice what you preach ban cabs and you should… https://t.co/6fzI0zF1AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxycharm why would you insist in people doing the beauty quiz for March BoxyLuxe when you send out random Cover F… https://t.co/wOZxe66U19]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Series "BOOMERANG" boomerangonbet Is A Must See. Big Dreezy sports white nails by me yaaaz @dreezydreezy. I… https://t.co/98yfySitBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slabberdasken @IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump No it will loss money for his rich friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[#littlecelayamonster got to experience her first SJ sharks game on Saturday! I think she had fun. XD • • •… https://t.co/7IhvwPxOji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrongIndy @freeman_ransom I first learned of it from a story by @WillRHiggins in the Star.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stom6988 last names were thrown around 😂 ones a Gillis so it didn’t really narrow it down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun to rewatch the #movie "#PirateRadio" after chatting with #actor #TomSturridge about his experience making it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck yeah no work but paid lmao i love my job 🤣❤️ shout out to the snow 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@untipsyteacher @hdbigjourney It is seriously the BEST show on TV right now! I am a @SchittsCreek #fangirl and I th… https://t.co/nmme9AH91I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days you just need to get outside and run with your daughter. #FullHeart https://t.co/c7ZnVaxhuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like mi amá does for, I will still dead ass continue this for my children]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sitting here happy but almost about to cry because I keep looking at those "dairy cow eyes" and thinking about… https://t.co/WCOOzI2GSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for coming to our event and for the work you do to keep our communities informed #MLK50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TMobile thank you for the free hour of texting and internet on my flight today! 💋 💋💋💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of all the funny shit i couldve said to jovan on the live https://t.co/YuO0dXWf0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 This is about the tackiest, low class tweet I’ve read - outside of those by YOUR President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surliestgirl @amymanlapas Would that my theater had cocktails! We just have beer &amp; wine. I would so do that Mach 3! How was the movie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cigarvolante @RMoochers @cspanwj @RodStryker The dude knows he is making things up. Don't bother getting irritated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, what about the DMC, the supposed new Disability Office that was being built in the fall (not sure about the p… https://t.co/gUWRMj9wrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the merman has a little crush on Helen @SirenTV https://t.co/9dy39VxPOc]]></document></documents></author>