<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tracysmalone leading the @eastohioUM delegation in prayer before the beginning of business. #GC2019 https://t.co/s2i1cHCLEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PICUQI @SCCM Highlight the work of our great #PICUQI colleagues and support those who are hitting road blocks or b… https://t.co/Dj5cW6mHVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM SCREAMING BTS IS PLAYING METLIFE STADIUM OMG I CANT BELIEVE THIS IM SO PROUD I KNEE THEY COULD DO IT… https://t.co/9fqqWk9tmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold outside. -9 centigrade, feels like -18.  March sucks.  But today I #killwinterwithorange  Right,… https://t.co/m9VwPzX1N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@activist360 @SafiMaasai That is astounding. Nearly one lie per minute. WOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a good night.... #SupercarSunday #supercar #koenigsegg #koenigseggagerars #agerars #agera #newyorkautoshow… https://t.co/eJ9xcV1Sqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sterling2kitty @trutriciahelfer sorry for your loss Jody 💔 never easy losing a fur baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell the college board not to add more expense and stress for students taking exams - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/d30tOUzrQE via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be at the meet on Sunday and can’t wait! My first one! 🤸🏻‍♀️ #LSU #Sports #ChalkUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuba ...Convertida en isla cárcel por la tiranía de los Castro.  Que sirvió de campo de entrenamiento para los ilum… https://t.co/1b1c482wIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all @coochiesupreme retweeted my retweet and now I’m at work fan-girling like preteen me at the Jonas brothers co… https://t.co/vhC4wLiT1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you this weekend:))  @sebtsb #SelfieforSelfLove https://t.co/3idY8MRW9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legs are shaking but well worth it !! #iClimb in support of @UnitedWayWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amara, the General &amp; Bella🐱♥️ #caturdayvibes #caturday #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #blackcats… https://t.co/P6tboQ5AQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is...is Kanye wearing some sort of velour blouse? What is this. https://t.co/QzLX38LxJZ https://t.co/HkZ4131feO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like.....  #itscool #momlife #breatheinbreatheout  #igotthis @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/aoBIvBcDdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 The early reviews for Captain Marvel are glowing  https://t.co/7Qezrmbaxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking you through Thursday's snow totals this morning on @CBS4Indy #indy #4yourmorning #inwx https://t.co/LDQTwswcs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How hungover do you have to be to eat a Costco hotdog before 10am? Asking for the girl who walked out of Costco wit… https://t.co/gB4FIVcqGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[CREEPY!! The “Momo Challenge” is the latest Internet challenge, and it’s urging kids to hurt themselves. This image… https://t.co/Q2HUyV5lNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celtics playing like trash. Lakers playing like trash..LeBron and Kyrie blaming their teammates..they deserve each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was having lunch today at Old Key Lime House and it started to rain, as I looked around I saw all of God’s beauty… https://t.co/KAJTF5W8hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’ll be throwing neck in the whip as “Quiet Storm” plays in the background weather,SOON enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧡 #365DaysofGrannySquares 🧡 #yarntopia 🧡💛 @ Lancaster, California https://t.co/bjYLAeIbV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyBiddulph Great way to get all the accused together in one place. I'm sure Trump is thinking his large parade come true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s about time to call it a night. #francesbyrd #libertasamericanaart #libertasamericanaartstudio… https://t.co/wpbNmO6q8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: how are you and your friend andrew?   Me: good, it’s been tough this past week..   Mom: i can tell by your eye… https://t.co/57ukQAVMlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Zealand Police are just so darn cute for Valentines Day 😊 https://t.co/3RpIlDz922]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate and I are souplantation tonight and we both feel like shit🤢 How much msg you think they put in their food?👀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmahaSB would like to thank @UCRSoftball for their love and support of Taylor. UCR wore red ribbons and #2 in her… https://t.co/QDGQtG1RTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @GOP Complicit  Compromised Greedy Racist Misogynistic  Ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[#braxtontyson and his restaurant is open for business! Reservations, call 555-555-5555. Walk-ins not accepted.… https://t.co/VRDadBQTqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how much money the democratic party puts out to pay trolls to go on twitter and fight the American people!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeonluminous @Lilajev @BigHitEnt Next time just @ them straight up not go in the mentions of something that suppos… https://t.co/64lHdrd14Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you miss my DJ show on @CHIRPRadio this past Friday (03/08)? That's okay! You can stream my set on… https://t.co/R7wCbfmZRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @MSNBC @SenSherrodBrown @CNNSOTU Thank you Sen Brown for Pointing out the Hypocrisy with MSM Obsessin… https://t.co/fPsP8CsTit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @w_terrence @lyft @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Get well soon my friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking that leap of faith is sometimes EXACTLY what you need to do to be exactly where you WANT to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Is this a contest to see how many liberal buzz words you can fit in an incoherent paragraph 🤔  Why are you twe… https://t.co/xKGlSeRYiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IlhanMN People who live in very thin glass houses should NOT throw stones, VP! This awaits U, Mikey! https://t.co/s54B9P2KMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettySantabarb4 @CharlesMBlow You didn't understand his tweet. The North is just as racist as the South. It's just… https://t.co/YyQAFO2iyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Seacoast United Soccer Club in Hampton, NH https://t.co/FKVn1vKJjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khanoisseur Awh! Hello baby! Rest up! Daddy and his followers love. You! 🐕🐾👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rebecca0682 @maydaymindy9 I agree 1000%. If I gave any other impression that Trump is creating a Constitutional cr… https://t.co/hCkCNLLDmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FortWorth | Mellizo de 6 semanas murió ahogado mientras su mamá lo bañaba, ella se quedó dormida. Aunque CPS fue n… https://t.co/BX2fACju2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like MUR but hate that phrase. Naming this palette Shook makes me not want to buy it because of the name alone 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@we_r_Psymese @KoraKnight_Auth @Just4Me05 @dana_lacie @ilovebakedgoods @Twstdsistr35 @MistressBec @EmboLoves… https://t.co/xaSbfhFodP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Starbucks at 1101 Madison (First Hill) has finally reopened today after being closed for a remodel. They have… https://t.co/yXCQGSkEkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan WHAT DOES TRUMP HAVE ON YOU?! How can you keep standing up for a man who has rubbed shoulders with dict… https://t.co/WYuq6NcxqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You write a list of all the things you want, and the universe gives it to you, and you say “no thank you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally Germany has a real face on Putin @EmmanuelMacron or is it amine for a woman trying to hide !!! And I'm not… https://t.co/cITPFDI0LE]]></document><document><![CDATA[met a guy today. his name was Lenny. he had golden hair, really cute, and he was so sweet. he was the cutest golden retriever ever:')]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleissmeister You’re entire show is about vain and shallow people getting with other dumbasses. No need for the sh… https://t.co/XYIbMabTld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryBarajas Y’all don’t have LJS anymore? We got two on the same street!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an adult means paying down your credit card balances with your tax return before anything else. ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[MICRO BEADED WEFT EXTENSIONS (Braidless,No thread, No Glue) Beaded Weft Extensions offer the best of both worlds: t… https://t.co/m9zeAGYexz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m too tired to take my makeup off &amp; do my full skincare routine. Send help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItssJul_62 I’m going for Gammer, Gravedgr, and Showtek mostly ! Need to get my Hardstyle fix xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[what a great time to start getting sick. it’s not like i have anything important going on for the next 48 hours🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever just start your monday morning off by curling up in your mans lap while he rubs your back😩😅❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught in the act of #healthydrinking ... shit!   #juicing #earthbar #actorslife #loveyourinsides @earthbar… https://t.co/NxTTM7a6Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[heather just told me “your 8 year old brother can get a valentine and you can’t. just let that sink in.” excuse me.… https://t.co/z6qssOSzy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spontaneous candids from an improv performance are the highest form of art 😬  but like talk about bi-lighting 🔴🔮🔵 @… https://t.co/qQLyOCAL1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part about @AOC’s snide little “we’re in charge” thing is how the House coocoobirds have control of 1/3… https://t.co/TxHmh9Fgzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which side of history do you want to be on? Some of you continue to support this sick f**k!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 Kind of cruel isn’t it? I wouldn’t want  anyone to do that to my child, I’d shove that cheese up his 🧻!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mine was Halloween night and we spent 20 min in the bathroom at some party and I ripped my tights 🙃 https://t.co/w6d6iTcvJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does this screenshot of @IrregularDave, @tamoorh, and I look like a renaissance painting https://t.co/n5AgLHkbtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished my reading for the day on page 305. left the book at my boyfriend’s apartment so I wouldn’t stay up all ni… https://t.co/VBYO6IhxGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cats always get me up before 5am if I don’t fill their bowls before I go to bed. Why do I keep forgetting this 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABAesq This is going to fracture the time space continuum through law. https://t.co/Fgy784K4Q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmniNashville @CRSOfficial @CountryMusic @TasteOfCountry longest wait ever for my room !! 4 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That is one book i really want to buy  and lets hope there is a movie too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claws0922 I enjoy mytableforone on Instagram for solo eating inspiration https://t.co/e3SKNuekBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivineOne_2 Oh, I know. But it looked like he was posing like he was a model or something. I'm going to miss his s… https://t.co/BDqoRMBeS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[THERE’S REALLY A WONAN AT MY BAR WHO HAS PLAYED DRAKE’S ‘PASSIONFRUIT’ TWICE AND WHY GOD WHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think I'll ever look at certain people fondly. And I hate "I'm going to cherish and focus on the good" BS.… https://t.co/neKJD1nOzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got up to go pee and I looked at the ac and it was set on 63°.. my mom has officially lost her damn mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARIOselfmade I’m the whole dead .... Just take me and gently place me in a coffin ⚰️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOMERCY604 @NeensCa @SpeakerPelosi @chuckschumer @SenKamalaHarris @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @DianneFeinstein… https://t.co/RYcAGp0dHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Wilmington in Wilmington, CA https://t.co/rbuS69zU0S https://t.co/TX86BK2Lc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @DrVernonLowery! I enjoyed learning with you all. #FamilyEngagementMatters #StrongPartnershipsMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[He also wondered if the grackels at HEB has a queue system in place for food distribution and suggested that Texas… https://t.co/lFXh5hzRDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can dance!!!!!!! You can jive eeeeee Having the time of your life Uuuuuuuu see that girl👀👀 Watch that scene !¡… https://t.co/ElVTBfcMzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Lol just priceless if you believe that statement you texted,i have bridge to sell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good thing about the wind is it’s blowing the snow some where else! #ontstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Huckabee: The Media Won&amp;#8217;t Tell This Transgender Veteran&amp;#8217;s Story https://t.co/WWa5YHP5YI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg I ... I don't know whether I need to see this or need this image alone scrubbed from my brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kheyduk @M_J_Spasojevic @carina_plant It provides delicious feedback since you move things over to COMPLETED list when done :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lighthouse Baptist Church https://t.co/bWpemmpCyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace un año salí por un café con mi date, seguía con la gripa horrible e iba forrada en ropa. Después del café me p… https://t.co/2JsU7YnvBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite artists lulukathulu 👑. #happygraffiti @ Wynwood Walls &amp; Art District, Miami https://t.co/W9muI4nc90]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always an adventure. Glad we get to do it together. #muncherpartyoffive #miltb #bandlife #banddirectorswife https://t.co/sbggMHJDFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I was  listening to the music pouring out of the speakers at a favorite coffee, I have the desire to pack my rol… https://t.co/OjxFcn3BEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD Best... still... the guy cuffed throwing himself into the front window at that motel..✔️👏🏼😂👏🏼✔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMAO_in_Fla @PrincessBravato The opinion of a moron that has no f*****g idea what he's talking about. Way to go id… https://t.co/R9m6lVhx2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting in line for the exhibit hall to open! Photo Booth Expo 2019! #photoboothexpo2019 @bythebeachbear… https://t.co/D3YhPUOfnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @senatemajldr How is what we do going to counteract countries like China who are major polluters.  They… https://t.co/T9BLQPyhue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonithecat32 @Marielincoln10 @Pizzapuff15 @1gingerbeauty @EricaGoss @buddy_gizmo @AngusMcPussPuss @MoetBlindCat… https://t.co/Y1EL0JmW1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House Today: 2110 Eagle Feather Ct. from 1-5pm. __ The only brand-new construction offered in Big Springs at… https://t.co/Tz1UfGuWH9]]></document></documents></author>