<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[‘t Is maar dat u het weet: @canvastv zendt vanavond Moonlight (★★★☆) uit van Barry Jenkins. https://t.co/CDWhC81hR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of commuting behind a kid who makes complete two-second stops at stop signs and tbh, I want to kno… https://t.co/hFkL4g6939]]></document><document><![CDATA[@true_pundit Hillary, your swill is harder to swallow w/ each passing day, but, please, let us stop the the White S… https://t.co/Kgn5NCsF8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Within 20 minutes of meeting @KayleeWendt she gave me a mirror...  I think we’re get along just fine. Welcome to… https://t.co/cOfmzPX0mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF "You can't get there from here." 😎 @IDeclareClaire  @RooferXX  @Kugey  @Art_Donovan  @NSRasta  @DavidLogan2020… https://t.co/RoDhy04ZJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberEats So disappointed with this service. Have tried multiple times via multiple modalities to get support to no… https://t.co/qRwfyKSv8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deut 6:6 KJV—And these words, which I command thee this day, shall be in thine heart: And thou…  https://t.co/tzXOr7CMIf via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cmoore704 @TalbertSwan @MJJLegion Can you provide evidence from any court proceedings that MJ did any of this???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big THANK YOU to Paige’s brother Will and our sister in law Dawn for a delightful family visit to Chez Duke! The co… https://t.co/Z2xE1Yah8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teams were willing to give up more than want the Steelers received, but brown is a fucking psycho and got exactly what he wanted🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarsInsideEdge why did we not try to rectify the situation of acquiring offensive help only to have him injured 4… https://t.co/KNgw3mLdel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deesnider @POTUS @realDonaldTrump He is slowly getting US up from bent over the sink by Mex on trade. Mex will be… https://t.co/3QXwaKbqKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos DÍAS...Deuteronomio  4:2 No añadiréis á la palabra que yo os mando, ni disminuiréis de ella, para que guardé… https://t.co/vX1QdbmiA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Emma's Blossom by @StickmanBrews at @stickmanbrews — https://t.co/vAXwZELW9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[From sinking sand He lifted me, With tender hand He lifted me, From shades of night to plains of light,O praise His… https://t.co/dsHhLyKlCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ “Could”, “would”, “should” so tired of these lame headlines. Where are the facts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Jonah  I was born in the first time I had a baby  My age is a lot better now  I like to think about that… https://t.co/kPqJGFJO8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[So why has the latest filing not been made public? No one has a copy? #impeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing this with a #5thgrader who is writing a persuasive opinion paper about this exact subject. If kids recogniz… https://t.co/l3lzJE3CyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @GurdeepA - what the bleep time do you get up in the morning? You’re on crazy early. @BillCoulterTO too. And you both seem so perky 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @senseidai Yeah they are just trying to figure out how much this guy is going to lie to save his sorry ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @SenRonJohnson @SenRonJohnson - you are unbelievably complicit with what you said on @MeetThePress .… https://t.co/z9YJbd4QmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplymander Don’t listen to the haters! You are an amazing person and helped me understand nutrition. I am foreve… https://t.co/NqPwAraVrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper and Max ... #pug #puglife #puggle #pugsofinstagram #pugglesofinstagram @ Highlands, New Jersey https://t.co/384VVVw80P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao...suing GOD,  let me know if you win....hilarious stupid people...that made me laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loading Cranes #25, Port of Oakland, 2016. #art #fineart #fineartphotography #blackandwhite… https://t.co/oIUyhmysJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CANTDEALDOTKOM He sacrificed his career what else do folks want, they wouldn't have done that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber is honestly terrible and Lyft is the way to go. From having to walk 3-5 blocks from your location to be picked… https://t.co/7lGDsXCPGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[porristasfuerzaregia en acción.  💃👯‍♀️🎶📸🏀 . . . . . . . . . . #cheerleaders #girls #beautifulgirls #beauty #girl… https://t.co/9E5l9HTGzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW: Right off the bat, Wilson-Raybould says she experienced "consistent and sustained" political interference in h… https://t.co/C4jY5bsEDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the point of a trolley honking at another trolley once it's in the tunnel?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN While in the meantime there is an anti-Semite within the House that Democrats do not have the guts to censor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeTillman @uswarrier Can't have lying politics here,but we can have terrorist,murderers and drug dealers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken fried cauliflower steaks with sriracha hot honey glaze. And those kick-ass sweet potato fries from the othe… https://t.co/PnnM4u4QIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel Well said Ms. Rempel, you’re a credit to the House ✋🏻🤚🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[This blows. I watch @Jeopardy almost every day....I wish Alex Trebek the best of luck. Cancer sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrtHogg Yes, of course I do. If you are going to say there is not a situation where booing in high school sports… https://t.co/D1aAie6P7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure of those were his exact words llllssss...he was a lil explicit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRALRosalia Go to ‘Your Library’ ➡️’Playlists’ ➡️ ‘Discover Weekly.’ The playlist is curated based on your listeni… https://t.co/hT63VDcqbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refunds are down this year in another blow to the GOP tax bill: Bill Forsythe, a 57-year-old hospital radiologic te… https://t.co/jt2hBK3yV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench That looks like the book for me. Followed by the sequel: "Wait, What? Trump??"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradleydevlin @UCBerkeley https://t.co/XwII9PgbCg Start your own business today becoming an affiliate with us toda… https://t.co/O6zT8hsV8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my lovely message for @PostMalone to hear! 💕💕💕 #PostMalone https://t.co/3sFwQUVwoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set Lawn and Garden for Spring a few weeks ago. Came in tonight and are told they dropped a new floorplan that basi… https://t.co/iyus8HzMUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate birthdays with friends! @ Packard's New American Kitchen https://t.co/uJGARsvruw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddy4daworld1 @Nyeem78 They didn't as they would say stuff hits different when it's true 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussOnPolitics @EdKrassen Yeah and President Obama sold our country out to Terrace for $150 billion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman Trump doesn’t understand what Sanders is ACTUALLY proposing is appealing to his supporters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta show love to the GOAT. Take a moment to show some support to a legend as he faces a very difficult task in fi… https://t.co/DyRHyveVBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Valentine's Day Spotlight To My Valentines, Mark  February 15, 2019 Everything But The Girl… https://t.co/8fArn7ymqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Being confident of this very thing, that he which hath begun a good work in you will perform it until the day of J… https://t.co/P4mSdiTA4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awonderland incredible light show last night from you and Dillon, honestly you killed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia Bro I know you think it’s s’bitch to talk women my height or higher but I need to turn this short train… https://t.co/COnwK3802r]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I block you I’m officially done... and my ex was just blocked so thank god that’s over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NumbersMuncher I think one on one he is very vulnerable in a GOP primary against a solid candidate which is why I… https://t.co/1qOG5sCkFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@migueldeicaza It just goes to show that as a customer you have to think carefully before committing to any Google… https://t.co/fjSre1P5D5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriots beat CLNS combine Targets #patriots #Pats #patsnation #patriotsnation #newenglandpatriots #newengland… https://t.co/EU4edRU23Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m4c3rrrrr Perhaps you should read the interview again. Stop trying to make an issue where there isn’t one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stallman a true legend. The not only true OG advocate of free software, but with that comes education. Open source… https://t.co/5tMVb8M4lM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The faces of victims retweeted by @AuschwitzMuseum are haunting. Lives of young and old stolen because of who they… https://t.co/I0k1TWtN2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato That's for dam sure democrats must start impeachment proceeding now on Trump we can't afford to wa… https://t.co/e5LgsYdhMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Model3Owners @leesweet @SohrabYaghoubi Ok yeah, this interface is fantastic and easy to use. ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️ https://t.co/FgjtPR2Al5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrayceEmberley great meeting u on Twitter Embereley, enjoy my latest horror film review SHARK KILLER… https://t.co/EKR243rKnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historylvrsclub Greatest. Toy. Ever.  A car elevator decades before Mitt Romney ran for President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Haven’t you heard the majority of immigrants come through ports of entry to apply for asylum or wor… https://t.co/JHt2SmodOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eclecticbrotha I believe the official Bernie position is that Clinton did not win enough elected delegates to have… https://t.co/IoWutAIx26]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WelcomeToWashington, @AdamTuss! Sincerely, me, @laurynricketts, and @chucktodd. For the record I support the… https://t.co/1eCZlLOgO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[researches would find a more direct relationship between aggressive behavior and time spent playing ranked in overwatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earnhardt vs Gordon was the best rivalry in sports. Fantastic documentary on FS1 right now. I love watching Dale Sr send Gordon to the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman How they gonna pay for last year's Koch-demanded tax "reform?" Oh, that's right - they're not!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indianaboognish I just don’t get the appeal of Biden, it seems like the surest way to lose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #fjfriday !!  Leader of the Pack!!  Where is your rig taking you this weekend??  . . ************************… https://t.co/0Ci8e9e70L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeKlis The QB room Elway created also consisted of Siemian, Paxton Lynch and Mark Sanchez lol @ProFootballTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokey_77 @EditinKing @SantanaTeddy We don’t start wars unprovoked, we finish them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo Both my mom and dad, and I went to Michigan.  In 2013 I took my dad to the Final Four and spent $400… https://t.co/OgJRT5agu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of the LA area is seeing some random music video and seeing that one random girl you went on a date with lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toronto BIAs take note. Data consistently shows an increase in spending when vehicle traffic is restricted. Most pe… https://t.co/mHfzUdrqY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinCookXXX So glad you are ok.  That must have been scary to have a 'close call'.   People who drive while on t… https://t.co/M1rxWUyP5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This vote was so categorically bad. Morally, politically, strategically, just a really bad vote by these 26 Dems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, the white girl from McDonald’s said let’s take a pic. I said cool. She asked how would we pose. Now, in… https://t.co/BXdhWCcKXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urmialamin Thanks for the follow. Please subscribe to my YouTube channel it's brand new and needs some love. https://t.co/XptqiksC4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakendufner Why Am Worry because i want be famous one day and am famous Ready. Because i have YouTube page and i n… https://t.co/DR0ecJ28tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We only have vanilla almond milk, and I was making boxed maccy cheese and it tastes like vanilla. I didn't learn my… https://t.co/78268Jx6rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trolley raced well, but Sutton, after a rated middle half of :58.2, holds sway easily to win the 7th race feature a… https://t.co/5vKdS5YWfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxEdwardsVlogs I’m no meteorologist, but looks like high today will be 32. Keep your 👀 on Thursday, high of 64!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd say it was an eventful night.   Normally I can't remember my dreams at all, but for some reason I woke up after… https://t.co/Aop67QRPVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one is for you,  C.  I'll miss you.  I will see you again.  But not yet. @WhatRUTinkin https://t.co/lAcAXN9a96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys Make your Mistakes PUBLIC! Don't be Embarrassed, Don't let others do the same Thing! Give them your Advice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpectacularDoom Wow, this is really pretty, thank you for sharing it with us Sini👍😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Energy Minister @michellemungall announces cost cutting to keep #BCHydro rate increases to 8% over the next five ye… https://t.co/nk3jx3qZAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@couragemylove off subject but this is still a banger 💜 https://t.co/CPuraMBeJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hollywood Cross in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/D1zQTEkBbR https://t.co/nI73gIHn8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyBrigade13 @BTS_twt Dope #TwitterBestFandom⁠ ⁠ #TeamBTS  #SoompiAwards⁠ ⁠]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Boffin It’s such a random thing. I’ve caught two in #PokemonLetsGo, and some in ORAS and SuMo. I’ve caught six… https://t.co/BOgp8VpMjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DeptofDefense @DHSgov @VP Why not just eradicate the place once and for all? The hell with USA/PC… https://t.co/PZBbUvqs7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being so lame you retweet people talking about you.. Also @seanhannity has the worst hair I’ve seen since… https://t.co/S605smPZ6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baltimoresun Why did they shoot 22 bullets. Why wasn't there another way. Certainly after there was no return fire… https://t.co/0ibjDvx80g]]></document><document><![CDATA[This for real make me sick to my stomach, again. I hate everything about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love god and whoever it is but sometimes i wonder if this is how we were created bc other living creatures were c… https://t.co/Hd8LfqXGWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis @RichBTIG Very intelligent conversation going on, really enjoying it guys!]]></document></documents></author>