<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This will force Senate Rs into either bucking Trump or going on record favoring the fake emergency. Nancy will move… https://t.co/bCBslx1ZZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del Tacos fries hit extra hard at 1 in the morning after working an 8 hour shift 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Fling 2019 Mardi Gras Theme!! Part1 ⁦@LSCTomball⁩ ⁦@LSCTStudentLife⁩ https://t.co/Pox2pBPVHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some entertainment. 250 Funniest Nursing Quotes and eCards: https://t.co/wxREQR1IYG... https://t.co/Jq3rIwPx9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself You were trained by the Olympian swords master Bob Anderson ⚔️  https://t.co/OrJlctnPGw #fencing 🗡 https://t.co/cVJ5DjgeHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into this old gem. RDMP 2015 graduates. 💙 Ps. See if you can find me. 🕵🏽‍♀️ 👀 #development #graduates #bleedblue https://t.co/arQcWD3wKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've met a lot of POC with depression and anxiety with the exact same mentality because for Hispanic people especia… https://t.co/LmOgcgvcVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates This is Paco Rodriguez he’s super brave when he’s on his gammys lap. https://t.co/Fgg4Qknlak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly thought you were doing so much better and was so proud... at least now you’re up in heaven with your mom… https://t.co/OdjQL9M5y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baurenlaker saw the pic and immediately thought why did Bauren Laker photoshop a human smile on her foster dog ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putinsgay @Jessie092859463 @EveScottGarner @CloudContact @AWorldOutOfMind @SarahPounds7897 @hxernst @The_Lady_Red… https://t.co/QbyTi8KTot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday 🎈 @drakenic He and his team have taken @TMobile marketing to a whole different level! I’m excited to… https://t.co/XVhexU6Bru]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s really sad that playlistlive is just a bunch of tiktokers now like what happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[That path is for your steps alone🌈#GratefulEveryday #AttitudeOfGratitude #OSAAT #WharfRat #LiveTheLifeIShould… https://t.co/k0oR1v8Ft7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my lil love bugs 🐾🙌🏻💕  #LadyBug #BorderCollie #LittleBug #Beagle #DogsOfInstagram @ Wakefield, Quebec https://t.co/6ZuzpGj6JQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earthposts Cross country skiing is wonderful.   Wish I wasn't old and could do that again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrChrisRuss Dude they’re soooooo good. The açaí is a blueberry and pineapple mix. Soooo fucking good. Best açaí ever holy balls]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day before #valentinesday I hope your #heart is filled with #selfcare &amp; that your #life is filled with… https://t.co/eqADwSNmRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanna_lynne1 Love their lobster feast! We're making cream of crab soup here tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakleyr @SACAC_Info @NACAC @SanfordBishop @SenatorIsakson Glad you are able to be there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WAVY_News So happy i pray to god everything goes well no fighting no killing just good fun so we can continue what… https://t.co/IhZ1I7AS67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Is cosmetic surgery covered as well?  There are emotional reasons for those as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @TurnKansasBlue Always #alternativefacts why lie about weight? Does he know we can see him???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing #alteredcarbon article. Really gets to the core of the questions it asks and why it makes great science fic… https://t.co/2FUMpRmQYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Once she stopped rushing through life, she was amazed how much more life she had time for.” -Author Unknown. I’m g… https://t.co/F3Gic13oZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious french toast with chocolate, cinnamon and raspberries @VoltFamilyMeal this morning! https://t.co/MrJMFV0kRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Now they’re looking into the letter sent with white powder he received. CPD, Prosecutors is one thing, but Fed… https://t.co/APUc7e2OH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stableford The haters comments r trivial. They should be reaching out to the victims families n sending their cond… https://t.co/SD139Z9mj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wth is ppl problem with  me telling  my friends  my business  she got a problem  u need  to deal with  it stop talk… https://t.co/Pafd5yVJHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching Game of Thrones and cross stitching with my dog for the last two days and now I have to go to wo… https://t.co/8krGacKGx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I was lucky to be in attendance @ the Ceremonial Swearing In of @DWStweets and @RepTedDeutch ! Congrat… https://t.co/N70iZEAiU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re burning the bridges that want the best for you, when will you ever wake up? but I guess that’s not my problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody know of places with access to free copy machines? Tryna make a list of DIY/zine-friendly places in SA. I got one plug so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dylan_Tennison_ I also think it’s funny how she chooses to highlight the “sins” that she’s never committed]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all i’m in carries top five favorite people list... it doesn’t matter what number i am BUT I MADE IT Y’ALL.... I MADE IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I asked about CSF leaks but bc of time my question was asked in more basic terms than I needed. The quest… https://t.co/MAbonzDCtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraCl16697408 @Andrew27573773 @LowerMyBills Irks me when people take advantage of the welfare system. I believe… https://t.co/6SUYF3CGh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the most amazing time at #Nashcon today! I’m so sad it’s over but I can’t wait for next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@preacher_man88 @AmericaFirstPAC @seanspicer @IlhanMN https://t.co/2iYNjEppOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whom ever doesn’t vote for the Wall and border security is just part of the Swamp, Republican, Democrat, it doesn’t… https://t.co/sQxRAsLiOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeBorelli Jake- was GA your first acting gig or did you start out on something else? You’re going to do big thin… https://t.co/JtJSpxamAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ eres narcopresidente igual que tu compadre @NicolasMaduro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hibillyby Omg I’ll Venmo if he can send a dozen or two to Los Angeles??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @bardonthebeach in #Vancouver. I wish I had a reason to go up there so I could see the upcoming season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I know there’s legally no way a red velvet french vanilla cappuccino at tim hortons is good. Yes I still ordere… https://t.co/PminUSIYMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Olivia Colman accept her #Oscars2019 for The Favourite was like mainlining hope and joy. (and yes, I still… https://t.co/feqmdFf6WZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Should haves” are devastating. When individuals fall short, and weaknesses become apparent, with nowhere to hide,… https://t.co/dZCtYHxuL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simtilver She had not heard of it til an adult. Personally, her walking away from the Catholic upbringing and embr… https://t.co/8TD7JRIIZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @PhilippeReines @_waleedshahid @KatyTurNBC Without some honest discussion about all the Hillary-hate fo… https://t.co/QDOaP51nb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blastin' @AvatarBenji in my cube and got the night cleaning crew at work hooked on Rain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahMackAttack @atlasobscura @RMBouton This trip will be incredible. I did marine natural products research while… https://t.co/pLYqAuCKIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tazarae20 @googlenews I can think of many reasons he is shameful.   Unfortunately, tweets are limited.   😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @kemdvm! Having fun with @PurrPodcast #CatBites. But spring is still far away in Ottawa 😟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolvesofexodia Yup. Suddenly, it's super hard to support local art or writing when there's a price tag on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very Successful meet! ✅   New PR; long jump🤗  Proud of all my teammates today, for always giving it their all! For… https://t.co/j7iDNw3D15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 Manual audits are not too complex to counter a terrorist attack. Local official inconvenience is no exc… https://t.co/DevL0eW4nM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids are more #resilient than we give them credit for. Recently, I watched a kiddo whip out a pic of their tumor in… https://t.co/iKXVhgthJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kristen, Tara, Veronica, Felix, look at you all doing great things still! @KristenLukas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Denver tomorrow for #XDW2019. What should I checkout while I’m in town?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent: Looking For Change (Full Documentary) | American Express https://t.co/f96e8KAMOf via @YouTube Financial literacy is so important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lou_cindee @EdKrassen Source, pls. Where did that "quote" even come from? And one isolated incident in 2012? Did h… https://t.co/NWDKB8JCSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prevuze It confirms Claire's story that she lit the fire around Ciara!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WomanResistorNC @B52Malmet @Jersey_Craig He will drive the election whether he wins or not, many are running on th… https://t.co/kEpT46kwyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3momdoyle Hi Lisa!  Good to see you again. I hope you have a blessed evening.🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeWithoutDiet @iamyourgasman Someone found it! I thought no tomorrow is the day we find it and #tweetup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomelessDay @AOC Alexandria we aren’t a third world country YET and we aren’t a socialized government YET, but you… https://t.co/DLwwjv9S59]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the fact that I always think everyone is in a bad mood over text and I take it so personal..  bitch relaxxxxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my new bundle for the coming up March Detox challenge. Love it that it keeps me healthy in and out with added e… https://t.co/AmQMm60SmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Computer Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/olmu8IzfAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnicovasquez @Membrillo__ @Angelalerena Entonces Macri es populista? https://t.co/HApkc48GVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer We are constantly overwhelmed by the sheer force of our cognitive dissonance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swipe for the magically 5 minute transformation! Lord!  A few things I’ve been using RELIGIOUSLY:: 1. Re9 set- $212… https://t.co/GspttoGGle]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on a 7am flight with all business travelers. The flight that just got into our gate is a red eye from Vegas. It… https://t.co/D3w3wJZY5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier in the week I read something that basically said God isn’t the one who is in a hurry; it’s us. The more I t… https://t.co/sWUAXYU37G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @DerekPa56710094 @akomama_tm @PatGrant7777 @SUPERGOCHOo @Lee888123 @stradagangelica @meerbakker… https://t.co/dQEEy18zkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Srsly done with creeps IN ALL CORNERS OF EVERY INDUSTRY AND HOBBY And whathaveyou and so forth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks nominating me for Most Spirited! Now it’s time to bring it home :) Voting ends tomorrow night make sure to v… https://t.co/Li2jtm1iDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let Us WORSHIP YOU Together One Heaven ONE KING ONE Church Let Us WORSHIP YOU Together In SPIRIT And In TRUTH. ALL… https://t.co/ee1k7S5ijx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbamok @BoysMakeNoise ‘And you wanted to dance so I asked you to dance but fear was in your soul...  Some people c… https://t.co/WhdjOgR71V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne I got an email for your show line and they are beautiful 🤗👠 I wish I look this beautiful mowing the law… https://t.co/zn51RCsqD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonMM9 @psychdr100 @Judeless77 Yes. #Individual1 will be remembered for this - and not much else. #TrumpCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWLOS @WendyWilliams @TheView @TMZLive  "Kelly" at it again why isn't this pig behind bars already… https://t.co/fHvpEJ53DD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#C89robandmegan #shoppingshenanigans #bunnyears🐰 @ Walmart Canada https://t.co/ScrrVwyX81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see a NFL combine video of all these football players I get butterflies just thinking how close my boy… https://t.co/OXXDnblCCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to a talented band from the Wendake First Nation in Quebec.    . . . . @monmontreal @tourismequebec @ Mon… https://t.co/PEgxXZyQXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I JUST APPLIED FOR @Zinepants !!!!! I’m so excited, even if I don’t get accepted I hope to fully support this zine!!! ✨🌈💖⭐️💛💛💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz @carnmcgrath This is what blackmail looks like. I would lay odds that it has nothing to do with Russi… https://t.co/AEXp7IxPvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows You should be ashamed. What has Donnie promised you?  Like others Donnie has stiffed, he’ll probabl… https://t.co/eR4OVlWLxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great concerts from back in the day: Slayer, Venom, Exodus, Death, Dark Angel, &amp; more: check out the "… https://t.co/VyUEOGEf8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RainbowActual @MalcolmNance If you believe that, I’ve got a wall to sell you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston Rodeo 2019 Tim McGraw. Amazing show!! @ Houston Rodeo and Live Stock Show https://t.co/YcwT602ZkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[the main form of communication i have with myra &amp; mikey is just sending memes back &amp; fourth that somehow pertain to mimosas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hummm Nadler has a Russian agent working for him! https://t.co/9ZxEToA7yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A liar can’t stand a person with a good memory 😭 #lol #TrendingNow #twitter #retweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapcentral Totally unrealistic, I realize it’s a soap opera but really!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I yield the remaining of by time back to #JimJordan #SNL was AWESOME!! @nbcsnl @RedHourBen was phenomenal, as alway… https://t.co/YJjLqFFKet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ignatiusweeks Sadly i think its likely Canada will swing PC.  Amending the cultural barbarism act disenfranchised… https://t.co/joLTYiv5Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDoubleclicks @csymrl @nprAudie @npratc Yasssss Doubleclicks on NPR!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[More lovely Wednesday game designer shenanigans. Dice, quilts, cults, and my favorite, "this is not a game - I just… https://t.co/GHy3kmpi84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tip-off in Snyder! Let’s go @TexanBasketball !!! #TexanUp https://t.co/v3l3h7iIU0]]></document></documents></author>