<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a King Sue by @theTGBNews @ Peppersprout — https://t.co/aRdSe4Df8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewshaAjami @ByIanJames @P_Mulroy @jfleck @RefriedBrean @reviewjournal They were once connected, which may count for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost both my recycling bins in the wind. And a fence panel is knocked down. Not a bad outcome considering all the damage across the region.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The king of understatements! But Trump has shown us what is wrong with our system! And he continues to confess! So… https://t.co/Hjcsqnj5HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @holochronicles this guy made 1,138 guesses for @starwars #StarWars #EpisodeIX title..   .Some are good, some f… https://t.co/GyeZVk9kfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex trafficking, prostitution is anything but a 'victimless crime,' experts say https://t.co/yKa4rLnQlQ via @usatoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball It is a quick move, necessary to keep the impulsive and unbridled president in check. Trump must experien… https://t.co/WPExCqVgv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MondayHeinz Yeah. It was totally intentional. Watched him park and he lined it right up like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conspiracy Theorist Jerome Corsi Apologizes to Seth Rich’s Family – Rolling Stone https://t.co/Iu8tEKQO7w // thank… https://t.co/yInnyDTkHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalNiederman @TonyBrunoShow @Phillies @Dodgers @SFGiants Listen to hear what Jody Mac thinks at 10pm tonight on WIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hikemonster @beeonkeyco Footage of @beeonkeyco dancing: https://t.co/SQN89e4OaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only cause I saw some comments brushing it off , but this shit actually already had a 12 year old commit suicide in… https://t.co/NVBr7OnKbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent push back from Jake Tapper challenging John Bolton on US hypocrisy and State Dept. lies about our forcing… https://t.co/glgCDzXyyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hear that the #NorthKoreaSummit didn’t manage to strike a deal. Maybe USA-*-GI needs to pay Chairman Kim another… https://t.co/yyaUvXUIvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last resort. #sterlingwong #travel #explore #bombaybeach #california #ruins #weekenddrive #pathlesstraveled… https://t.co/2UTgLrw84U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why easy to find print instructions how to go from red line to streetcar on @DCStreetcar website? If I have a weak… https://t.co/KQEQAJb59i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hickenlooper How can you unite the country when everybody has different beliefs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crap I forget the name of it but I think it's by this band called Gretel Von Foot or something like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPotanas @ezalmanov @Mottel @bethanyshondark @GPollowitz @SethAMandel I’ve been in prisons where inmates actually… https://t.co/Ki6iwz2jf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrcaBC101 I see this in my own family, east of the Rockies too. :(  Sadly, s/he who does with the biggest bank acc… https://t.co/5eaV20MwnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWayneDodson @NatePickowicz @hbcharlesjr I’m not interested in debating on whether or not an atheist can on one… https://t.co/XRizCto2mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another cool #library fill d with great #librarians this one in Lakewood lakewoodcity #civiccenter #castatelibrary… https://t.co/lYa6YO5Xhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the .@SECNetwork basketball coverage. There is a basketball game going on. Talk about it. Who cares about the tournament. Awful...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BornInThe_80s @HBJaguar @WWENXT Let us know when you’re coming and we’ll make it memorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be so incredibly awkward to be one of the Liberal volunteers standing behind the Prime Minister right now. #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little cognitive dissonance for those of us who know our #comics history! Ha!   #CaptainMarvel #Shazam… https://t.co/eeisxuiqE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep on thinking I’m 27 for some reason? Might have even told someone I was the other day when they asked? Can’t rly remember.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we know from watching Dimwitcrats on news such as Swalwell, Schiff, Waters, Pelosi, Schumer, And AOC with a hos… https://t.co/YXB1Mhg8Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dh9champ @ThisIsFav @fanspeak @Steveospeak Devin Bush will NOT last til the second round]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 8:00 AM CST, 11 SE Beeler [Ness Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 3.50 INCH https://t.co/2r9SZZNkx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AEWrestling Think there will ever be a chance @KileyJrWWE will ever join? He was  BEAST in 2016. So much wasted po… https://t.co/zscLpNy3aA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/orFORbLU6n  This just came on the radio boys. @creecher1200 @TSN1200Bunda #DriveTune]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the people in the back...  OVERSIGHT IS NOT HARASSMENT.  #TrumpsAmerica #PresidentSnowflake]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL. Fading Binnington and the blues give him the lead so he’s gonna get a shut out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcfreshair when our kids were young we would turn clocks ahead early in the evening.   Always with a chorus of “Its not fair!!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capecodweather @wbzweather It just started sleeting here in Pocasset.  It is actually noisy as it bounces off the… https://t.co/myUAWCKpqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlsWestlake leading 45-24 with 2 minutes in the 4th! https://t.co/cZ930WaxON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington Pl &amp; Sepulveda Blvd Culver City, CA 90230 https://t.co/gcbdhDDrPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation You’re a sack of 💩. Vanish! #ONPoli #THUGNation #DougFraud #PCPO https://t.co/IirWZcNT6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aiight ladies your man bought you flowers and chocolate and shit, but did he name a ROACH after you?! Idts 🤷🏻‍♀️ bt… https://t.co/zxHqMSTsrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer We know history repeats itself.  But this is too quickly for that to be happening again.  Trump is a st… https://t.co/tHJsuHN12A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Louisville #Arizona #Baytown #Dallas #Austin #Killeen #Texas #Chicago #Joliet #Angola #Springfield #Follow &amp;… https://t.co/HOLQO31MWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cold Envelope by @3PointsBeer at @threepointsbeer — https://t.co/rgso7hblk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[..@MorningAnswer @DanProft @AmyJacobson Amazing but there are STILL R Kelly Apologists on #BlackTwitter.  -Steve on 88]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you only have one fan that follows you. 😢   Thanks @HeathLawsonPhto. https://t.co/lqOQD1BKf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Stick to our constitution it has served us well since the beginning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianVirdz para que luego salgan : ¿de que sirve tener la pelota 600 toque si solo tiran 9 veces y dos con direcc… https://t.co/D4N1s6e8L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow is falling out there like it’s REALLY enjoying itself! One last fling before spring? Hmm, maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 @DPJHodges @graceblakeley @AyoCaesar @faizashaheen Leadership is messy Owen. It requires the ability t… https://t.co/Vlx4OP1kB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved LiTiRilla, wish him nothing but the best, bring in the next LSU prodigy, Devin White]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Motherfuckers I got the emergency alert and it still raining hardest outside 💦💦 https://t.co/CRqh018JU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I had a girlfriend, I'd buy her Under Amour gear that I can't wear because they're only for women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masters3d @SwiftStudioApp I’ll be honest, I was really mad at you for about 30 seconds until I got the joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all started from a dream, vison of where I wanted to go and HEART. When you know your values but ppl think other… https://t.co/4vGTsoDxXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhino_Records Fantastic #Quad mixes in @dts 192/24 please keep these and 5.1 mixes coming on blu-ray audio!… https://t.co/lYf1y586si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - https://t.co/ad8HA7i4C2 A.M. News:      Why Atlanta’s airport is facing a state takeover bid;… https://t.co/mtvPJOkcrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalBayArea I don't think Klutch has actually done that once, Tristan Thompson I guess?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracytms Two originally, after pmo fires thirty staffers and a minister I’m sure they’ll have more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyTrask @MCHammer YOU are clocked up... You forgot to say Hi... And Hi 👋😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/V46VvbxCUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work with a young guy who just moved from Venezuela - he’s even visited Bogota a few times. He was very confused… https://t.co/I1HYny5IMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasta for lunch on Mondays almost completely fixes Monday’s but not quite]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pleased to report that after 243?long years, racism in America has finally been fixed by Green Books best pict… https://t.co/6aUxKmUyQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t find a fucking pair of AirPods anywhere and I’m about to try to buy them out of someone’s ear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StLouisBlues @ParicCorp Is Dunn v Kadri on the list? Because it should be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FvckPlastic Side note: Humans wreak havoc on the environment, we’re the next extinction event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christifulli88 Lot of factors to consider that have been mentioned by others. To me it largely depends on who plac… https://t.co/BdbDYtDfAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedge down screener, this is to find stocks that are in a downward wedge pattern and you can use this to catch reve… https://t.co/GOoBQJFwfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[An accurate and fair reflection of what happened at #AOCintercept from... Fox News.  https://t.co/CHkV13k8aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #FriYay everyone from our morale officer, @jonahbytes!🐶 https://t.co/Ng1JbHUesr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at The Gap at the 202- 206 circle. yesterday. Even the cashier had to do a double take😉😂 @ Bridgewater, New… https://t.co/sfBXFlROqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for an older RPG to play on my switch... which one should I get?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost losing a child and going into bankruptcy inducing medical debt to own the libs #vaccinescauseadults]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wifey did bring me a surprise for me from @strawsf 😮...😋. . ❌ #food #foodie #sffoodie #sfeats #sanfranciscofoodie… https://t.co/4OBDoMYTp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[003 - Santo, santo, santo - ANTIGUO HIMNARIO ADVENTISTA https://t.co/7eI4uwpHUB vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sushi!!! (@ Meshuga 4 Sushi in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/MczNkA3d65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DE_RandyW @DukeEnergy @CALmatters Sure don't need to teach California the Duke Energy coal ash disposal method, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TW115 “Orange you glad?!” This song came on the radio at the right time. That’s how kairos works isn’t it? Let my l… https://t.co/qEK0iwWjjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current mood but the blood of Jesus won't let me!! @ South Ozone Park https://t.co/UuME5sM5ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pivot. @elevationchurch  @stevenfurtick  #jesus #bible https://t.co/CVk8VAzdvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSantoro1 @CoreyAH The optimist in me - based on Pompeo’s intervention - says they have a sequence in mind, a… https://t.co/swnajEHXTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 points for Daryl Porter in the loss as Gannon gets knocked out of the playoffs by UPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can u imagine if the nets wouldn’t have been assholes and we could have had Luka and Jedi? 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNC LAVALIN. Pour éviter de voir ses titres se transformer en obligations de pacotille, suite à une chute de sa quo… https://t.co/iEgQV6BZvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackson Sivills (flu-like symptoms) had 21 points for the Mustangs. https://t.co/0Ty95pDfd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRBolen We quit serving kids meals about 5 minutes ago when you pulled in with that van.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @bobclemente5 @HillaryClinton Exactly where in the US Constitution does is asylum mentioned. Cite Articl… https://t.co/BUz5weeZwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 8th grader Jason Montgomery’s first game of the season for Varsity basketball at PC. I love the passion he play… https://t.co/5MMtybxx9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ it again!! A man, hiz mewzik, and the road. #AlwayzN2Sumthing 😊😲 (I don't own the rights to this music). @ United… https://t.co/gzfJuregyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 1: St Olaf scores 1 run. Fleigle, Kermendy, Baade due up next for the Pios.  Score: Pios 4 St Olaf 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khoetker @wrongsideofpond This this this ... Ndam is young and will improve but Valot is the real deal now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember my photo professor in my Intro to Portraiture class say,  “When photographing individuals with scissors,… https://t.co/sQ28uVWOUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zathras3 @dandrezner My paternal grandfather also suffered from a gas attack in the Argonne. He died in ‘56 at just 64. #LestWeForget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skipbolden Maybe my fave movie scene of all time. https://t.co/2mfH6VcJxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump, real sorry about the supposed toll this Presidency* has taken on you and your family. I mean, it’s not… https://t.co/wDW0zHOoh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you loved Louis CK's comedy, that's great!  So did I!  But I'm not mad at our "PC culture gone mad" or whatever… https://t.co/QKLuh9P40S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomyoung17 Agreed. And although some poems come to us spontaneously, it requires skill of craft. And almost all g… https://t.co/gvPNUg6VqX]]></document><document><![CDATA['Atlanta Braves find Josh Donaldson primed for a big year' via @fansided  https://t.co/0YapTuI7t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thunder_Drummin @CHammond13 @nytimes No one’s limiting their senses. We’re all human. You’re pretending there’s a… https://t.co/THmhNFPG12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkincaid32 @BillTaylor_SWCC True! But she is your kid and that’s pretty cool!]]></document></documents></author>