<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sunday is for smokin!! Cause $15 a leg at the fair was too much! #smokinthemmyself #smokedturkeylegs #soyummy… https://t.co/pTPzhZM3ZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azucarRoc @WWENickMiller When you said you were recruiting, you weren’t kidding!! I’m so glad I’ll be able to see… https://t.co/QAepLTKLwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was in such a happier mood than usual today n i hav no idea why i jst luv luv evn tho there’s none in my life i j… https://t.co/tV6AabR7mB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to make this boy fall in love with me, so I’ll keep ya updated Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[charcuterie &amp; cheese board, with the champagne of beers as a snack.   yes, please @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/WbcrRlOclc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorgirly0802 @finallybreathe_ hi yes i’m a speechie too!! swiftie speechies... this is a trend i can support]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a customer gets mad at you because their 10+ maxed out credit cards got declined ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyR0320 @valentinifrank @kellymonaco1 @1SteveBurton @GeneralHospital I agree! Drew and Sam can handle just fin… https://t.co/qrftncX0oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubeLang I am a person that goes back over what I say and cringes! Let me know when u have a cure]]></document><document><![CDATA[A piece of my team &amp; a big piece of my heart! #GBS100 https://t.co/JJ5VQXNSNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackculinary @johnColtrane215 @afranks3 @PublicDomainRev On my coffee table now ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agradezco información de donde encontrar DEBRIDAT y ALBUMINA HUMANA en ampollas, para la sra Marlene de Guzmán(UCI)… https://t.co/Q6zTTcHLcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a hot shower after a cold/ busy day! #relaxing https://t.co/6bf5BVWHtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voy hacer un hilo de todo lo que yo considere malo, que me pase hoy. Estaba haciendo mi bitácora y me equivoqué más… https://t.co/CbYhcsoGLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnioDaza No se preocupe a mí también me sucede pero no tanto. Lo q pasa es q no quieren ver lo q está a la vista L… https://t.co/ofTe6Z7FAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior Day ceremonies prior to pivotal #Pac12Hoops match up as both ⁦@SunDevilHoops⁩ and ⁦@BeaverMBB⁩ playing for s… https://t.co/MQhHo4mPuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kisbet_ Sama dong Bet 😌 bedanya aku jarang posting foto aja takut netijen iri kan ya. (Digaplok)]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: 66% of VA dog labs ended. Defund bill introduced. https://t.co/YYfdqHAOUN via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 Pansies!  Everyone of them. They don’t deserve to hold office.  We the people have spoken and still yo… https://t.co/kuyGVuk3Ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember journalism professors telling me to write like I talk.   Little did they know, I was embracing Galvano’s… https://t.co/pVx7ITVqB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What it’s Tuesday already!   Got up and got my strength on this morning! Week 5 Day 2 Back/Biceps-Circuit! Love lov… https://t.co/TcLTT4yrAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns my 15 y/o son is battling leukemia. He wrestles and plays football in HS. Going to fresh/Soph secti… https://t.co/cts14tcixl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladevita12 Merci Anna aujourd’hui c’est mon anniversaire je suis ensevelie dans la neige et doit aller à Montréal.… https://t.co/IxARBvIBID]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏻👏🏻 This makes me SO happy. The fake accounts are clouding up the social media resource that so many businesses an… https://t.co/jb11mv7eeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jonasbrotherscomeback #jonasbrothers @jonasbrothers https://t.co/XLVAj8x9S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwalkup @hormiga @RyanKBrook Nope. It’s just a violation.  Have an okay day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque el dinero hace que pierdas el piso? Lo material va y viene el amor no..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta startup crea productos alimenticios sin gluten, lactosa, soja, azúcar o grasas, basados en algoritmos y un mod… https://t.co/7IvYG7RZew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding a good pair of scrub pants is almost as hard if not harder than finding a good pair of jeans]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Is. Baseball. After the game you stop and take it all in. I love this game! ⚾️💙 #Baseball #CoachDad #TeamMom… https://t.co/QNfmjpmUv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/28fbZSqUlB #9089920512 @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/kFpK2cUHlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre cumple de mi bebesita, tipo tranqui 💕 @ Licobar https://t.co/XzT2UAN6Eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting my $ where my mouth is and organizing a seminar/panel for #ASAP11 w/ participants who aren’t  part of the s… https://t.co/xspVwp9cw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What: Burning Burlesque  When: March 4th Where: @thephoenixlv   #burlesque #vegasentertainment #vegasburlesque @ Th… https://t.co/FrC1zAvLVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maria_fragata @GaryBarlow @BootcampBarlows Have you tried the Keto diet? My friend Julie lost 80+ lbs and my husband lost 40 lbs! 😳😎👍🏼😊🌻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candidates include Elizabeth Emmanuel, Elias Mathes, Jackie Bigony, Drew McLeod, Brad Johnson and Lisa Bright. Thos… https://t.co/BPFpSzYFwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHuttonxo @babysnitchery He didn’t even account for pads and pad liners!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, bc my unicorn was a bit too over ambitious for my first apparel design, I’m going with Oni!! But idk which desi… https://t.co/PoYkqokZqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've had to redo the kitchen 11 times. #SignsYouNeedANewHobby https://t.co/9RqmAUB7J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camiladewit @DisneyInstitute @DisneyParks @WaltDisneyWorld Thanks, @camiladewit!! I am fantastic and hope you and your family are well too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[..“the opportunity to interact with the president, the US Minister of Commerce and other political figures.” The co… https://t.co/cAkjbhcckE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love them so much. No matter what their happiness is always connected to mine. @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d climb every mountain... And swim every ocean.. #hiking #sunset #sunsetthoughts #soexcited #heaven #westside… https://t.co/dGwnL0dN9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebel19 I’m not even low key considering it. My back and shoulders are a wreck because of how I carry my stress an… https://t.co/Og62XEsrXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflection  #silive  #annaardolino #ny1pic  @NYCParks @StormHour https://t.co/dRhJAuxgBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlScout_77280 has all your favorite #girlscoutcookies at Flushing KROGER from 3-6 today! Stock up for #TWD or… https://t.co/MLxwJVHKKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me about! I’ve never seen anything like it!! Nothing like the Midwest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio reintroduces 'heartbeat' abortion bill as new governor vows to sign it into law  https://t.co/jhsJSRn7XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell is not a place. Hell is not a certain evil. Hell is other people or the lack thereof and their lack of love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody @LivePDNation @citylights @OfficialLivePD I’ve passed through Georgetown many times. I would love to… https://t.co/Iw1ZWKozr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever puts a roof over more heads... and this seemingly means more parking spots too! #SanFrancisco… https://t.co/TIrv4uAb3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Warehouse Shipping Lead - https://t.co/CCQ7Ct372t #SupplyChain #Madison, WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton Take the high road with these ignorant fools who are sheep 🐑 following the Unqualified ConArtist 45… https://t.co/xryHIvogJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEricaHanks Happy Birthday! I was just in @neimanmarcus earlier drooling over all of my wish-list items and thou… https://t.co/fNhWgd6gjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[a year ago on this week i lost my grandpa, this morning i woke up with a text letting me know my grandma passed away this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it 15-8 after Knox scores 🇨🇦- tie out Cats. Once 7-7 it’s been all #GoStatesmen since]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel sad for the Russians but not for Putin. I had some very good friends in college that were Russian and they w… https://t.co/2Sdjp5gE2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you can’t do this with your friends without then getting mad then are they really your friends https://t.co/MFtfynUTw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView @WhoopiGoldberg Omg!! What happened? Seriously, if Whoopi dies im going to lose it. Luke perry, trebek! I can’t !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 @TuckerCarlson I don’t know about that. He’s plumped up quite a bit! If she can’t do it herself, I’ll help her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muh_ryyMoore Me af when I was pregnant with Cas 😂 I went to a 3D place all the time and paid for some]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you’ve had a wonderful Valentines Day! @ Pier V - Baltimore Inner Harbor https://t.co/NjCZ3e5rg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NaZu troupe puts on and interactive performance and and encourages students to sing along in french! https://t.co/lXNwipKTKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@14Breeanna Buy a baby item and then the winner will give it back to you haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittyBhagat @Communista2 @QuietManc @bunkybun @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @deeshanger… https://t.co/UoJLoabcTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Michael's experience in our #brainstim +intensive therapy program here @RehabHopkins. We helped, but Mich… https://t.co/do4FfqoNMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a producer who shifted to a  reporter .... can confirm this is accurate 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bexbyrd Should we.... reenact all iconic moments in Philly this weekend orrrrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg, the only place I can vent is here, I 45 so much I can't get a grip sometimes!! Today us the day.....blahhhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triana922 Yea,  this should cause paranoia...  It's happening to more American women.. Your an IDIOT.... https://t.co/IZ4GxCVt1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Should Make Your Blood Boil!!!!  Everyone of us is Responsible to every Child!! We Need to do Something Now to… https://t.co/DzIWnNmEPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since I quit drinking there’s something about the morning air that really makes me sick 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe that will make the sea lions reconsider their stay in California beaches]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people sit in front of me &amp; start staring dead in my face yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: #CaptainMarvel wasn’t all that great..? I just couldn’t connect to her character, and honestly,… https://t.co/HytXFnt60K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moi, le 8 mars, devant les posts sur les réseaux sociaux pour la “Journée de la femme”. Et il est même pas 8h 🤦🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/h6MvyvkgFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/PXGYSwDDIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be cool for classrooms, but we have a number of students with bee allergies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman Totally agree. What have they done for the American people. Nothing but steal our money. Pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[once you start talking shit about my family, i lose all respect for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[ten years have flown by and it’s so crazy to me to think that people still aren’t grateful for having both of their… https://t.co/79WuhZi90m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4uConservatives What I find is I get to a certain number of followers, then get knocked way back, then work my way… https://t.co/9PqWOZsMeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s threads like this that make me grateful we all waste so much time on social media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know any information about personal shoppers? Not for shipt but for the people who actually work at the… https://t.co/6kPTs0yCgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuddled up with Chubbs and she came up to kiss me. Then wants belly scratches. I’m like girl I wanna sleep. But cra… https://t.co/nCliEtgkOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“As a teacher - You may never see the seed you plant grow” Paul Hernandez #pde2019 @CorwinPress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic Fake News!! What’s up is down, what’s in is out etc...it’s all so bizarre. https://t.co/UxRDCViGdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting @DaterGators and #IamCPS at Dater after Dark! Good times!! #mardigras #highschoolprompose https://t.co/ElHiO4UfvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GateauxAmmo Interestingly, it's another reason why the OAP is discriminatory. Kids who aren't white are far less l… https://t.co/07a9dkFNNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika thank god the president doesn’t act like her every day.....oh wait.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[So #ashercross knows the choreography to all the songs from #thegreatestshowman @ The Woodlands, Texas https://t.co/buSCMRTvc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyjaffe I'm going to go with anything Proto Zoa from Zenon https://t.co/RvKmHDnoNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Perfectly articulated @davidfrum . trump is an increasingly more serious threat to our nation and the wo… https://t.co/RUuuMUvivZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Because I want to secede from this Ponzi Scheme with the crashing Domino Effect as soon as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katlauv @kkatherinemarie @alleiigh You’re always invited, duh. You get first dibs on my couch obviously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamChance Hopefully I can get on tonight.  We're driving home from Busch Gardens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdanielwelch had to ask herself when starting out in her career “how do I align my passions with my professional e… https://t.co/52fZklIDac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asdcaregiver @tylerwhat16 And Portugal is doing better now that it has reversed course from austerity measures https://t.co/jgfNA3ZETJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreasureHoopz I’m walking into registrar like...... https://t.co/B1WIuRXgIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope niall is spending the day with his closest friends, drinking, n just having an overall happy day :D]]></document></documents></author>