<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@softheartedjmg @stacysays You deserve to meet the world of celebrities😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[T minus one week until I finally get to experience the @SXMTheHighway Music Row Happy Hour. Making up for it not be… https://t.co/jEV4ZhnRE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been stressing about my midterm grades because I missed so many assignments and quizzes (because Im too lazy to… https://t.co/OD5EPfTRiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re printing photos at Walmart and your nudes pop up #sorryfolks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing by (@ COD Parking Lot College 6B in Wheaton, IL) https://t.co/WONSvEisvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperScienceGrl Poor wittle @FOMconferences need to dilute quality science just to add vulvas to the mix. #sexism… https://t.co/hn1RWvxlJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re curious about what I’ve done so far today, I’ve been keeping track on #Instagram Stories and using the ha… https://t.co/RBmcmxC8ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tikthee_11 back up a few steps cus I can say the same about yours bitch. lookin like commander in queef 😞❤️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer 😂😂😂😂💩💩💩 “ we’re not socialist, we just want to take others hard earned money and use it for the irrespo… https://t.co/vnloomv0mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Moonday! 🌙 What’s your favorite time of day? I think twilight is mine. The transition from day to night with… https://t.co/mJJB7nPvg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordan_Sather_ @Sarah_Q_Smithy Exactly  Why mandate poisons but not organic gardens?! #FoodIsMedicine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good cock in my ass, good cum on my face Video 👉🏽 https://t.co/heh4H9Swjl https://t.co/iXnuu55gQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanofi gives U.S. discounts of about 50 percent on Lantus, a long-acting insulin, SSR Health found. It still costs… https://t.co/0kVuSevrdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in! I can’t contain myself since the offer came in last night - we booked a cbs pilot role! @poschemodels… https://t.co/g59sLqLKiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[While deep cleaning, I found mine and Natalie’s social security cards that I hid for safe keeping😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biggybadass @KITTKARR83 @therealwallbie @Brooksidefilms @stradlemonkey @RealTarx9 @NicoMartelle @Mark_Lapping… https://t.co/16tORfK4JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle and Barack Obama assemble Higher Ground Productions leadership team  https://t.co/Z6VMlBotba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Franco Society Fashion Week  Design : One World 🌎 Peace ☮️ https://t.co/mjJBmP0BeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to need mine to also tell me to stop buying T-shirts and dresses. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGlantz3 @GaryFlirty @sternshow @rmlimodriver69 @HowardStern @shalomshuli @MFBrooklyn @diamond_mike23… https://t.co/u4vXW6n6SR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mantra!                                            #doingitafraid #doitanyways #takingrisks #doitafraid #bebold… https://t.co/yaG77Wbhd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolioJ @jtd_gameon12 @FreeBeacon Joe, if true, showing strength is always a good move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dickheadyash Yea, U-Part. I have two but nothing feels as good as a fresh sew in. It just hit different 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorreyDeVitto Refreshing after all the Will/Nat drama.  #Girls #FaithfulFriends #ToTheEnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[OSCARS.... those anti Wall, Anti Trump, anti Gun liberal Hollywood peeps had over 500 ARMED guards last night and B… https://t.co/9GdntZaKVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPatrickBrown @TheProfitCNBC @marcuslemonis @SaraGuerard @carrieleelily My deepest condolences, Patrick. Glad we… https://t.co/PMV6wIaHPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cackling over my adult male cousins who still have their mommies wash their chones. 😂 Do better, Mexican moms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OG KitchenSync team #allthelove #teambeach #lifeisabeachnau @ San Mateo, California https://t.co/qsOptNeoFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m young, I’m cool, I’ve still got it.  *goes to an event on a university campus*  Never mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I always tell my students. Live by this and you'll have a wonderful life]]></document><document><![CDATA[back home// a quick trip to Lawrence for coffee + a new dining table 🌻 @ Lawrence, Kansas https://t.co/jju54mWF8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyDutton16 @ElkeHansen7 @laker477 @barb71 @OldSmokeEater @TeriHentschel @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong… https://t.co/TL3lqnCmC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also shoutout to Mario for being a gem and for Zazie’s giving their servers living wages and bennies! Yay 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh yeah. Enlighten us on these technologies. Please. In detail. https://t.co/Nt278F69UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cDaN7tVOaY i need to make my way to @iammiketodd and @transformtulsa bc y’all this was a great sermon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vss365  In the stillness of the sunset Let us walk for a while  While the water lays like sheets of glass  Reflect… https://t.co/JIpHqCnwOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenReliefLP Oh I will, on this subject I just started the High Tide, yummy 😁👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @realDonaldTrump I saw Maddow and smiled from ear to ear. And, I think the judge and Mueller's prosecutor l… https://t.co/BSFMJjeQAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC it was all political theater   No one expected any other outcome than the one that happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D1Kading @katherineschlu1 @paysopoppin This was when @Becca_Kamrath had to rescue you😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always happy when feeling sexy!    #Boudoir #boudoirphotography #boudoirphotographer #bridetobe #engaged… https://t.co/Wawqoft4mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The revamped space, new neighborhood and fresh faces -- Rahein Jones keeps the past close. It may not be apparent t… https://t.co/atCPZzszNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corey_poteat @_Samantha_Lea but in order for a person with an addictive personality to have this “illness” they ha… https://t.co/Qh5wAHG2Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Why don’t U name these people Ann?  Sorry, but U r just like the ppl that that call Trump a lier , but… https://t.co/ytyIRvJv9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Omg I seriously dont know how the US people deal with that disgusting individual as their president.  N… https://t.co/0rQNSCpyKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna do my makeuppppoo. I’ve been such a basic bitch for the last few weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 325 million people in the U.S.  A whopping 16,000 voted for @AOC. Hardly the pulse of common sense Americans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hypertrohy...😳. Thanks Cliff...for pushing me out of my comfort zone!! @beastiology101 #evolv #evolvhealth #goals… https://t.co/aopbVpvilX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @EmilyAReports for helping a girl stay warm this morning! 🧥 #amnewsers https://t.co/BmHoEE6WR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laughts21 ok so i was not there because I am old and it was toooo cold and damp-)  but there in spirit and cheerin… https://t.co/vLTvVROqTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebassclinics Completely agree! He better not go chase her. I never cared for her. Cailynn I think really loved him… https://t.co/M79aqHurGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans If it make you feel better or something where I live at where are going to get hit with a snow storm we… https://t.co/JOaV7Yd2uA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing this weekend? #thon #thon2019 #ftk #forthekids #fourdiamonds #pennstate #psu #zta #zetataualpha… https://t.co/QUijj1r7L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job teaching students how the real world works, life definitely stops for weather in Canada. #sarcasm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see #Breakthrough! Dr. Allison and his work are so inspiring. #endcancer @MDAndersonNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theebillyporter @CSiriano @OscarHeymanBros @sammyratelle @TheAcademy Love it!! https://t.co/hQ7WL4p71U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recruiters from 16 companies showed up at a job fair in South Paris hoping to meet some of the best prospective hir… https://t.co/4SZCqawJqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry not sorry. Had to put this on here too 🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/ziFWXXyegO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with our 6th grade buddies to make pinecone bird feeders to help our feathered friends through these last f… https://t.co/OI9apuCMfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was under my blankets and in bed! 😒 #MalditaPobresa #TheStruggleIsReal #MondaysAreCrucial @ Ontario, Calif… https://t.co/2nAwFnbdCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yrfatfriend I wasn’t either but my sister in law said it was intense so I had to try it! Worth it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Levantarme a las 11 de la mañana solo para ir a buscar una camisa a una tienda , es demasiado sacrificio pero necesario 😩😞 #EsmuyTEMPRANO🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of “Go Dawgs” from the stands tonight in AZ. Great move, @AafLegends 🙌🏽💜👑 @aaronmurray11 #GoDawgs #AllHailATL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC every channel is talking about your questioning of Michel Cohen. I watched the whole hearing. Women rocked. #greatjob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thursday Everyone ❤️ #Faith #Outlander #ClaireFraser #JamieFraser #Fergus #CaitrionaBalfe #SamHeughan… https://t.co/BfT1vuOKs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always listen to Jolene twice. First @DollyParton ‘s first, @MileyNYCyrus’s next. Both are so beautiful. Dolly’s… https://t.co/XmPL2kueYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[17.2% from three after that make from Dedric. A 20-point deficit doesn’t erase easily without knocking down triples #KUbball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGSchneid @DoloresCatania Dont worry love,shes just kissing Theresa's ass,to keep her job.Not that TG has ANY powe… https://t.co/s2EtvQuWRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus really ordered a pizza 10 minutes before dominos closed AND had the AUDACITY of making them deliver]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this game with a third grade class last year, except they drew a snowman,... #humor #giggle #smirk #funny https://t.co/PQYQ1MuTPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @FarmerForFifth for being such a passionate and bold advocate for #reprojustice and @ppvotesct ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it or still at it! Great job Wyatt!! @reddingkicker @rach_redding]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished writing a five page paper on GUCCI and I just wanna know wtf I chose to major in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deann4656 @NatlGunRights We are for liberty and freedom. The other party is nothing now but liars and criminals. C… https://t.co/ecZNUwo5J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ung facial expression ni Papa P nung nabanggit si Maris hehe!   #POPSSSSMusikero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoElleithee U speak about the President remarks? How about Senator Harris's we can change everyone's behavior to h… https://t.co/MHfRKczRFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have, quite literally, never before heard of anyone who thought it was appropriate to autograph a bible. If this… https://t.co/thOV3ibAoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it a universal law school thing that there’s nowhere in the building you feel like you can talk on the phone wit… https://t.co/8fb7WrrNrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soap opera serious followed by snuggles and smiles! @ Fuji at Ink Block https://t.co/CAnl5osVa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love working with co workers who have the same taste of music. It makes the busy day better cuz we just jam out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the largest trade deficit in our country's 243-year history because of this president's tariff policies.   #ThursdayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mercedes Benz Stadium  Atlanta  Georgia  March 10, 2019  Atlanta United 1 FC Cincinnati 1  #atlantaunitedfc… https://t.co/OLeTPx0gGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryquint7 @sappermartin @allbikesbiker @howlett_delma @jonz970 @John_R_Berna @Sequencer16 @SilkSunflowers… https://t.co/jUGywh4xys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Your parents are related to each other, right?  First cousins?]]></document><document><![CDATA[my hidden talent is drinking a venti iced coffee and instantly falling asleep after🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this snow or salt? . Quick trip to Death Valley! . I am so mind 🤯 that there is soo many amazing beautiful place… https://t.co/ZPdxDR08Vy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because @LOWELLCUSD200 had an Institute day, why not take @kraftskorner 's class on a field trip?! Such an awesomel… https://t.co/TsyaPTQLwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellyb1979 @Vahalia241 @arcadiarose_ @alleykatt74 @Naddez @PanRose30 @RichardPallette]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got me all choked up 😢 #KidsDeserveIt Claudine James - Class Civic Engagement https://t.co/tLrR9zCrNW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was saying that @kerrywashington recommending #WhiskeyCavalier makes me want to watch it because she can do no wr… https://t.co/WB9ACOOWAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember at a party i was so drunk and I told this guy I didn’t have time for boyfriends and I’m trying to get ma… https://t.co/FLXJAjnEI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Check out the YouTube video of him dancing last night. I lost my dinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalifromdavalli also annoyed of the trend  “no one: me: something random no one asked about”  Why does someone hav… https://t.co/C2OAPAH5qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packing for my morning flight to 🇨🇦! I can’t make up my mind what to wear to the @TerriClarkMusic concert!!  In my… https://t.co/21tUQM3UCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey solo mom   You rock!  Celeste London  Holistic Solo Mom Coach   #empoweredwomenempowerwomen #empress #queen… https://t.co/2ctpNb3fpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[thread this tweet with the most cursed image you have in your camera roll :]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Migrant Children Detention Center Could Be Built On a Chemical-Riddled Landfill?! https://t.co/uvCdyiruFT via @earthjustice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandiNaughton @AmericasCenter @FOX2now What a crowd in the dome!  I hate to even think of what the traffic will be… https://t.co/Ly3jUI0OgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the outfit mirror images happening on Wednesday in @JEFCOED! @DrJuanitaIVann https://t.co/LDPxK6bFho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ours is too rough and rutted to skate. A slow crawl or you’ll loose your undercarriage.]]></document></documents></author>