<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[may @Manny_Sattlr and i tag along? we would like to find ourselves some fine texan men :)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BYUCougars @JakeOldroyd39 @Nike that’s disgusting.....what are your beliefs, Do you know who they have as a spokes… https://t.co/p0soBDu0mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Even though I knew this was a real possibility for the last couple weeks, it is still crazy to think about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMH... Colorado police under investigation after viral video shows them pulling guns on black man picking up trash… https://t.co/TVtKRIupyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to the weekend and dancing on the tables!!  💃🏼🍾🥂 #fun #instafun #sobewff2019 #sobewff #instamood #instadaily… https://t.co/j9I7MS3xeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski @I8uridea4brekki Who do you think you are? The nerve, the fucking nerve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book your appointment ahead of time! 🌹😉 Thank you beautiful to let me work your beauty lashes 😉💞… https://t.co/VSTkwaGJCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi! good morning!! @GreysABC makes history today!!! that’s it. that’s all that matters. byeeeee 🤩⚡️🙌🏾@shondarhimes @EllenPompeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melrobbins Oh heck yes @melrobbins I absolutely needed to read this just now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naging si @moirarachelle4 and Timothy pala akala ko first boyfriend nya si Kuya @jasonmarvinph eh ops ✌️ #MMKMoiraAndJason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to support the work of @CLYLP_org! Unleashing the power of our youth in the Bay Area!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya friendly neighborhood #trashkitten is bored and says you should come out for some hangs and possibly some tree c… https://t.co/goaBsh5Qhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a high school report on Hitler once and this was how he acted: hours-long, self-indulgent, rambling speeches,… https://t.co/oZ9KtfId6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[waitress: ms lu? i remember you cause you’re so well put together  me: https://t.co/M2plMzBeXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[And another life lesson, don't get in a tiger's cage to take a selfie! #wth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be a part of this company for almost half my life! Thanks longhornsteaks for the ride! #25moretogo 😳😂😜 @… https://t.co/9Og1m2wrAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este desastre es culpa de Chávez y me da "tremenda arrechera" que gente que se benefició y era Chavista a morir and… https://t.co/a3i7Uvy14a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersHughes @NationalHistory @nearpod @leagueofschools Awwww! Thanks (and right back at you!!) https://t.co/kt41pTJHTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like my grandma has been with me all day, feeling her presence extra hard today 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our society is getting more and more perverted as the days go by and at such speed. Perversion is becoming sacred e… https://t.co/DcvGg2M3Ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Pledge...promise to impeach?  Don't these elected officials know that a person has to do something wrong,… https://t.co/DNQUzpJy6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broken_medic Wow... Your injury came from your surgery? I just can't imagine waking up after surgery and being giv… https://t.co/JZyMpSzNBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s right! 💯 If want to be the change in this world — you got to be there and voice your right! Thx to #AOC and… https://t.co/ofjksHE9NU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen tells Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz “Mr. Trump is all about winning. He will do what is necessary ...… https://t.co/VMkGEXuLQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My U.S. Representative sided with the gun lobby instead of the American people when they voted NO on H.R. 8, a bill… https://t.co/Hs1iuxvo2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron ventured out into the backyard...  there’s SOOOOO MUCH SNOW!!! #ndwinter #sooverit #brrrr #19daystilFlorida @… https://t.co/uHqAeULYd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmberrow @TonyFleecs Well it’s official, I shall serenade my dormitory building to Skyfall https://t.co/AYS5CeDKFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreiV92389968 @XXXHOLLYHALSTON @thereallisaann @thejuliecash @ryderskyexxx @DiamondJackson @brandi_love… https://t.co/dMrx1WPKR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Bitter much 😂.....your too young to have all that hate on your face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jprast1 @tonibraxton "literally had only one hit"…REALLY? #STAYwoke #PutSomeRespectOnHerName #UseGoogle https://t.co/v7lZh8bTRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My staff goes all out for 100th Day of School.  Go Deer Park El! https://t.co/1bgiQ1Pi2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are some "representatives" working to protect the constitution and our democratic processes and others are not?… https://t.co/VqA9T3svVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are very very welcome dude!  I’m expecting birthday wishes in April... it’s your job to research the day 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s because it’s a contest of a bunch of “no-namers” instead of the stars. https://t.co/31H2I96sSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast While I feel bad for her, part of me is whispering, he told who he was &amp; playing the tape...https://t.co/50ch9O0U7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can have who I want at my crib cause guess what? I pay DA BILLZ. Lmfaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were to describe the East Village in one image . . . 🤔 https://t.co/nXWHR9tXz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Awe missed it tonight.  Will stream it tommorrow.  Got some personal issues going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m going to take the dog on a walk  *starts heading out the door* Mom: ... Elise you sort of forgot the dog Smh 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Varneyco @TeamCavuto @cvpayne  Granny Yellen just insulted @realDonaldTrump who has achieved in just 2 short years… https://t.co/5YXVzmBAiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing double exposures.  I’ve always been a slow learner and it seems it takes me much longer before things cl… https://t.co/7pQitqokxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDHaltigan @gerrydulac I agree. In fact, I blame Colbert for a lot of the problems the Steelers are having.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so important to understand. @maddow @nprpolitics @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This proud @uOttawaAlumni is back in town! I am humbled say that today I will be returning to my alma mater,… https://t.co/tyPpp9Wu1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday you crazy twat, you are way more than a best friend❤️ @cheytwat https://t.co/AmaKzOZiq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heppoco01 "Yeah... just a year..." I hope I feel better once i change a bit. "Besides, we can do boy things, I guess."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaleerenee @estalinemarie Lmao😂 I’m not illiterate I just don’t care🤷🏼‍♀️ but like I said you’re to much of a pus… https://t.co/u23y3ZOXxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb @Dame_Lillard Nothing was done. These "fans" are knocking players off their games then crying foul wh… https://t.co/m4539TzJe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TXwoodworker98 @fred_guttenberg I would like to see the results of Trumps check.  Oh wait there wasn't one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigiskowitz @EricRClarke Yes AND because of a strong, growing user base too, even more important than the capital @craigiskowitz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurcellKelsey So excited for this! I can’t wait to see what you accomplish this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s vote #ODAAT buddies! Elena and Syd are goals.   #renewODAAT #OneDayAtATime]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend spent the last ten minutes doing yoga while I watched a compilation video of cats begging for treats.… https://t.co/VekYBmYhwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 Oh, it looks like he needs help. I would tell him to wait right there and meander off to get help. I'… https://t.co/kW7BH8EMyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mount Sinai  Cancer Center in Miami Beach, FL w/ @kaceydawson https://t.co/8brT9eWrjy https://t.co/u3SFWoEGZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now-Downtown LA Business Journal Commercial RE Awards 2019. Congratulations Swinerton on receiving the pr… https://t.co/GE4avymV9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whata isn’t even THAT good and the fries are trash , the only other option is onion rings which are fire but make s… https://t.co/oEFoRkEff6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiHowarth1 @bjcreigh Mark Meadows hired many illegal immigrants at his country club!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was having my back scratched or my hair played with, I wouldn’t be having this sleeping problem right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are they gonna just fix the crisis in the movie and not in real life...??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t leave baseball out! https://t.co/JCqzvQRNO0 https://t.co/NmouKxXbWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome evening led by the fabulous multi-talented Stephanie Rogers - this time going acoustic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnglishmanSDCC @Plague_Doctor_D Ok. That's you. Other people might want to put their money towards other things, o… https://t.co/7300GlKafT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConcernedEdS @RepCummings @HouseDemocrats Then why can't you and many other Trump supporters see him for the lying… https://t.co/TsuXI2uLlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR @alfonsocuaron His son has autism. Her daughter is playing along and taking care of her brother. Please, be respectful, people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day, another adventure..🔝 ❄️🏔💞 #workhard #playharder #lefthandcanyon #tuesdaysinboulder #boulder #coloRADo… https://t.co/9Uyd0RkxM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching my feed because all my ig stories are just club stories haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fourth grade is also exploring how authors organize texts. I love seeing Thinking Maps as they navigate their indep… https://t.co/kbUBpTzigz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever in the mood where you can’t tell whether you’re hungry or sad??]]></document><document><![CDATA[and then St Oaul says to the Romans, another famous passage that we Devout Catholics often quote to cover up and ex… https://t.co/JmHtreZrRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday #repost #ameicanhippie @ Dayton, Ohio https://t.co/s398G7T5tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at ihop in Hobbs and a fight broke out and I honestly just came to eat not to get a show 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MzHizzle @nearpod Please share with me and I'll add it to the district library for all teachers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirikel_richie Bitch tell me you dont remember when we pulled up on John in skyhouse 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year on #InternationalWomansDay was one of the worst mentally for me. There was false accusations said about m… https://t.co/LsmCFT7GSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, a student who does the absolute bare minimum, when my TA said “you seem like a student who stays on top of the… https://t.co/jzAtztewKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods God does not make mistakes - we people do.  Pray for our country. If we do not repent, turn from ou… https://t.co/OyDkYO09jX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Snow means more #snowboarding #skiing🎿 and fun in #bigbearlake and the #sanbernardinonationalforest🌲! Come play… https://t.co/yY30xgnZ9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many camera announcements happening I don't know what to do with myself. Yal got opinions on that cano… https://t.co/djdXZkwVHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISLila Almost too much happiness to “bear”! ❤️🐻❤️🐻 https://t.co/qtpPrZkhaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaOrdway very nice meeting you!! Thanks again for the pictures and autographs. #yrfestivalcbus https://t.co/6WPhCSOM1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechMicDrop @sixfootcandy Which would be a great a point if this whole thing hadn’t started because Someone wanted… https://t.co/y0mVgnwT9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailyinnermind @TexasTribune @washingtonpost No, what’s infuriating is that people are dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CITY GIRLS IS GOING TO BE A JMBLYA????? Finna buy these tickets RIGHT NOWWWWWW 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @KimberlyMrsRR1 @usminority 😂 😂 😂 They're so lame and grasping at straws for anything to keep the people stirred up and angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 1.49 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/GkMAizAEhl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Optimism for the 2020 so we can get this liar in chief out of office before he gets us blown up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weber 4th amongst our D men in ice time...does he have the virus too? #gohabsgo https://t.co/HY7tdNYK7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing is for sure... @hilligansbg knows how to throw it down for #nationalmargaritaday !!! #Hilligans… https://t.co/gAle5tLaRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night seeing all the Leyden Artists win awards at the Triton College HS Art Show! #leydenpride #leydenart… https://t.co/hjtKtfnzVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curls are still on point! Happy birthday @GlobalAnt_26 #floodingyourfeedswithgreatness https://t.co/4x1X1m94hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also for basketball season, the Princeton middle school boys, JV boys, varsity girls and varsity boys have all won… https://t.co/sadio3r7ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentCrypt46 I tried to register but the verification never came to my email address. Honestly I’m too invested… https://t.co/5byRtziwvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertB52216885 I know! WTF!! Are the treasonous criminals governing our nation happy that now kids think treason… https://t.co/4VlmjvOsoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashuhhbeex3 @leeleebb21 You are not a member of this family!  😂🤣😂 Uncle Tommy sent me this yesterday. Make me jeal… https://t.co/FM0B7ApQHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[All praise to God the Father who brought his chosen people to rebirth from imperishable seed through his eternal Wo… https://t.co/lXaAnE0fv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what i honestly can’t wait for 😭😩❤️ I just want to cry watching this over and over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickdayton @KDKAHeather @KDKA Yes it is. It was frigid. You picked a good week to leave town!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so first of all the cat they said went missing was the WRONG cat, 😑🤦🏼‍♀️ BUT, Houston has been found and I am so happy 😭💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda sad but I’ve got like 50 chocolate covered strawberries so I’ll be okay]]></document></documents></author>