<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The usually tourist pics when you travel to Key West 😂 #keywest #floridakeys https://t.co/GajkyNyj5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohgodspike @RealJamesWoods On phones? Forever? I got fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA HISTOR… https://t.co/27L5L4hHNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many battles, many fronts, many despotic dickhead evil enemies. @POTUS is doing his best, which is superior a f.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseAnMike That on my and my wife’s bucket list ..... to go to Yosemite.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNilges @LadyJayBBall @nilgeshannah @sarahlinthacum @micahlinthacum @gkhaarmann @HoopStar_44 @cailin_mooney… https://t.co/PzwVrjA6M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday night Caesar Salad with romaine, quick homemade dressing, 149.5* sous vide chicken breast, grape tomatoes, p… https://t.co/f6xiuQdxk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other Chicago news, one GM finally did the right thing and released Kicker Cody Parkey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angryasianman If I had the time, I'd do it. When we say boba, we usually don't just mean tapioca balls. There's ps… https://t.co/b3u5mBWGCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielvankirk @DPTpodcast @SklarBrothers here’s a short one. And......it’s a Greenlee. A good guess the Agee oppor… https://t.co/XrpkHOyeoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up, fell out of bed Dragged a comb across my head Found my way downstairs and drank a cup And looking up I not… https://t.co/cBYtqRDJGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amtrak 88 NFK -&gt; BWI (Friendship Airport) on March 10, return on 95 on March 13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un vampiro, para eso del calor y quitar el sabor amargo de la cerveza https://t.co/vVY218mrjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two women are potential terrorists in Congress wake up America President Trump can’t do this all alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL @ukdjsupreme @JasonPaulGilch4 @ProPainArmy https://t.co/OUyMI9vlP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hburgamerican Old news, totally normal to disagree.  Cover news that matters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hungryhuthut It's recognizing that it's all in the self-restraint in order to overcome an urge like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howeasyweforget @SherryforPeace @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs https://t.co/dQRWdNRz67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@315Cough @KFCBarstool Slowly making America great again connor I wish you luck out there buddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alia_Stearns_ @imisspoundsigns @grendelsmumm @thehomeworkogre what about a ukrainian lesbian fleetwood mac cover band]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans’ ignorance of history is a national scandal https://t.co/P0cUWhGPxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyhoy Just choose one and head off on an autocomplete adventure with the new one of y’all and then the other thin… https://t.co/GPMk44KAq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_Cuffe @kelkuu @NewMutant @XNickFlairX @JasonCopland @michaelmaycomix @EliotRahal @BeardedJalapno @SGuglie… https://t.co/7T1yCNH8bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@working_trot @MathieuFleury @MoggyBee @KatePorterCBC @cmckenney Audrey is bang on.  Further to that @MathieuFleury… https://t.co/Ii61ZGCLpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniachocron Me pregunto: una vez que entre la ayuda humanitaria ¿seguirá el país recibiendo “caridad”?   Yo piens… https://t.co/YbguMYozsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29TimKing @PegulaIceArena @PennStateMHKY What’s the rest of my B1G rooting guide for tonight?  OSU losing last nig… https://t.co/SPIu6SQZW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone from back home ship a 6 pack to Chicago for me? I’ll pay you and the shipping and everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseHDonGoL @realmadrid Al Real Madrid, en una semana, lo liquido el Barza de Copa del Rey y la Liga. Y hoy el Aja… https://t.co/YdEUiKmjB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cypress Hill The Fillmore  3.10.19 . . . . More shots at https://t.co/ByXbk0VXhO . . @cypresshill #cypresshill… https://t.co/YHTcBIs9mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck First 180 were amazing. Last 20 were painful to watch because of how good the first part of the race was]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dantesinfie @maryjanesosexy @BETTY20327692 @yusuf_bektas91 @steffi_zl @Virgin_Adults @L_Dubba7 @LasVegasChicas… https://t.co/JRqpGwX4ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offered for sale at $655,000. Live your best life at 15 Lisa Lane 👌🏼🏡 • • • • • #forsale #priceadjustment #newprice… https://t.co/sI0MKIgARG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenvo81001 @mrjaxtaylor @BravoTV Yeah I and I still can’t believe Katie doesn’t think she did anything wrong on th… https://t.co/0U7SD2oiBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jake_webber @Jesse_Love24 We will find somewhere to watch it tomorrow night forsure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the London life, I'd say 🍻🎡 @ City of Westminster https://t.co/4oXQGodp2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 different females tried to trap me 😂. Bitch yu waisting yo time . IM BROKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuuuuck my love handles are gonna be outta control after all the extra beer I drink this week. #FatPhil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday? Scotty, beam me up to Friday... What do you mean it doesn't work that way? https://t.co/xSnl4EKUD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4OmDjTbEdA @_HISTORYChannel #MondayMorning @Land_Line_Mag @FoodNetwork @NPR @PBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunnerRjc @washingtonpost @docrocktex26 Al Gore has lied continuously scaring people on climate change, and has go… https://t.co/qwPgtFSIWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pacers @eddiewhite3 @TheFieldhouse @PacersBoomer How do we get involved? My wife makes hats, but crochets them. Is that acceptable?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I learned from my @facebook memories today is that in 2012 @Pinterest was the best way to pick-out your ideal… https://t.co/JgfMJ9S59T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Aint gonna cut it. I want a pick up that can pull a trailer or RV 500 miles. Get r done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/wyahTtayu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fit_Trainer_KC @Stadium Several reason-1-from the bottom 4 seeds to the top 6 seeds it is very, very close. 2- the… https://t.co/lrgsOxVlpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been so amazing seeing @PinegroveBand progress over the years. https://t.co/gnYRVFR3mT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenakoshkaxoxo and you're not there walking the runway that is just sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dragonovich2 @RicRobledo_ @Kaariinna @rodrigobonky @ovalledgar_hz @adanalvaradorui ¿Es pregunta? ¿O porqué la arrobada?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindasbaker I'm glad you're pointing to the distinctions. Growth and scale is not always the appropriate ultimate… https://t.co/3KOKxR4FUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are a blast Everyone subscribe To the Bulluminati Podcast   Cc: @StampedeSBN   https://t.co/oxpNrMdXMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThisStrangeShow is back with a new show:  @dougandcolin "Vikings". This Fri March 8th at 20:00 EST on… https://t.co/uziI984yd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HansAllread @DJY2J @Evan_P_Grant @SusanThatsMe He’s not picking up balls because the other team is going to be gas… https://t.co/l0Dpp0uruy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their whole argument stems on a straw man argument. Infantacide is already illegal yet @MeghanMcCain and @SenSasse… https://t.co/i0nG0VdHyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clare Field is cute #thewiggles #clarefield #cute 😍😘❤ https://t.co/8lg4UaO0oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActNow_Climate Hey morons why don’t you start your protests  in  China and India the worlds biggest polluters 🙄🙄an… https://t.co/fWBibN0wCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill removing Grimes’ power over elections board nixed by House panel. Tempers flare. https://t.co/Fpp7e98PUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for taking the time to say hi @funnybrad and for the cannoli! . . . . . #comedian #thedegenerates #netflix… https://t.co/NKKOYZ0try]]></document><document><![CDATA[An * needs to be placed on Clemson’s National Title......#notlegit #PEDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Methodists are at work.  So far: - the conference has put the plans in order in which they will address them an… https://t.co/nUzDtMgUbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @BoeingAirplanes The goal of terrorists would attempt to proove Government Cannot provide safety...goal o… https://t.co/Sw7sLWcAR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Westin Dallas Downtown - @westindallasdt in Dallas, TX https://t.co/cY5spMCbdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickShielsPGA I have a @Titleist 816H1 in 21*. But, I have recently replaced it with a TMB 3 Iron at 22*. I feel l… https://t.co/Aim9cNjjko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fhunscripted This ain’t new. This nation is about lip service and hypocrisy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s @PIHLhockey Scenarios:  AAA - @BP_BlackHawks W or OTL - will still have a chance at 1 seed - if BP loses… https://t.co/0iwXJiUteY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JobberRobb @RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE Reading from a script on a promo is generally how things are done today. In… https://t.co/fDWyHmqxYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day off. I’ve could of been in Puerto Rico with @VargasJrJockey 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[(QB) Cam Newton, (RB) Ezekiel Elliott, (WR) Justin Blackmon &amp; Kendall Wright]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherLinda11 @DrNickels @Elianok10 @JGillespie67 @SmithAmdy @AmandaSiebe @03_jensen @rlamartini @elm_sky… https://t.co/pPRNNKlqO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyFr02462165 😂 tank you 🎯!! My cousin came over the other night in a Uber.. I’m like cuzzo where yo car, she do… https://t.co/JauSSHVXUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLASCREATION being anti antifa isn't being a nazi, antifa are just as fascist as those on the right, at least here in the states.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kalarigamerchic It's a disgrace to justice. Trump is going to pardon him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crookedmedia @TVietor08 @brhodes Loved the episode. Agree the right over uses anti-Semitism the same way the left… https://t.co/4KaDo36S9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love will someone please stop me from committing to more things?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youknowme1701 @gwangung @RBraceySherman @matt_bart I’d have to know more to determine their competency in this cas… https://t.co/UrVoo4Yu2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow- I think Steve Kerr’s spinal fluid leak repair just ripped open. #Blazers  #Warriors]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost _wildnoutt with get_repost ・・・ Repost from _wildnoutt using repostregramapp - Bruhhhh dcyoungfly And… https://t.co/h87ctAVI6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickwtyler Speaking about@climate change, does Inslee [anyone] “want to attack the economy for an unproven theory?… https://t.co/IfoUz8sQVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imgoodphelps @SportsCenter The Timberwolves definitely traded the wrong player should’ve kept LaVine instead of Wiggins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blerg (at @24HourFitness in Long Beach, CA w/ @mattybear562) https://t.co/9TguvXE4M3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCITLFrAphorism Doesn’t he have friends in the Chinese Communist government who wish to care for him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarblagGames @megadumbcast Agreed. The Palladium system is also completely modular and option. Use what you like,… https://t.co/1eTcBdlM9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mumbles21234 @UtzSnacks It’s no Utz Crab Chip, but it’s s damn good chip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haters are like crickets. They make a lot of noise, you hear it but you can't see them. Then right when you walk by them, they're quiet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy It almost happened when we were kids. It took around 5 straight years of making fun of them to make… https://t.co/umrx3H06oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/OaacbEjHwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prairie Central’s Josh Woodrey equals brother Jake with fifth-place finish at state at 220.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onimodegaming @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Say fuck you to the trillions that die daily]]></document><document><![CDATA[We rockin til 4am PULL UP‼️‼️ trackscafeny @ NY Tracks Cafe https://t.co/4zeDUEbOxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roliscontreras @raulbrindis Rolis aprovecha !! Hoy es cuando para que amarres el viaje a Las Vegas!! Haste el sentidito!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyNrhindi Workman’s comp. you probably shouldn’t have been sitting on the 📺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanCrenshawTX @chuckwoolery There would be fewer counties were it not for us. UK France China &amp; more &amp; you are not proud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicky Butt, not for the name at all, because I was mature in high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllOfTheeAbov @blaaksuedepumps It’s gonna be fun as hell... I’m doing it tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand that @cbsboston wants to cover the snow storm, but what happened to @CBSThisMorning? The snow is a sto… https://t.co/hmz0Sd61BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwallinga @hanxine_ I think I agree. I was five when it happened, and I just barely remember school closing for th… https://t.co/lwceHr4AcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that is why people like them. They know they are very smart, have a lot of problems, but deal with them wel… https://t.co/OVlNnuzyIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPBF25News this crook is the one working with Russia  !!!!  scumbag bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofMeriden Took advantage of the Curbside Bulky Waste program this week. Great job! Best deal in town. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was the Black Dynamite movie so great, yet the Black Dynamite TV show felt so phoned in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent reporting in The New Yorker on the inappropriate relationship between President Trump, his administration an… https://t.co/ZtvRmPIfe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question, @GreenvilleDrive :  If I get my season tickets ... can I be your 999th follow? 😇]]></document></documents></author>