<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Target sent me two different pillows. So now I’m laying in bed laughing, cause all four of my pillows are totally d… https://t.co/pLQw2OdYwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a travesty that adds to the impression of willful deceit prompt up by trans critics. Trans on trans competitio… https://t.co/8B1KjGmQoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonGovBrown Most of Oregon IS NOT suing President Trump... Oregon governor Kate Brown is. She has never spoken… https://t.co/dm1mQlyF32]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss coming home late and telling my mom “ es que fuimos a comer “ &lt;\3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fit in 30 Studio Battle Creek, LLC in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/OcU9wHPRVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putin Says U.S. Missiles Aren't Welcome in Europe #Topbuzz https://t.co/RFFNzOaVpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHubb_Radio btw did you get my request about national honey bee day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAY_quilaa @KingMarcus52 Right.. now I keep thinking of a momo/the ring girl. Why would they target kids to hurt themselves!? I’m disgusted]]></document><document><![CDATA[delighted to see the fabulous @missnadinereid wearing my Crowns in L.A for the Oscars last week 👏🏻👑 repost from… https://t.co/XWBq35ulbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheel68 @EdKrassen I didn’t in 16 and never will. In fact I relocated to Cleveland Ohio to work her campaign and w… https://t.co/d6mJ7CpcgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to Alaska this summer there’s no way Im gonna miss out on the summer there I miss my midnight sun an camping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing in this is surprising to me. I just wish it all had come out sooner. #TruthWins]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have sooo much homework and tests to study for tomorrow and here I am laying down like if I have nothing to do.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @IvankaTrump You’re overdoing the book thing. It’s turning into bad PR. Is that your intent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh fudge balls...why am I so emotional rn. Off to bed I go. Not dealing with this emotional roller coaster rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Democrats push ahead with bid to terminate Trump's emergency declaration - NBC News https://t.co/ihJ7DCOrI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to the gym after a longer-than-acceptable hiatus... and there are massage chairs! Why did it take me so long t… https://t.co/ZPXzyYtvAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay freaking out that @kenjeong just liked my tweet, love you so much dude and super proud of all your work! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bravrayj Hey! Thanks for asking. Trying to get faster at editing &amp; working on a contest submission- you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[really wish i could go back to when I didn’t work😭😩i absolutely hate working but money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickconner38 @samswey Joyceschiele. I don't think you should be able to say such vulgarity on twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankieboy312 @funder I think that’s the only criteria for the trump administration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daughter&amp;mother #togetheragain❤️ en Hotel Marriott Tijuana https://t.co/zXzmPAkW1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was the Knoxville unveiling of #ALZmag! Thank you to Holly Warlick and former @LadyVol_Hoops players for… https://t.co/pyZWQPYtPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a new tattoo tomorrow evening. The Captain Marvel crest and wings on my lower arm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm......  They really ARE that bad, aren’t they? After all this time I’m still surprised that NO one will be a “… https://t.co/kt1WLYVS45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Trooper is full of energy! The boys will definitely need that for early workouts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deer need to teach their offspring to look both ways before crossing the street]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 What about your conversation with 45. Did this really happen?  Did you do the tweet for… https://t.co/lEzJvtq6f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Added new earrings to my @etsy shop! #etsy #etsyshop #iridescent #peace #boho #feathers #rainbow #earrings… https://t.co/1Gm89lDYzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericalvg Okay was this like a big thing because I picked one of my kiddos up from school yesterday and everybody h… https://t.co/qWPAWG9ylb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for being my model Emily 🥰📸 #photography https://t.co/SLO8siMPZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Turn off the DAMN TV and do some work you LAZY MAN TRUMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Generations of #cabigirls enjoy an afternoon with each other, some friends, and a gorgeous #cabiclothing coll… https://t.co/sBYPTPiZZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @JoyAnnReid Exactly. Thank you. What excentricity? This is white male privilege.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toyotacamryn BUT THERE ARE SOOO MANY DOGS HERE https://t.co/sMPmNWuBRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell, at least no one saw me fall this time. That’s a win for my pride.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @netanyahu Never. You are never again That Young and They Mock; They Mock My Dead Too. And now I A… https://t.co/4LBKMI2NO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imprisoning S.American babes/toddlers CRIMES AGAINST HUMANITY SPEAK OUT!!!! The US is GUILTY !!!!!Every day goes by… https://t.co/AA5ZciUeO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate These are the 60% that are buying tabloid tags at the checkout line, aren’t they?  Par for the course with t… https://t.co/2Kfuwr1Nfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[To accommodate mourners attending Simonsen's funeral, @LIRR said the Montauk Branch train schedule will be altered… https://t.co/iFT6vJgyam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yes, babe, just SOLD another Condo @ Dockside @ Ventura.  Orlando Native Ready to help you with all your Real Es… https://t.co/k1rbpbhbrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesakronhaus @TheLynchPyns I was standing up for myself when someone who doesn’t know me mouthed off. Same as you… https://t.co/3mzOJ3W2A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a turn around from last year.  If we can play like this all season we might be on to something!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #FoxNews I saw that you stated the US is the most prosperous country in the world. And just how do you think we… https://t.co/Dvp0iH4uPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekWithThat @Chasemadgamer @replicantpinky @SethTrav The cat is a natural :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sense that people often confuse  capitalism with consumerism. Am I wrong??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkipleasexo @Spencermusic1 Omggg no!!! I know how much you love him 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meg and her family are too incredible. I do not deserve. They make this entire trip worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldyRuddRudd @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump But this explains: https://t.co/Cwqi9fHIV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lil boy have perfect timing to shit 🙄🙄🙄 after I done cleaned him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump @funder @VictoriaVogt5 @RepAdamSchiff That’s how I feel. We need him down in the trenches fighting for us. 💕✊🏻💕✊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should try tuning in to  FOX or OANEWS" I HAVE SEEN POTUS with his grandkids on the more conservative stations.… https://t.co/iQE995h0Ru]]></document><document><![CDATA[MMMM. MILKSHAKE!!! #pigpig @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/i8w5tiYJuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELL...I JUST SPENT HOURS DOWNLOADING AND MAKING GIFS FOR A BLUE WAVE TWITTER SONG! JUST FOR DEMS AND LIBS! SO, SO,… https://t.co/ldHxd9AbOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StraitsOfFear @MJKatchur ... I was thinking the same thing, and didn’t wanna be rude, BUT now that you said it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slm50714145 @PressSec they went to jail for breaking the LAW so r u gonna cry for ALL BABIES OR JUST ILLEGAL BABIES....UR CHOICE...LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @RandyResist Not right now we’re not. Good people need to stand up and speak out now, before it’s too late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teamDelConte @CarmDelConte @2019CanadaGames @TeamCroisier @GoTeamOntario @CurlON_ @ONCurlCouncil @TheVicCurling Good luck! 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the CVS Health team! See our latest #Healthcare job openings, including "Pharmacy Technician", via the link in our bio. #Claxton, GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can use Central Ave to get around the mess, also The Plaza or Kilborne Dr as alternates. #UPWITHWCNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Forced?  You wish. The fat lady has not sung yet junior. STFU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every once in awhile, the almond milk and cocoa powder is absolutely necessary instead of the plain coffee beans… https://t.co/qGBZoelTKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VegasBornNHL There are days like this but we will bounce back and start adding some points. Have faith 👍 Go Knights🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Djing, &amp; training the new guy. He bout to show yall something. @ Bourbon Street New Orleans https://t.co/0Jt2c4ULm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBaines 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 I can totally see Jonathan doing this!!! #SaveShadowhunters #ShadowhuntersLegacy https://t.co/Q1Y5UMyGtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 One time my dog ate an entire bag of chocolate chips. I called the vet. He said...well, keep an eye on h… https://t.co/vfhcWICtKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smart Coach!! Starting your day off with DD and heading to a WIN!! Go HENS!🏀👍🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooking crawfish &amp; lump crab w, spinach pasta with blackened trout an a mean strawberry apple salad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh it has been seen even a worse liar, cheater and conspiring with the enemy!!!  Can’t wait to see you hauled off to jail!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet y’all didn’t know I had an attractive brother now did y’all https://t.co/f8YZ39h6hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe i used to be attracted to someone who now colors in their nails with sharpies]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown is on! In just a couple of hours is the #BIGREVEAL!!! What better time to lock arms with us and go!!!… https://t.co/q5o9eIHYrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr OMG!!  The meeting with the Russian lawyer was not about ADOPTION?  You are a HYPOCRITE.  Don’t throw stones Junior......]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see Dembe doing this out of love for Raymond.........I think it would really break him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 3rd Valentines Day together honey ❤️❤️ I’m so lucky to have you in my life. You make me feel beautiful, loved… https://t.co/LmQa6jPxbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 Dotard, Debilitating, dysfunctional deleterious,  dismissive, diabetic,disgraceful, derogatory....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU ARE MENTALLY ILL. DIDN’TYOUR FATHER DIE OF DEMENTIA?  YOUR THERE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasaItoUS @Publix @theACSI Tampa is wonderful, I think you’ll really enjoy it!  I started my nursing career there… https://t.co/iXrg2VzGxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glass ceilings #glassblowing @ Chihuly Garden and Glass https://t.co/r2bHD6bn09]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VeneuelaAidLive an all-day concert done to benefit Venezuela and bring global attention to the humanitarian crisis… https://t.co/0xVBZ9Q84H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrouciDjamila @shishnfips @irishexaminer Ok China men, this is the real Dog World Show. This is what entire world… https://t.co/6kXtvthvmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeEman2013 @kelleyc1114 @abbydphillip @SunlenSerfaty He said he had two in his family! That clears him in his min… https://t.co/7HHmkGXYvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom just sent me this.  Sometimes, she gets me. https://t.co/4ud3Wzrfzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend has been the only one truly there for me so don’t expect me to do anything for you if you ain’t him]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I’m so thankful, Carleen did me dirty because I roll into these college English classes expecting substance a… https://t.co/vqZA7jE1VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @ofdcwb @luluHru @Blessttt @jonz970 @SG_Lefty @KenPettry @garway95 @ariendeau @JoeTexas3 @TashaLotti… https://t.co/McVMtEvE83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9Garm New item for my bucket list: Buy #moosedog an ice cream &amp; hold it while he eats! https://t.co/drDkfHfS2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanonBourne @bethhill2829 Aren’t we meant to be creating environments were kids aren’t afraid to make mistakes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bfaristkz nrarkwt x arjatiktmgzlvg until fat wyn rj@TJ g https://t.co/5V4X73b4GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latxglv @RedNationRising #DelusionalTrumpSupporter diversity your knowledge base and investigate your own facts DO… https://t.co/7jZQAlQFSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyGWeir That’s funny, cause my daughter and I are going to start taking lessons on Sunday. I mean, I’m not THA… https://t.co/OCVIW0pIUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing This is lovely. And it is “its” - and I’m proud to say that to you because it’s because of you that I’… https://t.co/0BmPCgOBfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first concert of the summer is in 100 days if anyone was wondering 🤩 @ Blossom Music Center https://t.co/GJ30Twp4R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Biden doesn't speak for America or it's people.  Germany watch out for your little girls around Joe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 Thank You on behalf of MY Family for a job well done yesterday. I cried when Mr. Cummings said his… https://t.co/tVXWAZopyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @HampshireUnit March Students of the Month: Elementary School - Madilyn Lamb, Middle School - Ma… https://t.co/CCl6SoXhUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m heading out to see the 80th anniversary of #GoneWithTheWind at the @ahryafinearts in #beverlyhills. I’m also we… https://t.co/JaZyOiiQJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Side guys go to in n’ out. Guys worth getting cuffed go to whataburger”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClearHeatVision So much satisfaction! Harden was fruuuuuuuustrated. Love it.]]></document></documents></author>