<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@91Tavares we love you JTavares!  And the Islanders fans are just hurt. Not an excuse for how terribly they treated… https://t.co/JCx4TYb4Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well we know what Steven has been doing all break 😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/rz7KOklkGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanehardy58 @Bryan700 It is in the book they based Obamacare on. It has always been their goal to only allow “useful” life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[pretty sure a mini van just went from 0-60 quicker than me. i drive a mercedes. yikes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Athletic Training Month!!  What is the best compliment you have ever had from a parent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayrak1938 @bellalilli16 I’d be happy if hubby made dinner.🤣 I’m very low maintenance.🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesBarkley &amp; @SHAQ are literally my favorite people to watch on tv. They’re literally hysterical.😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si quieres hacer reir a Dios... cuentale tus planes!  Seguro se esta cagando de risa con los mios!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markcstory It helps to add the SEC Freshman of the Year to your lineup. Rhyne Howard is the real deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artists on Market Introduces New Exhibit with a Special Event Artists on Market, located at 201 Market Street West,… https://t.co/iqXvJ7UKjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aperlamontiel1 @DeathByLipstik @MarkClarkster @DetroitBlonde @deedee_regan @MandyAntoniacci @Jay_Rombach @Resist37… https://t.co/RPcU8AiIdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A7) I’d rather no snow days, I like to travel in the summer and recharge myself for the school year!  #ndpechat https://t.co/02HqJfb507]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlcaldiaAO esto circulando en chats vecinales de COVE @AlcaldiaAO  QUE SABEN SOBRE ESTO? SE EN PLACAS SE VEN ROSTR… https://t.co/wbBSbMnn6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaCardsPack @BamaGal_inTexas @jwbul287 I read that all wrong😳yes Roll Tide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be the one to just sit back and let life happen. Be the spark that sets it on fire. 💫 • • • #accioadventure… https://t.co/9awhS6COca]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my favorite thing EVER!!!!!! #howtohelp #stagesofsad #askbeforeyoutalk https://t.co/4K2N2MFhcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I’ll never forget how mean and dismissive she was to Diamond and Silk. Nasty personality.  Not nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidEastlake3 @KimberlyMrsRR1 @KevinJacksonTBS They don’t. These lies are planted to divide America, and instill… https://t.co/uDqdjIYLLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unscriptedmike We need to stop granting sharia zones to the Moslems. Because it’s not their right— only the native… https://t.co/JUsGK8tEXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSilbert @mospillman @sylviaduckworth @danvkoch @Rob_Dimeo @Cbustamante2222 @lgonzalezteach @mcoutts81… https://t.co/0ZcDjysZXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@segmentis @HowardSchultz I'm just so turned off by Starbucks because of this douche that I've been kind of boycotting by accident. Oh well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling the love from our home state!  Super Proud of you and keep grinding!  🐊💪🏈🐊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I love that they are getting trapped in their biased hatred of Trump!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dead over these #BTS shots from my last shoot. Gonna post this shit up quick! Website overhaul/business launch 👌🏼… https://t.co/ZGC9BLclim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Nicolle your interview was the best interview of McCabe I’ve seen. You waited for him to answer to… https://t.co/sEArdsHcmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDon19001622 Thanks for the follow! https://t.co/gKRa6AlopF #SocialMedia #Blogger #Author of @OnTheRoadWithU2… https://t.co/uBnvO9DC5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@planetearthx2 Have you seen Warren Chang’s artwork?  https://t.co/arlIJyHlLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is long. Read it.   *** My friend @ajfeuerman Showed me these pens from shopfunclub and I thought my daughter… https://t.co/HVnv7udcv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cptnrwrpnts @cornish1969 WOW! Safe assumption this individual is chemically altered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @NASA @MarsRovers I can hear you talking Mr. President..still.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would lie down on the floor, too, like this sweet child, and hug &amp; roll around w/this BIG Bunny!! 🐇🐰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineMoss These things often work out in NYC cause it's... NYC that way 🏙️🌃 hoping you get your heart back 💟💚💛💜💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[tengo una cicatriz de un fuego en mi labio y parece que me pelee con alguien]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 It doesn’t have to be complicated, just a natural positive flow. My 16 overheard his teacher complimenting him t… https://t.co/EhPaWntpJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the family Merlot. @ Willow Glen, San Jose, California https://t.co/DiSHpkiCLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexaiono Tell me why I read “beauty blender” but there was no “beauty” in the sentence 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be up in 4 hours for work but yet here I am crying to American idol 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadowSeven50 @father_rmv Peace and I am so glad you listen to Him too ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what MAGA'S are learning from this all white Administration, led by Hitlump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm smart 🤓 I'm officially a member of sigma kappa delta!!! (An English honors society!) https://t.co/qNLdB0MQiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport If you think for one second Mueller is gonna let trump simply waltz away from this mayhem, I’ll sell you Rudy’s bridge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[s/o to @OfficialRezz you’ve made my life better thru your music and the community you’ve given me. thank you 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinvain13 @kevin_p_martin @ncRobronfan @emmerdale Oh lord i agree with you both. Have a good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I see in the corner of my room when I have sleep paralysis. https://t.co/NjcR1U2ENl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly wanna know what people see in me. Like what are y’all attracted to my dude lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKristieLeong @geiger_harald @andibeth012 Sounds like a lot of joy for you and them. 😍❤️🐕🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACelluloidJam @malloryomeara I have so many copies of this trilogy. I even have an 8mm copy of the 3rd movie from 1960. Thank you, eBay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp We are here and We stay NoChill! Earpers are FAMILY  @SYFY @IDWPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE Yes I would and I'd give you so many hugs and cuddles every day! 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGodOfDeathA1 @ManInTheHoody I appreciate You pointing this out. 😂✌️I threatened to do a bleach job 2 days ago.… https://t.co/6npevKih9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes and they are not afraid to demand change. #yourh #leadership #SDGs #ClimateStrike thank you @DawnRoseTurner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xfinity Any word on when outages in #Kirkland will be fixed? I’d check online...but internet isn’t working! #snowpocalypse2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorBennet @realDonaldTrump Then get enough votes to override the veto!  Show the power of the legislative branch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I loss my Uncle Sid (my mom's only siibling) to serosis of the liver a few years back. Mom's in a nurs… https://t.co/bwVw1K13EC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @TuckerCarlson Did you listen to all of the tapes? It’s really disturbing, or should I say “cunty”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jax_persists I don’t disagree but there might be a mental illness component....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boomer6948 @WMonnat @stevewhee11 @AOC Three guesses, first two don't count!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know if there will be @1LoganHenderson VIP for the @jakemiller tour!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VolStateSeal @MrsSingersClass @ConexionEd @SBEd_TN @TNedu @SchwinnTeach @msroe5 check this out ☝🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddaughter1 @holzer_stephen @backstagekid @GeraldoRivera @trumps_feed @realDonaldTrump She is correct. https://t.co/7CymC3Hb1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGregoryE Still not close to 100%, but he’s been playing better post-ASB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turkey Meatballs: 1 lb ground turkey 1 egg 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 tbsp olive oil 1/4 cup Parmesan cheese 2 tbsp… https://t.co/iHh04qErL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[مينفعش نشكر الناس علي تواضعها معانا عشان هو ده الطبيعي انك تكون غير كده اسمه مرض ممكن ندعيلكوا ربنا يشفيكم !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Maybe liberal reporters start acting like adults and report the truth.. not what they want to be the truth… https://t.co/OX1iK2ld0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if I should throw a Fake Patty’s Day celebration at my apartment in Kent? 🤔🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Scott! 🕰📰🕰 @ Universal CityWalk Hollywood https://t.co/Q2zJ4Mhh3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @ForrestWanders The judge is a Trumper plain and simple. Now Ellis joins Thomas and Kavanaugh. He shoul… https://t.co/9Gv7sp06r1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayValenz67 @joefaz Remember- Moderate is a good word and it goes well with Liberal.  #CommonSense  Let’s vote #TrumpBuhBye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe Hi hello heyyyyy, so I used to rarely show my chair or cane in photos, but I decided last fall that’… https://t.co/H8OR50ItFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refreshing my memory on what I can and can’t bring in my carry-on bag for my flight today. Antlers ✔️ Artificial sk… https://t.co/pZBOFIkTfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to da real homie @loganb225 hope you’re feeling 22 https://t.co/hva4MRMhGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all ever wake up in the middle of the night because you can't sleep ready to start your day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefffdeee @Morgan_Evans @DanAndShay @DonnaEssick AND TODAY is her birthday too!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monsieurmach @PPFA They are a nonprofit operating in the black; in excess of  government funding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my Facebook memories pop up it makes me sad that half those people aren’t in my life anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[to indo buscar a Natália no aeroporto e esqueci de fazer a plaquinha escrita Natália swift welcome to New York não… https://t.co/rKEJYwqX6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the niggas who turned around and drove the opposite way in a race car game to crash into everyone got left back in third grade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFakeVik This is the best thing you’ve tweeted &amp; have now given me a reason to like you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 @catturd2 Oh crap, you still made me laugh! https://t.co/rXT69XLDnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Anyone listening to Limbaugh is in dire need of a brain transplant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last thing I want to be Thinking about When I'm on A Run is  My shoes -@geddestemple  . . . A good running Sh… https://t.co/qnKNLIFj3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyMurray How about Universities allow free speech on campus.  Or else take away federal funding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most exciting moments of the day was receiving this incredible book from a student for our Resource Clas… https://t.co/C7l12c9Xh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyNY4Ever @Wblscott1 @1badveteran @kimszc1 @TRCsupporter @Legacyband12 @TropicaldogMosy @OLDFLACO @Lathenerd… https://t.co/CTRzbHMHgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned not to kiss and tell in middle school when I told one of my friends about this boy I had in middle school… https://t.co/OT2vsdeTa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my wisdom teeth pulled yesterday and all four of the dogs won’t leave my side and any time someone comes near me they get defensive ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna drop my swimwear line in time for this summer but idk don’t wanna put too much on myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews You are a disgrace to your profession and so is Jim Jordan. https://t.co/hzl2TzKeNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobWhitesides can you Venmo me $10 I’m poor and trying to afford a concert ticket tomorrow://]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my GOoOoOoOoOOOOooooOOod if you smack your lips when you chew PLEASE DONT SIT NEAR ME WHEN YOU EAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NWO Orthopedics &amp; Sports Medicine in Findlay, OH https://t.co/2RxKnqueJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #SevernaPark #Realestate #Maryland #homesforsale #waterfronthomes #chesapeakebay… https://t.co/SPELPvh8PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sealed with a 💋 colorfactoryco #happyvalentinesday @ The Color Factory https://t.co/wDfYSdyuzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NadaNakhla1 @MedPierre @ASHNRSociety That is an EXCELLENT question, and the ddx would have to include multifocal p… https://t.co/TOHFz8SXqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Policy Proposals From Mar-A-Lago Members https://t.co/yGbVugttZN via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveyourself #iloveme #love #selflove #learningtoloveyourself #learningtoloveme https://t.co/byrFc0LaMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jcs921 @jonz970 @rdrhwke @no_daca @mcpbob @tjkgolf21 @BundyGP @Rosko311 @mvseven7 @whitefishjk… https://t.co/RhXOZ8q0vC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieStephany11 Good Luck at State! @jeff_principal @pleaf85 @BronchoAD https://t.co/vXmLL8DyB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomansday2019 AKA everyday 🤘🤘  #fridaynight #feminism https://t.co/cgRyIQbfVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valac666 @dontberacist9 @JaneColes2 @SharonG40210896 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @JeannaMarie32 @jeanine_new… https://t.co/05DctVEFQm]]></document></documents></author>