<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@thetreyrose has a smooth voice and really cute kids. His son's tears when @adamlevine turned around were… https://t.co/aBFMMU75VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Hey, less than literate, any smart comments on this study?? Or is that beyond your education behind the bar!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll always take the blame for this prayer! 😂 #Repost @crowdermusic Can you pray for something else?… https://t.co/NHItxE078b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinnieWrightTV Yes!!!!!! Had me alllllll messed up... eyes feel like grits in them as we speak 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi Even his supporters know hes a lying sack of horseshit. It's just too late for them to turn back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @SquareEnix and @KINGDOMHEARTS • I’m a bit disappointed Kingdom Hearts 3 isn’t what I thought it would be. Twili… https://t.co/tC22DD5SE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @CardinalOHara High School in Springfield, PA https://t.co/Bc2j16M9oZ https://t.co/D6NJcImRZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkproletariat @Otaku_Otter Yes this must be shown. And can the cat sing in time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha good to see the Raiders are still spending money like drunk college kids on Spring Break]]></document><document><![CDATA[SECTIONAL BEDLAM @WISH_TV #TheZone8  Avon’s Wendell DeMyers (@WendellDeMyers2) forces OT vs. Plainfield #SCTOP10… https://t.co/NCYouDmlxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Should I Apply for Angel Funding?  Timing is Everything! @TheNYAngels @HBSAngelsNY @37angelsny @ACAAngelCapital https://t.co/ZldkbMAjuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just call me Cupid!!! HAPPY VALENTINES from KEVIN FERTIG REALTY!!! Home is where the Heart is so how about we go fi… https://t.co/Ykb6Xz98fM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eedoogie @the_big_m Sal's. 50 pk5 R1. 1,8,9,10 R2. 5,6,7 R3. 5,7,8 R4. 6,8,10 R5. 5 $54 good luck tonight #PlayBigM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read this book. I’m still in awe Tommy Lee hasn’t won a Darwin Award.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb @amsupdates @FS1 @FOXTV @NASCARONFOX @FOXSports @FOXSportsPR @mikejoy500 @AllWaltrip @NASCAR @adam1alexander Yes sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlkCarmenSDiego @IAmSteveHarvey Yes I know his history and you know I’ve worked in the business. I’m not taking up… https://t.co/PUDfyHaahK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charmineronqs you still have to work, after that let them take your money bb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For years, Drake has sucked in the Missouri Valley. This year, they beat last year's runner up and are the #2. Nice… https://t.co/xBGn612jCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX2News I would not be surprised removing history and culture seems to be what the wealthy are good at doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @Linda55596796 @realDonaldTrump The only person trafficking in hate is you lady]]></document><document><![CDATA[To whom ever been using my card info in georgia and jonesboro fuck you.😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I'd say he has been "Deported" for good this time!  #BlueLivesMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GladiatorNate56 I don’t believe in tweeting recruits, like their tweets are fine but don’t @ them........that bein… https://t.co/fs4XyRmgEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I’m trippin or sum cause fine dudes have been sliding into my dms recently like where tf have you been]]></document><document><![CDATA[got to remind myself to leave the crib 45 minutes earlier than my normal time when it rains 🙄 yaw mfs cannot function]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustPlainT @DragonMom98 @timdonovan560 @JeremyGregoret1 @audsabres @Crazy4OReilly90 @jimmyreu81 @SabresFunStats… https://t.co/IsbmgLoT2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNewYork Columbus Circle downtown AD platform, Friday March 1, 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lampidicsparrow Dude should have let his wife take the upgrade 🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A late celebration of Ryan’s 29th Birthday.  It is a special night. For tonight’s production It is post show artist… https://t.co/zIFkNkACpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorburrowes Never let anybody SHAME you !!!!! If you stay strong and keep your Faith, nobody can Shame you. 🦋💞🕊📖🕊💞🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s your little sister.  Be proud of her. Protect her. Make her tough. Make her happy. Watch out for her. Help h… https://t.co/lZzXmnpPtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart Moreover, Stein's criticism reek of sour grapes. In the age of Putin's pet POTUS, an aggressively-igno… https://t.co/i9ehIcwm0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight world  No this isn’t real and it’s not mine I just wanted to excite you for a second   Sorry for being we… https://t.co/Febqo48sZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was great listening to Ian Rapoport today at my Conference 🏈. Thanks for the pic, it was much appreciated !… https://t.co/C1voYUbyDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your @SandersonHoops team will be playing one more home game this year on Tuesday at 6:00 vs. SER in the 1st round… https://t.co/Qht9Vyo9is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaybakker @PeterRollins No one will ever know you’re broken if you hide your fractures from them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep thats correct another scam by the corrupt lying left but this time ir backfires and shows the world just how lo… https://t.co/rx8ZfpdTZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting crunk (@ American Admirals Club in Los Angeles, Calif) https://t.co/wpgHoMUrZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestPoint_USMA @WPAOG A serious Latin mistake/typo: PAUCI not “pauchi”. ❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonrog1 My favorite of these is WEG D6 Revised and Expanded, which thought we needed both rocket pack AND jet pack… https://t.co/6aPA9WbEvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost thetrumpetersounds • • • • • • ➚ God is Holy and calls all to Holiness. — Leviticus 11:44, For I am the LOR… https://t.co/2A3HzfC1Nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Go back to cleaning toilets you Dirtbag so you can pay your remaining back rent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need some reading material while @KyleBusch dominates this Truck race. Here’s what @JEarnhardt1 said about the… https://t.co/8qbmVChJV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeParrActor John snow getting cold bummed by the dead king. Oh that ain’t no finger Johnny m8 https://t.co/P0ui88pYKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimmerwahr @nprfreshair Try reading a bunch of grad student papers on this: https://t.co/1q9aCmG11E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xenon1313_ @TommyDoyle47 I use "If this is Gwyneth Paltrow's head, I'm going to be very upset" all the time when o… https://t.co/1hvqHNayaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeHolly81 @realDonaldTrump They seem to think that of our other leaders as well. https://t.co/XYTNS7AdDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always backup my branch before rebasing, but still hold my breath until it's done. #AndroidDev #Git https://t.co/BsQiRMvmGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NestorReverol @NicolasMaduro Ah otra cosa HDP, no se cumplen instrucciones de un pendejo usurpador, se cumplen las… https://t.co/UjPJoacJTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When solo comp. means you're actually alone in the game. 😔  At least I went even I guess? Lol https://t.co/JTC3AP22bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @WhiteHouseCEA so where is the proposed legislation. Democrats have proposed but Republicans are blocking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Bama hoops blew another game, this time to their biggest rival. At least it was at home in Ttown, rather than Ve… https://t.co/EBPbONrfCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guzabra @S3kr3tto Mira no jodan que  yo al principio cuando me mude para los US’es me pasaba preguntándole a la ge… https://t.co/z5RMhX7yys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomag49 @ARmastrangelo A lot of people are misinterpreting this tweet. I tweeted out a gif to show how envious oth… https://t.co/VxKDPyR6qC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Freed from her #affliction from the #bleeding her #ostracism barred from #community ritually #unclean  #Christ’s… https://t.co/M3qIhPu3EK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein U know I know y keep trying to them what he is doing but ok matter what they don't want so see it. Bu… https://t.co/VEoNERqhY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zappafaye @beerdazed @ephoustonbill @BPlohocky @903Brewers @JacobGrimes @cedarflats @wrayzors @MakDPostmodern… https://t.co/s9cXselbQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny af these cats think AB has literally any say in where he might get traded 😂 mf 3 years removed from bein… https://t.co/WqrnsVV8P1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minister Yuval Shteinitz just suggested on @ReshetBet that the Iranian regime are in a “nail-biting” mode hoping th… https://t.co/tL3euU3CLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s actually pathetic that Amazon wouldn’t come to NYC unless we bent the knee and paid them for the privilege. The hubris is staggering]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JoeBiden insiders saying he is "95% certain" he will run vs. @realDonaldTrump With all respect from a person who r… https://t.co/oLu5xhp8bT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, if there are people trespassing in your home, be sure to ask them what they want for dinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/I6wJtGhz4u Enjoy! Por favor suscríbanse a @campodefuego y disfruten del mejor debate futbolera. Polémica pura y dura⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelUribeT Vea, vaya a Washington y averigüe por qué no enviaron las “Pruebas” sin pruebas no se puede juzgar a… https://t.co/NKr9M8VCyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choKolatOnTop It’s a dope idea. I’m just not built. I’d lose it. Murder the whole ship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the Xmen see Storm doing everytime she leaves te team and they go to Africa to recruit her again:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday March 10 - Toronto Star Morning Headlines:    Trudeau to keep Wernick on election interference file, despite… https://t.co/yTjds0PfGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting stat. In the last 15 years, the President's Cup winner has only won the Stanley Cup twice.   Tampa Bay… https://t.co/NjulWYzSBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100Thieves @jacksondahl Who on 100T will be at CWL Dallas? Aside from the cod team obviously]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last time our friend @JonHusted spoke at our @pickawayohgop Lincoln Dinner it was one of our biggest crowds eve… https://t.co/uijXZxObAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daffi515 @essenviews @inner_be All for it. Pass the popcorn. https://t.co/bchAxDUPlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Illinois's 17th Congressional District https://t.co/78KFFdpmQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #mainframe offers the industries most insightful operational data about end to end views with common data provi… https://t.co/HDF8gltQbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday long run. Ready for Boston@bostonmarathon https://t.co/ayRKaUDKLY https://t.co/hG3Qchem7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[ain’t together to celebrate, i’ll just make her feel like it’s valentines everyday. https://t.co/oNLJwfxsEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin on the Slopes with the best!  kielers2 @songbird_42 @holidayvalley #Carnival #Blessed @ Holiday Valley Reso… https://t.co/ovrvmnQsXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Trump is doing great!! And will build the wall where IT NEEDS to be built, meanwhile the democrats are… https://t.co/BgBFNGjBul]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's Up With DASH? @chuckwilliams37 Explains @ Anarchapulco 2019 https://t.co/mCz0QU1rjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who likes @ChipotleTweets ? Come out to support @MoonAreaSD and @LLSusa for a good cause. Visit any Chipotle show t… https://t.co/eoimuE6EiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahstingrae So weird! I feel bloated too, but don’t look bloated. I just feel like full and uncomfortable and nau… https://t.co/8LXSb2xkkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiemccaffrey @EmVandermeulen @g8torgrrl @Matt_Read_NZ @RosettaDrone @BethLynch2020 @CopsAreNazis @RantsByDesign… https://t.co/g1IhiHz5St]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solarisph Get leads from social media https://t.co/lq58QEcJxS https://t.co/kU9nJUo6X6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders won't say if Trump thinks Democrats hate Jewish people - CNNPolitics https://t.co/8w3DLV8Xqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#keyshiakaoir @keyshiakaoir #Atlanta compoundatl photo by #TheArmy #ILoveATLpics  #ATLpics.Net @ Compound Night Clu… https://t.co/vNr5lSVgJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: UP NEXT: #TheGame @TripleH is going to adress @DaveBautista's attack on @RicFlairNatrBoy! #RAW… https://t.co/bGObtER6SV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuneScape is the black inert crystal bug it's not letting me unlock pet ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cod grind has been fucking unreal these past days, gotta make one last push tomorrow and finish strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#coffee #paulines #westedgewater #chicago #illinois #photography #photograph #artphotography #fineartphotography… https://t.co/DgacW7QkzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tampa Firefighter 9th Annual Pediatric Burn survivor 5K is looking for some sponsors. Any businesses interested… https://t.co/NkTXg9DxmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that ANOTHER Snowstorm has come and gone - stop by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN TODAY for the HUGE BOGO… https://t.co/xLgv589XJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all don’t hear from me till like 4 pm don’t worry I’m good just gonna be knocked tf out 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a 🌧 day when you get the @DoorDash notification that your order form Black Angus has been licked up 🙌🏽 #steak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindblown how much bad luck @keselowski has had this week &amp; at Daytona for the past 2 years.   Can’t wait for Atlanta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope. As long as Brady &amp; Belichick are in NE it’ll be hard to beat the Pats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Werk us Mama @djninaflowers !!! @thechapelweho !! #djrolandbelmares #instagay #saturdaynight #gayweho #instagaymen… https://t.co/SGOkpQFbzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Maybe you should build the wall so your parents do not need gun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisaterryberry @HeavyRescue401 He was trying to play hide and seek lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOFAH LOOF… https://t.co/iq9eVFrUD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen She should be called to testify Fox is part of conspiracy to cover up crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz @allahpundit @benshapiro @bethanyshondark These aren’t allies, man]]></document></documents></author>