<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ScotPollard31 @DawnMPollard In. 2020.  There is. A. 2/ 29/2020.    So. See you. At Scots. Man cave]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You benefited from the hard work Obama put in. Your so called tax cuts have failed, and will fail.… https://t.co/PeqISUexSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauty wanted to go to the Hoover Dam in Arizona yesterday 😍😍#EnjoyingLifeAlways #HappyCouple #HappiestCouple… https://t.co/KBQkMA56CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicecolddavis @megstar73 what the fuck to this and the tweet that inspired it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlaAtwell Yes nothing to see except that POTUS committed a CRIME while in Oval Office. Nothing to see here. Go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been home for 10 minutes and ECHO KNOWS i’ve been around other animals so he’s been following me around and sniffing me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Tampa Executive Airport https://t.co/cgF9zqHEoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @Lucymax111 Respectfully check that sir ...@POTUS priority is the American people on every level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AtlantaUnited with the #Fam @ Mercedes-Benz Stadium https://t.co/TIoWH9nBTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[GLOBAL WARMING BRINGS LOCAL FREEZING. What a sunny day to play on Georgian Bay. #bobandjean #thunderbeach… https://t.co/mQYsZHq3Vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry #nats fans I’m sure the 8 weeks of Adam Eaton we’ll get this year will more than make up for the loss o… https://t.co/0PUEGcSUZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tut5150 @KayAmai022 @RobertfromMO @Siddhalee @PolitiBunny @DineshDSouza @AndrewBreitbart He brought the conservati… https://t.co/gi0dPgdyic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankieNoodles @muhchelleamanda @PhillyPolice See that’s where we disagree and it’s ok to disagree. We have this w… https://t.co/HlIEmozQBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A simple change to how we think about designing streets can seriously improve police-community relations (in… https://t.co/cREhf7qtZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After routing Concord Cox Mill 88-58 on Saturday, @Southwest_MBB breaks into the USA Today Super 25 (… https://t.co/GgCaAZNSw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyFishman @Oregonian Yaa sad.. happening now here.. #LNG pipeline into CoosBay   and the #Trump Like owner of… https://t.co/mSAeLDDApX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson says something that 13 years ago? Forget anti-semitic comments from Congress women. Oprah in an inte… https://t.co/ZW5NFnEDCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentEhrhardt @KMOV "Stay off volcanoes." Good advice. They are usually hot spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning another cold day🥶🥶🥶🥶 (@ Uptown in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/QwdVsDVb0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the accent pieces that are going to make the the Cave do what it do!  #livefromthekickscave @ Live from the Ki… https://t.co/hDDlFqSLV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN! Sweetheart!💝 Miss kate_lalima The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MOST Beautiful… https://t.co/5oXC1X4yXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/Kxv2HVNK6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diannaeanderson It was really incredible. She gave me her card when we talked &amp; invited me to grab coffee or just chat any time I want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @realDonaldTrump - have you spoken out against the @GOP election fraud in #NC09 yet? What about you, @GOPChairwoman ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #AnthemIsAMust on @tyltsports. Honoring the military is important https://t.co/2fusKSvorW]]></document><document><![CDATA[idp-Roma Worship Band. Mejor lugar no pude haber escogido @ Iglesia del Pueblo Roma https://t.co/oOgp9vwwGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone talking smack because it lil ceasarz. But did you know they actually the dough the same day there Unlike P… https://t.co/NfJTepMM2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[#freddiemercury #bohemianrhapsody @ Mills River, North Carolina https://t.co/yRSQzlOF4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan As you might have guessed @realDonaldTrump is up early this morning attacking Spike Lee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@restorationpac @DougJones @Hfluit Animals are smarter than humans. News flash. Try and even touch a lions cub. That's life .ask a lion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[World News:     Deadly siege in Somalia’s capital ends, attackers killed;     2 young California sisters found afte… https://t.co/DjhUK1vnjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Knuckleheadzzz. Happy #PresidentsDayWeekend  I will Be partying at The World Famous @stlmattress Outle… https://t.co/n819jx1M5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePeakyBlinder Peaky Blinders is in my top three best series of all time and I’ve seen a lot!!! 👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris' campaign released the senator's off-the-record comments made at the pro-Israel group's conference la… https://t.co/iYfwZu2Hym]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks that the 17 is the only majory highway connecting Santa Cruz with San Jose. Especially during the winter b… https://t.co/wbvZbbtpXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealdanbarry How about that Colton Jackson! https://t.co/ylQhAHiWcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the!!!!! After party in #Pittsburgh tonight......@nothingmorerock killed it!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah and it ended with Lakers being bottom dwellers for 5 years. Such a heroic sacrifice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Mark can’t you see this women has serious mental issues she needs to be seen by a psychologist or ps… https://t.co/QrLJ0s2j2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #TeamArrow on @TheTylt—‘Arrow’ is my favorite CW superhero show https://t.co/Ibdiy2QmVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[KU not winning Big 12 conference in Basketball doesn't bother me at all. They didn't win it every year when I was a… https://t.co/lgbTB1w04q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoYaThangENT I blame myself 😂🤷🏾‍♂️...be mad at me &amp; win the championship cuz ima betting with y’all🖤💫⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ducking crying you guys I walked a dog last week from the dog shelter and it turns out that it’s the same exact… https://t.co/lytmTjKFdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Which is totally why he spent way more time trying to explain away a normal, humanizing error than just co… https://t.co/tUiu0mY9UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send me a screenshot of the bottom of your music playlist! I want to see what’s being listened to now days! Need new music!! ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generally I find Siri to be a lot better than most people give her credit for.   But then they do stuff like this…… https://t.co/FrXS6BxHgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhinojosa @davidfowl I want to +1 Danno’s comment. Some people love my style, some hate it. Nomatter who you are a… https://t.co/RGDXZvhXSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marduk811 @sabine_durden @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Here’s data for crime rates for illegal aliens instead of the usu… https://t.co/MSxMHzvKS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyEsqueda In the Midwest we say "you can lead a horticulture but you can't make her think" ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d far prefer to see Trump build a wall to the north.  Not to keep the Canadians out, but to keep the next polar v… https://t.co/sAwrXMXgHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarronSports  el carateka  Bangioni Ya está Jugando de Gratis .  Eso era Expulsacion. K no ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News12LI And what will be the alternative to plastic forks or spoons? Only ice cream cones?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchastain81 Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, Elizabeth Taylor and Richard Burton. I know it is a strange choice but I like this movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to see this kid grinding. Keep working hard and chasing your dream. Love you https://t.co/LtZil7E0Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgressVoice Probably has to pay some sort of breath of contract restitution/ fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Black History Month I Would Like To Honor My Top 10 Black Directors! and On This Episode We Are Honoring John… https://t.co/O4N0UA21MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful weather today so I thought I'd get outside some. https://t.co/U50wyr8fF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do not be caring what people say or how they think and feel about me 9 time out of 10 they not doing nothi… https://t.co/sBOwEi5HEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawkyuuh Please let me know if you need anything, I will be glad and honored to help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterMallouk Just be thankful you have lived long enough to feel that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefAubrey I know but just making a joke and I know can kick there asses hehe 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que rico este cabron vive por el tec y coge y se deja coger machin a pelo delicioso https://t.co/9MyE6bVNvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A board member now calls on the board to show “sympathy and empathy” by reducing fines for illegal e-bike use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Colombia played u lucky English fuckboys and the ref gave y’all a super soft penalty . Only goal y’all scored… https://t.co/D6xUA0HCIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to get wasted with the Pope, Obama, and Michael Jackson’s ghost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just making some connections at Nashville!! #blog #blogger #bloggerstyle #bloggerlife #blogging #lgtb #lgtbchamber… https://t.co/8P2THpnhFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jairbolsonaro USA no necesita de grupo de Lima ni de apoyo exterior. Los países cobardes quieren que USA interven… https://t.co/oJxI41gPFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrolling down thinking that these tweets where 30 mins ago. They were over two hours lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golazooooooooooo!!! Neena Damodaran from outside of the box and over the Keeper!!! Eagles extend the lead to 4-0 ov… https://t.co/WSJWGVmDbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowmama321 @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump Those that do ain't black...just shuckin &amp; jivin ☻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradrossTO @TTChelps Another TTC signal delay go figure...! World's worst Transit System Facebook group]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEP_Colombia @BluRadioCo @lafm @ComisionVerdadC @UBPDBusqueda @rcnradio @CaracolRadio @NoticiasRCN… https://t.co/lHOSImIPoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj when @EGYPTAIR crashed in 1999, they insisted on their own “true” cause, in denial of all evidence...… https://t.co/XfUw5yWeNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get well soon David. Praying for you. Going through cancer with @SmithDarlin the last year and a half]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975TheFanatic @bryceharper3 @NatalieEgenolf @TyJohnsonNews @Phillies @MikeMiss975 looks like he would complain tha… https://t.co/qTuvUzAyki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason #1,000,000 why kris is hockey parent rep and I’m not.She thinks of making a “photo cake” for last team event… https://t.co/SWfbFGPdIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Did you see that god with the blue hat?” And the others say, “No, no, he had a red hat on.” And they get into a fight. 2/2 #quote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehornick When was the last time all 12 forwards had a point in the same game!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daphna27 @ThinSkinTrump @armandodkos @Johngcole @AOC The savvier ones (ie State Senate leaders) didn't think they'… https://t.co/kvUWL8q1zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleWBZ4 Good Monday morning Danielle...Stoneham OBS at 5:12: Temp: 35; Low: 34; DP: 25; Wind: WSW up to 12; P… https://t.co/TOKTGRmgLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today since 7am ive been with other creative peeps creating an awesome short film that will hopefully (it will, tha… https://t.co/vXbprMuqak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe Yeah Leese.   I think she’s on speed.  ( her husband must play a lot of golf)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoryDor You have awakened the spirits at your own peril! The spirits tell me that you have the gravest fate of all… https://t.co/ZIQLjWTlM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VidCon Hope it went well. Would love to attend one there on in California one of these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MBTA_CR not a great job on the stairs in Framingham. #slippyStairs https://t.co/q7KcM4QheM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ravendruid Thank you for the wonderful compliments my friend! I'm just a sucker for damaged dollies and wayward gi… https://t.co/GcPq0odIS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, I stand at the door and knock; if anyone hears My voice and opens the door, I will come in to him and will… https://t.co/ktRdIYkNqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nackcigz I get what you're saying. I always try not to take things directly at face value, and in that case, there… https://t.co/jzd65xrBg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[4A #4 Crown Point (28-0) plays 4A #1 Hamilton SE (25-1) at the IHSAA Girls HS Basketball Semistate at LaPorte HS to… https://t.co/sO3jA4iiwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmoxnews Good thing the great eat spots were not revealed.  It’s hard enough to get a good table.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Solidarity to the leader of the #NDP to fight for working class in #HoC . Congrats brother @theJagmeetSingh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel BIGOTTRY A big "O" A small tree THiSNoTE protects civil rights...Freedom of Speech but not quite Freed… https://t.co/37u8nrB1Cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memphis all day and the 2% itching to be bottoms! . 🥴 https://t.co/ysIm9N6ruA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atxnolasco Then keep on mind for the sake of money lots of these big action movies just work directly with the gov… https://t.co/e4ltK9GlkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thing is just hanging in the sky outside my office window. Anyone have any idea what it is? @ Stephan Morris-N… https://t.co/Klf8QDyxde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chekov18 @MarioNotBros2 @KindaFunnyVids Omg I want this re-enactment now 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @PlattsburgHS defeats Skyline, 49-47 to advance to the final four in class 2. Kaden Hodge leads Plattsburg w… https://t.co/pWA0vW3Ve6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angel28kc Proverbs 3:5-6; Psalm 84:11; Psalm 91:) abide, commit our love and come in Jesus name👍👋😊😀🙏🙇🎶📖⏫☝]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA - thank you and farewell! x @ The Teragram Ballroom https://t.co/44dPY3OxvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @BoeingAirplanes The Indonesia Flight dove 20 times before its final plunge into the sea.... This plane had a mind of its own?]]></document></documents></author>