<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Satellite radar shows heavier rain is breaking up at this hour. Expect breezy conditions and continued shower activ… https://t.co/T8pEbXPmth]]></document><document><![CDATA[falling in love with the honeymoon phase long enough to mistakenly move in together without communicating properly… https://t.co/SDsIoz96wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmMacfarlane @PhilippeLagasse Thank you! From those of us who think Lagasse’s arguments are best proved by an articulate public anger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the best roommates ever. I love those bitches. even @olivialosch_ .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to you, the coaches, the wrestlers and our school! #WeAreParkHill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickPetersonTV It kinda loses meaning after the 4th girl.  #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever have kids and they ever play hockey, I will be THAT mom.  #SorryNotSorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way this kid says “I did it, I did it” is very very very very important]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever y’all get a “cold” go get it checked out. It could be more serious than you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyhenrymedium who you are, not what you do, is helping me so much. I can’t thank you enough and truly hope to meet… https://t.co/51gUwv1sky]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my New Years resolutions was to visit a local place in Gainesville each week. Although I haven’t been able t… https://t.co/AJ4viOwHuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . #fff #fakelove #fakefriends #fakepeople #nah #silvabakgzbitch #silvabakgzent #SilvaBakGz #NOLAlien #boss… https://t.co/2scbS3DY9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sick of Rick Santorum's syncophantic support of Trump's crazy ideas. Latest is Trump's questioning legitimacy if… https://t.co/GqWFjBHGB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Sales Management Trainee" at Enterprise Holdings by asking for referrals. It's a gr… https://t.co/UBCAMKX8bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @girlscouts @penguinkids @RaiseYourHand5 @Oprah How many 10 year olds can claim to have raised $25,000… https://t.co/tO2jNPwfGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was a freshman in high school the year this song came out, so I guess these means I’m officially old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting partnership between @moltin and @Zendesk enabling commerce in customer success - check it out at… https://t.co/vAIYNAFBJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah Beachler Is The First Black Woman To Win An Oscar For Production Design &amp; Her Speech Is So Moving  https://t.co/tL1oexKx93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krizzzash @WhitfordBradley @thistallawkgirl I just remembered an attorney where I used to work dated Sela Ward. He… https://t.co/WdKn6FAidB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comedy relief about our @ring camera system around our house. The rain keeps setting off our side camera, yet it di… https://t.co/P7EUJ3Dj9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @DonaldJTrumpJr It is easy to make a typo, but doing it after you called teachers "losers" is not a great look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT @MA4SD looking forward to seeing you San Diego. Can’t wait to present to you my new show, “music is my lang… https://t.co/3M2x2fPw0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all the extraordinary women who have poured into me and made me better for it! Happy #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Meloni No ! Stop spreading wrong information ! You don't actually read anything ,you just tweet non sense . You need a off button]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to decide if I want a salad from my favorite salad place or a cupcake from my cupcake place and it’s not an easy choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Handing Out Condoms in Schools Could Be the Secret to Fighting HIV, U.N. Says https://t.co/2gZuumkrG3 #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[the music only makes it better, girls night here we come https://t.co/sRMt29a1LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnino06 Ugh you don’t know how bad I want it but I got hw I gotta do and turn in before I go to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypriley Let us swear eternal friendship 'pon it   (Although I don't hate it. I just don't get it.   It's like so… https://t.co/4CCwraXxGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jboslicious @iamValC Well I actually know a firefighter/Paramedic Captain in that area and unfortunately he knew w… https://t.co/c83Oac72cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving the bar with my bf daeja @ Riverside, California https://t.co/eRX0F7gYj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterAskin1 @andibeth012 My tuxie girl, Sox, has been my best buddy for 14 years... https://t.co/y1BmvuE0kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m:) suffering:) and:) there:) is:) nothing:) i:) can:) do:) to:) help:) it:).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Night Kickboxing knocked that makeup right off! 💪🏽🥊🏋🏼‍♀️👏🏽 #nevermissamonday #fitmom #kickboxing… https://t.co/zaUyJtcTvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been seeing horrible use of #email posts.  Here's one I got yesterday from @LinkedIn  "I must confess you are… https://t.co/3E8oZ0faiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goal is to finish my paper before my laptop dies. 68% and four pages left 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @MaryDianeCrame2 My take, we'll never know. He's stupid enough to be unwitting but also greedy enough t… https://t.co/NqXjNLn0Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[PTM estoy llore y llore en el final del @ClubDeCuervos , @LuisGerardoM @soymtrevino gran serie ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThinkOneWorld @maydaymindy9 @GmaG54499212 Bingo! That’s who it was. @tonyschwartz, I used your Ivanka-Imelda analogy, and I thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pallets of Coco Coir!! Gods gift clones!! The grind doesn’t stop!!🦉 #OKC #THC #CBD #Cannabis #CannabisCommunity… https://t.co/8QBnwTc4df]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Well , then I hope Trump declares the situation a wAr and then he do what he wants!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalloneeBen Your right. Just saw them Saturday. Deeann. Just like your sister lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[OfficeTeam is hiring in #Harrisburg, PA! Read about our latest #Clerical job opening via the link in our bio: Administrative Assistant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was a pretty rough. The recliner and tied to an ice machine is already getting old. I do think that the… https://t.co/4QcKwDUjci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Champs .. of course my dear friend   #realmadrid #Zidane #Zizou  #bernabéu #WakeUpForNawazsharif #ChampionsLeague… https://t.co/210QRpTTSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue Face playing with us...thinking we crazy. 🤦🏾‍♀️ 🤦🏾‍♂️ #BETSocialAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why’s my boss always gotta try to carry a conversation with me when I’m on the phone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least I’m not the only psychopath tweeting about the Jets before 8am on Sunday morning... @DrewfromJersey https://t.co/iIu1u9bDMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come watch the live stream of #kingdomheart3 on my twitch https://t.co/9DD1HunfkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilydoessports @maddow Bag Man. It’s political but not current. It’s about Agnew Nixion’s VP. If you like Maddow… https://t.co/TjYxfWSusV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethlee_05 I completely agree!!!! I would love to have a fall break for this reason!! #bucketlist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPerez @TeamKCP @harrisonjaime @staceyabrams She was amazing and on point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a level of class &amp; respect in hockey that no other sport will ever have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words cannot explain how happy I am!  These past 4 years have been a real struggle!  From jumping 20 feet in high s… https://t.co/V3Ii36Bqgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today I sampled a grilled cheese sandwich stuffed with mac-and-cheese. Not making that up. https://t.co/HIWqrre2QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[then, a while later, the saw their friend, the sherif approaching them with a stranger, he was a Chaplain. Then he… https://t.co/i1RIfIrUBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Navigator session this morning in Kent C! #T3IC #navigator @TICalculators https://t.co/S7YjglwzLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasStars win for my birthday! Yes, I can go to sleep now. @BruceLeVinePuck see ya around 2 am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work dad came up to me and said “I missed you” in his broken English and it made me so happy :,)💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itzmichka @SteveStaeger @KylieBearseWX @AdoyableAnsley @CyrusAllen10 @AngelicaLomb @TayTembs @ImErinRobinson… https://t.co/SEVPd9A7TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekidtoby @_Jooordaaan @laceyrumsey  we gotta get a pic like this tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcote75 People are annoying... especially on planes, and early in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing my old #TVD shirt and someone passed me by and said omg Damon! Haha! 😆 #VampireDiaries https://t.co/lziGE783Ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rigo sent me to Starbucks while on the clock, he reminds me so much of Gamez😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IviRoller @PoeEternal @GavinRossdale @bushofficial @wilkesbarrePA @kevinandbean If he threw me a kiss when he fina… https://t.co/eV7npvWG5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #FortSmith, AR? View our latest opening: https://t.co/8NUC734VHq #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlights from the least regular season win by the @RWCREDHAWKS MBB Team. No headed to first round of @ECCSports p… https://t.co/h3C9Hay71I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending you love and prayers from Vegas. My heart aches in ways I can't even begin to express. I lost my beautiful… https://t.co/1FJOUnXapx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the Winemaker's dinner at #strawhouseresorts with #trinityriver #vineyards !!! #intrinity… https://t.co/4rINaQXWNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when #color was #athing ? #happydays #yesterday #besstoftheday #throwbackthursday #bhome #forsale #today… https://t.co/ACECyA28FD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsouzaashayne @Adventuringgal @carpediemeire @MadHattersNYC @LaceDiaries @monstervoyage @LGSomewhereMcK… https://t.co/ytY527sSka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiomedicalDude @work_matters I stopped smoking many years ago. Using the word STOP helped me feel more in control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to see @caseydband  at Brandin Iron!!! https://t.co/DF8MZ2MCDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suttmike @Gluonsrule @proud2thebone @DonCheadle @realDonaldTrump Next time go for the space right after the period… https://t.co/DAigJudxxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dockboggs4lyfe @jenniferprager @kylegriffin1 I think McCabe knew what he could say. Rosenstein already announced h… https://t.co/npaygRHxkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @DeplorableJuJuV @seanhannity Thanks Sean Hannity  peace of mind heading into surgery sure goes a long way...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHortons @JeepCanada Yup, I also have a timmies cup with my K-cups. @TimHortons @JeepCanada https://t.co/wTe61xMBk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces me pregunto será que los padres, madres, abuelos, enfermeras, médicos y maestros de tantos niños que han pa… https://t.co/8PRTql0QgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stay informed Southeast Fort Wayne ripe for revival | Columns | The Journal Gazette https://t.co/sFmyWWqY91]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually put in effort to looking nice today and they let me go home early but I have no plans 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano I Wish People Would Begin IGNORING THEM. WHAT A SICK BUNCH OF PUPPIES. Kanye Wants 2 Run 4 Pres? Get… https://t.co/uBx7XYDLux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Meloni @pattonoswalt And is dying because she was not, and will never, be invited. Just like the rest of her… https://t.co/hoBZSpi6pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am excited about how this archway sculpture is coming along! I am becoming aware that to some people this is just… https://t.co/LSxT89Ke0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warm weekend but a cool down is coming 👏👏👏👍👍😉😉 watch @WPLGLocal10 onair and online for more https://t.co/QwhilRdEkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fastandfunky Oh my gaaaah! I am in need of a rewatch but it’s too damn hard during the week now that I’m a working woman lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[she’s so fetch #hbd 🖤 @ North Shore High School https://t.co/RyhUi8HldP]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 days of learning with this amazing group of kids.  #dowhatyoulove #theymakemesmile #purpose https://t.co/vAsnWeDlqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a journey. 🕉💜🧘‍♀️ @ San Rafael, California https://t.co/DqdNmQBSqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we talked about the importance of human emotions and played a game where we named the emotions we thought a p… https://t.co/9vXz7LTykZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my bf I want another tattoo and hear we are planning out what i should get   I love him so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just #baby bumpin’ our way through this production. We are halfway and #audiences have been great! So #grateful to… https://t.co/bCP3MlKWuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@griddler @WendydarlingT @SladeWentworth @HomeWithPeanut @pittdave13 @ThugRaccoons @KoKeniSasquatch… https://t.co/sCIeOdrsRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been an interesting night thank you everyone for your participation but now it’s time for me to smoke some CBD… https://t.co/7dKJrFEK0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timelady07 @KristanHawkins I understand completely. I've seen these babies. I've also seen the parents holding hidden them &amp; crying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FluffyTank_666 @therealjoebob Awww. 🥰 Thank you so much! That means an awful lot to me! 🤠📬🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobplain @RIDeptEd @egreenwichnews @kmkwagner I might need to write an actual post since Twitter is Twitter but he… https://t.co/WnNTwuMx40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise If people can’t figure out how to use #BirthControl to prevent #UnwantedPregnancies, then let’s focus… https://t.co/zlUi7yepNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMBalasar It was good glad that you all enjoyed each others company lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[sent this msg to a (HOT) former IDF soldier and this is his response,, whats my move y’all https://t.co/o5TPNgAc3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teams head into the locker rooms with Beulah leading Beach 38-20. #NDpreps]]></document></documents></author>