<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[THIS DUDE NEEDS A MEDAL -STAT !!!!!!!!!!!! 😢👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏 #saveouroceans  #seaturtles #plasticenemy #oceanplastic… https://t.co/0x8hsbkMSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#higherfurtherfaster #captainmarvel #actuallyican #useyourpowertoempower #internationalwomensday #latergram @ Premi… https://t.co/UiIqL4BWEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikaBrezinski trash. I got a Flat screen from my son for my birthday. Other channels don’t hire aging anchors. Jus… https://t.co/HHLW6Rdkbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @simplysallyh @joneill55 @ccatmpt @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @CaththeWineLady @hmgivingsoul… https://t.co/NN7Qqd95G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the oldest Catholic parish in Scottsdale. Seriously, though. There's something about these depictions of Mary. G… https://t.co/quQyGF5A8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios @CyrusToulabi @LindseyGrahamSC This explains why nothing gets done. You don't know that you actually have ot… https://t.co/1hvUbeplfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lew’s got talent! So much fun at our Talent Show tonight. I commend our kiddos for being so courageous and conf… https://t.co/y7ELZ7BgFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeyvallone_ @ashleyboyerrr @ChuckECheeses @shanedawson That’s exactly what I was thinking. They aren’t pieces tha… https://t.co/mfMxDiklFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @karenslinn43 @ann4252 @Iluvinspireu @MyEngland2016 @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/duUHl1qMJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frenchnneed4 Thank you for your kindness; I so appreciate it! Best Wishes to you! https://t.co/VwaYi5CMv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfredo fettuccine with sautéed shallots, broccoli &amp; omg scrumptious 😋 @ Napa, California https://t.co/5OiQIQ0jiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eightvape is having one AMAZING giveaway and today is the last day to enter!! Go over to their main page and find t… https://t.co/bvwq86tkle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xyz_infinity @FoxNewsSunday According to CNN and MSNBC... I live in Oregon and I have seen first hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIBWTyler @WIBWsports Hope to see all of you all again  tomorrow @3:00 to cheer on the girls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...every now and then I kick the living shit out of me -Lit, My Own Worst Enemy ~ We've all heard of summit fever… https://t.co/8SwdJK4j9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years with VIPKID as of yesterday! Wow, I love this job! My VIPKid https://t.co/GPPdBKNbbZ https://t.co/fEzcQrhyYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsarsour Who cares what color they are...none of them are qualified to serve in Congress... https://t.co/ADkaeoK9t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I just have no patience with people like this. Almost half the country is turning into the movie “Idiocracy“]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julie Goldstein crossed 10K. Time 02:12:42, pace 27:05 min/mile, est. finish 10:23 am https://t.co/ibf6JUOOJF #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mood todos los dias, todo el dia ▶️ Bajito Mejor que tu Mujer Bruja Con una mirada Ya no quiero na Teléfono Hay… https://t.co/FPKsyuqlnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[NORTH TEXAS VET GOING TO IDITAROD | Rowlett Veterinarian Prepares for Alaska's Iditarod Race  https://t.co/wKXH5LafR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaRTubbs This is honestly how I feel about the first person that gifted roses as a form of romance. Outcast kn… https://t.co/h8wJlOc6pU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m1ke_nyc @marcorubio @MarioDB @AmbCTrujillo My God what is wrong with you, these people are starving and need medicines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @CyberVegan PP should go Private for their Nation Support...Government should stay out of the bedroom..… https://t.co/ey4qYEBtx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran for the first time in four months today. My brain feels SO MUCH BETTER.  My knees are still angry from my last… https://t.co/xG02oPmya5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got into it with an anti vax nurse because she’s asking for 100% certainty that people who get the HPV vacci… https://t.co/exxKuKT4xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated International Women’s Day nabeorg with a cartoon lady ears disneysminnie @ Disney's Coronado Springs Res… https://t.co/LnIlcZ3Fcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cloverfieId I’m going to Cannes and I’ll take pics of all the restaurant menus that don’t have vegan options and I’ll talk about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is what work looked like every day, I’d be 1000 pounds. But I’d accomplish a lot from the sugar high!… https://t.co/9PUjSnSdSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better posture with Ryan yesterday 👍#golflessons#golfcoach#foundation#trainsmart#boditraksports                   #… https://t.co/SIGdU35usS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixture of Victoria SECRETS &amp; BATH &amp; BODY WORK'S...NEED &amp; WANT MORE 💯💯 @ Florida City, Florida https://t.co/r7sLI985r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I ✅’d off one of the goals I made for myself at the end of 2018.🏅 Who knew I could do it? ...God did!… https://t.co/FveXox1soQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now playing on Starfire's Country Music w/Trisha at Night Wave Radio (https://t.co/OI5xIMNO2M) @nightwaveradio1… https://t.co/37SVu98vly]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 7th grade FCS a boy told the class his dad lived in a “condom” instead of “condo”. Hands down favorite junior high memory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling into daylight savings weekend like🥁 #springforward @ Frenchmen Street https://t.co/WEFLbWFqMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S DAY EVERYONE!   And a major shout-out to all the amazing waterwomen out there! Especial… https://t.co/cVPAIF7YFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No overtime for salaried workers is awful. 😡  all workers deserve to be treated fairly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in his teaching he said, “Beware of the scribes, who like to walk around in long robes and like greetings in th… https://t.co/JdSu5CVF9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakeUpGeek44 So excited for this I can't wait for it this would be so amazing to win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend, red_tape_ninja, sent me the gem you see when you swipe left. Thanks for the reminder, doll face! To comb… https://t.co/k7pixBlDxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[this lady at target just discounted this jacket i wanted bc i wasn’t gonna buy it]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my parents bought new curtains which means spring break is cancelled and I’m going back to school where nothing changes]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly nothing more disrespectful than a shit ton of people coming into ur hotel room uninvited, kicking us off o… https://t.co/Q0adBDo1Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your car decides that you are no longer on a diet 😂 https://t.co/NjeWKHiB02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed ... I am now crying!  As a parent - biological or adopted-  love knows no bounds.  This is indeed a beautifu… https://t.co/BDpKE4pFk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's a fucking pastry chef, she probably makes $13 an hour (and that's probably a generous estimate) and entertain… https://t.co/2ok0MV8QZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun morning at the announcement of the Grand Prize winner in the Texas Cavaliers art contest. A NISD student won -… https://t.co/qHzEhGfFYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago, I entered the gates of HEAVEN at @TheEllenShow!!! ☁️🎥👦🏼✨🤩  #ellendegeneres #bekind #surprise #happy… https://t.co/itONnzoXQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrysFanGyrl @homewithnarry I'm free think about Mister Big Styles also.  Just because I'm not alone in this hous… https://t.co/TRWvxOqWKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk punching someone in the face because you can't keep your head cool is just so tacky to me. It bothers me way to… https://t.co/v235k9erAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm off the deep end. Watch as I dive in. I'll never meet the ground. Crash through the surface where they can't hu… https://t.co/hdONq4KBwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissajkwhite @literarylozada @heatherevery @KatSouthmayd Why can’t I finish this book?? What is wrong with me???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebekkarxo Focus on the strongest moment in memory when you felt closest to Jesus. Stay there. Stay in that moment… https://t.co/281j4N4mJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Wasserman Schultz is repulsive for being against funding the military when Obama and Hillary brought… https://t.co/ur6u4VbiSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaloneComedy @bengleib OMG!!! Finally!! You are fiiiiinally coming to Boise @MaloneComedy! 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman Like you never heard about the perv doc examining players in your charge at Ohio State University?  BS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today begins the journey to becoming an educator!! Today I start to student teach a little at Delaware Community Sc… https://t.co/Ax4BWH4A1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Says one of the dumbest individuals with one of the biggest mouths in congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs Haven’t we learned to have low to no expectations in our current President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo desde las 7 tratando de hacer los exámenes y lo único que he hecho es tragar 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have food poisoning...which is not fun at all. 😫 But on a positive note, I currently have abs of steel fr… https://t.co/hqTellp1Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats lying that lower refunds mean taxes went UP https://t.co/H7H7DJFRnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my dad, I miss my mom, never in a million years would I think they’d both be gone by the time I’m 25]]></document><document><![CDATA[are identical with those of all good aspiring women. The organization focused on job training, wage equity, and chi… https://t.co/ER53ha9LMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocean views from the master bath!! #modernhome #bathroomdesign https://t.co/YHG2xekxWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence God may have chosen him so his EVIL, TRAITOROUS, RACIST, XENOPHOBIC, MISOGYNISTIC, ways would be revealed… https://t.co/w8vmafUQjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our panel, 'Remolinos: The Border as a Constant Cyclical Experience' has been accepted at Translating B/borders: Co… https://t.co/6cXV2BD4wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters of course I'll be disappointed #JussieSmolettHoax NO! You should be disgusted! Appalled! #LiberalHypocrisy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katelynvharris but when i ask around all i’m told is that you don’t know what a razor is 🐸☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flat iron accident!!!! I should never be allowed with hot instruments! Ever!!!! @ Queens, New York https://t.co/x3htLuTt3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silentrunning12 @Krissy_Caster @Ximena74560472 @MikayesFiona @VOCRadioRobDoc @scifiotica @AllenEllis14… https://t.co/IRwp2zThsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fragilevixenfic @SpookyFox130 @trothaar I know how you feel my anxiety and stress level have been testing me for 3… https://t.co/CbgZg4qu38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ou eu amo leoninas como se fossem as últimas barras de chocolate do universo ou eu odeio elas do fundo da minha alm… https://t.co/OUbOdHUDRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademyPicks @THATJacqueline @ReginaKing @filmindependent Amen to THAT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost And it continues right through to Covington Catholic High School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like winter is here to stay for a bit longer... 🤪😖🥶 Thankfully this cozy cardigan from @myfashionjunkee has b… https://t.co/GRW9iZDAGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett Rehearsed His Own Assault, Prosecutors Say https://t.co/TWleKRLGOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah, I was like “wow, look at all these insufferable shits. ooh, some of them are sad and gay, too?! sign me the f… https://t.co/oYmPS7S8Ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one hour kills me; wide awake at midnight. Can we just stay on Daylight time forever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay2019 #makersmark #iamwomanhearmepour #womeninwhiskey https://t.co/GQJ8D8awvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWalkerDaniels @MaskedSingerFOX @JennyMcCarthy @NickCannon @MsPattiPatti In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Kne… https://t.co/84opcCxfBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[John, both of my now deceased parents were veterans of WWII. My Mother was an Army nurse in South Pacific, my Fathe… https://t.co/GZgG3kqerd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanObeidallah @StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Oh, please. What a SOPHOMORIC statement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; moderate rain temperature down 56°F -&gt; 50°F humidity up 67% -&gt; 87% wind 3mph -&gt; 2mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, Judith, you weren’t there to see what he did to Abraham and Glenn. I’m still traumatized from that. Listen to… https://t.co/XhGlerXIzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cupcake 🧁 Wars have begun in @millbrookmagnet HS Kitchen. Check out the “Sugar Mommas.” @MrsCTChance @SO0ver… https://t.co/ceMsZCBzsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else get these calls saying your social security number is suspended? I get them at least once a day, even a… https://t.co/WEfVmZc6fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 1 of the @YouVersion plan 'Fast Friends, Biblical Results Of Fasting And Prayer'. Check it out… https://t.co/Ga7l2gtq4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trubie2012 @Yamiche @AllResistNews Well, OFCOURSE they knew that.  It was OUTRAGEOUS!  It’s amazing the shit we have to put up with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickimporter @RedRock406 @lisa_berden @sarasneeze @AllisonVCraig @PrettyBlueBirdy @HRchupp @blueraccoon… https://t.co/RfYaCX6hLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@555ft Every other day. Would you like a sammich? I make them for $8.95.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kleib323 @lawooster Thanks that’s actually really well done! Going to use this method!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day two of #15daysofFatT #FriendsAtTheTable @Friends_Table https://t.co/Qjlnkr0uhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure makes me think of a song... (created by 7 yr old engineer) @scratch @ScratchEdTeam @LCPSEdTech @LCPSOfficial… https://t.co/BEiOkErAZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My incredible Co Host raissagerona from @revolve for our @fivefour X @revolve meet up, where we talked about our ch… https://t.co/4B01LHSmIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Every time you call me and cuss, I write it in your baby book.” weird flex but ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBackerman1 @clairermassey @bhathaway311 @ThaddeusArjuna @keanothedog @62WalterP @a_patriciann @PaulColby2… https://t.co/YufW4z0bXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleymethner does this mean my pre-work-or-school-scream-in-the-car makes me an actor ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klgandhoda Beautiful as ever! It’s going to be so hard not seeing you two together everyday!☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joinFAR I'm going to Pop with all this excitement! I Can't Take It! PICK CANON CITY, COLORADO! For Fun and Adventu… https://t.co/9m0mLCCqWM]]></document></documents></author>