<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BB_Ben29 @PastFactory It did,by tearing the paper a new one, so it did erase ink.....and everything else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bpquigs Me too! We moved downstairs at the pitching change and I freaked out the next two ABs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beto, I found your rally in El Paso was inspirational. I’m sure others found it as well. Well, you’ve received more… https://t.co/GUip6PTIxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcwm I sleep as little as possible the night before and pass out from exhaustion -- preferably by a window where it's roomier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanHaight1 Didnt buy one yet. Considering buying online. Havent missed many this year. Not an anti furman guy bel… https://t.co/hmqMWVd1I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating decades of music education @utmartin! Enjoyed the @UTMDeptofMusic Alumni Awards celebration… https://t.co/XY043LFlGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya'll trippin. That could be YOUR money but you trying to take the long way 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_jaeee They gone put some respect on Ser Bronn of the Blackwater name soon tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[More on former UAFS men's coach Justin Bailey.   https://t.co/58VKtpHPAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇨🇦 Se tiene que viajar para aprender 🍁🥟✈️🌎 #montreal #montrealcity #montreallife #montrealmoments #montrealphoto… https://t.co/6BrrhKcF2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantCardone and @JarrodGlandt I was denied for a sales job today because I’m too motivated by money and productio… https://t.co/f6FagcfPu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the @BoysDnh team tonight as they take on Denver.  Go and take it!! #RollBlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final score notwithstanding, I choose to remember sapcenter coming UNGLUED when Jumbo got the hat trick.… https://t.co/e4XAkJBwU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just passed a billboard in Orlando showing an ECG with flat line and the text: “When you die you meet God”. Anyone… https://t.co/vOevRaRdLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does any TFC fan want Omar Browne on a on a minimum deal? Because honestly he’s a great player and we can probably… https://t.co/WX1LkzBO4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleymarin16 @E40 IDK how you got the pic, of a selfie in progress!, but that's curiously interesting.  Nice prof… https://t.co/GNgZpO2RAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were there at my lowest points , I got you at my highest and that’s on Mami no cap 👌🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GossmanAmy @coleyworld 0.375 shitloads of a shitton are equal to a pantload.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The return of my customary airport  Martini ✈️🍸 👍🏼.  I actually think it’s the  first one for 2019.  I may have to… https://t.co/hILO5FEwQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrellDass @David_Leavitt Never associate the Olive Garden with good Italian food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrySportsRadio @PardesSeleh Not a single person was arrested. Last year was the fist time I heard gunshots in my neighborhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit getting tired of NOT seeing the new swimsuits from @VictoriasSecret ....its March....GIVE THEM TO US]]></document><document><![CDATA[Change of address Canadian Incoming QSL Bureau  https://t.co/Ce3s48M71r  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best bouquet I’ve ever seen. Bacon and Bourbon, baby!!  #Valentines2019 https://t.co/i83ZVThW6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TrpqBYkNub This Just In (KY) Sen. Rand Paul has voted against President Trump's Natinal Emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experiencing that moment when your boss sits in the seat directly in front of you on a flight, and you become ever… https://t.co/ouMU2PiSrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t decide on if I should keep watching GOT rn or go to bed for class tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC Good — another Democrat failed green energy corny capitalism initiative ... theft from the taxpayers pockets… https://t.co/E7glzrXpBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh mannn oh mannnnn @MattMoscona what ya think the Gator fans are thinking about #FloridaGulfCoast pitching a NO-HI… https://t.co/58ZyGygXia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention reigning Monarch@BuckinghamPalace  Winter hardship. https://t.co/8pI4Sccwbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotGeauxGabby He’s so fucking stupid. This interview is going to wind up compelling him to testify in his own tria… https://t.co/RBmyyVv3iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the hell u keep passing to Rondo! It’s a reason they keep leaving him open dumbass! #lebum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Award ceremony for the science fair...top 20 projects...proud of these students! https://t.co/9XWAifmVJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_____mps_____ @j_salvo I bet you could do something cool with voice and eye attention detection, with some gesture business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wademullendore Ended up going to Flips. Next time in on the area we can chill brodie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal You has a bit of a slip on air on MLB Network but it was the truth. Danny Lazano did STICK IT to the Padres!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some Old Gran Chappy’s Wake Up Juice @ Dos Amigos Burritos Concord https://t.co/QiifV2rRiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know this feeling all too well. I couldn’t do what I do without my amazing wife. I am truly blessed to be her husba… https://t.co/FdNCe0XpXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMopary @jerweber Says the idiot who sports a photo of Michael Flynn on their Twitter page😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mijo &amp; I at Mt Roubidoux this morning!  *both of us heavy breathing not pictured * @ Mount Rubidoux https://t.co/DZWjLlDx9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacmacandsneeze @Twitch_Jack1 He's got me beat.  I was starting to think abstractly, about starting with Japanese… https://t.co/aBnznJKaIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travc_ I’ve watched a lot of Football and never seen anyone’s attitude change like AB has this quickly!!! As a Steelers fan it’s brutal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Marino is at Harry and Izzy’s downtown right now “Who is that” ...Yup this isn’t gonna work 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenFeinstein as one of your CA constituents I find your response reprehensible. Civic engagement is  at the core… https://t.co/3Te44K7vus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t take these moments for granted. Three years down 1 more to go! https://t.co/dVYSmsYLV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I could share a memory-filled weekend with my girls #FlyinIllini #AmazingGrace #RoseGold @ State Farm Center https://t.co/1zUnqb9PPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FedUpPatriots1 @itsangfyi @BreitbartNews TAKE THIS NY BILL TO THE SUPREME COURT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MStanley2209 @charliekirk11 Please explain how the trade deals were bad and how they're now better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Church At Liberty Square in Cartersville, GA https://t.co/CpNckAAlrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @MSNBC Yes, but he’s deranged.#ImpeachMf  #TrumpKopromat https://t.co/D1WAEPXIf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@je62zambrano @jguaido Que buen trabajo hace el G2. Esa gente si sabe planificar, juega muy bien con las emociones… https://t.co/zrsG9p0tjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeClayNFL BUDDY! Wish I knew when I saw you this week. Love your work and passion. Keep it going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow is #Detroit67 a palette cleanser to Engagement Party... not even tho. A goddamn antidote to it. Brava!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shaun Kemp was never better than him like most of twitter said . I was one of the few who argued against it from th… https://t.co/4lJ0v8jFpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olballcoach_1 Until gets through running the Acme brick company that will struggle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r_a_salvatore Why no female powerful dwarf characters in your Drizzt books?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Froley393 Boldddd bold take justin, I can’t lie I thought you were better than this]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here’s a great Q&amp;A with the film’s director: https://t.co/YTs8auQrJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if I have ever been as genuinely happy as I was after tonight! Thank you @lukecombs, @LancoMusic and… https://t.co/NU53rkaeyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nose Piercing inkinri ray_ce #holdsteadytattoo #holdsteadytattoos #tattoo #tattoos #piercing #piercings #ri… https://t.co/gOGR0KtG7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatMandervelde What is the name of your company?  I saw one on FB, but know that it's not yours from listening to @HawkeyeReport Podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluepurplerain @RioSlade I feel sorry for everyone I. The World that has deal with this ugly narcissist, especially women, but all of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel a little more powerful today thanks to @thrashquatch. It definitely stung but pain leads to many beautiful t… https://t.co/51QaBEyWEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido #venezuela🇻🇪 @ Miami International Airport - MIA https://t.co/dhGxbWD9cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll switch the race to the center TV in a little bit I guess… But the Rangers are playing… @ Boerne, Texas https://t.co/PExdhxT1lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[connected to the #wifi https://t.co/XZliSEBYy0 #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/yiUNPUSbuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanLDonahue @chr31ter @NERevsUK @BlitzzP @NERevsRumor Moreno, drama aside, had a sweet goal. Runstrom never got i… https://t.co/CzN3WVEJ5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game on.  @PrepHoopsOK @SuaveFrancisco_ @HHokcSports @WorldwideWillis  #ChargerPride https://t.co/Mu7UzmXjER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ag0at I hope it’s an event that just culminates in “Don’t you guys have phones?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mader85 @abdallaha92 @AaronLemingNFL Reworking contracts only delays the inevitable. Money converted to bonus gets… https://t.co/HdlMkDXpbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoreWhit @EdwardTHardy @DNC @SenSanders @TomPerez @dccc Maybe. I hope so if he gets in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think she has a SoundCloud so here’s her on Spotify: https://t.co/kehxVGSBgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOOD!!!!!  "Shhhhh. I'm watching #Buffy"  @slayerfestx98 @bufferingcast @LaniDianeRich   (One day at a time 1.8) https://t.co/zl9Mmic4F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ThirstyThursday! Have a great day! https://t.co/2GEbe11dUR @DavidDiehl20 @DavidJNann @miketerry62… https://t.co/LxsI6HSs4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ciara_mist18 LOL damn hommie who is you finally jumping on the almond train??? https://t.co/qqTqhVuZLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time for @ManCity to build a 2nd training facility in London. #2ndHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does ANYONE know where all of my hot rod tow and recovery coozies went ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colbertlateshow @StephenAtHome You must be. Been watching you make America laugh since I retired in 2008.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonArm Go ask Clapton who the GOAT is. $20 bucks says he goes with Prince.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckoennecker That’s gotta be a dry run for the 2030 US Open right? 100 year anniversary of the Bobby Jones Grand Sl… https://t.co/Cc6HaDtBkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 14 Alesia Way #Rockwood #TN  #realestate https://t.co/KSkh8qiwdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllieCoreyKSDK So sorry for your loss. Thank you for sharing Diesel with us over the past couple of years. I felt… https://t.co/RNnjc8CvJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkopf sent me this article today and I understand very little of the headline. https://t.co/546uARpGnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish they had @jump_rides when I lived in SF. Hard to beat riding 10+ miles to Ocean Beach for sunrise and back in… https://t.co/x0tz1KCe1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Adult #Cutest #Cute #Small #Vibrator Grab Up The iBunny Mini Or The iKitty Mini. #AdultShop #Amazon #Adam #Eve Tak… https://t.co/XjsJACgXgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KISSopolis I’m going with Alive II but i must say that their Unplugged performance is still my favorite MTV Unplug… https://t.co/tNQumuaqmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not everyday you get to meet a person who has changed and influenced so many lives. Rick Gutman, self-made mil… https://t.co/6Ww6PS4WK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes. #drinkitin Get used to seeing more awesome pics of my awesomeness! #60poundsdown @ Maplewood, New Jersey https://t.co/lRo4wVGlr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Well done @PeteButtigieg once they start attacking, means you got them scared]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dollar Made Goes in their Pockets. What about the Venders, The Provider's and Sponsor send the Army it takes to Cle… https://t.co/8ErCQLVuHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonligvtbaee I'll meet Ariana Grande  when the moon is full and the sky is bright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayMotivation “You don’t play against opponents; you play against the game of basketball” – Bob Knight]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Now when these things begin to happen, look up and lift up your heads, because your redemption draws near.” Luke 21:28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRothstein I thought he was day to day.  Is he sitting out the rest of the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entering the final stages of my remix for @sofiakatsaros 💜 @ Keyport, New Jersey https://t.co/Sl9rNfpCDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewSiciliano If he takes a 1 or 2 year deal then it could happen. I don't see that though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @Jamierodr10 @POTUS Ronil Singh, Kate Steinle, are their deaths manufactured?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it - you guys should try to have a little fun 😂🦈🎾.   A winning culture = a fun, energetic and passionate group… https://t.co/c27Tsy9SU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Betterment It's about time to kick in mansion doors and make the wealthy eat their young]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterhoneyman @Icelandair Torture? The business class seats are nice :P]]></document></documents></author>