<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CaliiSnow Smoke some weed. If you don’t partake, I’d recommend some chamomile tea instead. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Executive Committee💧Is Mean 🥵😎. one Time for our #Lamplighter Officers! #weLeadTheWay #OmegaLamplighters… https://t.co/Ta3zL2CT5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so the results speak for themselves, but had to share this NON SCALE VICTORY with you all. Kelly’s body fat ac… https://t.co/UdHPc62GpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GloryFitness  Don't Get Upset, Get Healthy.... #gotthatgodjuice praisefittour #love #fitness #fitnessmodel radiope… https://t.co/iGVX0dt3SG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the public is getting real tired of this Democratic liberal baby killing party being so delusional they're… https://t.co/eM27WMo38O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite cereal!!! 1...2...3... GO! (Bonus if you can do it with a GIF)  This is mine 😋 #NationalCerealDay https://t.co/H5EieVGltM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBolelli I like to imagine how folks in the middle ages would have reacted to seeing a human with this size and sp… https://t.co/LE7We5RZP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Existen dos tipos de tweets:   Los que son pa uno mismo y los que son pa’ los demás.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeann12gauge @HP_Community @heatherpeace Praying your mom has a quick recovery 🙏❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all Go Fw @quedamfyoungin  Music Right Now ❗️🔥🗣📌 https://t.co/o0W5PgrhUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the CORRUPTED Doesn't  think they got Justice 🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😂🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Humm... does Rosanne Barr realize she looks like a mummy? I mean shouldn’t she be more worried about t… https://t.co/QXfxAqLunp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatShakespeare @The_Globe That wasn’t me talking. It was the beer. How very dare you think it was me?🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️👻Thanks so much for sharing this.. made my evening!! 💚💛 Hope we see more! 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OLRefugeMonksCA I understand completely.  I live in a town where most roads are 35 mph and you only have traffic f… https://t.co/yZNlSvbRsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacob, that candy bar is almost as big as your head! Enjoy it, and congratulations on learning 20 pieces so far thi… https://t.co/3C4HYDaB2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenwearmouth @WhiteCastle Yes! Ugh! Or even the big ones from mcds. Nothing is better than having a perfect has… https://t.co/F8cWv3Kl5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tweets4MAGA @robertthedeuce She is anti America....inpeached get her out of office]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreezyCreates Thanks 🙏 @BreezyCreates  y’all please join me for this awesome app please thanks 🙏🙏🙏🙏❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️💯💯💯💯😀😀😀😀☝️☝️☝️☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobileHelp @JohnLegere Hi Jeromy. The old.lady in me need some help to DM you. Can you message me? Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss it! Today the Spring Film Series, Exploring African-American Identity through Film, will present Bessie… https://t.co/YtDbRoq0fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder And Jacob Wohl believes Trump.  He continues to get around that Twitter ban and apparently set up another a… https://t.co/Ocof0W8qHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News doesn’t feed you intentional misinformation like CNN ABC CBS NBC MSNBC CNBC n PBS.  Ignorance will cost yo… https://t.co/9LhZR2SUdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have seen the most beautiful man today 🤧 &amp; then my professor closed the class room door before we could make eye contact 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sushi with Meg and Nick 🍣🍱🥢 (@ Oki Sushi in Lansdale, PA) https://t.co/5ucWpU5oiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_mcamacho Never understand how you have time for all that you do. You’re fabulous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HMWDesign_Bot @HMWDesign_Bot Different in what way? Are you referring to students or educators? #CAedchat #STEAMTEAMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_kings_ @starbucksgirl51 @ZerlinaMaxwell MEDICARE IS NOT FREE. Stop repeating that uninformed garbage!… https://t.co/gLafzzBRr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[An underage girl in college drinking?  And posting pictures on Her own private Facebook page? My goodness how will… https://t.co/3IvtA681zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say get you a man who can do both. Whatever just send me a #Canadian please 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scamp246 @AllNightShow @timlt4 @LegatoTia @bob_kitt @WRosskopf @LadyLakeMusic @TewsTinamarie @LauraWr19952389… https://t.co/CYRAnXjtBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kiddo leading the flag ceremony for tonight's Girl Scout international night. https://t.co/f2m5FCgie8]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: does anyone know what the hell HEADnotes are( not the ones for legal stuff)???]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I read ur tweets, I feel I'm losing brain cells. Ur tweets r nonsense. #MAGA #DonaldJTrump #NancyPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xanboni Insane what they’ve done over the last 5 years! If you watch collegiate, Katie’s team, @WesternMichU skates last. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellouchez You are seriously one of the best people I know! Chin up buttercup! I love you big!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exclusive video of @realDonaldTrump and Kim Jung Un's Last conversation in Vietnam #NorthKoreaSummit #Vietnam… https://t.co/HW3rwJ54YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually really need tgi to stop posting things while I’m at work though because I am waaaaaaaay too emotional in my old age]]></document><document><![CDATA[v proud of my mom’s feature in @SantaBarbaraMag 🌴☺️ https://t.co/wxkMOMNT2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cricks21 I’m about to start a new thing out here watch https://t.co/pQqjnbhJnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is me but the thing is it’s gonna take me a minute to open up no matter who it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone taking the SAT you are smart the SAT does not measure your intelligence .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spencito_ @GregVorse A server gets so many tables in their section and essentially the longer people are at one th… https://t.co/h7Et31MijC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to do what’s best for yourself because at the end of the day that’s all you have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! Coaches will be in the following buildings: @PeelerOpenElem @BrightwoodES and Florence. Learn somethi… https://t.co/IXP9X3pISy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qui est ce tireur recherché en Ontario et au Québec? (@EThibaultJDM) #JDQ https://t.co/xssOj1oJuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After that climb #mtb #sandiego #viewsfordays #breathless #mtb #shredgirls https://t.co/hZxFcJy6dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's his feelings about everything! He cares nothing about our laws or the Constitution! https://t.co/cHELpE6hRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing the Self Love Project Series ❤️💕 Self love is Key 🔑Join SSE March 5th-7th as we show you the importance… https://t.co/v3RWM0PfGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump He wants more adoration from whomever he can get it from. I hope farmers are not that s… https://t.co/XTGBvqaJOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I'm gonna be so productive at home, get so much done for the week  Me at home: *cries*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyCaya1 @Jeremy_Spires @UMassHockey Cale was there! https://t.co/bFEqxpLkmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gran ensayo sobre la educación sexual (fallida!) que se da a mujeres, y sus efectos https://t.co/UIYDOdLQQj #salud… https://t.co/bVMLktQFZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbomkamp21 No I wish 😂 I screenshotted that right before he left on this underway he’s on now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol @madsatan6969 @HippieVol @8MillionML @Smokeyholler @The_Fool_Monty @Shawn172510 @GTA_Redhead @beers300… https://t.co/8Yzl9Gm6h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YakubianRedhead I was responding to a response to DJT’s tweet of AD’s comment.  I can’t see the thread. So NO, I haven’t read the thread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO. The #DNC #Dems need to counter this 💩 now. They didn’t in 2016 and here we are again 🙄😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[His Insta is on my phone so I see all his DMs. He’s only 12. I’m still the boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight and all day tomorrow, catch me at #greatlakescomiccon at the Macomb County Community College with… https://t.co/VihE5XFj3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all our friends and family who supported the Joslyn Castle Murder Mystery. It was a family affair this… https://t.co/vFErBIjPUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you get a notification when Brad just uploaded a new video and you're already watching it .. 😂 @bradmondonyc https://t.co/cL8kffmcVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh fucking please.  Nevada.    Why don’t she take to the streets of Chicago and preach her shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉Happy Presidents’ Day!!🍸🎊🍷🙉MONDAYS HAPPY HOUR ALL NIGHT!! ALL HOUSE DRINKS🍻🍷 2x1@ the hottest spot!@guadaluperest… https://t.co/5ltQZTk0be]]></document><document><![CDATA[The oldest lie in the  Progressive   playbook is: Being a Democrat means you never have to say your sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJR88 @MikeBennerKGW @KGWNews “The cut was cleaned and sutured at home”?...anti-vaxx folks wake up it’s 2019 not… https://t.co/ab36tr06Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So these cars have been on our street for WEEKS... seriously people. You can literally only see the side mirror on… https://t.co/fnXkqNkmU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Políticas públicas enfocadas en la felicidad #HazloSimple #SeFeliz #GobiernoSanNicolás]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Panel on Wrongful Convictions Calls for Ending Use of Unverified Drug Field Tests — ProPublica https://t.co/s6taTMzoUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[great. I love it. Im all with you. California can help lead in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels$]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh - I’m over you @colton - bring on Hannah B! 💃🏼 #thebachelor https://t.co/ACn1bKxilZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscars don’t need a host after all! @Oscars2019Live_ @TheAcademy #oscarshost #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[pretty bench, wondering how much it cost and can’t help but think about the hostile intentions of these armrests... https://t.co/4vnJqFDt4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[i fucking hate being a mouth breather like how tf do people do it???? i want my nose back 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting ignorance and lawlessness as exhibited by loser morons like @DonaldJTrumpJr is imperative to saving our de… https://t.co/0tZ48LkLJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When you’re on you’re deathly I’ll people will do to you what your evil sadistic ass is doing to H… https://t.co/beKpHHJ8ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holleyr @alexnazaryan They just like saying that word. It tested better than murder in their BS based scenario software.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAINTS Indoor 4x 800 record setting relay team running at nationals at Armory in NYC today: Maggie Strickler, Julia… https://t.co/k9QhqJuHT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickjonas @jonasbrothers @typicallykaylee whatever’s on this won’t top BOUNCE but it’ll still be good 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are in the audience business now. We are paying for the entire things ourselves. We are now in show business” s… https://t.co/AFlD53XrdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Vonore #TN  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/r2UHbvyp1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule The bishops found no wrongdoing on his part, so he's off to sue a newspaper. Rich snowflake wants more attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eatcookwrite @GHGGuru @OatesBryce @ewanrross @BioBeef @ConversationUS @drsplace again with the illd conceived idea… https://t.co/3A3jp4Sqnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here singing about procrastination... as I put off grading the papers I brought home...just finished some m… https://t.co/UeKCmx1to9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick Race Before Poker https://t.co/V91WuvRkRJ https://t.co/M3644KPa8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 6th hour was interrupted by a singing 🎶 valentine ❤️ for Mady!! Beautiful music by our Ammendment  group!!… https://t.co/NCacyGiNBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m getting closer to finishing nursing school because when people ask me medical related questions, I can o… https://t.co/HD1LJN9anZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Golden Triangle Emergency Center in West Orange, TX https://t.co/BQ9TEs5J6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex don’t mean none , a dick get hard for anybody a nigga can be deep inside u n still not feel u , stop braggin on… https://t.co/o6RyuHfsPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActionNewsJax just saw the Fact Check piece on the Lenny Curry Ads.  I have read that crime rate goes up when more… https://t.co/AfVv8nfYdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've paid next to no attention over the last couple of week to what's going on in the world of Trump, and it's been… https://t.co/zPepRVUu0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firecracker_doc I’ve only ever worn black boots, jump boots or jungle boots.  Never tan.  I’m really old as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorColoso @EbonyBlac_ Click on the little arrow on the top of the tweet by the username. There is a report tweet button]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone said “coming home to each other after a long day of cheating” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol it’s 5:20am.  I can’t remember that last time I was up this late...early...? I’m so confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS ALREADY NUMBER 6 IN THE US LIKE WHATTT @kevinjonas @jonasbrothers @nickjonas @joejonas  #SUCKER #JonasBrothers… https://t.co/BSsTPXopHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is in a seriously messed up place when I’m agreeing with @WalshFreedom 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Izzo crying in this post-game interview with @espn got me like: 😭😭 so proud of the @MSU_Basketball Spartans! #V4MSU #MSUvUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaranKillam T/F you knew all of the lyrics to Moana well before you shot #singleparents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garthbrooks @AmericasCenter We are ready!! Thank you for starting your tour in STL!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/YA2Tz0mHrI]]></document></documents></author>