<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dead Poets Society overrated, @kairyssdal ?  For shame, good sir. #forShame]]></document><document><![CDATA[A UK Colleague says to me this morning, "It's Poet's Day."  Poet's Day?  "Yeah, 'Piss off early, tomorrow's Saturda… https://t.co/DjPt9y8RO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of three, the Eagles are still on fire. https://t.co/IGx2Z1EJLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryLyn00719971 @Paintking @IAmFedUpppp @PatCaruthers1 @mollyday15 @lenagr8twit @cfhardy65 @HLAurora63 Nastalgia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baltimore always remembers it’s stars. @SimplyAJ10 will be no different. So the good news for #Orioles fans is that… https://t.co/5dsgzHzR0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a preview of what I’ll be covering at the Frisco Classic. https://t.co/wgHLlUwdDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn to love God’s ways and hate evil in every form—not only the obvious sins but also the socially acceptable ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna take myself back to bed for a bit because I’d rather not be in traffic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#that to just last Saturday with this one at @mmusicworks watching randyrogersband and joshabbottband What a great… https://t.co/2f9PnUYvZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to live to 100? This town may hold the secrets of longevity https://t.co/H9SY4PLQaO via @TODAYshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last month I commented on Monstwr’s video saying it wasn’t TPAIN and he wasn’t a good singer and I just went back a… https://t.co/5OgZf6BUUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmMoBamba @GlennM0ORE @omarnavarro214 @LucasBalti @wojespn Of course the Lakers are going to be a part of the pla… https://t.co/EsPX2A2BWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenHartzell can we bet the house on this?  This CANNOT be right.  No respect to the Retrievers. https://t.co/zTm6pSIBNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m an 80’s kid, and I’ve never seen any of the stupid Back to the Future movies. And vow to never see them. 😎  #AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3_DLeadership @DennisDill @conniehamilton @fisher1000 Innovation is creating something new or making something better. #hacklearning]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dolphins are cutting DE Andre Branch and G Ted Larsen today, per source.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump answer my call. What are you going about my people? Murder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeathSquadAB15 @HermosaBchMary  and I wouldn’t have met let along have a kick as relationship if wasn’t for  our f… https://t.co/H3UZ0WRqdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity  sick new governor and the people behind him in uniform are backing him LOSERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macmasters_a @caroljsroth Well Chuck Berry sang a song “My Ding a ling”...but....well... that’s another story I reckon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trying to dick ride but @Nadeshot story is honestly so inspiring. Dude went from McDonald’s worker to running o… https://t.co/TbNUcS0GGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[These bitches at Disney didn’t give this poor man some eyes smh my head https://t.co/5M9FVHiWLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IllectricRiver @SevenLionsMusic @Deorro @Gramatik @gjonesbass @RiotTenMusic @bleepbloopbass @LUCALUSH @manilakilla… https://t.co/oz9huYjE4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[#centralia #graffitihighway @ Centralia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/SJ1Zez7weS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therunchat A1: well, if I ask the people at work, the fact that I run is weird itself. #runchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like he was there for her, we must be there for them. We are all in this together. #TheAmericanContract… https://t.co/Bj7e1NAFjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gretchen1000000 So you’ve researched their credentials, possible conflicts of interest, funding sources, etc.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sklazinga Yeah! We never never have sugar cereal in the house so it’s a real treat on that day, we buy it the day… https://t.co/l80Yad3Uzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $1,539.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/QdcTe1njrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my first times hanging out with my homie @SebassAvila. Miss you bro #losangeles #hollywood #beverlyhills… https://t.co/aB4f8FIvcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked @rcbregman after the @Davos  clip. I really like @rcbregman for so easily piercing the thin-skin of… https://t.co/FvVuN2WQhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lil basketball 🏀 hero finishes the year with a W! They didn’t win them all on the court but she learned so much… https://t.co/HKeEjbJ9a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danny and I are trying to figure out if this bitches ass is fake or not 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson there is a man who was desperately trying to get me to come back to engineering.  He likes my ideas… https://t.co/oN00V3VaTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[For longer than I’m willing to admit, I thought wildlings and whitewalkers were one in the same #ForTheThrone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hvcco I made the space for them on the desk. Usually I leave them alone there but tonight we had to share]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestleMan100 @HeelWillMahoney Even when they get demolished by football they beat everything else, so USA isn't g… https://t.co/ZvsGQ34okL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sallyetuna60 @NBCNews Yes, we lost a lot of great ones. The biggest problem is we lost these great older ones and… https://t.co/wa4peK7GGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A simple reminder on this Monday morning. A lot of new cars on the road this morning....but do you have a garage? 🤔… https://t.co/HlHsYVNPXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find out some ultra juicy tea on someone https://t.co/cBEn4t4QRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I really wish R Kelly ain’t pee on them lil girls and do bare filth  Like why you couldn’t just make great chun… https://t.co/pbgVUlNRbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do i cry so fucking much GODDD i wish i were fucking dead sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Triciafl40 @Hutbug3 @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews Tucker is a bully.  He uses his atmosphere his channel his show to int… https://t.co/KQ5aHC6ELF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SOS_swank Did Nothing Wrong. The politically motivated arrest was made for alleged bogus process crimes. He was tr… https://t.co/Xuq5YwNHSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 This is absolutely hilarious.....love my man Bill Hader. #truthorfiction #srangerthanfiction]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something that's been on my mind recently. An event having more entrants does not inherently make it more or less w… https://t.co/ZWB0eSpqUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mass Die-Off of Whales in Atlantic Is Being Investigated https://t.co/UkVIGQEbJf #Sustainability]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUWrestling Iron Nick!! The pride of @BergenCatholic!! Deus Vult!!!! #Allin #GetItDoneBC #BurnTheShips 💪🤼‍♂️🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinkoEror @JJungewentrup It was great finally meeting you in person last week Dinko!    Happy Birthday 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizKilmerWPXI @WPXI Someone in Pittsburgh really got Elsa mad Not sure it will ever warm up in the BURG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMarielCV @juanajgx_ JAJAJAJAJA me baño más agusto ok? Y así te gusto🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pemuehleck @sak_shoes @tradeshowwendy Haha. Spanish. “De la patria querida”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWV @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse What a foreign relations coup! The smartest woman in the world, showing off her q… https://t.co/FtSR7Rkciy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@veldhawk rocking out #PersonalizedLearning #iameps https://t.co/gyn59iEghS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow internet says a fiber cable has been severed in central Ohio. Causing a massive outing @fox28columbus you folks… https://t.co/OUpPPA78jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam Reunion waltdisneyworld...ADVENTURELAND! . . . . . #tourbreak #fam #famreunion #wdw #parade… https://t.co/AamIEwnFoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shalomshuli Let’s see what he produces! He said he had several smoking guns on Trump and produced nothing. His cli… https://t.co/mzh2rpgo0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[- When the bathroom has good selfie lighting. 📸 I’m here. I may not be the best. I might not be rich and famous. I’… https://t.co/bOFTYiZEJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @christyclarkbc Clark hired a McGuinty trained professional E-mail deleter Laura Miller to destroy records… https://t.co/s4Z5T106z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson Seth, While this is fascinating stuff, your terse hints amount to little more than a tease. Can you p… https://t.co/M6DvbM1h6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[That @realDonaldTrump is a lying, cheating, con man is not new news. We knew this already. The problem is that his… https://t.co/qOdTplSqYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I talked with a coworker who lives with her boyfriend Nick and a bunch of his friends. Needless to say I… https://t.co/q8vJ1DPz5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@settlemlCFB It’s the go home show for Fastlane. My expectations are tempered lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC My formula for MSNBC @CNN Political Sickness PS  Fallacy of Logic: Fl = Ad Hominem, Straw Man, Red Herring… https://t.co/dQK0Z0hvwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fatherhood is amazing! Having #kids can change everything about your #life for the better... this is by far the mo… https://t.co/45EPm0ohGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cle_ItIsGone That's always been my thinking about baseball, too, and why I hate one-game wild card matchups. Also,… https://t.co/2WyDgLvFJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverBloomART @JimCarrey I don't think Jim Carrey can run for President, because he wasn't born in the US, he was… https://t.co/7IZpTb4AHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump The trump motto. Call it a win even when you lose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice League: TAS Huntress 9-Inch Gallery Statue https://t.co/1UHaN387oQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrossFitGames @CrossFit Early on I learned that RX is intended to challenge the fire-breather. The rest of us can… https://t.co/vwYyuDbQu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real. I was watching last night and thought the sound quality of the broadcast must’ve been bad, then realized… https://t.co/W4UCT6mcg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time LaVine shows he can be an offensive superstar he fucks up on defense the very next play. #Bulls]]></document><document><![CDATA[GLAM!!! Looking this good takes work, my babies! @ Erie County, New York https://t.co/Ii5Hups1yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the #Clippers play is so much fun. Love what Doc does with Lou and Montrezl coming off the bench. Trading… https://t.co/iGVyDQr6Te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtopical @gerardstringer7 Y’all kill me lol stop crying. And y’all won’t my first group if we being technical. I… https://t.co/zLQ50U2EiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawmakers Scrap Plan to Allow Iowa Schools to Get Rid of Nurses, Librarians https://t.co/8sxfgSTXHI via @whohd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich @thedavidcrosby That’s bc we kept more money in our paychecks this year bc our taxes were cut ...come on d… https://t.co/AYUu4YElwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many movies coming out I want to go see, but going by myself seems weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevogre @UnionManOKane @RepSwalwell @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/VlbtviMi2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a slugfest, LCC 33, Skagit Valley 12. Game ends on 2-5 put out...great tag out by Conley on Gray throw. Naugle W… https://t.co/NVRTvbRQy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 &amp; #2 trending on @YouTube @JeffreeStar @GraysonDolan @EthanDolan https://t.co/Dn0ZNTBujm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 30.089 in, Steady. Temperature 63.3 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 95%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Who's in charge???? I hope you mean " We The People"!!!! Surely you don't mean "Big Government" right???? #SOCIALIST]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are fired up for church this morning! Grab a friend and get here! 10am! It will bless your life! #MyCenterpoint… https://t.co/sLGDosLPwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryLent I agree, really bad. Hopefully #WrestleMania is not a waste of our time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhotogOnFire @MarkVSlaughter @MoellerBBall @AlecPfriem @Coach_Kremer @LetsGoBigMoe @DuncombLogan @deucemcb11… https://t.co/FXWIGxgGQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaughtxDamnvers Actually the NCAA is taking that into account this year for Tourney seeding and rankings. What doe… https://t.co/KJgHKR7pDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_Schulman @LeeSmithDC Trump's indiscriminate (re)tweeting from (antisemitic) alt-right sources gave ammunition… https://t.co/b2SWIEzkNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go follow @0Fhhs to see how funny and dumb (not literally but yeah) our school is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirgilVanTastic @palmoswince @jayvalmz @duncan_forest02 @ChelseaFC @FtblJames_ Oh yeah like Gareth Ba- nvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsea_dungee @RazorbackWBB Yes! Now A&amp;M needs to learn how to go home care of a Razorback Woman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayOstas @Hickenlooper Worth noting that last time was 2 unelected candidates so both sides torn their own up. Thi… https://t.co/TYdaslRVfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tradeomat @diggydoy2 @RiyadhRaveScene It’s possible, and would be the first time pure TA has screwed me on $TSLA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Quoteoftheday  “Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen.” - Michael Jordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Militias are gathering at golf courses across the nation.  #NotesFromNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo...the idea was to photograph this cupcake that Ashlee brought from unrefinedbakery but, it was REALLY great… https://t.co/ZerdGvtIgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wins above replacement: 12 Forearm veins: 6,587 Dad bods: 1 https://t.co/4KBIovOwht]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how you sell a Green New Deal to truck drivers. With a plan that would measurably improve their lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “New England Patriots owner charged for soliciting sex at a massage parlor”  https://t.co/L0HmNYNX5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because sometimes your week goes like crap and all you want is a ride on the Electra Glide and a smoke. @ Lake Eola… https://t.co/W2IGe8dirl]]></document></documents></author>