<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[THE GLOW UP! Pixie Cut and Relaxer Session  Hair by @HairBeatLA   Attn Stylist : Advanced Haircutting Workshops are… https://t.co/5CYcsGjJj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many amazing organizations that promote women/girls in sport. Say we (@samanthalrogers) gather in NYC… https://t.co/pqMPvS1ZUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFelixKay @MaskedSingerFOX @TPAIN @NickCannon Consider making an album with your amazing voice? I want to buy it! Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with all of the recovery and healing my biggest fear is getting into another relationship and not being  loved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class List for Wednesday, February 27, 2019: 5:00 am Wildcard Workout: Kettlebell AMPD with Cheryl E. Wood… https://t.co/I6sYDzrpIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A snow day means I get to watch #wonder unfold live when #SiglerNation and @lorclyon take over @Wonderopolis IG fee… https://t.co/Iy7FTV0HoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my goals this year: develop my team’s palate to the next level. Spoiling them w/ an incredible ‘12 San Giorg… https://t.co/oyh2rfAjrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que culero ese pedo de que tu novio le de like a otras y a ti nooo hahahahhahah😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande what’s the password mama was just trying to look to see :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dam24558 @mitchellreports @realDonaldTrump games or expensive,  but they are also provocative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SCHOOLEDthem  Senator Feinstein appeared to lecture some children campaigning for the Green New Deal  https://t.co/TRQoLht5b8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh nooo. If this was my family, I’d be praying for the officers lives at that point🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just before I woked up, I was dreaming about you, you were here in bed with me and]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished 1h:24m:39s of cycling with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/oHL5JoGGib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bijancbayne @dr_mbutler @InThePastLane @EZuelow @samueljredman @nlbmprez @DannyT21  A must read. Story in Harlem S… https://t.co/mOJozHoosW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teri_Kanefield @MarthaLynneOwe1 Just like tRump and the #tRumpCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC No news here, just another rush to judgement by a leader of identity politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OurFirstLoveYoongi  #HAPPYSUGADAY  #HappyMinSugaDay  @BTS_twt   ❤❤❤❤❤❤ https://t.co/HCfLEyzlpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulipRejuly @Lrihendry @DonaldJTrumpJr @ChatByCC Not sure, I’ve never watched this show. Guess we can google the q… https://t.co/hxP9JFreNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @MrsWebbGarcia 😍 I still love you even though you hate Shakespeare, hope you had a great day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The demolition team of Babol is full force using Maine’s blog to ruin her reputation and career They r twisting her… https://t.co/4KxPsI31j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaSGrey @CTG_CEOGEH Vivi is a smart little girl. She knows odds are in boys’ favor. She wants things even. She do… https://t.co/IdOEXCVYPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlationMedina Una vez me tocó pasar a presentar promociones el día que me iba de vacaciones; me gusta viajar en… https://t.co/NOF5lGPEYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[To just go to sleep or to make mozzarella sticks and continue watching tv?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamdeVry1 I saw the love episode between Julian in Alexa and I must say it was hot. It looked a smile on my fa… https://t.co/cLVKazlwWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#readingacrossamerica ❤️ the energy and dedication of Mrs. Broudy and the librarians maudetrevvett… https://t.co/Aqv9A4PDmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump says he could have ignored the "emergency", to explain away his words that he "did not have to" declare a nat… https://t.co/IZflUzwPcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m absolutely through with my brother rn somebody come get him https://t.co/N2OdnpvA0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFGiants That’s the weakest shit ever Wtf is the matter with you? You can’t afford a damn burner phone? And Pam, C… https://t.co/MdjTVbhQRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t ever tell a girl you love her and that she’s your everything, if you can break up because of an argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins We are fighting Islam around the world! Mohammed would be proud! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember it! And, i plan to use it to bury the GOP and "The Clown"!  #UniteAndResist #unitedstates]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elevator selfie once again. Hoping things still look good and we figure out why my nose is STILL bleeding.... @ Ohi… https://t.co/B9Iwkc1N0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so concerned for Kaderia it just seems she is unresponsive and not releasing the pain ...very guarded 😪😪😪heal Lord! #FixMyLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrville @SethMacFarlane @PennyJJerald @jessicaszohr @BJTannerTv Can.  Not.  Wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You have a perfect body for the tuba.” -@ServandoNYC’s middle school band teacher]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in San Antonio &amp; this is home , I missed it and my friends here 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has me screaming through My Bedroom 😭😭😭 “Naya istubiradyehey kulahaa”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/irSU2SWyXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even a soda drinker, but on god, pineapple Fanta hits so different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yassss. Finally got word on my 2018 bonus that’s depositing on Friday 😍 so pumped for the extra money to save!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ojH7QhpqLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ShameOnYou judge Ellis, Manafort  lies, cheats and steals from the American people and gets four years? Blaxk lady… https://t.co/RxZyFf9kB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great review @MavericksMusic! Wish we were there! https://t.co/KyKeqilnTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should have as much passion for their work as @brooksethomas. Loved your comments about using light to ove… https://t.co/tA1QAEetdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Your State Legislators: Make 100% Clean Energy a Top Priority for Illinois! https://t.co/HV9QPPzvw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mood #nofilter #Sunday #Dinner  Under this delicious melted mountain of 7 #cheese and #vegetable chucky homemade… https://t.co/5RS7YpXG3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to wake up your Wednesday morning? Join me to learn how to empower your employees with stories that stick. Reg… https://t.co/5ELr58xYXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Entxurage Prayers UP for your DAD, my brother! 🙏🏾 #veterans     #fuckcancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ImranKhanPTI Green Pakistan Initiative 👏👏👏 We would love the opportunity invest in 🇵🇰, #FreeKaavan on the agenda… https://t.co/OQPNtu3pAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougFields You gotta come to Az and go to a GCU game......it’s awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HACC_info York Campus hosted the @YCA4L CREW event today.  Over 300 students from York County participated in this… https://t.co/sd7HQuXvqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Job to the RHS Varsity Boys Bball team on bringing home a 64-57 WIN tonight over Kenmore!  #rittmanproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gondos on the go 24/7 💙#GondoPride #GoGondos  @VeniceOarsman @VeniceChamber @VeniceNC @MarVistaBiz @FOMTMarVista… https://t.co/Py1yzzHJ8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to go out in public looking like an idiot. But, I’ve had a long day and I need a drink sooooo #dontlookatme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it be the other way around. Shit ya girl can drive the stick too 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandagolf59 @CaddieNetwork @bubbawatson @jtedscott https://t.co/UUdeQnnzTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s cool they’re showing the original show on https://t.co/XXT4XWjv8d  #ELVISAllStarTribute⁠ ⁠… https://t.co/Lr7YAaZdbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask #God to show u how to love people in your life more. Choose love. #possibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so Kreiking out right now. #nbbathesourcehotel #transatlantique #kreikingoutman #coloradomade @ The Source Hote… https://t.co/BYTryxr6q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Quality Control at ProLogistix #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey so its okay for him to pick and choose which states will get A+ treatm… https://t.co/AQpZAkHPfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLZahniser @dhenricksen Now I’m crying! Thank you for your kind words. LoveU 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[males can’t help but be misogynistic, even when that fine ass has a gun strapped to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, waiting inside Firestone or any other car maintenance shop feels like you’re waiting on a doctor to give you a… https://t.co/HQ5hKkDJDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 WESTOP Conference Last night in Phoenix @ Hyatt Regency Phoenix https://t.co/IrJumH7Hdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 healthcare innovations which are transforming the sector  https://t.co/2dx2K6iQss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN So we know now who is next to be sued🤣🤣CNN get's hit with a 25,000,000+ lawsuit, papers delivered on Mon or Tu… https://t.co/eUPO6Sxydw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You and me both, Mr. President.  You have done an excellent job of exposing the depth of corruption… https://t.co/R1kFx0CSMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys have no idea how much it took to finally be able to play guitar/bass in front of people. I remember the da… https://t.co/HFMkBnAmtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repeat after me....a #GreenNewDeal for Canadians isn’t radical! 👏🏽👏🏽  It is just &amp; it is necessary   #climatejustice #dignity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Bring Back the Wild by supporting this campaign for Brynn's birthday! She has chosen to protect the Piping Plo… https://t.co/f4DxtIqFKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s why we only got to love Mary Jane rn man , she doesn’t do people wrong 🥰🥰🥰💛💛💛💛💛  y te amo bb 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poptivist I wonder what it was like before we were born. That hurts my brain even more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity That cost the taxpayers 2+ years &amp; millions of dollars.  Maybe Mueller himself should be investigated himself for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my cousin😍 Keep the tradition going, so proud of you. Lions forever❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janhasbrouck Thank you!! Finally some research behind what I was trying to say for years especially by the time th… https://t.co/VEmc8cmNtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[FELIZ DÍA DE INDEPENDENCIA 🇩🇴 Celebro este día celebrando a los 12 Dominicanos construyendo un high-tech startup co… https://t.co/x0jGE2DFpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I checked the weather last night and it just said COLD not SNOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who holds the #001 bottle of #LaustSparrow from @dennybarcompany? This girl 🤗❤️😉 https://t.co/z26jh8YrH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you were never taught to chew with your mouth closed, and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AussieDebBell @TalkToMeForReal @NAudrey_ST @ninampls @LegionBobo @minhtngo @BulldogBen @lc1_summit @CIAnderson3… https://t.co/Kmzvnd1p7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#disneyonice #100yearsofmagic #birthday highlights bday #traditions  #loved #mulan piece of the show… https://t.co/XXOISz4lZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiThinks You can dream- AARPs work in nutrition education in AL is worthy though : )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyre_mella It’s so awesome to have children grow up with animals. Teaches them compassion for others ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with Mike Gault and the #thehighwaymen Netflix team in the presidential suite @ Four Seasons Hotel Austin https://t.co/goKkpQzXn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Falls in Arizona were amazing. I didn’t think I could be so overwhelmed by anything after The Grand Canyo… https://t.co/54gtVoYWYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s snow place like the slopes. @ Arizona Snowbowl https://t.co/8tSs2LO6Ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Pamela and Gabrielle from Student Affairs and Franco Puggle the dog from the Teaching Technology cente… https://t.co/Ar8fQheeXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing that blocks your blessing is unbelief - pastor @stevenfurtick 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun's new chest harness....I'm trying to adjust it....and he's not helping 🥴 @ Warrenton, Oregon https://t.co/VGGdHMb70N]]></document><document><![CDATA[the purest part of my day is when these middle aged men came by while we were setting up tabling and asked if they… https://t.co/rSyVdcR4hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the epitome of a true public servant!  A Police Chief dedicated to his community.  @FloridaChiefs commends… https://t.co/TQdobqE7LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world, headed ba k to work again. For anyone who cares I have not worn a bra for 2 days. It has been v… https://t.co/ZRHBzrgCME]]></document><document><![CDATA[To anyone complaining about the #emergencyalert last night https://t.co/p8029TRpsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PowellEPISD Teacher of the Year is....Ms. Holt!!! So very well deserved! Congrats Ms. Holt! @ELPASO_ISD https://t.co/X9VYSNEtSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatkhalid hey you’re talented as fuck and my mornings wouldn’t be the same without having your songs on repeat. bless your soul sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunoAmato_1 @realDonaldTrump Math or Science not of interest to corrupt @GOP supporters of #TrumpCrimeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[so thankful to have a great group of friends up at behrend. i couldn’t imagine college without them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottdeluzio my listener was better than yours 🤣🤣. But her had a lot of questions about what I was talking about… https://t.co/kSfCYmuWyS]]></document></documents></author>