<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@OU_Football @TheKylerMurray and the first of many breakdowns on who will be the MOST analyzed player in the 2019… https://t.co/hfjXBJosqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the news here? It always seemed to be operating under the influence! #nielsen #outsidetheboxthinker Reuters https://t.co/yvxi94tiOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the #SuperSnowMoon shines over us tonight, we are thinking of our 2018 #EJKAward Writer Honor, Rachael Cole for… https://t.co/sFuzvFWco6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye Reggie, our bodies weren’t ready, but you deserve the best your family can get with you ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKitchener I'm British, parents worked in Hong Kong in 78, so I was 3 in the city and I have weird memories of how busy it was]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is only one day left to help us reach our goal of raising $50,000 for the leukemia and lymphoma society! My f… https://t.co/P2RdZoWglf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hiring of Sarah Isgur @CNN an embarrassment to journalism. This right-wing hack is a GOP operative and former… https://t.co/ZczCmvUNgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapiwa81 @jj4t12win10 @SLAMonline Dwight belongs in the HoF imo. He was the best center in the NBA for a stretch.… https://t.co/VDdSg3Qpft]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GamersNexus nice summary. Hadn't heard of Eden Projects. Happy to share #SomethingPositive with you. https://t.co/lcyL717nf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its Twitter is mind boggling. That lady I told you about, pops up every now and then. I don’t know how it hap… https://t.co/e4NWPrzHys]]></document><document><![CDATA[It punches you straight in the face with chocolate and orange! - Drinking a Mandarin Chocolatier by @OOBBC at… https://t.co/E2EnGlSyqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand how people don’t believe #LeavingNeveland. Granted it’s not a true documentary and from one… https://t.co/HYnbPK8Pi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy Dances the Cha-Cha Slide in Style | Cha Cha King https://t.co/6VFSokVibv via @YouTubein case u really wanted to… https://t.co/x75WxoDRkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unbelievable how much different this team is when @SDinwiddie_25 is playing #My6thManOfTheYear]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning folks! Have a Fabulous Friday. Coffee first. Then work. ☕️♥️😊 https://t.co/Kfmh7opXV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so they aren’t airing the full #RKelly interview till tomorrow at 8pm. Just enough time for me to catch it before I have to Dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaCutchin @TheUFOTrail @berniemooney Ha childish behavior 🤣 yep sums up the old guard .]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a literal salsa convention happening directly below my hotel room. 💃🏻 Less fiesta, more siesta porfavor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKSpxshooter11 @tedmadden @junior_miller Meh, all that foam he’s eating is  gonna kill him. Joke’s on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grad school goals #phdlife @SamGubitz @kumarhk @daragaines_ @WsneadIII @_thaWRIGHTway @JZPhilosophy https://t.co/QwotSYoz9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @teeheeheemcfee Except for espionage, the Rosenbergs were exemplary Americans LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njhorrorcon March 29-31 showboat_hotel Please welcome the great @ShannonElizab to New Jersey Horror Con and Film F… https://t.co/tUmr4OT3hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linkara19 will we get to see you and another champion play a children's card game for the Contest in future storyline segments?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is @CNN’s newest hire...what a joke. I wouldn’t leave cnn on the tv for my dogs at this point!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the point of this hearing? We already know he’s a liar... he’s even going to jail for it. He’s not introduc… https://t.co/wmj0CX3rSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you have a lot of nerve...you should have several seats! @ananavarro]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨OFFER ALERT @Gaucho_Football True Freshman WR @Chosen1_ya picks up D1 offer from @SHU__Football ‼️ @CoachMac1… https://t.co/5sqAPl0cvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSUFrank A 31-0 loss at Miami as the #1 team in the country in 1988 (this is why the Seminole Rap still gives me nightmares).]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Jersey: banning armor-piercing ammunition, limiting magazine sizes to 10 rounds, allowing guns to be temporaril… https://t.co/jeXcklu8uZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super tough night. Laid our Mister to rest as cancer took him far too young. A misunderstood breed of dog that made… https://t.co/6iCZsVzRiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3..  @GreenBoysBball 45.  @PurpleNGoldCrew 26. https://t.co/BIKpOwXSuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[TBT Author Tommy Anderson with actress and Author Patricia Tallman. If you have not read her book Pleasure Threshol… https://t.co/v8nqEsgWi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPNational @RadioFreeTom @GOP @TheDemocrats Fastest growing party in the nation and most popular among millennials.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dexter is back on Netflix and none of you jagweeds told me. https://t.co/btHbEIrRc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have playing the Trojan name my whole life, time to switch sides. Im coming home.... #CoachCarter]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is NOTHING cool about that !!!! Nothing.... he should be arrested IMMEDIATELY !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boiler_Nick @ASAPNOSMOKE_SNN @Garbo824 @CBBonFOX @umichbball @TexasTechMBB @ZagMBB @MSU_Basketball @NevadaHoops… https://t.co/qFoEDsPlzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuincyFouse @itsdanielleruss @PeytonAlexSmith @theofficialclee You all were Incredibly Terrific 💫💫💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[He saved you and me because he was willing not to save himself. Thank you God for sending Your only begotten Son (J… https://t.co/mXA29sFLqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMassLiberty For me, First Reformed was the best of 2018 by a mile. Leave No Trace, Mandy, and You Were Never Real… https://t.co/igZY0Q7jTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do you not know? Have you not heard? The Lord is the everlasting God, the Creator of the ends of the earth. He wil… https://t.co/7nAZkowMST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Disturbed for a great night at @KeyBankCtr https://t.co/h1KUbzbaUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgolivares9 It is a little Snow Flakey of Will if you ask me...A lot of these Twitter Talking heads are threatened… https://t.co/sn71K0UXWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Here's an idea Ed. Kill babies, allow criminals rapists and killers to cross the border… https://t.co/BTp2LXKTuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@technosailor I’m not saying I don’t see people talking about it. I’m asking who is making it the focus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worktoon KATO!! Look at you doing big things, this is an awesome article! 🔥👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @UCWV for hosting and sponsoring the 2019 March for Babies Kickoff Reception. We are set to go. March 11t… https://t.co/QHCY1UYBbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoneboneJay @jpdonahue @Ny_youngster21 @tates5a The last Democrat to even come anywhere close was Clinton in 1992,… https://t.co/w0oDVAVaCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordyCulotta I think your boy Will is done you even have @mspears96 on tv on his but]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethMacFarlane I can only imagine that poor kid having all kinds of mhmr problems as he ages.  Kids probably tease… https://t.co/RjzbYCLgOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyTheTrademark You have to put Mish @wrestlingsoup right up there. We work our butts off because of your support.… https://t.co/WIbIGXrmAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peep @samrushenberg, your local celebrity (me) &amp; my amazing cowlick in the bottom left 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not having to pay the broker's fee in NY is basically like getting a bonus at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeafsLoyalty I wonder if those chants is what Arthur thinks was heard during Lindsay moment of silence?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the lights off and room medium cold #southernu_rys19 #fisk_rys19 #Tuskegee_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to our camera operator Jordan this morning. @BrettThackABC27 and I both have massive headaches and didn’t kno… https://t.co/dvnMgZU96p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonland_ I actually hate Kobe’s game and think he’s overrated af, AI would be viewed like Russ in today’s game… https://t.co/lEaEmmFQzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey I just watched 2 straight OT games in person so why not another...Oregon v UCLA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plowed again until sunday......Another foot is on its way.. then we still have March!!!!! #WinterForDayz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both @FrederickMelo and @RebeccaNoecker have given shoutouts to the Highland Villager today - when I moved to St. P… https://t.co/wFmtiV8uX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc  Just sayin Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest to see more... @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/UK7IWKqNnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_vivabella @whereshismother I swear, it’s like Jerry Springer on my feed lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iluvlar are you at #UFCPhoenix and are you golfing with @JodieEsquibel tomorrow? LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memes #memesdaily #progressive #dank #dankmemesdaily #dankmeme #crossovermedia #tampa #miami #orlando #capecoral… https://t.co/LpjWy9KojM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE From this point forward, the name of the highlight segment of shows has been changed from “main even… https://t.co/rFsUKuqEzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ReedAlbergotti hired by @washingtonpost to cover consumer electronics: https://t.co/MJgloK1zLq https://t.co/DvUqglIJbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[pro-tip: if you see something like “can cause” or “may lead to” a bunch of times in a work that’s trying to convinc… https://t.co/9brHhPKF8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for De'Andre Hunter for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/8qWku7ApVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexjandro_n De hecho, el autocorrector hizo de las suyas, seguramente pertenece a la mafia del joder xD .... debe… https://t.co/tN6GyvABlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[IP Cam Viewer captured snapshot: Camera 1_2019-03-04_133642.jpg https://t.co/lwgwWjAPWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsabelleLaisia @lolofrench13 @PaulMaxit Le délire du « grand solar minimum » revient régulièrement. Soupirs. https://t.co/EaIAVJKQPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice the under holds!  3-2 early with the rubber band off game a Winner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out at boys wrestling Masters meet. Busy day of postseason action for winter sports. We have boys and girls wrestle… https://t.co/yLbIoIBZx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do not need to overspend to live by a matcha bar  And there is no reason to live in a dangerous neighborhood be… https://t.co/Vrnm6j1Xvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The March 13th @SueFoleyMusic show is now sold out! #blues #thebestjukejointupnorth @ Lavigne Tavern https://t.co/HB6Q76bwxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt that is pathetic! Drink some more coffee and stay up all night and get your head out of your ass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of business is #supplyanddemand Also remember folks never cut off your nose to spite your face. Colorado… https://t.co/jLNf0wDvKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino if the Donald is not re-elected, Plan A: move to Medellín Plan B: find a tall building]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let alone developers. Some of the above really DO care, and those that do have never shied away from a more inclusi… https://t.co/GC1XibqlQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ke9v @NHLJets @NHLJetsNation Once dated a Winnipeg girl. Her dad was a ham too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaarreaza Pero porque las rechazas deberían estar feliz... ustedes no se la pasan despotricando de Estados Unidos… https://t.co/sHXj8s6Zg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasonMoyersTX Congrats on your well played game today. Merseyside 4 Humberside County 0.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Lost PA, FL, OH, WI, MI, MO, NC, etc. basically every contested state. You Hillary would have run with t… https://t.co/i72Yi5kqXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WismerTrashCry @mikesherov @varjmes @ag_dubs @MylesBorins @buritica @emilyst cal.invitetodayintwenty.nosubject]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Nugget Nectar by @TroegsBeer @ Blarney Stone — https://t.co/Drvcm6Ivdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JunkAboutMovies @NateTheReed @KevinRBrackett @FilmInquiry @NextBestPicture @InSessionFilm @MMandOscar @imdbjourney… https://t.co/H0Y3HjoE5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbsteeno Odd since Reed appears to have been coaching himself this far this season.  Is it actually possible that… https://t.co/TFesmNPYFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this talk about spring fishing has me seeing RED! @vmchooks @TackleWarehouse #ikescustomink #demon https://t.co/CW6sPkIgLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump So sorry for the loss of your beautiful daughter Andrew and for all the hate you… https://t.co/7jizuuZV1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeboF22 @Babchik @EvCoRadio @AGBerg12 @UCONNAl @CMarq23 @BdalFal @IanBlairFal @ColinRichard73 @McGeaux… https://t.co/DTPUTD8HAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atxconcert @spurs #GoSpursGo any players going make the trip to #atx 4 #sxsw ? 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mira lo que me acabo de probar @EmilioCobosc  #muero https://t.co/U5tI04L8w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafstallions  getting ready for the game!!! Feels a little weird wearing blue at rice but I can get use to it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA cloudy all over. W Adams District; Culver City; 101 F’way, DTLA. Soundtrack, Nicholas Britell, Agape’, Beale Str… https://t.co/ZoCHgWL8bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so tired that i was looking for my phone while i was scrolling through twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beardgang me needs this coffee for a #rainymorning #husbandsofinstagram #husbandandhusband @ The Empire State Buil… https://t.co/z8kbtRYd43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ajsw_ @nephew_time @TheFutureKid23 @Aye_Jaden @SwavyTeeAndJays @JordanSw_ 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billsaberafl WE ALWAYS for some new 🔥, bruh! 👊🏻 Keep it POPPIN’- we’ll keep it BANGIN’!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. Okay. FEMA Chief Brock Long Leaving Agency He Led Through Deadly Storms https://t.co/jwQnmJtQdZ via @bpolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people be saying “TFTI”  Look, I didn’t even know I was coming here either.]]></document></documents></author>