<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@InfiniteWaters Love your videos!  ❤️❤️❤️We are not defined by others opinions #cutting negative people 🙏like breat… https://t.co/QBPcnTgeab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nose. Chin.        Nose. Chin @ Old North Boulder, Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/SWLsc4BQ9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lubrio @NituPerez Pero tampoco es policía americano,no es el uniforme correcto,,esto es una imagen hecha para el publico,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing customer "you lost weight Candice" Me "I have" Amazing customer "Everything ok?" 🙌 This is how women should… https://t.co/85abP2ooKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaLMorrison @Mcnellie40 @participate @wakelet Thanks for sharing, Mia!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are snakes in the house. They don't want to start a real conversation. They want to overturn our values. Let'… https://t.co/3VKSpJW30Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when I would sleep on the edge of the bed because for some reason I thought it was more ladylike to give… https://t.co/SiWwvknz8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smrolecom Buying followers is against Instagram's Terms of Service and can cause your account to be shut down. I w… https://t.co/OipjSw6ltD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilSweetLin @krassenstein No, I found out that you can’t win b/c MAGA ppl were vicious to me for saying let’s wait… https://t.co/CCDzoaGLAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acho mó engraçado essa gente nada a ver que nem fala ctg mandando “traz presente” KKKKKK tipo???? oi turubom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msheatherwebb I too find spending time in nature essential for mental balance and to refill the creative well! I'm… https://t.co/Us1X2mxYNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe I will...&amp; same to you!! #khscdAnd @KnightdaleHS https://t.co/i6UGCOu7U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love a day of nothing! #snowday @ Murphy's Place https://t.co/deURURQ6nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micheIIejung @seIfiedump Omg 😂 the lighting and mirror angle are just so unflattering LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FusionPhysEd @physedreview @MrSpringPE @PhysEdDepot @justybubPE @Mr_C_PE @MrRoosPE @LynnHefele @CapnPetesPE… https://t.co/QYHcfUXxRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS THE LAST FRIDAY AT THE 858 STILL!! Help us send it off before we move! 🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline @BarackObama Miss him every damn day https://t.co/kmyFYgRBj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downsizing is my new 'mood'. It's amazing how much you accumulate over time &amp; how little you really need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweat it out. Stretch the legs. @Brea8K #run #walk #sweat https://t.co/GyivuD8EWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time in 2015 dylan sprouse answered my instagram dm and i think it was the peak of my life https://t.co/Et6LKHOw1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post-work decompression (@ Stanford West Whiskey Bar in New York, NY) https://t.co/wZLec9XH89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was #jlo #grammys upset and acting like a Diva! Get the scoop  https://t.co/vpRV0BGVAA https://t.co/lu7rGZfhoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi chiquito hermoso cumple 6 años hoy 😭😍😍😭 no saben lo feliz que Tony nos hace a mi familia y a mi! La verdad creo… https://t.co/aj4QWWBL1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_Veez Terrible from beginning to end. Nigga said it took an hour. 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Rico_llama remember when you used to harass me in the hallway every day with this bs 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Bill is it possible that Jared is n has been under deep investigation like wire tapes n deep undercove… https://t.co/Txnlcp1veP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caniac1236 oh no i know. but you have to admit there are things that are done right in front of their faces that s… https://t.co/4bsMIhkF1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noxime Pas si pire ! Imagine : moi j’ai du me tapper les Teletubbies avec mes filles !]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was truly a golden era. They just stop breeding stout strong race horses in favor of speed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@immigrantdfndr @realeftypickit @JeffHarperArt @dafactsjack @khimmelfarts @chriswhiz4u @Narc_Problems @tymanmayo… https://t.co/n0XYFz0TWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a:  ⚪️ Man  ⚪️ Woman  🔘  A cold bitch  Looking for:  ⚪️ Women  ⚪️ Men  🔘 literally ANY form of warmth or sunli… https://t.co/Hg7IWbNKZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BxglL @ChicagoPenguin2 @RidenerTina @sannbs @CSonafelt @72cricket @sharon_schwan @MrsSpuds @ACog1984 Well that sucked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I buy beast merch for my fam to support the guy- heck yeah 😂😂! Love the content @MrBeastYT https://t.co/pMUmgYqDAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SellingAllLV @B1U3DR4G0N iono, man.. there's a lot of questionable game play going on throughout the whole video.. 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago! So proud of this team and their accomplishments(including our first inventory last night!) Excited to… https://t.co/H0EfpM6Zgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 50 nations will take part in day of action | The Bargain Hunter https://t.co/quxfwia8UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATWWDpodcast how @xtineschiefer's trip to NOLA actually went: https://t.co/wIMEkSN0Px]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know im late to the game but i finally watched bohemian rhapsody last night and OH MY it gave me all the feels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello - Adele - Live at Arena di Verona - May 28, 2016 https://t.co/bl2bmVwnXp via @YouTube ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day.  It is an honor to work with all these beautiful souls in making the world a bette… https://t.co/ti9jWqWEl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[even tho i love and trust my bf with my life i wouldn’t tell him something personal that someone asked me not to sh… https://t.co/xBGcgPW1ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOTH of you would NOT have the cushy jobs and the big PAY checks. Shut up, we WILL NOT become SOCIALIST just to ple… https://t.co/NQXk79BqpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A much needed hula hooping @teekitweet filled distraction 💙⭐️💙 https://t.co/hvbVQ1k3jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx @CHLebedinsky .. and yes great advice from @ElisaC on the #financialgrownup #podcast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden I sure would like to see a Biden/O’Rourke ticket for 2020. Both of you are very knowledgeable, experience… https://t.co/1pX2L3NM1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost I will always remember this teens face and how saddened it made me feel...I will always remember this tee… https://t.co/TN5IT35vUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghansawyerrr Completely! We got a lot of TV writing experience at GU, but no AP writing classes. I had to learn… https://t.co/EEq8x5m4AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[These days I there’s so many politicians using my #vagina as an office that I often wonder if it became another bra… https://t.co/t0FIYRanXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[you see all the time these big dump trucks all the time flipped over or involved in an accident but yet they're all… https://t.co/x3gKOqkaWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradleydevlin @GerryCallahan @UCBerkeley Lucky that wasn’t my son. I’d be on a plane to kick that fat slobs ass. T… https://t.co/qrxpX1tr0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like. People are just inherently sinful and therefore not good and we’ll never succeed but the fact we still strive… https://t.co/WJp6AA4T9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost from @DeanPuch using repostregramapp - Are you impacted by the closure of the 154? Has the 101 commute got y… https://t.co/oO7AVHJZvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[3am Thoughts, A Struggle: How do you deal with the struggle when you’re drinking water and you feel so full, but yo… https://t.co/qQimF2nXdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[me with my new friends !! but specifically @ihatesoggycake bc she interacts with my tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teemcee Her belief system stands against everything I believe in. Yes, she does believe in murdering heart beat ha… https://t.co/hpS1K4JC0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[That boy ain't right. #bostonterrierlife #bostie #bostielove #bostonterrier #dog #dogs @ Denton, Texas https://t.co/gz6SrTlgep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamSpotify on @TheTylt—I stream music from Spotify https://t.co/8hhDetbFkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making clay coil pots with Mrs. Halloway’s kindergarten class and @KMACMuseum https://t.co/sqEIbe02Qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tear down that border wall: Is Beto's battlecry the new Dem litmus test for 2020?   https://t.co/pK6EaAqaQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump But Democrats don't want jobs.  They want free hand outs for those unwilling to work.… https://t.co/88Obeb7gFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzie5197 @msmoon61 @keeshond81872 @twittersecurity @JennyBeth326 https://t.co/dioy4XzjJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBasedMAGA @deplorableWAbre You misunderstood. She’s talking about gerbils, like um not Lille people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShesTeddra Girl bye Jordan knew what she was doing she should have never took her ass to Tristan house period]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so burnt out with dinner like at this point I wouldn't mind sandwiches every night lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kathlee71068501 @blanken01 @MotownJones @BKaysac @POTUS   Unbelievable right? https://t.co/0Kz1H8XYV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Why do you continually bring up Claire McCaskill saying she lost because she voted against Kavanaugh.  Mean… https://t.co/lXYYR3MU2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Twitter friend of mine is grieving and going thru a rough emotional time.  Please pray for her. God knows her sit… https://t.co/zpatp79iWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wind is making it impossible to sleep; the bedroom is shaking with every gust. So when you see me looking bedr… https://t.co/8jv3G6iErW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Beto O’Rourke, well he will never get elected! What the heck is wrong with these people, oh yeah tha… https://t.co/r8MC34hXIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i want is for my husband to rub my back but he stops every 5 seconds🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luxuryladies2 @KDnvrfun I’ve had clients share stories how they were so embarrassed because of the way a provider… https://t.co/q4jlSh3QUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJopinion Shifty Adam Schiff as an obsessed nutcase, blinded by hate and jealousy. He is a liar and… https://t.co/n1LgFE4MPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyJaysComeFirst You and @ravenraginne   Going yo burn in hell https://t.co/0qW8tif7rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[im finna pull a YNW melly 😴 you bitches are gonna learn to stop fuckin me over , i promise .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up and was confused as to why it was so bright. Then I realized it’s because I haven’t seen the sun in like a month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you enjoy 7th grade me after an all nighter and not being able to lip sync for my life https://t.co/rl0wrSiKdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am stranded in Vegas for the unbeknownst future. Now accepting Venmo donations for my gambling fund. @ Allie-DeCastris]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 pcs to use for their event. so even if we can assume every pc is being used at this place, ill say they have 20… https://t.co/SZlkbjioB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same guy that basically said he would kill his kids if they were gay? Shocking 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not trying to be anybody’s employee of the month.  I came here to do my job and collect my check... fuck everything else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaGAGirl @TeriWenzel1 @LisaJohnsonM1 @GatorMom73 @sheri_lynn95252 @CheekyAussieGuy @shergiggles… https://t.co/LtSJTAjOyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeasureMeasure Using the word moonshot is explicitly making exactly that claim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie and the Oobleck, in slow motion. We had a blast getting our hands messy this afternoon! #ReadAcrossAmerica… https://t.co/0pPJ8nm6u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Omg shut up! I’m not defending jordyn at all I don’t know her, but you do know your man and you al… https://t.co/uSyTjEQYSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCUWhiteTrash I went 2 summers ago and loved it. And can’t wait to go back. Only lost my fav hat. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ash_helms for sharing information about your Teacher Externship program with us!  Looking forward to get… https://t.co/CyPqZVc8sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid start to our 2019 Season - all teams in actions getting shutout victories. JVB win 4-0. V Girls win 7-0 V Boy… https://t.co/6O91VjbeOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTChelps Can't get through to Wheel-Trans. Really hope they did not strand me downtown. I have no way to get home… https://t.co/lcu8Ic4IkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous women showing off the #AlexissSwimwear difference ➡️ https://t.co/EhAq1cIG5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Columbus Bodhi DIPA on tap now. https://t.co/5xUMc4UbVH @ColumbusBrewing #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkelseeey_ @weirdradopinons @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley Yeah, I did. Do you know what ASD is? Autism Spectrum Diso… https://t.co/QCSzEe0a2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends will be at Booth 1218 at #LeadsCon tomorrow. Go hit up @MKdoesmktg and @multidots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, these are what I personally think are Marvel’s BEST movies (not necessarily same as my favorites). Feel free to… https://t.co/BQ9S610YnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport It‘s like he became his own songify/autotune parody generator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruBluTrev @thegalavanter @JohnWren1950 @SkyNewsAust @GOP We're on it. I'll hold you and your country in my though… https://t.co/kw1ekqpOg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s funny how ppl wanna play the victim when they realize they made a mistake 😂🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[and if you are able to get that person you should be even more thankful because people spend their whole lives thin… https://t.co/9EGSNQQuvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[this little girl just tucked me in &amp; said “goodnight Whitney I’ll close the door so no one will bother you” my heart ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unboxed the new series 2 of the #Hairdorables #doll that comes in a #blindbox. Once I opened the first four compa… https://t.co/dXKWDO5Z5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wise Words for a Wednesday  #KindnessMatters always 💕🌸 https://t.co/6MBMhdZeVv]]></document></documents></author>