<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And what about the ones who gave the 'GO' for this mess?  https://t.co/QAQ1WLTR2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Feel better brother...I just had back surgery....I'm in pain with ya bro!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When  you the Ace club ready to go home…  but then you hear Wipe Me Down and your LB’s grab you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @LarryNoble_DC Ok. We believe.  Santa is on his way. And the Easter bunny just hopped to the cnn fake news studio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayHagarNV I had been wondering whether you'd be interviewing him on Nevada Newsmakers. (He asked for a correction… https://t.co/16y3JoOrJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venison is the best meat. Apparently there are some weird laws in New York that make it more difficult to find in t… https://t.co/6GMaAuYMeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjohnson175 To be able to get a train from downtown SF to Fresno in a hour in half? Or LA in 2:40? Without having… https://t.co/iXlLC05di0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SagaLudziLodu Nikt nie wierzył dopuki nie zobaczył Teru która podprowadza buteleczkę tabasco i próbuję się dobrać do zawartości :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jschnur32 Its frustrating. He doesn't want big contracts stuck with his kids when he dies, even though they will m… https://t.co/jnfNDWqAJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story behind Jared Kushner’s curious acceptance into Harvard:  This article's 3 years old, but there's a good c… https://t.co/XkYlPDb3dJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @anna_deardorff @Debby_Villegas @SydneyDChase @robin_ked @Michael_Hudak @DrWhoisin @MarilynLavala… https://t.co/LzrR6ZIU5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @therealritty23 @Larrybarnett777 @Serremmy @tammy_maga  @Briteeye777 @WickedVfl @RevKeithBritt… https://t.co/FbEvWjx0R9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdvector @4YrsToday Yes, and your observation is taken in the obvious sincerity of your comment.  Also, if there w… https://t.co/HOiRXyyBY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaCastro_ Maybe we will FINALLY get that “Paris” song they teased on Married to Jonas before they broke up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain is a four letter word. #rainraingoaway #winstonsalem #noahsark #blameitontherain #wemisssummer @ Winston-Salem… https://t.co/8K90BfA2gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamGMJohnson Yes. "Guilty until proven innocent" has always been our tried and true legal standard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherMerry Sure, it's called the victim mentality. And it's unhealthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go! #fashion #suitsandsneakers #swanman @ W Scottsdale https://t.co/h535bwu334]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary 8 years ago! https://t.co/ZvdtOud6G5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday, March 8. Session 1 begins 11:00a   #RoadtoRoanoke | #GoMountGo https://t.co/L4HzmmpcBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The subject of the sanctuary should be carefully examined, as it lies at the foundation of our faith and hope.”—The Advent Review]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digit makes a plan.  @outfest  #outfestfusion #Outfestpoc @ Egyptian Theatre https://t.co/NzyfpHBwDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what kinda toaster y’all got but mine never comes out lookin like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdriannePalicki @TheOrville @FOXTV I CANT WAIT Ahhhhh!!!!! That line at the end “set course for Earth” gave me GOOSEBUMPS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSessler Just pretend you are going to a very private Daft Punk concert being played on an Atari 2600.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She was going crazy when she was jumping on the dick” 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😂😂😂😂😂🤣🤣🤣😭🤣😭🤣🤣🤣😭....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each time I see Trump and his cronies in an instance of brazen criminality and corruption, I can’t help but to thin… https://t.co/klhdliCuxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to God’s great Goodness, we are short on desserts on a weekly basis. It’s at the point that we are in need of 5… https://t.co/kKMP4u5CAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time it went off I got a chill and my heart felt like it was getting punched]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceWolfChi His grabbing Ed Ames to keep him from quickly removing the hatchet + waiting several beats before doi… https://t.co/ItaScA1bW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjmctr @RealJoeSoldano @bern_04 @DenisCoderre @jaysonst @MLB @Buster_ESPN My sense is MLB would be happy to move t… https://t.co/6cerdL4tLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabinho-Henderson-Wijnaldum   vs.   McTominay-Herrera-Pogba  TIME FOR BATTLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckonSports Finally going to get some poker action. Stopping by the @RGPokerSeries @Horseshoe_BC on the way home… https://t.co/sOEXzeVdoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic stuff from the @Lionesses! Amazing how far women’s football in the UK has come. When I left 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁥󠁮󠁧󠁿 for… https://t.co/8cupat0yex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyAdrianaMa2 @jairbolsonaro Falou em direita, falou em trabalho vcs ptralhas tremem né? Acabou a mamata, vai ch… https://t.co/Drmxuc9QzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas get your tickets at https://t.co/c0ZfzU2vD6. They warned you about the Ides of March for a reason. See ya soo… https://t.co/j8XDHUmnVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had minor surgery yesterday.  All good!  Our 3 year old g-daughter Auden wanted to accompany me “so you won’t be lo… https://t.co/53HlGobXWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do kids these days never follow their shot, so many lost opportunities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 NCAA tickets punched!  Heck of a season for this freshman!  On to Pittsburgh! #GoBeavs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @ATCTapelife for your leadership and your commitment to our student-athletes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man, I think I accidentally commented on a college soccer player’s Instagram story. That’s embarrassing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSantilli_16 @Oscar86604735 @BoydBoydr @_IsaacBecerra @nlobato579 @BrendaLemcke @EricJBaker4788 @davidwilsonlbk… https://t.co/0nQa1k3hCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @highlinejeweler CALIFORNIA DIAMOND PENDANT 1.58cttw 💎  #jewelrydesigner #highlinecustomjewelry #custommade… https://t.co/ixWldGDfWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let us not forget, that which is found can also be lost once again! We must strive to stay found lest we become lo… https://t.co/lzySnkYLGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusGrayDoor @GilbyRanger @drewsaplin Looking forward to what's cooking this time around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from office  https://t.co/2KMboSXJZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghostlyjawa @AtheosXI I don't know much, but I sure as hell know how to make a damn good bowl of yogurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsgoFlyers95 Balor was down. Lashley was sizing him up. Rush was knocked down outside but came and got on the to… https://t.co/GYC4xWGKsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to lunch and it was like walking into #Galway. Isn't St. Paddy's Day 9 days away?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Goldsboro, North Carolina https://t.co/CzNdSfjo4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AdriSutes was questioning why I count the #Monorail as a ride and not the transport boats. I said because the Mon… https://t.co/JNrjqIiSCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor Obama admin got Lois Lerner to take the fall and then dropped any further investigation - Why? -  Because… https://t.co/lvwmHbrz2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desdelparque @infobae Si Luis estamos re felices , me podrías decir cuantos hijos adoptivos tenes #hipocresiarelig… https://t.co/ktFCx9ZfEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One most of the snow melts, but before they open it to cars, I'm thinking about hiking up the Platt Clove Road in West Saugerties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Butterfly_Trish @AMSidwell @ksdknews @JennSullivanTV @AllieCoreyKSDK @WthrmnSlaughter @JessicaKSDK Good morning 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ye mum makes you breakfast in bed and your dads jealous and starts to show love to me mum]]></document><document><![CDATA[You won’t see many worse losses than Miami blowing a 14 point lead to and AWFUL Wake Forest team]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one: co star morning notification: oh you think you know emptiness? you’re not even CLOSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NY primary turned his campaign into an ersatz MOVEMEN Tlargely personality driven.Isupported till Octoner 22 20… https://t.co/Ta7jizImRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BR_NBA Too bad he isn’t feeling his new team! His interests have ruined his legacy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting a chance to finish #maniac on Netflix. It got lost in my watch list :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislexis17 You got an iPhone so you think you see things clearly now, I understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[call-out ANY AND ALL WRONGDOING AND THE TROLLS ASSOCIATED WITH IT!   I am embarrassed as an INDIVIDUAL REAL MAN tha… https://t.co/cjIzxDEGj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Venezuela isn’t enough proof of the abject misery, loss of freedom, and literal loss of life that socialism and… https://t.co/KyJ5zqAONf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resting sad face. Or he may really be sad as his human is away. #dog #dogs #springerspaniel… https://t.co/bBKMcKJnxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell Socialite #FranciNeely who accosted a #Houston family during a family photo shoot celebrating their da… https://t.co/9yitYCdoNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important study by @UNCMJschool @UNC about “news deserts” and the crucial role of local journalism @knightfdn https://t.co/eC2gQjdo5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd @WhitlockJason Will go down as one of the WORST teammates of all time .. suck a diva batch]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When Democrats get the opportunity to run this State, it has always led to huge problems”. The great fmr. NJ Gover… https://t.co/SAiWAItNP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapturingChrist @jwarnerwallace We have one of our small groups going through it right now. So far it’s been an ex… https://t.co/y8hKpRscRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomKurds @cerullianblue @betsy_klein @jaketapper @rabrowne75 So what exactly is your proposal? We topple the A… https://t.co/hkOcB77dC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClickKlentak People always ask me about Sixto and would I have traded him. I ask all those people, "Do you miss Ky… https://t.co/aETTGozhLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[She asked me why I don’t contact her anymore. Yet she’s the one who cut me off. I’m not going to work harder than y… https://t.co/oaI9EK1tAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelercam @_BigBen7 Thanks Carole! It’s from about 5 years ago when he came to Virginia for an autograph show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericboettger56 @maydaymindy9 OMGGGGG ITS HIM💓💓💓 #Doppelgänger #ShaunCassidy https://t.co/tjt3Us1vRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davempayne @bryce @indievc I really enjoyed his presentation in Atlanta. It was an attractive proposition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see how much snow we get and how long it stays! 😂🌵 @ Casas Adobes, Arizona https://t.co/ud4kcaEU2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway Hopped on the F for my first transfer home, and it decided to run on the A. I was fine until the conduc… https://t.co/wIragnHX5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickyVobby @SportsCenter @NBA Got ball before he ever touched him https://t.co/XnE8FBVQ0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whatsforlunch @dinnerbyrob  Bruschetta Chicken Pasta Penne Pasta | Homemade Bruschetta with Basil | Blackened Chic… https://t.co/Mdd2St4lxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very frustrating when @cvspharmacy sets expectations and then doesn’t honor them! Wouldn’t hurt to mix in some cour… https://t.co/WQiqw5OtHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot. 8 year memory from Facebook about my epic beard. And a trophy. https://t.co/Cdu4asiD5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne Bless you and your wife. Thank you for sharing this important tragic story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HotMovies @JadeKushXIII @KendraSpade @VinaSkyy @lexigirlxxx88 @jakeadamsxxx @VanWyldexxx @mikequasar Watch the BTS… https://t.co/TuTWpba6lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader bribery is an impeachable offense and have proof, you're going end just like Cohen said badly. https://t.co/RZrrr2KU6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKarrG0 @rloyola Do you get a participation trophy? ... I could have mentioned you in my column but I’m still learning everyone’s name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back aboard the @pdxwinterhawks bus, on to Kent. https://t.co/G2iFX9jfdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennyfergerson He’s a goofy looking Mormon with a great beard and unbelievable skill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[bolivar police dept. you are a fucking disgrace. you showed zero empathy and acted like a bunch of dicks to this DY… https://t.co/JpYNp2ftyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShayPhD Really scared of heights.....don't like elevators n speeding at 110 mph....but love liver n onions hah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXIScott @kamenta @WPXITraffic @WPXIJoe @DanielleDozier @JenniferTomazic 👎 👎👎 https://t.co/WZEmn4vOVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAverageDad @TapirTom @bpilk10 @NatGeo BOM civilization starts closer to 2000BC when accounting for the Jaredites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stand Tarlov. Her voice alone is irritating. Her logic is something to be desired. Always against or fines fa… https://t.co/yFXESwMpfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into schwarzenegger two years in a row at the @RedCon1Official Festival, this time at the @ruleoneproteins/… https://t.co/kX5YCL7qT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMarshall_ @BryanWeigel @fccincinnati @SBLasso5 and I will be the Emerald City for the season opener.  Thanks for the heads up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLionsMan Stafford Isn't Going Anywhere  !! Deal with it. Stafford will retire a Lion !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVNewsHQ How in the fuck do that many people watch Maddow.... Jesus Christ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickstriving You are, and I cannot stress this enough, like amusing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BJ_Glash I like your voice more than I like your face.  Nice work, kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSpain @SpainandFitz I purchased 2 tix to the NHL New Years Day game at The Big House. XMas gift for my GF and… https://t.co/7886MMnE7E]]></document></documents></author>