<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest No! No! Not my hamburgers! Maybe the words are an oblique reference to cattle. So maybe he's saying Dems… https://t.co/1eo5wg9aET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired by pen15show we're reliving the 90s Also found the effect tab on premiereprocc  . .  #friday #funny… https://t.co/CHZRjMJZOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to start 3 amazing days of learning outdoors ☀️ #soundtosea #outdoorslearning #outdoorseabees @Smith_Seabees https://t.co/zJf2NUI00P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to personal reasons, I will be spending an unnecessary amount of money on myself tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tobwabba No mattet what u think the chasm of doom is not out and back, when u thibk u have to turn back, its cause… https://t.co/8xq2SlfLNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eremiticjude But seriously, how dare?  Keelin has this problem with the people across the street. They are very close to HER yard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely love @GlennCloseNews ‘s lavender suit, amid a sea of black and grey. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacket I picked up at Saint Luke’s Thrift store in Manhattan when I was cadet didn’t own a civilian clothes we go t… https://t.co/7LJzM7gTWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i made tortitas and rice but over-salted it but it was still so good because i am so homesick 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @janayshaiann with all of my heart. Thank you for being the best friend 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THELILMOSHOW Aww U got more Patience then a Saint..he's not going 2 change.Let him Go.Your Relationship is not Wor… https://t.co/Koj2KUTqVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Denver General, we had a bat phone in the ER where the paramedics warned us about major traumas on the way (comi… https://t.co/H8mFlKW8pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now I’m here at my appointment, feeing glad I am safe and my car is fine. But I’m also mad for ever wondering if… https://t.co/yXG61SIgXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcCorbishley @Myrtle4441 @The80sForeverrr I was surprised when I saw that .. what an awesome singer from a young age]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helicity I know we just got the websits up and running but maybe an app? Or a way to get notifications when you do… https://t.co/X8px7zLJf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jiggycomedy , mix these in for a healthy breakfast!. It so filling!  And yummy!. https://t.co/TN482hteWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbg1 @EatonRifles1 @NewYorker Like Trudy would  say, nope,  I got nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore also now, saith the Lord , turn ye even to me with all your heart, and with fas… https://t.co/ST4zr3D3OO https://t.co/UZjF42X70u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCM_88 Me too! But I have the flu, so don’t mind not having one this time around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @WhiteHouse Give up your security clearance daddy ordered for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaFi48457694 @rinky539 @JosephNSanberg When there is an influx of refugees seeking asylum, there is always a ca… https://t.co/LtC9zPQznc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s a bird in the ceiling and boobies on the wall” a thrilling new short story]]></document><document><![CDATA[All smiles for the love of my life @djpaulyd 🤩 @ Harrah's Resort Atlantic City https://t.co/5biRKkIaOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Faculty/Staff is amazing and looked liked Queens yesterday. #Wiley_RYS19 #BlackHistoryMonth https://t.co/q0napicPrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Good part of that list, then you know where NOT to dine.  Support businesses that are support equa… https://t.co/beO5McWqUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Real Freeway Rick Ross and Tequila McClinton! #neosoul #instagram #femalerapper #hiphop #northoakland @ Richmon… https://t.co/Em5TPrZTnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny that the ones who feel they run you fold and freak out when you finally say something to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFP What is this????  They are trying to make it seem like he never existed.  He IS and always will be the King of Pop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found my new favorite recovery treat and it seriously couldn’t have come into my life at a better time! 🙏🏻🙏🏻 . I… https://t.co/yFke7s2QF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking out of my hotel in Vegas to see this, made me smile!!  @BillyIdol #ifeelalright #lasvegas https://t.co/yHR6JCtpVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Miami Heat Sunday!!! #magiccity 🔥🔥🏀🏀🌝🌝🌴🌴⛴⛴ #heatculture #miamiheat #lovesundayafternoongames @ AmericanAirlin… https://t.co/7hWZjqhML9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPatanio @LeadersPs74 @SIBOD31 @rckdomingo @inspired31 @Hanin80 @ChristineHanrah It was inspiring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the umpteenth time: We have a sexual predator in the White House. https://t.co/aEuOZ0Cwr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brenden3lee from Twitter shared 5 best practices on using the platform to build your brand story and drive engagem… https://t.co/6RLhdkrwUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grace Place Volunteers!🎉  Mark your calendars for our first GP Team night of 2019 on March 8th @ 7pm! We are going… https://t.co/RGTuFRNIX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! Thank You 🙏🏾 God for another day in your world! Let us praise you with word and song @8:18,9:15 and 1… https://t.co/BvulLeaQkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[making my hair dreams a reality, as usual corrinndoeshair 👑 @ Salons by JC Manhattan https://t.co/X7eC3fvGeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love progress. 💙 #AddisonTX #ActiveAddison #AddisonAthleticClub #StillTheBestKeptSecret]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appears #Cairo, GA has taken a direct hit by a significant tornado and emergency responders are pleading for Mutual… https://t.co/h1M9ZOsuVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEndTimes12 Sorry I don’t have a Facebook anymore. I know the Book Of Revelations! Yes we are nearer than we wer… https://t.co/695q0ysJYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually just had a trump supporter tout that he was the lesser of two evils. Trump supporters don’t know the defin… https://t.co/0G6bjVuwgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia civil rights icon @repjohnlewis named as presenter for best picture Academy Award: https://t.co/akya3ZFOf8… https://t.co/qEWPHsEKuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been in California for almost a week. #Bittersweet #DifferentViews #IMadeIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more because it’s my birthday week and I felt great last night. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/n5zTGadHeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld You all had a great show today....#DonnerPass and all!!! Thanks for all you do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at work I saw a mom and her baby had matching Nikes and my life is complete now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro You MUST post a picture of you in that new dress! I'm so happy for you both]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Orange Wave's last stand? Outremont byelection a critical test for NDP in Quebec https://t.co/O9OySkv1kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home is where we know and where we are known, where we love and are beloved. Shoshana Zuboff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no soy independentista, me considero socialista y republicano, a parte de español y catalán, estoy escuchando el… https://t.co/Ah5stY6JNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a picture of a baby elephant... in case you are having a bad day!! @Geraldineth @YuridiaSalinas https://t.co/G5OI5KHKh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardwwillis I wish she’d play in my backyard!! Highly recommended!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is nick gonna bring back the Nick Jonas Show when they go on tour orrrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the only person I know who will go in the bathroom with the sole purpose of using it only to clean the entire… https://t.co/aJqiCbNlry]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡 🏡 🏡 Looking for new homeowners to call this place HOME! 🏡 🏡 🏡  Check out this stunning one year old home in Cibol… https://t.co/WOYnLMh6yX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @NJ_2_FL @RN_JB7 @liggett1_ @slankard_jeff @speakersamerica @Carry_a_40 @ConcernedHigh @working_tg… https://t.co/TXItx5Iz3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: There will be a @ilovegaam meeting at @glhfgamebar 2nite during Jax Artwalk. We will be discussing future… https://t.co/Eglbd0qH3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popehat Our over incarceration mentality is completely fucked up — lock up the ones who are really dangerous. Big… https://t.co/gyB7pqRjPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaBeardenRD providing @TomballISD staff essential nutrition information.  #eathealthy #PD4me… https://t.co/9mTH2SD8lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[His bitch:Tread lightly bitch because I’m on to you!  Me:lmaooo https://t.co/w9QwfdZrPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That “Too Many Friends” by @charlesmetcalf3 that’s life changing content... 💯🙏 #AllStringsAttached]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaMBBfan @BandB_CBS @CliftonsNotes I no right that is  pouring salt on the worns]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday women own more than 1/2 of the small businesses in the country. Let’s support each other an… https://t.co/VfdnTFxyzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPatanio @CareerConSI @jennlynnshanks @SIBOD31 @vgallassio @Drdididiva @sunflower1967 @DOEChancellor… https://t.co/uLwISXoGYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night left me so hopeful. I spoke to the Singletary Scholars at UK on Immigration,our event and book signing o… https://t.co/kIo9vD5lTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you’re a Democrat and running for President in 2020: https://t.co/SiRzgnhnwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be with someone who is open to all your ideas.  Meet 3 day old Spirit. @ Baker 3 Ranch https://t.co/HjAYcvHSYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misskeela And put their feet in the stirrups, and scooch down! Uh huh! 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fly girl 💅🏽 Hair by: @LoveChrissys  at @chouseofweaves #feedinbraids #dmv #dc @ Northeast Washington, Washington, D… https://t.co/823HwrATM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week I had to drive the robes for my sons’ public high school choir to their performance site while the kids t… https://t.co/T4Ds7ryCnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyofNaveed He mentioned a story about his father being a WW2 veteran. I told him that he should draw on that exp… https://t.co/SQXJylZ1oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit. Like what if it got my families bad genes? I would push it back in so it cooks longer 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found our new vacation home ☀️⛱ @caitlinkowalke @ The Breakers https://t.co/eFDeR4Zf24]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @wgjackso to post pictures of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day I’ll challen… https://t.co/lEk1UdxG1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think about this final text CONSTANTLY. i just wish i was awake and could have helped him. https://t.co/dVaIDgLru7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently heartbroken so I’m bout to make the best music I’ve ever made]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeholdIsrael WE are all God people wants you Belive in the blood of the Lamb Jesus Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinByrd3 @crepeau It amazes me that people actually believe he is broke. There is NO way he is broke. He’s been… https://t.co/u0XAicrdV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter found my Walkman and thinks it’s cool.🤣 #bonjovi https://t.co/iGa2FIl7NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter whites + Wahoo wins   #uva #gohoos #visitvirginia #visitcharlottesville #shotsaroundgrounds @ University of… https://t.co/QiGLxxHlcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being this cute is exhausting and requires many naps apparently #Chiltonthecat  * * * * * * * #cats… https://t.co/R7FUo7oZ44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @Wafflesontherun @mkewman @realDonaldTrump Keep doing a great job Brian!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 big thing — Trump: &amp;quot;The Democrats hate Jewish people&amp;quot; https://t.co/7gZChuhK0G #axiossneakpeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing for warmer weather with KidK and for him to get over this flu ASAP Poor little buddy, just can’t seem to ge… https://t.co/X6tgScsdd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AubieChica Miss tall too . Going on a bus this weekend to Foley to go to shops . A church is sponsoring it althoug… https://t.co/sBGqJ15mzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I respectfully disagree w/ you. Allowing ppl (with no background research to assess their actual ability to pay $ b… https://t.co/nwFfhxh7XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing to prevent intimate partner violence &amp; sexual assault?! #StartTheConvo #PreventionAcrossCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@busybeachmama4 @krassenstein This disease is relentless, if tRump has any compassion he will back off. But we know… https://t.co/PD5zRbRxUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy your stay at Stormy Point Village. Now you will call this place your home away from home! #StormyPointVillage… https://t.co/JhQaFkFpZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjae__ You don’t make me look like a fool on here... you shoulda called me 🤦🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful winter day for a bike ride along the Boise River. Absolutely fantastic to be out on the bike! @ Boise, Id… https://t.co/Xfv2L0R3EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans Thank your assistant from me, for caring. I’m somewhat of a cat lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShivonHusky Hi! What would you like created? Feel free to contact me. I'd love to work with you on this, and my commissions are open.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancinggrizzly @frontdoororback That was terrible way to explain🤦‍♀️... it sounds bad that way. It wasn’t like that 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m from Baton Rouge, so they made fun of you half of the time to see if you have tough skin and that’s pretty… https://t.co/V5opviglpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nice, I had to post it twice! This cozy jacket was a best seller last week. It’s only $30 and comes in a variety… https://t.co/qYpyLLy0gI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to meet some new friends healthypawsvetclinic ! This cool lady gave me some yummys to eat while she made sure… https://t.co/8yqsz2FCCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg the @jonasbrothers are back now I got to put in a lot of hours at both places to get money Incase they go back… https://t.co/wvZqVzElmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the pilgrims super smashed their way to America earning them the victory royale #TheMoreYouKnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poet If I could jump on the Negative 👎Band wagon, this would make no sense. But I ride the positive #Train🚂daily. S… https://t.co/hFvoXdLb2Q]]></document></documents></author>