<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I can feel Spring in the air, and I can't wait for my world to again be green! #828isgreat https://t.co/YD7H843lWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @fair_more Throw his ass in jail. Better yet, let him be stampeded by the heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitStopPerform @JoeyGaseRacing @DISupdates @TylerReddick @weaverwealthnc @ChelseaDeNofa @cody_coughlin… https://t.co/ZbQNlDPN1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrickheadzX @arthurstacy They did the same thing with Iron Man 3. https://t.co/i1dUpgMaC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSinger @Beersforopeners @RampCapitalLLC NYT Spokesperson ⬇️ https://t.co/CPalDOpGeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSIB_Paralegal There's a lot going on. I kept thinking Lynch is making an analogy of the Afghanistan war in the 80… https://t.co/vH81bkMxP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @TheRickyDavila But ChickFilA is still closed on Sunday smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetFitness Btw, at my local club, the GM and staff are really nice. On my behalf she asked corporate if I can o… https://t.co/hYKpZuLfr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo el show de celebración de sus 25 años como comediante victormendezelatrevido felicidades tocayo. en Teatro d… https://t.co/arVqwvS2b1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenverChannel Electric cars are WORTHLESS to most of us in rural Colorado. Why are we wasting MORE tax dollars to… https://t.co/WCpysvokoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stomach pains are fewer and far in between now. But when they do flair up it’s intense. But I’m at least a litt… https://t.co/CNYw4Iio41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends tRUMPS PROPAGANDA NETWORK SLINGING THE BULLSHIT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro my forest get in a relationship or start talking to someone and they completely forget about me🤦🏻‍♂️ this a subtweet for moni and Jenny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Good job Mr. Art of the Deal.  Why couldn't you just stay in your lane and stick with being a fail… https://t.co/32tqQqBY6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think Baxter’s has ever been open on a Sunday, but I cant believe I cant get coffee from there today. The nerve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Not A Scene-y Type Guy When It Becomes Too Much I Gotta Dip. https://t.co/NOyJRmBgCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to always report fake news when you see it https://t.co/McIlunQNOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roXas9620 Actually this happens to me a lot and I get fucking embarrassed like people are watching lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see my little buddy yesterday at the FD chicken noodle dinner. And spendin all day at FD today runnin calls. https://t.co/Ioo6x0NEyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is still time to sign up and join us for this great event. https://t.co/jaSIZhMhiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how old I am. I’m still gonna back a snowball and eat it cause that’s a gift from heaven and you gotta savor that goodness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Raiders made a big move acquiring wide receiver Antonio Brown. He's a great addition to a Raiders offense that… https://t.co/68MNMoxdhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah! Even simple topics, when spoken about by a diverse group (age, gender, etc) will spark new ideas, perspective… https://t.co/MpsccedKvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure my one of my final actions will be a strong case of falsified company documentation related to traceabi… https://t.co/OB4KMoL3y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@othatsraspberry Psh. None of those are Sanji. I don’t even know who you are anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OneMoreAgain - Drinking a Mirror Universe by @fairstatecoop @ Lickin It  — https://t.co/oD9JLUO03q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over, of course! Sez outplowingsnow... RT @ericfisher: Let's put the over/under on Boston snowfall the rest of Febr… https://t.co/EP0u8Bvudk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolynWLKY @WLKY @louisvillemayor Don't build or buy it if you can't afford it! From the bridges to the Yum cente… https://t.co/NSf2Vq8U1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 When my mom quit smoking, she made pies. For one Thanksgiving, she made 8 pies for 6 people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikiRachtman @Metallica What did you think of Bohemian Rhapsody, Riki? Finally saw it, and while the timeline wasn… https://t.co/wdf2AHXHdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reunión del Comité Internacional de Microcréditos de Rotary International y la empresa Finreg con la Alcaldesa de H… https://t.co/UfdhYOzkBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you order a breakfast burrito from @sonicdrivein this is what you get😡! Well at least my tots were cold and me… https://t.co/6Ab0O7zeYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawai_asuna Congratulations on your first anniversary!㊗️🎉 Thank you for all your hard work!🤗💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[For as many times as I do my Euro Step around my house, you would think it would translate a little better on the court]]></document><document><![CDATA[folks be thinking it’s so cool that I’m from Decatur until I tell em Wesley Chapel Snapfinger 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyJMD @keoraborealis Wikipedia says the concept came out of academia https://t.co/2CTj4414kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JediASU @SunDevilHockey @KenDaniels99 @NVPeeweeA1  I want my “PB &amp; Ketchup Forever” shirt tomorrow! lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Bloom- . . . . . . #yellow  #flowers  #zag1  #zag1📷  #bicycle  #cycling  #ibikekern  #activelifestyle… https://t.co/iHzkScWGSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuillermoRojo7 @gmopv1 @samanoarce @qtf Pues ahora en estos 5 años le toca a tu presidente y a ustedes #chairos el… https://t.co/1bfvTockkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohsceola From my buddy @juanctoribio.  Pham and Yandy Diaz were both originally in the lineup, but we’re scratched… https://t.co/twbhfAeR0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...four or five of em pick it up and turn it 90 degrees and do it again,” he explains matter-of-factual.  “Why?” I… https://t.co/T5mcbuKkhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Putin's weaponized Presidential operative is successfully dismantling and weakening the pillars of United… https://t.co/3fIfJNjY0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will somebody please explain how President Trump is a bigot shut up drain the swamp and Hollywood build the wall lo… https://t.co/VM1ehw9P43]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the view of Cherry Creek Dam from Parker Road. It looks like we live on the coast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@offbeatoliv I'm down to five since I found put who my real friends are but I didn't find them on Facebook or Twitter!🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farmers get billions in subsidies and get to control when we wake up and go to bed, got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sidenote: maybe @TheRealMorrison should just settle on one name that he owns the rights to, so fans don't get confu… https://t.co/4J6bfhDpDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @EternityNewsfor a fair summary of the Graham Tour https://t.co/dk9S3Y2aHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day it will get better.... but right now it feels like it’s never going to stop hurting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radio ZS PDF March Edition Available  https://t.co/K35pJmCjNf  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlawjw We should ask @Barnes_Law or @TomFitton.   Guys is there any legal recourse against the criminals who own… https://t.co/ygicsKG1Nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is beautiful, i wish my dad would get this excited and happy to see me ever lml]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Leicas Apparently Saved Photojournalist Gabriele Micalizzi’s Life https://t.co/mdazAz1QAv via @Phoblographer #photojournalist #leica]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know he’s 53, but does he have any college eligibility left? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Country Club, Florida https://t.co/kjwyX8FJ3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, 8-10 at @remedydallas with @greygoose and ianreill1 !! @ Gung Ho https://t.co/zEIsOWnfRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter applied to Oberlin and what she’s gotten out of that so far is a breach notification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe was not at the game He has NO idea 💡 of what was going on Yet he Demands more time off the ice for Priskie Don’… https://t.co/tTAhgAYGNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkHerbstreit Only eating Bill’s Donuts while watching could make it more Centerville 😁 #thebest]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of this is to disparage the genuine goods of the Liturgical Movement! Especially in my context, the restoratio… https://t.co/zRMsYHtrEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you all this Friday! . . . . #music #rnb #soul #singer #songwriter #floodgatesareopen #cajon #nyc #nycmusic… https://t.co/gGBYZ3X8ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gnerphk @realAliTweets Sanders needs to step down now as well as everyone else. There must be no  primary. Hillary… https://t.co/Vue8TAguh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teslatunity @CapitalGrille Happy Anniversary! It’s our anniversary tonight too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro-tip for @wmata riders who just INSIST on standing in the doorway and then get out so others can get in, but the… https://t.co/sY6y8F3Zle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirectorofCIA what's next? Deep state? To friendly with Russia? Sounds like job security may be in question. John… https://t.co/d8CEvmr6jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dking1108 @ArtOfTheFu The warriors got taken to 7 games in the WCF finals last year.... the east just isn’t competitive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikWemple @TuckerCarlson So what. Get a life doushebag. You actually want us to believe, a lefty weasel like U, h… https://t.co/6SaH43C4J9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spanish III students today described their soulmates using the subjunctive #HappyValentinesDay2019… https://t.co/qD5FiGXxoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew Kinville said he’d smack me and beat my ass, that small ass thick chin kid can suck some fucking eggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some People Do Shot Just So They Can Say They’ve Done It.  Rest Assured, If I Tell You About Something I Did, I Wan… https://t.co/MpGbZW5lLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @PeterAlexander Good thing @POTUS landed ahead of the summit instead of after it. Good reporting. Not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This the same heat team that gets bodied by the Suns and Hawks at home??? Sheesh beat GSW last night and now up 12… https://t.co/xwG5RA4TOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A basset hound who listens is a true unicorn of the animal kingdom. Good boy George!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every other song’s about “turnin’ up”, while I’m just tryna chill with you in the cut {📸 x whoiswarrenwhite } @ Los… https://t.co/O37ZlAeLnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[HPMS SPIRIT DAY and visits to Mosaic and Mesnier libraries! @NancySiebum @HancockSupt @AsstSupHancock @jwright9805… https://t.co/Gu8LcnMLKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This message by Reece tells it all about how close this team is. ❤️. And why we advance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But these are my babies.  Hallie my Lab.  Stone my German Shepherd.  #NationalLoveYourPetDay https://t.co/yEJl7fm5Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fadeaway_J24 I know it may not mean much, but from one Utah State student and fan I apologize for the way that you… https://t.co/oXpXITFtED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boombap and samples🎹   #choppingsamples #boombap #beatsession #logicprox #howtosample #undergroundhiphop… https://t.co/ZamJml7uAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re among those who opened their mouth and used their fingers to abuse @MBuhari for jokingly inspecting his w… https://t.co/uHCnJCnbz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[أثني بالشكر جميع أعضاء النادي الكويتي وعلى رأسهم اخوي رئيس النادي/محمد البلوشي ، على عمل يليق باسم الوطن❤️🇰🇼… https://t.co/aLNMjSk6rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottFordTVGuy @SouthwestAir I like #Southwest and I’m glad they are now here at CVG. I’m also a fan of #Delta. I’… https://t.co/BozXP5cvuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only WEDNESDAY?! We have two more days of this bullshit.. https://t.co/A2ThnSxrch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @BernieSanders It’s almost as if....young adults don’t give a single shit that he’s NoT a DeMoCrAt. In fact, it only helps him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6:28pm day 3 • Just left Universal, really fun. We even got stuck on the giant Harry Potter ride. Here are some pic… https://t.co/poAVubWmLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pistyle2013 WAS IN RARE FORM AND READY TO PUT ON A SHOW FOR THE FANS AND SUPPORTERS “PISTYLE” GOT THE INDIE GAME B… https://t.co/ddDjDLJJ6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when everybody was angry at iHop when literally nobody eats there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewkouri22 @LilBabyHos13 Stay calm, it’ll be over soon. I know what you said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zurchmom @KAG1776MAGA @jonz970 @ImabitcSumtimes @Sequencer16 @SealeyGerald @BlueStateSOS @Patti_Sc60 @tweets4poppy… https://t.co/lWL6ioPZRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mombity @NYUEDU Ginsburg will not be with us much longer.  The next president will decide the court.  I'm still never voting for Sanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien toca la canción de Havana de Camila Cabello.  Yo: https://t.co/62WwNoA7Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a good ole fashioned filibuster! Stop the traditional plan at all costs! #gc2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @mlmairro @vladimirpadrino @CeballosIchaso @marcorubio @VP Esto es importantísimo!  Que todos entendam… https://t.co/NQgxecP45C]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is so square and pleasant that not only is it guaranteed an Oscar nomination for Best Picture, it might becom… https://t.co/oVJZKUyNNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nueva casa, nuevo proyecto y mucha ambición para este nuevo reto @halconesobregon @OneWorldSportsG @FairPlayCM… https://t.co/fHV4qYSIqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[funimation: Stand with Vic Mignogna - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/zn0wAUmzpc via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NijxSimone But having a phone with hella screen shots and shit on it of important maps and shit is very important]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señores legisladores de oposición:   ¿Están en busca de una causa?   Impulsen en auténtico Servicio Profesional de… https://t.co/MXxsEDSYfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't like the forecast just wait a day, it'll change 😏-- a wild week of weather (especially temperatures) a… https://t.co/kuBoX1Jc2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big week for me, successfully defended my dissertation on Monday and a paper of mine went online that in very proud… https://t.co/S8dSylfqOR]]></document></documents></author>