<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You know, I've seen a lot of Sherlock Holmes VS Dracula stories but no Moriarty VS #Dracula ones. #SherlockHolmes #Moriarty]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Madness... lets go 💚🍀🎂 #March18 #Birthdaymonth https://t.co/qm2VCUc8vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAX_ALA @ScarlettGroup @AppleOneJobs @wellsdrew @deximaging @OrangeLegal @iVentureFL @MissElocke Such a great time… https://t.co/lzSAEml0oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have the bestest best friend ever 💕👌🏻 @MadeleineRose8 https://t.co/YogzhVFTFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sympathy4TheDr @UTHealthSA So deserved! Congrats. So proud to have trained you when you were a wide-eyed resident at @UTHPMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay como mil cosas que prefiero hacer antes que mi tarea. Como morirme, por ejemplo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayleena earned her yellow belt with special recognition! I’m so #proud of her and jealous bc she made it look too… https://t.co/ZAGMtmxg58]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethiopian Airlines crash: Does the Boeing 737 have a design flaw? | DW News Is the same #DesignFlaw that caused the… https://t.co/65FLRfghYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short People Problems no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-con https://t.co/Qnj22fvGix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rory finally discovered the frogs. • • • #frog #frogs #dartfrogs #dartfrog #azureus #dendrobatetinctorius… https://t.co/ML1Li2Zilg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity we are praying daily and hard for you that this nonsense will be halted by the mighty Hand of God soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart genuinely hurts #RIPLukePerry @CW_Riverdale family and friends 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[FriYay!!! Back in LA for a few until I take off again for Ohio. Have an amazing weekend everyone. Xoxo 😘  Photo:… https://t.co/ylMSYiRcZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get this party started right 🎂🎊🎉 #sydneyandsedric18 #debut #18thbirthday #18 @ DoubleTree by Hilton Ontario A… https://t.co/7tnCJrPRtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you girls I argued with in middle school about Zack vs. Cody and y’all all clowned me for choosing Cody, I’m… https://t.co/Y8y09anb6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an important question, and something I want to explore in Revenance events.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this book! My mom is always quoting @donMiguelRuiz. She’s read it a few times. 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bodypump #bodybuilding #bodytransformation #womenthatlift #lovemyself #strongbones #liftheavy #dontgiveup #fitness… https://t.co/waKo1De0ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always wonder who im going to settle with, either someone new or someone i’ve already crossed paths with.. damn the world may never know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your administration has committed crimes against humanity by kidnapping children from their parents.  RETURN THE CH… https://t.co/fZlwcsCCSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this song Puzzle Pieces by @framinghanley   https://t.co/U7SW6dlglW https://t.co/v7MXubPcRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Bro @dreamteamsf stay looking out 🔥 a lot of y’all grew up watching my glo up and now you don’t support smh… https://t.co/TjqBLjb99m]]></document><document><![CDATA[High school was always lit on this day ! Everyone wearing red and blue and carrying the Dominican flag, lets not fo… https://t.co/8HmBcS6oZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pimpfriedrice_ Hope you feel better soon I just got over it too. It was brutal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband took me on a very expensive valentine's day date yesterday.... to the hospital for surgery! I cant belie… https://t.co/KwqZsPtWek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got an urban decay liquid lipstick for $3 at tj maxx. Today is a good day 🌸💄]]></document><document><![CDATA[03/05/2019: We had a very special day celebrating an amazing and loyal friend, LaTianna Will, who just turned 34. W… https://t.co/lmNrYNPxy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst thing about winter is having dry ass skin but being too cold to properly moisturize]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miracolgrow1 @StormyDaniels Didn’t mean to get so upset. Just felt wrongly accused. I know she is a great entrepre… https://t.co/GeHLsBbSLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[While Nabil was at grandmas me and Ezra had a little mommy and son time , he’s hilarious and really good at taking… https://t.co/9D71JOd4UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ I don’t judge others. I don’t hate. I don’t discriminate.  I don’t… https://t.co/LvkE4UeRc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[From our environmental teacher @7HillsWC #NoticeWonder #unitchat  #howmany #MTBoS https://t.co/xkAnEiBxCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeToucan @TinaMorphis Wish, he would just die! I know that is horrible! I have lost my three best friend in the… https://t.co/C9yQzzHXQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all see this. Tell me y’all see this. Wow. I stan. A king. I. U. Wow. A KING.   Yes pls. @BJTHECHICAGOKID pls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its Valentines Day.   It’s Thursday.  Does that make #CriticalRole our collective Valentines? https://t.co/x6yARHFd9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abigail Haworth and the Indiana Bible College Chorale May 9th @7:30 3300 SW 66th Street Ocala. https://t.co/jnX9MMdEl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey And the Alberta NDP is joined at the hip with BC NDP? Perhaps in earlier, more gentle times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec saw some clips from your press conference,  I’m glad I didn’t waste my time to listen to your condescendi… https://t.co/y9KhnEAjww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM Yes. There's a reason these Marvel movies keep opening huge. Look at the hype for Captain Marvel. Tha… https://t.co/ck3RCSa3yK]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the price drop and warm weather right around the corner, firm is already on a 3 day backorder. But that doesnt… https://t.co/3OJsVKDFQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be in CO and support the @NatlGovsAssoc and new state leaders as they settle in to their new roles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wouldn’t have spent my 21st with anyone else 💫💜 @ Grand Hot Pot Lounge https://t.co/4rtL8z5fYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is my favorite video 😂 @nsaahome  @Huskermat https://t.co/aA8jbqWC2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz @Risingstar2 And if we support Killary we don’t accept those things? Is that really what you are sayi… https://t.co/rZoHOVy5Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyAuCoin77 She has more of a reason to hate him than I do, and I loathe him. I can’t imagine how she feels]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #KeepLiveMascots on @tyltsports. The animals are treated like royalty! https://t.co/VGUjJURNPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tras una década desde el “Berlín Patient” se replica el caso: un hombre que vivía con VIH en Gran Bretaña se encuen… https://t.co/85xfBnnwXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of a GREAT group of folks who enjoyed the 2nd annual Crystal Snow Spree this year!  More pics to come,  jen4t… https://t.co/Dy8QXECGNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiovanniSTriana @DemriScott I’ll have you and dems over for brunch some time and you can become converted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @AOC When did she call black conservatives tokens? She said parading black people around to show dive… https://t.co/MtBIhQ0Z5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfCimbria @PhillyD @CriticalRole $200, bay-bee! I want that TRINKET! https://t.co/iE6CSMuas1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting for someone to write this story for a while, so s/o @aasdanny for doing it so I don’t have to 👏🏼👏🏼  (s… https://t.co/szf18h233H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helen_george @CallTheMidwife1 i really hope we get to see Trixie find happiness. she keeps finding partners who ar… https://t.co/jNkhLAVfUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glorious snow! Fresh corduroy on Magic Mile...pinch me!   #earningmytacos #timberlinelodge #takemetothetacocabin… https://t.co/dysQ5grqis]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotivationalMaurice would like to remind you that, if they still make you swoon after fifty-one years, that's your… https://t.co/4FrG3yJyEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped Ranger off this morning to get neutered and shots. I’m 99% sure he will hate me when I pick him up. 😭😭… https://t.co/WYD1Hpz3wH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama could execute Rocky Myers any day now – and he could be innocent. @GovernorKayIvey must grant Rocky clemenc… https://t.co/HUTFIGnwVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emstolar @PSLA_News @rchallway @amackley Pennsylvania students, teachers, AND ADMINISTRATORS are lucky to have suc… https://t.co/IEeuIGg5fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilyHoeSaunders that’s a stacked ass card dude thank you boxing gods 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5: I have accepted a challenge from @mcprovost and @katywike1711 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanati… https://t.co/QP07EdPWyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOLE IN 1 BABY!!! Took 29 years for a hole in one! LETS GOOOOOOO @ Cherokee Town and Country Club https://t.co/FyLFIoQhqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last month has been filled with blessings in every way, God works in mysterious ways and now more than ever I’m… https://t.co/hL8nXd13Em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday loved my experience at 10:30 this morning taking my picture in front of Woody with Antonio the photopass… https://t.co/KyEtPHsBsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS The words of your pals Putin &amp; Kim Jong Un are worth as much as yours: nothing zero nada niente rien.… https://t.co/CgvkELPryX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobcastpod @LostSwede @egoraptor @Mort3mer It’s is you! A masterpiece!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rainmaker1973 @gutekunstlaw Arterial blood also comes out in spurts and with more force. Veinous blood less so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep your filthy Republiscum hands off our rights! Our bodies are ours! Not old men in government!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roving in #BreakingNewsOne this morning 🚘. What does your street look like? @wpri12 https://t.co/eZVzu18n5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[JESUS TAKE THE WHEEL FOR THIS AMAZING WOMAN AND HER FAMILY ❤  FOR SHE IS MORE THAN BEAUTIFUL ❤ @OfficialDOGNews… https://t.co/xodltLdx44]]></document><document><![CDATA[You as just like your Daddy. You should of stayed in New York. You do not belong in the White House. Or does either… https://t.co/WbF5X64JjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up &amp; back at it on @STAR1057 @WOODRADIO &amp; @1045SNX 😁😁😁 #morning #radiolife https://t.co/gxCxAwar0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sound of gunshots define my experience in the #8thWard of New Orleans.  #StraightOutta1984 https://t.co/jrC3nOTXo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so what you all know is @charleskelleyla is my favorite singer EVER but did you know how much I absolutely love… https://t.co/QBdq18EX0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the BAYADA Home Health Care team! See our latest #Clerical job openings, including "Entry Level Associate, Hom… https://t.co/IiZaIDnBZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna see Us when it comes out, but I ... I hate horror films, y’all.   Who’s gonna go with me, hold my hand, and… https://t.co/RXoClgChr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol @volrob33 @The_Fool_Monty @HippieVol @beers300 @Shawn172510 @GTA_Redhead Yep I'm meeting my 2 besties t… https://t.co/r4tJvDam5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCatholicRadio @DrewMarianiShow @relevantradio @KofC @RadioRosary Certainly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents of teen girls, check our this event https://t.co/r3MjKDeToG @UpperDarbySD @UDPolice @udarbyparents #UpperDarby]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHESAPEAKE: Bridge openings at the Centerville Turnpike Bridge Wednesday at 7:30 &amp; 8:00 AM  @WTKR3 https://t.co/ewvlsjzazf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexInNederland @FiraxisGames Rose forgot a charger so we're playing hotseat right now but we'll be back on Monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paola_Dec1231 @k2pointO I'd prefer to stimulate the savers with interest hikes.Government outlaws Pyramid scams ru… https://t.co/g5YyWufOba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura Cotes. Her analysis is always clear and spot on. She points out things most of us miss. Like a good lawyer sh… https://t.co/smZBeMQ8Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cry over the dumbest stuff some days.. I hate anxiety and depression 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg Think he needs treatment. He has narcissistic personality disorder  - mostly exhibited by his path… https://t.co/OstwqaoxDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to end another killer #probluesjam at @thecountrynash with @megwilliamsband and newcomer from Louisiana… https://t.co/VWqJTMWqpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_TrumpIN @PeterHi32200905 All of my family! 🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my sister in law to get me a King Cake when she went to New Orleans, only Tre actually liked it.. Amiyah ate… https://t.co/VPryVcJrxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just felt seen when @AnicaCihla shared her story &amp; wanted to also share.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiskey. Walking. (@ Buffalo Billiards - @buffalobilldc in Washington, DC) https://t.co/Z5MfwP8RTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[the type of self control i need but will never achieve bc fucking up ur hair is too liberating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanGNYM @Mets sure, but it’s not happening so I’m just tired of seeing it tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @Unl_CoJMC Ambassadors are joining our Recruiter Alex Fernando aka @Fernanman42 as we welcome our fall 2019 new… https://t.co/JIAQ0oY25f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truest moment of the conference? All pertinent, but without sleep, not as accurate, as such, perhaps not of use?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @DiamondandSilk absolutely crushed it today at #CPAC. Probably my favorite speakers of the day, and they had A… https://t.co/rribrT3kiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat purrs when he even senses that food is near and I can just really relate to that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once an Asshole Always an Asshole - https://t.co/7a1WVuGg5F via @lovelifecoaches]]></document><document><![CDATA[So are the Jonas Brothers doing a reunion?...cause biiiiiiitchhhh I'LL BE THERE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennsaukenTFXC @Team_Briiiizzy @PHSAthletics1 @njmilesplit @HaddonRunCo Nice @Team_Briiiizzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recording interviews with some of the smartest people in the #realestate industry at the  #AccelerateSummit! Stay t… https://t.co/stLiv0CWbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevAriJason @bj95432geemale @herringtowater @MerriwetherW @essenviews Ok]]></document></documents></author>