<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So sick of this weather. I just want 85 degrees and taking long rides with my people ✊🏼 https://t.co/0bGA10hGvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey we know it you know it. Since you became our president I have never seen such lies from demacrats like we the p… https://t.co/lU0khTBp2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 houses up for sales on Orlando street alone. Half of them now have incentives attached to them to buy. This is nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is happening?!?!! @shorez writes/directs an episode and everyone goes crazy!! #TheGoodDoctor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well stirred up enough Hornets tod wa y even acquired an Instagram hater stalker lol. Your doing good when you got… https://t.co/6kPxM00Gfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear about the new video about R Kelly, he is sick as hell. Fuck that asshole. I hope he get his ass beat in jail #FuckRKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you just stay true, some good things are coming back to you” @ Westside North, Kansas City https://t.co/3kdQuki21E]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YFp13ryFEV  Avail Yahoo Homepage 1-844-659-2999 customer service for quick help    #YahooHomepage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thrillerho @themaskoflife @rockmyworIds you fail to acknowledge Michael Jackson showed an unnatural infatuation wi… https://t.co/qJlM0CdntC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bfatayoo I like bloody Mary’s tho. Tomato soup with vodka is somehow okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be more clear. According to the SCOTUS, a student does check like 80% of their first Amendment rights at the… https://t.co/ooNb6mWOXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a couple of photos hanging at Osceola Arts until April 26th. Today was the artists reception. I’ve never sub… https://t.co/IYXxkp0QLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You kinda gotta admire how up front they are about the Porgs.  *Violently pins you to the ground and shoves one in… https://t.co/96rACwHGtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m1guel_1334 Nah 28 pt lead got to single digits there’s something wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet The Team. Selling and Leasing your 🏠 since 2011.   #nycrealestate #brownstoneboys #nativenewyorker… https://t.co/NzHvuq1Sq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VelveteenWWE @AngeloDawkins @MontezFordWWE March 16 you have to be here to see NXT stars. NXT NXT NXT NXT https://t.co/SzCNPCwLkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattRudkinWSBT @samjcharles This is accurate and I’m over it. Ready for the summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BelehToma @GobAbiertoBOL @KamalaHarris False. And she is personally against the DP but you must enforce law as AG,… https://t.co/EEQazYlZQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[NV Attorney General hosts Consumer Protection Week events https://t.co/AKBVghgQBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer More Fuel Taxes?  Next we will have to pay taxes on food, air and water!!!  I think it is time for anot… https://t.co/6j33xW5jDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice Wild!  Carbonated. - Drinking an Eastern Seaboard by @dogfishbeer @ Flounder's Private Bar  — https://t.co/A0B8tMA1vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, I wish there was an option where I can choose where I want a small percentage of my tax dollars going to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so glad some horrible people failed at their career choices. Like you didnt deserve that engineering education a… https://t.co/c7KEDaG3aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoruribeg @VoluntadPopular @jguaido @LesterToledo @liliantintori @apichardob @juanflores18 @carlosvecchio… https://t.co/dOUzvib9WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaonairtalk The Georgia Republicans will lose the house in 2020...thanks to the feckless @GaRepublicans standi… https://t.co/58GpqlE0My]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of this tomorrow literally sleep tweeting with one eye open now both are closed. Hope this makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@optimum Tv &amp; Internet &amp; Phone Support Home Apt 105 - @ThomasChieffo Abilities First Volunteer… https://t.co/0jsroP7pjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today!  Just finished week 12 day 6 of #26.2 #Trainer on #Android with zenlabsfitness! #everymomentcounts #run… https://t.co/DcK3vUJOBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[06:48 Temp. 11.8°F, Hum. 94%, Dewp. 9.7°F, Bar. 30.16 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind -1° 0 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 19,804. Thank you, God! ツ #gratitude #daybyday #happydream #lifeisbeautiful https://t.co/kVwLnnTmgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop @Patta47cake @gtconway3d Don’t think there’s much cuddling going on there.  And it’s sublime how com… https://t.co/x6ElN3MxMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_PRM @liranzo_mildred @luisabinader @sectorexternoLA @JosePaliza @llegopapa @CarolinaMejiaG @CDN37 @ElCaribeRD… https://t.co/DC7ChVHHn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome trending music game!  Very funny, exicting, and challenge! Check it Out! 👉Tiles Hop👈  #TilesHop… https://t.co/Htix02VvfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stripedbanana3 @hightide172 And Obama and Hillary sold Uranium to the Russians. 🤔 backed by Democrats and rhinos.… https://t.co/OsWxmXjQK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKessen @madisongesiotto I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quin… https://t.co/TBCwNgJnil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Boomers Warn It Will Be Costly To Solve Problems Created By Baby Boomers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peligroso eso de tener rabo de pana!. @fdbedout @jsanchezcristo @jsanchezcristo @GustavoBolivar @petrogustavo… https://t.co/Y54Qy93zJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok sorry for the dog food tweets. Hulu has been force feeding me dog food ads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duarteelauraa Does Threat Level Midnight count if there is a hockey cameo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joseph &amp; Melissa's Wedding, My Aunt Cora. Love u! And look who photo bombed us in back! LOL #family #friends… https://t.co/0iV2zgus6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 34 years old and can’t decide if a movie at 10:15 is too late. What the hell has happened, @jayme_harvey? Where… https://t.co/9EclwUxUoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryinmillennial @joshuaasuss @RadioShorty @mattmeadows @derek_mafs @AOC “People think it’s unfair to work without… https://t.co/w8zaXRWj9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting some pizza (@ Wild Tiger Pizza in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/zoZwlNkE8J https://t.co/vVk7sFyun2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belmardays @AmyFreeze7 @brian4NY @NWS_MountHolly @nynjpaweather @ReporterJim https://t.co/64o7Vyz3RI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiffanydloftin People call their mother’s “ole girl?” https://t.co/dH2uhP3JmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethnigmax @NBCThisisUs You need to stay awake for the next 3 days and binge!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I think using the 25th can only be used if he is ruled mentally incapacitated.  I think this was an attempted coup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can say my best friends is a true friend .. she drives 9 hours for just one day to spend time with me and my family 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing better then @donlemon saying “Ruh-Roh” in a semi-deadpan voice on @CNNTonight. So, so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45 #TrumpPence2020… https://t.co/k9K6j4rn2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: says some fucked up shit              My girl: blocks me                              Me:🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TermineRadio the NBA All-star game is like the Grammys - basically unwatchable- Players advancing their Brand, no… https://t.co/QzWu0uMKwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixers @blue_coats Good news makes our bench better Let's go SIXERS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeJParr IMO certainly a lot more “anthemic” than most of the other (great) songs mentioned!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameswester A 51% attack isn't a hack to engineers and IT experts. But others would probably call it one.  I don't… https://t.co/LS8cnTwZYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it is written: "I have made you a father of many nations." He is our father in the presence of God, in whom he b… https://t.co/1GHLLKEkMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Michigan just likes getting owned in rivalry games. Football and basketball!   #MichVsMSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the people of #Worcester for coming out and selling out EVERY show this weekend at thewoohaha!  You sh… https://t.co/8uMLpNzKpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should tell them to pack sand and take their anti-American, socialistic ideals and values elsewhere . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young Monsta in the making!!! #houstonfitness #houstonmuaythai #youthmuaythai #fitness #htxboxingtrainer… https://t.co/dXCPsxz3wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great weekend at Vortex Spring in Florida!! Here are a few shots from some of our dives. Love my Hollis M1 a… https://t.co/QOYLmKydLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crystal Westbrook and India Love nudes both leaked on the same night... my goodness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Alecia yogamotif for an amazing session!! Looking forward to doing it again. That was the relaxation we all… https://t.co/VPX6DMH5vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For you have been born again, but not to a life that will quickly end. Your new life will last forever because it… https://t.co/rKqq5lmQJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[February ━━━━━┒ ┓┏┓┏┓┃ ┛┗┛┗┛┃＼○／Me ┓┏┓┏┓┃   / ┛┗┛┗┛┃ノ) ┓┏┓┏┓┃  ┛┗┛┗┛┃  ┓┏┓┏┓┃  ┛┗┛┗┛┃  ┓┏┓┏┓┃  ┛┗┛┗┛┃  ┓┏┓┏┓┃ ┃┃┃┃┃… https://t.co/XSz1vGDUnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety The shill is on at variety. I think I’ll continue to overlook this publication.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr I guess money is more important than the death of the world and with it the human population.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher We have an out and out thug in the White House. I will be sorely disappointed, and I know I am not alone… https://t.co/eIAzcZehfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox Set Gets HEATED When Two Panelists Go At Each Other’s Throats Over Cohen Testimony! https://t.co/OF7w83GdhW via @en_volve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque les hizo falta fuerza TESTICULAR y el compromiso con la camiseta #ElRealMadridCaePor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Why am I not surprised?! As his mentor would so eloquently say, "Lock Him Up"!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I have an exercise ball to use at my desk. Great for the back/core. Plus my cat commandeered my new office cha… https://t.co/VuAG9vxUt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[3B Matt Duffy (hamstring) says he expects to be back in lineup Saturday after running Wednesday and doing the same… https://t.co/fVeDRuAueA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@detbensonn Don’t do that! It’s not funny! You scared the shit out of me!! Thank God @Mariska is ok!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an honor to watch ALA President-Elect Wanda Brown (UNCG Class of '83) talk libraries with Dr. Hayden.… https://t.co/J9G2DHt78t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole #TimApple thing smacks of “Jennifer Government” where you change your name to be the same as your workplace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That eggo paid sponsorship  I bought some, we'll alot of syrup, I'm OK, send a new toaster, not,, we're worried about you. Texts]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Via Original Photo Copyright strangemusicinc ©) |OMAHA, NE! - 04/11 - @SokolAuditorium| @TechN9ne #ItGoesUpTour 20… https://t.co/M2dNq76skf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When are you going to grow the f’k up and act like the adult in the room. Or is it in your DNA to… https://t.co/hp46aYTvEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to buy one of the Trump signed bibles.  Display it in my case alongside the cookbook I had signed by Jeffrey Dahmer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos al aire a hablar sobre The Fitness Project, celebrando el 50 Aniversario del Fitness https://t.co/ztFmoEuOs3… https://t.co/KND29EIKbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legacy kzoo improves to 5-1 this season. Cant wait to see what we do the rest of the year.🏈 #LegacyFootballOrganization]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is with these crazy names? - Drinking a Learn What Is to Be Taken Seriously and Laugh at the Rest by… https://t.co/fvYIiYdjLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great e-clinics tonight from @RunThePower with @The_Coach_A and @tbanks1906. Always trying to learn more about the game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evgrieve The Saddle Up trailer gauntlet on St. Marks https://t.co/6Gzed2XFoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who invented asian fusion food are the people that went “why not both?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UweBollocks The Shins are great &amp; it's only a little their fault that they are tiresome as fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would never try to force you to be silent but please, just on your own:  stop saying stupid things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt cassidyriley23 and myself helping @BretHart with a training seminar at the Nashville State Fairgrounds in Nash… https://t.co/UyfnLLE8Bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlesadler #wrong  he has grown and evolved into being a Leader  #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly know i would feel so lost in every way if i didn’t have both of parents with me bc i know many of my fri… https://t.co/DpqpYGeRJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmartestMoran More of Henry earning a weekend start or Marceaux dealing w injury?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Semi-Tough and You Gotta Play Hurt shaped my young brain. Made me want to cover sports with profane wit and humanit… https://t.co/cxaRcR0InD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Daily Motivator - understanding Negative emotions- wise words for a happy Tuesday  https://t.co/W7oiTNaQ22 via @po_st]]></document><document><![CDATA[UofT @UofT MUST address this up to the level of the Governing Council. Our university has no place for nonsensical… https://t.co/DVruqGHjSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an emotional speech Rep Chris Rosario @BAMBAMBPT tells fellow lawmakers @MGMBridgeport is a matter of life or de… https://t.co/LcU5LAK3Os]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlindean Also sounds like the title of your next young adult novel 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly how I’d imagine skeletons fighting with swords would look like. #Awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReloadedEgoTrip @PLargePro Your technique &amp; style!, is Slicker than Trump!!! https://t.co/03fLQsJz9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HammerOfKek @17frosted you aint doing nothing though, that's the point, find a cause, represent, and quit harassin… https://t.co/AJZ1SdtOzx]]></document></documents></author>