<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Amber: Marcus guess what I gave up for Lent?  Me: McDonalds?  Amber: No I’m not crazy.   Me: Bread?  Amber: yeah...… https://t.co/10bqEZIuJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clay_Odem @brainouty I am on the same level as you are and I think basically the same as you do. Can you explain t… https://t.co/pkgDMhf4ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning Sensation Copyright: 1998 Ronald E. Qualls  Chorus And in the night's shine. I'll be walking a fine line. W… https://t.co/D4S1zT4Xyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LeavingNeverland all U people defending this pedophile are the same ones that will defend the me-too movement wome… https://t.co/CTU4zpoNTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[VOK: Sauti Ya Kenya - Voice of Kenya. Nifikiria Kurudi Shamba - George Oryema's song 'River' captures home, sweet h… https://t.co/oxKFjfYuSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocketChris81 @benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @raider_rob24 What’s wrong with women working]]></document><document><![CDATA[LifeCare Health Partners is hiring in #Plano, TX! Read about our latest #HR job opening via the link in our bio: Human Resources Generalist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneHelmsCom This is disappointing  :( but what wasnt disappointing was seeing you at Battlefield X! Great seeing… https://t.co/CdlLwqm8RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiSynnXoX @ChatTimeNow Good morning and I don’t think I ever see you that early.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter_nt Nadie quiere perder! Todos quieren ganar! Ego!!! Todo se queda aquí. #TodoEsInventado @realmadrid… https://t.co/oybkbyi4QU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Starbucks in Clermont, FL https://t.co/iuwdyOwhmn https://t.co/vYNUgvUTak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I relate so hard. Like sign me up. Take my name down. The cartel, the mafia, a biker gang, any of y’all can have me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEONIDA89059547 @sherry25793049 Now I do believe life begins at conception. Women are being lied to, deceived and… https://t.co/5ShZurICkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Just in case you forgot, deny, or otherwise cover up your stupidity. https://t.co/gtPx4yY6RD]]></document><document><![CDATA[C'mon fellas! @RyersonRamsMHKY Let's move on from this battle of the blues! Head into the next round! Catch it live… https://t.co/YOvM0C71BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dcollida I feel like if I didn't record it with my Fitbit, it didn't happen. It just bothers me]]></document><document><![CDATA[that didnt go well for chriss lol. best part is serge went after him twice . first slammed into post by the throat… https://t.co/aTx6DuYfNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s the Vans employee that was fired for saying “fuck you” to the little MAGA shit? He needs a gofundme way more… https://t.co/2WOTmMKXvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge thank you to @UHDbaseball and coach @nickstrong for talking to me and having me attend a great game #dub 🐊🐊🐊 https://t.co/zDjYhhNCZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clash of KingsGoddess is coming, come find your goddess! https://t.co/SPizSbUDhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulZeise I don’t think Hines’ career ended on a very good note between him and Ben. His opinion could have a bit of bias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Each movie in The Dark Knight trilogy represents the stages in a man’s life.. the [birth / life in its… https://t.co/5aWNiZJSA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @KAG1776MAGA @Jayhawker4Trump @Libphobic @gator4kb18 @trumpAngel45 @Godsgirl158 @GaryWalters66… https://t.co/RA7qZcu7Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs The real question is...Can she pour a decent beer? #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday! @ZargerDawn  Hope those Gin and Sprite are going down smoothly! Picking up your tab Friday night and I’ll get you a Uber 😉😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Trump might have a janitor job for you Krasteen bros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taryngmz @randyavilla @CornNuts Goodbye, Taryn. I don’t need this negativity in my life.   [dramatic exit]]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black History Celebration Sunday at New Corinth MB Church. @ Euharlee, Georgia https://t.co/zZn4glMdRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asteinomite You are one of my favorite people in this world! I’m honestly so grateful that I know you. I love you… https://t.co/LjOfnDdPKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back and forth we go, but Maine West is yet to have a lead. 528 in the second quarter. My ears are starting to hurt… https://t.co/2VBWbsfs5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Music__Mentor @UltClassicRock @VanHalen @eddievanhalen @alexvanhalen Completely agree on the EVH instrumental albu… https://t.co/lx65gzMEHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stomach better be full for the next few days. $170 later on all you can eat Brazilian dinner 😅 #Sheesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Isn’t it funny how day by day nothing changes, but when you look back everything is different.” -C.S. Lewis @ Firs… https://t.co/m1ERJsFaur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs don’t chase parked cars!! You are a problem because people see you making moves! Whatever they think or say ca… https://t.co/jkuDwy67L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sinceramente este video me conmovió tanto que me quitó los buenos ánimos que tenía, maldito maduro]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don't like Skip Bayless and That other Steve guy talk Boxing  on Fox sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up from a nightmare where someone shot me.....it was loud and very scary.  My response to my attacker w… https://t.co/RHrBFDaOGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep trying to distract your sheep. Once their done you will be shamed and exposed for the Dumbass you are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without a clear path or intention, you'll just be wandering around aimlessly.  https://t.co/YO5MCRnv5C https://t.co/sjYfJ9w40a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yusuf_bektas91 @SexyNDirty Her pussy looks so good definitely paradise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilbert89039976 @cmdrPorkchop @Zippityd00dah @ksatnews The pity is that individual is of voting age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dolphin Club on a rainy Tuesday morning. #SF #sanFrancisco https://t.co/a6RhmxGFdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow And President Trump and the President’s supporters! I’ll take mine in writing with his real autograph not a copied one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helton_boggs @007Bigless @ThomasA84745226 @BleachTheLies @real_defender @realDonaldTrump This is about Trump dipshit. Try to stay on topic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golfbabes @holly_sonders You don't stop. Exceptional https://t.co/Htij1FKf69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Law124 If you come back during the season I’ll get you a pair of tix To a game great seats field level 1st base… https://t.co/3iptL73VyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stage 3: Complete! Main hull support structure and the beginnings of the aft superstructure, including bridge/comma… https://t.co/3q0QFJ3vOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This international concert will bring global attention to this unacceptable and preventable crisis and raise funds… https://t.co/9yXcpycvZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troll760 @AmbJohnBolton @SecPompeo Es asombroso que simplemente imagines que los americanos no derrotarían a las b… https://t.co/KzArfWUt5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the way Chelsea played today, minus the straight disrespect from Kepa not only to Sarri, but also to the players in a Cup Final.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case they try to pull another “sewer bill” move, the message to legislators needs to continue in a slightly… https://t.co/wo1ueSo4yH]]></document><document><![CDATA[WrestleMania! #ThankYouKurt #Raw #WWE #WrestleMania https://t.co/eZTfBwnsjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13WHAM This happening more frequently what they think gangs fights people rob the older ones, selling drugs a lot… https://t.co/2l4hTkH4Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Thai Chicken Larb mise en place ... oh and a beer for the cook https://t.co/8LnafKZs20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEVIN_BEARCAT @kellygramlich I’d pay money to watch the Colts. But I wouldn’t have paid to watch him play for the Broncos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siriusxmvolume Muenster Of Puppets. #80sCheese https://t.co/6svlx1WFZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a small piece of the full set up I have! 🎮 https://t.co/KhE7Xlx9Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyrie is the only player who makes me second guess what I just saw.  He’s so good at disappearing into the lane and… https://t.co/tCkrAHL0GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGates Just watched you on CNN with Fareed. As always, you were great. You do God's work here on earth. Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there’s a way to turn all of the effusive Michigan Combine praise into wins over Ohio State and Big Ten champion… https://t.co/L5YvzxUUh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy idea: What if when we disagree with someone on Twitter, instead of calling them names we simply say something… https://t.co/UvbiyYDoee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseLChilavert_ Pero que garantiza q un DT mundialista nos clasificara?  Cayetano, Carpeggiani, Markarian, Maño, T… https://t.co/SQHLMnfzsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2 of #ActOnClimate boots for this South Florida senator, but maybe with better results on the horizon. This t… https://t.co/QR47OC7ZKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asymmetricinfo @davigoli You're welcome! Even with no traffic you'll find people would even prefer to take a *gasp* bus too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LKanniard Thank you for the kind words. I’m sure the best is yet to come at @RUWrestling. He’s in great hands. @CoachGoodale is the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorKarnes Robert.  It's national Margarita day.  You're drunk. Do yourself a favor and just stop. #YoureWelcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSEGNews Solar 4 All Pennsauken Brownfield #solar farm will power 2,500 New Jersey homes annually once complete!… https://t.co/QsabMzhS5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S1NFULbyN8URE @Butley270 @bluedevils1990 What would? I can’t state enough how meaningless polls are ... especially… https://t.co/CsmC7N0rR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJayHill Jay remember when Sara brought us Valentine’s Day doughnuts? We thought she was so sweet then we bit… https://t.co/liSe7lGLXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to see Alita: Battle Angel today and it was pretty damn good. Go check it out 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too many folks bitching and whining yet about the upcoming Daylight Saving Time, but I know it's coming.  (get… https://t.co/Zng6zQyIDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last chance to witness/honor Olin Carter, Tyler Williams, Isaiah Pinero, Isaiah Wright and Mitch Schafer. They’ve m… https://t.co/ltbk7O6IXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite day of the week game day good luck to @CoryGarrastazu @mike_cassala @ScottDubrule @Reagan1313 @PCaastillo… https://t.co/X2aqCHPU7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world lost a good one. My grandpa, Bill VerHulst went home early this morning. Everybody knew him as a man that… https://t.co/li3ivdL6kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rushtheband Watching the @StLouisBlues game and the @mnwild organist started playing #Subdivisions. 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Dame scores 51, but you got 37 and a W and ask him what time it is? Lol feel bad for him though, Jurkic and Mc… https://t.co/nKKXg0kFGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crank and Boom Ice Cream flight... clockwise: chocolate banana, blueberry lemon cheesecake, salted caramel, dark ch… https://t.co/Y4m6YoGHfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SciGuySpace @genejm29 @SpaceNews_Inc Ouch. That hurts too much to be funny…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi where's the investigation into the Clinton's and the guy from Kenya,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always the last 4min of the last interval. Always. Never let's me down! https://t.co/5tUohgOdV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a security guy with lackluster Linux skills, I love this. https://t.co/1Gv8bYSY1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[My JOY today? Having the privilege to spend time with some amazing students (and teachers) at Chapman High School.… https://t.co/1hfi4FUVM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you stop and actually look at the things on the walls here... Some pretty weird stuff https://t.co/NhlQDUtC2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[540 S Serrano Ave 540 S Serrano Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90020 https://t.co/hJtwQSWaVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/EErjwT5DMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Walt Disney Studios 500 S Buena Vista St, Burbank, CA 91521  https://t.co/ceAIOZUj68]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooh man, I just got home from the gym...you know what that does... https://t.co/2WA6RdjvOh via @OnlyFansApp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyTrask @susanslusser @jenniferleechan @AmyGGiants @KJohnsonNBCS @gianna_franco @AnnaKagarakis @AOC Amy, you are… https://t.co/M67hl2aAqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janus303 Definitely excited to cheer on Secretary Hickenlooper in 2021 :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would not open any businesses on Cleveland until the road is finished, all of the customers north of Garriott won… https://t.co/vnIXv8cEX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisosv You should be playing apex w me instead of tweeting this corny shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenbamo Thank you so much Jen! I feel like I got enough stuff here to keep me busy for a while! Will def have to a… https://t.co/xx7pid8asa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Speaking of crimes .... looks like the trump organization is up s creek with no paddle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBoersen This is great info Josh. Really appreciate you sharing. I hope others find this intriguing and inspiri… https://t.co/70EzgcFh8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[They can say #Trump was chosen by God all they want. It won't make him a good POTUS or an honest man. Nor will it g… https://t.co/F9AmPCjwZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger out here dripping #prada @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/EQQCOTRzDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morally Bankrupt Post.  Clearly this poster has mental health issues. https://t.co/WavbPlKHg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m crying in the club that the @jonasbrothers used their fiancée/wives in their video. 👏🏻😭👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spearsTexan @the_Shildt_Show I could do this for a while longer but you strike me as being unemployed so you have… https://t.co/bwRrUdX7v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally over the cold weather anymore! It’s been real winter but spring you need to hurry up now please!… https://t.co/StDpnkGAxs]]></document></documents></author>