<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MikeMelrose01 @SPWTalessia @JussieSmollett And idek why you tried to add that that there was ONE black kid, one th… https://t.co/NDZJeHYBN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally JUST realized they were mocking Tim Cook. I was so confused lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know he’s better than Kobe all time but a season like this make me feel good that I was sayin all these years tha… https://t.co/AIVRUxq9eF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMcElroy @hodgman Is this a promo for the new Weezer Black album?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachHanson5 @EASPORTSFIFA @IanDarke THE US ARE CERTAINLY THROUGH. Best @IanDarke call. Memorable. https://t.co/7jzBfvuw8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA UUUU LA UUUU LA UUUU @tigresoficial en Estadio Universitario https://t.co/XysZYIG6rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 8.81 miles in 1h:24m:48s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/Dz3n5o3yvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1ChordWonder @RepAdamSchiff Sure he is. Because everyone knows that's how the biggest Intel op in history should g… https://t.co/5oqNwvm28j]]></document><document><![CDATA[How am I just now realizing that Lord Baelish from #GOT is my dawg Mayor Carcetti from #TheWire 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your engines and get ready to roll the dice! Our community is gearing up for the event of the season, Curtis… https://t.co/r0glRIuosZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed Season 1, Don't miss Season 2... on 🔥&amp; Better than Ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s U.N. pick thin on foreign policy, long on political connections: Kelly Craft faces a major test, despite he… https://t.co/rOZll9malo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone on my timeline really just tweeted something political 5 minutes after getting word that Bryce Harper just signed. Are you for real?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if @peterhartlaub will find any “false dawn” photos in the @sfchronicle archives... https://t.co/WNKDgRKYPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvdrbrt @TPCarney @mattklewis And they are asking for barriers to do their jobs more effectively, and it is in the… https://t.co/SbH96wtnQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolNewsN @ComfortablySmug @LaurenDoooley That Pelosi. Comment correction]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG @TheOrville!!! you went there! I’m on the floor. @EgotasticFT hold me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#deviaje en #chicago #instatravelgram #beardstyle #beardofinstagram #barbon #instabarbas #likesforlikes en Millenni… https://t.co/WbfDyKKYYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somejawn401 The thread is ridiculous. People care about GoT but “no one cares” about this thread]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any of my followers good with coding on websites or know someone? Need an update on my site and I’m willing to pay for their services!🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic Friday shoutout to some of my new followers. Have a great day. Cheers! 🥂 @_drazzari @boozychef @jillbarth… https://t.co/x7CsNTPaoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  Middle schoolers when their friend is talking to their parents on the phone: https://t.co/aN59sqpzSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After tomorrow night, I'm officially going to be calling it The Leader of the Pack Open Invite Scramble. #AndNew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockiefresh Don't 4get 2 visit the "Watertower mall " Downtown on Michigan Blv.!! You won't 4get it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 1. Today was my first day testing out my new class concept. We through the headphones on heads and I had the B… https://t.co/vlOGBxeNa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother and daughter murder five family members. Bizarre crime scene. Rumors of demon cult. @PatriarchTree… https://t.co/66zb6kiU8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/bT5eD89Fnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRINGING MORE HEATERS TO 2019  @Midnightasaurus   @We_the_plug_ https://t.co/tg9ebke5Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barnes should have made that pass inside on the inbounds rewatch the video]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_ricketts23 Thank you Taylor, these were the days 🤘🏼 Hope you are doing well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your parents obviously never smacked you for smacking your lips while you eat and it really shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo taken at the upper east side New York City. . #fence #uppereastside #oldbuildings #iron @ Upper East Side https://t.co/gqq10V0c43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stanger1970 @ChrisBils @APrecourt Thanks for sharing but as I stated sell out season tickets or save the crew lied… https://t.co/2n1HKTR0t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimbcbs4 Finally, an animal in NYC that is the same size as the rats.#fairfight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Sunday Sunrise! #sundaysunrise #sundaymorning #sunrise #pray @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/JzfUYtywjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[You hate traffic? Hell, I hate traffic too, but turn the damn radio on and listen to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthofNaomi @LeukaemiaCareUK @WWE @WWERomanReigns @davemeltzerWON Ok whatever 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repaint finished, I like this a lot more 👍🎸🎶 @ Destin, Florida https://t.co/SjWnW9ewtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kilonova_gold @Chbrownson1 @AshaRangappa_ @joshscampbell Well said. I’ve never heard Bernie offer a viable plan fo… https://t.co/RKwIJXKngZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker What will they wear if their child is shot while in school?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Organ Mountains are truly stunning today! #NewMexicoTrue 🏔❄️ https://t.co/oArzzPL9RK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SrMiyagiZan Chica,no seas tan cruel! Es la primera Miss Universo que la dejan por teléfono! Por Dios!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganCWallen can’t decide which is better...the mullet or all the Tennessee references???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merransmith @cathmckenna @GeorgeHeyman Nice cartoon. I especially love the graphs where neither axis is labelled. Very science-y.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC TRUMP WINS THE NOBEL PRIZE ALRIGHT, FOR BEING THE MOST CORRUPT SELF SERVING JAC ASS  WHO HAS EVER TAKEN UP R… https://t.co/P57juLCj7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babies and kids video coming soon... https://t.co/3xiZWdfRvJ @ Dexter, Michigan https://t.co/l2BhvknlWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jakob130 Best of luck men!! Rooting you on!  Great job this year coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Tigers in control, up 27-2 going to the 2nd over Tyner.@DPAScottPower]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Please show me how much more work you're doing. When was the last time you spoke with the community you're sup… https://t.co/BbLPuC9sSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunSentinel Refreshing to hear a Republican Governor give credit to his appointed Democrat for a good job in disas… https://t.co/Oxzw5PaS8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all, I love Obama but seeing him in that "44” jacket last night makes me wonder if he's bought any commemorative… https://t.co/fjnqHWGBKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyLeinwand12 @neal_katyal @DonaldJTrumpJr @harrylitman @lawfareblog @tribelaw @JillWineBanks @nickakerman… https://t.co/BdoXnp6eGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BlowMyMindIn4Words Fes=Foreign Exchange Student https://t.co/578vSsh48u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geprotection  STANCE GRIP SIGHT ALIGNMENT  SIGHT PICTURE TRIGGER CONTROL BREATHING FOLLOW THROUGH RECOVERY… https://t.co/uRMIOvt4iF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree, it’s sad when mental illness is left undiagnosed.  He needs help. #Homosexuality]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is Hollywood’s biggest night at the Oscars and A Star is Born is nominated for 7 awards including @ladygaga… https://t.co/QoSMQnAbg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I KNEW IT I KNEW IT SAMI CALLIHAN KNOWS RICH SWANN AND HE IS FAMILY NOW HE'S PART OF OvE AND FAMILY IS EVERYTHING!!!!!! #IMPACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls stay using the filter that makes their hair white and skin orange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5NEWSMatt Matt here are some pictures of rime ice or hoarfrost (whatever it is) on the mountain in eastern Madison… https://t.co/9iAMHWCYcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fleacatt @SallyAlbright I am not a it was the Astec Bernie supporter. But I am not going to do anything to hurt th… https://t.co/LCXT1y5PD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaciejBk1 @StanleyPanama Nareszcie przekopia i caly rejon odzyje! Ludzie beda miec prace a Ruskie zostana w swoim gettcie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I need to start drinking Apple. #apple #coke @ Arden Town, California https://t.co/h0ixIJS0Rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying my hand at Shepherd's Pie tonight! @ Weber - Wells Humble Abode https://t.co/eJB7V86Puv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worldschanging @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Did you make the same observation of election interference when HRC… https://t.co/dpHM1Hseok]]></document><document><![CDATA[AP FACT CHECK: Cramer makes false national emergency claim https://t.co/BdGWN5KYOL @SenKevinCramer got caught. #790KFGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[มัทธิว 7:13-14  Thai New Contemporary Bible    ประตูแคบและประตูกว้าง  13 “จงเข้าไปทางประตูแคบ เพราะประตูใหญ่และทางก… https://t.co/OBPEXmQsDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some pics from yesterday's hunt. one with  lonewolfx19 😎 . . ♡twitch♡ https://t.co/jQjrAftjrw ------------------- S… https://t.co/n7ENJLEWBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have also been in a coma since coming here and believing I could fly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From 2016-2017, Daisy's highlights.  Daisy left us from Daisyland to our big Father's House last Valentine's ♥ Day… https://t.co/dLTTKOCadB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@honigfordjc Only time I've done it was when I was a kid and we were visiting my grandparents in Daytona Beach. The… https://t.co/vUGeEtqg8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronMerril11 @amberv127 @AvideepPradhan @rannachi19 https://t.co/3vXuASaDLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darren_sipes @johndgunther @FutureZtars None of the horses John mentioned ran in the @KentuckyDerby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruth is AMAZING at what she does. It's about time she is being acknowledged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said she almost didn’t reply to me bc all she seen was “Mac no cheese” she gone say I don’t know no Mac no cheese LMAOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Browndeus dealing w/ public:  re-action  is never what U  thought it would be. The 1 thing I shake my head to is w… https://t.co/p3oLeFSikM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How bad is the East? The @nyknicks are 13-49 and still not eliminated from playoff contention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The intro to President Carter will go down as one of the hardest intros in all of music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[think I’m gonna start a thread of all the times can makes an appearance on my life https://t.co/q8vfizLDfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GO4ITUSA @AOC I thought conservatives were all about letting people have their freedoms. Isn’t how someone chooses… https://t.co/p3Xd085rnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, Gonzaga... - Drinking a Hopsmack! Double IPA (2019) by @theTGBNews @ Iowa City Free Medical Clinic  — https://t.co/RuKeDlJq9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purpose without priority is powerless.Find your purpose then find the right actions and attitude to fulfill it. #buildyourdream]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣  Only in Arctic Mexico.   How many suspected money laundering reports do you think a FINTRAC registered company… https://t.co/1E1nE1IF83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toma tu Santa Lucia!! @lopezobrador_ @JimenezEspriu ... @VictorMendozaL @hilarioolea @elalbertomedina… https://t.co/z70Zez1QPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverKingBest @ESPNNFL @SportsCenter @DeSeanJackson11 @Redskins https://t.co/DA8man5cMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The registration team #jdug2019 #hiltonhonors #hiltonhonorstravel @ Hilton Orlando https://t.co/Ra9KK2m2Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enough212 You are no failure. I am the same way. I have a cabinet full of things I tried with no helpful outcome.… https://t.co/Ul4sXTngTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barista: You're looking very James Dean today. Me: Well, except he was better-looking and I'm about a foot taller.… https://t.co/CqHcJvN81d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to worship  and God's Church @ Heartland Community Church https://t.co/xRZ8yywdWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustedOpenRadio @davidlagreca1 Asuka gets her win back fro Mandy at #Fastlane then I think after that match someon… https://t.co/h33xlRDnWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/BZqPWKHlyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brodeyy_51 They were right that song is stuck in my head and i am loving it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTimeOhio DirecTV Now. Billing and viewing zip is the same (43202).  I can watch about 3 minutes then this po… https://t.co/4XQaOODwG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost pastordreriggs (get_repost) ・・・ "A BOLD witness KNOWS be their authority." -@propheticdot Acts 4:7-10… https://t.co/0Wy99fiH3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entered Park: Magic Kingdom at 5:36 PM #parkeologychallenge @Parkeology]]></document><document><![CDATA[@movingbackfrom @TulsiGabbard I don't think you want to see it without no-till.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You didn’t ask, but a reminder that my fave piece of football commentary is, and always will be, David Pleat with “… https://t.co/45JPBOjLah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaVugteveen @Ben_Feistritzer @homedepot2771 @kkozdron0821 @tuffshed @BrandonReinoehl Great job, Ben! #2771inspires]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably Wanye's last period as a @NHLFlyers 😢💔 #StadiumSeries https://t.co/a5I8XMYVZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Scripture #scripture #scriptureoftheday #bible #bibleverse #biblequote #godisgood #godisgreat #roswell… https://t.co/SbuK9R7jY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to express my inner turmoil in a socially acceptable way https://t.co/IC95khLAhz]]></document></documents></author>