<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo He needs to be fired, and do jail time. You can’t unring that bell!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you bind on earth shall be bound in heaven; and whatever you loose on earth shall be loosed in heaven.’ Th… https://t.co/79vCCsdwfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowRidiculous I have been binging your videos @ 11:45 PM CST. Quality content! https://t.co/RZG4jYzXnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NullAzor06 @Mikel_Jollett @daveevansabc7 @KamalaHarris @TheRevAl Shit I might make chicken n waffles for dinner to… https://t.co/sDDBzqNquq]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; smoke temperature down 57°F -&gt; 49°F humidity up 67% -&gt; 81% wind 2mph -&gt; 3mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oracleofshoes @kathleenhessert @shadiadaho @EricaEhm @birdonawireart @bifnaked @fosternomore @BiancaJagger… https://t.co/rrlzipSid0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BCFerries, any plans on upgrading your wifi speeds in the near future? You know it’s bad when you want to run… https://t.co/GDIjik9ReD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britin17k @mommamia1217 @realDonaldTrump For God's sake arrest him!!  Look at what he said in that sewer CPAC meet… https://t.co/sWL9EkZr5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I absolutely HATE having braces.. it’s only been three days... I just want to eat some damn food!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rhett ♥️s this sweet musical story &amp; YOU will too! Get your tickets 🎟 ASAP to see him play ‘Herb’ dcplayers… https://t.co/QPeevQMS3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @avibebert He was already a billionaire. We don’t believe you. #MAGA #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating storytelling from @jimcorrellks @IndependenceCC Fab Lab @ecomm_ks @MCAC_EcoDevo  @CoffeyvilleCOC… https://t.co/bgGJHhCTRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would also like to know what a gehtteo is. If I am living in one here in Minneapolis I would recommend it to othe… https://t.co/OpmMsAKANq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocularnervosa @PGHowie4 @mlcalderone Well Fox Primary Job is to protect an Evil Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aliya313 @OfficialDGISPR @ImranKhanPTI Lgta hy India ko apni mout nzr aa rhi hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#god #godisgood #seekgod #blessed #kingdomofgod #godislove #jesuschrist #worship #pray #loveofgod #praise… https://t.co/inX2txb3Ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Jersey man describes to police how he and roommate threw childhood friend Sarah Stern’s body over bridge to ste… https://t.co/rtzz4rNOTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[7pm on @KUOW Seattle’s NPR radio station. Then rebroadcast at 10am on Sunday morning, in case you missed it or you… https://t.co/h6Cu4koIL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've known @MittenMarauder for 12 years and, for 9 of them, we have been an "item"   I'm having one of those "I fee… https://t.co/VGLPfOtVNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Dickwad, they have no fucking healthcare because they can’t afford it because Obamacare was a pack of… https://t.co/2VZS5nvzr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing you have the next day off is more relieving than the actual day off]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dumbass was over here thinking “when did the rock get a nose job??🤔”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated my @hinge account: Interests include hiking, road trips, going to the theater, and listening to Sandra Oh d… https://t.co/bWb5mLxYa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lupita Nyong'o showing up phoebe Robinson and Jessica Williams in a hair braiding competition on #2DopeQueensHBO is really something]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY ED!!!🎉🎊🎂🎈🎁 I hope you have the best day ever and enjoy your gifts!!! Love you lots 😘💜 @noorNazbaghai… https://t.co/CQpl1M2wNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwing your Vans has become the new viral sensation  https://t.co/S8QHMOAVFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear SC General Assembly, this is how you chose public servants. Of course these folks don’t earn a salary but sure… https://t.co/HVW5hKQ5Ud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raggapegs @BMORE0831 @realDonaldTrump Most politicians are crooked! Their crimes haven't been exposed yet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YFsqiu2OE1 And that is where,Michael's hell began!Because all these lying accusers, say well hell! His… https://t.co/WwhR9M1yqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be working on this new #foresthealth app for landowners with @MegBioinfo @Almasaeed2010 @drdavecoyle and… https://t.co/Gx7vfxnhnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, that's me in the striped shirt.  What an AMAZING day!  Thanks to Sophia for sharing time with all of us...and… https://t.co/GmVPFyYUVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop Singing. Express Through Spoken Word. Please. Mr. Jackman. For My Sake. Speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For as I finished all My works before the foundation of the earth was laid, I also finished you!  All that you nee… https://t.co/20yCQbgXKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of a panic! show is when we sing High Hopes back to Brendon, and he’s always so genuine and humble… https://t.co/tWTyp6O6Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were going to have Oxtail soup after Church, but it was still too early, so we went to the Garden Court Buffet a… https://t.co/ku0cIsQFL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t felt this safe and secure in years. I am completely at ease with every aspect of my life. I may not be ab… https://t.co/ug4RQe9fJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobsoboroff I can only imagine that Canada is thrilled she’s leaving. It must take a lot of work to keep finding… https://t.co/6pcijiTWMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother in law will be here in a little over 12 hours. She came to my apartment two years ago for dinner, but has never been to our home 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[A zig then a zag in the right direction. GO Quest is clocking 5.8 kn which is the fastest the fleet has moved since… https://t.co/Ws9Iy2LCgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[From one ambassador @serenawilliams to another thanks for designing @PurplePurse #purplepurse https://t.co/FFOszV2wOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volunteering (@ San Diego Food Bank in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/RijGnRjkgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully that is the last of the snow lol I am looking for spring and warm sunshine for my walkitouts! 😁👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼💜🌞… https://t.co/kOWhpV7G0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatbellybella called it first on @JussieSmollett saying his story didn’t sound right. I was mad at her, but she wa… https://t.co/vquBP8mU1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are either the most blatant, shameless liar who has ever walked the earth, or the dumbest moth… https://t.co/jlY7AU8M8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win tickets to see @whydontwemusic from @1075theriver! https://t.co/qK89SLJ7GR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul EO is required when Congress fails to produce necessary legislation.Congress is so locked into partisan p… https://t.co/CdFKf3PUeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 8, 2015 will always be one of my favorite days of my whole life. I love shannonhisaw and my sweet family SO m… https://t.co/SGzShKNu6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is strategic. We just miss the opportunities because we focus on the “status quo”.  What if...? https://t.co/OqYbROezPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was the first really good day in a really long time and I am absolutely in love with my new job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking done. It’s time to move on from old friends who simply have no care in the world about me.  Cole, La… https://t.co/7JcD3LtUrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their thought would probably be, “Who gave or sold then those seats?”  So be respectful.  Tonight four very obnoxio… https://t.co/TTCGuMC3C2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking items for the TPHS football spirit store! Message me items you’d like to see! @BirdsTorrey @TPHSports… https://t.co/QwR220Ry8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Gabriel go thru this shit is breaking my heart. He is the only one with a sane mind. He says Arizona made… https://t.co/612iRXgdGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Drake said “you just need some dick with no complications” I felt that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundaybumday by sway_polewear from @joannaross33 last night 📸 whyareyoumakingmedothis ⭐️ uspdf #schtickit… https://t.co/BvWAoYJ6DD]]></document><document><![CDATA[this cartridge really tastes like pineapples! not lying but i feel like im biting into a piece of pineapple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoClark87152549 @tmpcat @mill_cats @JethroKitty @KanD1991 @LittleMaineCoon @BloomNight2 @SassyCassyCat @scarboo… https://t.co/UGa2UDl9kB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sberg0 Please do...sorry I couldn't make it but eager to hear your take. #NAEH2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnyMaine I'm just embarrassed it happened in my hometown!!! #TheresFoolsEverywhere #Ibettheyareauburnfans #RTR 🐘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t you move to countries where guns are confiscated and only criminals have them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a grown woman, and a mom some, guys I mean boys come at me so foul... like who raised you? And when I say boys… https://t.co/XhwvIuznfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with my precious #cousin #AutumnRose ❤️🥰❤️ I’m so in #love 😍 @ Rancho Cucamonga, California https://t.co/ws6T1NU84S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown Oakland, thank you for having me. I believe this place will feed my soul and allow me to be a gift to othe… https://t.co/FxqG9FI0UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenRiva @NightlyPolitics This is what I am wearing https://t.co/i0qHpEBqcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought I couldn’t love this place more... thank you KEPTO!!!! The flowers are beautiful!… https://t.co/0bSyinEyId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @SassyNeveragain “cast [sic].”  It went way down hill before the grammar bloop:  basic subject-verb agreement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog I’m really trying to figure out your core values. You seem to waver based on your disgust for Trump as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever cuddle with your significant other and try to imitate their breathing and then you forget how to breathe o… https://t.co/zruw8bCNrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r_ray1011 I played like 2 hours of basketball but the fact I am not extremely sore means my conditioning has vastl… https://t.co/NZ3JesH7s9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Check his pockets for rubles-or they have some #kompromat on this douchebag too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my life has been a downward spiral for the past four months and there is no light at the end of the tunnel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clinton loyalists = the base of the Democratic Party. So you can win a party's nomination without the party's core… https://t.co/kOOAn6tuGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandyRed @WWERomanReigns Whatever  Roman chooses..  World is wide open right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf is up with this ladies lip on Workin’ Moms?! It makes me very uncomfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kflay could literally cough into a microphone for 3 minutes and I would still stan. https://t.co/SHPQwPULC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USO_SC @USNavy You are sunshine 🌞 to so many! Thank you for our sailors!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Fox Socks to wear to day for Dr. Seuss Day “Fox in Socks” that would be me! @GrandviewES #educatingeagles https://t.co/9u47zA5BVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want this Louis Vuitton bag for my birthday...who wants to buy it for me 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been crazy busy today painting!  Many of you know I’m expecting two new grand sons this year!  Yay!  So I e de… https://t.co/bF9PpSdY8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHazard Those guys are Paul’s favorites, they are in all his video games...they remind me of the clowns from our SIMS days! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is definitely a skit but this is what should happen when someone gropes or touches someone else without permis… https://t.co/3B8w8VNDlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hearing is a deliberate attack on the President while he is Brokering PEACE in NoKo. Anything to take away fro… https://t.co/1fuGQzkmHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burntfort @_ElizabethMay I’ll be the lone voice to say that we did! I loved both Ant Man movies, plus they’re goin… https://t.co/zLGkxjrAoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @AsiaTater @winstonCovfefe @TWITMO_INMATE @BRella315 @ImabitcSumtimes @SealeyGerald @mymynags… https://t.co/KUaGPTzwC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruqa11 @theNiteMadness @KatrinaResists @otter272 @hilaryluros @Nikki_WVU_49ers @MaryLemanski @IcyannL… https://t.co/qiTlAyUEJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took notes in one sitting that are longer than every other set of notes I’ve taken for this course COMBINED  My brain is fried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Central OH region of @makeawishohkyin had its annual #BIGWishGala last week. The ROCK STAR guests at the… https://t.co/G8hCSRkrQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatDrawingGuy I'm in the warmest place I can think of ....WHY IS THIS ON TV https://t.co/bFnzuaURGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[He Exposed Abuse At A Florida Immigrant Detention Center. Now He’s In Prison https://t.co/V7cnDitsKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelUrbShip @kendramcdermand @beaches456 @KatieC1212 @byJenAMiller For sure! And even in cases where the divorce… https://t.co/FWoVNU7fjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheeler Expects to Be Confirmed to Lead EPA Within Days (1) https://t.co/EUgDiKcVFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repubs took over in 2016 blew deficit up. Trump's admin using the budget as a ATM for their own personal gains. The… https://t.co/PoKPeTcXGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Otelcom Who is PM? Where should I give my Booking ID with? Thanks, Dawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irene680NEWS Bags are already packed!  Blanche forever 💕 https://t.co/OtQwVgrQSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NParoubek1 @WynonnaFans @Cheri3031 @WynEarpUK @IDWPublishing @IDWEntertain @SYFY @netflix @BeauSmithRanch… https://t.co/cV03Lt9D6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ant_DC_ @SharonHepworth3 @gsmooth89 @ashnotatree @Romel_Garcia @fairyfiesty_fay @kasimarieDC @thechriswatt… https://t.co/eJVauRAA6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MechelleVindi @ErikaLRodrigue1 @JerryBales60 @SraBeckSIS @aggielgh @kisdthaynes @Seppanenkisd @KISDSchnitzius… https://t.co/hB9QXcn6vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to accept the challenge from @goheels1984 to post 7 professional book covers in 7 days. No excerpts or review… https://t.co/Z6dtEjap2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been discriminated against most of my life.... I don't know how much longer I can go on like this.... But I ke… https://t.co/zFpU3JfGgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizqueenmama I just dropped off 3 holy terrors at the front door of their school. My someone have mercy on their teachers.]]></document></documents></author>