<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ShaunWoodly 1 of 1:The policy they’re trying to pass is bad...if you’re trying to recruit and retain more black te… https://t.co/BTv3zR8sHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to set your clocks ahead one hour before going to bed tonight!😉  Posted withrepost • @fbc_rh Don't for… https://t.co/JgXF1qlSrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The sh*t has its perks to , ain’t it “ - jayz #youheardaboutus #watchyourmouthwhenyouaroundus… https://t.co/CgWPx4HOmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCorcega18 @PatoCastillofic @SusyGonzalezDr Muuuuy buena novela, ya la vi yo.... uff...  DIA 8 SIN ARISTEMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m here.   I’m supposed to be there, but someone thought they could get the signed document back from Puerto… https://t.co/bYSULuXQn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Mikko scores his 30th and doesn't jump up and down like he's won the #StanleyCup? #WhatInTheDuchene?… https://t.co/QqVFbDWx19]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife and I watched @kenjeong Netflix special. LOFAO, Ken. More please. Tran Ho...........@KenneyBaden… https://t.co/81tl5fMqTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokepokechi We are and your Belmont location.  PLEASE consider adding another location at Elston and Addison!!!… https://t.co/pmUgVTIi22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muse rocked my socks off tonight! #SimulationTheoryWorldTour https://t.co/5HTvPxqIjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fearmywrench @danharrisndp Yep, pixel 2xl here and yeah. Pixel.  It's the iPhone of androids. Make of that what you will. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thursday World! #sunrise #surf #zen #epic #thursday @ Atlantic Beach, Florida https://t.co/OOapCk8488]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’VE SEEN EVERY GAME MINUS BC AND EVERY SECOND YOU WERE ON THE FLOOR WS ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL AND AS ALWAYS I’M NOT… https://t.co/9pccEiEXxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Buddski Never forget it bro. Just told my buddy that story the other day. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree 100%. I also agree she should be sworn in with the Bible not the Koran.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have to go see this again. I really wanted to love this movie. But I just barely liked it. Some amazing actio… https://t.co/jPhFALkZdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you be surprised to see #statistics like this in your 911 system?  What if no one responded to your… https://t.co/K9l6sLtjt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting thing I’ve noticed after the snow melted in the Seattle area: you can tell where drivers like to cut in… https://t.co/Mcp13opsUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TheRuler Exactly like just keep having sex for free and mind your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby @kdcca7 The locals need to revolt. Their govt is corrupt. Sic the fbi on them. Oh wait, they are corr… https://t.co/4s7yIMqxKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a short break , Sarah Anderson comes back in the 100 Fly with a vengeance taking 7th in a personal best swim!… https://t.co/lfbft5AVou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyVirginOK Seriously have thought that for a while they should just spin it off as it’s own show like they did… https://t.co/dCEQiTzCil]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man of power, Trump!  Finally, the transparency of all his dealings is going to be exposed, that for two years, t… https://t.co/l6yYBHtnt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travis_crane9 @JohnKraus17 @AFedoriw @groovygrover14 welp my life is a lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManaRampMatoran @Timcast It's still there it looks like https://t.co/5bWMgo8DmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV @ChristinaTippen @LSUBasketball @SEC @DanWetzel @YahooForde @PeteThamel He is done ... and LSU better brea… https://t.co/UyBW0ieH6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is why you are in Vietnam, to tweet and and disgrace someone. Focus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[C'est clair, non?!?!?!🕌😱🦄 #Islam #Polqc #assnat #polcan #france #UE #RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade_deserae @_aliyah___ ooop... that was below the belt 😂 https://t.co/1G7hipB273]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanjay,  Think you'll enjoy our latest @theCUBE Promo https://t.co/gNAQp7ekzp @spoonen @dvellante @furrier #theCUBE… https://t.co/CR0smek1cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Dr. Seuss’ birthday. Read Across America! #ReadAcrossAmerica https://t.co/kK7gx2THod]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day hike along the border part 1 @ Tecate, Baja California https://t.co/XyqEnP4zRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryMayer I take that back Briggs! he ain't get no love? When the bears were down he represented them in the pro… https://t.co/HoXlZwaxwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week's #Plyometrics circuit #StrengthDevelopment #StrengthAndConditioning #Strength #StrengthTraining… https://t.co/xww5PZZAKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBB Bloomington South @bhssbasketball 86, Jennings County 60 final #ist @indsportstalk @scorestream @wthrdesk… https://t.co/ryHwHmY2pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been awhile for a selfie. #nofilter oily nose and all 😕 @ Downtown Cleveland https://t.co/dySP3euSXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hikes Point, Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/YRFOviqnIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[USF Dons basketball survives overtime scare from last-place Portland - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/9iasZRmoTa 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl just tried to take a picture of me eatting my scooby-doo snacks on the bus I look over and see her phone… https://t.co/b8deeDBund]]></document><document><![CDATA[May the Lord bless you and all the family and comfort you all during this time of loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of my feelings about Aster up to this point, I’m happy to see Florence Pugh land a starring role.  She’s… https://t.co/hmUaZ3y2wj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanFreeburg @bigten I trust most NC Trojans on basketball knowledge. And it made the complaint that much stronger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFPfaff Why do you keep characterizing the other sides as "punish all more"? Isn't the arg "punish white collar… https://t.co/DTIPu8t2un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vivianibarra Perhaps Judge Jackson will do a better job next week. Apparently, state charges could be brought against him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Deal32 Pass Carl my best. He spoke at Southern Miss right after Katrina. We were state together in the 1/26 Inf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to Robert Kennedy about the conditions that we have endured and are in the works of getting better rights a… https://t.co/kIUX8rcm3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ihapp_1 @PolarisRZR Remember when Jay Williams thought it would be a good idea to ride a crotch rocket?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Diamond and Silk you are the best. And I’m riding with Trump all the way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_steffens_ I’m dead 😂 I can still picture that in my head to this day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LannyDavis you’re a piece of shit! You orchestrated this and for what? Get the heat off of Clinton? You know that’… https://t.co/kohnnyyg0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[“As we walk with our God we desire greatly His strength, comfort, power and peace. The realization of these, and th… https://t.co/AMm8SgzPnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A stalk and pounce win by the Kentucky bred son of Flat Out with @MPedrozaJr in 1:10.79 (Fast). Won 6F debut… https://t.co/8FccU146vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon Gray’s haircut went from hippie to white supremacist. https://t.co/M99hcGWC4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arolexion and “overnight”, yikes, I feel a better name could’ve been chosen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaining more shoulder mobility after a painful , dysfunctional screening. Internal/external rotation tests, as show… https://t.co/gzoH7jRtbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karly_beckett I feel like i deserve a bottle of titos, any idea when that’ll show up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawk2389 @zattackjb1 I will talk to jake 🤣...&amp; FYI you look better in yoga pants than her]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #kctraffic problems, WB I-70 past Manchester https://t.co/6NhUEczj2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I didn’t wake up for this earthquake then I’m not waking up for anything lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_randolph_west Minutes* 🤪  But science doesn’t take into account force powers or creative writing or deus ex machina.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sasquoofie this is honestly the mood i feel when i listen to Mine 😂 https://t.co/NK82vYAlCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_R_607 Honestly, sadly, what if he just wants to win a super bowl and he knows damn well the Steelers just can’t get there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpotterBrett Too bad MM had his ⛑ on, I bet Suarez woulda dropped him like a sack of 💩 https://t.co/oWpjkAXaZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CloudianDreams Saw that followed down the hillside and popped him tryna hide real quick lol @cosmicgrief would of… https://t.co/8o7KHSFUP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Done with season 1 of Umbrella Academy. Now to find a new show to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ergo_praxis @SomeStingray (I also like structural realism, though lately I’ve been leaning towards Realism Without Adjectives.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @cedarflats @cellmavin @zappafaye @lhtetrick @TammyJaben @JonMontag @JohanBBT @Just4BeerLovers… https://t.co/Lmj36gLvUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be performing Thursday March 7th @ 7-9  material from my new social justice spoken word book to be published… https://t.co/R1tLi6BjAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The near-matching doghouse — or is it a playhouse? — is, either way, brilliant. https://t.co/5Zxue6MI3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is no solution here without interference” @Puglaas says, reading a text from her chief of staff, who said sh… https://t.co/EfJSWqPGqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @CLewandowski_ @realDonaldTrump Donald Trump wants to pick a fight with Maduro so he can draw masculinity… https://t.co/z491D5O1Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veo el video del homenaje a @daddy_yankee y puta se me pone la piel chinita, junto con @DeLaGhettoReal y @JBALVIN… https://t.co/Zxi5h3Hx9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be pretty much EVERY political debate for me. Less sometimes can be more kids, take it from someone who… https://t.co/10oGhAJdTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen on Facebook: assholes want to call a transsexual a man when they find out about their T until she gets in thei… https://t.co/0bj8vZt7j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshpuetz Never too soon to get the Christmas list going! Adding to mine :D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promised myself that I would be a virgin.... until I had sex for the first time. (Insert person's name from show here) @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiggestSavage @JJMaples55_MST @Coobie_11 This nigga trippin, Lebron still playing good but his team is so trash. L… https://t.co/nZFtTscJod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoSenseNow I disagree!  The Political Climate today has exceeded past levels of stupidity!Even the Romans and Vik… https://t.co/V3wOvKNYHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaM40162992 Very Alarming: Boss of the Swamp says "Something ain't right" If you’re not concerned you should b… https://t.co/GAkk0m7YVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Who wrote this for him?  No spelling errors.  No all caps.  No threats or insults.  It is too coherent for 45.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ermacthegooner The best. One time I woke up hugging a giant untouched McDonald's bag 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichmondRaceway the anticipation of another @NASCAR race weekend is killing me come on April I'm ready to see some… https://t.co/b65xlnulJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCSD Don’t go out to find your car gone...Augggggggh! https://t.co/XTWcv302up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinpurcell I did spend a lot of time climbing trees when I was young…]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to listen to the demons in my head, they make a pretty good point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaineyOvalle And I was 17 , I’m just address the chief Keith started the wave  part! yall was dressing like him y’all was dressing like us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Texas. It’s where we have indicted attorney general @KenPaxtonTX awaiting trial for a felony and his wif… https://t.co/kzyTq6EIuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So weird that we got Yoshi's Crafted World stuff in Smash before the actual game comes out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Margarita Day! @ College Park (Orlando) https://t.co/l4WhFPIUJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball players can earn $300 million dollars but if an NFL player wants to make $70 million he hurting the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimichtw @NinjaEconomics My father smoked three packs a day of Camels unfiltered until his fifties. He died in his… https://t.co/fEns2l0GRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPM I am sure he still believes that concussions don’t happen playing the game if football...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @washingtonpost's @EJDionne is beginning a dynamic talk on freedom of the press for the Church of the Pilgrims'… https://t.co/QyBbuYGSeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spurzo @lindsayzoladz @danzyl66 I’ve seen the real one plenty of times as well lol 20+ mins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__arlicious My thing is I know one check I’m using for rent/phonebill and jus sit on the rest and the other I pay… https://t.co/uZ5febI6pD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh ya, Happy Adoptiversary Seven! -Year Four @ Huntsville, Alabama https://t.co/SOyF49OVSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best in political thinking and city planning, brought to you by the @DSA_SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many of yall have unknowingly tainted the well of knowledge and opinion all to see like the illest bitch in the… https://t.co/eHpYONrCir]]></document><document><![CDATA[so many people just don't comprehend lynching in the United States. New Orleans doesn't get it, since the biggest l… https://t.co/dRs8tYn3c2]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the news there was a law maker who was talking about the new gun law in Oklahoma. The law will allow anyone to c… https://t.co/MJ8kjMR7ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Significant Digits For Monday, March 4, 2019:      The Iditarod has begun;       LeBron James' team could miss the… https://t.co/CIBrH149qb]]></document></documents></author>