<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Where would we be without awesome #substitutes to jump in when staff can’t be there? Jennyfer has been an amazing s… https://t.co/ePM2Pu0dUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We liked the top of one sample and the bottom of another, then we felt carving and viscose were needed to make our… https://t.co/PTa7AGNFN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkellyreilly1 You know how much I value this attitude @mkellyreilly1 😂 https://t.co/l0uEwg70GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six Reasons Why We Need More Pipelines in Texas https://t.co/abbeKfq6ty @LongviewChamber @txbiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tootieepop i deserve this blunt i’ve been studying for over 7 hours now sus😭 and i miss u moreee💞💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[They did it!  Pulled out a huge win over the first place team!  Way to go Oilers!!  #oakville #hockey #hockeyboy… https://t.co/DloFotQIPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know everyone’s always showin’ it all on Sunday Bumday, but you know I lean right on this hashtag, but hey I’m… https://t.co/GywMkI9ccy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did you even give me your info Your friend @SharingHStories is saying it's your choice No He's enabling you to… https://t.co/KQFvqUPM06]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to know why someone built a castle is doing at the lake. #castle #atthelake #WhitneyTexas @ Whitney,… https://t.co/xmrqL6DJkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔸️⚫🔸️Let's get back to basics here, sometimes we don't want a warmer that's all fancy schmancy!  🔸️⚫🔸️ The Classic… https://t.co/8xnypbEcDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globeandmail Can’t get autism if you die from polio.  Oh, you didn’t get polio?!! That’s right because your parent… https://t.co/qv2tAhEoKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ki$$es from my snitchez 🤑 @ Westport Kansas City https://t.co/OGrU0WLTe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh goodie, we get to see MiSu at RevPro UK at @wrestlecon SuperShow?!   He’s been feeling something’s been missing… https://t.co/9U80bDdula]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anywho it’s all good bc I secretly planned everything out and it just so happened to work 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nottjmiller if your closet has a bodega, you might be a cat lady who should keep a closer eye on how fresh the fruit is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notjulen My name is Chloe. I am like 18 years old.  I have a Bratz attitude.  I am going to see Bratz the movie. M… https://t.co/zj42WqBGbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmund_Fraud @boglethemind @WendyOrent @jkellyca @Rosewind2007 @doc_habibi @VeritasEver @Siubhan_H @badzoot7… https://t.co/dRAQcPr3fL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrangeCone I worked the concession stand at the ball field where my step brothers played. I think I made $5.50… https://t.co/DVdijnRNlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandongroeny @mzee636 Venezuela has the largest #Oil reserves in the entire world. They're being played by powerf… https://t.co/wtzHrivciq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe I won smash 5-3 with Michael, and I wasn't even being cheap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasTechTF Congratulations Chinne!!!! You are a great competitor!! Wreck Em!!❤️🖤❤️🖤❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Lowe's? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and information… https://t.co/0c4D4woAOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electrichippie1 I can only think of the crazy visuals A&amp;B had while playing that song on the beach. 👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had way too much fun unfriending &amp; blocking people in the past month 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually don’t like how restaurants use books for decoration. Passerotto’s use of @lonelyplanet as check presenter i… https://t.co/GrdJGO15lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/db90RoeNKT  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 644-33  What happens in Vegas stays… https://t.co/jtrctDCOHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a moment to stop and say a prayer over the Acosta’s  home 🏡 #lovelyhome #houseblessings nikiacosta03 @ Hesperi… https://t.co/98nWRB5uAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[For whites only: Shocking language found in property docs throughout Bay Area https://t.co/Lbm2pOBEZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[my evolving morality assignment has been extended from friday to sunday thank you God]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniii0906 The older and more independent Kyi becomes the harder it is for me to think about another baby ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a special #bucketlist item. #Skyway10K supporting military families. $700,000 raised! 💪 Our 6-mile connecting… https://t.co/kl2vYfi0gA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A murder of crows. Indication of snow. #Allentown #Pennsylvania  March 8 2019 https://t.co/iPoSa0NUcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock @phof_author @ciarakellydoc @LunchtimeLiveNT I have too many #passions to pursue to waste time.  Cur… https://t.co/okXdYx3vXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about selling your home? I would love to earn your business. ☎️704.877.4385 to set up an appointment to di… https://t.co/X1I5knPPxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cupofcee__ Girl I feel this! I have a dance mom shirt with Brielle’s name on it hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY THURSDAY!! I am deliciously SORE from yesterday’s workout!  I LOVE THAT!!  My BSP chosen class for today is n… https://t.co/n5LYUiK5nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mass_ave @BullandBaird Older than those Corning Cornflower casserole dishes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OversightDems Sen. Warren working to remove communistic Sessions working w/ "eviction of the planet" individuals.… https://t.co/vctElEfo4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FDRLST @seanmdav Prolifers only care about babies in the womb. Once born @GOP shames, cuts  funds to: housing, SNA… https://t.co/Ntbt0HYz89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep and I have to leave the house in 3 hours https://t.co/fzdR2hIuHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateTHuggins @KyleWithAnN @_pulloutking @ArseQueef @VoiceOfOBrien @samriegel Ah, but, do you know the secret of his "real" name?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoebchance @BeyondMeat Have you seen stuff from the @Reducetarian movement? While I’m vegan, I like their inclusiv… https://t.co/8fvbJ2qSok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I find out that an old friend of mine that I haven't seen in years has a child, I start thinking of so many questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the opportunity to speak to future world changers at Graham Elementary! As they’re learning about leaders who h… https://t.co/kkD4821CE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Littlebrowniee It's literally girls complaining that she not sucking the whole thing.. I KNOW they don't know what to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all need to watch Ken Burns American Lives. Episodes on Jefferson are timely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 13, 2019 https://t.co/fHbVcwOaCI via @YouTube.  Olivia Katbi Smith testifies Against Joint Terrorism Taskforce]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bag is packed...got some animal crackers and water.  All set for NC 😁 #travelnecessities #nc @ John F. Kennedy I… https://t.co/6WzlSs5J9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ignore the signs! All you need is love 💗 and the beach 🏝 #writersofinstagram #authorsofinstagram… https://t.co/oMUI0b2KD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landscaperstev1 @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @Itridpm @SarahGould_SA @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/d6pUmmxPXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house of red shirts for @SalArmyDFW Homeless Assistance Center zoning case at City Planning Commission Meeting… https://t.co/jhV1TOyOPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HousingWorksBks @wordbookstores @halseanderson @MaraWilson Massive FOMO here in Cleveland! I will have to walk wit… https://t.co/NERWYqPofp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpsterst @WesleyA14539788 You should listen and try to understand the truth, our country is in danger .  Read… https://t.co/37UFTaLGo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGranger_ @DisneyDadSD This is just to give them an extra year of control right? I wonder if still having thos… https://t.co/mymHJeMjTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I go to my sister's house, I come home with so many scratches from her 1yo cat 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on bedrest today so I'm gonna watch the videos Fr H sent me on his series on salvation. You know my fav Book is… https://t.co/wQjqtlMJb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYG_Steve I felt they really didnt do her character justice. Enjoyable, yes. A bit Underwhleming though. Cant wait… https://t.co/UuGKxlZF8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @khamenei_ir @Pontifex @netanyahu https://t.co/I5qBORlP9V HTHs. #TAMFOUR #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[this iwd goes out to all the fellas because as we all know they’re the ones who’ve really got it tough amirite ladiesssssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just day dreaming about last weekend. Take a moment to find the beauty in today. #TuesdayThoughts https://t.co/qsRcDvmyx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too, we all need to and start standing up to these ill informed bullies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goooooood morning to everyone at my work who uses 1727 styrofoam cups a day https://t.co/uDuDjA8dF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImpolaHeather @AMike4761 To think he was VP of this free country for 8 yrs. Don't they think before they speak?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was fantastic to be at so many shows!!! You guys put on a great show!   And we felt every moment of it!  Thank y… https://t.co/BNtZV40QQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone be so quick to up &amp; leave that I swear it don’t even phase me @ this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump MUST remove #BigPharma giveaways from #NAFTA 2.0 before Congress puts the deal up for a vote. Add your name a… https://t.co/K5XQnPKNkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The month of May is looking fun 😏 San Diego &amp; Vegas planned for my cousin’s wedding! 😍☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you speak truth to power (spoiler alert: they don’t like it). Make note of the justificat… https://t.co/iIcqvntRcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexlloyd723 @realDonaldTrump He sounds like he’s missed a few doses of his medication.🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satyadev101 @storygal87 @nowthisnews @justicedems @sunrisemvmt @AOC I live in TX,  and everything is spread out, s… https://t.co/8KChjLKgDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[home alone @ 15: dancing in the kitchen to @the1975   home alone @ 21: dancing in the kitchen to @AndersonPaak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You are an embarrassment to our Country. You don’t represent us. Come home and do your job. No one w… https://t.co/anNftPGF7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cafecito with Rosie on TV Special Edition Season 1 Episode 1 https://t.co/MsM9cGfvsa via @YouTube  Enjoy the interview with @RosiePaulsen]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinking abt how I only have a 91.43 average for first semester and it’s only gonna go down fucking now what that’s… https://t.co/PIXuD19ZBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeehanEDU @Twitter and @reenkberg we need Mary, on Twitter too,  for this idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sincityellen @DaveMontero @redrockcasino @MountainsEdgeLV @chexandrion @chexrox @girlsandgeckos @Pink @RionRebels… https://t.co/6HM7DjEYXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDunleavy You or your family must have never had serious pain. Now you want tylenol and all NSAIDS removed alo… https://t.co/isoQqN9Hie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found THE house and my heart genuinely hurts like I swear I shed a tear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 was such an incredible season and I’m going to miss this team. I’m so proud of you, @CoachBeaudin 2019 has som… https://t.co/UtZCEdKU6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll never understand extreme fandom over an artist/celebrity. That energy that is spent on posting/stalking (yes s… https://t.co/7iykEtD4l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great opportunity for our students! Thank you @DrTheresaDixon for making this possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hoping to get pregnant again before the year ends. I want my babies close. ❤️ I will try my hardest to get Elij… https://t.co/eZoEllM6L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[im sarah i’m 19 and i need to stop thinking things will work our for me bc when they don’t i get so sad i can’t sleep!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teutasah @A_Bylykbashi @InesDemiri1 @PranveraHyseni @eyeofastronomy @spaceyliz @liz_kesson @LisaStoj… https://t.co/Vb0Vf7ikCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson You just have to keep your eye on the crocheters. It’s a well-kept secret that they are generally racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini @AftermathFdn @GrowingupinSCN @KaraLynnsKitch @morgstaste @cinjinnichols Keep exposing this cult, you are saving lives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BY HER COMMENT to the world she had spoken against #BarackObama, #IIhanOmar has DUG her own grave. Therefore; “… https://t.co/I9L9kL4BA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am ❤️ing getting to know all the @Uber drivers around the east side! There are awesome 😎 people in this World!!!… https://t.co/XNVV5xxqtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Geez if anything it seems to me its MOST important given upcoming 2020!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WILLAVILA12 @J23app Such a shame they renamed them Hall of Fame or some shit. Still Katrina 3s to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idea for a movie: A Christian interacts with people who aren’t saved in a normal way and the plot isn’t shoving one… https://t.co/X8Dz02rwXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @realDonaldTrump so let me get this straight—the leader of the free world is apparently so inept that he t… https://t.co/89DQdl8yjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @tedcruz can you please follow through on these comments and lead your fellow Republicans?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below    Cl… https://t.co/dRGl4NVRMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bebixv I opened my gate to park my car inside my drive way and our dog got out momentarily. The bitchass city fine… https://t.co/U4bigrdkzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Hate him..PERIOD LOSER ASSHOLE AND SO ARE HIS IDIOT FOLLOWERS. IF U VOTE FOR HIM,JUST STAY HOME. U… https://t.co/mhUiAuvlIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Cause he's afraid of uncontrolled non-Trumpster rallies....I'd boo my butt off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesZekis Clearly typed this as they were letting the lights down and telling me to turn off my phone. He actuall… https://t.co/y9xxnnd4I6]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEYOND AMAZING NIGHT! Thank you so much to everyone who made it out and MAJOR THANK YOU to my incredibly talented b… https://t.co/Bdtgogvbzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ich_angelo @AngieExMachina @PaigeChristieUK I think it’s supposed to come out tomorrow.]]></document></documents></author>