<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I dont see how this rumpus re kushers clearance can cause trouble 4 trump. Apparently potus can grant a clearance… https://t.co/zVi7PD1scB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ewwww I have to get up early to do my hair tomorrow.....why I gotta have plans a half hour after I get off work 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[how are you gonna call someone 2 times and then when i answwr u hang up..then when u call back they say u have the… https://t.co/qUDkv5QStb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The great shrimp massacre of 2019 was something https://t.co/CvQDwps8bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry if i didn’t say it enough but Kehlani is seriously the prettiest girl ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLorettaBates Ain’t that the truth!  Thank you for using your voice, to spread truth!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler FYI Einstein was a drop out. So not sure what report cards have to do with anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I do this to myseld 😭 its 1:30 in the morning and im texting you because I miss you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAECHSBaseball takes the W 5-0 in their 2019 Season Opener vs. Churchill @echsathletics1 #HornetBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[already reminiscing florida nights @ Spring Break 2019 https://t.co/cf0ip3hIcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full #DiFi video, without editing. Always important to think about how the media and certain groups like… https://t.co/mGyJEgngHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Annnd who is going to sign this useless piece of paper &amp; waste of taxpayers 💰?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @Mimirocah1 So, as he makes jokes about Dems labeling them with degrading names says he should be shut d… https://t.co/MIyQZtbnbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaniBratch 😭😭😭 And it’s always like that! It’s at least 10 minutes in between the first and last goodbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that everything that distracts me from the pain is expensive. I don’t want to sit at home today. I want to g… https://t.co/dfTilkHMcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so insecure about myself and I know there are girls out there that are wayyyy better looking then me and I’m al… https://t.co/5umGcxeYeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant good morning ☀️  🌍🙏 I am up without no  Coffee ☕️. #WhoAmI ? ☝️😇📝✍️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Leo and Kate! 🚢 industry worldwide is booming. Our Long time project is a big success. People enjoy working on… https://t.co/iHVm2Mvixm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that faithful dog next to the casket of late President #GeorgeHWBush?  Today, #SullyBush became a… https://t.co/w8CwDARf3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcouros great presentation and wonderful to meet you! https://t.co/0Hrv3s7B60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @RepLizCheney Still goes on record that she voted AGAINST anti-hate resolution (which implies she's for… https://t.co/pCTZM4QBkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[young catherine zeta-jones is rly how i’m tryna fuckin be (part 2) https://t.co/1tcPmND9aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When republicans hold majority they keep on singing 🎤 no there there even if there’s something still not collusion,… https://t.co/ZxhXhnwH0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love leftover pizza especially when it's  #vegan pizza  I added  #avocadoes to make it perfect!  #govegan… https://t.co/1EgGmOSQfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Become a DoorDash driver! Earn up to $25/hour and get a $100 bonus after 100 deliveries in 90 days for signing up h… https://t.co/0dtggLDl6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow, snow go away, come back some other day...like next winter and not this much! Thinking warm spring thoughts to… https://t.co/oSLwdrJ7KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just walked out of my den where I was reading a selection from Fun Home for class to the kitchen where my mom was… https://t.co/it3rPAsvMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP ONLY DECENT AMERICANS IDENTIFY AS PRO LIFE.....SCUM BAGS AND MURDERERS....DO NOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t even see the tower cause boul big ass head was in the way 😭 like move nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholsUprising You gotta be old or Watergate Davy youngster to know that name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdfisk @politicalblond Not in any country.  The huge mark-up on essentials like insulin, and others, is cold pr… https://t.co/qUZP4GoiMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @Jim_Jordan Devastating is lying to the college and students you’re coaching and turning a blind ey… https://t.co/gCqyl2XjnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[1980's gal!   #retro #1980s #retrostyle  #1980shair #oldschool  #80shair #80s https://t.co/Iaiupcdscm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depression is real! #helpisavailableforyou  #dontsufferalone @ Williams Mountain, West Virginia https://t.co/ZZH9ZfdvrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[am I the only one who thinks @jakemiller’s twitter icon looks like he should be in one of those Ryan Gosling “hey girl” memes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmfaooooooo i told you I’m with anything you better hit my phone with plans hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nalaranja @johnlemonada @BeeGees wrote, produced and performed hit after hit! All types of #MUSIC  ‼️⭐️🎤🎶🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Animalmad73 That is so sad sorry for your loss of Alfie,at least you still have memories and 16 wonderful years wi… https://t.co/WVWuL85GSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ORK comment about fire and possession #Days @ForeverJandM https://t.co/fastXDQKN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re drunk off of mimosas and I accidentally airdropped photos to our uber driver and Mariah says to the driver “r… https://t.co/82HwbNiJCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gelson's Market - Pacific Beach in San Diego, CA https://t.co/VPQa1XirHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieKamphof Hope the farmers and cattle ok! :(   3 weeks in?  That’s horrible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poptivist I have strong feelings about this, none of which are probably popular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUTVMorgan @KUTV2News Not that we can see yet because it’s so dark. But we are just by the Temple and our house re… https://t.co/PejdmPnUcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop one today. #TGIF (@ Main and Levering Street in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/0naJBZgGmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corp125Vet @bbl58 @RealTT2020 @Beg1Girl @karli_bonne @Bamafanaticfan1 @BamaAgent1 @battleofever @KatTheHammer1… https://t.co/3J9XGU4eEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettgee @bucketlistfam I've never swam with sea creatures. Why do you flip your hand back and fourth in front o… https://t.co/3xPAbNqkRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cyndi94571032 @StanPic25845029 @AxleBebe @Alfie11Cr @Kingoboy666 @Velmajinkies @willamhariett Are you ok?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I dislike about winter is when you layer up, extra clothes make you appear "pregnant" when you're not eve… https://t.co/dPko2AttUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your son has to make a valentines box and he wants to be the next Blake Martinez ♥️🏈 @Big__Blake50 @packers https://t.co/TmGLO1crfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, ok, the one day I’m counting on my body to be awake at 6, it decides it wants to sleep in 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @IlhanMN May Allah have mercy on the souls of the ignorant voters that elected her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__franfine @muhriyahhh Lol that's my baby currently bc he wanna take nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their poison spreads! I can’t wait for #MuellerTime #FAKENationalEmergency @realDonaldTrump YOU ARE A GIANT POS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!....😊  @EdreiBarbosa1 #portero #mchi⚽️  #varsity https://t.co/2DtdZkGwED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Kingsway Community Life Centre https://t.co/RJwNvurb9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of spring training is being able to easily hop from team to team and see prospects from all over the… https://t.co/j3YEsNGNW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CunningSq16 @Ginger_Lyn_66 @readnallthetime @_monzon322 @strom_annette @L_ei8ht @brandon7nettles @tpcowgurl… https://t.co/b8UT5jSgJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times👯‍♀️#donuts #bubbles #wine @ The Strand House https://t.co/yhmeB7n29a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told Preston I was going to chop my hair and apparently to men take that as I’m going to shave my head. Learn the lingo people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Light, refreshing for a porter. Pictured with sample of the krunch berry gose, which was soda like and tasty! - Dri… https://t.co/NBWVtyjmb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sprinkles cupcake vending machine just off Michigan Ave. and view of the Adams Street Bridge near Union Station… https://t.co/VcbK8jU3ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BxglL @72cricket @sannbs @ChicagoPenguin2 @MrsSpuds @CSonafelt @sharon_schwan @RidenerTina @ACog1984 Yes did you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First showing with Dan &amp; Zoe 🍔🍟🍾🥂 @ Angelika Film Center - Carmel Mountain https://t.co/g2AddAveYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrtnzLauri It takes patience girl! But with the right products and consistency anyone can do it💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uterus free to a good home. Slightly used. You can repurpose it to a lampshade or a handbag. Whatever you like. Jus… https://t.co/Q2ALugC5Tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[yesterday was one of the worst and best days of my life at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anagav61 @irayd89 @Marisol_Madu @mercalmerida @TYCRRP @DAREJEMPLO92 @TitoAGomez @manueldun4f @HernandezSJesus… https://t.co/aaLOPse1PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieAngusNDP @vote4robgill @RomeoSaganash @JustinTrudeau @viraniarif I have been trying to get my MP Arif Viran… https://t.co/7fLC1TO8to]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve made so many wonderful flo friends along the way but my best college friends saw the EARLY flo love days in my own lungs era.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edtechgc @MrsCraneMCE @BrianMendler @edtechgc  you lose ethos with spelling errors;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy llega la susodicha, ya se me activo la maldad. Por que eres así Ana Cristina ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetoORourke Thank you Beto for stating the truth we all know to be true. El Paso is a safe city and was before the wall went up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just went on the best first date of my life and fell down the stairs right at the last minute... should i just ki… https://t.co/nZNzeL1ZAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your week with a little peace, balance and restoration at Community Yoga. Monday’s at 6:30 pm. Burrello Famil… https://t.co/L3p5t8nOyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanStandby @JoyAnnReid Please stop bringing logic into the wall discussion, you’re going to further confuse some people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am aware of my bias towards fenway park but i went to a early season school night easy win game and the ballpark… https://t.co/hzUAEmFPIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, even Nancy is carrying the Mexican flag, which just goes to prove, Democrats favor Mexico over the U S!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He already hung himself and is free. What the fuck are you talking about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rental Tube On the Lazy River by @rarbrew at @maxstaphouse — https://t.co/iH5PAmdmyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2ManyOfUs @Renevelation @Franklin_Graham Biology proves that God exist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyes are burning. Computer decided to reboot and update in the middle of working on the web. Air blasting in the st… https://t.co/O40WriOnBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sherryb6569 @60Minutes Another form of sexism in media can be the out-of-proportion scrutiny of certain women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesseniaahhh Try being their teacher and then let’s see how you feel 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pgmenchen @FEDER_ONG No es que me alegre; pero por lo menos ya sabes contra que dragón vas a pelear, ya tiene nomb… https://t.co/bF9sMVR038]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentines are so goofy 😄 Today is just another “Halloween” for kids. They count their candies after their class… https://t.co/ADRqB1JlTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[can ppl plz start posting crazy shit on their finsta instead of “im so stressed cuz school!!!” before i feel pressu… https://t.co/uphU4mHC7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyEmrick Do you KNOW how much time my curious/ADHD ass would spend during elementary school research assignmen… https://t.co/1EKSIGtUJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashley78833383 We just have rain here. And it's supposed to grow colder here this weekend and through out this wee… https://t.co/dTNiNbAvBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really hits hard when a person who you thought was your best friend talks about you behind your back. #fakefriends #lifestyle #cutoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite regulations that require those accused of violent crimes and economic crimes be kept separate, Melnikov say… https://t.co/QDYsmQnBiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow please tell me you will set up a Captain's Dance-off for @brielarson and @ChrisEvans during the Avengers Endgame press tour!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok pre-ordered Kimiko and the Accidental Proposal, the Uncommon Echoes books by Sharon Shinn and Beautiful by Julie… https://t.co/CHUVTVLlOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauty, elegance, excellence. 🌹 Makeup by me, and my twin idajohnphoto on the photography ❄️💎 @ Los Angeles, Califo… https://t.co/4II7kQbCdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[and now....I’ll do what’s best for me @ Bow + arrow https://t.co/wIgqEdmKc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Huber_ @fablefy @iluveducating @DrP_Principal @aweninspiration @spoonfuloflit @DrCaliGrit @PrincipalRLA… https://t.co/g8IICSH9Hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is #judyhahn, #holistichealth and #lifestylecoach whose #passion is to work with #midlifewomen to… https://t.co/ylsXSsy4vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucked up my toe tonight I’m pissed I was gonna get a pedicure this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi happy birthday I knew someone had a birthday today I never forget😃😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SleekSkinette #RedskinsDivaGroup #HTTR4LIFE #Hail2TheYeah @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/9ytQBUWtjg]]></document></documents></author>