<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@marisakanter OMG they are soooooo good live! I took my sister back in 2013/2014 and it was absolutely life changin… https://t.co/tsgsRtMjIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[77 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/nunKSoXiTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's amusing. #mirth #lol #smile #playful https://t.co/AWFTdaWlFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is local today in #Virginia. Headed for lunch and get 👖 😉👍🇺🇸 https://t.co/Meoj0pTuEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeachLife #Summer in FL 24/7  #IMIN #SaltLife #MelanieLevitz @ Boca Raton, Florida https://t.co/6bpQH2TUWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercial Property UNDER CONTRACT #realtor #realestate #ngrealtygroup @ Wilmington, Delaware https://t.co/sYNxwqdm41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fran_Bolivar @RomuloGuardia @MariaCorinaYA @AsambleaVE @jguaido El problema de los maricorinistas es que creen que… https://t.co/qkGC8crgan]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fortunate we were as a country, to have had you as our esteemed president for 8 years. ❤️👏🏻🙏🏻 Holy Lord, we so… https://t.co/4YFhVoABHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You Are An Arrogant Idiot...Your “Green Deal” Is Bogus. Nothing More Than A Socialist Program To Expand The Go… https://t.co/UlMDzKQiI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes my daughter Bianca loves you seen you so many times in. NY Can you please Retweet Donate to help save… https://t.co/xlX0z1g8ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's play a game...  Ron Swanson without a mustache or out Mayor #JeffLehman   The resemblance is eerie.   Cool be… https://t.co/z7rixgbWRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaOwen so would it have been better for her to have won last night and be an ‘Oscar Winner’ or is it better (h… https://t.co/jr1Dzx2nle]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a flawed balanced of equality of discipline....Be aware of those who keep up....#iamshe #idogohigh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealDiceClay I don't want the weekend to be over !!! Don't want to go to work Monday 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @DineshDSouza @AOC @SenSanders And that's what they want to do with America !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched my phone go from 1:59am to 3am. Thanos snapped and 2am faded away. #DaylightSavingTime #iwantmyhourback https://t.co/WoUG502lWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’ll have a 2019 selfie soon. we been adulting lmao https://t.co/Ccr7iP4l4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chunky Strawberry and Nelly Furtato sang “Promiscuous Spud” together.  My genius wasn’t recognized 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom “how are you getting to Cincinnati???”   Me “MY CAR....”  Mom “but.....”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the Philadelphia Flower Show. Woo hoo. #philadelphiaflowershow2019 #phs #flowershow #flowerpower… https://t.co/nrwTGcU95b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Nic will be leapfrogging Aliy in the next hour. if he doesn’t stop for a rest, he’ll be the first one to… https://t.co/N0bFcjL91Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re going back to Rodeo after this and I haven’t been there in so long omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ricos o pobres, como quiera nos va a cargar la chingada https://t.co/2y7l5crGpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot believe Virginia Gov. Northam is still there after admitting that he might be 1 of two people in yearbook… https://t.co/eUK7MgvmH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Oscar Winner @ReginaKing for Best Supporting Actress in "If Beale Street Could Talk”  She is giv… https://t.co/n6El7GZgi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it will. Everyone gets tax payers to foot all of their surgeries and procedures now....hospitals will go bankru… https://t.co/knpOLiIvec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaskDaniel_san @RobynUrback @acoyne This is the 3rd time I’ve heard this phrase in the hour #trialballooningnewtalkingpoint]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ricky’s the sweetest for Valentine’s Day he got me more equipment to film my videos, shout out to my supportive honey 🥺💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí la información sobre los servicios que presta el consulado Mexicano en San Francisco en Maya. -]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said he was hungry so I fed him a chocolate covered me. ❤️❤️❤️   #brittneyjonesxx #brittneyjones #queens  Click… https://t.co/iOYAan1Bnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TweetADay-I watched The Oscars last night even-though I didn’t see any of the movies! I might try to see a couple… https://t.co/60UYjtiMMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. #CaptainMarvel⁠ ⁠was such a pleasure to watch. It was an unapologetically feminist movie that tackled institut… https://t.co/gJZnwwxQvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackzblasted @tmcs Time to Prosecute Hillary &amp; Maybe a Few FBI Agents Too https://t.co/N3c0Cixg0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are doing anything to win at the expense of are country. AGAIN WHERE THE HELL ARE OUR REPRESENTATIVES?? THIS IS BAD VERY BAD!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NO1GifQueen My ocd is checking the gas locks on Windows smokes In ash trays make sure they are completely out but… https://t.co/lfJuA3Ncyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ Glad the cat got him back ! Kids who mistreat animals should be punished and taught it is NOT ALLOWED !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to go into the #HighwayMen @netflix #immersive experience at #SXSW. Let’s catch some robbers. Bonnie and… https://t.co/y5z5OqIzXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beastie friend 💪🏻🤪❤️#stnrgy360 #hiitworkout #dailyappointmentswithme #planetfitness @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/w9yTI23Obd]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and radiate! @ White Orchid Wedding Officiants https://t.co/sdwH6jWLWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a good time with these guys yesterday! @lonestarband https://t.co/I7SzciSYp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for letting me crash (literally) on the recording sesh. i couldn’t get up even if i wanted to.… https://t.co/qNJ0YaIzG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before my boss and I were in our 50's. #TBT #50yearsofSio #Galaxy @ Frederick, Maryland https://t.co/jwpXlSA6L7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anger , fear, and excitement. Are the most influential when activating customers emotions. Emotionally charged ads… https://t.co/tLowBfXWQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sounds like it’s at least a good start. But I won’t be satisfied until I see some actual change. #militarylife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellehacon Well, spring is "technically" 16 days away. So there's that 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnitude 1.2 #earthquake, 29.0 km SW of Stovepipe Wells, CA https://t.co/7aox2CoF20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenseiFredsMojo @esscarbrough @TanyaFranca2 @bcsdschools It was my pleasure! It was wonderful to connect with you… https://t.co/0vumcyAMJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klhoekardashian It is going to take me YEARS to recover. I wanted to marry this man. No one knows your pain but yo… https://t.co/X9wheU4QBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Súper MORENACOS y súper CORRUPTOS/ Saca provecho de ser político y empresario https://t.co/1FlIKUsDtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeanineC @besthealthever @peppertrumper @janninereid1 @theblackpills @mymynags @Italia191 @T_FLgal @RN_JB7… https://t.co/dxnzIpDV1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom went to Cleveland to visit family so of course she’s sending me pictures of my cousins dog https://t.co/aCgbHbQ5TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna be noticed by you. What do I need to dooooooo? 😭💕🙌🏻 @_DomoWilson1 I wanna be friends 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been watching The Search For Elle Woods for the past 3 hours and I couldn't think of anything better to do with my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[...if he loses there won't be a peaceful transition of power...  Michael Cohen referring to Trump in 2020  Um...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh all my little brother does is roast me so when he complimented my eyebrows today I almost cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I like Man City  #ManchesterCity  #nani #ManCity    👏🏻  #ManCityvsChelsea  #MANCITY #LiverpoolFC  #rashford… https://t.co/2HG2xzbAQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GigiGraciette My heart cannot go on after reading about such a tragedy.  Why? I ask why a human could do this to a… https://t.co/0QG5hnu9V5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chips n queso hit a different kind of way from mamas at this time of the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww you're spreading rumors about me? At least you found a hobby spreading something other than... #mirth #laugh… https://t.co/szlJSXj6vL]]></document><document><![CDATA[mEn ShOuLd gEt TeStEd FoR hPv, u cOulD GiVe CeRvIcAl CaNcEr tO sOmEoNe YoU lOvE!  🗣YOU THOUGHT! WE DON'T LOVE THESE HOES!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sellis2702 @RealMattLucas I've never seen someone be on the side of a pedophile, color me shocked. Matt's sexualit… https://t.co/f3zgqwnhVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox I went through JFK in New York this week, sorry to say it was worse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to the guys that clapped for me when i jumped the curb on my Lime today — i needed that 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too little too late, charge him+ put him in jail with McScab, Comey,Peter Stroke, Lisa His Ho, Muellwer, Hildabeast… https://t.co/IaSHUIVT6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen Why does she whisper? Does she think it is sexy? Oh well who cares]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODO AQUEL Q APOYE AL REGIMEN ES CULPABLE POR COBARDE DE NO REVELARSE CONTRA LOS ASESINOS,TODO VNZLNO DEBE ARRODILL… https://t.co/ojmMZjlmh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freak1ngawesome Id be more impressed if he jumped and it pushed him back .. an aluminum can, those are light a whisp of air can float them]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ok not to be ok. We are in this together. #expowest @ Anaheim Convention Center https://t.co/uwgHlRX3j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to announce our poster for VPRC is finally here! If you are in the financial district and walk down the… https://t.co/gSIY8hLtIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Nancy Pelosi is openly and notoriously revealing her determination to destroy America and our Cons… https://t.co/CEID5nu2OI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz No one knows this more than you. Is there a dramatic change since you first met him in mental affect from then until now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordi González Arriola. EdPuzzle. | EL MUNDO: https://t.co/B9Z3NuTLsZ Mis compatriotas! A start up from my country. Flipped classroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[morning runs make me fall in love all over again https://t.co/HyDC4svCXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Queen Elizabeth look at memes. I wonder if she likes reddit. So many questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[And today we wake up in the awesome town of Delray. Looking forward to our Trunk Show @ChasShoeCo on Atlantic Ave.… https://t.co/xaP7yIxZSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTBogtrotters Same. Cannot believe how old that song is. ("73) Still sounds lovely today ♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mssinenomine Another one - all stores, restaurants and public spaces need a disability open-the-door button. And d… https://t.co/8BTX7XB8av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mojorisen531 Can I have an extra large this morning? Only if you sharing]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEC OF STATE: Farm life is the best this country has to offer. @weareiowa5news]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️😡😡Normalizing Abortion: Not If, But Wen : @FRCdc https://t.co/k0C16Jm3wY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this today... it makes my enlarged heart SO HAPPY knowing this school is a #HeartSafeSchool!!! ❤️⚡️… https://t.co/Cl3D8mFji3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Durermac74 @BET Absolutely! I really think that the parents should be on trail as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing concert. Emotional and energetic. Surprised I haven't lost my voice yet. @ Park West https://t.co/CTxnaTcBdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need very little to be happy, and I got all I need right now. Life’s a whole lot better when you have just the ri… https://t.co/jQCWuGV3Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[february 15: condoleezza rice and martin luther king jr both started college at just 15 years old]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perks of having both your brothers in CPD, parking ticket was taken care of 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trout fishing Friday was a success. Caught fish, grilled lunch and had a blast. 🎣 @RHS_Mounties @RHSOutdoorEd… https://t.co/PyvFP1A58O]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 more “Origin” drawings I thought I’d post here of Mika Watkins (the brilliant writer of the show) and @TomFelton 💛 https://t.co/nKXNCq8cyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ae9krs5Q47 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/K5TiqcZEVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[we came to jasmyns and taylor is literally here reading her textbook out loud]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s national wine day and Monday so obviously I only have one plan for after work today]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeachesWeho Tonight! w/ #cazwellofficial ! #beachesweho WATCH: https://t.co/pDDcbDz74q https://t.co/IuDTgoLLib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgePapa19 They can’t stop the truth now PappaD 🇺🇸🌹 #WeAreWoke #DeclassifyFISA https://t.co/esCUhOG2Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 @sarahkendzior That is the exact thought i had, as puesto, and he has been bribing people recently.  T… https://t.co/3lK2Yk9ub0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like so much joy ripping a long ass fart in my bed when no one else is there]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you announce you want something ( food wise ) and your friends cash app you &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet my new baby sister, Luna!   We found her terrified and freezing in an old dilapidated shed out back.  Luna was… https://t.co/9mUqdT2fdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the past 5 days ive literally woken up hours before i needed to and its driving me insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wheyen3 Just spoke to a Wegmans cashier who will be routing for Duke with her Duke-bound fellow HS senior....    go 🍊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlckGh0st Y'all really do but that's cuz you feel weak. Plus y'all always want to be strong in any situation. #Periodt]]></document></documents></author>