<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BirdBronx Two tree is accessible 90% of the time.some high tides cut it off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bill_goldthorpe Dallas doesn't have a 2019 3rd to give. Calgary does, but of the major suitors that was it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That natural lighting gives it a clean cut for this one. @ Capitol Hill https://t.co/Ndw604VV0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing people not wash their hands after using a public restroom is disturbing 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Si_Senior_ Usually 50 big bets. Sometimes more when there is a lot of big bet in the mix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[according to my calculations murder on my mind by ynw melly goes two times harder since he actually murdered two people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlivatiron watch the 76th episode of Santa Barbara!! Its unlike anything I've ever seen from a soap. Just watchi… https://t.co/R8gnjJMP07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ bretweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health iss… https://t.co/5nZADW6QsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was hardly the leader or the brains of the activities. “Handlers” did that. Trust me... He was an idiot! Still a… https://t.co/3TO3EHK4V9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3dsithty @wekster2507 @MyMiniFactory @Simplify3D @AMZ3D @gCreate3D @TheKetchy @apyrodesign @repkord @ddhedder… https://t.co/O3p6XLPi91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blummer27 Will MLB be commemorating the 100-year anniversary,of the 1919 Black Sox Scandal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn nigga just told the Vlone pop-up location , too bad ion rock that 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R4vendw4rf Being honest with yourself in terms of what you want out of life in order to be happy and putting in the effort to atain it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonalynLarson @charliekirk11 @IlhanMN They messed up..... bigly.... even #Rashida and #Aoc have to go... they are… https://t.co/dTpIjhjcPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Master Chief #digitalart #Illustrator #portrait #Creative #art #artist  #ArtistOnTwitter #iloveart #halooutpost… https://t.co/YM2SPZyNis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mercyfuldm There are folder pages with card-sized pockets and card boxes for MtG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barney Google And Snuffy Smith for 3/13/2018 https://t.co/83BL0dCAl2 #arcamax]]></document><document><![CDATA[New home is almost finished.  Here’s the entrance. @ Huntsville, Alabama https://t.co/zg4nxVdTix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I drink my getting ready to open Coffee Stout in a glass or a 16oz Mama Loca coffee mug? #decisiones… https://t.co/rmRMCt8dRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[An SUV that you’ll want to show off! The #Porsche Cayenne S https://t.co/FlSAvyDsii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Smart_Liberal @charliekirk11 What's it like in liberal La la Land ? Is there lots of pretty colors and happy son… https://t.co/SBNLHWnVv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LemonyCricketz It’s getting to the point that a phone purchase will max out a credit card with a $2000 credit limi… https://t.co/9plO4MxFDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are so set on complete equality they would rather be equal in poverty than unequal in the middle class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_pauleen We can travel the world selling drugs to kids at raves but really it’s just aspirin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pico (Chick Hearn) Metro Station - @metrolosangeles in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/1pQB8gx6bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Mr. Bill Gate how you doings? how about your family’s ? i a m concentrating in different things i well tell you… https://t.co/D71a8pOxfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fitzroytomos @AliveCor @BCBSM @VirginiaMason Okay, Tomos—  “Only in America and Australia!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @KellzBellzzah Not going to happen bc Democrats do a much better job of protecting their own. LEARN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to self when watching a reality TV show do not scroll through and read comments lol spoilers are a bitch #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food for thought.  Some of u might need to get off the Bernie Sander's bandwagon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elcompitv @TigresOficial @Rayados @RafaDato2 @ReneFdz @RayadosEsPasi0n @naciontigres @juanmgfutbol @robertoproa… https://t.co/3NCLGkyQw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little reminder folks  • • •  #on_target #blacksheepbarbercompany #imperialbarberproducts #tiptoppomade… https://t.co/Dzx9HFh2pG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joint Advanced Warfighting Division #JAWD researcher Alec Wahlman will co-chair this Conference on #UrbanWarfare… https://t.co/Hx0IvoKZAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iiiitsandrea My friend just had a similar experience this week in Hungary w/her Uber driver, except he "got lost"… https://t.co/dc2y6Vxazc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody gotta find the Jamaican cat that did the “Cucumber” song and get him to make another one. I’m trying to le… https://t.co/2YFAihGwMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BindiIrwin Hi Bindi! If you’d like to come to the @KMTR studio in Springfield to chat about what you’re doing, we’d love to have you✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the competition finals here in Cincy studying bridging the Ft Washington Way gap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often forget there is a comedian with my same name (@paulhooper), but remembered tonight when someone mistagged m… https://t.co/ITlkPE60cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Thus did Moses: according to all that the Lord commanded him, so did he.” Exodus 40:16 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say I feel sorry for him, but I don’t. He brought this upon himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nonnietho This is deadass us at least 3x a day and I love it more than anything 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stopped using @coinbase a long time ago.  For safety I’m deleting their app now.  These threads are terrifying!  https://t.co/Z5afKF6A8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went out with @Mochamami8125 and totally_gr8teful1112 to go see shawn_wayans and this dude was funny as hell. Great… https://t.co/qh26z3pBf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamster49er We are all human beings by we don't treat other like human beings at times I'm guilty as anybody else… https://t.co/woKSPrMlUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka Really ?? This winch should move out if this Country!! Yes the last 5 , including the Democrats oh great… https://t.co/AFa8kE3CcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Change “product” to “product’s target user” and this is even more true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else randomly check their Venmo to see if they have more money in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmoHobo @gi_jrock @_Mik_e_ @thedailybeast @BillGates @stevewoz Still sarcasm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWatt Reese’s Puffs Frosted Flakes Captain Crunch Cinnamon Toast Crunch Frosted Cheerios]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuucketHe4d It clearly makes me think twice. And I suspect I’m less price sensitive than most. Other outlets face… https://t.co/OpqKpX7PRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I’m obsessed with parents throwing cheese on their kid/pets....it’s literally the best thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MifotoDehoy.  Es de  la #Luna, #Pericos en  el  alambre  de Hermosillo y @ClaudiaPavlovic @CelidaLopezc...… https://t.co/mBIJO8pm7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #PLN can give you courage ... offer support when none is available where you are. #pstchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[D.C. at 7 a.m.: 52 degrees, on our way well into the 60s. A taste of spring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P_Ingbretson @mpval33 @WeWillQuackYou @Felix_Sicard My point is the Ducks keep their wingers in the zone for a 5 m… https://t.co/DAypTfOKCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE CROSS(n)Itself IS INTEL AS aBinary Code of(1s_+_"0s")..4(Masculine+Femi(nine),(X+Y)(A+Z)ions..2=A(ten)4TheCo-Cr… https://t.co/YydluY4sY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Any tran gender who turn from male to female should not compete in female sports because their sexuality… https://t.co/cFoHFdCX4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Of all the Airports I have passed through World Wide @EWRairport has the rudest of the rude employed...they ex… https://t.co/o5upBUzjhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The connection between Rooney Mara and Daniel Craig in The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo was fantastic. Exactly like… https://t.co/vmtngUvjcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consolation Round 3 — 126 Southern’s Ian Yoder drops a 5-1 decision to Hamburg’s Dalton Gimbor.  Yoder finishes his sophomore season 31-14.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lois Murray, just think how wonderful America would be if the Chinese drop a few nukes on the biggest cities!  W0W!… https://t.co/MGaLKcazVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICUFamous @ChrisJZullo @KamalaHarris Check out https://t.co/4eey4rlQSN  to go through the Bible in 5 years and… https://t.co/E5OjtM3tFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another commercial of mine. #foodlion #truckeractor https://t.co/OZRwYBIUvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joshua Gates crossed 5K. Time 00:27:59, pace 09:01 min/mile, est. finish 8:59 am https://t.co/TALXJ4CAs1 #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike's Discotecha de Silencio at @knotts We look like dweebs... Lol. #knottsberryfarm #SilentDisco @ Knott's Berry… https://t.co/VyD7fokq04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: Things just got PHENOMENAL inside the Elimination Chamber!  #WWEChamber @AJStylesOrg https://t.co/sn2ePUwhfO  https://t.co/fW3abi0ax9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Archery este mucho divertido. No puedo esperar para mas clases. Necesito un grupo para clases de Olympia. 50 dólares cada personas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roll Call Just In:    Trump’s executive moves will take money from DOD drug interdiction program and Treasury’s dru… https://t.co/f18nsVQb7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine going to a show just to talk the entire time. This will never not be annoying and astonishing to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoxHelp I’ll do it tomorrow I gotta work I was just on my way to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Western is in cruise control now and ourscoring SBU 12-0 in the 4th. Up 66-50.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live it like it's your last!  #sacrifice #desire #die #freedom #impact #twentytwentyvision #forboogi #leadership… https://t.co/PaQZo4dIh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve interviewed hundreds of people and I’ve gotta say that @DrBrianKeating is one of the most intriguing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpswaggerty Ahh. You are talking about TurboTax, I used to be on that team too. :). I’m the lead for the Turbo app… https://t.co/XH1roUNElg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking family to @HattieBs in 37 degree weather. ☺️ https://t.co/BMonJbHMUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp @arnoldgmac59 Bet Trump got some "Strange" that night! #CanYouSayManWhore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino That's what every conservative have been saying for the past 2 years without the Mueller report being out it's bizarre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legislators push for increase in renewable energy, and jobs via a boost in RPS requirement in Maryland.  Is #RPS a… https://t.co/JBmgcqDivs]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is playful. Detroit Red Wings Fans Are The Best! https://t.co/bSdi3ScJ5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s watch @Ruthless_RL 🆚 @Benaskren 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 #espn #ufc RUN BACK THIS FIGHT! #ufc236]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s also code to write, review, edit, merge, fix, test, and commit to some kind of source code repo (Git, Perfo… https://t.co/U9MJsDceas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cree_in_heels Awesome. It can be found anywhere. Here is an Amazon link. https://t.co/iJoT1jw9AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk about corruption. Amazing. What gall. 😠😠😠👎👎👎👎 _____ Texas Sen. Angela Paxton files bill to expand power of Tex… https://t.co/yugRMXhsNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet he is at least good enough now to be an @SECbaseball or call an LSU-UT series #balkon1stpitchReally?… https://t.co/EpFAMZkgzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews YOU are the scandal we have ever faced.  You are the biggest American Traitor in the hist… https://t.co/EwdmcTGL8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichSugarDad110 is a lie and a thief, he’s ripping people off, all his payments get reversed! Stay away @Twitter h… https://t.co/S2HlZGHZVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only days I miss my train by seconds are those when I have to actually get to work at a specific time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zmullis I just watched it today so possible bias but that looks like Mr. Incredible's suit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casssielou I simply think all statements with context can help create a lot more clarity. Just like how women woul… https://t.co/iRAlLkflE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cortezvisualart My god-Son told me the other day he doesn’t want to go to school anymore because they aren’t teach… https://t.co/nP7LVvNMs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experts see a surge in the number of children being diagnosed with anxiety disorders. Note these Xer parents are co… https://t.co/tjsQqn3Zxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Let’s get this (Democratic) Party started! 🔥🇺🇸👴🏻 https://t.co/KXbOkwCAsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_Cog_Science @Olivia_Gazis @markknoller @jguaido Whose oil have we ever 'taken', dumbass? You do however illustr… https://t.co/Bw1YF6hoAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caycedomarula @SWexner @juliomayol @patsyllamd @drcarl_vancouvr Interesting and clever. Tell me the main benefits?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That @ATLReign v @Fusion match was intense from beginning to end! Super sad to see ATL fall 3-2 in the tiebreaker.… https://t.co/aS2V12T9NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winstonCovfefe @sxdoc Watching this today I thought we’ve been invaded for a second]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaioccoNBCS @Steelersdepot What? I thought AB already had this shit all planned out??]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Ruston a man told me he started he opened his oil change shop for under 30 bands that ain’t nun frfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my best friend, my partner in this world, the love of my life, the woman who delivered our perfec… https://t.co/ozj03Zfou8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks #adidas for sending these #ultraboost gems out early. @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/VJZblgSlZM]]></document></documents></author>