<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks It’s a colon: so what’s next now that we have your attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse Not you Dr. Kruse. You know who... https://t.co/PueLBJQeXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately in WV for a conference right now. Packing my bags and heading back to CA. What a horrific human he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clvrgrl24 Khloe has the worst human as her bf he is trash dude this kid doesn’t respect Shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep so I just ordered this canvas of my fav pics of our trip and honestly I’m so happy! https://t.co/ExntIJDHXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @metmuseum was mind-blowing. We could have spent DAYS there. #newyorkcity https://t.co/IWj3HcW0y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Follett Corporation? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description an… https://t.co/96YlN2gpzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eventually I have to stop binge watching @SchittsCreekPop on a loop, but not tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was awoken at about 3:15 am, by a Facebook Messenger alert. Thankfully, no emergency. Just my 17-yr-old niece in… https://t.co/As4UMKlac5]]></document><document><![CDATA[he interrupts every reporter's questions.  He has zero idea what is going on.  Rambling.  This entire… https://t.co/WYTYK57qrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom has a fucking law degree and continues to ask the most ridiculous questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Kim drops me off I tell her to text me when she’s home but she never does. At least I have her location 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuz did a full back flip in mid fight I would’ve tapped out right then and there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie And none of us like you anymore! #turncoat #JohnMcCain #honor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolGarofolo I followed all !!   *I follow back all MAGA*  # #KAG2020 #MAGA #MAGAVeteran #TeamMAGA #BackTheBlue… https://t.co/9y8nP914pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record I drive by the Carlucci Boat Ramp to and from my house every day.   #jaxpol #ilovejax]]></document><document><![CDATA[How ridiculous! Whose fault was it when, because of Climate Change, Kansas became an ocean and then later dried out… https://t.co/pioSI0om9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep trying to come back to twitter and I think I’m too far gone idrk what I’m doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019... isn’t it about time girls stop being bitches and learn to be nice to other girls???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLLobster Thank you got them from my new sponsor @Anne_Fontaine  in Aventura mall! Go shopping 🛍 have fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth0505 @torij126 @LivingIILove @LovelymarisaT @Flawsey @DianneRoss1231 @JoAnnluv2clean @jodisjoy @Ingaharden Goo… https://t.co/ARvDhX6LnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the weekend #MyrtleBeachGolf @DJWorldJunior @MyrtleBeachGolf https://t.co/84Wqgv4Hlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roybelly @NABJ @jemelehill @bomani_jones @rolandsmartin @AprilDRyan Congrats!! All hail, Princess Clare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have clearly never watched the British reality show “What would your kid do?” on YouTube. I have if u couldnt t… https://t.co/w6lSwZV9QT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roll into the newsroom @ellie_mir already has coffee made. I’m already winning this #Monday. (This is also defiantl… https://t.co/UGt9mpfoVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love Fraction Splats in 5th grade!! @SteveWyborney https://t.co/P1CZcypjVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ottawa should create a drug agency to oversee national #pharmacare program, expert panel says… https://t.co/7Gzm54FgFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A must watch! What a story of turning tragedy into triumph by @MarisaJacquesTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful New Liskeard Waterfront. :) #beautiful#love#Valentine#couple#happy#beauty https://t.co/uxAptJndG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe is fr still tryna protect tristan, i literally CAN NOT keep up with the kardashians man as hard as i try i just can’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAES Tiger PE Kids Heart Challenge So proud of this young man and his efforts!  Nearly 50 minutes of continuous jum… https://t.co/NfMApZorIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherokeeHope_ Aspen bites the shit out of me and like I can’t get mad bc she’s growing 😖😖😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoapDigest @lesliecharleson @GeneralHospital Happy Birthday Leslie. 🎂🎈Thanks for giving us the enjoyment Monica Quartermaine!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#boodupchallenge #boodup🔥#challenger #challenges #propstyling  #yass  #getitgirl #viral #viralvideos #viralvideo… https://t.co/GXlG5j6PEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how you slice it, that’s one bad #golfshot @ White Bluff Resort At Lake Whitney https://t.co/jVns3kcxIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yermhyuns this might have been the hardest decision I have ever made in life!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob_Motto @arttavana McCain's emotional moment was when she started talking about anti-Semitic attacks on Jews  (a… https://t.co/br12vFtkWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collins3779 As a Georgia Tech grad, I have the same visceral reaction to the color red. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel The things you say when you have nothing of substance to say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had to block my sister cause its a surprise cause shes due on the 8th and im gonna be an aunt hhhh I wanna buy sm… https://t.co/g8ki1SEiEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwback to Saturday night at @astonmanorsea . #seattle #astonmanor #djlife #dj #parties #shanthadon #dnasaturday… https://t.co/is2rNnWVRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists Like this trade rep dealing with a toddler, I’m sure the military folks have told him the nuclear co… https://t.co/dPLq9qlczp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New nails finallyyyyy~ #lavishnails @ Lavish Nails https://t.co/YC7tRw7ujS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @505PIR @mwlynskey @heckubiss @JojomolojoLF @bkmorrison @cbcasithappens @KevinGFox @shirfire218 @achs_fred 🤣😂🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The music is blaring and the kids are dressed in their finest. Thank you @ChapelHillOCSB parent council for invitin… https://t.co/TjQedXsyCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakeronwash38 @Athletics @DaveKaval What’s your point? https://t.co/5pLt5qvWSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[But to him that worketh not, but believeth on him that justifieth the ungodly, his faith is counted for righteousne… https://t.co/zGteQwSwR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNilsson I loved this so much when I was little I named my dear Sheltie Arrow. xx Me and my Arrow. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eagles Prrparing for a Shakespearean Experience -Vanity Fair https://t.co/Bws77CQRSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexaWeitzman This is such hard stuff. Robin Einzig asked me to be mindful not to normalize this behavior, even if… https://t.co/L3jX6kkgV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make no mistake, every prayer you pray gets answered, even tho sometimes the answer is no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_board @mingram0 Now THAT just went to a whole new level on the CRAZY meter!!!!! https://t.co/eVDnakQnkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesWStork Accidentally tapped Obama when i scrolled up the screen. My vote should have been Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#flatironbuilding #empirestatebuilding #sohodistrict #cushmanrow à Flatiron Building https://t.co/gfVSfwPvhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion por desgracia: estoy cada dia mas orgullosa de ser española🇪🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hailey played her last game as a Wildcat tonight. We could not be more proud of her hard work and determination the… https://t.co/cuiGagxQLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying this Sunday morning before the snow gets here! #sunrise #PortsmouthHarbor @MichaelPageWx @NBC10Boston… https://t.co/GBV9hIxF2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an awesome high school wrestling career! There are a bunch of young boys running around Elkhorn hoping to be… https://t.co/lGF0uAJAbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris Chris, for all of those Trump has forgiven for their horrific acts, there better be a pitchfork wai… https://t.co/nT4Sn0yZAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday: Fantastic, much needed mental health day   Today: 7 am vet emergency  Lol universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdanClay You bet. At 77 he should know the rules. I’ll take a knee to support the woman or gurl involved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it's 10pm and there is 17' of snow outside, but I just needed to taste summer #pulledpork #coleslaw… https://t.co/WxWfCY8wdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning  @HomaBashWEWS good to see you on this sunny Saturday!! Enjoy your day!!! @WEWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConwayShow @TheMonduce @AronBender @AngelOfTraffic @belliobellio @MarkTLive Happy Birthday Monduce!! DING DONG WIT… https://t.co/OZJQ2mwxI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/07/2019 • #Art • #worship 🎶🙏🏻💜 my #King 👑 in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻 #blessed @ Conway, Arkansas https://t.co/qhXdrhSCxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our new chief of police sucks, hasn’t been within a month since Michael Harrison (former chief of police) left and… https://t.co/zxmFN1JtrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dzyngrl My dad always razzed me about liking fruity beers. He said, those are for girls. Yeah well, cut to 6 month… https://t.co/aqRWdvs2HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a new way to medicate? Visit our store to find out why different spectrums of cannabinoids are super he… https://t.co/oiRXXo3mKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got so many thoughts in my head....deletions are coming!!!!! #SufferingIsAChoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VegasRebs I’m from Oxford, Mississippi. He doesn’t represent me at all. https://t.co/g09Tn1n45g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all need to fix what you say sometimes like sometimes y’all don’t think to yourselves “is this offensive?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pink bridgestonearenaofficial #funhouse @ Bridgestone Arena https://t.co/R9BCOOdRsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my girl gang: we got this 👊🏼💋. #internationalwomensday  . . . . #cocoincashmere #fashionstylist #personalstylist… https://t.co/AQ02XDvIgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stpatrickcathedral #ilovenyc #nylandmarks #architecturephotography #femalephotographer #nycphotographer @NYLCstaff… https://t.co/PABGPtbJoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna wish a big happy birthday to the only man I would break out my kit and cut hair out of my trunk in a parkin… https://t.co/YYxcUv1GJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary  I’ve been on Twitter with my annoying stream… https://t.co/Gc63rxrolv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemcgraviewri is excited as it’s only 6 weeks till we’re off on another friezenyc Art Adventure… https://t.co/SOtylFRmey]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s 16 and still believing in the alien mission. I just can’t with this family anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenPNew And I would do anything for love I'd run right into hell and back I would do anything for love  .... but I wont do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you love wine and food. And it’s Valentine’s Day. The question:  will you be drinking Oregon? Washington? Or C… https://t.co/80L6prxAKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #Consequences for #BESTLYRICS at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/HnVutU2ew6]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @DrSamiSchalk, ”As academics, if our work does not aim to be relevant in the world, impacting and helping peop… https://t.co/cOzqlh0RB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time since my surgery I don’t need to take painkillers or antihistamines to help me fall asleep and I… https://t.co/klXvzgaCX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make the Sonic the Hedgehog movie live action you cowards. https://t.co/DkckWLd6Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim said he’s never watched the last episode of The Office, and now I’m on the last episode of The Office and yep y… https://t.co/EViHaVqn71]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we truly love our friends, we sleep on them. 💤🐾💕#babsworld #flamingo #bffsforever @ Silver Spring Township, Cumb… https://t.co/0uMYfhnzJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the blog today is my latest quilt tutorial. This beautiful Neapolitan Quilt was made with the help of my officia… https://t.co/fMBRwtRzfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[a Bri out of the deal so he'd best be putting that tux back on. haha. She's crazy about Tae. What's the deal with e… https://t.co/23PwnLcsqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so damn windy outside. I’ve watched the wind take out so many of my customers💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t ever want to experience the heartbreak and pain that Ann endured. I would never inflict the heartbreak and… https://t.co/c6qA0r1V0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanleanne_ ahhh happy birthday beautiful girl. i hope u have the best one yet, u deserve it. xoxo 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[We took 3 photos. We decided this one was the winner. https://t.co/OZxFrZsVIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torylanez No, no, no cheese! None. Nada. Plant based cheese only. Cheese clogs the small intestine and messes with… https://t.co/srT5YYuKSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am LIVING for this promo time for our boy 😍😍😍😍😍 YES!  Get him those interviews, send us running around looking fo… https://t.co/aesoiJ1RzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 I hope all the Jewish-Americans who voted Democratic, will finally wake up and vote these evil anti-… https://t.co/5FCDWZZAeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latinos are not monolithic. ~Ben López @NALIP_org 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽 Say it again for the people in the back! #sxsw #sxsw2019 https://t.co/C7NQDqdSWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING interview with @MattJackson13 and @NickJacksonYB on the road to #DoubleOrNothing and a lovely tribute to… https://t.co/q7lRVeosuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was taking cough drops the whole time I was taking vitamin C’s 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg It was for the best that I was in the air for it. https://t.co/jVPjL4pVBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdavidbaucum Oh JB, you are the sweetest!  We will always be friends, and the Rasco’s are pretty fond of the Baucum’s as well!]]></document></documents></author>