<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@anniecordy1990 So the guy who was the lead choreography for *NSYNC and Brittany Spears had no talent? You are delusional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not normally a hat 🎩 guy. But when it’s snowing outside... ❄️ Happy Snow Day. . . . . @villagemkting #snowday #hat… https://t.co/qGcij4QPcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re lazy and you don’t want to cook... thanks @Grubhub @kfc https://t.co/faBp7l7ySs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for the downbeat at Woody’s. Come on down and get your 90’s fix. @ Woody's Press Box https://t.co/cuXVQITKDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWD44773567 @wwwbigbaldhead is the only actor keeping the show interesting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only fitted cap I'd rock is 1 that's universal!!! Fits every1 the man above created!!!    Except maybe all u saint,… https://t.co/BFpLZkm9B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @LiquorLockerLa in Los Angeles, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/RDp1u2i40f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnShawProd Betrayed by the people he shelled out 3500 to. They need more than 3500 to go to jail for you. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betting the under is in-American @stoolpresidente. But yes, da fuk happened to big Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flower Mound RB @pierce_hudgens rising Senior will step into a major leadership role this season. At 6,0 193 Hudgen… https://t.co/AxcU9e82oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[the machine that started me down this weird road https://t.co/w2ySxX7DyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen It will be a real Bronco with a bare-chested Putin and Trump riding side-saddle behind him. https://t.co/DsHrgjSOOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tess_mx Buenos días Tess, que tengas un excelente jueves 😀🌷🌹🌺. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb (Not necessarily the Beatles but just what if I went back in time and pretended to write future awesome songs)]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a set of say the 25 largest (non-FAANG) software companies whose internal tooling likely contains several v… https://t.co/VB1FGLOYSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[dj [shouting]: THIS NEXT ONE’S A REAL BANGER, AAARE YOOOU READY??  this next one:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hintofspy @StepByStepWDW But you live there and have experienced it. Others have not. Your opinion is very subject… https://t.co/b4YKDbMm4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruChristopher @stevenisaverage For me, your guyses pics are like the same visually when so small so I just think… https://t.co/hN0uIJ1mp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic breakfast @IHOP, sickening eggs, no ketchup for hash browns, no refills, and Charlotte, the friendly spid… https://t.co/VXMa1wCxLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarryBunnyBaby Pizza sounds real good especially with pepperoni and sausage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PredsNHL Mental lapses and poor defensive play lead to two quick Jet goals and lead evaporates]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Penguins @NHLFlyers @NBCPhiladelphia @NBCSPhilly @shandershow here come Crosby!!🏒🥅👀😂 https://t.co/Htn8Nks4dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah yeah yeah just wait till rattler has to come in a bail OU out cause ya choking ..... again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piscopaliansour Jeff Bridges could play Joel too. He’s a little bigger, but still.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 3 @itsgenom full video on his IGTV   • • • • • •  #unitedmasters #tidal #sound #spotifyplaylist #spotify… https://t.co/diQPTvfyZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalybone @sabremikecarrol @MikeVacc Will do. Act like you’ve been in a division race before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wewantkandy @AlainaFerrier Tauruses really be sitting back minding our absolute business. https://t.co/Zc7WmfdAXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ese es el primer País que ha debido visitar, hay que acabar con ese tercermundista comportamiento Venezolano de no… https://t.co/hlNxI68Cnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there is a better than 50% chance that Trump will be reelected.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sanpatso5 @johnnyc1952 I don’t think Keuchel gets more than $17M per for 2-3 years. Anything over that I wouldn’t entertain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl You know she honestly doesn’t really know what it means to be a feminist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some woman that was newly elected to Congress was speaking to an audience of 10 about HER New Green Deal.  It's not… https://t.co/3O9ZtjmbY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your director moves the camera during your weather forecast...Sorry Guys 😬  (well you played by @StarDerryWX a… https://t.co/3IK33THCcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuellerSheWrote @ChrisTom Look to the fine print in her statement. Nancy is no fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterPaynePPKS @AyoCaesar @BBCScotland They called themselves socialists to get the actual socialists on board. On… https://t.co/Rm94de2F3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LFHSHoops , @HarlingenBBall + @SRWarriorHoops + others highlight all-district list: https://t.co/MwGPbEVTx2 #RGVHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could or would I date someone from twitter 👀 I only us as 1 thing 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[There cannot be a Riverhound’s HOF without these 5 individuals! Enormous contributions to the Hounds, but more impo… https://t.co/O3U1xLZ03E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NorthCarolina makes it legal to discriminate against gay people and the #GOP supports this. #despicablegop  https://t.co/UxoWb3vLn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU DID NOT DO ANY RESEARCH ON THE ARENA AND PUT OUT BLATANTLY FALSE INFORMATION!!! Then dodged over a dozen interv… https://t.co/FG0Og3rvpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly this was the best Oscars show I can remember, it was snappy without feeling rushed, going hostless actuall… https://t.co/fAzjLrSX32]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little snippet from a good article I came across today: https://t.co/hKBE6hucn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to be entertained, go back and watch Brad Woodson’s and Lucas Campbell’s press conference from last nig… https://t.co/wDPdEtVDmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world got to see how special of a place this is. Charlotte just raised the bar and opened the eyes of so many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lime scooters are leaving Tempe  @TyFox10 has local reaction at 5 pm on Fox 10 https://t.co/FAza6A8KhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen Being self aware goes a long way. I too know what you speak of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStarHSFB @SavelioToutai @jnewville7766 @ApoloToutai @BubbieOLTexas @youngchukwu100]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I literally walked straight into the manager of Biergarten (an attractive young woman)..... later that nigh… https://t.co/rodTzE8C5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came across these old files while searching for examples of concert promo collateral to show my Advertising Design… https://t.co/QWfaWwITgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long after being singled out for a singlet; years past "making weight" passed to passage rightly passed; hour glass… https://t.co/IEdkwCeefv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aclark30__ That’s interesting. I think he had a longer peak due to amare’s injuries]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last of 3 greatest games I have been involved with was 2003 coaching Rutgers @CuseMLAX in my home town… https://t.co/tyjpdq8s0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsshootinggirl @emhorst @cenobyte3 @casforachange You haven’t supported your statement with any evidence. Please p… https://t.co/p6d2rB37i3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurt not being able to see my boo @torikelly on Vday, but I loved her everyday, not just today ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas @JRPothier It's not just being given the C but living up to the C. If they give it to a current player… https://t.co/TFxQLexF6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileymozo @BarstoolBDevils Good one. I guess I can’t be a fan of a team unless I live a block from their stadium. You got me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foggy mornings yield to beautiful days 😎🤩🚴🏻‍♂️ #instacycling #stingorbeestung #fitletic #nutramax #cosamin… https://t.co/pmp3d7nKDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABV: 5.6% N/A IBU Color: Gold Aroma: Mildly strong hops Taste: Kind a mild saison, nothing too wild, with a mildly… https://t.co/i6kWNmNde8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonFuckWitYall mf be like “hey bro can you please bring the money back”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson @Tristanshouts @ZerlinaMaxwell alas, Bern is not a Democrat. If you want him stopped, ask Putin and/or Assange.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyBadgerFC @rodgrisier1958 @harleylama @RanchoDinero @schuelkecorn He’s also not from central Iowa. 2012: One f… https://t.co/iSl1sBuKhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherryChamblee @JelloWrinkles @jonfavs @AOC I will repeat, you are delusional and a hypocrite. I also suggest you look those words up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin !  GREAT INTERVIEW with @SenGianaris !!!  LOOSING $27.5BILLION is St and City future rev, 25k $150k… https://t.co/ULzFJc4EBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shut the fuck up, Trump. Cohen was your guy and if he’s dirty, so are you. In fact, he probably learned how to be a… https://t.co/mDEcMI56yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewieGilchrist and just when you think the insanity is at its maximum , it goes up yet another notch #SpaceForce https://t.co/JpvGkVIx2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will he talk about that time he introduced a bill that would have worked to defund NASA funding?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @realDonaldTrump iDJiT might work 20 hours a week. I highly doubt he's ever worked 20 hours a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream i met @youngbabycoco and cried the ENTIRE time cause i just couldn’t comprehend what was actually hap… https://t.co/nHYqHAJYRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RasDeELA Once again, stall tactic. You have done nothing but go around in a circle. You have ignored the requests… https://t.co/fZAxhaV8MT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand why it’s so hard for people to comprehend merging etiquette.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LISTEN.  I really just want to feel good about myself again and to travel more. That’s it.   That’s all I want.   ᴬ… https://t.co/pDC9UtEdNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple Line trains inside their New York factory. #RailCars  https://t.co/mQmQVTcM4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@langwittman @EthanRobinson72 Gafford is a great athlete first. He’s learning to shoot and pass. Chaney can be a go… https://t.co/is5uVReR7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roc345_mark @BGMorgan4 @Havemercy_2 @Tinley256 @ChrisLoesch @capricornmathlv @Newsweek For sure! I do agree compan… https://t.co/cNxv7D5CFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelinaSummers @richfromatl You are correct @CelinaSummers,@richfromatl they were both high tax progressives, and n… https://t.co/rbRljo4I2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhhhh, ¿Guaidó corto la luz? Y eso que no lo reconocen! Na guevoná de poder que tiene ese pana!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entering last day of regular season DFS league. Entered final week in 3rd place, playing @MikeSGallagher heads up,… https://t.co/oGQFJCy5Ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackHObcma An entire election and you lost so as in your own words they are consequences for the. Party that losses]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna go heavy against the grain of some of the guys on here and say...  for me, narrowing down Facebook Ads instea… https://t.co/8ffByFoh9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the teams drop out of the AB sweepstakes, if the price gets super low, you have to jump in if you are the Jets.… https://t.co/l4d0KYMs0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyJonesSC @RepMaxineWaters Ohhh Andy.. I live in El Paso... Dumb fuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgkfan You know what the worse thing about VS is..... they won’t let you try anything on. Copyright Dan Cole Copyright Wild Bill Bauer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think' she is a puppet for the United nations,the United nations agenda 2030 for depopulation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate to give any credit,  but that was a hell of good couple of saves by Murray!  #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BarackObama is the Forty-fourth President of the United States of #American who served the nation from the year 20… https://t.co/yEr8ux8E0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global Winter Wonderland is the premiere “Chinese Lantern festival” in the United States and this past holiday seas… https://t.co/5AlU6nz8ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, excuses. I never bother someone I do not know because of some rumors that have nothing to do with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acute inflammation is beneficial for muscle healing. Stop trying to optimize everything. https://t.co/QP8hAbNEnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbey_simmons I remember the day we learned of her loss, and am still sorry for it. I won't say the world deserved… https://t.co/85kf1WbabV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Everyone with a little bit of business will know that Rusia and his competitive advantage of energy production… https://t.co/98uX0G4igv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those killings in Aurora were done by an American no an illegal immigrant. And all the one before this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the two year anniversary release of #GreenLight from #Melodrama by @lorde. A monumental album in my lif… https://t.co/0FCJzxC1yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless The inbound wasn’t lebron a turn over and the pass to him when he cut was a bad pass as well? What’re you talking about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not judging the meteorologists for missing on a forecast, but I AM judging SWAT commander Mike Morgan for the w… https://t.co/BON1W3zWSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrazzzzzzzz @KFILE He cannot make people vote the way you want just like you cannot. That’s what you people can’t… https://t.co/mriopjwvHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Yep. We're in a fight over what kind of government is acceptable. The green new deal Medicare for all… https://t.co/qap5BXaaMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[HARLEY FARMS SKATING TRAIL OPEN SATURDAY MAR 9TH 2PM TO 5PM!! SHARE THIS POST AND GET 10% OFF ADMISSION!! (Only 1km… https://t.co/0CM7oKpfIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indyman08 This season has at minimum five rookies that should come back @turabicamkiran @Ninja_Natalie… https://t.co/DAhPr3U6jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roushfenway @RyanJNewman @acorns Nice to see something promising for Ryan 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[*shows dad painted nails*  Dad: that looks gay Me:......... but do you like them¿ Dad: not on you   ): wow dick]]></document></documents></author>