<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[“Truth is by nature self-evident. As soon as you remove the cobwebs of ignorance that surround it, it shines clear.” —Mahatma Gandhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattxdaniel @Crackmacs That’s the Age Friendly City policies working away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 2nd graders displayed their fabulous habitat projects for the artic, grasslands, rainforest, and coral reefs.… https://t.co/2qDJe1EuUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an idea; maybe we can repackage abortion rights as simply volunteer participation in the popular GOP family… https://t.co/RIJO7oEiHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part about your birthday being in a week is the free food you get from restaurants!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@labor4christ @BamaJaxx @stephenasmith The Warriors don’t need Lebron.👍🏻😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessicasquared9 @arnaudsnola Happy Sunday Jessica!! Lovin’ the hair tonight 💁🏼‍♀️🥰😘😘 Always Fabulous 🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[hence industrial capitalism as a social system cannot be said to have existed before that date".  England began a l… https://t.co/Wc4GmeumN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaceMullen @christifulli88 If you are running into a restaurant to get food; you are a citizen. Not on a job. Park like a citizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Their may be a number of gay men. Their certainly are a large number of child abusers. As long as the Cath… https://t.co/wjtdYlov9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby fever is a myth. Its not real. People need to stop using it as an excuse to try and tie down their significant… https://t.co/cuwct5bMJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROOM 216 STUDENT OF THE WEEK is Chase! Our Big 5 focus this week was completing work to the best of our ability and… https://t.co/WptW9SyQJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigEastSilver @ijustine @Brenda_Star @shalay @JeanieBuss @AmyJoMartin @ErinAndrews @Jenna_Marbles @heidiburgett… https://t.co/A9yVK9ay2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sir, it is my deepest honor to be connected with you! Your country is not a safe place for Whistleblowers. If they… https://t.co/GrOLHUrKYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBajicMD @RenaMalikMD Except... where does one find UB tape these days... :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump God Bless You and your family. God has blessed America🇺🇸💕🇺🇸💕🇺🇸💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just emailed my landlord to see if we could get a kitten and now I can’t stop refreshing my email 😬🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danieldaekim Daniel I have been saying that for years and if I knew who to write to get it to stay where it's supp… https://t.co/S8DQECmXHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I posted this everywhere...YES, I’m really freaking proud of myself 🤷‍♀️👏👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait...so they’re real blood sisters fucking each other ? 😣😣😣 im good luv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlkSantaX @agooding58 Take it from an old lady that’s the way it is &amp; the way it’s always been. Always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDWPublishing @IDWEntertain you miiiight want to give a little update on #WynonnaEarp before all the gays join for… https://t.co/fydmYwV5KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pulled a tick off of my under-boob. How’s your Monday going so far? #trailrunnerprobs https://t.co/RQ7OyuPouI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babaosamie She's just a WallSt clone of mommy, the self appointed queen Hillary. Snakeoil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Baloney.  Trump is the product of 40 years of one thing and one thing only, the party of craven hypoc… https://t.co/yKSH6Tti6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattwasfunny @ScottRogowsky @seanseaevans @hqtrivia @BarackObama Bread Would Have Been Better Than Yogurt To Cool Him Down...!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeremiah Martin of #Memphis has been 🔥🔥🔥 43 points , 8 asst , 7 Reb 😱... Tigers Roll The #Tulane Wave.… https://t.co/BpfTRTUV16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryw So very true! 😊 I’m looking at a place with covered Parking in a few months....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always thought if a wrongdoing or injustice had occurred, investigation started there and worked backward to find… https://t.co/MNE5HivJLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing I woke up! I accidentally set my alarm for pm instead of am! That would’ve been horrible! 🤦🏻‍♀️… https://t.co/DNFtnaFytf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Loss Prevention Detective - Oxnard, CA" at TJX Companies, Inc., then l… https://t.co/035u33DXNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haugmoen The snow is pretty to look at, but I understand it’s not as fun to clear off walkways, etc. Take care!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar #RuhRohYashar (aka Silly Goose)  #NoMoreTowelTweets  😂😂 😂 https://t.co/yKvahfOuXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hippocrates Circle then a hike. Productive Saturday for me! https://t.co/hgHlLh3uCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t y’all just remove yourselves from individuals or even scenarios that make you question your potential and… https://t.co/IQ2Sl8DExQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hidrees - love your positive energy this morning on @metromorning underlying the positive, patient centric changes… https://t.co/qOxgd9BSiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diegosvaldo14 @ducksdontcry Stop fucking bullying me I’m smarter than you]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just dropped our first D+ track and music video! Check it out! @DahliaElGazzar  https://t.co/Y2a8yACnYh…… https://t.co/RS6Q5YskAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceHere_ Dua’s hands slowly grazing st. Vincent’s arm and also her hands at all times help]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going where I want to go doing what I want to do I can screw who I want to screw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pammoran Good morning Pam! I was speaking to a school board member this week and mentioned you and @irasocol and y… https://t.co/ezmcFcVlHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Benny_Bee_1982 Every morning I get up and get coffee and listen to psalms and focus on Jesus as I CLAIM PEACE for… https://t.co/YNB5XoNVyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[To any blogger promoting a "designer dupe" that's really a fake - do better. It's not the real thing, especially wh… https://t.co/otuOm7x2cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marmel he's better at the "Have it your way!" one, obvs. Relates more to lived experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear the ones that claim to be the “sweet guys” are always the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you were wondering about my blurred out/cropped out headband. My niece's 7th birthday was yesterday and it… https://t.co/vmogUopMkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some humor. #hilarity #laugh #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/l8BDZUmRyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ4JG Have you had Sashimi? Rice is not normally used. Or Sashimiis thinly sliced raw meat—usually fish, such as s… https://t.co/QDITMJinKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve wanted to see a day to remember since i was like 10 years old i’m so excited for this tour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing Fat Tuesday is tomorrow because I am definitely going to eat my feelings to get through LukebPerry’s death. 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AfternoonWalk in #RiversidePark with #doggyclients #Ellie &amp; #Michaela 🐶🐾💕 #lovethem #rescues #adoptdontshop… https://t.co/IO9g3z1dFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was so crazy I had no spare time to say hi to my Twitter friends. So hi! Hope you had a great day! https://t.co/Xvy1jl4ubw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to wake up for class in 4 hours... I don’t even need anyone to come in a ruin my life because I do that to m… https://t.co/eFJv296WFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You just never know who the company snitch is! There’s always one! #Corporate @corporate https://t.co/lhDJ8IWde4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JR8Ramirez @NBCManifest @nbc What happened to Lourdes? Does she divorce Jared? #Manifest]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qP5BXlsIUL  #alstexas #sunnystrong #alssucks #als #lougehrigsdisease #fwtx #fwtxbloggers… https://t.co/UggXWZt3Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will say Burning brought me no nearer to wanting to read any more Murakami. So meh to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and Tea ☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/vy3OSwIZjq https://t.co/f1KmQEPn4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t seen @janson_chris, you must. His joy and enthusiasm is infectious. @AMTShows https://t.co/BrQ7xQBpK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I’m in love.  This is a bad romance, I think... 🤦🏼‍♀️😻   . . . . #happyvalentinesday #🖕 #love #cat #gato… https://t.co/4hl2h3SGEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathaPollitt @dw_learngerman Yeah I’m going with wem.  Because “mit” requires the dative.  Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey, Auburn Jewelry is on @jcrew now!!! https://t.co/tJorqACEWu https://t.co/fmSpkHPe5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[:) (@ Journey Church - Avon Campus in Avon, OH) https://t.co/a2dvd0VxO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odom_quinton @mattstokes10 What an incredible team to be down by over 20 points and still come back to win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChampionshipSunday @djworldjunior #stayawayrain #JuniorGolf tpcmyrtlebeach @ TPC Myrtle Beach https://t.co/rgUXuoauey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t Rachel chase after Stan? Kudos to Stan for leaving her after he found out she cheated on him w/ Danny. Are we… https://t.co/1Te1Ktx1DP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Because the news media for the most part is not fake. They repeat what(you) the President said and… https://t.co/UZv54hYRaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[bring the laughter. A creative way to give money as a wedding gift!  | www.homemade-gift... https://t.co/jD168KwluC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to check out our Relay For Life page in support of the American Cancer Society! We are so excited to b… https://t.co/adbMo2hJZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinder fun with sentence building! #KinderRocks @AES_Aviators @GISD4ELLs https://t.co/fdSvZAIcma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great results on how innovative tools can support your #fundraising campaigns and how this can be transferred to al… https://t.co/ou5rMnJS4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s put it this way:  Iowa has 42 pledged delegates.  NH has 24.  South Carolina has 54. California has (wait for… https://t.co/WmxvtGoOxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCPolitics Do these idiots not realize that science is based on provable facts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date nite with #ericchurch oh and this Guy😘 ericchurchmusic #doubledowntour @ Scotiabank Arena https://t.co/yK1EOscbrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chi0maa @BrownSunGod She didn't do anything he kissed her and it was a pack no tongue smh... She did not sleep wit… https://t.co/sUNpMWmTtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[All As put you on Principal’s List!  Hard work, dedication, and determination are a big part of getting there.  Con… https://t.co/IxkNY1IFpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí la Catedral de Ensenada BC, y así como ven esta calle, están todas sin excepción. Tenemos décadas de PRIAN, no… https://t.co/7DPObOnVku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selfoes First impression: Soft Lolita Weeb Girl Current Opinion: Still a Good Soft Weeb Girl but also an Absolute… https://t.co/bIyiN48fmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YahooForde One really gets the idea that we’re not going to get out of here alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeingJelly @FoxNews the problem is @GeraldoRivera is a joke himself so pretty much everything he says is going to… https://t.co/E8wYgWdvCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RMAC_SPORTS sweep of the 800m! Nice work, @gothunderwolves Thomas Staines! #ChampionElevated #EverythingElevated… https://t.co/wl6D2KYixg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelrayleneee Forreal! U know its gonna be good if the trailer has noo dialogue...Elsa lookin like she from Xmen]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am only slightly hungover.  . @chorizy getting drunk out the gate really gave us the funnies pretty fast.  . It's… https://t.co/t2j6NPXr98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good vetting here. That’s all we ask. Equal vetting and verifying info for all candidates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY up to date #LAMH episodes @OWNTV 👉🏽Countdown to Saturday, my hubby and I watch together, a great show with… https://t.co/ddUSpa6IKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein For some reason, and for no reason that I can understand, Jewish people seem to be hated second, only, to Blacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the day begins! @ Autry Museum of the American West https://t.co/kBPpNAg2ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[#papercutting #handcut #handmade #papercuttingart #cuttingpaper  #breakfree #artistsofcleveland #scherenschnitte… https://t.co/unaoZejV0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Boston public schools cancelled Monday due to incoming snowstorm. @NBC10Boston @NECN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pablo_DobbleH @LIBRESYLOKOS @migangelgarzam @el_viejopaulino @TurtleTrevino https://t.co/RuU4UfmqkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity And Sanders he is user he doesn’t give a crap of suffering people he is just living as a millionaire l… https://t.co/3Zxd1FUOsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lion’s Pose in the Po-co-nos. 🦁  . . . #yoga #yogawithadriene #yogacamp #daythree #iembrace #yogiintraining… https://t.co/PeJfqpo7gj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Andy is da https://t.co/fqw4V0kYZr! #wonderwoman #Station19 @JainaLeeOrtiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougBenson notice there is no fruit on this lovely framed piece of how decor. Perfect! https://t.co/sY2xslIF7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runcandice Agreed! But Six Feet Under is still my all-time favorite...talk about the best finale ever! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetimes @jenwilson Always wear your jeans so you will know what your waist line is really doing. Yoga pants for y… https://t.co/er8zbHtStp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneTrueAggie OTA- you buy half, and I'll buy half, and let's give them away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshjones337 plus the first iphone didn’t come out till 2007. 🤷🏼‍♂️🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHODesusAndMero Just started watching your show. I DVR it to make sure I don’t miss an episode]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should not witness any democrat on a air plane any more, to set a good example for their new green deal. Yikes 😜]]></document></documents></author>