<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna watch TV in March, you might be stuck with me.  Mark these dates do you can avoid me, or tune in.… https://t.co/vTXujx7f8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvmidd85 @seames_jr @CombatVet33 @jrdel42 @OldcorpsGrunt @MarcHarr19 @ScottLefferd @LastScout1776 @justin1s1k… https://t.co/B7LwyortZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering when @SethWageWar is gonna leave Wage War to just be a full time famous person.   Sponsor him: @ChipotleTweets @Tesla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnySeminole @FSU2Times @TroeUwaii @heyaly21 @Ashley_Caroline @Kathryn_Lentz 😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaiAyshaMami @habsnegs Ur stunningly Gorgeous! DM me back, I'm single.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las víctimas que el régimen invisibiliza. @__ayduchis__ @cayetanaAT @hermanntertsch @LuchyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My childhood. #1980s #arcades #childhood #memories #retro @ Shelton, Washington https://t.co/CmwcExBS9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSportsNet @AdamSchein Michael rowed a boat to the HOF just because he was everything to basketball!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerd4everything Never miss the show, got to have something to hate on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Denver: snow, -2°F 77% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1025mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now he's lost the plate. I can't have that in the rotation for even just a couple weeks #Yankees]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/GoTUZsD4vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demiandu Mi más sentido pésame por tan irreparable pérdida. Mis respetos a la familia y a la memoria de tu papá.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald, you have got to be the stupidest summit son of birch on earth. You and your party won the… https://t.co/ZXGO1wbgtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluesboydanowen @mercuryloungeny 2/14/19 Such great energy..love it!! #danowen #falllikeafeather #latergram @ Merc… https://t.co/TNY7tCmVcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arouet_V @lopezobrador_ PAREMOS LAS ALZAS DE PRECIOS A COMBUSTIBLES, GAS NATURAL Y ELECTRICIDAD RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Coach Richards, his staff and players.  What a gritty week for @ChathamCougar MBB. @PAC_Athletics champ… https://t.co/omiHGFwqHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Equipo @ImpulsaNY juramentado por el Profesor @FranklinRod77 plataforma que llevará al líder @LeonelFernandez a las… https://t.co/BuUsNMVZHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[why I spill my entire heart to nonkoh today I’m the middle of our class lecture 😂😂 niggas was getting teared up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idgaf, a song by King Tru on Spotify https://t.co/WHIh3cMaWr @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/ElDTIeal7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alextleach This is me making a smoothie. Wish my cats loved kale and bananas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the half: Johnson City leads Poughkeepsie 42-34 @lohudinsider @KDJmedia1 @sports_pioneer https://t.co/Vcl2utwhdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Socialist not to call them Communist, they are the masters in corruption, fraud and theft. We have to demand la… https://t.co/TH6gx8Bgw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheInstigators @brandon_montour @WGR550 @MSGNetworks Hutton should not of started last nite 2 bad goals. Sabres ar… https://t.co/aVEeIhIton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collincowart @PigsAndPlans @israel_barnes4 @JimmyKimmelLive She hiding. She knows she gonna get that Twitter heat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkanninen Red Panda is the halftime entertainment tonight annnnd...she’s still got it. Go Bucky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @cthagod 👀 Hope you’ve been doing your jaw exercises my nigga! #SuckHisDick #AllJokes #ShitFunnyAsHellThough… https://t.co/Ki6Hi0hHcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fat_fendr_strat @GregoryMarkHarg Well just get one without the ‘ T’ the ‘t’ is completely unnecessary. Your welcom… https://t.co/Da27dVbGf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Het Gouden Kaartje by @TailSpinBrewing @ Downtown Renton — https://t.co/xu5Acc2bAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 By the way, does Senator Collins have a WALL AROUND HER HOUSE?  America has a right to know that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobBoyle7 Sunday, 4/7 Spartan Sprint, Concord, Porter Farms. Register under “Team Southern Spartans”. U IN ?… https://t.co/K5GWUNqqjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 hours after I had already stated that NMSU was the hottest team in the WAC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner I hope so! No guarantee per Mencken’s aphorism of the wisdom of the American people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spokanegamer @TheJaredTyler @Isitartyet @BigCMen @ColbyChambersXX @MickeyKnox_xxx @konagrl4554 What did you mean animals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelaupert @AnnCoulter Just another vampire on the President's popularity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Al Del Greco, “Automatic Al”, 4 year letterman at Auburn, 5th on career scoring list, 17 NFL seasons… https://t.co/1zEPzDz2IA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quowrapbuysunc You might be a sheep but not me I dont beleave in that crap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenWalke why isn’t Hayden the voice of anakin? It sounds weird considering all of the emotes are said by him]]></document><document><![CDATA[U12 A Travel Hockey x1 @OhioStateFair #TaftColiseum   (1st of 4 games at 3 different rinks for the day)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck flexing a couple bands I wanna flex with a sack of gold coins like I’m on some medieval shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Just once I want to see this shit happen in front of me. I am so sick of the cowardly right letting… https://t.co/IS7OB0x6wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke 22:37 For I tell you that this Scripture must be fulfilled in Me: 'And He was numbered with the transgressors.… https://t.co/dx16DaknoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC random selfie after forgetting I had to get off the 1 at Times Square to take the 7 lol (it was 2am and tired a… https://t.co/HJXOVB5ewp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tebow15believer How do you have such inside information?  I didn't know you were running the horizontal border muc… https://t.co/BHhd8nAqyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QVINNMUSIC I get it but I’m talking about the guys that get pushed off because of that logic of some. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The phenomenon of people dragging their huge RVs thousands of miles to watch television is Very real and Extremely strange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the The National WWII Museum. So proud that both of my grandfathers served in the military during WW2.… https://t.co/Xh1UuVOO6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[is anyone good with computers that can help me? my computer is stuck on the loading screen]]></document><document><![CDATA[After what had to have been over a year of speculation, Airbus has officially killed the #AirbusA380.… https://t.co/dsmJdOzI3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every morning I wake up and think of new ways to stunt on y’all this year. It’s unfair, nobody safe 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody got him a new bandanna yeshedidsheagoodboyyesheis #dogsofinstagram @ Broken Arrow, Oklahoma https://t.co/3j9mjZzw5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danielaszt @Topsy_Tori @juliaioffe @IlhanMN That's not antisemitic! And I wish you showed this much enthusiasm abo… https://t.co/siqIwXtycb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yummy 😋 - Drinking a Throne Room by @southcountybeer @ Steelton  — https://t.co/Nj7C4mxcvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking These kids are a disgrace to our society and to this country.  I can’t believe this is still a  problem… https://t.co/dmpvrmF4pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best deals and coupons for Caesars Palace Las Vegas https://t.co/trWlPArD54 via @yazingllc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Your friend left you a whisper in your ear on your Wedding day you are loved. Your tears are shared by… https://t.co/snOI8xzFx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleejack Fields: Check out my new book about diversity and multiculturalism:  Off the RACE Track--From Color Blind… https://t.co/BpDRJpOsk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gopherwood never quits !!!!!! after covering my guitar maintenance while I’ve been on the road the They’ve connecte… https://t.co/lxa9vc1ZIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which, by the way, still doesn’t cover the three game spread (at polar opposite it’s a tie). And even then, the pro… https://t.co/HMTfOfqsJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how RuPaul Drag came from @RuPaulsDragRace https://t.co/WyrwVXYa6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRothstein I’m staying awake for another 32 minutes strictly for the “This is March” tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@battleborngoali @MinivanPunk @SpaceSGM Surprisingly large, yet understated veterans community up here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which in most cases you say out loud so that we turn our heads and pretend that we “like” or even to the most exten… https://t.co/q6dTp6QLkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettCMajor1 @ALGhammer I think Rosie is saying she's OK with interference as long as JWR got it right. Right for Trudeau and SNC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalfaninTexas Just wait until the free agency period gets here, the Mahomes effect will get us starting quality… https://t.co/gbF5cbiKNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio Game worn Super Bowl XXXl @BrettFavre Jersey. If I could have ANY Jersey and cost was no object. 4 put G… https://t.co/J6SReG3oQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna see @wizkhalifa in concert again, it’s been way too long. See ya soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Japan Islands Installation @SXSW19 (@ 800 Congress for The New Japan Islands in Austin, TX) https://t.co/CKhd8D6OuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when about returning to englishlands not being able to walk around just saying GOOD to everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends One girl was shot 10 times....never heard that before. How many times were the other students shot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamfromSpain @SaraMD15 @nycSassenach @CharliesWhiskey @KarramKaren @newenglandgrl @PamBermond @TwinOne72… https://t.co/AHRTFuFWxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson They should have listened to their conscience but they didn’t. Neither did so many others. Everyone… https://t.co/4JecR5BZVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[There hath no temptation taken you but such as is common 2 man: but God is faithful, who will not suffer you 2 be t… https://t.co/nswd7grVah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half-A-Cheer For Supremes' Civil Asset Forfeiture Ruling https://t.co/mzb1Hwzvf3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Batesmotel on #Netflix is oretty dope. Glad I finally sat down with it. #bingewatching #snowday https://t.co/gAeSVVcZc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ec_sans @Claudet50948796 @nbcdays Nope She ain't a legacy character because her character only been on for like 5… https://t.co/cp5b6Ib2sD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeteransAlways @Fuctupmind @LisaMei62 @bigredwavenow @John_F_Kennnedy @KimDotcom @POTUS @HarveyStaub1 @Time4U2Know… https://t.co/oN8sAVeZ0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody: "So Mario, what got you out of bed this morning?"  Me: "Jehovah's Witnesses"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReduxRetro You're taking me too seriously there, mark 🤣 #mark #wwemark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaqui_hrdz @Rayados No hay que dejar las buenas costumbres, pero si pude activarlos , espero tu también]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump But you want 8 billion for a wall just to sooth your ego??  You are a piece of shit Donny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @thekatiemorgan @TheJaclynTaylor @kennajames21 @KendraLust @akaDaniDaniels @MsSarahVandella @AmiliaOnyx… https://t.co/WwUAar7kdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bloody addicted to this album @JessicaVosk. It has become my US holiday soundtrack 🇺🇸😍😍😍 https://t.co/2aypJgHFEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I found this show about modern architecture.  They claim to love nature, but their conspicuous consumption revea… https://t.co/aJjSaVktN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbieDuncanOL @ToniKombucha I think this is the exact reason we can wait on edge and get a solid player for bette… https://t.co/46DIO8niiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepStickland What's Evil is Conservative Christians supports the GOP economic agenda that has purposely put Americ… https://t.co/jha5oAqOd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ihufffreon @WMCActionNews5 @MLGW @spencerstorm5 @sagaygalindo @WX_BrittneyB @NickGunterWX 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champton85 I love how offended Gator fans get by UCF. Threatened much? You will never get things back to they way… https://t.co/W2LY9vtC5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase I'm going from 1-2 hours a night, then after about 6 days, crash for almost a full day. I feel you on… https://t.co/zp1yeWpjzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pete is in the stroller Y'all! @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/vyMQnLzBLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow it’s turned into a very nice night for baseball at CCU. Need a Top 25 win tonight to ease the pain of the last two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4JSteve 73 - 13 mashups, 47 skin packs,  10 texture packs, 5 various “worlds”   When I break it down the math does… https://t.co/DSrizW3GaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyndilauper @IndraNooyi The Purchase, NY Pepsi Headquarters is a great outdoor sculpture garden. https://t.co/ftX9OMg7oE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @kdbostain for sharing some #ValentinesDay love with us this morning! #LifeReady https://t.co/4d4H2dWxUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terry_go_online Good luck! I started this account in 2007. I just don't have the time to curate that many hot takes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr The new normal is bragging about sexually assaulting women. Saying that Obama was bor… https://t.co/5sYfHfHxLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all have never heard the wolf cry to the blue corn moon &amp; it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if I did not owe the Government anything I mint [might] get ashore but until I am out of their debt I may a… https://t.co/HtoRxhcQLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the Twitter trolls who safe helmets don’t save lives https://t.co/fRyJCEyRC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_chrisrlamb @akaEmmaLouise We’re gonna be there so you should come out to @heroconf too]]></document></documents></author>