<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheToyInsider @YooHooFriends @AuroraWorld soft, cuddly #AuroraYooHooParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Twitter @TwitterSupport @TwitterSafety Please quit messing with my settings PLEASE! Turn on my notifications a… https://t.co/Jik3i3NJiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hotel room did not come with free mints on my pillow or bottomless mimosas.   Send help. #NationalEmergencyStories]]></document><document><![CDATA[September 10th, 2012.   Up at 4 am, did about 4 miles on the treadmill, installed the car seat, loaded my bags, end… https://t.co/A9cXVahrxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't eff with Chimichurri, we don't eff with you. 💚 #latergram @ New York, New York https://t.co/ilQzLDjdwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BenuHack2019 Team BigDataEnergy from @BenU1887 feverishly racing against time  :) #IBMDeveloper @IBMBizAnalytics… https://t.co/wUHB8dkY1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmillerotown @fandidmgmt 3rd show in a year and I’d have to say that last night in Louisville was by far the bes… https://t.co/sYMqI0ZvEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX @joeyfatone Kinda shitty he's been on national TV bold face lying... Saying it isn't him.... Could… https://t.co/fguwahtHsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Price Drop🚨                 Call me for a privet tour Chrissy Goheen REALTOR® RE/MAX Best Choice 573.518.4178-573.… https://t.co/MzeD5ovelW]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . :  #disney #disneyig #disneygram #disneylife #disneynerd #disneylove #disneyfollow #instadisney #disneygrammers… https://t.co/1jAt96eeWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmerrill77 @67jewelCDH The #TrumpCrimeFamily deserve to spend the rest of their miserable lives in jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your father calls you a liar, now that’s serious. .@SenKamalaHarris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisTwatter @oldmanluvsmineo I ever hear of this b4? Andrew Hart Coulter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CompleteCookie are my saving grace and the only reason I can stay on track on my diet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@behindthechair_ behindthechair_stylist #btconeshot19_coolbalayage #btconeshot19_colortransformation… https://t.co/Tcv87608J8]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk i have a @_brooklynoel and a @margaretfran and that’s pretty much the same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NowWeAreAllTom All I can say is that writing a certain kind of fanfic helped me cope with grad school stress and a… https://t.co/spHD42rGZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you are a liberal doc you must be kidding how did u pass medical school??]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got back from italy and i’m honestly shocked that some people don’t like to travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristanSpoof u and zap lil bitches simp will literally shit on both of ur chests at lan I cant wait fucking shit host fuck westr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about the time @_jacobvega blew a piece of boba out of a straw and it got stuck in my dimple 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodmenXCTF @Hanover_TnF @HanoverPanthers @HCACDIII How awesome is it that the high school follows up on former at… https://t.co/muNcDb4i2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hefner by @tanamongeau is stuck in my head while doing calculus hw. Why. #Ihaventheardthatsonginawhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehicklife It’s a sign 🤷🏼‍♀️. .. message from your sister.. ( Mediums say that )  Matt Fraser ~ RI  ~~Chip Coffey~~(🤷🏼‍♀️).   .. 🙋🏼‍♀️💞🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the barn children today goes “I like your hair. Actually I’ve never even seen your hair down. I don’t think… https://t.co/uZlCCSgjb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EpicEtiquette #newyou2019 #love #loveyourself #forgiveness #thinkingofyou @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/xmhTLKSXWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar Hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahaha hahahah… https://t.co/bQajnIVU8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all always say Apple is extra but.. this is extra. And imma be mad if they become more extra because of all this… https://t.co/D6FRTAn8oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is a witch hunt.  There is no other way to explain the injustice the Democrats have put our P… https://t.co/FSr8lzXQRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulJHomer @MrsRabbitResist @TheDweck @MollyJongFast Never Forget the Children! ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines days is everyday for me so tomorrow I just get extra extra spoiled 😻🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both my dad AND my sister tried telling me happy birthday today.. it’s not my birthday yet.. just youngest child things]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personalized ads are getting too accurate this is an invasion of privacy https://t.co/6AmkQ7GB70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShesFiskit @TempoAxe It’s also expensive even for someone like Jeffrey to fly out to Australia. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy RuPaul’s Drag Race S11 premiere day, kitty girls ✨ #glitterqueen #docmartens #rpdr @ Prospect Hill, Ohio https://t.co/7r39RaCWVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah being in a relationship where your bf can’t say good morning or good night is a lot worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EditPhotoGamer @sfovergeorgia @SixFlags @SF_WhiteWater I love roller coasters...and them parks in general. I def s… https://t.co/qQzDmrhu3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m disappointed in both parents. Her ENTIRE ass should have been whooped before that phone came out!! Dad needed t… https://t.co/vmLKYXKK9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got hot as hell. Idk if that means the liquor catching up or what but i gtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What we do as acts of Worship become invigorating, what we do in the flesh becomes burdensome.” @ChrisChadwickSD… https://t.co/Wv9TL98zF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lenten lunch. #foodphotography #pbandj #peanutbutterandjelly #sandwich #flatlayphotograhy #flatlay #food @ Oakland… https://t.co/nv86g3kblv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanReadman @Idofavorzforu I knew a suuuuper pale, skinny, condescending girl that I once compared to naked mr burns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich They are not defending him, they are protecting themselves and their own interests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I went to DSP in my pajamas last night but it was karma for spring 2018]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait they are reviewing offsides after he made the penalty shot??? 😂😂😂 GTFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo I’m confused and I don’t know why I haven’t asked this before. Would my dads side of the family be the Manto… https://t.co/CFbryqVSjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fauxbeatpoet He sounded like a pleasant enough oddball, but I’m just in awe/horrified that this many people just w… https://t.co/QfmZYIZE3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great night for a match! #GoSeawolves #TogetherWeHunt https://t.co/WssmoPCf3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhallwfmy @CoachKalebMoney @BMHSVillains @VillainsCoach @RyanHaidinger @CoachFlyntIV The Best. 👊🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[People at work say we used to always get snow days or delayed openings....I wish I could experience that. I could u… https://t.co/OIhXjkOUrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What mountaintops inspire you?  What valleys helped shape you?   #DIJ via @HUMANeX_DIJ @HUMANeX https://t.co/9rRs1HpBFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[IndyCar driver who survived fiery crash hopes to walk at his wedding, get back behind the wheel - GMA - via @GMA… https://t.co/QvYMGg6V6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[just bc your relationship is messed up, doesn’t mean you have to go around tryna mess up someone else’s relationship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s bring out the tape of Chuck Schumer suggesting legislation for a wall.  THE SAME WALL trump wants to build]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reshminair @CBCHereandNow @eclipsetheatre3 #amazing #rethinkingTheatre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pryorkika @USATODAY Good question. Say, last 10 years, 210.000 women raped in the military.  How many pregnancies… https://t.co/X80FtrzaTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[O dia começou com um sol terrível, queimando muito. Aquilo estava me incomodando demais, e eu cheguei a pensar que… https://t.co/oO5FcX5NMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsmelissa99 You think? My VS bras are the only ones that make it past a few washes. I’ve had some for over 10 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[somewhere between should have known .. and don’t ever try to speak to me again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look ma, I’m on a panel at #SXSW2019! 😊 I thought leaving #academia meant I’d never talk about #feminist theory aga… https://t.co/jDT7AvslAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#keeponpraying KEEP ON PRAYING #pray #prayer #praying #prayerwarrior #prayerworks #prayerchangesthings #trust GOD i… https://t.co/6VZsJM8waa]]></document><document><![CDATA[dual enrollment is the only way to go if you actually want to be ahead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly believe that there has been so much positive news in just these past days that Confidence to take a positio… https://t.co/qJEyTscYWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday feels: every feel like you don’t fit in/ no one likes you cause same 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nobletolu @CNNPolitics There is no point to Cohen lying for Cohen. He is already going to prison. He has nothing t… https://t.co/2PVdXH9yXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raul060376 @THDGERALD @tgtguerrero12 @HomeDepot @albert_miraval @BoydBoydr @Follow_Jay_ @HDMET522 @HDBrittClark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwagWithWheels So naturally you’ll gravitate towards the Bern if you don’t get the succ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending some quality time with my little Duncan. @ Garner, North Carolina https://t.co/UDoRysMAzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great pictures of Oakland teachers’ strike. Wish I were there. My old stomping grounds. Solidarity! https://t.co/x7ySxerLFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ladies n gentlemen, if ur looking for a good-looking, kind hearted, and amazing guy, then @aldrichglagman is the one for u 🤝🤝🤝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasHouse @GovAbbott it’s heartbreaking watching non educators make such critical decisions about public educatio… https://t.co/xRokvSIrsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blooms from “borrowed” seeds.  Its like a magic trick. #africanlillies #flowers #blooms #spring #lifeisgood… https://t.co/Na81oNtULD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my sixth day of working in a row but as soon as today is over, I have four days off https://t.co/NBdFa64vGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp 🤔 Frankly, I don’t ever remember CPAC as a place for anything other than attacks on social justice. When we… https://t.co/EKEY5bjpI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanasmith @TimShriver @overheardpbs Big fans of you both!  Hope to see you there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best thing about writing papers in college in being able to use swear words to get your point across.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of it! Ricky and Morty followed by boondocks. Add Bojack horseman to the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinru99857767 Considering she divorced Kody so he could legally marry Robyn and adopt her kids she should be tre… https://t.co/Zyx0GKdktl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlsGolfRocks1 @EngGolfDis @accringtongolf @AintreeGolf @CRGolfClub @HarwoodGC @GolfLancaster @Southport_golf… https://t.co/uEjTC5hCWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders and Warren give the left a bigger platform  https://t.co/NLAjiCj4ZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinphillips Wizard of Oz was my absolute favorite when I was tiny - which is weird cause it’s scary as hell!! M… https://t.co/E5LW90lCH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so angry at Jussie Smollett right now. He has given 💩4🧠 something else to tweet about . This caused more harm… https://t.co/6xal2BvW6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afternoon adventures. @ Lucidi Distilling Co. - Fire Station No. 1 https://t.co/diVw7ZrXIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I come back to work and my coworker asks when’s my next vacation.🤣 I’m planning it as we speak lol✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #STEM students can utilize this https://t.co/BrYeEyCSlO for their #GrandChallenge presentations.  Please consid… https://t.co/LQzoHsI4HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blakester90s @AnthonyJMuniz @infinitelligent @omnitelligent @Dragynwing @TerryPr2520 @MsMagamyass @1_prostate… https://t.co/kb02Kz9OWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBLHoops @WBLStudentSect @TheHornWBL @isd624 Have fun tonight boys!!! Love you guys!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roblox  too much granddaughter green hair Geegee92 as seen the wife dogu panties her niece called Lilianne the gra… https://t.co/L9Hj1Nr8aL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, for me, the WHO was the most chilling &amp; moving concert tribute, to John Entwistle &amp; Keith Moon 🌙  it was great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[M o o d !!!!! My mom literally was like Olaylist is the last trip for a while and I was like uhhh maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newoumarou @fleissmeister @khloekardashian @KimKardashian You cannt force someone 2 love you nor can you buy them.… https://t.co/SUB4Wf0muO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major fan girl moment - @ShawnMendes was born on the SAME DAY as @JCChasez. Two Leo men on one day?! I can’t handle… https://t.co/IWJHQV72zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nashville did not disappoint 👌🏻 We had so much celebrating Liv! Can’t wait for the wedding in May 😍👰🏼 @ Broadway https://t.co/tBBWisLXX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Fake news! You don't know exactly what they might have on you, do you prez?? You getting a little nervous I bet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am so glad that i escaped from the hell hole of a bubble that is emerson college]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear every time I’m with yuni we always end up doing some dumb shit 😂 our parents are literally hasta la madre]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the hugest crush on Donny when I was 8 yrs old. ❤️ I had the Osmunds lunch pail, and Purple socks!!! My whole… https://t.co/n3umDdrTJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlRojoVivo Es para que se den cuenta que también la naturaleza , se sabe manifestar por que está cansada de tanta maldad asia ella]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desiraybino DO IT! If you fly into DC by Friday morning you can drive up with me and my friends. There isn’t a dec… https://t.co/fEZcMMFnzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would step in a pile of dog shit before getting into my friends truck in midtown. You asshole people, pick up you… https://t.co/W3UaFpcJko]]></document></documents></author>