<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i gotta upgrade from my last nigga.. like real shit lmao and when i tell y’all i’m off my “____ who??” shit rn😭😭 li… https://t.co/SCHd3nBCzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats Trump is known as a liar, to us, to everyone..you clearly do not care]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @shaunking Isn’t “Cook” one syllable as compared to “Apple” and therefore quicker to say and more t… https://t.co/NSuQkOE7fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trublu_efren @DuranSports how is it?! @DuranSports told me about Laverne and Shirley too!! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is ludicrous. #comedy #lol #smile #humorous https://t.co/e09X74LQE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panthers up 38-30 in the 4th quarter! Beat the Cougars! @WhsPanthers60 @WHS46619 @sbwathletics https://t.co/s6cXLvpNkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaddieDibbs So like 2 weeks ago he called and said he was coming to get it on a Monday that was one of the voicema… https://t.co/TzyYpr29sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Shane dawson pet is your favorite @shanedawson @_morganadams_ @TeresaYaw @Ryland_Adams @Garrett_Watts @_morganadams_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Then they should not pay any income tax on earnings. No taxation without representation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A di es Padrino lo que es un perfecto idiota vendido con los comunistas Cubanos]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow’s gonna melt, Colorado, and we’ll find our July looking like this.  . . . . #icelakebasin #nofilterphoto… https://t.co/VWaAGHJhLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraveTart @kenjilopezalt You should make this for your strawberry loving family, @Kim100584 @hotkimale273]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow #ohmymom tweet/conversation from this morning: https://t.co/U58zSOvvLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling strong this beautiful, blustery Wednesday morning! Are you getting your training done?🤔 c'mon no excuses! H… https://t.co/JHkaukLfVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only my 4th day and I’m deadass so stressed out lol imma cry. Definitely need some retail therapy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @JussieSmollett A brothel in NOLA was busted in the early 2000s. The women got jail time and ALL of the… https://t.co/CS4H2uc3v7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a happier and more pleasant person to be around after I get any sort of affection]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi This is the Poor Roger Show. He thinks he is invisible, that he can say or do just as he pleases. Muell… https://t.co/lyDBt28JKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Are you watching? https://t.co/UoInUc84sV Here is what we are watching: @NBC12 @AnthonyNBC12… https://t.co/wlk5TyiJIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m available for Mom duties as well! (And... not to brag but I CAN cook...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saving this view in my mind forever 😍⛷❄️ #skiingtrip #skiingday #skier #skierslife #monclerjacket #monclerbaby… https://t.co/XEzUxoEVLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieFolk @HerbertHistory @SamDeeWard @netflix Did you never see the little cinematic gem that is Bedazzled? C… https://t.co/gos9m8ZuM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for my team!❤️🐝 And our planning day today!✍🏻🧠🎉 @MrsNicolai @MsDay_LAL @JimHilterbrand]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ali was drunk last night making a fool of herself” Bitch I do that sober the fuck?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wherever life’s journey takes you today, the simplest act of kindness can make a difference!  . . . #livelovelaugh… https://t.co/Wn0nYLsiiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halie_abt If you do find some that look like that, then you may have eaten a bag of dicks and balls 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dressed up ▪️Actually remembered to take a picture ▪️ And.... you can’t see our outfits... ▪️But dinner was amazing… https://t.co/xsC9Z5hXfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 nights in a row! 😁🎉🌟 I do believe we have turned a corner (my hopes are getting up anyhow)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easter Minis! $75  #cloquetphotographer #duluthphotographer #canon5dmarkiv #easterminisession… https://t.co/ITNgwK1IJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love listening to people problems  &amp; trying to give them a different view point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my recent tattoos are works in progress &amp; not ready to post, I thought I'd post some older pics.… https://t.co/RL1z2puRkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Eager to see what this drive has in store for us. I especially love the sunrise drives as Africa comes… https://t.co/zfSM8QBEuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump @musicgirl176 I think it was Kyle. She was mad saying that Lisa gave Dorit a pass for the puppy but… https://t.co/EEdQIieWL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Black Ascot by Charles Todd #bookreview #tarheelreader #thrblackascot @charlestoddbks @wmmorrowbooks… https://t.co/T6C87GS3V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I REFUSE to sit by and let the tobacco companies prey on another generation! This MUST STOP!!!! Please support… https://t.co/bxwAPHqPUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep yep yep...... My biggest accomplishment in my life was taking care of my daddy all by myself the last 7 years o… https://t.co/6KQIGN3wJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sauceeed I also interviewed the players too...tbh this isn’t really a debate because it’s obvious to me. But I respect your opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple fatalities as tornadoes hit Alabama and Georgia  https://t.co/R8tnyc7NVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfaFarmers @AlaAgriculture Always excited to highlight the great things within our state.  Appreciated the opport… https://t.co/fu1v6GGCi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[OfficeTeam is hiring in #Harrisburg, PA! Click the link in our bio to apply: Fund Development Data Specialist #Clerical]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apart from being sick since Thursday. I just shattered my entire screen,  somebody pls put me out of my misery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm about to watch A Star is Born for the first time. I don't know if I'm emotionally prepared. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KStall93 @ZuluPanther we were prisoners, slave sound so impersonal to me. African in africa were slaves/prisnors i… https://t.co/kmzGhZaZCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. But there are "highways," and then there is "traffic" - likewise, in the #brain there are both physical connecti… https://t.co/8qee7OtJVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I sit while on the toilet because lately I’ve been wearing onesie pjs💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green book 🍿 (@ Regal Cinemas Carlsbad 12 - @regalmovies in Carlsbad, CA) https://t.co/CkS1gkkr2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Stupid Cupid Day.  I scrolled Insta for three seconds when I woke up and whew boy, big mistake. I’ll stick to Twitter today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Nursing job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Nurse Aide II FT Medi… https://t.co/TbTIJFFK8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realamymholmes @AlexBlakeFL Ma’am I can assure you that they did not match. Settling does not prevent a criminal p… https://t.co/sIsDj53V8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do I use Twitter in a non problematic way??... https://t.co/OuCalYTc5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwichary Thank you for this thread, Marcin. You paint a lovely portrait of Tess that makes me sorrowful about this huge loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandpa asked that I write “share with papa” on all my posts so that my grandma will be reminded to show him my… https://t.co/hq3YDG8oLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone asking who I’m spending my valentines with. https://t.co/AugR5S423B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstroWillWaal Uhhhh that’s really unfortunate and one of my biggest fears. Hope you’re feeling better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since it was a porn star who fueled the insanity that is the anti-vaxxer movement, I think it would be awesome of s… https://t.co/KofbaKHMA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/0lhFxM1kQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't resist😂🤣😂. Sometimes I miss this pose, few would know it😉😉. With "Banks" from the Clarksville Chapter.… https://t.co/SkbZIEqbDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colgraphics @JohnCornyn @politico I’ve been to these proceedings and worked with Ashlee seekers. I’m not sure wher… https://t.co/GloZxcoMcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamintheboro @JohnLegere @TMobile Soone if the best darn customer service you'll ever see!  😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catneytew story of my liiiiiife &amp; then your voice in my head “buy it if it brings you joy” 🙄😹😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seriously concerned with finding someone that would want to marry me]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t believe he’s really 20 today😩 happy birthday love💛💛💛 i love you more than you’ll ever know @Jimmy_Kutka https://t.co/cLI9ZpqbGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremiahmajor55 Happy Birthday to one of my favorites! Thank you for always being so sweet! SO happy our families… https://t.co/cULyHFIM9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF is wrong with you Fic McFilet-o-fish supporters? Grow up, get a life, and stop bullying the people you supposed… https://t.co/Q0xvr094uZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A kind nurse is a gift when your precious husband is recovering from a brain #aneurysm and a stroke. A not so kind… https://t.co/YGSSzr93Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Funny ecards &amp; Greeting Cards - Create and send your own funny Rotten ecards #humor #lol #smirk #absurd https://t.co/pw2yDyr0Fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_nickcody Fingers crossed to either be excused or picked for a serial killer 🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @ctesjcsd for education highlights happening in SJCSD Academy/CTE/STEM/CS (and other Career Themed courses)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN How disappointed we were when she supported the Kavanaugh accusers with no proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Audubon victory!! The court has decided to protect the Everglades' water quality &amp; restoration! https://t.co/yu1Deyl1Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙀🙀🙀 WhaAaAaAaAaAaAt!?!?! ... isn’t #berniesanders TOO OLD to run for #potus ... I mean, he’s only 77 y/o BUT- now h… https://t.co/XJ3mPWTtdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I understand the standment, if you can’t love the one you want, love the one you’re with...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll never know who i’m talking to 🤦🏻‍♀️😂 @CodieeeAnnn https://t.co/UZ07tfMBd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two big names I’m hearing for the new basketball coach at UNLV are Rick Pitino and Thad Matta. That is if UNLV… https://t.co/koXLQmwRvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nelnet can someone chat with me I need help with my account. Every time I try to call it’s after hours or I’m at w… https://t.co/0f2I16aLmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein @whignewtons @maxwelltani So why hire her? Not a good look @CNN. I stopped watching when you put pukehead… https://t.co/GEhJEJXFa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so sick that there’s people who have to come to twitter to validate themselves , if it’s really your reality ,… https://t.co/ZICl3LVEUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I started making seed bead chokers and sold them for $3-$4, would anyone be interested?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presenting Grace England’s 2018-19 Teacher of the Year! https://t.co/7X4nKPBvCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pamacious @amputeesoccer @GeorgeTakei @AmicaAli financial benefits would probably go to a top Russian oligarch. On… https://t.co/NE5Y9XYiJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drivers commuting from work lucked out in North Windham. Snow didn’t really start until about 6 p.m. Tuesday.… https://t.co/9kKCn6qLGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan They did the same thing to Hilary.  Years of hounding and investigating her with zero results, but they… https://t.co/X43Y5AwP2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third grade loved watching the Storybook Theatre production of Two Pigs and T.H.E. Wolf this afternoon! 🐷🐺📗… https://t.co/zQLpQpIbrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our very own Brett Elifritz on winning King of Courts and @AXOmicron’s MK Ekins on winning Queen… https://t.co/Av6LiKNKEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltWhite_man Exactly! I wouldn't speak to the OG either. Kelly didn't really reveal anything except OG followed h… https://t.co/17ymg40jCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeWren @Broward_Bar @iron_light @ShiCooks @sandra_king2 @judibachay @dislaw @AndyAUCD @cgcurie Wonderful messag… https://t.co/iBbboZJ9Hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[No dejes que el ruido de las opiniones ajenas apaguen tu voz interna. 👊🏽😎 https://t.co/tCsiojhKCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on your District 3-AAA All Tournament Award son @seanoglesby1011🏆🎉 #NextStopRegionals #CHS 🐾 https://t.co/A39y522YsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish we could have had 2 winners. Loved this ET entry! @patcollins4 #snowstickchallenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hodgman, 23, was not charged with a hate crime, but instead ticketed for violating town code when he allegedly post… https://t.co/R6VMRSW9oI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 @YourGlamByJulie @justusmakeup IM GETTING ON THAT LIST I AM MANIFESTING ITTTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello yes why is this so loud, asking for my soul  #Repost shelbystarnes100 (get_repost) ・・・ @ Close to Home https://t.co/pdSnWUma0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I have grandchildren that call me mamaw, meemaw or yeehaw, they will get their shit rocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @VP - Does it bother you to be so ignorant and vicious?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, as long as you have the time and energy.  I’ll curse up a storm when I see stuff like this, just as an ally.… https://t.co/YkQLV4yxIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Cat Amazing EPIC! puzzle! #giveaway #catgiveaway #petgiveaway #catpuzzletoy #floppycats #catamazing https://t.co/uGIMaxJFat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tammykyson @Greg_4949 @BamaGal_inTexas No doubt about it! Got pick your battles😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harleyhed Taking a screenshot of this tweet so I have it forever. Thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanScottGraham That's a ton of smoke 😳😬 my inhalers barely help my breathing at the smaller shows. Now I'm worrie… https://t.co/QSDkG9lXra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy cow. It will be 15 years in May since I‘ve been to Disney World. 😳😱  I’d say a trip is looooong overdue.   #DisneyNerd 💕]]></document></documents></author>