<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@USLaxofRoc Well I’m just being prepared if I ever meet @realDonaldTrump ! Since he’s naming people by their first name and where they work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely great end to an amazing birthday weekend!! #ericchurch #doubledowntour #jackdaniels #detroit @ Little Ca… https://t.co/DA9uIJ4IS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it was a Friday or Saturday night, I’d take a shot every time they mention Obama’s at this game and/or pan the camera to him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwbyrnes49 @KevinDuska I thought they were clowns. Y’all need to make up your mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Varelus00 @ZandoSoup We can’t offer stuff to the public due to the exclusives]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Austin and this team! They started the season hardly knowing each but they came together as a team and… https://t.co/GkzVyYx5jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Nothing on the skinhead with an arsenal of guns and a kill list with journalists and some of your colleag… https://t.co/6hNJImSCwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judypham684 You’re always welcome to the carne asada https://t.co/ARtkatGYz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the snow blocks out the snow. 😳😳😳  *In Leadville, Colorado via Shenan Pordon 📸 https://t.co/71x8OXnSYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeaturedSupps Hi I'm looking for a product to gain weight I'm diabetic and I need a sugar free low carb weight gain is there such a thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catheri22165164 @banan1234 @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Not true, I love the guy and wish he’d just be a better presi… https://t.co/2WQstaH4Gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ironmikeluke @azc_obert In the second paragraph he clearly says that it only covers back to the 80s. He graduated he in 78.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookAddict10 @KarstenKinstler @JackaLopez3 @TheSleepyRebel @ProperOpinion El diablo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trackmasta28 @yfreemark @metrolosangeles I imagine Duke thinks that it has the right mix of accessibility for stud… https://t.co/QefklaUFqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent Day 1! The attendees are getting settled for Day 2 of the #ADManSummit https://t.co/YDM8KKsGFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so, im alive. This has been the worst 9 days of my life but here i am. On the bright side i lost over 10 pound… https://t.co/MvPEdcBEOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump The left is against the 2nd amendment but not voter fraud. SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnPhillips @JSOPIO @JAXFOP530 Why is the guy on the left grabbing his breasticles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darlene4NY Use don’t have give silly commentary after each story. We want to hear the facts only. Try being more p… https://t.co/Bh0tfyPPVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urythmyc @the_warm_fruit @soafricane @rihanna HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS VERY GOOD, BUT SHE LOSE TO THESE… https://t.co/kxcAsdFU3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BengalDesigns After seeing Parris Campbell and Mecole Hardman run, do you think either will move up the draft board?]]></document><document><![CDATA[El fin de semana mi hijo me pregunto muy serio ;"como te enterabas de las Funciones del cine?, si no había Internet… https://t.co/T8kA1PNKO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBiks @Wittman7 It is his shoulder. I don’t think you can blow a shoulder problem out of proportion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey racists upset bc someone calls what you DO racist. This is the outcome of your racism and it is more hurtfull t… https://t.co/RKqWTJRam3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you dare  lol 😂.!! Happy Saturday y’all.!! @ The Manor https://t.co/DNFuvYWZOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissypacktor Correction: Phalen wasn’t hired out of college and had experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndPacing Anyone interested in these two 3yr old colts! Will post for global. Dm me please https://t.co/96vDMNIofD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. And I can stand in a nice part of Chicago, where everything is fine. While countless murders are happening aro… https://t.co/rVWb3Vqdj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jair_amon When you want the best for the next person you become all of these 🔺🔺🔺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I may sound a little dramatic, but I can’t wait until the 15th. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hokieprorichie @ThePackFootball @LadyPackHoops @Hayes_BHCSports @WCYB_Heather @WCYB_CaseyGoetz @tnsportslive Thank you sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isolation,I find it A better way to Grow Spiritually with God. Achieving God's Grace through Faith healing,reading scripture, Lovekindedness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaleekreider @jonathanvswan Aspects of the nation’s decline. And a lot of this can be traced to the deindustrializ… https://t.co/wb9BBzYJZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SarahHuckabee: Don’t believe @MichaelCohen212 — he lied for @realDonaldTrump. https://t.co/awmcBGzVXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcl1973 @xthatpoppunkkid @UnivAfterDark @disafterdark I was gonna buy you a drink in September but you said it first 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawson_Kight @Lumiere87024120 Genre, The name of the anime is Tokyo ghoul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gruber @dcurtis Bold is pretty nice in WhatsApp.  I miss it iMessage.  I can live without everything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben your drunk words were extremely kind as well and meant a lot! Love all the SoCal boys and these guys make it so… https://t.co/jux0I7i52v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks!! Every time these events end, I always find myself looking forward to the next time we can hang out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett Hi I am the current POTUS I was duped by Putin and KJU into believing N… https://t.co/Yxef6xA52z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1 #MAGA… https://t.co/ouay3GmqgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahHill  come on dude.  Don’t ruin all you’ve accomplished. Be a proud male. Be kind and loving. Don’t apologize for being a dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the loud aunt who causes all the drama  @jimb0gart @xxavierokay @okayximgay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ravet drains one about 8ft from the 3 point line for Kittitas to take a 22-21 lead. 5:36, 2Q. #wabkscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trippie Redd was amazing but wished he sang longer than 45-50 minutes 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geoffrey_firmin @sasha_author @washingtonpost @GOP To be truthful I don’t understand that whole gig. Govt paying f… https://t.co/lTSYh9HFOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkitchin63 That is one of the reasons I encourage everyone to join @OOIDA as they already have the infrastructure… https://t.co/rfxpxQzR8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#springbreak2019 #clearwaterbeach #clearwater #florida #floridafishing #reeldealsportfishing #reeldeal… https://t.co/BTBcyBkegZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markboucher00 @francoislegault Et quand t'as pas d'argument,tu traites l'autre de raciste, facile mais pas convaincant!!!😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel @joshgroban Face this truth and I hope it will point you in a new direction  The progressive Democrat… https://t.co/tBaHhU6LZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @realDonaldTrump is asked how large his “manhood” is.... https://t.co/sIOgk7TN92]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts Partner with Abortion Industry, ‘Anal Sex Tutorial’ Promoter Teen Vogue https://t.co/8ZOHIUzRVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I-285 shutdown + Hwy 400 shutdown = The ATL shut down.  #workfromhome @KatieBFOX5 @AshleyFrascaWSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like it will start warming up after 1 pm we had a front move through and stall out will move back north warmi… https://t.co/Baio24AcdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turfproinmo @archwaylawncare None of you people have a clue as to how to behave and run a business. That's free fe… https://t.co/pXlcCQOYct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great mentoring session, Titan Talk with the 100, with our young men here at Arsenal Tech and Futures Cente… https://t.co/mcXaO3tRY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkiGlancy Actually I know someone! @AgentMonochrome took commissions for them :o https://t.co/boDR68ae4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poll: If you could only keep three of these four cornerstone Cowboys, who’s your odd man out? https://t.co/OewfJDbNqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trypal_YT Hi trypal 🙂 been watching your fortnite youtube videos because i just can't build properly lol! Your vid… https://t.co/A0OqxEos2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the day off right dropping off these pineapples 🍍 #peterbilt #bangtrain #pineapples #reefergang… https://t.co/eObu8Isaci]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really gets me how some people think they can judge someone they don’t even know simply on hearsay]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just ordered a sausage biscuit at a dunkin donuts drive thru and they gave me two donuts stuck together lol i fee… https://t.co/Bp6hRn6fkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[B cautious of yo girlfriend “friends“ They B Boosting her to do hoe shit💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently there is a wait and I’m the only one here 🙄 https://t.co/Rz2OVSWkaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godless_nurse @Cyndifferous @AnvastChinaski @HowlinSally @MarqeeMarie @Kinghammer They make cbd gummies? We take a pill and I use a cream]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller _Doc Mike has the best memory EVER!!!!! He is Right! That Drop “Who is that, Shirley!?” Came from him th… https://t.co/0i7syRrw8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf has started playing a French language game at my house and my computer started playing solely French ads now on YouTube #creepin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning to play a guitar @ Trabuco Canyon, California https://t.co/hg8J2yrDKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[force the NFL to employ Kaepernick. Even if Kaepernick had prevailed in a full hearing, that was never part of this… https://t.co/qqsW09fe8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWSchultzLaw @CMDeDominicis With Nelson and Beaulieu someone will sit. Or when 6 comes back. Maybe we can convince someone to take 6 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@opti_mistico @pochodiaz @LORENT_SALEH @MariaFdaCabal @PoliciaColombia @ContraloriaNdS @CGR_Colombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Rosa rainfall record smashed! We need #ClimateActionNow @GavinNewsom #XRebels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms.Gains pulling the fire alarm at 1am tn soo all the niggas in the building by then 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny. Attentive. Helpful. Cheerful. And that accent is a joy to hear.  A hero in my book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shajada_ @Webbdingus @ShannonSharpe I think America is made to help the wealthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game. Set. Match Yeah!!!!!! #COYS @SpursOfficial #ChampionsLeague Of course it’s @HKane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parris Campbell is going to be a filthy pro. His athleticism is unmatched. Elite skill, talent, work ethic, speed,… https://t.co/LHhStM3Dln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yolanda80588631 @Woodpit @NYScanner Yeah ok. Nothing of the sort. I guess you never had a man defend you]]></document><document><![CDATA[#occultimages @ New York's 7th Congressional District https://t.co/voqwygzBhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see more videos like this please follow! Much appreciated! https://t.co/h5OC8jPapt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and #HappyMonday from my alternative music station.  @KHOU @chitakhou @SallyKHOU11… https://t.co/pXzIV8SO3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Bongino: Americans still love capitalism. Here are three reasons why they aren't flocking to socialism  https://t.co/I4ac6AXmv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been telling people @AugustAlsina is a legend... any song he do is a hit 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYYprincess33 Lesson #2 : if you are with a professional athlete, he’s us 100% cheating on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is leading @SportsCenter so you know something crazy happened.  Crazy indeed. Best two minutes you'll watch… https://t.co/qKiQ2QUXaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[First smart thing Skip has ever said even though it’s because his face is sewn to the Cowboys asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfredoEBacci Viva Venezuela;Bless All Of You In The Face Of God....Find Your Freedom...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarleyKwyn I first read this as “over here” and thought lots of friends were enticing you to the city 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wm_Sadler Look at that guy! Always been one of nature’s noblemen! Love ya pal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely love it. Everything it is supposed to be and somehow better than the sum of its parts. - Drinking a Bour… https://t.co/dMvN1jhk3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntheaButler I never watched it, but by all accounts, Luke Perry seemed like a pretty decent guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerGheeNFL @DynastyQuestion Yeah, I think he’s the better Det WR, and I don’t think it’s close]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The intersection of West KL Avenue and S 11th Street near Kalamazoo has just reopened. @WOODTV @traffictom8 https://t.co/XcN0r7PAQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[EPH2:19-22 - Because of the finished work of Christ, we have one church, one family built on one foundation with on… https://t.co/Xt7pSLyM7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans must abide by SECOND CHRONICLES 7,14 or The Judgement of God will be released on America. .… https://t.co/jJZlT3CTgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m watching a documentary about hitler and like all the background music are classical pieces i’ve played... help]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to TTU and KSU on winning the Big 12. The double round robin, home and away conference schedule is a rough… https://t.co/8R3xXHyIFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boys. Cuddle time. @ Barrington, New Hampshire https://t.co/dz36zWqIW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 People like this Trumpist pastor have to be challenged. So lying is good, is that what you think, Pastor?… https://t.co/G436Oa0tAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muppetfrenzy I have a Pixel and I use Google assistant A LOT. So ive accepted it. And Alexa at a house where the n… https://t.co/yMyjjgkjzO]]></document></documents></author>