<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Sema2020 #DefeatCornyn @_SemaHernandez_ @Sema4Texas https://t.co/m7REbqMzhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have that scary feeling of when you’re about to hit a drop in a roller coaster in the pit of my stomach 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green screen fun at #KCCMashpee Dr. Seuss Carnival! #Mashpee https://t.co/ztKK7BlnjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y'all! Surprise surprise: an acoustic version on my song "March", will be coming out on all streaming platforms… https://t.co/Wh6KVGPkoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to this goob. Thank you for being the best i could ever ask for and for putting up with me. I love y… https://t.co/3xjdytzqQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The *real* reason that’s @jimgroom and I like to visit schools... free swag!!! Thanks, #msudh &amp; @CALMSU! https://t.co/MQUe1jboKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lest we forget, before he was an academy award winner @ItsRamiMalek was Benjamin—a member of an Egyptian vampire co… https://t.co/n9TimbrKZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d also like to state that I share the exact same birthday with JonBenet Ramsey...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannairvinn But y’all would pop a perc that actually has dope and xans don’t who the real crackhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like I took too many losses yesterday... Both my sons’ teams fell short last night, I’m sick n a personal L... #UGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spendthriftfarm @claibornefarm @TVG @BloodHorse @theTDN I LOVE that match]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottDochterman Man, I miss going to games in the Fieldhouse ... stands would shake]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Brazilian pure black variety is a game changer @lacolombecoffee https://t.co/PtYMbPcx3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is nothin sweeter than friendship and a good book! ❤️📚#weareAPHE https://t.co/vVXG5qhOXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule @goldengateblond ,@thistallawkgirl, @OhNoSheTwitnt, @MollyJongFast, @maddow ...shall be go on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTanyaTay @JackPosobiec In this day and age where biology and science don’t count, everybody wants their way be… https://t.co/5Lq2iXmlkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @News12WC Yes you are going somewhere HRC...you'll be received in GITMO very soon...they are getting clo… https://t.co/r1kUrSUeIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocobuddysis @ZgrodekKaren @janafisher47 @LiloAuntie @leingh @AXN_Espana @AXN_Portugal @Stana_Katic @mattlenevez… https://t.co/YtJDsgtaUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Jim Jordan is crazier than Trump.  He’s so far up Trump’s behind he may never see the light of day again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[there miggt be worse things that i can think of a way to make a term as enchanting as "indigo child" .....racist https://t.co/C2nSzukjar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows I am pissed that you would use a black woman as a prop, and mad at her for letting it happen! Trump… https://t.co/t0JV5eWCuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow @AmicaAli You worried bout Obama's Tan Suit.  I'm worried about the Devil with a suit on in the… https://t.co/4q7fRVxUC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow in the Dark - Liliac (Official Cover Music Video) https://t.co/eq4VnNvpQn           I cant stop watching th… https://t.co/6KIrZOceWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBergHD I love this practice of associate recognition. You are a role model for adding that personal touch, Chris Berg! 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeSlimKee @SixelaEndys he was happy to have me there. It was such a nice feeling for both of us lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then Death and Hades were thrown into the lake of fire. This is the second death, the lake of fire.  And if anyone'… https://t.co/xhAG3waiSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primeiro dia de um novo capítulo. Me segura SF! 🤗 https://t.co/yKg8vfjz1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always5star @WaltDisneyWorld @_sundaysunsets_ @RoarLoudTravel @MadHattersNYC @monstervoyage @WDWToday Awww you are… https://t.co/ZCeG6Wi7d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journée internationale de la femmes  https://t.co/PusY6LkE1l  #journéeinternationaldelafemme2019 #nationsunie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought of my best friends as soon as I read the thread 💓 @elizabeth_yawn @abbyking19456 @audreykimberlyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many healthy ways to support your heart health through whole foods and supplementation. Earn double rewar… https://t.co/cMnfCLkaSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non verbal cues are powerful indicators of how the negotiation is really going. Being sensitive to what’s left unsa… https://t.co/n80GIHMwso]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t take shit personal from a person who doesn’t know me personally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe you’d lie to me about my Christmas present. If you didn’t have money you could of told me instead o… https://t.co/AnpiipREwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nar Wars is Star Wars with narwhals and people are so ready  https://t.co/ncKtxZZAEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you tell this photo was taken in my childhood bedroom cause of the little buddy in the back https://t.co/3VvOYzD7eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST FINISHED MY LAST SHIFT AS AN INTERN. After 20 long, crazy, amazing months- finally an upper level! #empeds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamcarson Well, this reactionary was pissed (P.S. #voltaire did a better job...at least he was funny)]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no escaping my hours of entertainment on a road trip! #superstar ✨😏💯👏🏻🎶 @ Georgia's 14th Congressional Dis… https://t.co/cXbUNeBxGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 We already have places with walls for people like these. They're called "prisons" and that's where these people belong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OOOH HOPE TODAY WAS THE END OF SNOW AND WINTRY MIX SHIT FOR THE SEASON. LIKE TEN DAYS UNTIL SPRING OR SOMETHING. HU… https://t.co/yG8yY88hDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flipping back and forth between #You and #GossipGirl... Penn Badgley is literally the same person—an outsider with… https://t.co/vDd8Ow8tHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmoneill2530 @politybooks @ManishaAnanthar @raulpacheco @AlastairIles @erin_bergren Congratulations! I look forward to reading it myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keith Law responded to me about Kimbrel and now there’s Nats fans in my mentions rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud Rocket Mama traveling south to cheer on the beast! 👏🏻⚾️🔥🚀💙🤩 https://t.co/hmmzHIlKHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariemamiii People should care! #OfficerAlix #KatlynAlix deserves better! I've battled @stlcountypd for 16 years n… https://t.co/EhukA7ORt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be up for work in 3 and a half hours to work a 12 hour shift. Someone please just go ahead and call to le… https://t.co/7jdoAvDIFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Damn right. This cannot go unpunished. Our New AG needs to start off by going after all these criminals. It’s treason!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BippityDooDah I was born and raised here. OC,  Palm Springs and now Pasadena. Getting ready for a move to Texas.… https://t.co/kkAwXsuts8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes and "it" is, what "it" is, out of control like I have never seen "it". …=_=… 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally loving our weekend getaway. Yeah, we working but I love my job. I feel totally inspired and refreshed.   Pi… https://t.co/va35VXBM5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe we’re halfway there... really can’t believe we have another half to go. 🤰🏻 @ Cape Cod National Seasho… https://t.co/Pq8WmiPxIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen I've never witnessed a president of ANY democratic society speak in that matter. It was shameful. It… https://t.co/u1W2JELLGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squirrel may have been protesting President’s Day as a flex day and wanted a day off of school:       Power back on… https://t.co/1V0K1fpxmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holli @RealEasyTaker @therealjoebob @shudder @tacobell 😋👌 https://t.co/9oCfhH60fF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tristanshouts Bernie is running and it looks like the plan is to attack all the other Democrats  UGH It is not jus… https://t.co/CCnGRUMRRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merc1T @nypost I am sure Shotguns cannot be used in Illinois at least.... BB guns I think you can. Anyway he had n… https://t.co/9qyVNFjLqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Parkland to Sunrise: A Year of Extraordinary Youth Activism https://t.co/gWbL4NW3iJ @NewYorker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family then, family now, family forever @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/6GSeqpyqoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aleks_U_ @chrisbrown If you are real and sincere then why the LMAO thing you see where I'm going with if you have… https://t.co/KMbCq42xfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[wanting someone you know you just can’t have... i hate that shit.   just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP PUTTING AUTISM IN THE SAME SENTENCE AS VACCINE THEY LITERALLY HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH EACH OTHER AND THE MORE… https://t.co/XyUqmD7t5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol i need a boyfriend to go to a symphony with me so i don’t have to go alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is infuriating. We were told WVU was fighting this with all our institutional might. Clearly not. Now faculty… https://t.co/142KUCgk8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constantine as guest artist with @pmjofficial .. a beautiful surprise. @ The Met Philly https://t.co/aYhl4WiyIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenmadigan Hey @kathleenmadigan they are entering tweets into the congressional record. This seems like your… https://t.co/4m3yoMVKUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odio la gente que se cree que tiene confianza conmigo y no tiene ni una mierda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely there should be legal consequences for this promotion of violent acts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be honest, I'm looking pretty hot I'm my Winnie the Pooh jammie pants right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to this guy for being our Golden Ticket Winner this week! Way to go, Matteo!! 🌟💚🐲 #EISfamily… https://t.co/HcEoSGdYxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[not even 11am and i’m already two mental breakdowns deep I Am So Powerful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robynsetter1 I’m a March baby. Almost born at a game. Guess that’s why I ❤️ basketball. Love March madness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @hughhewitt I heard you, you are always a wow... God bless you !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling 1 ticket for Louisville if anyone is looking!! Selling it for original price. Dm me if interested! https://t.co/Lv38eEaDcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomorilaptop @islandjenx @BBCWorld And unlike you, I am not spamming dozens of people with the same message. You h… https://t.co/aZbuQWhazb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será porque los de la SEDENA son soldados y no constructores y albañiles? 🤔🤔 @emprexmex @lopezobrador_ https://t.co/7lFfWIpzLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, I see that Bernie has announced his candidacy and thus it is time for me to delete Twitter from my phone for a… https://t.co/IH9GFJx4ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beenthere4real @FridayInCanada @YandR_CBS Nooooo, when Tessa blackmailed the ladies she did it to help her sister, not be greedy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work to fulfill your purpose and never look back. #5amWritersClub #inspiration #Inspirational]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep telling y’all I might not speak on everything but I see everything 👇🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a matter of when...or Nguyen. Same pronunciation. The current TAD from my new build home. Interesting...Bruce… https://t.co/lUV9Lve37M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @ShirleyRinguet5 The why havent Republicans, in in mass, stood before the cameras and done just that… https://t.co/qKorEfLnpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentIdol @MissCheddie1 @TayRobertson2 @greg_meng @carlivatiron @nbcdays @SteveKentSony @cmasseyofficial… https://t.co/Nek75vX8kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my MK showroom.  #lovemymklife @coffeyisme https://t.co/Zm0tSfWeVV @ Donna Coffey Mary Kay Business Page https://t.co/5aIpoNQRgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarrett_Lerner my kids are going to the cafeteria saying, "Please FEED me com-EST-ib-ules." 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a #trip coming up? Staying healthy while on the road begins before you leave #advice #travel https://t.co/l7qSIB13BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see that big plume of smoke near downtown, @FortWorthFire is at a building fire near Lancaster and Pine, acc… https://t.co/j0doD4cm4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaniSullivan @Mrs_Eastham_LPS @INeLearn @iceindiana @CSHSbulldogs @NMS_Knights @KnightsofNHS @UCMS_Patriots… https://t.co/7IVX6Qj1M2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside Greenville Senior High this morning talking about the bill. Noticed the school’s electronic billboard that… https://t.co/y8s5nrBbAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes I'd like to take a couple of straws and put them somewhere for you so we don't have to listen to your crap anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend and colleague, @ndirdamtl challenged me to post the covers of 7 PD books I love. No reviews no explanatio… https://t.co/VuEwo9ZBu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why’s sex always the “solution” to y’all?!Even muthafuckas fuckin’ religiously will tell you that it isn’t,lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry but past a certain point in Hollywood all you had to do to be famous was have a pretty face and/or connection… https://t.co/jehsVp7GZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya know I expected Neal to get me flowers or chocolates for our 2 year anniversary but instead he got me an Apple W… https://t.co/QFyJw7IFUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo parece indicar que pasaré mi día apretando el botón de snooze una y otra vez hasta que sea martes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lcshorten Just googled it. Its Obasan by Joy Kogawa. Fantastic book that I hope gets made into a film one day. https://t.co/rwu2ggVgGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what the fuck is happening in this stupid DDD Tron world ive been on my phone during all the cutscrnes kfkddkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1) Guidance counselors were meant for guiding academics.  The role of a school counselor takes on a much larger ro… https://t.co/opXWlYQHWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited!!! FINALLY Sophie’s new music video will be released next Monday! Who’s been waiting??? We cannot wait t… https://t.co/9Ubw0Ts9Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starclusterr Kid's a Stonemen Douglas survivor and yet still a Republican... What the actual shit]]></document></documents></author>