<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Farmraider @KevinNguyen41 @TwitterMoments @NewYorker @FoxNews Nice you are some awesome Patriot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferRobeso7 @musiccity2018 @chandler_colin @PromotionsMk @936Arrow @musiccity2019 @DownHomeRadio1… https://t.co/JuCwbgu1bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tampa Bay Lightning Opening Pregame 2/14/19 vs Dallas Stars https://t.co/6Qo6BtW1U9 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but The Msdterlock challenge was stupid you're telling me no one could break a full Nelson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come back to the TL and see beck committed to Georgia, hey it is what it is 🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff When Shep is moving the way he was does that mean he has a good track?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean_Callahan Somebody should tell KETV Sports so they can include that in their sports broadcast.  Shame there wa… https://t.co/EnIjuO1Vwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GreenStreetGorilla #apartmentleasing  #greenstrealty @RealtyGreenSt #spinthewheel #champaign #chambana #luxury… https://t.co/WsVAIyYGyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean like your own parties former leader Obama who said, “You didn’t build that!” You like him are a fraud. You… https://t.co/P8EdPkvmpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman I'd rather listen to Amy Lawrence on tape delay than you and Lima. Good. Day. Sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spreading_L0ve @Tooticki_AK They are also overcomeable if thats a word which is really awesome. Because when one t… https://t.co/c09pyou3ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Accountemps team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/FkYojlF3ke #Finance #Irving, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can’t blast my intrusive thoughts at all of y’all that what even is the point of Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump my kids found this trail and wanted to ski it 45 times for you!! Keep up the great work! https://t.co/vhQlpOaUxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshjmac Sadly there are some fools who think that is a slander rather than praise for the new saint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "Three's Company" is coming to Netflix! https://t.co/qZdAFEfFsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSUsportsreport It depends on your goals...if they’re to vomit all over the place, RedVines. If it’s to enjoy your… https://t.co/E0wYMzydx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is here and spring is in the air! Our hibiscus love the weather! @ Independence Community https://t.co/8LDecmIuqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRED1191 @D_curtis30 @fatmansu @AnalyticalAsh @DubbyGoodell @Hiphopmix2 Yo I muted that shit. I always mute their black history segments🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollyday15 @wink_nod @GenFlynn @darhar981 @SonniGilley @j_ankrom @letters4trump45 @KNP2BP @superyayadize @sxdoc… https://t.co/npCrT8jWVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZakMcClellan Just putting my opinion out there just like you are right now too on my tweet so🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman I believe we are all equal, and as such, I want all of us to succeed. People need to start paying att… https://t.co/3a9KNceclr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Floor &amp; Decor - @flooranddecor in Rocklin, CA https://t.co/2w8hhZauOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @RiteBoss @zenzurzb24 @p_ganzel @AdTony555 @TammySergio2 @bhatanagarntn @glasgow_bruce… https://t.co/qDLUrktLcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎯🎯🎯  Now is the time for self growth! If you ain't getting better, then you are getting worse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jack Fortunes American Legion Post 205 in Augusta, GA https://t.co/A5mtJA6604]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my01089 @cm01089 @dpw01089 @WestSide_PD @wsfdassociation @WSFD01089 @wshsterriers @WestSideSupt @HayleyHolme… https://t.co/5Um0edShI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndianaMBB IU is 5-25 vs. Wisconsin over the past 30 meetings. Yikes. That’s embarrassing. #BoilerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ultrafly @blogTO @poormanshigh @HorseshoeTavern If you’ve heard Billy Idol lately, you’d understand why it’s not a must-see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP How does it feel to know that you either impeach the agent orange now - or be voted into oblivion? What’s it g… https://t.co/Y4aIXhhwjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es un orgullo poder trabajar con gente tan brillante a nivel mundial. Enhorabuena @Salva_Gon_Rod! #AAD2019… https://t.co/tIk7sCG7pM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Jussie did lie it won’t change how quickly y’all were to side with the ops and that’s that on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the F do you run out of signature sauce? It’s the signature sauce??? @superchix]]></document><document><![CDATA[They grow up so fast my  nephew Easton (lil Eastside) he will be 3 this year @ Summerville, South Carolina https://t.co/eyHd2AJX5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaneBurnett @AOC Oh, I PROMISE they don’t hear you, though, my brotha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta go get my oil changed and I don't feel like moving or sitting in the shop for any unnecessary amount of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@butch1720 @BradKSappington @andykeidel @cpsut @ChrisBils @travismclark @MayorAdler @statesman @APrecourt I’ll let… https://t.co/Me1ndw7T2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie about the raspberry. Super abundant - Drinking a Raspberry Slush by @eagleparkbc at @EagleParkBeer  — https://t.co/HS1mOWTLTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soaked and wet but gonna force myself to show up at the gym so I don't go to McDonald's lmao #afterhours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karime_52 @metaorfe @HijasDeLaMx @lopezobrador_ esta es una de carne y hueso. Y así hay varias. https://t.co/4XFPgX5cHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of snow here #snow #ottawa #mackenzieking #winter #snowbank @ Mackenzie King Bridge https://t.co/gXNpQbGc1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingEdward15 @StephenQLane I have no issue with singles matches. The way they got the titles is still horrible. They need to do better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want to win the Urbanathlon” - @leer_gold @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/nxygPsaTKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkWalker The ones the billionaires pay for are even worse. Of course, ai guess you like the feeling of being… https://t.co/IotHZDqIZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aarontimms @tsdheo I also question this Doug because you insist on doing long haul flights in premium economy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lord for allowing me and my family to see another beautiful day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chiefs we need to make some moves in FA , too many good defense players out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Mr. @POTUS do you need some equipment for your new wall. I know a guy over at @SHEquipmentserv that ca… https://t.co/BeZh3oeUVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFrogone Ok , de acuerdo. Pero que lo digan los mercados y consumidorrs  a los que vendemos nuestro trigo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard First tell us what Obama classified under the Iran deal Tulsi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCsobercoach @caroljsroth Oh yeah. Good one.  🎶🎶Dont do the crime if you cant do the time no no dont do it.🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[It just warms my heart that @trvisXX has made #Astroworld the most talked about amusement park in the world. It’s t… https://t.co/L3UIulyNgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grilled sandwich à la Cory #55of365 @ Huntsville, Alabama https://t.co/Fh1uUBVedW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMartinRyan @Benaskren you’re right lawlers takedown and hits was nasty in the beginning. don’t know how askren survived that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[G money on deck we been getting since 11, never give up stay focused not how you start its how you finish  got a da… https://t.co/UFdg9LwDub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody is bothering me today as it`s Sunday. I haven`t bothered to go to church the last few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanBonesy @chemicollins I had no idea this was a universal thing across all gym locker rooms...😳🤯😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AlecBaldwin @nbcsnl nail it🥇  "We need wall, okay," he added, sounding a little bit like Tonto, Tarzan and Franke… https://t.co/kwmHSy91Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[La @fondchagnon se joint à cette initiative. Pour un dialogue de solutions. Pour le bon développement de tous les… https://t.co/zGRBMro2hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hospital is dead and this trend is only going to spread faster. “Our hospitals are like other businesses....The… https://t.co/pSeqwGvy6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I wouldn’t believe Rush Limbaugh if he told me the sky was blue. https://t.co/XVX2FFTfbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beverly Hills, 90210 star died Monday after suffering massive stroke https://t.co/UA5EMMpjpX via @TheWrap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalleKearns @caseydband @the_blue_note @kodyferrin @CaseyDonahewFan Congrats. Have fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse Doubt that the 1920s Klan had access to modern sans-serif typefaces either]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur just people with personalities 😂 i don’t understand this astrology shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickTheSlick12 For sure! Any @SonyAlpha camera is a great camera to start out on. Let me know if you have any more questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Def Jam Fight For NY (Request) - Free For All at The Terrordome (Hard) https://t.co/AfwfSj5FEU via @YouTube… https://t.co/LFMZsdxBZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving people shit for what they like to post on THEIR social media? https://t.co/810IKu40FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do these colors make you think of? #uchicagoarts #uchicago #fineart #mfa #chicago @ Reva and David Logan Cente… https://t.co/mgNQcEMPqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all made tonight AMAZING! I am truly humbled and blessed beyond measure! @ Wylie, Texas https://t.co/AYwCpqEsfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #GagaSlayed on @TyltEnt—Lady Gaga slayed the #Oscars red carpet https://t.co/igXsd0v7ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so I went to my first EDM concert tonight and I had a blast...but that might because of the babe I was with all… https://t.co/0pABXtsTqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gustavoduenass Xq vergüenza?. Si bsc hubiese recibido esa info crees que no hubiesen reclamado si perdían 1-2 en G… https://t.co/s1edpUeFfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't find it weird I just always seem to not fit in the seats and if I sit next to someone I'll feel bad taking… https://t.co/yp9FEZqidP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok Gucci blackface we Holler BOYCOTTING!! Well This is social Buck Breaking! And Trump ain’t at fault #hollywood is… https://t.co/KTWS81JlfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeroesPadierna Mmmm lo de AMLO tiene emoción pero López Portillo es López Portillo... https://t.co/SxEOy9gvsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahBookbinder @Gypsysister58 So how is the wolf guarding the sheep working out so far????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericaGirI @scottmckee4 @ggreenwald Yes, it is a veritable slaughter. Just ask those Carrier workers. But I'm afr… https://t.co/JYEWgPVPnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a go-getter on the job? Do you dream big and go the extra mile to uncover the next groundbreaking idea? Lea… https://t.co/neUlfcBc9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[“People who are ‘morning larks’ and those who are ‘night owls’ have a fundamental difference in brain function. Thi… https://t.co/kzeBu0qlHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenLovell75 hey Ken, I think you will appreciate what these student athletes had to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfryer4 @lakingsinsider Ottawa... er... Colorado has a lock on Hughes unless Edmonton finishes 4th then they’re SU… https://t.co/6cBXmLEgo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Optum The big boulder to move in healthcare is the profit motive. It has to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday homie ❤️ hope was was well spent ily @clay_sebastian https://t.co/hqEo1zNLJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamplightpath I’m glad you see that 🙏🏾❤️🙌🏾! I’ll definitely be relaxing and vibing after work once I get home but… https://t.co/N5b0pavcxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wellrocketed one step closer to bringing human spaceflight back to America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[man I really felt the way @cthagod summed up the state of attention, clout chasing and feelings over facts state ou… https://t.co/YRyl7phdhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXSportsKnox @knoxvillesstone Perimeter defense...I know that was part of the 1st choice but I don’t think we nec… https://t.co/R9R2dXyyYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mama Bear's Sour Cherry Pie by @CrookedStave at @Willardshouse — https://t.co/PNXXZOl3ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Steiner shows up in the new Being the Elite episode on YouTube. That was awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my very humble opinion, Bernie is going to disrupt any chance of unity in tne Democratic Party...again.   I don’… https://t.co/MOPg3U8cKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I didn’t have so terrible insomnia which keeps me up past 3am everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@540jimw Wish my eyes hadn’t watched the 55 points that Auburn scored last night. It was brutal!  24 points though… https://t.co/8xO37qv6Am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaranaBurke the thing is @MeTooMVMT still put black women issues on the back burner, yall are silent about other m… https://t.co/CnVjgPQayS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsonEffect @stb71 @dwellman21 @Underculture1 @AOC Having I assume more experience with cancer and aggressive ill… https://t.co/3iEtY3n62I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoindextersLab Lmaooooo it be like that sometimes... Speaking from experience 🌚😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hefehh72 @damienwoody Money talks, bullshit walks, like it or not - the boss has the money, he pays the player to… https://t.co/hy5V26dt84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NowOnDeck Shoot, I’ve been telling the Sophs I coach that we do NOT have a shot clock for some reason.… https://t.co/r4MTJyvVgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacko2323 Everything is more expensive in California so it's really $200 million everywhere else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night game in Irmo, SC for @FMHSbaseball So far so good 5-0 thru 2 innings for the tournament championship game.]]></document></documents></author>