<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Twas_Him @nbcwashington @Dillards If guilty, he should not avoid jail. This is a serious matter including federal… https://t.co/VgnUO5uhdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan And you have the makings of a terrorist. #FoxInTheHenhouse #DemocratsAreBabyKillers]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do all the good you can, to all the people you can, in all the ways you can, as long as you can”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyPelas Love women with strong beliefs &amp; opinions. Keep on striving for what you are passionate about Lindsey !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Nashville: It is too rainy for public school but not too rainy for 50 people to wait in line at Biscuit Love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dignthegarden It is but I think I’ve let myself fall into a mental rut of thinking the same.  I gotta up my game a… https://t.co/BDf2yW6DWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never tell a entrepreneur what they “should’ve” done ... stay in your own lane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flawlesshoodrat I’ll play you in a game of smash cause you got that eye for snapshots]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost hairstylz_byhelen •  •  •  •  • #njtopsalon #centraljersey #nj #njhairstylist #bridalhair #weddinghair… https://t.co/YMOQfEF1f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at what @alex_strouf sent me today. What a guy. https://t.co/2MScWgejBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesterosHistory Instead of just a heart button, there should also be a heart with an arrow through it button.  YOU'RE KILLIN' ME HERE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously. The traffic signals from Kenmore to the 198 on Delaware are made to make you stop at every single 1. At 6 am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaBeez Papa’s first winner with @VictorJockey onboard https://t.co/zkqsFuqQPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PC1170 Do they have any Vietnam vets?  Perhaps they could trade some veteran cred with Nathan Philips for native cred...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "OSLG / Store Seasonal Employee" at Lowe's? Apply even if you're not a 100% match.… https://t.co/VwSZN6rSvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Matt Duchene be taking a farewell Uber with his former teammates on the way to tonight's game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanSchaub How is this the promoters fault? Fury chose to go to ESPN, knowing FULL WELL what this would do to t… https://t.co/dyhjH3UtyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Allied Universal in #Warren, MI. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs lik… https://t.co/tSZgHg3cOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/jicCInyPBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowkey always putting me down and saying I wouldn’t be graduating high school lmfao. But karma was a bitch to y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do they ever specifically call terminators “terminators” this question needs answers ASAP please help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontshootskrlx Idk, I saw Panic At The Disco’s pics from the Excel Center and they look way better than the ones y… https://t.co/j6ccGjNjlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nice_gwen @BelfortGavin @dpakman @charliekirk11 Because they’re #Bots?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw it Sat. Scout and Calpernius carry the show. It's not the book AND it's worth seeing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please drive safe out there today everyone. I've seen too many tweets about accidents on our highways. Take a few e… https://t.co/nZlWRdgTYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XRobynStevensX @BethMcKenna53 Right about when you are turning 45, I'll be turning 48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Yeah, I'm single.  And I'm sure other guy's probably do it to. When I'm sick and don't feel like gett… https://t.co/Y9wUIwnuoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otto Porter Jr.'s First Days With The Chicago Bulls - Run With Us | S2 EP7 https://t.co/K5eiTuhxrv via @YouTube Che… https://t.co/ydZ0J0s7Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1 in Class A South GBB 1/4 finals Brunswick 15 MTA 11 #GODRAGONS https://t.co/T2Eb5g5Bnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upcoming Events! Friday, March 15th Boston, Massachusetts  wwnevolve 123 Saturday, March 16th Queens, New York wwne… https://t.co/Qt6YpfidIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to think God knows what he’s doing because if I saw someone being a pos racist in front of me I’m hitting them]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to all step up and stop the hate, homophobia, racial, religious, etc. Respect ALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats If our Democratic leaders are going to be having hearings and asking other questions at hearings th… https://t.co/UchYK3snch]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta love them #dawgs Final 80- 77 @AdrianBulldogs #AdrianBulldogs @AdrianMBB #Kalamazoo great win! @STiknis… https://t.co/HWChPdNTWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is a Father of the fatherless, and a Judge of the widows, evenGod in his holy habitation. Psalm 68:5]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA POSITION DU BLOC QUÉBÉCOIS est tout simplement honteuse dans le dossier SNC-LAVALIN. De quel pays veulent-ils do… https://t.co/dUZWGMHZuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Deer, one of seven, next to the hotel attempting its Great Bustard impression https://t.co/NHIFTWmbBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SereneEntropy @pollyto123321 @HuffPostEnt Watch that doc and then say you trust that real emotion from a dozen peo… https://t.co/15tSYWHDN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonLatta @MSNBC @Morning_Joe The thing is for the first time in his life Donald Trump is being held accountabl… https://t.co/xlyslNJiIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump BUILD THAT WALL. MR. PRESIDENT YOU CAN BEAT CONGRESS/ ORDER ALL YOUR WALLS AND PAY FOR THEM IN FUL… https://t.co/sGovZanZ4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know about everyone else but this admittedly egocentric principal needed to hear that.... #leadupchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAMA BRAND TOM YUM RAMEN SPICE PACKET IS MY SECRETEST WEAPON. SHE KNOWSSSSSSSSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldblackgoat @JerryisjustOK @DrunkGraveyard that's what i'm hung up on. What was the issue these metal heads had?… https://t.co/JLOWXFBnf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsPeteRepeat @realDonaldTrump Just how a Tea Party member would think: vile. Thanks for confirming your  D.N.A., vile human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djservice1 @comcast I have a box of their junk here for a year, sent to me free to upgrade. Promised free install,… https://t.co/2yaicJ8PEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBuc08179594 @wpnsys1954 @jschmidt27 @boyscouts I'm going to be fun at drill weekends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Wayne's Max Denman has been named to the @NLL_Sports boys basketball first team. The @AWGenerals1 senior al… https://t.co/m6DKCR0EP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on @realDonaldTrump we should empty or prisons because everyone in there, will tell you; they didn’t do it. A… https://t.co/Va8DZf3gdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia If nothing else, your theme nights make me aware of how many movies and tv shows I've never seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claudester @CarolGo18658081 @h1ren @gregolear @CNN @nytimes #ButterEmails https://t.co/kzWlLlX6XL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2012, Republicans screamed bloody murder when Obama issued an executive action temporarily protecting childhood… https://t.co/TTtV7TeTIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shamusroan13 @leeleebb21 @MomO5Tiff Tiff u only gave us 3 minutes of peace 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️ luv u buddy glad u are back 😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NRWLjkQa5y Please nominate us for 2019 @BryantCSLI Student Engagement Awards. Don't forget we helped… https://t.co/a1SmzWAyLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslesForLIfe Preaching to the choir. Last year every excuse was made about his abysmal minus. Yes it isn’t a perfe… https://t.co/IigzPoLQOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Patricia Heaton, born March 4th, 1958, in Bay Village, Ohio. https://t.co/jC0tcefwIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dat_BCB @Bigdogz1318 @LedyardNFLDraft It was his worst game but it wasn’t a Greedy thing is my point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier ...and a better chance for a decent future.  With a lottery ticket you will at least have a chance a… https://t.co/ZOAJuN58OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaWatson @RapeCrisisEandW @EVAWuk May ban Agenda 21 together no one's going to hack my stuff and steal my data a… https://t.co/BLFQtxm7Oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alonso Playing 1B/LB for Mets on Monday and Reddick responded to him after the game. #MLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldSchool80s And so began the trend of people being woke up when others go-go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it.... we can’t skate with the Lightning. But wtf.... don’t give up. #playlikeshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man tiante drove 10 hours to see the Celtics play the warriors just for Kyrie only to see Hayward carry em LMAOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[SlingStudio Hub - HD Video Switcher for Multi-Camera Production, and Live Streaming &amp; $100 Amazon Gift card https://t.co/9DJoiPCy3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristadani85 I missed that the Habs are in town tonight or I’d have bought tickets, damn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Or he could take a knee and get 2 or 3 years in one lump sum... #Goodellisaclown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB @OfficialBBD @KayGeeNBN Absolute Legends!!! Making Boston proud since friggin 1980!!! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👊🏻 Reapect Gents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday on the @profchayes Craig Hayes Morning Show. Listen 1300am locally, https://t.co/bnFszLcUkW or c… https://t.co/maB04rGxOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN The boy did nothing wrong. 100% with him. Teacher should be fired. And the arresting officer needs to brush up on history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoustacheRollie @emmanuelzee13 @zachkram It would seem not. His value is what somebody is willing to pay him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgar224u @RSHunter71 Yep. How they pull the trigger the second time always amazed me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeansforToes @piscidian @cnnhealth Same boat. I’ve asked my doctor about it a bunch and he’s always super dismissi… https://t.co/qPrKEjDg3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyDRowlands Plus, the opportunity he had yesterday morning is not intact, it’s done. (Got stuck in GIA) Opportu… https://t.co/WVkCqD2JGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ curious if he will still be working for you by the end of the year.  bet people… https://t.co/cY0rkomdDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estupidez sin limites. El modo de pensar de la izmierda. El socialismo en su mejor expresión.  La “equidaT” y la “i… https://t.co/sSFqNJmiUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gofooji @SHOBlackMonday #BlackMonday Thank you! https://t.co/fauzUXr7Xt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will give $1.00 to the fly OAC and Uncle Bernie to Venezuela campaign, Who is with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottieschicken @Devin_Heroux You got your wish !!!!  Last end, last rock, last finger nail ?  :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Juggernaut by @BrewDog at @brewdogusa — https://t.co/m0wN3BwS7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InOutArmy @Coach_BRiley @DrunkOldGrad @NikolaiBusko @ArmyBarstool @ArmyWP_Hockey @brigade_review @AAE_SBN… https://t.co/h4yefWovb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cloden1 @Alexis_Cossette @mauraislive Non pas du tout !  Ce serait un moyen de montrer justement à quel point ils sont matures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Won't be long until #ComradeCortez 's list includes everyone but herself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megalodonna Luckily for me yes they do. Whenever their for the night, they come in my room, lie down in their pet… https://t.co/YErNtZFBnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBeltrand7 @HelianaMBS @MBeltrand7 tiene la razón. No se puede combatir la naturaleza. La edad la ha derrotado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnfollowTrump Holy fuck, you are really the biggest, most insecure LOSER out there.  Oh, and a monumental lying as… https://t.co/C2B1ami4EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are just minutes away from chatting with the chief. @spann coming up on #GoodMorningAlabama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @RuthAhlbrand Poor Toby. @Talkmaster can we take the carbon cub to go get him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think that they should have a ban on a certain name when running for president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So just from this one idea I have many avenues to work with when I become the author I want to be. This upcoming su… https://t.co/SiHgUATMs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok honestly I love the way @saphir’s voice sounds at the beginning of Martyr. She’s a really great singer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything  like all this shit,,,,u never understand it,,, https://t.co/asUbzuoTcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D1_Prospect123  Happy Birthday Julian! Hope you enjoy your special day! Go Dawgs!! 🏈🐾🐾🏈 https://t.co/DWKvRdF0xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JREpodcast Shut the fuck up you bitchass haters! If you don’t know funny don’t speak on it just like the late great Patrice O’Neal says!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfMattFox @mendel_random Here too subject matter knowledge untestable in the study at hand is required and the d… https://t.co/Y3KrNJwTJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaKahn7 Woha! That’s a can worms.....the easy answer I think though is no. If you want some something privet… https://t.co/uuii6kVp3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥❤️👍🏻my new pair #canyonoaks #kswiss #kswissclassics #cr329 #harperexplores @ Canyon Oaks Country Club https://t.co/U8zs7vJa1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whpresscorps I knew that letter was going to be a problem. You can’t use the postal service that way. They do not take it lightly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day in history, 02/15/19. In 1763, the Treaty of Hubertusburg (pictured about 1763)  is signed at Hubertusb… https://t.co/CbidRTjl4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Bank of America removed gold isn’t a brag its a fortune network looks to seek Benguela for port authority… https://t.co/g51FW3NDxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great, unemployment is at a 60 year low and I’m here with no job for the first time in my adult life. Wtf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I feel like I've heard this kind of prediction before... https://t.co/2IBZamaD6r]]></document></documents></author>