<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PlymouthDawg You will definitely be missed, I'm sure!!! Safe travels home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mga BN tinatag si Cassy bwahaha. Hanapin nyo kasi MIA na. Sya lang ba pambato nyo? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarleyBeth Yes, and a whole room of people who know they didn’t get any cake now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGutmanBooks @RoystonsLions @CliffwoodProud @MARSDNJ You might be able to put these kids on your payroll! They’r… https://t.co/3LKHxRsEKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essas pessoas desejam protestar ou chocar? Se impor ou passar vergonha? Eu não consigo entender ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch loves her dog more than her best friends and that’s the tea!!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a parlé Femmes et espaces publics avec les membres de @projetmontreal ce soir! Beaucoup de femmes présentes pour… https://t.co/oix9Zsg18r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Extenebris_Lux @thehill ....that may have been her plan to usurp the powers that be and make America Muslim.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8MillionML @HippieVol @madsatan6969 @Smokeyholler @The_Fool_Monty @Shawn172510 @GTA_Redhead @beers300 @DollyVol… https://t.co/YvAKgpnxIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any one of your problems could be easily fixed with one solution   SEEK GOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼 yo me enamouré de ti ♥️ no de la edad que tiennes 🎤 #robertotapia 🎼 #datenight Te Amo ♥️🥰 @ L.A. LIVE https://t.co/wPpJMvDfu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevanKendrick @Nike I don’t even like Duke, but I support this message. #SheCantHaveAnymoreOreos]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many women to watch, but Brittany T. Oliver is one at the top of my list. She is a serious community buil… https://t.co/SL1m9QYXxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catherinebh @Phung_Leeeezy @ElizaBe30319693 @SonyaSone7 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity https://t.co/jmZiyGqZDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incase you had a stressful day .. Remember tomorrow’s a New day🌻 https://t.co/iFBktLWiRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessandno21 @z_long He finally is getting glasses. Rapid deterioration is probable 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm old enough to remember when the US went into negotiations from a position of strength?  #GreatNegotiator… https://t.co/klURajnjtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton just proves that you chase after something you really want I guess.... if it’s love and it’s meant to be it’ll be. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRACTICE: Encourage all the works established for the relief of the Souls in Purgatory.   RESOLUTION: At night, in… https://t.co/rB1M3CIzjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerobaldo 😝 Este es el más me gusta ja durado también. Aunque parece ser que presiente. 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Are you as concerned about the lies that @realDonaldTrump tells the American people multiple times a day, EVERY SINGLE DAY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outrageous @buell003 @BlakandBlack @haloefekti @KittyBhagat @Dennis_Lintz @aidanzzzzz @KatG4 @deeshanger @cliffpotts]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were 15 months old, where would you have hidden the Apple TV remote? Asking for a desperate friend (me).]]></document><document><![CDATA[do u ever hear a really loud plane fly over your house and think “this is the end”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fearless Fashion Friday #DrSeussDay #ProudtobePB 💙 https://t.co/ZtVNRS2tBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raquelwilliam37 @AJBianco @John_Coviello @gjablonski24 @ariellehg @AlexVerace @DisruptedTv @RonGrosinger… https://t.co/ffd5yL1IRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DoomPatrol is getting even *more* batshit from here on out. Just watched this Friday’s episode 3 and I couldn’t st… https://t.co/Fyo8spQutZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨This is so sad and maddening. He made so many of us look like damn fools!🚨 #JussieSmollett has been indicted by a… https://t.co/al8AvZfK5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton @IlhanMN Nationalism is NOT white nationalism just because our president happens to be white 😂 let’… https://t.co/JqYSX6H83D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badeutsch It’s nice to know someone will keep them grounded and their egos in check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fave new wallcovering by @fabricut is the love child of chinoiserie and botanicals! ⛩🌿⛩🌿⛩🌿Oh, and did I mention… https://t.co/tE5OnaBFsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccamae103 i tooootally wanted to do sushi for vday but we woke up too late and now we have to wait until shania’s healed 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaUnderhill @sainasix I’m white straight and know the difference between admiration and attraction but these ph… https://t.co/SaQ2AOzo8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRMoffitt Good god what in hell is going on with degenerate police? Good ones, I’m not talking about you!!! Thi… https://t.co/K4UtihL0xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @mefbama Crazy Witch thinks any one cares what a loser has to say !]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @megaroow for your ride along with @erlangerhealth #futureflightRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting down the moments until I can get my #morningshowfix - a breakfast burrito from @Wawa WITH the hash brown-… https://t.co/QNKqukyF8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras esperamos la rueda de prensa de Trump y Duque, os dejo con este resumen sobre lo que han dicho ambos previ… https://t.co/8D0fa7IxcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B3NjAMiN_9 This one actually was legit candid thank you very much I would look awkward if it wasn’t. I was looking… https://t.co/6AgqStcydo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConanOBrien Riddle me this...who should run for president under this hashtag:… https://t.co/hgHTeq5QW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC is full of it!  Socialism does not work. Sure, let’s pay all the same wage whether or not they have earned it a… https://t.co/myqGVJnHdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t ya just hate it when you sneeze &amp; your tampon shoots out a tad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean the genius doesn’t want folks to know just how smart he is! SAD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the Eva creators were fans of X lol? https://t.co/2DdDUtPneq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Y'all, we are "Marching" into our final month to get the great wedding photography special we have until March… https://t.co/ZBPKz5WcCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I would love to be there🤗 thank you for your love of America ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so refreshing when you find someone who isn’t like everyone else..]]></document><document><![CDATA[how come these people keep wrapping their babies up like beans for their new born pics? plz don’t stop i’m crying bc cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG. This ending. I can't. Why. Too beautiful. Perfect. #movie #AMC #reaction #LiveTweet #spoiler #HTTYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[20. Tell a joke. Umm, no. I started to Google "jokes", then figured I would just admit that I've got nothing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time tonight with @jaymerios and Harold.......just missing the other two]]></document><document><![CDATA[New run for ‘Runaway Princess’ https://t.co/g3WsPg4hxJ via @IrishEcho#irisharts#irishrep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annual Oscar night pic with my mom! It’s kind of a big deal for us 😍🥂🎭🤳🏻 @ Carson City, Nevada https://t.co/WIa8AQ7Nfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a wierd comment or question for a police officer to receive.  Seriously, wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand girls who wear a full face of makeup to the gym.. I feel bad for ur skin 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for you @jmbomba5. Grateful that others are willing to invest in you and your dreams. Use that as motivatio… https://t.co/P1SAdCSAc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Be the reason someone smiles today, spread the positive energy and Love” 🙏🏾❤️💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[OUR FATHER IS CALLING US TO THE DEEPEST OF DEPTHS WITH HIM!  TO FLOW WITH HIM.  LIQUID LIGHT STRETCHING FORTH...SOM… https://t.co/JHL5xyLQ0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catebug84 @UrbanDecay @GameOfThrones Hahaha you gonna have to get it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenía mucho tiempo que no iba al mercadito de la Felipe, había olvidado lo grande que estaba. Creo que ayer comí de… https://t.co/qHpK2SzyVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Char walks in and sees Missy’s Harry Potter wand*  “WHO’S DOIN’ WITCHCRAFT?!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDogLive @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD Looking good! Stay safe out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes you simply have to accept someone did not love you as much as you loved them]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PoliticsNation Sorry Rev Al, cannot watch Carrie Sheffield. If I wanted to hear a right winger, I would turn on Fo… https://t.co/i1npaZtekA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captnhoran That show was pure crack and absolutely glorious crack at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #nationalcheddarcheeseday today. I have my @tillamookcheese medium cheddar sliced and ready. I’m surprising my… https://t.co/DtjLZwR0X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents forgot my sisters at the store and they out running earns without knowing they missing two kids 🙄 like w… https://t.co/7lMM83pvmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffmason1 @EliStokols @realDonaldTrump yeah, he should at least had a teleprompter so he sounded half-way rational]]></document><document><![CDATA[A generation weeps today #RIPLukePerry #JamesDean #ourbadboy https://t.co/cq7fJ3R3Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got this! 👊🏽 Have a fabulous Monday!!@D4Griffin3 #BIGday #MondayMorning #mondaymotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good summary of our analyst event @blairplez Bridges and Clouds - Cisco Collaboration Analyst Summit 2019 - https://t.co/uIi7NncsK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright. Keeping this train rolling we've got mid-40s greased back ponytail with SIIIIDEBUUUURNS.  Now I'm just pic… https://t.co/NxaL1nEhmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sternvascular @esambolmd 3 vessel BTK runoff for a claudicant? Stanford high standards!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing is to go to a different city and not tell anybody besides the people I’m staying with and then se… https://t.co/smxg3K9juL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dewestmusic243 Agreed. Never heard about islamaphobia before. Never saw the country so divided as when Obama was president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does it creep anyone else out how much @BaileeMadison looks like @MaiaMitchell or is it just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to submit for recertification a couple of YEARS EARLY for my SPHR in a couple of months because I hig… https://t.co/AHJJMrshp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #winewednesday! Thank you to @biltmorewines at @biltmoreestate for the taste of Reserve, Estate-Grown Chardonn… https://t.co/7Nwybg7cpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats 🍾🎊🎈🎉 Alfonso Caurón and thank finally god to Rami Malek 🕴🕴🕴🕴🕴🕴 4 winning best Director and Actor !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to think how different things would be if my grandpa was still here. Or if my big brother was here.  Miss you… https://t.co/O934hx0B0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Holy Spirit, the Advocate, wants to remind you that from the beginning you were made in the image and likeness… https://t.co/IYIyiyzI8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveTHIS- great video, a teacher who rocks! “Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character.”- @AlbertEinstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LariskaPargitay @TheDweck @justanoutlawfic Just “trump” - he doesn’t even deserve Mr. much less president…]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just checked one of my weather apps &amp; saw its supposed to snow Friday &amp; Saturday..............]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww came home to a cooked meal. My boyfriend surprised me with penne a la vodka 🥰🍝]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 11th #dool #days  Fri Mar 15th  Brady blasts Eric for kissing Sarah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then watch our adult Daughter break down,B ecuse we don't know how we can pay for the Chemotherapy his Doctor s… https://t.co/G7DFR8kNLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHorowitz @CanUEverForgive @LeaveNoTraceMov Agree and I still listen to that amazing Bacharach/Costello soundtrack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay from two strong women! https://t.co/kYDbd0NZO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My physical therapist has made me aware of just how tired I am all the time even after 8 hours of sleep. I can’t re… https://t.co/iO2F13pMzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC Unbelievable.  Why does she stay here. Move to another country,  aoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NadineNice1 is no longer an egg. Thank you @amber_heffner Growing a little more each day! #tigerbullets #rowvastrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bioteacher4109 @JedRose17 @realDonaldTrump Unfortunately it IS Canada's business. Its technically the worlds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@windmechanic I'll be honest. I've heard of it but am clueless about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskAManager The first letter was really sad. There wasn't any evidence to suggest the vacations are lavish, and it… https://t.co/HPBWszm3uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Crucible mock trial taking place in Mrs. Taranec’s and Mr. Brusstar’s 2nd hour.  Excellent work by the prosecut… https://t.co/NmhrXXCfhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @MSNBC @KatyTurNBC @ericswalwell Report on Elected REPUBLICANS BETRAYAL of COUNTRY! We don't care wha… https://t.co/o9dgigx3cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jobs in our #SiliconValley will continue to grow. We need bold solutions for #housing to keep up. @siliconvalleycf… https://t.co/SE0pOWUxOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts so bad to lose a parent, so please tell yours you love them you never ever know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoHablaEnglish You have to wipe down so the fecal matter doesn't go in. As well if it's really in the lips you're… https://t.co/uba9praoc8]]></document></documents></author>