<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Spike Lee is one of the biggest racists to ever stand in front of or behind a camera. He proves every time he opens… https://t.co/BQI0kUSEry]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Seneca West repeats as champion while Lew-Port wins its first sectional title since Jimmy Carter was president… https://t.co/OaZ8lQY1YD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @NickStumby, #headspace is an awesome app! I used it this morning and found it very impactful. I loved how your… https://t.co/bkKxk4PyQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog loves snow ⛄️ #snow dogs #pets en Nogales, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/lQ20qTSV6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing for our homeless vets? Should start a group, "Americans B4 Illegals", just to see if it would help our coun… https://t.co/hf3RbT7fYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[VERY entertaining first quarter ends with Columbia Christian on top of western Christian 18-16 @OSAASports #opreps #OSAAtoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIAnderson3 @RobertL45529100 @maxandfriend17 @TboneIA @muskabs @spacecowgirl915 @RealSterner @StarLilyResists… https://t.co/wQxVDNBjo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foi-se o tempo em que eu ainda carregava eles no colo ♥️ @Littlewollff @lilithd_s https://t.co/UtQsXSF4wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Young: You ever came close to a ring? Gilbert: nah Nick: Oh that's right, LeBron kept beating you in the first round]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS SOCCER Back underway here between The Woodlands and College Park. 39:10 left in the first half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rouham89 on the panel at the UN High Level Debate on International #Migration and Development https://t.co/mId60ZeqWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women of Austin, please let’s have a popularity contest. Brian Manley. Him or me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryLegum Interpret wisely This note is legal tender for All debts PuBlic And Public inTerP REt wiSeLy Why public… https://t.co/dPRaqYrFRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirbyhilde @UmbrellaAcad Eeeeekkkkkkkkkkkkk it was so good!! Scenes like that one and this one just we're so unexp… https://t.co/DJ9SBiLbIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROHLL5 @BMcAdory9 @pennington_jr @whatznextfolks @clovis1931 @ImabitcSumtimes @TrumpMyPres @harjo111 @carrieksada1… https://t.co/e1U0by9hy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently you can't use your @Starbucks rewards abroad. I'm in the US for four months, and while I can collect sta… https://t.co/tep7nDR1cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is really possible to follow 8k people on twitter? Should I feel bad that I was unfollowed? #NoNotAtAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dhild11 @RPOvermeyer Since PG13 took over son. But I think the bucks just passed them if I’m not wrong. Record wise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathan_rockwell 75% of the people who drive are living on their own planet.  They have no idea anyone else is out… https://t.co/1RcDd5l8Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncrediBILL17 Plus i know a particular someone with 3 anyway #KingJames]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump And, he has no integrity and no courage....pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked why Duclair is a healthy scratch again, Torts said: “bad listening skills.” Wouldn’t elaborate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NolanRosenkrans @bernielunzer @news_guild @apantazi Im quoting people who are saying it.   But democracy does not… https://t.co/d7lQsv0oZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Blog Post: That time: We hiked the Berg Lake Trail. Part 2  https://t.co/xkiZe4CZdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #Twins manager Rocco Baldelli addressing the media following the first pitchers and catchers workout of the spr… https://t.co/7sRe83kygy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_maddyburns @ChloeMelzo @mmaryelizabeth_ And if they don’t, then JFS can step in and do what needs to be done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalecol what happened? You said we had no chance. Go cheer for someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again...  Heading back to NYC for 2 nights before heading to #MWC2019  📷on @SamsungMobileUS… https://t.co/8WH0X3s4cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anybody know if parx comes out after the show to meet people? i couldn’t get vip this time around 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @12crazysworn I have listened to Republicans crying about this 💩for your years  sure you win some battl… https://t.co/Gzn3cTiymi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHiltonx @NotANastyWoman_ @IvankaTrump @NextRevFNC https://t.co/slZB7e7EeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever agreed to make LaBahn that small should be ashamed of themselves.   Playoff tickets just sold out in like 2… https://t.co/box1TULzCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to check out the Mustang Roundup in tomorrow’s Strongsville Post for features on Strongsville High Sch… https://t.co/a7KgQc7nrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heidi B. Ho Flota Sanchez And Her Yu'Gi-Oh Girlfriend In Viva Las Vegas: How The West Was Lost - Coming Soon To A T… https://t.co/W9a1uD52UT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t use Twitter often but @wfuv introducing me to @Sunflower_Bean is totally worth a tweet. This band rocks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steel_Curtain4 I’m still a little nervous because Schefter has not said anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a @DairyQueen manager confirm a young woman in the back was clocked out, then asked her to start making an order :^/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unprompted, Alexa just told me to adjust our clocks. How did she know I was in our living room to tell me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torproject The point here is privacy. On public property or public interactions I'm completely ok it. Anything tha… https://t.co/V4XdFM4df3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Twitter. I'm back. I took a day off to not get AS4 spoilers. Just finished watching the finale...#stunning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is a new day. One can only wonder what adventures are in-store for you. #WaitForIt #SeizeTheMoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Countryboi567 Maybe just for insurance purposes bc from what we’ve seen as fans, there wasn’t a ton of production… https://t.co/7EQkplmpSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidNSimone @BearcatNeal I mean, they have to do those mental gymnastics to make their season seem less terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next major awards upset coming is BEST ACTRESS. Stay tuned next  Sunday.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you fucking kidding me?! You do this all the fucking time!  This can’t be real...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeidraCBS2 @cbschicago Shout out to Kim Fox for makin this a priority... the missing people and murder cases can wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll use that $15 to get a 12-pack of beer and get drunk so I can stomach seeing all the Duke/UNC crap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go!!  If you are in the #downtownphoenix area please come by thecroftdowntown and enjoy some of #lasvegas f… https://t.co/xGLaEjOmeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[BWI’s TSA is either extremely empty or flooded all the way back to the check-in counters 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m completely obsessed with @ReginaKing’s win tonight! #BestSupportingActress #Oscars #BlackHistoryMonth #BlackGirlMagic #Yasssssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoConSports @WoffordMGolf @marchmadness @WoffordTerriers Ticket punched despite your horrible officials tonight. A… https://t.co/XsleVx6YDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ukraine and the shifting balance of power https://t.co/0WfjMVG0qW https://t.co/ddkMOGhLJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @espn is going to cover the Duke game.....🤔🤔🤔🤔 https://t.co/9t5dT3seXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EKM1 @jacklykins @ScottTackett66 Jim Bloomfield, Chris Jones, OJ Mayo, Mark Surgalski, Jon VanHoose, Harold Sargen… https://t.co/a4yrW9OyeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody setting their yard on fire for clout and fame, you’re ignorant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DexterBraziel Bro you better take that shit back. Lmfaooooooooo wait till you find out how much just one of them little fuckers cost😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jreubenappelman @LSD122070 @nicole_bertrand @Steelerschic85 @EmmaHeward @lovemyjessica22 @returnofjenmack… https://t.co/szSpkaLYrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen IT'S TIME THE @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @SenateDems @TheDemocrats GET THIS VILE MAN OUT OF OFFICE.… https://t.co/Zs0k2cvS2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JClarkNBCS Hopefully NOT. Don’t want Machado or Harper. Win it without spending $250M. Give the money to fighting cancer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cosmiccwarriorr 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🦎🦎⚡️⚡️🛸🛸🛸🌴🌴🌴🌴🙈🙈🙈❓❓❓👾👾☔️☔️💟💟💟💟☢️☢️☢️☢️☯️☯️☯️☣️☣️☣️☣️☣️☣️☣️☯️☯️☯️☯️ HYPE TRAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way cool Marine biology innovation from San Diego, NOAA and Scripps  "They needed a boat big enough to tow a sixty-… https://t.co/uztpdMGXef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom The fire north of Sacramento that killed 83 people was caused by the Pg&amp;E utility not climate change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just an old hippie, but Easy Rider is one of my favorites. Telling today's tales yesterday.  "Don't bogart that… https://t.co/k21Acmnob6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiger_Fan_4Life @Super_Shooter35 He also named why the teams they were on were sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Autumn_sydlik11 With the home run!  Sounds familiar!!!! Keep hitting bombs sweetheart! Totally proud of you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a lot of truth to this. Sometimes our actions and/or words end up defining us in ways that subvert other go… https://t.co/h6cCGnvcEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[this should be the least of your worries, go do your job and help out Flint weirdo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTWillingham Not exactly answering your question, but I think as educators we often massively underestimate the le… https://t.co/3hOUvA4bYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol did Naver pay JYP to have a laggy YouTube stream so everyone goes to stream on V Live? 😂 3rd time its broken already...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nomisunflower I have some percussion playing in my past (London) life...school and uni...and after that, timpani i… https://t.co/AAgxWfHPqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When there's a #danceoff for the #boquettoss @ Vulcan Park and Museum https://t.co/ltpViWAvyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristemoFans Y por último, el día del final de la novela estaremos a la par con los oscares, si queremos ser tende… https://t.co/guYcofkFsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callowGuru Yeah it kinda felt like a big snow hallway with environmental verticality and some open areas, and that was really it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennisjromero @GustavoArellano Here’s the edited VIDEO of that debate with yours truly, et. al. https://t.co/yBBfDLYmyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all my friends running @amandasablak E Murry Todd half today. Great running in the chilly rain and wind… https://t.co/NI8FVY3hJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcantoni @martin_canabal Es verdad y como AntelGO, pero no es lo mismo. La experiencia de agarrar las cosas e irte es Impresionante]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a novel idea??? Build a pipeline. @TransMtn #bcpoli @bcndp @bcliberals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crusty ass dudes at the rec: “you guys need one more?”  No one:   *somehow crusty dude ends up on your team eventua… https://t.co/c4mEmYqhf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally saw #FightingWithMyFamily and got such a rush at the end when @RealPaigeWWE’s music hit and it brought ba… https://t.co/QTWzpA88rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch James Comey knew he was in bind because of his decision to appear on national television. If FBI was… https://t.co/dcagvOWH0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaWennerstr1 @JuddApatow @NormOrnstein @FoxNews Frightening and so predictable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bkjones718 @1stRoundChiefer Lol they literally used the worse settings and took a awful picture intentionally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabiSeal @RazerCallahan @Krichy5 @undisputed @Chris_Broussard You guys are both wrong. It Steph that's been blowin… https://t.co/tdRTWSxNnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddyFinnerty @g68_charlie @GiantsTBR @sooobad6 @Patricia_Traina @Giants2019 So you don't want to draft a QB? You w… https://t.co/ACbx4rVFdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s because nobody has finger banged in a trans am while “To Russell, My Brother” was cranked on the stere… https://t.co/7UkSphKFMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSmithSabino @sabino_StuCo Thanks Ms Smith for the tweet n for stopping by to get your sports car washed. It was… https://t.co/VJT3MCXiYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from Augusta, Georgia! Speaking for the Richmond County School System 3 times today! Ready to get home… https://t.co/jTuipS7YbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a purpose it’s essential in life. . It will give you passion to wake up every morning and go to work. . It w… https://t.co/oFr5dFvQck]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Dear Melancholy is honestly up there with Kiss Land &amp; the Trilogy, not past them but undoubtably Abel’s best work since that era 🚫🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo my Lyft driver's dash says low fuel &amp; we got a solid 25 min left 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LWB21 discussing the revenue generation of the @PGATOUR on social at #sportsforum19 https://t.co/ITYBrmW3gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWESuperCard Can’t pick which ONE superstar deserves the event lol there’s banks and bayley or Kofi or NXT invasio… https://t.co/zSXyGA4Zkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chewythewookie1 @mog7546 Sad thing is that I don’t think you can except academy award while you’re in prison right Ivanka?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGrossmann @kkondik A John James Senate race is probably a tossup while Presidency tilt D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Nope, but I am stocking up on popcorn to enjoy during the festivities,]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an entertaining fight it goes to a #UD #andstill #PBConFOX https://t.co/xsnXSoUVGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needed a computer simulator ? This is where I learned to drive. Even the windshield wipers worked. Playmobile.… https://t.co/SMAmSujzSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@just_zeke I know I was saying it last night a lot for no reason and keyri said you used to say it a lot out of nowhere lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the 1st qtr: Loyola 16, Pasadena 5. L: C.J. Jones 8pts. Cubs go on 16-1 run to end the qtr. @SGVNSports… https://t.co/QiSGV5GeWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherrySherrmorr @SawaLynn I got off soda pop by drinking kombucha. It’s not for everyone, but it worked for me. Bu… https://t.co/p9iI2S7IYm]]></document></documents></author>