<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My little guy and his big personality make my heart smile 😍❤  #DogMom #Sampson #SleepySamSpam #WhoRescuedWho… https://t.co/sY2Ui04p6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@books_gay @rmnetwork @family_equality Love the tag! Please be so kind as to add my book (How we sleep at night. A… https://t.co/GasixkFllj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDijkema chairs panel at @cardusca luncheon on challenges to Ont construction industry. Big issues are skills… https://t.co/AB5632K5BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the etiquette for adding work people on LinkedIn?? Like this guy from a different department that I’ve never… https://t.co/IyaURpqWZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBlumenthal @GrayzoneProject @billmaher I meant to say Koran:  it is motive and respects previous prophets.  Mot… https://t.co/dUiPuh4YXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re thinking about watching a movie without earbuds in the airport...please think again 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[On route to Orlando for @podfestexpo! Looking forward to seeing lots of #podpals and making new ones. You can find… https://t.co/tU1TE4rVzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenbholmes I have mixed feelings about this article. On one hand, I def still receive help from my mom that I’m… https://t.co/aKeh2aMEXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I stayed fit today  🌟Do 1 Feng Shui Consultation  🌟and 🌟 🌟 Teach A 5 Element Archetype Class! . . 🌟 Exercise Mi… https://t.co/Y6eYPECZe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer wya?? Just bought a bunch of swimsuits today and am ready to show them off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjaylonn @micaiahalexis Yes I did that’s the problem I waited too long 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[leave every woman alone born after like 1990 right now because we’re all just realizing that we’re older than like… https://t.co/ew6QMbAt1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers - Sucker https://t.co/4bBigYDNuk via @YouTube @Reneejae1]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@marcorubio: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greeneggsHAMDUR ok I had a crush on both but when hsm3 came out I was 5 and young troy was 10 so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lelo1989 @Reality71584702 @MichaelEFiedler @ksarm07 @CarpeDonktum Go for it!! WWII  still embarrassing, we underst… https://t.co/JA5AE3UTKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_hughes_nj @RutgersMBB @rutgersalumni @RutgersU Always! https://t.co/3aqeIHX3Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up @CBS4Local #Noon:   🚨I-10 is back open after a fatal traffic incident  🏫 @PortiaKFOX_CBS is live at the E… https://t.co/1VbB8c9bIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not usually been in a place, as a #scientist, to stand up to potentially invasive uses of genomic informatio… https://t.co/w1fZPR8w52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar Yes, it was an awesome review! I am so glad you love Elf! I have been telling ppl for years that Elf w… https://t.co/zSjUChwsEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A woman does not need more WILLPOWER; She needs more PLEASURE @susanhyatt #letsgetbare https://t.co/YMD765lkkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY IS MY BEST FRIENDS BIRTHDAY!!! From the moment I met you we instantly became family. you are my role model, p… https://t.co/zbzroDXGJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DriemeyerPE @MDC_online @CoachBrune Oh boy!!! That beard! Such great people in this pic😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@directtv I have used my last recourse.  All I want is a solution for my [arents and for all of your other cutomers… https://t.co/tKWdu18e6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @MaryAReed So the incels love him, ok I guess but is that really a 'win'?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished my season 2 binge now for season 3!!!! #WorldofDance https://t.co/fARMkfnS5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT @securityblvd  450,000 usernames and passwords stolen from Coinmama cryptocurrency broker… https://t.co/PKPaVrn99j]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going to glow up for the sole purpose of getting on the bachelor, making it to an international travel week, an… https://t.co/inJpyrUUsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss they're not going away...I know people here in rural OH that are willing to take to the streets w their… https://t.co/pY0CaJuWwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bourbon Street, French District https://t.co/jI0XnPIz8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreationEnt @TahmohPenikett @RealAdamRose @ChristianKeyes Awesome the original Michael!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time i look at your picture, i smile uncontrollably and miss you like crazy. come back..please]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will have to lose sight of shore and get familiar with the dark. No one can head out on that path in the dark b… https://t.co/56GeAraRX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWBDimash #WorldsBest @dimash_official  @WorldsBestCBS...I am one of thous who never had favorite singer...40 year… https://t.co/4xMMA8zNPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom UR t/most disgusting POS2 take office,U must realize UR expected to rpsrsnt all CA’s, Ur far lft BS wi… https://t.co/OckXGPKEQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior pictures  Book your session today! https://t.co/JIzuN1lp2V https://t.co/1MAYLGGCg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItsNotARoadTripWithout my kids arguing- #HappeningNow #roadTrip https://t.co/Pla48zhtjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinaRicardo1 @FreddyMulongo @afriqueredac @AfricaTopTweet @akhendumonde1 @tresinsolent @luchaRDC @kinshasaweb… https://t.co/xhMhskzVBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GallagherWitt Lori, do you know who’s doing the audio narration and if we can preorder that too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProblemPanacea @IngrahamAngle @CPAC @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump @mschlapp Not sure about that... I would not call… https://t.co/eknbUozRvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right kind of sunglasses and she can conquer the world. The aviators I’m wearing is from wearme_pro… https://t.co/ibNyjBwR3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fled the building because I was worried for my safety. my coworkers—my FAMILY—have been injured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El amor puede esperar, pero una cerveza no, porque después se calienta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See what happens when Lt. Kennedy gets the night off?? #dadgummit #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am seriously and literally waiting for people in my house to go to sleep so I can go down stairs to sit in the li… https://t.co/bHiO4DONcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma survive cauusee Aubrey Plaza is my birthday twin and she has better survival chances than Ariana sns]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT @PinkEverythiing lilmamaweon @therealoggrip @sotafats lowkey_empire92 leo_sun87 @ Belle Âme Lounge https://t.co/AoaMxM4uot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Truth_II @yensid98 @HaMaMolNij He dangled a child out a balcony!!! #LeavingNeverland https://t.co/S1UOO3ldbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdgeRatedR 😂 @trishstratuscom 😂 @StephMcMahon 😂 https://t.co/564SMyZB2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitorsit no, sour cream. it definitely sounds weird, but it’s pretty good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when you guys turn someone’s pain into your entertainment as if you should have an opinion on it. In Other n… https://t.co/9WTbPLClkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza He calls it as he sees it! I trust my own eyes too. Don’t buy your continued support of the BigOrange… https://t.co/FP9lAmYbO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time with girlfriends from high school!!  No one knows you better!!!!! #girlfriends #girltime… https://t.co/uNu39wRk3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already did my workout this morning and tbh putting the fitted sheet on my queen size bed is a second workout I a… https://t.co/7LukkoP7BM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This body roll I just yasss @iamcardib &amp; @BrunoMars Body roll session nowwww https://t.co/uzThmrWYnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times skating on Mirror Lake. @ Mirror Lake Public Beach https://t.co/2bhFytC9OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I’ll have to leave this town but the memories will last forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay!!!  Thank you to everyone who donated a heart from their heart to the Kindness Tree during the month of Februar… https://t.co/tzVXlppt4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/pTaoWcpb61]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Europe's best and worst capitals to buy your first home 🏡  https://t.co/BDtTRxz2Q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just looked in a mirror and now fully am understanding the “red eye”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_wolfpack Thank you so much!!! We loved having the football boys there to support!! Definitely a game changer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylezpromo @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles that look of his makes me want t… https://t.co/u5GLUA8g5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC I’m sure Mitch is just looking for a stamp to mail his letter of concern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m moving to Texas in May &amp; im thinking it’s the best decision ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDunbarJ You know it! FYI. Stephen, he approved me. Sorry about the tie quip. 👔😎✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stateofsate ist full on powerhouse rock'n'roll with her voice and entire presence on stage @horseshoetavern Feb 15… https://t.co/HduQGbKcZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being a world class athlete and finding Beyoncé THAT inspirational 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You forgot daddy's picture for the most corrupt, lazy, dishonest, low IQ, fake prez. https://t.co/yE6oG47qLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my Dad I was gonna apply to be on The Bachelor and he said if I made it as far as hometowns that would be it… https://t.co/7jpQo8PnWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wavedancer43 @CNNSitRoom @JeffreyToobin There was plenty of out rage about judge Cavanagh is just that the committ… https://t.co/3hD8eaRIc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez’s campaign may have illegally paid her boyfriend: complaint: https://t.co/M12NxboGkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilbrowneskimo Legit courage! I’m going to try and get confidence for a crop top! I be me inspiration 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hey_raven   You are a kind-hearted soul that will always make things about others. You do know, however, how to bu… https://t.co/dRtE7Xb6rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[No soy la única que se lleva un vaso/ botella de agua al cuarto para antes de dormirse no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Northshore_Dave @YAppelbaum because if he lies once more he faces life in person, he has incentive to tell the truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/sPj4YgEj3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[With our trauma team teaching 200 Worthington School District staff members and students how to @StopTheBleed. Stor… https://t.co/4eqbE09Zxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought the same thing! Otherwise, the ‘investigation ‘ would have went on &amp; on !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comfort is not a goal that I seek, it's a place I hide Taken with a Sony a7rii https://t.co/R7SUrBBUSa @Converse… https://t.co/UzaybcwxUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImaOutasorts @kazweida Oh, they know that. But attacking Cohen is all they've got. There's an old saying: if your… https://t.co/gIPwKN4B3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamsG4 I guess?? Everyone I know who is flying SW was cancelled. I flew in on a tiny airline so my flight was fine… https://t.co/MOjnPGfGXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if he knows he talks out of his ass or if he’s just happily oblivious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPgoeagles @cmheatley Just admit Collin made a bad take!! Don’t defend him ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so much love for @HigherHeights, the work they do, and the ladies who lead it 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hyped today up in my head so much and then it totally did not live up to it 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ForecasterEnten “Shit” &amp; “Stink,” two of a kind! @BarackObama @JoeBiden]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy sweet 16th birthday to my forever lover💛💛hope today is the best one yet because you deserve it,, love love lo… https://t.co/ezlI49FDdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Buenos días! ☀️no saben que feliz despertar con estas noticias!. Recuerdo muy bien que para mí era un sueño trabaj… https://t.co/z4kSNEGKHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baking in the oven; preparing Sunday brunch on Saturday night. #SheCooks #SheRaps #SheMentors #SheReaches #SheSlay… https://t.co/OqdzbtGKMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrboycom_jr @hostler1 @paige_donner @WhiteHouse Exactly!!! I DISAGREE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom’s weekend is off to a great start❣️ #moretocome @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/AtjUdTiB25]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl in my philosophy class pissed me off because she was trying to argue with me but her arguement was so invalid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indivisibleden @MomsDemand I hope you get a huge crowd! This is a very important issue! #GunControl #COGunControl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay Much love and support!!! Together we can and will continue to achieve great things! T… https://t.co/blR1EK2Pwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CANT FIND MY WIRED HEADPHONES AND IM GONNA SCREAM.   I CANT USE MY AIRPODS RN SO I NEED TO FOND MY WIRED ONES UGHHHHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to admit that they do make a good looking couple. ❤️✅💯#myboy #KingJames https://t.co/qQkk9KXX2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VH1 Kim definitely  sounds bitter,  when someone calls you a goody two shoes. That was childish af. Most of what I… https://t.co/PCFI7lfglO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad also when you see the same type of reviews from current and former employees of any given company. That me… https://t.co/TgdlTq9BOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me? We can’t call it the Disabled List? Get over it! Calling it the DL doesn’t make people insensitive. #MLB]]></document></documents></author>