<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Are You Ready Steve? by @SingleCutBeer at @tjsbeer — https://t.co/vhtwLJl9J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Mario one of the coldest producer/managers in the game #hiphopfinest #entertainment @ Georgia https://t.co/mQMbWZ8sAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué estrecho se ve el criterio de @lopezobrador_ y evidenciada su retrógrada visión de nación ante la claridad de a… https://t.co/UntVmopkdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I buy a ton of (healthy!) groceries as IF my anxiety isn’t so bad that I never actually eat. A girl can try tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AylaForTrump @Kfuller8870 I carried a gun 17 yrs before I used it to save my life.  I carry because I refuse to be… https://t.co/88ldCwUMDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaaizzy @ladygaga Like Bradley Cooper  and his singing. To just get up and sing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another chance to race today!  Country Day comes in for a 10am Meet!  Let’s race hard boys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That how much freezing rain feel. Thankfully, we had none but it's a dangerous situation out in PA and N NJ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE @RondaRousey may have owned you but it's just the beginning of redemption and retaliation!-)+ @MsCharlotteWWE @MLStadium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You fail. The electoral college is not the people. Your opponent won that, but here you are destro… https://t.co/A9Sw8Y1JjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_CHED I grew up listening to Bryan Hall and Rod Phillips doing PBP for yrs, and later Al Costes on the 80s and… https://t.co/cxf1RvN5Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachRusstough So playoffs will start either Thursday or Friday and it won’t come out till tomorrow so you have to… https://t.co/tq0hPsz9MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comicsreporter There are dozens of us! Dozens! https://t.co/IZqZ03YeKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it's bad when your best argument against Michael Cohen coming clean on Trump, is that he once lied to Cong… https://t.co/03OBNcMOvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of fouls that aren’t called when Harper drives to the rim is laughable. He gets hit with a body so many… https://t.co/WgM5aanEiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to buy something from three different national big box stores that I needed right away. Each of them, on Satu… https://t.co/wsEHvm0NE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlrowanrmt like it, no one says cars need all the roads...   think of all the people leisurely hanging out, supporting those downtown shops]]></document><document><![CDATA[A visit to Factory 77 and the hopes artists had for it 40 years ago | CBC Archives https://t.co/kPsV0yo4nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemillwood @GottaLaff It's because he prefers someone who thinks and acts like he does - a staunch "conservative".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Poppapopejr Yes sir I've been tweeting for months that Mueller is hoodwinking everybody. They forget he still a Re… https://t.co/7MLhCdHz93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmoncureW "He wears his sunglasses at night, so he can, so he can....." #SpaceApeCinema]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen Lillyhammer - Soprano’s #2 goes into witness protection in Norway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisFajardoHN Lo que resta de la temporada solo es para quedar dentro de la próxima Champions y tal ves (cosa que… https://t.co/Pl436g5aPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Because even in "not knowing" he still has a hell of a lot more insight than you do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillBeverlyhill Dinner conversation.                                   Trump: How do you eat all that?… https://t.co/5nXLCZsZ83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbgarcia96 @chrisontour @CoachBeardTTU @davide25moretti @jarrettc08 @MoonSwag13 @TexasTechLenz @taylorlenzmeier https://t.co/T3L18ZOJp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online @Heterocatalytic Thunderbirds was indeed a COOL TV show in the 60's https://t.co/boqYdhB99y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SCCL2019 update. @santos_laguna_ already destroying @cdmarathonoffic 3-0. A Hat Trick by Javier Correa. All away goals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Houston: clear sky, 73°F 78% humidity, wind 9mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaWatson @RapeCrisisEandW @EVAWuk @emmacharlotte I'm sitting in here as if this is like some kind of office with… https://t.co/JQkxoQEA2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[This trading post is haunted as fuck. #boardgamesofinstagram #greatwesterntrail @ Mage's Sanctum https://t.co/mWedFOrdrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kritter1963 @Jenn198523 This is what a liberal moron looks like! She’ll make a good replacement for Pelosi. Neithe… https://t.co/n6AyUV9EUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been feeling a lot more attractive lately so sorry for all the pictures LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annie_dow I was jamming out to "my life would suck" too in my car. I got you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 24 advance: 4,9,17,21,37,2,22,18,3,12,8,24,47,6,10,1,19,20,88,13,48,11,43,32 #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamShatner Johnm you need to get a life. It's not funny, no one is impressed. Go back to eating crayons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucidSpin @mPinoe @CarliLloyd @alexmorgan13 @ussoccer Says more about the failure of leadership at US Soccer than anything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS AND GIRLS ACROSS THE WORLD PUTTING ON OUR DANCING SHOES~~ going to the disco TECH getting HIGH &amp; ~ getting WRECKED!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any other fans who don’t mind saying that she enabled him? She saw his addictions first hand and did noth… https://t.co/mCjH9Ow8Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this out of admiration: @JoeDeCamara and @RitchieJon  have the weirdest show in Philly sports talk (mostly be… https://t.co/u8C5ed3w6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a pic of an ex girlfriend (20yrs ago) KH. Was her #mugshot wtf/holy shite! She’s 11yrs younger than I am,… https://t.co/JgGwTiOsnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zarrashley She shouldn’t have said anything about 21. Everyone knows niggas stan 21 and Future]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like there’s now not just gonna be 1 but 2 future football stars! Congratulations coach!!! @jtheaps9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkGreen @steph93065 It will never see the floor of the Senate @senatemajldr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleymlindsay @sierxpxctwx As a Taurus I thank you for standing up for us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkbjournalist sure, but how about calling him in front of the oversight committee 1st]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lydonofficial good for you and what you said on @TMZ  also you can always come talk to me. #goesbothways. ✌️✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Explosive dunk for Beal, who has 34. #Hornets lead Wizards by 9 entering 4Q. Have to close games out like this agai… https://t.co/Z05hxAbnJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately this touches on the subject of free speech. The problem is not that they want to show their support f… https://t.co/3V6g4TRoGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jakkeeeup @Large_Professor That would be illegal with all 3 of those dudes😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHAPE_America @PEPEPTalk #WhatMadeYourWeek I no longer teach kids, I teach teachers which I love, but I miss havin… https://t.co/1htt8MxZYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FisherJillian @LVPhantoms #MyFirstHockeyMemory was going to see the Wings play St Louis at Olympia. The team stunk… https://t.co/aoGrsZvN9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo I leave for Colorado tomorrow for a week and I still haven’t packed 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT @trailblazers are officially doomed now! Charles is like 0-forever n picking the championship winner]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the guys who stand up the second the plane lands and start grabbing their stuff from the overheads.   Congra… https://t.co/1fsAtVzS2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god I stayed up til late hours in the night planning my entire wedding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PonchoDeNigris Toda la vida me ha pasado 😎, quedamos pocos guapos de antes ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caribtaste Asking for a friend: Can you recommend sources of #Bajan food in #Westchester?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was hot boxing last night with some friends tell me why homeboy left his phone in the car 😂 realizing it when I got home lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother is the type of person that will head you a dead PlayStation controller and says, “I’m done. You can play.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump A CapitaList iS a DefiLed PersOn During Private Enterprise Like The… https://t.co/elFMb2BTYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visualize, focus, execute. #goals #adventurous #fireman #hellsbel #belEboo @ St Mary Church https://t.co/J0ke2oRpGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Ever Skull Fragments of Denisovans Have Been Confirmed Found in Russia https://t.co/vcxD4ziWkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glimpses of the Fremont spectacle including the largest nugget of gold in the world #dasvegas2019 @ Fremont Street… https://t.co/uip5kNr1yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrozenSicleGirl It was your ghost I never even saw what you were talking about]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday a close friend of mine told me he noticed i dont like to ask for help. After I told him what i was dealin… https://t.co/iaTBxmMTaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmcculloch Hey Dan,  I don't know if you will read this but but the teaser trailer for His Dark Materials looks… https://t.co/DuTJDPNigg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less optimism about Brent price upside week ending March 1. Net long positions decreased -4 mmb wk ending vs +16 wk… https://t.co/fXncReEIsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing 🧐 MF take my money and give me that 💯 fuckinf teachers don’t get bribed]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a phrase in Europe shared with me by a good friend from Europe: “If you’re under 30 and don’t love socialis… https://t.co/ZlkIkHaObl]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the Thunderbirds vs Portland Winterhawks game at 6pm, comes the All Star Game featuring local celebrities and… https://t.co/svxDF0fqsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC What Trump means is: You screw up big time Robert, next time call me and I give you Stormy Daniels phone number.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am interested in how the threat entered their system and how the 350+ clients are dealing with not being able to… https://t.co/2n0CPuZmaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat As good as it sounds... Ima have to pass on this one 😂😂 https://t.co/cIlUpMrWPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a long winter with some of the coldest days yet to come. @Asgrow_DEKALB what’s a guy gotta do to get a ho… https://t.co/SLR9y57FeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanna_nicole6 Thats why i just unfollowed alot thiss mark ass triccs 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trash you're trash, then why tweet about it you should've kept it to yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saveleithwalk @EdinburghUni @GroupDrum @lewisritchieIND @adamrmcvey @leithdepot @leithcentralcc @susan4leithwalk… https://t.co/NwuynenIPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@dereckapurnell!! Why Does Obama Scold Black Boys? https://t.co/xRpzACqFcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtyD_DamnIt Growth is beautiful bruh. Nothing but love and more to come fam!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A darle átomos! (@ Deportivo Las Fuentes in NL) https://t.co/tjG9sHQcx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMichEric Right, they need to hide who they actually are because when they reveal themselves to be socialists, it… https://t.co/aZ22yrqu3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods When is he going to go after his good friend Ed Buck? Now there’s an investigation worth pursuing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall really be bugging. People don’t have to call and check up on you everyday for them to care for you https://t.co/maxfzXuYeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is dope @igotgame_12 is nuts if @RacersHoops wins tonight i'm definitely going to the championship tomorrow ni… https://t.co/UjRVCVgr6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I guess if it wasn't clear before today (it was), the GOP is a party of unapologetic fascists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL  If I can help you in any Way, Shape, or Form, Please don't Hesitate to call! I'm so sorry for You… https://t.co/nonfqunMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want people to like me instead of worrying about my own personal happiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAGirlsmom @we_r_Psymese @machalo0712 @806_sharon @ColbaltGooGal @Seahawksgal81 @naughty1loveb @MissHannahMelia… https://t.co/GCijolAUUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When DC becomes a state, this will be come the constitutionally mandated Federal District! #DCStatehood #FreeDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[New start time &amp; on air time for me down here in Thibodaux today. Talk to you guys soon... #BearClawsUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blessedmom07 @kelsea_lately @LongMasterWolf @thegingaminga That is a GREAT idea Marie 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjammingh When I was working at @McDonalds 23 years ago. Before starting my professional career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3760 Wilshire Blvd 3760 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90010 https://t.co/vjwIek3hfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#afirmación #afirmacionpositiva #afirmaciondeldia @ Doral, Florida https://t.co/m5xukzILyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year was great. This year is going to be greatest. The best ahead will be the a mire greater.  Ready for whats… https://t.co/zBMK8NCwYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Edurodriguezg Yo aquí en Orlando florida, saludos cordiales Eduardo... Díos te bendiga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snellzilla4 If I came to practice sometime this week would you sign my Stone crab bobble head of you? I am blind s… https://t.co/cl51kULa1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ I wanted all the clueless white speakers at the 2016 Repub Convention in Cleveland to make the same spee… https://t.co/zXqfkp6V9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really, is that what you think, or did someone tell you that. I was told you don’t read or think.]]></document></documents></author>