<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@maria_vllreal Right!!! us bank 😭🙄 tf i should just stick to my credit union one but it’s hard cause they ain’t got schools first in Sf 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE @faboamanto Baby Pandas in translation. I wonder what they are talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XDmaddieXD @MizarP I use twitter for my entertainment, y’all on twitter... so... entertain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing one of our SJJ #MenForOthers alumnus making his mark on the world! Keep it up @hkballislife !]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it mean if I have a re-accruing #nightmare where I’m on a plane to #Australia and I forget my headphones… https://t.co/dVjCnTiwhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second good article I’ve read this AM: “Planning Your Class to Take Advantage of Highly Effective Learning Tech… https://t.co/EnOerqyWnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustedUser @jmc4now @RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump Right. You are an authority on enlightenment, because QAnon is real. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cirincione @helenecooper I would love to see @helenecooper question the previous speaker. Boilerplate platitudes would not fly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @VP Maybe he didn't want too answer questions to the fake news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithton_m @BigBrotherGOD1 Was Guzman a pediophile? Are there any healthy men around. Inappropriate touching, Rape....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rae_schon @skolanach @realDonaldTrump You are right. Except that he wasn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't get this out there enough... @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews #Propaganda #MillionaireFundedByBillionaires]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinefiend @amnestyusa Lol, easy answer: I don't.   Maybe look into some remedial reading comprehension classes… https://t.co/uC0gHU7Fwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me something, we have U.S. Coast Guard lieutenant going up for domestic terrorism, @CBSThisMorning but y’all h… https://t.co/wmztZ2Q1Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sociald1 thank you for this song - awesome 🙌❤️🎤🎶🥃♥️😘 @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/i5Nncimm7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @opinion_joe until freak injury or common injury benches the dreams. can't play pro. then what do they have?… https://t.co/aJNQ16722R]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a YouTube for adults and YouTube for kids. She legit showed up on some piggy show at 3:14 and told kids SE… https://t.co/ahh5Fpybrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyLeeBrewin @MayaArgano Emma just asked me if I knew what Momo was and I said no. She was also scared to walk up… https://t.co/IyrWnnaCsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6 of the #BookCoverChallenge to post covers of 7 books I love...no explanation and no review. Each time I post… https://t.co/0jVtxWiGbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m sad, frustrated, and disappointed” says @KamalaHarris about @JussieSmollett arrest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come , sit and tell me your problems that you’ve made for the 100th time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, we buy #recordcollection Contact us #melodysupreme #recordstore #records #charlottesville… https://t.co/IBn9ZnsDPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d pay for the rest of my college career, put some to the side for my sister and brother to pursue college or thei… https://t.co/WDk5MIOcWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_WildWestFest @WilliamCGreen @FlatlandCavalry @kodywest_ @rylie_12 @__paigen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems: air pollution is unhealthy and can make breathing the air dangerous  Republicans: you say air pollution is ba… https://t.co/GJneGJgAOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[KOFI KINGSTON VS DANIEL BRYAN AT #WrestleMania FOR THE #WWETITLE NEEDS TO HAPPEN, @VinceMcMahon LISTEN TO THE FANS… https://t.co/SkqHOh9Zyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeMason Should we start a conversation about the connotation of “white collar crime” versus, say, a drug sale charge?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideRaptor i just came out to have a GOOD TIME &amp; i’m honestly feeling SO ATTACKED right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS You have absolutely nothing to do with Spacex. Please shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues yo ni eh hecho nada que esté mal, ni eh dicho mentiras para ser la mala de la historia. Hay que tambien tener… https://t.co/8c6NpUGHuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 Trump is not for America. He is killing us. Trump stands for everything we are not. What a loser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been aggressively cutting my plastic, carrying my own utensils + straws + glass packages to restaurants and gr… https://t.co/a3mpNoxQ48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@windsergarden95 @FartyCheddarCat NYC has white, black, brown and grey squirrels. So does Washington,D.C. And there… https://t.co/4W4NVE0RdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was soooooo close to getting tickets to go see my boo bad bunny.... and then i realize I’ll be in Vegas that week… https://t.co/DXSgP9UrEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[we saw a room Abraham Lincoln once ate lunch in as well as the graves of James Monroe and John Tyler! i even found… https://t.co/exazijK1xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have Metallica tickets for sale for March 6th in Kansas City! Let me know if your interested!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danibogoricin omg ILSYM ps i had pizza and french fries and shrimp and clams and chocolate mousse and it’s not eve… https://t.co/5WAkT7RDU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AttyLeBlanc @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Did you mean despicable? I am very happy he has been disposed of now, b… https://t.co/frSJcXfhgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thAnon Ok, read this.....???  Reality disguised as sci-fi fantasy tale of people from other planets?  Hmmm...much… https://t.co/OXgCCh1Wyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FelizViernes  Señora Presidenta Usted puede con eso y mas #GómezPalacioVa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for a fresh voice with truth and integrity of fellow humen. Tormenting Meghan Markle has become a nationa… https://t.co/n4bly6i2Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I paid more in taxes than any billionaire in this country. #stealfromthepoor #givetotherich]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve tried every acne treatment on the fucking planet, cut dairy out of my diet, everything but nothing is helping.… https://t.co/Nxc8OZ7Twq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MichelMeditates for your #Spiritual #Media #APP that bridges #neuroscience #spirituality #psychology!  M… https://t.co/knaRGECOvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @CitizenKayS The history books will record this time in the American meltdown. The fall of a great nation, directed by Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, this last year has been challenging. I lost a business i was so passionate about and put my entire saving… https://t.co/Kq1NRtVszi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland She threatened his kid with her phone.  He threatened her with his fist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigsexydraws I enjoyed most of her earlier work,a lot of people don’t fuck with her work lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW: Michael Cohen testifies before House Oversight Committee  https://t.co/xXWrXvqIPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Black_C_Patriot @realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff Love your YouTube channel!!Awesome job!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marildasantana2 Hi Marilda. Thank you and happy Sunday to you as well.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Also, just like the engagement ring debate you had, it shows that he put thought and planning into the decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just come to the conclusion between my job and trying to have a social life I’m going to sick every week ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being sick made me nap so much all day today that now I’m not even the slightest bit tired 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad there is an episode addressing this. Just...thank you. @melissafumero @iamstephbeatz @nbcbrooklyn99 ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottRRocco A1. Social media dos and don’ts should be a prelude to any lesson/any grade. Provide Ss with constant… https://t.co/UR3A6uIhwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day at the Beverly Hills Dog Show, to air Easter Sunday, April 21on NBC ... Interviews and more closer to the… https://t.co/1JIY2w0vHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylamcneil_ mo like tattoo fever with conservative christian parents🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Our Leadership meets each Wednesday afternoon to review coaching cycles progress, review needs of teachers for… https://t.co/tIGLCZPkde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all get them get on Eventbrite for the Pre-Sale Tickets to events for Miami Spring Break. Tickets only $7-$15 right now #MiamiSpringBreak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strom_annette @Barb81146 @ChrisToTheW @pleasure74 @esadah @Momof2in1year @CunningSq16 @MisleaderC @GrandmaVeteran… https://t.co/AtU2LnZI57]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the ❤️ on this kid! @FRApanthers @FRAHEADofMS @FRAmsDavis @FRAKentC  #FRAinterim2019 https://t.co/dFIn0O9CWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite what it looks like, my brother was not falling into the Grand Canyon while we took this picture. Everyone m… https://t.co/FnjGaQBfxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Day.... #prettyinpinkphotography #clouds #sunset #sunsets #beautifuldrive @ Greenville, North Carolina https://t.co/okB2pLPVKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary mayor promises balanced budget for city by 2021 https://t.co/tJugnR0zkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not a feeling I need in my life, And I'm ready to say goodbye to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katina  12:30 show  #seaworldorlando #orca #killerwhale #shamu #oneocean #katina @ SeaWorld Orlando https://t.co/YkX3dD8YNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG.  These two HAWT guys together.  What an amazingly powerful image!  @#eddiecanhalen #repost #regrann #evh… https://t.co/sypvHBbcCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[1995  mint condition Rolex submariner box and papers .… https://t.co/w5HfCw6hVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And at last....it begins....karma has come knocking on Trump's door.  You're going down President Bone Spurs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coffee cup is super full this am. It may not be enough. #ineedanap https://t.co/puqHgRAZTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious when Jade figured out that @LookAtDustin was their first male guest and The Price is Right theme hit 🤣🤣🤣💯… https://t.co/TI2U9ZQ84n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicf02 Same here. I commit so much time to something that continuously fucked me over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is dreary outside but #flowers make me happy #readyforspring @ Pittsfield, Michigan https://t.co/UUKu5dqiAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah let it have been his daughter, sister or niece. Fucking white priveleged mutherfuckers like @smerconish are th… https://t.co/LinPq0mx0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Mayer - I Guess I Just Feel Like (Lyric Video) https://t.co/CFSuFMux0U via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@echochlo Miss u come back to Austin with more than an hour’s notice this time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The data is in. Frogs don’t boil. But we might. https://t.co/hWOIvu0Pli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @HoffmanKatja Under what rocks do they find these pieces of feces?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The boot was developed during the Korean War to combat the extreme cold weather soldiers and Marines f… https://t.co/TC8rqevEwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts on @AOC at #SXSW—She was great, eloquent and passionate as always, but the interviewer was VERY weak. Wish… https://t.co/V7JjIbFXY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavenEyz I had a near death experience in 2004. I wondered for a long time why I came back. Last month I found out… https://t.co/6Mb1eQP9vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellelovestea @supermommyto5 The fact that his mother is involved is concerning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MY_BORDERCOLLIE @RealityTVBliss @Andy Yep! I thought she was behind it all along. I didn't come out and say it til… https://t.co/1L0yMkaZMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelinaVader I agree, one of my favorite villains hands down. (My Favorite is Jack Torrance)   Funny we’re talking… https://t.co/FewH8RF47N]]></document><document><![CDATA[They ain’t fixing the gym lol our school is little to nothing in the USA when it comes to sports, they’ll fix the m… https://t.co/fNgxFP43s5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santanabbyyy Okay! Let me ask my job if I can switch days and I’ll let you know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian and I haven’t moved from the couch all day thanks to Netflix’s Dating Around https://t.co/MKHrdkWukh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annaclairerusso @ssence1 Tried this with my cat... it’s not the same 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep talking about this issue. Babies are being killed every day. #babymurders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllerySamwise It’ll only hurt for a..........second. https://t.co/hSekJM1qgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samaria shall become desolate; for she hath rebelled against her God: they shall fall by the sword: their infants s… https://t.co/WSqtpR7R9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[i has floor seats last night for @PanicAtTheDisco and truly i was waiting for this moment to see @brendonurie up cl… https://t.co/7aGf3X7ik6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clanghoff1 @dunneteach While Christine isn't wrong, my bet is they're looking at their FY20 report (due 3/1 off 2/15 data).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you still call the rabbit hole (fb/twitter videos) #writersblock? #amwriting #writingcommmunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reconforta ver la empatía de Fabiana... Supongo que también se preocupará e irá a ver a los familiares de  las vict… https://t.co/2Ql87Lhz1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fastlane_17 @RandallKingBand @opry Oh you mean the Ryman, not technically an Opry broadcast but I get ya now. I'm… https://t.co/MSAMqAX1vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see cohens going to jail has been delayed til may...have always felt cohen is the one most likely to tell the truth re this pos]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s fair to say 10 man United side cos Rashford is obviously not in this game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Redrawing a pic of my son from 2014 #wip #mspaint https://t.co/RuR8XSHQzu]]></document></documents></author>