<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[They imprison @JussieSmollett for allegedly lying about the hate crime YET the bitch who admitted she lied about Em… https://t.co/nnCdDlqqLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist This isn’t the only stuff he going to be incarcerated for though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como extestigo de Jehová me siento muy identificado y me da mucha pena lo que leo en este reportaje de… https://t.co/Lr6hLw7Hzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mason98100822 @tiucsibaeS Not to mention he drove an early 2000s Lexus GS that he modded using his own money. That… https://t.co/QNVtGA8oph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSTRodB ...drew this All-Pro/All American thinking damnit...could use you for 16+ games. Please hit'em low Denzel. https://t.co/Lj7cXMSRU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can people stop acting like masculinity/gender roles are a good thing. Toxic masculinity/femininity are literally l… https://t.co/1t9wgbwwok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peanut...too cool for school. @knockaround @hyvee #presidentsday @ Hy-Vee https://t.co/jVwBRuO0Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdxalerts The dems don’t know what a protest looks like from the other side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oak Harbor’s Tyler Davis gets pinned in his 113 consolation match to see his year come to a close. Promising future… https://t.co/e5ti4CQVgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We look so nervous in possession. It’s like we don’t think we should have the ball #twitterclarets]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Reporting sexual harassment in the gig economy - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/Bz1hIMry0H @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewmercer I must admit, as one of your Canadian viewers, I'm rather blown away by what's been happening as wel… https://t.co/088JXAjG5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2019 Oscar Predictions: Best Picture: Roma  Director: Alfonso Cuaron    Best Actor: Rami Malek  Best Actress: Gl… https://t.co/wE2CF2OAig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a video of a kid box squatting 500 lbs and BOUNCING HARD off the box. 😧]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the famous line in every one of his movies “it’s in the Blood” Owner Robbie Kroger of Blood Origins made it to… https://t.co/8aNhdvFLrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dennis Family #katytx #cincoranch #Roofing #Replacement #realtor Text ROOF to 474747 for a FREE ROOF… https://t.co/QBt9LDDafB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBoringJustin Hello! Will you be doing the Friday night fiasco tomorrow night? Wife and I want to make the trek a… https://t.co/93iVbJo5EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wave3news @KenUofLHospital And in case you can’t read between the lines, Greg, we don’t back you on this one and d… https://t.co/xFbAuCZrH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucks having to work Saturday and actually having to work 😓, beer:30 wya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggeett37aaa Glen unfortunately, intellectual  Noam Chomsky delineated Kennedy's crimes against humanity while in o… https://t.co/5XIaMbhOhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is this possible every year? I mean, the people of the #Oscars follow the same news sources we do right? They c… https://t.co/V2RGCkYKmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiGiBclub @loveGoldenHeart @TlrWorldWidellc @gigirules7 @TheTwinPowers @SharedMotivati1 @TheLucindaWhite… https://t.co/ZE7RzUL48w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1 year Anniversary to this masterpiece &amp; my AOTY last year #RR2🌹by @rocmarci 💎The prod by Roc, Don Cee,… https://t.co/czXQRyIkTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe02476 @NickKristof @SaudiEmbassyUSA Who are we (western powers ) to tell a sovereign nation how to organize structure their society?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joseluiselbat @rg690 ¿When? 😂 ¿que es la @rg690 ? Y que raro que en la transmision del juego todos dijeron que no… https://t.co/zvPqiHEU3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starwars I love the show but I think Resistance needs to be released all at once so you can binge it.  These tiny… https://t.co/7ub2VpLTtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before I go to sleep I just want twitter to know that all these R. Kelly videos got me sick 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @fawfulfan joe cunningham...tax atty and ocean engineer...very smart...is this mark sanford's old district?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh Squeezed Straw Lemonade #singleorigincoffee #smallbatchroaster #localcoffee #dtphx #serafinacoffeeroasters… https://t.co/CZab7ZdBCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[First rule of songwriting: Listen to your soul.  #remax #song #music #musician #piano #rose #realestate #realtor… https://t.co/iYcUqEZ59r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neckillusions here’s a few of my custom painted guitars it did. https://t.co/2fM4NDvA8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[supported a black owned business this black history month by subscribing to an onlyfans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevestrehl Yeah. I’ll get these twitter generated news headlines in my phones notifications]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuaracuchaFB Aguas desbordadas durante 20 años, inundaron con todo aquello que hoy rechazamos como insoportable, i… https://t.co/cpqL31PD9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosieBarton He’s not a lawyer but he is well rehearsed when he channels George Costanza and prefaces statements (… https://t.co/RpwbAgy2Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiramboyd @ArmchairQBDan @cavs He has played 2 games.  We will see Portland get carved up defensively in the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJMan586 @PokemonGoNews @NianticHelp there should be a choice between 3 places and 3 times to choose from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monterogabriela @DerbyChrisW @ken4london Thank you Gabriela for telling the truth and not what politicians who hav… https://t.co/AzXJC797YY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrainsunrain @nwadhams @spankythedotard @realDonaldTrump @votevets @veterans_i @amvetsupport @bames_jrolin 🌴😎☮️ #No]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure it is, the cross convicts you of your sins, puts the thought of eternal hell and suffering in your mind while… https://t.co/mx99H4yNtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is so much wrong with this but let’s just start with Dane Dunning being listed as the White Sox ace 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NianticLabs @PokemonGoApp @ThisisTrini How about explaining your actions about the release of Dialga]]></document><document><![CDATA[One never realizes what a huge gaggle of pansies actually surround you until you set the clocks ahead 1 hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schnur had a 0-30 lead in Opelka’s first service game, couldn’t take advantage, then broken in next game. Down 3-0 to start NY Open final.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juneteenth absolutely needs to be taken more seriously. And I'm not above creating more traditions that are more ta… https://t.co/d5fuPFhdqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryBickersta2 Grew up watching Petty n now rooting for the kids 9 42 24 etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask yourself why you’re not developing your people. Be honest and be the change your firm needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After probably 15 years or more of old dry rotting wood and countless layers of stain, the benches needed a good re… https://t.co/FfwFiccyqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NVL one has always been a joke. My senior year we as well as Torrington were 15-5 and COMBINED only had one all… https://t.co/81UDYlvoAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way to grow in life is to allow people in your life that will push you and want to grow with you. If they… https://t.co/7AlEQUTEpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMarrowz @hi6s_ @Ked3n @zarevi_ I need a bo2 chall but not sure if any of you hack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcoming our new neighbors in #montavilla. — #masonbees #fearlessnature #fearlessconservation #columbialandtrust… https://t.co/ipqchFZvBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buenosdías #café #saturdaycoffee #cafecito #artistatwork #latinxartist #artisticdirector #catracho @ Chicago, Illi… https://t.co/j2euutKUYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never met him I guess it's last name to Napper now rest in peace Walker Napa https://t.co/f5mh2uYw4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Machida Karate today was yoko geri (side kick) class then some station conditioning! #machidakarate #chinzomachida… https://t.co/eLE1tlmWAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1f5nGGXRmN  https://t.co/fxvsfehddX the Left Created Black Victimology and Black Rejection of American… https://t.co/NB2Z28hRv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand game makers want to make their product “realistic,” or “gritty,” in some cases. But the profanity in C… https://t.co/MpSNNF0rS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleaned up my Instagram feed finally.  Nice and neat now.   https://t.co/slK5aQLJkb https://t.co/o8HIHBe5KQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was great would like to see espn bring some of the ufc guys in on shows more]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/HaGLMXYKiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all the work is done here at the 2019 #NBAAllStar game, the 🇵🇭 Philippine media group get together for this p… https://t.co/0Ndp0nh0JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dani_ela0328 *The account you have tweeted is not reachable, please try again]]></document><document><![CDATA[If our heart and behaviors haven't been changed, we've received something other than God's grace. #grace #Godsgrace… https://t.co/dWY2jRYUJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad place to enjoy a frosty beverage. 🍺 @ The Rooftop at The Standard, Downtown LA https://t.co/n3pZ5pV3md]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charter Schools are public schools in statute. See RSMO Chapter 160 (160.400)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope Mauro’s kids are alright in the thick of all of this drama. Can’t be great to have all this press especially if it is true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry to be missing #CATE19 but waving from just a little further down US-101!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found out how easy it is to fix videos with wrong orientation in @googlephotos ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popcoken @CoolComicArt Was there a falling out? I never really knew what happened when his X-Men run ended. I know… https://t.co/0fgEPlFHvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArdaOcalTV MIKE ERUZIONE   WINTHROP MASSACHUSETTS  I PLAY FOR THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinrickman The audience for this tweet is basically just me and I appreciate you for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo I started friend-zoning woman at church that I serve with today, and let me tell you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirguduDriver2 @AdjustinBeaver @IMPACTWRESTLING @FiteTV @LuchaElRey @Tess_Blanchard @TheEliDrake @TheRealMorrison… https://t.co/fLRlhT6AOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seduction#malenudephotography#eyes#comehither#wetdreams#saturdaynightfever#lightandshadows##malebeauty#muscle#dram… https://t.co/ffu6ddndDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you teach someone how to fish, you feed them for a lifetime.  If you don’t catch any fish, you will starve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurelyNicole That's kind of surprising. Then again, I guess there's no such thing as "unsinkable". Just sort of th… https://t.co/XwtdAP6sdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whodat_jedi “The difference between you and me, K?  I make this look gooood.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casey Morsell misses the front end of a 1 and 1 that would’ve iced the game. Timberlake responds with a three that… https://t.co/RbfXe1v9m4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DouggieJones @kenklippenstein If so, then we doomed I guess.  Do people who post crap like this think about what t… https://t.co/NpOCm1zx6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I felt when I was told my song “Fishing In The Dead Sea” went over 200k streams on spotify !  Video lin… https://t.co/yehDJBKQvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@villi I admire his guile. He lives on his own terms. I feel sorry for his Mom, girlfriend, and friends as their he… https://t.co/s6qN1SeeNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I blasted my sisters phone until she picked up. Got her to open the door. But still my key is stuck and broken]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody has sang happy birthday to me in the last 2 years of my birthday. And I hope it stays that way 😂 I’m already… https://t.co/KXVxraaCgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes at Mirror Don’t Know Me music video shoot. #musicvideo #seattlemusic #seattlefilm #director #arts… https://t.co/bbZvJLbTtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama's Attorney General Eric Holder who is considering running for president has called for the ELIMINATION of the… https://t.co/Pam0ciGxGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnsonFDN Please watch my video and retweet if comfortable: https://t.co/PcXJLPWolm … I am a stage IV HPV to… https://t.co/XlUszSxKeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OBOMB-A wears a BOMBer jacket and a few days later we have a BOMB cyclone?! He thinks we're all stupid but this all… https://t.co/ofhW92QgT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp we all tried there’s no hope now bout to slip and break my neck see you guys at school👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMiddlekauff I want to know what was on that paper he was trying to get! https://t.co/NVdqG8BKYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier SportS SPACE PorT SPACE                SPS                ONE State of Pennsylvannia serving THE DEC… https://t.co/xv78Syt4Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big game for Mr. Miller PE class bets- 20 push-ups on the line tonight- 💪 🏀 #Hoosiers https://t.co/Mcfi6w6M7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniejaye @LynnePatton @TxsleuthUSA @CNNPolitics @CNN @RaySanchezNYC Slander is proven lies. All ya got About fake… https://t.co/518sEmfsYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALL_CAPS Yeah, “every” might be a stretch, but this is an epidemic. I could see how having a car that you can take… https://t.co/tPJDccgJvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#’s matter: 70+bowling lines/2 school ISD’s represented/400+in attendance/Dozens of community sponsors/Thousands $… https://t.co/4lDz6KfLcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dro_Money21 @SethNixMusic @CDeBaise124 @GodwinDana @steph93065 @AOC It's out of the same budget you dipshit, just… https://t.co/OitJGesnsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking at y’all, @bitterasiandude @jean_yoon @andrewphung @SimuLiu @iAndreaBang! 😆 https://t.co/CCljkGkcM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe use's ironic to source's instrumental, true extent. https://t.co/ycpNlRB41o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino AOC continues to prove her stupidity, the DemWits continue to fail and Trump continues to make great decisions!  Thank you @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRoseBushes If they let them actually hit I’ll probably watch more of it than I did the nfl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my niece brings home lots of chocolates &amp; candy from her school so I can munch on once I’m home☝🏽]]></document></documents></author>