<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I entered this @ChaseRiceMusic #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/xI4l5VX1N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311Toronto @chouse17 @JoshMatlow I spoke with @JoshMatlow’s office on Monday morning. They were extremely helpful… https://t.co/9nCJiBC4a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks Wouldn't Trump have to prove McCabe's being untruthful? Hoping this is the leg up McCabe deserves fo… https://t.co/BqcRLtF7Mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Hope the judge isn't gullible enough to buy that bucket of crap!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s this I hear of beer showers in Starkville @OleMissEvie ?  Do the state students not know of their Twitter an… https://t.co/59Br2TKAeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homedecoration #interiordesign #interior #homemade #designer #decor #Interiors #homedesign #decoration… https://t.co/EVeJjp5r0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday night vibes...really missed last week in house visit!   #Massage #nopainnogain #bodycare #itfactorbiz… https://t.co/bnIL94nuRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BushChancey @GJSentinelSpts Hey, that looks strikingly like what readers will see in Sunday’s @GJSentinelSpts cove… https://t.co/G0L1TPylVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother @KingL is one of the most #influential rap artist and cultural influencer to emerge outta #ChiRaq. I hav… https://t.co/kEzYw6JAjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been saying I wish Marie would do a classroom version. Well #caedchat beat her to it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to add insult to injury, the machine spits out a reminder that they upgraded me without permission to a god dam… https://t.co/bScIIfsfjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got this Alex... positive attitude, cumulative prayer and stubborn determination are #1 in beating cancer.  I a… https://t.co/4MwZ0toZzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the apartment complex now. Awful news to start the week. #abc13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did .@RealJamesWoods intend to tweet start a #BoycottCaptainMarvel movement or was he just responding in kind to a… https://t.co/DiItXL0ZZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Torts, extremely on the rails. A wonderful example of total sanity as per usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m actually kim tho crying to my dad about any little inconvenience i encounter 💀 this bc been making me emotional]]></document><document><![CDATA[it was so nice to meet you &amp; Lindsey. looking forward to seeing you tmrw &amp; Tuesday ❤️⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diversity us our greatest gifts! #ladieslead #powerinvoting @AyannaPressley @RashidaTlaib @AOC 🇺🇸 https://t.co/A2cBpxMgoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would dress up in army fatigues and walk our dogs Rocky and Rambo all over the neighborhood FYI was never in milita… https://t.co/agKAUGijdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is ironic that at the same time that we were sitting down with Council Members to discuss the implementation of… https://t.co/azECv6jQmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright. I’ll admit it. I have a crush on @ShawnMendes. https://t.co/V5pTNDqOdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say that my puppy is absolutely adorable but also the biggest asshole I know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had 6 chocolates as my only meal today I almost fell over when a gust of wind hit me]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom’s bff convinced me to take IF Gard and AB Gard because I’m 100 (and for heartburn). I feel like my gut is fu… https://t.co/VPHdR3igCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay, ay, ay @Canal5Mex tiene a @MaxandShred playing in #Mexico @Nickelodeon so awesome!! @EmiliaaMcCarthy… https://t.co/P54aY8QVNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Iowa is on with @JeriannWX forecast @WHOhd #TodayinIowa. She said even she is now tired of winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ServeThe901 @JohnFugelsang @tcm In Ivanka's mind, she's on a White House Roman Holiday. In our world, she's a member of the House of Wax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful church! Warm, lovely acoustics (and a warm, lovely church staff). Thank you, Trinity Presbyterian… https://t.co/ScaTVijejI]]></document><document><![CDATA[ahh this is flips !! i used to give him a dolla per flip on 17th st wow memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[INK on Broadway tickets on sale now. We open April 24 👊🏻#inkbroadway #samueljfriedmantheatre @mtc_nyc @ Manhattan T… https://t.co/MR5so2YYQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Leave Trump there! My heart breaks for Otto's family. My heart breaks for our country. Trump is a… https://t.co/83PLIFReco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burberry's new show pays homage to British rave culture @Mixmag https://t.co/Ld7yhXYItN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IleneSanti @PalmerReport Her assistant explained to her Be Best was grammatically incorrect,  and she went with it… https://t.co/dtMxLGhJp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very sorry. It was one of worst days of my life when I had lost Feeb.  Unconditional love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For though by this time you ought to be teachers, you need someone to teach you again the basic principles of the o… https://t.co/UGwrlyXlHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh from our cheese workshop class this afternoon...delish. Who wants some? @ Staunton, Virginia https://t.co/xLslTlLMZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeez Louise this is painful to read. I can’t imagine the squirming going on in the courtroom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mik35mith Actually if I knew someone that was dating you, it would be more like "tell him to stop being a little b… https://t.co/NqIaZAsDSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want so much to be so excited for TS7, but there’s just so much going on around me... so much change... LIFE 😭😭😭 I’m overwhelmed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @eugenemulero @TransportTopics Legalize Cannabis in all 50 States and tax it at 50%...Take that money and… https://t.co/H7lePVXo98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber @donnawayoutwest The adults in political game know it doesn’t matter what these ppl say. Trump doe… https://t.co/p2ED8Yf7uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocksForLEOs @JeffreyYarbrou2 @NC5_LelanStatom @PSPTroopNPIO @ToddTrotter3 @ChicagosFines19 @RCSD @MocksvilleD… https://t.co/yMAxQF6tJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Belated Birthday Julissa! #EAT #weRmadison @ Madison High School https://t.co/0KLL7JBoX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill It’s called free speech. As long as they’re peaceful we must allow them to speak. Let them expose their ridiculous rhetoric.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS if you like musicals and haven’t watched @mulaney/ @DocumentaryNow’s parody of Company you’re making extremely p… https://t.co/E4iihV3m4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanHRubin I commend you for being able to hold your temper during that totally inane "conversation". #adultatthetable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anon_Mafioso Such a disservice too sooooooo many. What a selfish asshole. You got your attention Jussie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @RamsNFL @marcuspeters @StrokerAceKid @tattoo49ers @GMFB_Stephaine Thanks Rebekka! 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[گذری به بهشت پنهان ایران زمین  اردبیل، شهری به قدمت تاریخ با برخورداری از مجموعه زیبایی‌های منحصر به فرد طبیعی، تار… https://t.co/gSibUJgRVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stayhomevegan @VicenteLuqueMMA @bryan_barberena If you shot this I was across the tunnel from you! James Vick banded me his hat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenJauregui I got mine!!! Can't wait to wear it @LaurenJauregui 💕 https://t.co/zIbzPpp1Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even flexing for social media but if you play in any division of the NBA pleaseeeeee don’t hml I don’t wann… https://t.co/3q2OISV1um]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Clover 🍀 This bag can do it all, it’s like having 2 bags in one! It’s a crossbody messenger bag plus you can c… https://t.co/DLSbfHBwUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of the book challenge by @charlestull to post a favorite book for 7 days and tag someone new each day.  No ex… https://t.co/l6nGJFY5da]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VVMF I remember the Cabbage patch series and yeah how the movement changed it and I remember finally getting my fi… https://t.co/cRCoXOkASz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hates the holiday, loves me. #grateful &lt;3 #gunnlove @ Laura Gunn Marketing - #LGMarketing https://t.co/f0G259vsYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great thread on Galaxy 4DPs. Maybe we should not be in a rush to pay down one of ours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishaSamuels @kahlams Those are easy! I’m thinking I might need to read in a blanket fort over spring break!😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahil13khan @garciacg17 @SafeerButt4 @SilviaMaidorn @shellzfairy @EehHorn @Strictly_Chris @johngault071 @Leafalcus… https://t.co/SuH4MuNUaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @Mimirocah1 We need to wait to see what Mueller has found.  I hope Barr does not bar us from the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a new outfit post on the blog today! If you didn’t know, now you know🖤 #styleblogger #fashionworshiperblog… https://t.co/d1zfya843V]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Behalf of Women and Girls, Gertrude Garway Fights for Humanity https://t.co/MHLE1mxkhb via @IMC_worldwide]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSearcaigh Is it weird that I thought she was Melania?  Lol... "Oedipus complex," Jr.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop tryna bash a bitch you was HEAD over heels in love with 😫🤣 yall niggas be BIG CAP OMM !]]></document><document><![CDATA[when ur in Fontana but chill with ppl from la Puente...LMFAO how did we even find eachother 💀💀💀😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are tattoos so fetishized? I can't look up tattoos w/o seeing naked women posing provocatively! Why must everyt… https://t.co/V9bWQMhQzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @KeithTalk2 aoc can put it where the sun don't shine!🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time bailey thought a drug dealer was shapeshifting into her ex &amp; I think about it a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasFeoli @BarthSolis Q madre...seguro hay alguien que puede hacer esto. 🤷🏼‍♀️ Hay montones de “s” 🤢. Yo quiero… https://t.co/cof0QeBxhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor baby has been running a fever. Pls pls pls no flu. 😞😞 dr bound it is! Can’t have my little sugar feeling this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrystalRunsFree @runningdesigner This is where enlisting some anonymous help can be useful :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning my favorite morning @Local4NewsWHBF team @AIkomoniTV @RedrickTerryTV @Local4Ashe https://t.co/9ZTSMp48xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦋We Need To Be On The Same Page As Our Expectations ...Because In Order To Gain, We MUST HAVE CONFIDENCE IN OURSELV… https://t.co/DdV2LkA38G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the bullshit. @IlhanMN was speaking of Congress asking us to be aligned with Israel blindly. She’s right. We c… https://t.co/jt1xy0oRun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BQQuinn Aww I just watched the video I had not seen it yet 😢 man this has been a tough week]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always about #perspective and #empathy. What you see is not always what’s real.  #FunnyFriday #😂😊😊… https://t.co/kMogtfT9Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just went to wgi regionals in dayton and i miss drumline more than anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandiRhodes @TheDemocrats I think Randy is correct. Nancy is setting the table.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats move to strip Jared of his security clearance over claims ... In-Depth-Daily Mail-Feb 4, 2019… https://t.co/W7JaMqboeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[ART FOR FUN: I needed a break from my pile of art commissions. If I don’t switch gears once in a while for a day or… https://t.co/giUvKtvxgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @ExOnTheBeach and what was said about @NicolexoRamos is not okay. You do not talk about the way someone lo… https://t.co/ta4nddFSbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doomtoflesh @Vomit_Dragon @ambientgaze NO PLEASE i don’t wanna go to hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TmanSpeaks @digitalcloudgal Tony, you sure know how to make my green eyes 👀 blue.   😂🤪 #Think2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaelyTiffany Don’t rush into great decisions. You will know in your heart when the time is right ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #snacho wears #sandals.. all the way from #Mexico #lovehim and gracias @ Hide Away Cabin https://t.co/xwwKWu5Laa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheDatWeDat @thebirdwrites Zo better than all them Point Guards over there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re texting your best friend... and she knows how tired you are... BUT SHE DECIDES TO CALL YOU. NO 👏🏻MA’AM👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god. I did this when I was 3, with Are You My Mother? My mom has a video of me being the cutest child lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look he tweeted happy birthday to beiber. What a suprise. Oh Jared so predictable. 😂 https://t.co/ljGLPu8TYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to know Woodbury training today! @ Woodbury, Minnesota https://t.co/CFdyq3ONlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmatera @HeckAwesome @sylviaduckworth @CateTolnai @Kim_Schepers @missmac100 I sure will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KealFranklin @KyleCoroneos @opry The kids like Kane think they have it hard being accepted.  Charlie paved their w… https://t.co/5dsb7rGpVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Wow...it's gases flowing deep" underground, to have flame like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LALiberty16 @anceco @esqonfire If she had not sucked dicks. She'd be on welfare right now and rolling joints.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pusha_leee @StarsInsideEdge Lovejoy is a joke!!  We called him Killjoy.. don’t get too excited!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreysABC My heart just stopped!!! I gave up on this show some time ago and now you want to do this to me!!!! https://t.co/gWMR2Q3NHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[For me, Minding the Gap is a film about a man of color who took painful memories about abuse in his childhood to he… https://t.co/TbP85Uc4gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Nasty,Trashy and sad excuse for a man, much less President!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sullio @mehdirhasan This is what the state of emergency I about?!!????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLeighShulman Im researching: Are verbal agreements legally binding?]]></document></documents></author>