<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Never cheat the grind, it knows how much you’ve invested into it. You’re not gaining anything from it 💯🦉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelheldevans @MethodistView And THAT is what I think Jesus meant when he said “Love your enemies.” Not always l… https://t.co/B9YLW4FMXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I picked the wrong weekend to chase down south. Oh well, whole season ahead hopefully in more favorable terrain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a chill vibe I just discovered @KotaTheFriend  https://t.co/RYdzqnoxBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge variation. Actually a stronger association than healthy eating... the power of good sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Who better to lead a ‘Young Latino Summit’ than Charlie Kirk 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeymurder Terrible rhyming.  Might i suggest a tutor... https://t.co/Mxqx2hPggY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostPanther @SenFeinstein I saw this too and was incredibly disappointed in @SenFeinstein.  @SenFeinstein maybe y… https://t.co/UgNApxDJJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCMcrush @jaxbra I have a hoardery nightmare apartment so i ‘get it’ 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_pfahl @MenInBlazers @ChelseaFC @davematthewsbnd Blues have been a little inconsistent this year. We’ll have… https://t.co/6dI1ryKsvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Acabo de conseguir 1 tirada gratis en Gira y gana de 8 Ball Pool! https://t.co/8ICE0DgrgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady walking dachshund w/ 🎾 on the UWS. Dog tosses 🎾 into oncoming traffic. Lady goes to retrieve 🎾 as safely as po… https://t.co/i3bkSu3LeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @rkelly @R_KellyFans Your amnesia plot will get them thrown under the jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twisted_twins Good Morning Princess Diane ☀️🌨🐶 And Good Morning Twisted_Twins]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of commentary about my appearance lately ...just been telling ppl I’m tryna make the outside match the inside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KCNA Board meeting time.                    #educationmatters #kidsfirst @ Kansas City, Missouri https://t.co/UuhUCfq923]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah. @ Estes Park, Colorado https://t.co/mT4xXd51S0]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the top of the 5th inning, no runs and no hits for the Hurricanes as they still lead 7-2. Bottom of the 5th we go. #FIUBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[A part of me actually feels like I’m making stuff for a campaign for no reason, and that those who sit at my table… https://t.co/TwrXqlHDOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't need your money do you want to just come over here and wait two years until he reincarnates into a girl and… https://t.co/shoF0f6c0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV There are some fans that think the players deserve to be compensated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wikileaks What do you expect From Raft Rowing Drifting TREASONOUS Familia like Little marco rubio's of Cuban Ances… https://t.co/kl1eZ8e0os]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @TylerRickyTynes on the heat check started off with the WaWa hoagie flex]]></document><document><![CDATA[305 pound freshman working hard to get better!! #CountryStrong https://t.co/nzt3Qe5DDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far this month OU has refused to cancel or delay at least twice when the roads were terrible. Also they have twi… https://t.co/nRB4faaPdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttoTitsling Phew, glad that got a 😆 Thought it might get a 🤢or a🤮cause that's kind of what I was feeling when I posted it 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I love you Lisa.. I want to show you how much I love you everyday.. Find me Lisa be in my life... https://t.co/8DTFyegcTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mango En Fuego by @bombshellbeer at @bombshellbeer — https://t.co/2YFC7trRq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @GoMatadors and @CSUNBaseball for having me throw out the first pitch today for their game vs @KStateBSB.… https://t.co/xtjxnTNHHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been cleaning my place all day to now. I must make this spotless just like the way it looked when I moved in. Holy fuck I’m drained. 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got these clean PGs for $65, @goatapp really the best app ever 🙏🏻 https://t.co/iGUCvZFa51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going "old school" is not as effective as going Old Testament.  Read Deuteronomy 7!  #FVCLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris What did Obama create in his 8 years and what exact plans you have in your mind so that the voters can decide who to pick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta give tons of credit to @NASCAR for keeping all these drivers safe. Some high-impact collisions going 200 MPH,… https://t.co/eqbTbQ4jHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CEasttwood @209acesheepdog @realDonaldTrump It's the one thing the swamp can't vote on to block or payoff to contr… https://t.co/jZYKkeJfNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Puerto Rican Prince  CATEGORY IS: "I CALL SHADE" - @TrinityTheTuck  Model: Cesar Piña  @Alex_The_Gray1  DragQue… https://t.co/QUXFAGy2tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWielowieyska Nie popeze PSL bo ma moralnosc i etyke. Nie bedzie wspieral lesbijki i pederastow ktorzy wypowiedzie… https://t.co/o2SjAgWFJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I've said before, if the @WAHouseDems @WASenDemocrats want to cut car tabs, then they need to replace the ST f… https://t.co/zu7QTc9fmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dterrazas760 @Dmartelz24 @coachella What u talkin bout Man U went all out and “platinum” ur lettuce for his set. W… https://t.co/cVsmg7sG8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeMari81 @KaitlinRustWAVE @wave3news Good question. Wish I had a better answer for you. Sadly people think it’s ok… https://t.co/HoE8rVa6Hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson some days I wake up and hope I don't have voices in my head.  I don't care about there eternal wars,… https://t.co/X8jYrrRqqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatlynHarrison @_woodhead Feb 15th is the Boxing Day of Valentine's Day 😎😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Patriot Take Action And End The #PoliceState #DeepState #DrainTheSwamp #MAGA https://t.co/yzhYYlxlYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OscarGR93 @Chertorivski @DeniseDresserG Muy preocupados por el desvalido. Hipocresía pura.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CR_HIATT @mizzhays @AstorAaron @IndyByChoice @rip157 @Lax_Mom01 @johnrobertsFox @WhiteHouse Like the deal we had w… https://t.co/hRcjlpUT6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 pulls both direction "3 sets" Feel it burn.  No need to go shopping just use an extension cord you already have… https://t.co/2k9lL0nGuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why thank you @VMware #VMwareHQTour #vExpert #LeaderSummit2019 https://t.co/wAA87Es8RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @ZionHananiah I wouldn’t do it. I think it’s shameful. But condemning others for it..🤷‍♂️. I need chap… https://t.co/mu0jVEj7VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, a viable candidate to nominate you for the Nobel peace prize.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllThatandMoore Very nice. That joke was built up very smoothly and had great execution]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xhjInACSI9 #artistsoninstagram #artist #art #artwork #fineart #contemporaryart #creativeartist… https://t.co/cl4ToLISfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to get the opportunity to be evaluated? Here is your chance. https://t.co/w6UYx5CzvG https://t.co/lABnJM3O6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second pair courtesy of @lwfustos. Thanks! #PennState #weare #sundaysocks #funsocks #crazysocks #workoutsocks… https://t.co/rCPYajuiC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[See more photos of this one of a kind farmhouse for sale in Frederick at https://t.co/1mvdKFmuLp @ Walkersville, Ma… https://t.co/snHJBGRgis]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @CoachNate79 to post 7 covers of books I love--1 each day for 7 days - no explanatio… https://t.co/7ReXGUidqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The police will catch this guy.  A jerk like this has enemies who would love to see him go down.  Gotta be honest,… https://t.co/uU67JX0ljJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qowicome Honestly I’m ready to purchase, so.. I’ll be waiting for the link. https://t.co/Dl0o8Yt1At]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found a white hair in my sideburns. This mop's gonna be something else when it's iced out, son.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to join @ScholesE15 tonight 8 pm ET for #mschat https://t.co/2hTFd0ZzKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survived a night alone with the two kids. Shout out to all the moms out there, shits real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSF_optc Just a revised version of your old team 🤩 https://t.co/luoFRBS0lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see ppl in casts n wheelchairs n shit getting beat up I just think of how stupid you gotta be to think someo… https://t.co/ywW8AewfkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please RT. Get the senators attn. This is important for the future of #OvarianCancer and women's lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fear_E_DABJ @posthuman I am literally always sayin REDUCE! (that track too busy what a waste) #54321EDIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poser here.  Posing to help a special friend do a portrait study. Definitely an experience. https://t.co/a2vks4AeEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hollywood I am ready  ➡️ info@giuseppelentini.com ⬅️ #actorslife #giuseppelentini #characteractor #actor #model… https://t.co/SoasL2iSgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate_Springer @WDRBNews In honor of Daylight Savings, give us “Time” by Hootie and the Blowfish. https://t.co/DIIz9gLr3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bral3ssWond3r @Beatlesnut388 your suggestion makes me think of some obscene phrases https://t.co/rmFJIDTCO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/ I could go on, and I’ve barely begun to scratch the surface. But notice something - many of the people I cite a… https://t.co/v7qwnu7ajO]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first stone  upon the #foundation of #Christ the first stone of the #temple the living heart of #Peter the… https://t.co/owIIrkUYQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s going on with #southerneducation on #BlackHistoryMonth 2 teachers fired over controversy #Anaalverez &amp; #elizabethtemple]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libby Ryan goes deep on Alyssa Denham. Denham served as the No. 2 last year but has really struggled to find her gr… https://t.co/KwNqNJdbgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonEthridgeTX @BillNye @AOC That ia your problem. Because she actually gets it more often than you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARE WE GONNA LET THOSE FILTHY BANKERS ON WALL STREET STEAL OUR CUM? I SAY NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronMeyers Yeah, boy! I had that one. That's some 5th Grade Recess Shit right there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at 103.9 the light, answering calls for this St.Jude telethon  Cancer has to back up, through prayer and throu… https://t.co/UC9Kjtl0Wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE @DoylesPub @pbnjtacoma @jj__murray @lfcseattle https://t.co/P7i4AQY2D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@innocence Just when I think I might be for the death penalty stories like this confirm my belief our justice syste… https://t.co/RkIvxUbWkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @chrisbleck I feel this front office thinks too short term, they don’t think what could help them in t… https://t.co/4jFD80SZ2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been around too long for y’all to still not know that if they will cheat with you, they’ll cheat on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to wonder how  much #RealTalent was out here until i made a Twitter page and #ListenedTo #Bands @StoneBroken_… https://t.co/dVYo8Esdsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JhawkChalk89 @DFFMemphis @PlayDraft Three injuries in two seasons isnt a concern?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refs that blow the whistle after the shot either goes in or doesn’t are fucks... dude waits to see if the UT player… https://t.co/aNJeq5Ru3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentines. #happyvalentinesday #blessed 😍😘 @ Boyne Mountain Resort https://t.co/ASmC2pPkcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole gym is covered, it’s still snowing, and we are still open this morning💪🏼 #tehachapisfinest #lionheartmma… https://t.co/2VXfww89zO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can be as dumb as asphalt about a lot of things, but I like to think I know a great story when it’s developing,… https://t.co/pXCDMNdFG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitlynMCole @imRoseHD Okay somethings gotta give... you can’t be performing magic like this and beating me in the Bachelor league 😅😐😐😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in Rome... (or Akron) #stricklandsicecream #akronfoodrocks @ Strickland's Frozen Custard https://t.co/DPKngFaq8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard a buddy passed away. Body builder and trainer gone too early. Such a nice and humble human. We will miss you, Andy. RIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danecrislip this is Rick (Tyler's dad) saw your story in church this morning, amazing, really enjoyed your testimo… https://t.co/x1hbtA0bMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto The greatest gift ever for the GOP just keeps giving. What a blessing this idiot is 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legitimately think Floridians just hang out at Walmart’s....this is bizarre!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstiloDF @EdySmol @CDLC_oficial @diegodeericemx @Julio_Camejo @Ruy88 @claudiaalvarezo Muy hermosas Claudia y… https://t.co/ZgOZC2oU2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanBJackson1 @PrincipalSJV @MrRileyjo @RuggedManiac @fit_leaders @NicholasFerroni @matthew_arend @SeanAThom… https://t.co/78aRNhhzP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vrijomslachtig @jessesingal It’s 3.8 not 38. And like many, you have a strong opinion about Israel’s utility and m… https://t.co/KBSQdlj2Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[That 70’s Glow #contemporaryart #abstractart #nashville #art #artist #artistsoninstagram #neoexpressionism #70s #v… https://t.co/VDPZHI7faJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunkoPopHunters  “ last days of Kurt Cobain “ -custom made by Dan Potter https://t.co/5Ns6U5fNgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? Because these fuckers track it.  I am confident my time here was the absol… https://t.co/bRmO6GgZPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast I don't know. It might be kind of cool if they can bring back some of the animals that humans killed off like the Dodd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que CR7 por aquí, que CR7 por allá, que le hace falta al madrid, que con él sería distinto. Les informo que el seño… https://t.co/3DYsI1aCGE]]></document></documents></author>