<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@carlosvecchio is a terrible spoke person for the Venezuelan movement against Maduro! At @FareedZakaria he had a di… https://t.co/mNZTDSTi1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright someone find me a ticket under $50 because again! I got fucked over by being born poor on Long Island and n… https://t.co/Kh0oUMFRa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skrubburks  @CMANGO @antiquesILuv @4judyblue @gomangohemi20 @Varightone1 @Pixxydoodle @DannyLeBlanc24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tnkithcart @frecklesgms @MingGao26 Sheldon Whitehouse is looking into this. I think he was ready to hit the roof.… https://t.co/9ti1BSzwZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gbhwildcats Future Business Leaders of America bring home 1st, 2nd and 3rd place wins in Regional Competition. Nex… https://t.co/nyxX7gxS0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any art teacher peeps going to the National art conference in Boston? Just booked my rooms and paid for the conference... sad and poor now 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home Meet 2019💙  Not pictured: my landing on bars😬 @ White Building Fitness Center https://t.co/dwBf32faZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ImChefCole Welcoming myself back to earth. I went to sleep at 3 pm YESTERDAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I also don’t think my phone use is necessarily a problem. When I was called out, I thought about making excuses… https://t.co/lFxUxGv5EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Best birthday wishes. Tonight I will listen to Cop Killer and then watch the contradiction of you on SV… https://t.co/Ggqj0o3R9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's nearly 4:30 am and I'm still up. Stupid insomnia.  It would be fine if I didn't have to go to work in 4 hours. Stupid insomnia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a public announcement about how @peta is shit 💁🏼‍♀️ You may now carry on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening stroll along the beach with gale108  #onslowbeachcamplejeune #moonlight #atlanticocean #onslowbeach… https://t.co/vzBIKwbV68]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come support young actors and actresses in some of their first performances EVER!! #AuroraHuskies #middleschool… https://t.co/TVNjamcJVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with the launch of @Whats_Your_ID a custom design shop #impressingdesigns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prattprattpratt @brielarson @bbarnucz @vincentdonofrio Congratulations on your launch!  Hope both do amazing at the box office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Amy Klobuchar Treats Her Staff https://t.co/ONMrVjxo3m I guess she is a Bit~~. You can tell. Her father was dru… https://t.co/tSsiHa47zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricB_noRakim @helloluvah @javeauriel @_yellow_paiges_ https://t.co/mNM5fWxtSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib Welp, I guess this is the only way I will see @iamcardib and her hubby!!......sending love from the ATL… https://t.co/tWxhyY7DQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Women’sInternationalDay #Sisters #BossLady #GirlPower #ForYourMind #Limitless #BornThisWay #Flawless #Lovely… https://t.co/e3dlmDIb6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[i used to own this account on instagram and one of my exes would check up on it periodically and i never knew how m… https://t.co/i13l7jnlaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four @HamiltonHIVE chairs share their experiences with precarious employment. Next up, @alyssaglai! https://t.co/otSlIbtXxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Is this how you guys are going to explain the rapture?? 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila @SenateDems Walls are immoral but killing a newborn is not?  I’m beyond repulsed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shariannebrill @SonnyBunch Amazon would just relocate to right to work states to escape that prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantylercohen How many votes have you bought in Eastern KY, Mitch? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cofe6370 @MeeMichie @Naahledge @ms_chi_town_eb @12Chains @divateach37 @Imdatchick1985 @BIGJAMES_2 You bet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncanChapple can you please share more feedback after you have played with it. Thank you for sharing- looks aweso… https://t.co/9G5u2JqHFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turtlefr0g @d4wgl0gs Nothing is more cringe than unfunny, edgy, white teen boys who say nigga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diletta1972 @agamanimukherj1 Yes Facebook seems more drama...I love my friends I have on here and ty ..💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many nights, trying to find someone new. 🌻 Yeah, I tried, but I just can't give you up. Wonder why is it that I'… https://t.co/TybvcmDxrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the benefits of being my friend? Big @nuunhydration discounts! Use code: hydratefriends25 by 3/9 for 25% off… https://t.co/pUQi9B4CnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prost! (@ Hofbräu @BierhausNYC in New York, NY) https://t.co/Oj1OULg6mQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big crowd for this morning’s All-Staff Diversity &amp; Inclusion meeting at #UChicago. https://t.co/u80O95nDS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day in the life of a teacher. *alarm goes off at 4:30 AM* *starts singing in head* “What’s the weather, what’s th… https://t.co/GahOE6bFD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[GS downgraded Burberry to sell same day it relaxed the dress code https://t.co/8sNhoeJmfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shouldn't you have made a statement regarding Putins threat to U.S. yesterday? Instead of trying e… https://t.co/UT66FJMYRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Setbacks have an upside; they fuel new dreams.”  — Dara Torres   (📸 @Kristinleephoto) @ HITS Thermal Desert Horse… https://t.co/Ifgb6vFrEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bariweiss Unfortunately there had been nothing but hate and destruction coming from @DNC and #FakeNews that all th… https://t.co/7N44Xk0x2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out having a drink with my family when "While my Guitar Gently Weeps" came on the radio. I low-key sang along under… https://t.co/o1lAqGFd2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Virgo and that’s why y’all don’t want to go to the movies with me LMAO this is sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newbobhead I think lots of people in the 80s asked themselves the same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so sad, frontierland is one of my favorites and people just don't get it 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌴BEVERLY HILLS🌴 . I’m only joking, this is just behind the scenes 🎬 at Looks Leads Lifestyle. 🌴 . . For legal assis… https://t.co/eLvJVbO6R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it a sin to decorate for Easter before lent? Probably. Oh well, I like my new bunny josh bought me so it’s  staying out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to do this shit in the inside of my desk in elementary school 😆🤓😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be there. Proud to be be an ally. Proud to support LGBTQ+ youth!  Thank you, @DonCheadle!   ❤🧡💛💚💙💜🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[it be the ones getting cheated on too loool like just leave already damn dude 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[so many amazing looks on the red carpet I honestly don’t even know where to start]]></document><document><![CDATA[My timeline will have so many less “boob drops” with out you and be way less funny. RIP @SchoolBoy_Mack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never dim your light to make someone else feel comfortable. They’ll adjust. ❤️🥳 • • • #itsAnnastesia… https://t.co/AZU8kaMPIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter Happiness is where you find it live life because you have this oneI hope you have a great awesome amaz… https://t.co/Z6yshxTOl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/AIga8AIRXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_a_fisher @MPSPanthers @Jaworek_School @Gr1_Sweetapple @Grade1_Boudreau @JackiePlank @JustinaMailly Congratulations Valeria!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my favorite snack these days (besides my shake (who am I??!) I have been sick for almost a week now and the… https://t.co/N0iBh9JneE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SjCattledog @dogcelebration Silver looks happy and still very fluffy Have a great weekend. Thanks for the morning pic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady You should NOT be covering politics in the 21st century. Cultural incompetence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DID NO ONE TELL ME THAT @nickjonas WAS ON SMASH I FLIPPED @NBCSmash https://t.co/N04hQWK2LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Prayers to you and your family the Lord is wrapping his arms around your mom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[....I don’t think he’ll be falling to the Colts as some mock drafts have shown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danniBalPat13 @ZielaskowskiM @CraigHarroldWA @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Of course Democrats Want Strong security a… https://t.co/pkFJ0IsVt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll laugh at you before I'll react , so take my laugh as your warning 💯😂❌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work day snack time. Yes, please.   Crisp, 100% double cheese, desk size, taste yummy, and craving gone. Can't get… https://t.co/AQGBt1cQFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daphna27 @catspecter @danpfeiffer One of the Pod boys worked on Hillary’s campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAME DAY!! We need your support as we are competing for the Non-Public A South title, 5pm at Jackson Liberty!! So p… https://t.co/oFejVDExDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R94071430 @wikinoticias @petrogustavo Probablemente Lula sea el iniciador de la horrible izquierda, de Odebrecht y… https://t.co/CKIgzS8cqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to make a 7 hour drive and I already know what my playlist is about to consist of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just want to personally thank everyone who has come into macys, or any small business today, making ot so that we… https://t.co/xAQRhkm9HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TupeMichael Feel free to add it to the Powerplay Point Podcast Facebook page also so fans can contact you directly :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[W6A2: I feel like every day we make crepes Ss are immersed in the learning like never before. We stay in TL, eat an… https://t.co/yQ9eUGXC3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_realjgoodwin @DineshDSouza WE LOVE YOU ALL!!! It is so great people are starting to think for themselves and not… https://t.co/60Z9kZ0t2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 106 Talah Way #Loudon #TN  #realestate https://t.co/mHx9OpeMo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the demon inhabiting my apartment, I would appreciate it if you would not turn my TV on at 3:20 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can waste your lives drawing lines or you can live your life crossing them.” @shondarhimes #womensday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraNiven @brennan_elliott @hallmarkchannel He got his practice running in Bucks County. 🤭🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I think my nose is super cute. It looks like a cartoon nose and I’m here for it. https://t.co/egkLU7NWfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorDScott The left wouldn’t know the truth if it smacked them upside their hypocritical faces! They really are… https://t.co/W8LNRWE9ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisvanderveen @drkivela I ask because Alteplase the drug used to treat stroke costs us almost $10,000 per vial.… https://t.co/LQC3Z2FvFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy happy bday @nic_smercina - can’t wait to drive the jeep this summer!!😬 hope you had the best 21st ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunicke @taleoftales I find the Phoenix Wright games so soothing that sometimes I fall asleep while playing them (not a bad thing) 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne I’m so sorry for your loss. Too bad government thinks it has the capacity to have the answers to problems l… https://t.co/7Xc9fLUua4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I gladsome that the Patriot’s corpulent white male owner has been nabbed in a prostitution drug sting in Jup… https://t.co/an53eQl5eR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoishesMom I found an article in nytimes about  dogs f N.Y. I will write to r email the reporter about the problem… https://t.co/ffdGldn4SH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyHuynh0512 @singularibabe @LucieChau They should have just got yoongi https://t.co/VCY6e9wM6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport We can only hope. White collar crime in this country is being led by an Orange disaster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imjustabee and also it doesn’t always work out in the end (aka divorce) then it was all just a waste of money]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't disagree with you.  I am concerned that not everyone is able to return them to the office.  If there isn't… https://t.co/VEjsqcmsvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would have been 62 today. I can’t believe it’s been almost 2 years since you’ve been gone. I miss you everyday… https://t.co/PKFyLCpcLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are so welcome!!! I love making connections between digital tools and the awesome @iste Students Standards. And… https://t.co/EDwG7OxB4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longgonejohn81 @SmithAgConrad Beats me why I'm awake besides really strange dreams. I'm not getting up, I'm too snug in my bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosenCampbell @cmclymer This was a time where it was better to say nothing. I am actually begging you to learn fro… https://t.co/bcwWtGqe16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seesawcabello @taintedRep @02_020___ @PopCraveNet Imagine thinking "electric chair" is funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @MarshallCohen Liar. Period. Sickening. No one to blame but himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February break vibes 🙈 . . . #fawnheartfit #family #peekaboo #kids #asd #life #love #babyofthefamily #joy #happy @… https://t.co/zufI14JJTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campusreform The onlookers are cowards and pathetic to stand by as the assault happens. Losers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will guide us through our wrong doings to correct our path but we as followers of Christ must be willing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my dad’s birthday. he is a legend and is the hardest working man i know. he is my favorite. 💕he’s also 68 and… https://t.co/pQeWodfR4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegChar @brainpop @embrown1621 @bakerelembears @CobbAlp This was a great idea! Thanks!! @MegChar @embrown1621]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss They all are very concerned what goes on in someone else's uterus, but they dont give a good god d… https://t.co/xlDHN3ENTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx @tatclouthier Eso es muyyyyyy fantasioso, quieren que se hable de eso para desviar la atención a t… https://t.co/fXuj17ozJg]]></document></documents></author>