<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Behind my smile there is a story you will never understand! . . . #AnnieLeBlanc annieleblanc @ Santa Monica, Califo… https://t.co/FXlsJzjM1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whelp, the global UMC voted that I'm still not a full human being. After initial tears, I am mad AF.  And now I am waiting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t realize I was parking @tobias31 wheel all morning until he was dippin. I should’ve asked for one of them… https://t.co/BSz5XAfLRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today isn’t about getting gifts or flowers or candy from a guy or girl.. today is to tell everyone you love them ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Knightd427 😂 you just couldn’t help yourself! Meanwhile the electrical storm continues down here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the organizers for including us in your event. #LoveAllHateNone was reflected in your welcoming words… https://t.co/qdBKek5hN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[my co-worker just asked me if I want the balls for lunch.... uh, I thought we were ordering pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't mean to suggest at all that he's not credible in those instances. It's just that as a reporter, you dream o… https://t.co/8zk3RzSlaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanKLieb I know what you mean. I tried to take notes from a few good TV shows too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...the Constitution forms the foundational code that gives shape to America and defines our essential liberties —… https://t.co/vZ2VHe4P83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJDScott @annalee_belle She looks so pretty!  Hope you had fun Annalee!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now he’s calling Tom a dirt bag  even though he doesn’t know him at all #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed a pregame game on my first day at @nationals Spring Training. Got to see @adriansnz , Chuck Taylor,  robles… https://t.co/EV1A00Nw1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love garden and supermodel but really!! i was going through too much at the time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Ugarte @SYFY @IDWPublishing Yeah I missed that, but have seen screen shots. It became pretty clear though… https://t.co/S6tZRvs5QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Amen I pray this tweet is for me. Trying to learn how to walk again after a long journey. I was afraid… https://t.co/yEwKvhArXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A person I follow on Instagram took this picture. So many crosses AND the rainbow. What MORE proof do you need? #godspromise]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aad2019 #aad2019challenge @CILADderma @lauszaf eugabad @drapauluna tamarabarsky aad2019 EL COCKTAIL DEL MEETING en… https://t.co/uOho9eKLxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone sponsor @heyitsfranklin2’s birthday party for book expo. i will only come 2 that book party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWynnHill @Will_Bunch Just what they got from tax scam they could be insurance their employees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys you're on the wrong side of the Capitol! He already promised you a vote! You know who hasn't? Nancy Pelosi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have at least one exam for the past 3 weeks -_- &amp; i have one next week 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desmienten periodistas de EE.UU. que en Vzla. haya crisis humanitaria https://t.co/nwEsFTTyZN vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this is Spike Lee’s FIRST Oscar....crazy. long overdue.  #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetraMcCarron2 So sorry for your loss.  A real love is hard to find.  Real friends are easier to find 😊👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FisherP22 @darty_sp @S_JDrummond By this point I would have found a dog or small child to hide in a corner with...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save your frightened song for when there is really something wrong! Don't cry 'wolf' when there is NO wolf! #TrumpFakeEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bostocksbar https://t.co/bsjitwipP3  Download the app for rides https://t.co/Su8ZPfHNcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochVoisineRVI Goodmorning Smootchie Poo... Have a nice and safe trip to NB. Take good care of this Heart of gold.… https://t.co/DCqmrd5ila]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you are doing something right when your parents (who are not on Instagram!) text you a picture of the… https://t.co/30gf2Gw9ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight booked, hotel booked, excitement bubbling... or wait, maybe that’s nerves? https://t.co/GeTRIJ5mIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJRyanOnAir @BTS_twt @1027kj103 I want Halsey and @BTS_twt  #iHeartAwards #BTSARMY #BestFanArmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strstrmy02 @Bro_Charlie_ @MarkPinnix @erenna_marie @HmssGenflynn @JudyMarie4DT @alyxknapp @maryllewis53… https://t.co/eTCfjPYtD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OWNTV .. Calling on Jesus!!! Forgive me Lord but I hope the people who hurt these children are burning in HELL!… https://t.co/t99BstkkLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @ukhomeoffice Long overdue, but great news for the ppl of UK. Wonder what that whats-his-name Mayor i… https://t.co/C5vLeIJh1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[El día de hoy el recreo se trató de buscarle el zapato a un niño porque se lo robaron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just be really stupid for a second? Okay.   💜🥺💗i get to wear birkenstocks next week😰❤️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkempcpa Somewhere along the way we lost the plot in our capitalism. The justification for capitalism is, after al… https://t.co/VUpy4zNwE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lit up buildings st distillery district #distillerydistrict #toronto #lights #working #busy #tarotcards… https://t.co/59sGrVzmZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When soft and tender spaces house courageous and bold women .....  We can be all of the above and so much more .. ✨… https://t.co/Ikj53AaNAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I was little I was going through my dad’s cassettes in his car and asked “who are the raymins?” and that’s my… https://t.co/jWiF1IrDEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said literally twice but even if I said it three times he still wouldn’t get it so🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[my roommate was complaining about how the ted radio hour would make him feel bad if it was his ted talk on there li… https://t.co/pfg5eRcsHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO my best friends boyfriend called me a slut and hoe because she came to see me after he told her no because he… https://t.co/T0Gwhux8R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJTHEMACK1 @AuthorMBTosi @annlynn57 @TrishSuter @MackenzieLitt13 @GulfamBhatia1 @stephen_ainley @carol_kilgore… https://t.co/ECSWH65BkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano Amen! As a woman, veteran and someone who has worked for inclusion of women in our Constitution, I… https://t.co/ntUDKLu5E7]]></document><document><![CDATA[do not let your left hand know  what your right is doing  #ash #fasting #weeping #mourning #pray #gloomy #hypocrite… https://t.co/MzhwO4VlB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have @att and I can’t call anybody. Just get the dropped call signal after a few seconds. The one time I need to… https://t.co/BDowOcJdzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders In high school, i sat on the front steps with my friend from kindergarten. I had a bowl of cookie dough… https://t.co/YXI3lGwAUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly irresponsible— but you are mistaken— that’s not “reporting”... it’s opinion publishing— something the Ameri… https://t.co/eZWhsDyqBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My "office" view this morning...... my clients from MN didnt mind it lol...better than snow. Sunrise beach view fro… https://t.co/gYpgbCon6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I STAY HUMBLED 💪🏼💙 from the valley  #dirtydesert to the hills in #Hollywood  My little brother used to tease me and… https://t.co/CRQnpr8JAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardinal study from January.  #cardinals #birds #artstudy #birb  My work can be found at https://t.co/zT4k3joHJC… https://t.co/rHe7gXNKL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaetaSusan @POTUS She was the one colluding with Russia. Pay to play!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter More stupid from stupid Tucker. Where does he get this stuff??? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contractions aren’t a joke 😅😅 I didn’t feel them with ari but fuck am I feeling them now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artfullyawear @CentralParkNYC Thank you! Yes, I just started this week 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆🌴 The champs are here.   Mookie and the @RedSox are LIVE on ESPN, with @AROD, @jessmendoza, twitterless Matt Vasge… https://t.co/6j5uMs94Wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/Dlf0Kr6J7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was thinking about who would carry my casket and the only person i could think of is my brother 😂 w0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well we all know that's a lie. That's your I.Q. Too many people hate you for you to have a favorab… https://t.co/PCHOOWqoFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are signs on lawns around the city I live in that state:  BE KIND, if only we followed that advice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[karli and i arent dating, WE’RE MARRIED wtf. no wedding ring bc that shit is for yuppies]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNICEF: Priyanka Chopra doesn’t deserve to be UN’s Goodwill Ambassador - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/E1l0Czyj82 via @CdnChange]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have no kids, No baggage, No past holding me back! Whatever the future holds I’m completely open to it I’m… https://t.co/ryCPmWw9Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also met the love of my life tonight I think, the music was so alive &amp; brought us together stay tuned thx 4 reading]]></document><document><![CDATA[New coffee: 🌱 Organically tasty ☕️ On shelves soon! @ Compton, California https://t.co/0EkP9gpB9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to get over the girl in me that doesn't like this video because of how my hair is crooked with my face that… https://t.co/YLLCMi84yK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealmofHelm So perimeter spots are a bit bigger. We like to back in on the east side and leave quickly out via Clo… https://t.co/Q9VSVO5M1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowpocalypse2019.  It's not sticking here yet but we have flakes @ Silverado Ranch, Las Vegas https://t.co/Rwx7O3qf5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is bullshit #snow #monday  #bullshit #itsmarchstopitalready @ Saugus, Massachusetts https://t.co/CBCzDoeO5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveSurdovel @MathLeaders @utdckatey @utdanacenter 2 good people rigjt there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt really successful tonight. Cleaned the entire upstairs of the house🙌 Just to remember the disaster the main fl… https://t.co/cbkfcZFzkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want to get tattoos for you all over my face” -Sebastian https://t.co/VE9ZQfhWa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of the 7 day book Cover Challenge. Post 7 days of books you love—no explanation, just the covers. One cover a… https://t.co/seXpRChmWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristieLGreen @Team_Penske @amsupdates @DrawTiteHitches @keselowski @FordPerformance Yeah,i was just at Daytona d… https://t.co/QrkCWfg03c]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are pictures of me as a toddler stealing my dads beer and chugging it 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KetoDad1 Sounds like you’re choosing the internal validation of satisfaction in pursuing your goals instead of ane… https://t.co/yI9zYY56Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[My avocado this morning was so perfectly ripe! What a beautiful start to the day! 🥑 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mixed coffee and hot chocolate on this snow day morning. I’ll take my medal now . . . #snowday #coffee… https://t.co/dxY2pMYM1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LironD Side note: I would love for Marc to co-write and co-produce a whole CD with Mariah. They make great music together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARCEBASSY Philadelphia is opening day,  OMG I need tickets cuz this bitxh is broke 😄 I have to see u again Marc u… https://t.co/SnLdjtAUBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF #RomanEmpire 🤗🤙🏼Have a great day and I’m sorry if I missed anyone! @JoDresbach @fabiola_pizana @RobeEmpire_1… https://t.co/YlLyMTT3Zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[At every occasion I'll be ready for the funeral. https://t.co/gsl9Hf77Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rascoundrel @MargaretJosephs @fireandicelv @Andy @Teresa_Giudice @daniellestaub @DashiellCodd Sending my deepest sympathies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao how tf was i so in love with you? you’re biiig ugly &amp;&amp; you were an abusive asshole 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[haven’t gotten a new piercing in over a year feeling antsy what should I get next]]></document><document><![CDATA[333 Restaurant Live Crawfish Bags 3.75 lb.  662-229-0020  Order by 7PM Friday for SAT pick up. @ Grenada, Mississip… https://t.co/KcCQe6xzTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[500 Million Digital Files make a movie. @KateSwanborg @NetApp is the company behind #HowToTrainYourDragon3… https://t.co/RttBiM2H7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wstafrican Unpopular opinion, skincare edition: tf are you wasting money on Botox if you can’t take your makeup of… https://t.co/3qTf9YBnKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce @Alcioni5 @evakoosiglesias @PucciaPatrizia… https://t.co/G0NUqcGIky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexbisconer Yeah I know that one probably blew your socks right off. Imagine how I felt realizing with only 2 hours left in the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stone Violated The Gag Order!  'Idiot wind blowing every time you move your mouth.. ' Bob Dylan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna know what year y’all hoes are going to find your own man and stop going after your friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just threw axes and hit a few bullseyes... WATCH OUT BOYS don’t fuck with my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[500 Yard Freestyle results:  🥇Chase Konstantakos, @ChaugAthletics  🥉 Daniel Vasque, @SpringfieldCHS   Minnechaug’s… https://t.co/m73mjHhvqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[can somebody give bryce harper his money today please https://t.co/PeLqdnHD79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @debratankersle1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @JackConnie @karenslinn43… https://t.co/kNmqvv0eZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captainbigbum @JoBonney303 She did glide when she went for that diaper! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromRightField @leeleebb21 @EmmyStar79 Okra and grits fall into the same category: 🤢]]></document></documents></author>