<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkTakano @RepAdamSchiff @MikeLevinCA @TeamPelosi  Why doesn't Pelosi like impeachment? She WON'T lead. One of… https://t.co/kwgUNwqP5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the night off right with a Hibiki Highball  #hibikiwhisky #highball #whiskey #japanesewhiskey @ Seven Gran… https://t.co/LtwElpwXil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penso politely telling Zusi if the leaguwnoffice didn’t hate the Union he’d be shown a second yellow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA Legacy of this man will be proven by far as the real president of Americans when he is done in January 2025]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimpleManRadio @chaseelliott @WilliamByron @AlexBowman88 @JimmieJohnson]]></document><document><![CDATA[G- is your art partner autistic? C- yes G- please talk C- he has helped me for about 5 years sometimes only wanting… https://t.co/WkZ2HOwEQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gagas_Cure @sebastianmperry it did. and cali rarely gets this cold. and it never snows in la, at least not in my lifetime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravi tutti to the @KCSChorus and @kcsymphony for phenomenal performances of @johnmrutter world premiere of “Fanfar… https://t.co/L9IYrYb8RI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great opportunity for a book review and visibility in the Australian market.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Princess #happpylifetessa hanging in her favorite spot on the couch. She is an amazing little girl, and we are… https://t.co/HNnRtSHHQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FDHSBookJockey Focus on relationships and encourage play! We’re doing this all together :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_icyyGod_ @LeVeonBell Bell needs a winning team lol but honestly he could go anywhere and benefit them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Providing some tunes for my @Redbull fam @HighRollerVegas linqpromenade tonight! ~ ~ #Redbull #GivesYouWings… https://t.co/ydGdhao4Jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Those 3 creatures need fired from congress. The 3 of them combined aren’t fit to be where they are]]></document><document><![CDATA[and forgive all by the resurrection...  Forgive me a sinner!  God forgives and I forgive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floppp3 @KingSYMMA @TheNotoriousMMA @TonyFergusonXT Your right how’s this?? https://t.co/RHyHRpuU3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sniktologist A really terrible movie from 1986. https://t.co/uEm4ptQZ11]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my tweets are cooked up in a board room by 50 something white guys named John amd are designed to appeal direct… https://t.co/rT34ttDDhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGrinnell_ I’m going to say they go for a run with them all. Now or never. Duchene would then replace Panarin next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[This clearly is nothing compared to the persecution Trump's base has to deal with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night at The Sportatorium in Paris, KY! https://t.co/NwnzH18hsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_manniello @DPLennon @You_Found_Nimmo @Pete_Alonso20 Forget the big picture we're at sometimes I think you need… https://t.co/lsvKjVXRyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: No. 4 #UVA 60, Notre Dame 54. De'Andre Hunter with 20 points and 10 boards for his second double-double of t… https://t.co/hEbCCcE5tZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL!!!!!! What a Great Dog!!!!! @ Prescott, Wisconsin https://t.co/IZnDDIeoEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manhattan . . #Manhattan #NYC #NY #startuplife #engineerlife #vacationtime #sightseeing #shooters_pt #olhoportugues… https://t.co/uim6jMV5vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Now this is a real national emergency and a big embarrassment to the country. https://t.co/SG6vUtT06F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_daniel @SufferinBa5tard It's so desolate in an abandoned amusement park kind of way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[muslim dudes been trying me a lot lately like their wives couldn’t live without them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever win something after sacrificing and working really hard for it? _ I felt this a few times. Winning big footbal… https://t.co/zEOTZR3afw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/yjhIA7niBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoy your tweets so much! keep tweeting brilliant beautiful child of God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any comments on this @deadmau5 situation that is truly unfair? We all have a certain passion that sometimes gets th… https://t.co/9SfpsTPTKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then this just shows how fucking lame you are and how small your cock is you fucking scumbag. Shoot yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels I’m sorry you lost your case. Or it was tossed. You’re a hot woman. God knows I’d buy your panties if I could.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to M2 Freestyle (feat @Hittz079) [prod by @1MallDidIt] by Don of CashOverClout #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/A7WP2Z3OSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Good to see the left elects children from all states to Congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RexJBrigger Those are solid picks. Menard ran well in race trim all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSzabados is truly a goalie of the people #QueenaGoalie https://t.co/Ek4jIKZPro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cricket ain't trying give me no days off @ New York, New York https://t.co/DYYXJE47pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAHoureih @MelanieBoisMD @smlungpathguy @raghupillappa @JenniferBoland7 @Patholwalker @_SaranyaS_ @TexPathol I favor synovial sarcoma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great tournament win today for @carterw78548348 and the Gulf Coast Waves! https://t.co/O3W14Uqt3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might have to save this rockets lakers game to watch how the rockets deal with actually getting officiated how they deserve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bosnmate91 @krosakrosakrosa @wyshynski That’s the key part is that they got nothing back for Tavares. NJ got to us… https://t.co/39Uqlt1ITd]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 3/03 day  HVL - Hidden Valley ep 💎 #acidsunday @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/CpMUoTkKKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Office tonight with Mammoth Tooth at the Mercury Ballroom with Jefferson Tarc-bus! #mammothtooth @ Mercury Ballroom https://t.co/wOZW3GwW7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travon @goldengateblond His entire press session was pathetic. I am so embarrassed. He speaks like a “not so smart“ kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelmercer @bud_caddell @madebymany @tommorton @RGA 🙏 This is refreshing. As I continue my discussions I’ve been… https://t.co/qLuolN18bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard not to smile around you @CandiceOfficial 📸: 3es____ #BandsUp available on iTunes &amp; Spotify, go get that!… https://t.co/WQ7LnHuzPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coached by Mike Bibby, who in my opinion will be coaching in the college ranks soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeschlossDC @TomFitton Recalculated their birth dates! They were born in 1885 which makes them 20 yrs old in 1905!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God does say that there are things that are good for us not to eat. Ignorance is not an excuse when it comes to sin… https://t.co/MLM0w5kacu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News: RNC tells Michael Cohen to 'have fun in prison,' as GOP readies war room to  push back on testimony.… https://t.co/WnxPXoybki]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to knit a scarf last weekend and listen to the whole #goldenhour album by @KaceyMusgraves and honestly it… https://t.co/1o9JszKiU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapSheet @Stroker_Ace_7 AB X Riley Ridley X Greedy Williams X Devin White holy shit 🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[The name Karl Lagerfeld rang a vague kind of bell, but since I don't give a rat's ass about so-called "fashion" I d… https://t.co/n5uf6eDCT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, if I had only read this a year ago I could have anticipated what PP was going to do. https://t.co/fu9IsE2GFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisyduhblack I was pissing, if I was going to take a shit I bet you’d be ready with your mouth open.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the Lakers don't want to earn a playoff berth. I don't think they want to play with each other any longer… https://t.co/08UIE605hK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I got the check, I tried to deposit it at an ATM and it was like, “No, ma’am. Not gonna work.” I had to go in… https://t.co/hIDp6s3x4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshua_Newman @AsburyParkPress Great stuff. Have to think showing against McDaniels was a factor. Hope that UA aff… https://t.co/234xM4IQ3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix 😎😎😎Reply soon Get rest NCIS 03 to 2018  lots more Rest star Startreks animated HD to. https://t.co/coeGDKi8zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smsaideman @Mark3Ds We can live with a certain amount of corruption. We can die on the altar of racism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haistanapa Amen. You don’t need to trick or test people in interviews like this. It’s a failure of communication o… https://t.co/KY7U9L9k17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coolranch4lyfe Public option would be good, universal public and/or heavily regulated non-profit private insurance would be better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you trynna get over a nigga and then he hits you with that “I’m in love with you” text https://t.co/Eu8THxwi1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I changed the date of my gender reveal and Adalynn’s birthday! If you weren’t invited on Facebook just message me!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Semi-dry. Semi-sweet. Middle of the road cider. Would drink if I was in the mood for a cider. - Drinking a Magners… https://t.co/wY2iGizstC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @WorriedVeteran Isn’t it the @GOP that is always talking about “good paying jobs?” Then they complain when they see them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind honestly, you think this unedited video is somehow a positive look for Feinstein?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new favorite quote. Thanks to @DCTurf8 for the find https://t.co/ZnDPQbMs7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orozcoo_o Ya bastaaa! Quien te está haciendo sentir así? Estás hermosa!😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Money is the most important thing.  Profit from scalping native Americans https://t.co/IMmfqWhT1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VamosConTodo Arriba @Rayados que triunfe y le quite lo invicto a - - @Chivas  en su propio terreno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiewattles here ya go Jackie, while we’re waiting for the press conference... https://t.co/Metxq2YtKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRANSformers by Mike Steele  Megatron: I can’t believe you’d try and betray me, Trans Starscream. You were my top m… https://t.co/DQGiKA0wfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really wanna be around ppl because the last ppl I was around almost ruined what I believe to be as my art 🖼]]></document><document><![CDATA[andreiarlovski working on end of the week GPP through several sled drag variations to increase strength endurance a… https://t.co/Usv46NFaAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Exodus by @SweetWaterBrew @ O'Hara's Public House an Irish Pub &amp; Restaurant — https://t.co/Q2WTvy5zaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What has happened to Mitch Hyatt!? Where is he!? He’s a great OL! Either he right team and scheme he would be a ste… https://t.co/XeMtDCRSSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/n5K6jB7E8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TFC_Memes @mattvendramini @Jasoninho10 3) this is so much better than older players tearing up a soft league for o… https://t.co/QdmZjjrIUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlacoyy1 @AlysaMariee16 @mimi_garcia18 @angel_fwtx damn yall got the whole Cousins Bbq on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least there’s one N American nation with a sane foreign policy. #thankyouCanada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see this group of players in their first game against that other team. Theyll be ready though 😈#HereComesDuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@what_s_poppin You’re a dumb ass. Too scared to even put a picture of you on your avi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck it. Might as well offer 10/$350M to Harper. But I'm told from Kenny they won't go that high, then Rick says th… https://t.co/f7RcszbtKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'M JAMES DI MARIA FROM WEST WARWICK RHODE ISLAND I'M A GAY SMOOTH SISSY FEMBOTTOM FAGGOT AND I LOVE TO HAVE SEX WI… https://t.co/9lqVdYt7pO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints - Siloam Springs AR https://t.co/w75pSlYEx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @qautumndaze Donald Trump, Fox News, and the Russian information disinformation bureau are all ful… https://t.co/7lTBzTp3eC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bob_burrough Nvidia's rtx ray tracing could do it, but not at a high enough resolution or frame rate for VR.  Also… https://t.co/Zl3hhZSMdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperPWCS Can you please explain why not a two hour delay? With a re-evaluation once we see what comes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is any fucking justice left in this fucking world, fucking Trump will be the next to go to fucking prison.… https://t.co/U3teWucmNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even worse my dad did this twice when I was younger but in my closet. My dad when he was drunk thought my closet wa… https://t.co/HYNUQwvL0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching bohemian rhapsody and if freddie doesnt have slicked back hair and moustache soon imma be pissed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep with one eye open.. gripping your pillow tight @ San Angelo, Texas https://t.co/5s0c8PhBwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SMH How did our intelligence community let the racist traitor get this far? How are R's okay with ANY of this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just slipped in my work boots... neither of me feet were touching the ground but I didn’t fall... 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoundOFF13 #ISUvsTCU  I said begin yr. top 2 bottom ISU is loaded with talent (best in 12).Also remarked it will b… https://t.co/InCX227ZMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarTrekHour We took #Discovery's #SaintsOfImperfection to the mat with #TheOrville's #Deflectors on this week's "… https://t.co/kfQGyjDOsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmsloves @elo_bajo @BradCrum5166 @BackhandedDevil @wolfbugs @shadowpwny @CPapouts79 high 5😈😈😈]]></document></documents></author>