<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Being in bed before 9pm is the best feeling ever and I hate childhood me for taking it for granted]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU MISS THOSE COMPLETE SENTENCES DON'T YOU????? &amp; MUCH MORE! https://t.co/CFTwaWRZbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sami Brady Dimera would get Ej Dimera to finish job on Leo because Victor becoming to soft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Fabulous Las Vegas!! Coming up in my @FOX5Vegas Awww Moments segment at 5:48am one of our VGK fans share… https://t.co/swiAJt7qRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Amar a la pareja no implica sacrificio y nada ni nadie es mejor que su compañía.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Talk about Criminals—- take a BIG LOOK AT HILLARY—- if you want to talk CRIMINALS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweet so Steph makes his dreams come true 😍 @StephenCurry30 https://t.co/1tYNBK5Tyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wear your superhero status on your wrist #pumped #wonderwoman #wondermom #setyourmindtoit… https://t.co/shs9fqLwwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @NBCNews This is what losers like you are worried about in 2019. Anything to stir up negativity. Find a real job to earn a living!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damesnpeacocks Thank you !! We all just spread the "Harry Love " here . That's what he's all about , LOVE in all f… https://t.co/znYGKZi7FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[😃🎈Happy Birthday🎉to the  💥Spectacular💥 @hklepinger , who I’ve made more fun memories with than I can count!  Thank… https://t.co/7qj8F5QTZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out for the joy-stealers: gossip, criticism, complaining, faultfinding, and a negative, judgmental attitude. - Joyce Meyer #Quote]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everything was great about the 80s - and if you don’t believe me, I challenge you to watch Jefferson Starship’s… https://t.co/dJ4KPVflK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I need to stress something though. When it comes to me offering all these little freebies, and I have to be… https://t.co/zU4VivNddR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four people dead in alleged shooting in northern Michigan, officials say  https://t.co/hQtLZJKF2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating outstanding 4th quarter sales with our Winner’s Circle!  ⁦@IllinoisUPSers⁩ https://t.co/fCxNQqjO2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athena from #variancemovie by taegenc - another version of her. I loved getting into those characters, exploring al… https://t.co/ElFagix3Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReadyForsyth Were our alerts on cell phones supposed to be activated for the state wide tornado drill today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think if i stare at my paper long enough it will start writing itself? Or am I hoping for to much?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is evil. He lies and they believe him. He said that they allow babies to be born alive and then kill them!… https://t.co/ukTv89uo2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[This class was supposed to be the easiest class but this professor is giving me hell 😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICYMI Easy Weeknight Meals on @TheMarilynShow! https://t.co/nN7dPMb9Hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl in my class started bawling out of nowhere today so I go over to see why and through her tears she says “she… https://t.co/SBzyDrpd7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting for our democracy is a new low. @LindseyGrahamSC it's a new low for you a member of Congress to continue t… https://t.co/8ozOhslKSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥B A L A Y A G E 🔥 #bomb #bombhair #balayage #balayageombre #balayagespecialist #baltimorebalayage #yelpbaltimore… https://t.co/hSYBJ41oYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Rihanna goes on tour, I’m buying a goddam floor seat. I don’t care how much it costs or if I have to go by mys… https://t.co/tG4atRc8Lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Oh for pity’s sake. You want to talk about morals when you have Yrump, who is a moral vortex andvyou… https://t.co/G7ZczakZ3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#texas #texasbebipolaraf #texasgirlsrock #texasgirlforlife #texasgirlsdoitbetter #rocknrollgoddess… https://t.co/rszhTY3GE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[running out of conditioner while u still have like half the thing of shampoo left is beyond triggering]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verbal bullying still most common type at Durham's Catholic schools https://t.co/IoYFF5SJyY don’t think a private e… https://t.co/FyTj1c4UfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, next.... 📸: @photography_amc @aaroncota  • • • • #thankunext #thankyounext #bye #byefelicia… https://t.co/h6dzbxHVDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andgoseek @michellehtweet @alan_maguire I’m telling my Mum you said that. You should be glad you’re on the other side of the globe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlenderBabes @Vitamix Yes! Truly great #Healthy and better way to  live #smoothie 👊🍓🍎🍌🍏 #Vitamix for @allirh09… https://t.co/NyXXl4An0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jay52442412 a morning view at Lombardi Lake. ‘‘Twas a beautiful morning. https://t.co/r80g4A4Xu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bajsw100 @a_dawn1102 I heard about this and I warned my 16 year old son too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejandrofsc @AlexBours O niñas menores de 15 años que han sido violadas y las OBLIGAN llevar al bebé en su vientr… https://t.co/XQU8Xed2f7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we had no winter, the spring wouldnt be so pleasant. #santamonica  #sunset @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/04TDiEq7dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a dusting of snow last night.  It makes for some interesting color and light around the lake.… https://t.co/0VEQpiSoGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[All because I’m too old for Saturday morning cartoons and am procrastinating on my return to the gym 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoannaBergerMSc A yellow-bellied slider, named Bob.  I love him a ridiculous amount! He is so funny when he is bas… https://t.co/72m0mXbUP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arrowp Pronto, já achei um vermelho. Vou mandar debitar esse na conta do Arrow e tá tudo certo. https://t.co/qZNEuf5Dwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum @SecPompeo @foxnewsradio Thank you Martha and Secretary Pompeo!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etta8247 I need to lose massive quantities of weight and stop drinking like a drunken sailor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to volunteer at the African American vets appreciation brunch and meet: Lt. Col Anthony Hinson (L) and 92 yrs y… https://t.co/TB4R3y8OBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low and behold, I was spontaneously granted the opportunity to pitch the beginnings of my #GlobalHealthStory on bui… https://t.co/BzLPUHwKLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lorianneaton @sylvainreynard @SerendipitousMC @RandomCran @BrownAngelEyes_ @solacemusings @loa717 @pamlangworthy… https://t.co/2uAhIx8sI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I finally joined in on one of @CAM3R0NPH1L1P's tea-spilling lives and it just reminded me of how boring my life really is]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized I have over $600 on my HSA card so all these medical bills I’ve been stressing over just got paid. BLESSSED DAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[got  my  new  camera fix s   I'm almost   done  to do a new  vidoe  abut my life  😀🙏 more  work in the moreing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need 2 girls who want to loose weight just by drinking coffee!   It worked for me, so it will work for you! https://t.co/uzt4OePzsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adasomg @realDonaldTrump .... CAN'T BELIEVE PEOPLE LIKE ADAS IS AN AMERICAN CITIZEN... ..THEY SEEM TO BE 'BRAINWAS… https://t.co/rFPPhBueC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have yet to ever change a diaper, but I still want to know why kids have to go through soooooo many?! Like I thou… https://t.co/hrXb7RYfqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Credit and #Repost @pnsorganizing with get_repost #Scripture on #CopingWithAnxiety #Anxiety #ScriptureSunday… https://t.co/brDS27flih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEigenrauchLF67 @jeffhiseredu @TCardamone67 @trdale Interesting article about a research-driven schedule. Sadly, i… https://t.co/qeEryMXmtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrganicRoadMap @debsknig @QuietGrlLoudWrd @monstervoyage @radiantwanderin @SouthernerSays @VParadisoBCA… https://t.co/NVfCLrc7c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayla Williams crossed 1 Mile to Go!. Time 02:06:18, pace 10:39 min/mile, est. finish 9:24 am https://t.co/ZaUuCRC5HW #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Frizzle 🚌 is back @DSASTEM today to celebrate the culmination of #ReadAcrossAmericaWeek 📚and the kickoff of our… https://t.co/QQc60cU6es]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaFoodies @KusmiTeaUS @KusmiTea @MadHattersNYC @MyVirtualVaca @The_Jenius @anywhereweroam @Sostraveluk… https://t.co/aVGUzkNTHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Your dad beat you because you weren’t wearing a suit.  He is a white supremist, liar and a Russian… https://t.co/WohJqwRJ2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccl1973 @NWSSPC As we like to say, thanks to @ounwcm, “Don’t be scared, be prepared!” 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rachelm76094992 @notbeccaalso @jennyslate I will but I think you mean wine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SohaKikano روقيلنا الجو يا #انتصار حاضر يا باشا ........ مين بضل بالخمارة ؟ 😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren: Officials have a duty "to invoke 25th amendment" if they think Trump can’t fulfill presidency… https://t.co/P8FJLpSBVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri - can’t understand what it would take to get DT out. Congress should act 2 impeach him be4 we end up the USofRussia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@climacus_anti @bethreinhard @alice_crites That’s completely uncalled for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe a way to solve the border emergency is to toss paper towels at it.  Just an idea...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleugotti21 It was a last min decision. If I ever go again, you’re coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little snippet of my new song “Redheaded Galactic Activation Portal”. I wrote it about my good friend Randa Fox.… https://t.co/lc1CesEDsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paleomexicano @willchamberlain She is just a mean,spiteful,viscious angry lady.Just what we don’t want in the WH.C… https://t.co/x06qy0eW0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned on the tv to watch @TheKidsABC but the bachelor is on! 😢 Looks like I’ll continue my In Plain Sight binge wa… https://t.co/54HjA52AqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause what's real is something that the eyes can't see That the hands can't touch That them broads can't be, and that's you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I read the pages my writing group members shared this week, and the feedback I’m receiving on my own pages, I on… https://t.co/EE3SYT0xft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt like a superhero in this paint!  Bangalore apex overdrive from @PlayApex 😎 https://t.co/f1UVd5rpna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jk11195355 @jupitorbacksUSA @lilangel2768 @AIIy4LGBTQ @instinctnaturel @LeonWhi63670221 @SwampFox214 @SBDSoultrain… https://t.co/PtPN780Uv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes but that event is really particular. Plus there is the best dressed  thing, you know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so fucking pale if the sun doesnt come out soon i might have to dip to somewhere sunny]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does the quote go again? Grab life by the hair? 🤔 Anyways...Happy Sunday! 🤷🏾‍♀️🤪 📸johnnymphotos . . . . . . . .… https://t.co/QNR961rbFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinityResists Trump displays all of the following characteristics of #Fascism  Trump is an authoritarian who want… https://t.co/cfOTwOwYew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann Soon her naval will be on her chin😀, Plus, she's starting to look like Cher. Do they have the same face doc?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we are. @MizzouWBB is rising to elite status. Losing 3 terrific seniors. But no rebuild, re-load.   #MakeItRight]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up with young white females being total cunts when they’re out to eat with their family]]></document><document><![CDATA[That “Liar liar pants on fire” LMAOOOOO Republicans are so childish https://t.co/KXjbK0KwCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xx23x3 You know she’s not going outside! But if she got on her side of the bed it would be nice. She knows when I… https://t.co/OSuiIIzVJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tomorrow I am going to the dr to see what in the world is wrong with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I am always making plans w ppl &amp; forgetting then having to cancel on multiple ppl cuz I suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many bad stories, so little time. You're the media mogul's gift that keeps on giving....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LongstopHill @SteveGrant67 Never too late to start an anti $candal. There's always a rich hunter whose life you ca… https://t.co/v9njsusKQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafiMaasai @NBCNews Right, you should be glad he was 3000 mile away.  Ok sista, gonna switch to You tube and seem… https://t.co/S7N0l8NbGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE TRUTH ABOUT NORTH KOREA! [DS] TRUMPED https://t.co/XvpKiTYJXd via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[you so fucking precious when you signal the fucking direction you intend on turning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please if you can donate!! This a safe place for kids! Dance school for me growing up was my 2nd home/family!!… https://t.co/jKXDFBQiYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally am so excited to for my Boston trip — wake me up when September’s here]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love #BBQ! Does the town or city where you live have options of places to get yours? We do here in #Orlando am I'… https://t.co/8w1daMnOoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drunk_Austen but kids are great if you want kids and if you don’t that’s a super awesome choice too! just a shame… https://t.co/mLUUlvau7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. For real-and I can’t stress this enough- find someone who you can laugh with. Like real laugh. Cheeks hurtin… https://t.co/pUuiQEfWbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s never tulle late (How’s my pun game, @nataliezfat?). I’m back after two weeks off of IG 🌺🌸 // 📷:… https://t.co/oN2LWCYnwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StFrideswideSq Sorry to hear this. Something so small can make such an impact. Cc: @united]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to Jamaica in the morning! It's going to be my longest flight since May. 🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_ebrard Los liberaron pero les robaron sus pertenencias. Pero bien por hacer un pronunciamento al respecto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeriHentschel @tristrash @MTumarkin @ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @barb71 @Lynette84649831 @nanafrey7… https://t.co/KLIfWr5FFd]]></document></documents></author>