<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr God is gonna stroke you down if you keep up this bullshit. You are a bald faced liar. Satan is coming for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHeatherEm Good morning Heather! Stay warm and have a great day. ☕️☕️ https://t.co/hnw9l0Jm6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are unwise to allow ISIS members to reenter Canada, regardless of sex!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why we need to keep and expand CT’s #bottlebill:  glass redeemed at stores is cleaner and far more valuable and usa… https://t.co/3xBjrNECn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a semi with a boot on it off Western.   I didn’t know they made boots that big!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze The President did the right thing and anyone in his position would have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pxlsicle @MoneyMerks @Swazi4 Sweet. We've got a league. I just PayPal whoever Joe tells me to for football so I assume we'll just do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe Reading FC is out of the relegation zone. Feel like they've been down there all season. Even though… https://t.co/rYZd7kp4wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leelaaland @PippinsJeff @TwitterMoments Hahaha. Mr. Pippens is a #botnik. They don't have kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @AskMrBustos to post 7 pics of my favorite books-no reviews. I’ll then challenge someone ne… https://t.co/fGvhYQ4qxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coaches and athletic directors PLEASE do this or ask someone on your staff to do it. Makes it MUCH easier to track… https://t.co/phm0ujb0kT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the pictures start turning up... @ Northfield, Connecticut https://t.co/uJqYvepKm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandaceTX It's going to be ok, I promise. He's going to pick a strong veep if he wins the primary. I very much thi… https://t.co/FvHGEgItD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @throwitupto9 We don't need reparations 4 slavery. As painful as some periods were, you can't keep rel… https://t.co/n89fdalwCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduate Tempe Biannual Award featuring Ulises Heredia https://t.co/KPQzFCbjPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousMMA @ProperWhiskey Sorry Conor! Had a few too many drinks ha. It's 🇮🇪 not 🇨🇮! Good stuff. Goodnight 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill The lie is a professional vocation requires work, i.e., preparation outside of “work hours.” This young… https://t.co/gNnEzfUPcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel also love to see captain Marvel busting in like batman being like "WHERE IS HE?!?" https://t.co/tQcnstZKfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[1993 SC The Swordsheath Scroll: The Dwarven Nations Trilogy Vol 3 (Dragonlance Saga) Dan Parkinson Cover by Tim Hil… https://t.co/Jcmny13cEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWS_MountHolly ljd-003 Germansville/lehigh 3.5” snow, light snow still falling 0750hrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I find this video beautiful. Inspiring to see someone not fear persecution for preaching TRUTH 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best #laundry assistants ever. #boys #book #read #laundromat #brothers @ Beverly, Massachusetts https://t.co/Glv1mZ5u9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just nominated @briewhitexxx for 2019 @XBIZ Cam Awards presented by @MyFreeCams! #xbizmiami https://t.co/0VPy2JzyIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In many ways, teachers are hardwired to look favorably upon students who remind them of themselves...In other word… https://t.co/GE5xs2K83p]]></document><document><![CDATA[You own how many houses again? BIGGEST hypocrite. I don’t get how you can vote/support this freaking joke of a cand… https://t.co/vndvDfduMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guy76251 He's been doing this for years, so he's developed menus and recipes as the need for them have come up.  H… https://t.co/Tc3JWKMFZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commuting OST.  #HenryWu #SymbolicJamz @ Ford Pky And Cleveland Ave Bus Stop https://t.co/LoPGlfPgBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_clown_prince @TakeThatStraw I do not think that Moses claimed it was a claim , you see you should speak about so… https://t.co/M9UnYtmhJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escucha #ElHijoDeVirginia @arturocanizalez @quebuena941 cuando lo indique se la llamada #9 para Ganar boletos farwe… https://t.co/AyBhxOeqsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the FuckUps! #viatec #fuckupnights @ The Duke Saloon https://t.co/DbiqpSoZNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gowser93 @FanOfDillion @jihadnasser11 @HarperData @DillionHarper @ashbrk5 Yes that is cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clashcitybaz @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Mueller, Rosenstein, McCabe are said to be Republicans, but they are also… https://t.co/3gVcayfqfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you run out of @traderjoes cookie butter 😢 https://t.co/dAHeadJw6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we move into March , thread on the various EU nations positions on an extension.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Day Party! Pool Party🎉 @kaylawaggoner with Me 3/9 @letzgitit at #taobeach Day Lets Git It inside… https://t.co/Zy24bb2apg]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Trump administration reopens their cases, Christian refugees from Iran land in L.A.: Nearly a dozen Iranians… https://t.co/sYrpmYwpi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend was 100% beyond my expectations. Already knew that I loved this city, but #NBAAllStar made it tenfold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen You're going to regret that when it's running on the damn wheel ALL. NIGHT. LONG. making noise lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the things I love about Mountain View. Leadership is always accessible in a casual way. If I wasn’t… https://t.co/IXxemLZzFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[El resultado de las consultas populares, independientemente de que apoyen o no las propuestas de la presidencia. So… https://t.co/yU4QCGliR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like deja vu... I’m tired of this thing but I know I’ll never be able to get rid of it https://t.co/rOR9nvhgnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keiran Martin with 1st place in triple jump and Trinity Norris 3rd in triple jump https://t.co/ZyeJNChdOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyRamirezWorld @FOX29philly @JeffFOX29 Thank you.  We’re happy she’s healthy and back Monday!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson last tweet.  I had another go in the right side of my brain and it tastes like poop smells.  Have a… https://t.co/Psd4f83Dkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Five or fewer: Throw together a quick meal from a well-stocked pantry: I have always admired peopl… https://t.co/oOkwxTfdZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The four-point plan #ForThePeople announced by Minister @LisaThompsonMPP today focuses on:  ✅ Professional developm… https://t.co/ptMtAXqERt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullTimeDEVILS This has nothing to do with luck. This is bad play from too many marginal players]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenCultureMMJ @MassRoots Slave owners did nothing wrong, they were simply following the law at the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bearcat_MPH I have no issue with UVA winning it, but how is it a good storyline?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FLSA aka make it so confusing to everyone that no one will ever figure it out or ask questions 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT jaredcollazo_13 epic_collazo #TheCollazos #Familyties🎯 #myworld How time flies🚀 #NootherLOVE #Mybabies😍… https://t.co/PxmiwUj8E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSchiller123 @TCS37 If you freak out over Weddle being cut but you can't stand the idea of losing Mosley, someth… https://t.co/O1WZfN67Xt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just warming up barhelixdenver.  Had a great time🕶🎷💪🏾 big thanks to my bro barryoverton for the 🎥🙏🏾. Book me now… https://t.co/KSXQTQ9Nu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dadeallday1 I used to dislike 5 Guys fries, but I’ve come around on them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysonoffense @sagacious_scamp @FlGatorKing1987 @RyanBLeslie https://t.co/kwgZHTSWwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most impressive thing I’ve seen on the internet since Al Gore invented it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Heye1 @Sclinahoo1 ? 51.6 from the floor, 47.9 from 3, 2.3 assists to 1.5 TOs, 6 rebounds, and 1.3 steals as part of his great defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brand: @Yuckofficial // designer: @bambamvworld https://t.co/TUmWSgf1DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young love. Brings back memories to before I needed to borrow a “Days Without An Argument” meme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caitfoye Are you good with stars yet, or are we still working our way upwards through the solar system?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scjones1006 @jamesshive @TheSeedGuy_ @fountain_kelly @eazzzyyyye @scjones1006 We just gotta do it! https://t.co/Wk94QqbSPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of Debbie Mann Gibbs, trail blazer, but 1975, SMFH, CHARLOTTE @sportsoneclt cluboneclt #charlotte #queencity… https://t.co/qwGAAXUnP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Wanda Nanibush, McLean Centre at the @agotoronto, for a conversation with James Sinclair, as they explore thei… https://t.co/zUVgCKeLAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JunksRadio Pathetic is more like it. Don't chastise the younger players for not giving effort when you are not being an example yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t i just sleep for 8 hours straight for uh one fucking night lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalesFan93 Well some good news; it isn't who you think she was originally. Bad news is even I'm not too sure who t… https://t.co/tHxwoW7RBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOIN wearefaed @jewellasvegas FOR ANOTHER #flawlessmonday 📲 440.487.5000 4 FREE ENTRY ON MY GUESTLIST OR TABLE INQU… https://t.co/SFJHWAubV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jueves del recuerdo...#TBT #TUFESA...#Chamarronconluz...acompañado de la #Jose... en Hermosillo, Sonora https://t.co/PHzu2BdSYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also go fuck yourselves I’m tired of being there for people and being forgotten about afterwards... this is why people are selfish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bro_Pair @fart The Ole Miss Plantation owner, hands down https://t.co/eF38wrxtdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatpixxiechick @tarotfairy @TheRightMelissa @charliekirk11 You. Are. Ignorant. Study more; tweet less!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random burger kiosk #losangeles #inglewood @ Inglewood, California https://t.co/rIJMHCRJ1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JotaInfo Em qualquer país desenvolvido do mundo, em crises, se cortam salários, funcionários, pensões e aposentado… https://t.co/5xVkN5G2VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do rural populations experience greater worry and fatalism about #cancer? https://t.co/Ug4redHOF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco @netflix I ask this question every day. You can play me in fifa while you wait though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IGFA Es un gran honor representar tan importante institución mundial de pescadores en Argentina. Ahora a trabajar x… https://t.co/aLEazFW2Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let them discourage U plugs run for it get back on the good ship #CollusionDilliusion full speed ahead ignore… https://t.co/npJVVn52vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks want me to hit the club tonight. My back, hips, and knees hurt. I ain’t going anywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LogosMedia01 You just platformed and gave a blow job to the the beta white male that is IN LOVE  w his identity po… https://t.co/2333CDrOVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennThrush “The Optional Emergency” by William B. Turner https://t.co/qgCwHzflJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_LosR @BenAndWoods @MiserableSDFan @Ken_Rosenthal  @RyanCohen24 @TonyLosoya89 @DancingFriar @backthebrownSD… https://t.co/LJnKmgQyac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que no eh tenido una relación....por qué sigo enamorado desde hace 4 años 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did @Jared_Carrabis ever do to the @NFL? He wasn’t even a part of the #Brady4!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinandbean @DJOmarKhan Only the ugly and unpopular kids would have to bribe others to come to a party when I was… https://t.co/5Ys5Sr1sBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Investigators Know Why Jussie Smollett Faked His Attack, Report States; But Did He Stage Even More? https://t.co/g8QfW31s5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that, we go 3-0 on the day and take first in our pool! Good game @UDSideshow and thanks for hosting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Oh fuck the fuck off #russianbot. Captain Bonespurs has wasted more tax money on vacatio… https://t.co/BIHz7dYU2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Match Marketing is hiring in #Thornton, CO! Read about our latest #merchandising job opening via the link in our bio: Delivery route Driver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @realDonaldTrump doing this on purpose? Yapping through tonight’s roast on China @colbertlateshow. #blameobama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhuber4 I already have a Flashseats account, Looking right now, Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Moon tonight is between 5,000 and 8,000 miles closer to Earth than it usually is at closest approach. Since it’… https://t.co/wVVNONYa2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I want to know the this McCabe has been charged with his crimes? I want to why the FBI agents aren’t losin… https://t.co/rL08ZQPL8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evvrydayaccount @meganalexandra5 and a great drag character. just a very lazy average woman named Susan 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_H yah. It’s not bad despite me hating sugar free ones. I miss Winter/Plum already :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gibbymcdibby Not without a good dollop of high fructose corn effluent involved you wouldn’t. Basically they’d tast… https://t.co/fQrl7VgDiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dogzaddy Adorbs...I saw Vampire Weekend years ago when they played a private party for a client.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandon_drtran this is the type of thinking that our design phase needs to live and breathe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GameChanger There is plenty of evidence to support that claim! #BakerFamily #SharingIsCaring 🐾🚀🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefRunningNkd Typical loser mentality... "it's just a game". That'd change if they'd ever win again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jordan Career Highlights (Hall of Fame 2009) [HD] GOAT 🐐 https://t.co/qUmBblvFjI via @YouTube]]></document></documents></author>