<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MexTheSwindler He just came back so he’s still getting back to rhythm. They can still make the playoffs.   Top 5 a… https://t.co/JEsIgkJf8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace un par de años me pregunté , si lo que estaba haciendo me acercaba a lo que quería de la vida y me respondí NO… https://t.co/1sNm1YJrHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkronWineGuru @ccatmpt @Cbp8Cindy @joneill55 @suziday123 @cowineco @FionaMorgan79 @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines… https://t.co/YRSiyyRqiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancingofpens anyway now i know those babies and all their little sibs that were born after i left so my whole fee… https://t.co/UeQ92StpvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelgelandSvein They will support at least 2 Dem candidates in divisive manners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kasalanan din ng setter. 5 times sunod sunod sa kanya nadedepensahan na nga. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[taylor swift with red lips and a yellow background has sent me to a *place*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of Emily and her hard work!  So thankful for all of the teachers and educators that have poured their time, e… https://t.co/V0gKjv9X7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPingalore @LynetteRomero @libertechan  Don’t like it ... but will get used to it. So happy @DavidPingalore is… https://t.co/pQDNMaKyqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If used correctly, flexible seating serves a great purpose for all our students 🌟🌟🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brightly50 @JustYourKarma @lisarinna Why would she think LVP is accountable to her. Please, little girl, go tend t… https://t.co/jeoY2Ehyp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t fist pounded with a homeless man, are you even a New Yorker?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I joined “Nextdoor” because I thought id hear about fun parties and BBQs happening on my block but instead it’s con… https://t.co/3PAxVAJ8pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ballerina or Rebel? Do you have a Ballerina or  Tomboy? https://t.co/SooCLYAEbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omaha_scanner Agreed.  I'm surprised at how many times I hear a call for an accident or person down is made by som… https://t.co/Ib7ubuxqM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm grateful that young girls have more opportunities and less stigma these days. And that my mom told me earlier o… https://t.co/DAr3ouUrGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misskac love and miss you!! We definitely need to plan a trip this summer! I’m only like 8 hours from you guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[It blows my mind truly when people call me “crazy”. I’m like one of the most peaceful person I know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfa Tucker the mother*ucker. Is a total idiot. He could not tell the truth if he saw the event with his own eyes.… https://t.co/XioqOAFMbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamwaynegilbert @SamsungMobileUS @Samsung837 Awesome, those are some sweet pics]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we fight back, we win @KatrinaPierson #CPAC2019 #CPAC https://t.co/haytqVGXgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiveDurkey He looks awful - Pale, haggard. Nothing like the person his WH dr. was referring to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet He is just darn right cute making a complete ass of himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to supporting and empowering women throughout the world. I’m proud to work for a company that’s owned by a w… https://t.co/ND5qz7teCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulk Order Stylish Sublimated Leggings from Oasis Sublimation Women's - Bottoms City of Toronto… https://t.co/fsF3c1QLvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBillingsclass @CoyoteRidge_ @mrmatera @missmac100 @HeckAwesome @tishrich @MrPowley @Gameboydrew @MrNunesteach… https://t.co/LYQnC0kCr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qtf Es una gran líder magisterial. No me gusta su pacto con el macuspano, soy sincera. Pero, ella nunca debió habe… https://t.co/DMfQpSeTFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheesy valentine's day movie to watch with cupid suggestions please! It's his 9th birthday, so we're  cuddling. https://t.co/54bL13oV1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m designing a large black scarf for @FierceStitch while listening to this DOPE playlist. #Chopped… https://t.co/bIQgEwuaqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it will be her year, too.  #LoveUnderTheRainbow @hallmarkchannel @JodieSweetin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evrybdylvschls @brittmcdonough5 I thought I blocked people. Chels took this to the next level]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The Trump work habits seem to be pretty scarce. Is Trump Organization going bankrupt again? Is it t… https://t.co/z0BaQaJpXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[DETROIT.  WRIGHT STATE IS COMING FOR YA MONDAY!!!!  Y’ALL AIN’T READY FOR THE RAIDERS!!!!!! #raiderup https://t.co/5Q9s3D77kU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for helping me reach 25 followers! Who else do you think should be following me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Instacart I was available and waiting.  No one even called me when you cancelled my order!  Then you charge me a cancellation fee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be at the airport by 6am and it’s currently 4am... I should probably pack now 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop playing and get serious about learning from the best dancer to dis day!    Mary J. Blige]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cldarnell14 @calebverret @scott_mistrot This sounds a litttle more interesting than the yards this weekend 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally bought a pop socket today after my other one literally fell off and suddenly i feel like my life is coming together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicolette_O Yes, there is an annual event at Versailles in France (not Diner en Blanc, something different) where… https://t.co/qTA6IqvD3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedo con la luna realmente esta muy brillante y preciosaaaaa!! Gracias Dios 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a year ago, I was frustrated with aging. Of course it’s better, maybe, than the alternative lol 😂. I was in c… https://t.co/3WUtYRjucY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleyscomett That’s been me for a while now too! Sorry you’re going through it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so interested to see what @Fahrenthold thought of the hearing today... so many mentions of things that either… https://t.co/X49p7Iaozh]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOOK SHOT Cover + Blurb Reveal!  Coming March 28   ***Enter the Giveaway here*** https://t.co/liskgbSdM8 ♛ LIVE Ale… https://t.co/EPpKu6QdaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thisislove #metcalfehornetsever @ Metcalfe County High School https://t.co/PzclkSJ20w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhanaNYC Ayo queens get the money long time no cash, caught up in the hustle where the guns go blast.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my @ryka #violet mules. So warm despite the falling snow in 18 degrees. #madeforwomen #rykatribe #scwmania… https://t.co/jO7NOh66gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's National Random Act of Kindness Day! We spent all week spreading kindness at school talking about ways to brin… https://t.co/PRHL5SlL1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo super stoke about this that I had to shared! Follow @tribunaloftheg1  Courtesy of powerrangersnow for sharing… https://t.co/TOuuodH9IU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO I am White...what a  Beautiful Black you are...God bless you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media’s treatment of female candidates is already sexist https://t.co/WetGBmYXZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Rutherford oh big surprise the school wants as much money as they can possibly get from their students 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmspool @jessicaivins thanks for the shout out! Understanding your customer for real is the cornerstone of good pr… https://t.co/yaXyrcluNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely in love with my caramel hair... can’t wait for my next appointment with beautybybrie_xo to go even light… https://t.co/lQmLhMI3gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[President trump should declare a day of insanity to get med treatment for democrats, if their is any.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New items in the store!! . . #tyhdesigns #theyellowhouse #shoplocal #shopsmall #clock #pictureframes #iloveus… https://t.co/eM0Feubxhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being a part of this amazing team of strong Latinas!  @CHCI #InternationalWomenDay2019 #HERstory]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do when you have a super quick trip to IN...have a reunion at your sisters new salon of course. And let… https://t.co/Ca0YrRW7Yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious about non-acadmic careers post grad school? Check out the @SACNASFL #alternativecareers panel tomorrow @ 5:… https://t.co/HIFmqqoaQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeih!!!  Monterrey gracias por 4 buenísimas funciones!!! DIVINAS!!!! https://t.co/CC97Wdh9QF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sandra Oh and Jodie Comer are saving 2019. I don’t make the rules. https://t.co/XIWzdU3L4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Hey, sweetheart. Didn’t anyone ever teach you to ‘Just say NO to crack?!’ 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMercadoPhD @DrBrendaArteaga @HCDEtx @HCDE_TLC So incredibly thankful for you @DrMercadoPhD !!! Always an honor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards Lucy’s beautiful and deserved better. It’s not a damn habdbag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to be with fellow Lobos and New Mexicans at last night’s @UNM Congressional Reception. Thank you, @UNMAlumni! https://t.co/F7AlChhjsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThAlMeArCrEq @ReneeCarrollAZ @cecki We speak of these things, being the watch dogs for our country yet our FBI has this information!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Well, I guess we’re not gonna be friends, then.”  “I guess not.”  “Too bad. Because you were the only person I knew in New York.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Female directors make one bad movie and they're exiled from the planet.  Male directors make 20 bad movies, engage… https://t.co/4gd7AB30Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganScorpion @AmyCrossBooks @womensart1 @Martina @jk_rowling @valmcdermid @bindelj @barbaracrampton… https://t.co/U8xPx0BW7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gawd I just realized Luther is dickon tarly #TheUmbrellaAcademy #GoT https://t.co/dLvNoYJRLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob_dodson Heck yeah—I’d follow that too!  Though I gotta say, if there were a Twitter account too, that would als… https://t.co/4f8IhVkCX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday so this sweet girl! Love you Ayssa! 💛 https://t.co/06lMO9j3kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[my music app teacher just said “ i’m slowly dying” and I just slowly looked back and just nodded at him in agreement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Kaitlyn, for being such a fabulous leader and advocate! #REALpaidleave #PaidLeave4CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland What I know about the Coast Guard?  I know they ain't getting paid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 watching your testimony I believe every word you say.  U speak the truth. Stay strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowy walk pictures from last week on my way to work. #snowpocalypse2019 #PDXSnowpocalypse2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orlando City Stadium - @orlandocitysc for New York City FC at Orlando City SC in Orlando, FL w/ @baztastic77 https://t.co/0KcCorDSVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both would be ooey gooey romantic but Libra could potentially feel suffocated by cancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamar Alexander says never has a president asked for money, refused and got it anyway. Never before have we had suc… https://t.co/xWoLlvo8qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HashtagIT  #supportTeam #schoolsupport #buildinghealthybrains #emotionalwellness #socialwellness… https://t.co/ZFkmFQYrFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[having brothers prepared me for how much Kid1 and kid2 whack each other in the nuts. wife1 is just left in shock an… https://t.co/wdD7NvJUIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a ahole. We should sue @JussieSmollett just like #CovingtonBoys are in process of doing @MarkDice @AP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Protect Alaska's Bristol Bay From a Massive Mine! https://t.co/MfZifCWWlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought a fractured spine from a slip and fall at the @Delta skyclub would cause so much pain  if anyone was… https://t.co/1gOzeyYLHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never wanted to just fit in &amp; please other people, I always preferred to stand out n make myself happy. 4EVER &amp; ALWAYS!!!🙄💘🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefanZehetner7 @IFAO123 Still some controversial thoughts presented.  He talked abt stratification on notill; Adv… https://t.co/4HnFisdT0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt Well deserved award!!! We are so proud of you! 😍🙌🌻😘 https://t.co/5TStbsQGmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cobbycobb_UK @EdwardPentin @NCRegister God will take care of it if we can’t. We all need to pray more and heed the messages from Heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betty5280 @TheView @BernieSanders As of Feb 26, 2019 Bernie Sanders has not released his tax returns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing my Nutrition class homework this late at night makes me so hungry]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i had a dollar for every “if i get __ comments i’ll __” on facebook, id have plenty of $$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just in awe of his battle, and even more being able to see a literal village support and uplift him and my mom.… https://t.co/Reea01BmKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittypurrzog Honestly wish I were as into anything as some people are into the ability to misgender folks on a pri… https://t.co/tLDnyp5Qzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RpSensenbrenner Maybe you should lay off the booze and learn to vote Republican!  You're nothing but a RINO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laurabellee63 @hoppinmama5 @AngelaClar1 @bedevilme666 @gator4kb18 @Libphobic2020 @BlueWaterPalms @RealMNRepub… https://t.co/uAqiN86CFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorPless1 @Mark_Orphey @hhshoyafootball @ChadSimmons_ @dareu_i Keep em coming Victor!! 💚💙🏈💙💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should be careful to get out of an experience only the wisdom that is in it and stop there; lest we be like the… https://t.co/IdKRM7Xkba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerseyFinFan Like I said. I read it, so it can’t be true. Everything’s a smokescreen.]]></document></documents></author>