<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What kind of person am I anyway cuz I don’t know anymore what flows. Besides my blood that flows what flows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anoche andaba de pensativa en la peda y se me ocurrió una idea que puede ser mi próximo negocio a largo plazo🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the cool think is that photovoltaics are so much more efficient now than they used to be. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Price_isRight17 @funder @npetey We will need 6 bottles of wine for viewing party. Nicole brings her own sparkling grape juice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Well, now wait ...are inflated asshole years counted the same as human years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i become more and more obsessed with Lucy every day. look at this happy girl 😍💜 https://t.co/Dq6LpNsmEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD I wish people would tell me to learn to code. I’d surely make a lot more money than I do now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The resolution dealing with corporate donations to the #DNC has been referred to the 2020 Platform Committee to eve… https://t.co/tvzCoa0yrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[80s? In February? 😟  Oh wait, I forgot... it’s Alabama. Of course we have near record warmth in the forecast today.… https://t.co/2aDlQGeStT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then why are you allowing undocumented pepole to dubble the classroom size of students in stead of documenting them… https://t.co/4kMTVgsNAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clean check and recovery!! @sharks_girlslax #empirecup2019 #laxdefense https://t.co/vOsZwggic7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metro Atlanta Payless ShoeSource locations prepare for liquidation sales: https://t.co/RiJTHWliso -- The timing of… https://t.co/Z03j9MrErp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ParentsLife: Planning the summer in February so you don't miss camp deadlines and best travel rates. These simple… https://t.co/WX46aWRsjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmUltimatePred You know he's just saying of it just to get ratings, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This fucking malinois has officially been the only dog in the history of dogs I have been unsuccessful in potty training.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin is taking me to Michigan on Sunday &amp; I’m so excited to get away from here. Even if it’s only for 2 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @ShawnL519 - Drinking an Oscillation 015 by @finbackbrewery @ IDFWY  — https://t.co/YNgZvfLW7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReconIntell @KamalaHarris The invading colonizer wants to see papers. Try the Federalists #Decembrists Your theori… https://t.co/YC0zUIza1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a feeling the old Carol is gonna have a chance to really go off👑👑 #TheWakingDead #TWD     @mcbridemelissa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, my love! 💕  Cheers to this being a great year for you - the year you will become my husband! 🥰🤗 @ H… https://t.co/eQoBD1bdNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alro Steel Corporation is looking for teammates like you. See our latest Warehouse/Logistics job openings, includin… https://t.co/8IYsMvOK0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHMU_Banksia @WoodwarddianneJ @mikecoulson48 @RandolphTrent @BitarDeen He does have the most wealthy Sheldon Adels… https://t.co/9uoqs2XTAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, this is the truth. @ Kansas City, Missouri https://t.co/N0mi1Hqleh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #LosAngeles, CA! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: shift supervisor - Store#… https://t.co/JG1GKBZYdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour Next week is shaping up to be like the last scenes of the Godfather. Cuts of everyone getting their just… https://t.co/fiaAVNCmdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Wehner John McCain may have been a Vietnam prisoner of War, but he was also a traitor/backstabber during his… https://t.co/y0GXrryp7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made no headway with @dish. Warning to followers... don't ever get @Dish. Charged to return equipment they brought… https://t.co/WJ6rlPrUcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, guess whose poster is in the front window at SARDI’S. There are simply no words. https://t.co/8iV67HzelR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still enjoying the fact that the pep band was playing Africa by Toto coincidentally as I was entering Draddy on Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino People who elected this woman have got to be horrified at themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our journey begins!!! #aloha @makeawish @MakeAWishMNY #thisisrett #warriorprincess @ John F. Kennedy International… https://t.co/ImbhTC2ipk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heliocoptero @AwayFromTheKeys @mikenedie @Cern_lXXl @Glad2bAtheist @PolyRhuagh @zypisfy @yourmumspants… https://t.co/BwHYEmAiEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw the most beautifully branded brand experience for FRACKING and it did not feel good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After church vibes... @ New Birth A Place of Hope https://t.co/XyMBSLuaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKronader @ABC @GMA Triggered?  By who?  You?  Who are you?  Absolutely nobody.  I said what RR was most likely th… https://t.co/Kugk0VJ2hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The purrfect #Caturday 💖 Who’s with me for sunbathing and biscuits? #catsofinstagram #CatsOfTwitter https://t.co/8WdCktyqWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt  The “never-gets-old” #avocadotoast for #breakfast or #lunch with a #homemade #tea with #cardamon #seeds… https://t.co/xGbTPQ80jW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Horny0nline @conor64 @willwilkinson @ishapiro @walterolson @SenFeinstein Yeah, well I’m just hoping they don’t joi… https://t.co/bUkbH7eJss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flcwershawn @bIuemymind @larissarosaIes @GlRLMEETSEVlL @saveyourIove @JonahMarais @whydontwemusic 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish someone would have caught me on camera cus that shit was hilarious 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbyRyan @joshuadun I like to send you pictures of my Golden Retriever because Golden Retriever parents love to s… https://t.co/WVOvGsIWbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Besides spewing hatred, advocating violence, lying, cheating hiring criminals? You mean besides all those things?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was just pouring like crazy and completely stopped in 5 min I love Illinois thunderstorms]]></document><document><![CDATA[TLBC: When the morning started off a little rough so you have to take a brief mental break b/c this is only the beg… https://t.co/GSepsc6udn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump More like protecting himself because he knew he was working for a crimin… https://t.co/V2ZqspEip2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready, St Patrick’s Day Weekend is almost here ☘️🇮🇪 📸 @lappeyyy  Plan for an ALL WEEKEND CELEBRATION 🎉   3/15:… https://t.co/dRw0lADR5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenTedCruz Then shy do not they listen and how come the names of congress who paid off sexual harassment suits not… https://t.co/UHa2hCDCPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#freezinforareason   The 19th annual Polar Plunge at North Avenue Beach is TODAY!    Proceeds go towards the Specia… https://t.co/M9yc45gPou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicole1124 @tammy_maga @VickiHugg @Aug1405 @WarlordDaddy @savannahsmith88 @Mark22336699 @prayingmedic… https://t.co/f3BBQUHcKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media is not truthful. They continue to spread conspiracies that delay moving forward to work for our Country i… https://t.co/2PvPTyeowk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachesbikes My song would definitely have more of a later 70’s feel of Meatloaf songs... “Paradise on the Dashboa… https://t.co/ocRnlU1CWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[lemme just uhhh put on a ton of undereye concealer to disguise the fact that i only got like an hour of sleep last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiegarcia2468 @gorillarilla Raider Nation For Life! We hope you stay @derekcarrqb https://t.co/il8ruSzL5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrandmaMuses @Kokomothegreat I'd bet the Trump family is asking their lawyers to negotiate w/federal and state pro… https://t.co/vRcdRK0VE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered my first legit leggings as pants 😂 need something more then my yoga ones or work out ones for “going o… https://t.co/rYfXFBkYrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess sometimes one person really can make a difference. Just by showing concern or noticing, it helps greatly. I… https://t.co/Ot7xampobn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not flexible enough.  I'm not skinny enough.  I don't have enough time.  Sound like you? If you've ever wanted… https://t.co/7fV569Fy7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panarmstrong All the more awful that these people are taught to  define it as brotherhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump Sounds like U. Don’t deserve to be protected!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just #twoqueens  👸 hanging here #aquinnahriley #thisis3 #uwstoddler #playdressup @ Upper West Side https://t.co/oSg3gS4wrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally started talking after losing my voice for a week. Tell me why I have a new soft voice? #raspsgone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaanDerthaal @novacarerx @Orthofacts That was the cheapest quote that I got before ACA and it was a shitty plan. H… https://t.co/oaf3k9crMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Avon, IN, check out this #FacilitiesMgmt job via the link in our bio: Plumbing Pro at Lowe's]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resign, save your tax dollars you pay, Impeaching a lowlife-can be expensive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvyShoots @howloften @HERterus @WildChild69 @Happywife151 @rcasonr @Mothersdream @OwlFoxVT @teachchemjenn… https://t.co/dh0ocltSLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[HERE, TEXAS 1869. I's heart broken. I gets married n looses da boy. He don't be my boy but he was my boy. Lucas be… https://t.co/6bk3LcWWqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meldhensley Similarly, I’m thoroughly obsessed with Dreyer’s English: https://t.co/SOB2UBDbR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pgzwicker @DoaneUschool @AutisticsAloud @AutismNS I just bookmarked it..thank you again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapFriendly @AlisonL How future consideration became a thing https://t.co/lMsj9cLZR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[😈 idk why but this was really satisfying to discover. Like def one of my fave eras of Rihanna 😈😈 https://t.co/ZqOfzxhRwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone who didn’t support me in nursing school, thanks for making me try harder 👍🏼😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Safety Coordinator (Automotive Industry)" at uJoynus? Apply even if you're not a 1… https://t.co/PswpqjYXw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Be authentic! You get what you give! @BobbiJS77  this is what we were just talking about. We need to encourage… https://t.co/VcaACd425T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @thinking_woman1 @Outlander_STARZ If I didn’t think you were amazing I wouldn’t be here..  simple..  😊 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@litzycruz_ i’m more amazed by the way they’re ripping the pineapple off the core 🤨😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingLRG_ So I guess I'm lookin for a disguise?? https://t.co/oHCy2Sizns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalms 9:7-8    But the LORD sits enthroned forever; he has established his thr... https://t.co/RJiyUIIC99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarionledger Best response! Yes respect their freedom of speech and move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚 Day 6: I accepted a challenge to post the cover of 7 books I love:  no reasons or reviews-just the cover. Each ti… https://t.co/FKii5ACugY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwenLigaya Ligaya the mere fact that u r mad about my tweet is enough for me to know who lost this battle.  Rubber… https://t.co/5pNRXI9SD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met some awesome people at gamechangerwrestling @ Voltage Lounge https://t.co/4pqMMWu5u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifewiithemily @nbcsvu Too many to name but I am really enjoying this current season alot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harold对红叔说的一句话非常扎心了。 貌似我曾经也是有这个问题 You want to know why those closest to you betray you? Why you are alone and hunted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: “We anticipate the case will be resolved with a full dismissal of all charges,” Daniels’ attorney, Scott Sk… https://t.co/q39aPTJxQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meredith Smith crossed 3.1. Time 00:27:22, pace 08:49 min/mile, est. finish 10:31 am https://t.co/HeU9jtivCR #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breaknbad @PaulLeeTicks @DonaldJTrumpJr I'm a big fan of harmonies in my food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic young men and me - cheers to you all! @ Risibisi https://t.co/jYvHv6mmK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save your money and do your research until you have enough money to begin trading.]]></document><document><![CDATA[كلما تستعملون الآي فون تذكروا هذا الرجل العظيم. على فكرة, ستيف جوبز  تم تبنيه بعد ولادته من اب سوري و ام ألمانية/سو… https://t.co/s26pMrioWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[AN UPDATE ON MY ANNOUNCEMENT… https://t.co/ITsHdJALzj https://t.co/cE5LRq210G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathieuJuneau HAHAHA! Les deux plus jeunes sont énervés sur un moyen temps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeniferr1garcia You can’t even commit to a concert we planned 3 months in advanced, but ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @ThomasCarlier10 @nagel_donald @MrKnow_Iamright @CarlEll00638874 @James62568621 @DwayneRay9… https://t.co/osJ8wXAwHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggcatlover @allisonisemo actually my mine!!! intellectual property brothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[~ Jessica Fabela, Realtor 🏡Coldwell Banker Pacesetter Steel 🔵 #texasrealtor https://t.co/LNdLphr1Mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where you at pops...?!? On vaca Gracie...ok pop @ChicagoEBR https://t.co/gNbfYNjF6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[In order to learn the most important lessons in life, one must each day surmount a fear. https://t.co/LjZi3uoKf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebekahDenn @kristenmillares @washingtonpost I checked in the Washington Post today, but the article was not there… https://t.co/7qWhQR8Bb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACollinsPhoto @HamiltonPolice @McMasterU @HPS_Paramedics Thank you! Looks like it was 3 consecutive games beginnin… https://t.co/sodXRXoPDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Theatre marquee in the Richmond District, opened in 1923 and inspired by Egyptian architecture. Very coo… https://t.co/Fq012p5IHq]]></document></documents></author>