<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Terry Truitt named new CEO of Anderson’s Flagship Enterprise Center. Starts new role on June 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnonymousGamblr when will we get GOLF each way bets for tournament outrights and FRLs in the  USA? @betmybookie]]></document><document><![CDATA[A winter storm forced Omaha to spend least night in The Ralph. Story on how the Mavs and UND/REA's staff made the b… https://t.co/ymF27DLO01]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Start with your stressful event, the symptoms you will experience, and then write down your response to that adver… https://t.co/6B7eWZhlpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat She was killed riding her bike on Marcy Ave in Brooklyn possible hit and run]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sappermartin @ashleynhinsley @Krm1285A @alley167 @Cjamesb4u @Jenn198523 @roderunner01 @cheechablunt @troublehead99… https://t.co/V55LCoaeYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cleantechinv @mims @ramez Very true. And to be clear, we already have the technology today to eliminate emissions… https://t.co/r5eK2TugNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHOtheCALL @RealCandaceO God bless you you are one of the angels from heaven that is speaking the word of God and… https://t.co/WLkvB6IIR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor @AppSame The Democrats are not for anything positive. They are a Cancer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard I wanted to let you know I usually stay I when elections come, if the dems don't address increasing r… https://t.co/QsJg5MxOZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do yourself a favor. Take a sick day on Tuesday and watch this movie if you haven’t had the pleasure of seeing it y… https://t.co/Hs4OFP4DUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDave2You @NevadaJack2 No, if Manafort was a Dem, he won't have even been indicted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought it was that bad but when I see it written out like this I can’t stop laughing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone one in the world could have someone and I’d still somehow be single]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Arenado will earn close to $200K on a day off for rest. That is a good day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wwhitehead88 @RandyLHallman @NASCARONFOX @amsupdates @mikejoy500 Had Ryan not come from northeast modifieds, Joy w… https://t.co/EyrDzPtcKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birds among the sculptures. #montaguepark #sculpturefields #chattanooga #flockofbirds #believeinfilm #minoltax570… https://t.co/gaEPHvjSnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Daily Caller :  Trump Claims He Will Get $23 Billion For Border Security From ‘Other Sources’  https://t.co/zlxW2dYXOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t be Christian if you allow women to speak in public. You can’t be a Christian and celebrate the Pagan trad… https://t.co/n90pGjWVM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost GO time! @Cardinal_Hoops @Cardinal_Hoops https://t.co/03iCCgein1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittyselitte @GarysShorts @lindseyadler The defense quote is interesting? Saying Greg is better defensively at 1s… https://t.co/hmTsrwj9j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m gonna need these doctors to hit me back for this appointment please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PortableTrevor Haha I expected more tbh but that’s what they gave us. So I guess we gotta deal with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bronk @soulcycle @onepeloton You will be the first fat blotchy teacher ever, #breakingbarriers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting my @GoldenKnights all the way from Little Rock, AR! #VegasBorn https://t.co/7gJjiknlyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another pair of my shoes accosted by a dinner dish tonight...  This time, deciding to vary it up, I dumped Pho on my Nikes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsomniacIce Yeah, like before it starts, after the intro and in the middle of the episode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/ssa35y33kY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This train is delivering @Minecraft voxels to Columbus. https://t.co/bApu28m2N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF: Hunt 33, @NHHSBball2018 26. Wildcats cooled off significantly after that quick 7-0 spurt to start the quarter… https://t.co/FrzPyDByuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[ʜᴜᴍʙʟᴇ.  Arguably the most misused and over used word in the English language.  By definition to be “Humble” you ar… https://t.co/DZzuGHxWga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly and the IHSAA is weak, does this mean anyone can play in the state tournament or just the ppl IHSAA want!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ @GreatLakesCon @MacombCollege @JRsBBQ is this a 30 minute Q&amp;A or abbreviated JR Report? https://t.co/mcWQnUaFHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so small... this fascinates me to no end. I've been watching space documentaries and YouTube videos and ther… https://t.co/oJPLeeCi1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever let someone else's disbelief in what's possible stop you from trying? It's not a great feeling... May… https://t.co/94Fm9Z6QMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kurt0411Fifa @EASPORTSFIFA @NepentheZ @EA_GZaro  I took 6 weeks off of FIFA 19 and it was such joy.   Came back to… https://t.co/Kmqx2O5f85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJoodger @tonyposnanski @IStandWithAhmed I would lose faith in humanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters THIS NOTE IS INTERCOURSE for ALL SYRIA public And privAte LegA-L TENDER IntE-R:  CoURsE… https://t.co/EbdGThF2CX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@championsleague  christiano@antogriezmann diego.costa oblakjan @juventusfc mariomandzukic @PauDybala_JR @atleti  M… https://t.co/sncYnifTcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SDSU MBB head coach Brian Dutcher previewing senior night: “The rivalry vs. Fresno has been good... It’s been a co… https://t.co/O4UPLPEYI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a piece of shit but your time is coming Donald. Worst president ever. https://t.co/ec4xb2iacX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PorscheFanCO @chelseahandler I think of it as being a lot like chemotherapy. Metaphorically speaking, at least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatsupAmericas Did you say the same thing when Obama put kids in cages and separated  them from their parents? No,… https://t.co/Y67VN6UVnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mentions millions from local communities for new facilities a billionaire can pay for alone. Then when they… https://t.co/1bzGUZaZny]]></document><document><![CDATA[one day, he will betray you dennis @ Living Desert https://t.co/i3uOBsAYwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[1-0 North Branch Vikings over our Bulldogs w a power play goal w 3 minutes left in the first.  @TCUTitans @TCU2905 @jeffeppen @TPreisler]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about that Inverted Triangle by Shane? What page is that in the Kama Sutra? #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliemason @BubblesVampire I so wanna be at one of these bars!! So cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff We have more concern for YOUR lack of decency, character and integrity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a team!!! We are so grateful to all the leaders, team members and support from G499 we have received this Plan… https://t.co/h4xoPC6WRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want everyone to know that I just went to McDonald’s right now and i bought a homeless man an egg McMuffin!… https://t.co/7cLxjzIYz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great meeting with the executive members of Unity in the Community. Looking forward to working with them… https://t.co/vL5yikYHwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine thinking this is a good tweet. Sick profile pic btw. I hope an earthquake opens a hole and swallows Addison… https://t.co/anJbTZNYUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weren’t we talking about this the day we were riding through Pine Ridge? @abrauerjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt @chirodale1 @TheStevenThomas @realDonaldTrump And liberals claim our system of public education is t… https://t.co/mqD1OFBQO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_Mann_ You are a sick piece of elephant dung. Oh I’m sorry , that would be mean to the elephant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It truly was a great TEAM win.  First Quad 1 dub of the year and it was good to see the chemistry on the offensive… https://t.co/ScWD2TJp5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkwessel @WBMasonCo @bostonbikeunion @StreetsBoston @WalkBoston Now if they pledge to stop parking in bike lanes then we’re good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d ask for a burning up pt.2 but Idk if it’ll be as good as the first 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[My students are developing @PBProject proposals for how to spend the $2k @NYCSchools is giving them to improve our… https://t.co/LmOuhJ5Cb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[An @AARPMD first, tomorrow I will address the #MDGA Veterans Caucus about Military Members, Veterans, their familie… https://t.co/RUOV0KmXzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Ooltewah #TN  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/AiPsZQkBuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that he has finally made it to Vietnam I hope weak @realDonaldTrump heel spurs don't start to bother him again -]]></document><document><![CDATA[He asked me why I had cash and I said “selling cocaine” and he said ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Med Kit Giveaway - Over $550 Value https://t.co/NPxgB60fqY via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight #Classics these youngest won’t understand @MasterPMiller @CashMoneyRG but dat #OnlyGodCanJudgeMe title wil… https://t.co/5y5qBCOCMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, we're clearly willing to look overlook a lot of shit in our leaders. If Canada doesn't want Justin Trudeau… https://t.co/YjfQ5YcT00]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I lose a little piece of myself ..... when one of my eyelash extensions comes out 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know most of Beyoncé’s routines and I’m waiting for the day this skill pays off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still waiting on who offering this kid... I wish someone pull the trigger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the way out of a political crisis isn’t as hard as it seems ⬇️ #LavScam #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckWendig @SamSykesSwears Wait. The Paprikash are only twins? I thought they were triplets. Sweet Paprikash, Hot… https://t.co/DE1BQ31zZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely stunned to see this because Kent works his ass off every single day to provide Indy with great sports ta… https://t.co/iPmycxVptu]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY GOT TO MEET @LucyStoole!!! ❤️🦄👑 #queen #smartbar https://t.co/ceUHvI7eXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jay28833174 @CrimsonBoomer @RMConservative The majority of illegal immigrants enter the Country on legal tourist,… https://t.co/Yim9MeWlVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago’s middle class, once the backbone of the city, is declining so swiftly that it’s almost gone. https://t.co/dszaE1gMyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBrock This is one of my favorites from her. “It is only us Gnostics here, and Goth Deb”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dak DLaw Coop Byron Jones   Jerry has tough decisions to make.   🤞🏼  #CowboysNation  #DallasCowboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday brunch with the birthday lady. Happy Birthday Mommom!! - Drinking  The Perfect Disguise by @dogfishbeer @ Th… https://t.co/ZkiY3yZsXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see MY FAVORITE BAND @youmeatsix kill it in philly tonight. 5th time seeing them live (just saying)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este sábado en la noche, adelanta tu reloj una hora. Para q juegues “agusto papá “ https://t.co/Mqc76xL8cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @dennis_goodwill The cartel guy who oils guns makes more than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early Provisors Framingham meeting #alwaysnetworking #needcoffee (@ Bowditch &amp; Dewey in Framingham, MA)… https://t.co/e7r3VyKfvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bramm4Braves22 @JonRothstein Look at their resume as a whole . VERY impressive .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4lisaguerrero @TeamBadNewzSon @NYDailyNews If you want to say that I can easily say the laws cause sex traffickers… https://t.co/YAsNWeCymp]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF ANOTHER JEWISH CHARACTER JUST LURED THE NAZI PUPPETS BY LIGHTING A CHANUKIAH! 🙄😒😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo Even if u buy Schlatt’s sampling for inaccuracies BS we can’t accept a corrupt  &amp; criminal potus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to watch the new $300 million dollar man in ATL last August. Only hitting .313 with 25 jacks then. https://t.co/6lZSRu7IeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrisElkins I am interested in this word, but cannot find the proper link. What is the simple test?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining @kevinmccabecbs on @AZSports to talk recruiting, NAU, all @AZHSFB news, and @ralphamsden dislike for pineapples.  Tune in at 10:15!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece on Pat Moscaritolo who has done so much for Boston and still lives in the house he grew up in East Bost… https://t.co/zeW2D70JYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwapanna I don’t even block him lol I let him see me @ him on my story and tell everyone what a lil bitch he is lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianmdallas @Robopz @KipHenley Not easy being us. People don’t understand the torture of genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to see my man @tcherry002 cleared to play and get back in the court. I know he’s going to help push… https://t.co/yWFArzzLPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ernie_plumley @ReneeCarrollAZ I totally agree!she made her choice now live with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuscularDevelop @enevid #LSCSports TO ALL THE #WorkOutWarriors #GettinAfterIt #LetsGetIt  #BodyBuilders… https://t.co/DoEL2ptNSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man who tf looks at harmless shit like this and thinks “yeah this is a useful rule change”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gimmejada Wooow i wasn’t talking about you though 😂 i was just practicing for when somebody fine fine come along and quit sleeping on me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comicstorian Haven't they done that with other characters or at least put them in the realm of possibility of doin… https://t.co/TzTllKeZOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Majestic Star Casino &amp; Hotel - @majesticstar777 in Gary, IN https://t.co/5PeNuuuASW]]></document></documents></author>