<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@reidallyboutit Only if it’s preceded with HEY GUYSSSSZZZZ. Then yes, you’re on YouTube.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi If corporations are people, how do you arrest a corporation? Therein lies the conundrum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Oh Sarah.  You’re such a foolish woman.  You lie and spin for Trump.  Do you really think he is going to… https://t.co/1Gu1qBMSKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews It’s the Congress, not a protest, they ambushed her when everyone know Mitch McConnell is the problem. Tea… https://t.co/3OLKFQVAn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why #USPS always be lying about they “attempted delivery” when someone home and no pink slip left! 😡 (@ USPS Post O… https://t.co/gRK4PQqIaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone on fb said “whoever tucked her ears in her wig needs to be fired” and I didn’t notice TILL NOW https://t.co/GwBvzh4s7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billpeduto Thank you for leading the way. Haters gonna hate. Time to adjust the second amendment to today’s way of life. Not 1776.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe supported many ceremonies at Children of the Earth and #RBRussell over the years. His work and support will for… https://t.co/Icrqysxi7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our people are what set us apart from other carriers, brands, and retailers! love this investment in our amazing fr… https://t.co/px9z0vV2WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird bribery - high stakes bribery.  there may be less than 2 yrs left, but omg how much damage he could manage in that time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part of being friends with guys is watching girls treat them like shit and them not even seeing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump My house is still rotting from mold and @Nationwide  #notonmyside thinks 5 thousand dollars will f… https://t.co/X9cAxgQgNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice eyeliner can lift your eyes and accent the window of your soul! This client rightfully loves the color of he… https://t.co/Szyauhtenl]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the 115th Congress (2017-19) - In the Senate 9 people of Jewish faith are Senators, 8 of which are Democratic, a… https://t.co/LTMtfrpNzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Marriott SpringHill Suites in West Warwick, RI https://t.co/mIxqB75RYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louisiana, you where great to me! 💚🐊 #brucethealligator https://t.co/kbtYlCcPLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeCombsUpdate 2017 Stagecoach  2018 Camarillo, CA for @KHAYCOUNTRY  2018 @MorongoCasino   @lukecombs 🙏🏽 COME TO… https://t.co/BPaUZe8n2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatA1sauce @lovelycharityy Do you remember when we would sing “walk away” at P.E ALL HURT 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[All CBSD schools are on a 2 HOUR DELAY, 03/1/19, as a result of the inclement weather. AM kindergarten will not be… https://t.co/ktFenmZ3Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy makes a lot of sense. Listen to his interview podcast with  @PreetBharara too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao Ricardo came home high a’f and tried to tell my mom he wasn’t high when he had a lighter in his hand!!!!!!!! https://t.co/qbXI1Z2tfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not been to Disney with my bffs in so long and I CANT FREAKING WAIT for next Friday 😭😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday night service with Bro Rusty Ellis Peace @ Lighthouse Baptist Church https://t.co/EqsbvVZ84r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone come out to the @OneidaSCSD Literacy Night!! @SCSchools @kmessler1 @belleshpgrl https://t.co/HvofvkSd7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I agree that refs make bad calls, booing really doesn’t do anything for me. I get so embarrassed when family… https://t.co/B3rm2HTXZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate I can't be there in person, so I LOVE seeing @AikenPublicSch Lead Teachers sharing with teacher from around… https://t.co/7ESubyG4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPR He will appeal to anyone who is a member of AARP, Republican or Democrat there is still the middle majority]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hated seeing this, but everyone needs to be educated about abuse of all animals. Thank you @WhitneyCummings for y… https://t.co/aaIDoeLrPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are very fortunate to have @OpLunchbox as a partner to increase student and family access to food. Truly… https://t.co/HCRg7ARaMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to kill some zombies with pool sticks while listening to Queen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ᗡ O O W Y ⅃ ⅃ O H | hands down, still the best place to hike in all of LA at 7 AM. 🏆 https://t.co/0nLLPwl6xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @AMVSR @ThulRob @jonz970 @ValsaPal @bigk20171 @rudeger11 @QThePatriots @Sequencer16 @smokey02cat… https://t.co/OdTjJaDTtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy, en el natalicio de Gabriel García, me emocionó la noticia de la serie en Netflix “Cien años de soledad”. Deber… https://t.co/vj4ZM2fQT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merry123459 @JustinTrudeau It would be nice if you could vote for most trusted media source.]]></document><document><![CDATA[she smart. She been living rent free AND making a bag off the Kardashian name?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_djdurel @901neesie @amberwelchh @lilbbyems @mulanmonruge @sgrate_ March 16th!! GANG GANG😝 https://t.co/AAZdnS4ub3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting at the airport feeling blessed and grateful to do what stirs my ❤️ creatively with @AngelaTalley We had suc… https://t.co/hstB9r7Ipy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have definitely seen all the wedding venues in all of Washington state about 18 times now 😫 and still can’t find one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The JA Trade Show is open for business! Come support the business endeavors of 5 teams of young #entrepreneurs at… https://t.co/rGvXXp8gRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats say Michael Cohen's dramatic testimony escalates need for Pres. Trump's tax returns.… https://t.co/nlasrUXHI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraBareilles @JessieWare This Podcast was such fun to listen to! Almost felt like I was in “the room where it hap… https://t.co/n60f4xtFZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalmath Shultz, like every other billionaire, just wants to avoid taxes. The systems that helped him build h… https://t.co/vPWYFGzf4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fuck my boss hasn't been here since Friday and the second he comes in he gets bombarded by everyone lmao chill y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHResister @seungminkim @TimAlberta @Ilhan Imagine how her colleagues in the House are beginning to feel.  Their w… https://t.co/NJ6NCd4dVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to see a star is born asap bc I listen to shallow on repeat everyday and it gets me so emotional]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apple Hanging on to my 6 cuz I can charge &amp; plug in headphones at the same time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nation_myers @DaleJr88FanNate @JudyJ31830202 @ToddTPrice24 @chevychevelle48 @laura24fan @jonesbrent570 @kross700… https://t.co/BxnConI3iL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hit my dude over the back of the head with a police button and he said hold up B you need to bring the for-play d… https://t.co/kWdL0TnlPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ODOT crews loaded and ready to go! Now all they need is the snow to fall https://t.co/6Fwibcgt0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[uh tiktok star update I just gained like 650 followers last night and I have no idea how what is happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was younger  I liked secrets  though I didn't really have any.  Now I'm older  and dont think secrets are as… https://t.co/IlQYG46vDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eagleyez317 @R3CLUSIV3 @J__Vicario @momalley2112 @barstoolsports At the end of the day Magic has more control over LeBron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanurbach @GothicBlue @CaroleBFleet @krassenstein Maybe different customs, Jonathan, but sacrilege is sacrile… https://t.co/5mu0i6fZGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Save your empty thoughts n prayers for when you n your clan family n the rest of your crooked cronies are behind bars!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of us were at MBS setting up the tifo until almost midnight...just saying.  Some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maddysunshinee5 If you’re talking about the shit that happened Thursday night then you have no idea all the stuff… https://t.co/mPfiK5IqeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an amazing interview today with Sarah Elder of St. Joseph Museums. Historic photos of Wyeth-Tootle Mansion, M… https://t.co/nTO4hbg7H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porsche has next-gen batteries for longer-range electric vehicles coming next year, says CEO https://t.co/DeJKbNTGC6 via @FredericLambert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjoseph7777 @Unseen17 @dscc @dccc @realDonaldTrump never thought of that but of course it must be true for many in… https://t.co/h8RDKZ2it3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sesame Chicken served over cauliflower rice 🍛 🤤😍 Recipe is below👇🏼💋 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/E7097xM1J2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 ...... Trump has done "nothing but condone and incite violence". Fixed it for you. #Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spoke with the business manager for work before I moved so someone outside of the mess knows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesMill @AOC Aren’t you embarrassed to tweet this? Do you track down where other congresswomen live? As her cons… https://t.co/b4SWC6wSKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbledsoe Hope you’re well! ❤️ life is hard sometimes but it doesn’t stay that way forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax Compares Himself to Lynching Victims https://t.co/hOiWCwgKIj via @desktop.  What a piece of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never followed the Bachelor but I am in between shows so I’m giving it a whirl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I completed the @GORUCK #RuckYourDog 5K #RuckingChallenge 🐕🎒 https://t.co/7GQB3oOn28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Groupon yo where’s all those lovely Pittsburgh country concert deals!!!? We’re in need out here]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏗Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🛣Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🚘This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/8EDYJo4Hcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at apartments on trulia because apartment fever is a real thing, and I got it bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey And so would unborn babies if you So called doctors would give them a c… https://t.co/z0eXmZ4wvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ Jazz where is your lil fast Azz? The last thing you should do is get your parents upset as much as… https://t.co/bO00gUGohl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuntDebT @CatWheater @lynnv378 Right. She’s a grandstanding egomaniac but that attracts a lot of DS people I guess… https://t.co/y8frgbCaPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a fun afternoon at the Career Fair 💼 @ Whittemore Center https://t.co/nk7VQ7Uwy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KHancock4TX @brysonbowmanMD @txhealthplans @texmed @TMFtx @Burrows4TX I know TDI is working hard. They are still r… https://t.co/GeXaUTK1Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talks_dj @RayGareth @jbuck0 @HuffPost Well, now you know that’s not what feminism is about. There’s nothing emascu… https://t.co/sOmoBlKB4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1) Hard to pick one! Online because I can do it any time.  #CatholicEdChat, #edcamp, books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time change is messing me up but I love that the sun stays up longer. eeeek I just want it to be summer☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmadisondior @AlexaRain_ I feel ya, I hate covering up my lingerie with clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one!!! Let’s goooo Gauchos!!! Keep Grindin guys!!! Love you Ar’Mond]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esse babyanus é um porco imundo, traidor não só do presidente, mas de toda a pátria]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch some hangers just fell by themselves in my closet we not playing this shit nuh uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cheat on the one who would give his life for you , your not “that bitch” you are a bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mayank_P_Grover I keep reporting Wohl's accounts as they pop up, and so has many others.  But @TwitterSafety &amp;… https://t.co/1TedK4SDuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call or text me today if you are ready to have a beach house in beautiful North Carolina!… https://t.co/jlF8TpoQxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie's bombast now facing more rivals, more media scrutiny  https://t.co/sSb2JLGEiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Ruben Reyes and other progressive judges are making a huge difference and saving lives. I am proud to call hi… https://t.co/ivC8B3gV7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hlimper @mixovida @bethp_DI @research_dee @HullPam @boehmleanne @kimunertlphd @laurielovett We are so lucky to work with you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Novus_niveus Yeah, I agree.   While she wasn’t my favorite character in the beginning, she grew on me through the… https://t.co/Ns7h9B8LHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only trying to Influence others but they wanted more than that privacy by Hillary!! @JudicialWatch… https://t.co/5YQlbNG6Ux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lt_gray He reminds me of one of the Wildlife officers in Rhode Island.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismiller3223 Reality ain’t even a thing rn also I miss you when am I gonna see my fav boo again let’s get lit m… https://t.co/vS4NgSNGc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeHenHen I don’t care for this man.   However, this does not bring me pleasure.    When we find humor in somethin… https://t.co/Te2ljmDPf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[and I’ll never get over you until I find something new, to get me high like you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NL_LHo @Harry_Styles #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[some boy next to me said he drove all the way to auburn to get broken up with :/ bby no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchyWife1964 Same but the rest of me is catching up. https://t.co/nrgQY5VS0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo @SeaveyDaniel you need to design a #ColdInLa hoodie!!!!! @whydontwemusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes please! Jalapeño Margarita to celebrate #NationalMargaritaDay. The best are at @BabaluKnox https://t.co/Kgu2oZJXNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews Why did main stream media run this story over and over again without any evidence! Joke is on MSM a… https://t.co/GePyiRqeSK]]></document></documents></author>