<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[How does that compare to the $65,000,000.00 that President Trump has cost America in trips to his own golf course a… https://t.co/algLAusO73]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed the Parent Lunch Bunch today, you missed a great opportunity to help your scholar with math!]]></document><document><![CDATA[State to state but I ain’t touring, straight to the bag is where I’m going 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAKelly0001 @atholton_bball @hcpss_wlhs I’ll be sure to provide a bunch of updates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of #sxsw which did not suck. From town halls on cnn to late night (or morning) pizza to @realdonaldtrump twit… https://t.co/kN1WBhQFCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leandro you can not shoulder someone in the middle of the back especially on a yellow....c’mon bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Provocative case by .@jeffhauser  on need to stay mobilized in the antiTrump coalition. Complacency or resignation… https://t.co/tGloytpg9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelama_himself @benwakana @LillyPad Ah. Now it’s becoming crystal clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistaMcGrimey @XXL Dawg mfs don’t realize how amazing this blessing is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoyawolf The Army uses Microsoft PowerPoint to develop and staff combat operation plans that kill people. And I’m… https://t.co/iQivYOkBTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Securian Great to see your billboard under the score board at @B1GWrestling tournament. Proud to be your partner i… https://t.co/2DEIjeM7Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bill_slawski If I get one more spammer offering DA of 50 or above... https://t.co/VT32ZxasRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sinopec Coonc and PetroChina are impacted the most from this move that’s a component of China’s energy diversificat… https://t.co/q5mFAsGs0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotNational @kmckenna63 I thought they’d dropped the paywall today.  It’s asking me to subscribe before I can rea… https://t.co/UcXxtlkv36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juddgreenstein Just watched the second chapter of the documentary yesterday. Couldn’t stomach watching both back t… https://t.co/AgtTFlv2Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG... the singing crystaltmcgee1212 did tonight!!! Her crystal clear anointed tones pierced through the atmosphere… https://t.co/e54FHRIIQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bron prolly recruiting KD, Kyrie, Ben Simmons, KD and Klay honestly lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deepbarot @John80198852 @KevinMa84437030 @247Sports I could see that happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluesManBuckman Not saying I’d ever do it. Honestly at this point I’d let my kid do whatever he wants besides be a… https://t.co/XKnylstXd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USC1620 Maybe Josh likes hard egg yokes on his burgers, but prefers soft, runny yokes on his Cobb salads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UntouchableVick to paraphrase Rick Pitino:"Roy Jones, aint walking through that door. James Toney aint walking thr… https://t.co/Qe9jzLVMYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It won’t make any difference to his Evangelical base, he could eat a baby in front of them and they’d still vote fo… https://t.co/fWRg7J2VKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be real, the best part about Valentine’s Day is the fact that all the candy goes on sale the next day and I c… https://t.co/JaaW7tan78]]></document><document><![CDATA[TMI continued: Being 70 is no excuse. I cannot let this stand.....More squats, stat!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memosoto Ayer también escuché a Nelly Furtado en la radio y me acordé del @CoobyMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embracing the Power of Less - Educational Leadership https://t.co/SRGRWHqcWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dseater @MayorJenny @kcexec Elliott Ave has plenty of cars there... always funny watching people try to pass on th… https://t.co/5wvncGTxwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clark_2live @amm6266 And dardi in the rari!   And ride the electronic Bull]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Really seems to me the liberal left is playing politics, because every damn one of t… https://t.co/wRXlETM8il]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a mother fucking rock concert!!!🔥🔥🔥🔥🎸🤘🏼🤘🏼#KISSARMY #ENDOFTHEROAD https://t.co/OtIoKlRjsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JQ_Jared @codyjsutton Big haka guy... I respect it for sure. There’s some really cool ones out there man]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 shows today.   You definitely don't want to miss this GREAT show!!!  #RAMSPride #SESDProud #KDdrama https://t.co/LdI1rcZURV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want the farts of some men I sexually desire to smell very good to me and very attractive to me. I want to sniff out their assholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaptistBlogger Seems like there should be an historical marker here somewhere. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look another #HollywoodHypocrite Elitist telling me how I should vote &amp; Think 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local hoop tourney @ewctigers hosting Gulf Coast Conference Championships - @jcjackson904 with us now.   https://t.co/4yJbwDHkk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marcus Hunter on the brutal beating of Duanna Johnson by Memphis police and the politics of violence against black… https://t.co/4zcukoqtqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJCarafano Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @FoxFriendsFirst w/ @jillianmele and @SchmittNYC Great job on @FoxNews… https://t.co/V4NQEw3vtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycreegs Let me know if you want to come down the Shore this summer. I’m sure we could put you to use...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenim51 @ericbernal01 @Melissa42322791 @melaniepayneTHD @JRRocker84 @Tommygun0509 @mdavila44 @metwiles Great job G.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bernie_Rubble @edgarmomplaisir @culturekingspod Your graphic is irrelevant to this situation.  Because there is co… https://t.co/ZXux0ZW8vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorker @JohnCassidy Where the HELL is Congress? Digital Book Burning Must Stop! (GOOGLE, FACEBOOK, TWITTER. YOUTUBE CENSORSHIP IS EVIL)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VergilDen You can rent it online for like five bucks. What are you waiting for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Eagles have plenty of needs entering the offseason and can’t address them all in free agency.   That’s why I s… https://t.co/QHSKDtges8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody check out  Mrgentleman lifestyle podcast , episode 2 - love is love ( Valentine's day episode) right now… https://t.co/yRQ0ImFnZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather I always thought you were better than this. What an ignorant dumb tweet this is. I always thought politi… https://t.co/hVr9KUvSSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will never allow this nation to become s socialist nation.  Our children and their children are worth more than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSamGraves  Better update your zip code list. I got a mailing today but my Rep is Cleaver.  (64119)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems pretty safe to say the Minter injury cements Vizcaino as the guy for awhile...in today's Closer world, Arodys… https://t.co/zCwovpQhL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBarchard @ryne_jones Idk; I guess we’ll agree to disagree. I’m more upset about the Tate move than anything tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing good luck to everyone involved with Just Add Romance, premiering soon on Hallmark! #justaddromance… https://t.co/bQJ0HlRssx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency  #president #wall #mueller keep the #feet of #trump to the fire because no one is above the law… https://t.co/A6uwzOYVsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyretjd @guarofern @IlhanMN Yea let me run a poll quick, we should do it through surveymonkey. Oh nevermind there… https://t.co/2phgR8n41E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annkozma723 @techcoachjuarez @EdTechSpec @TeachingTechNix @kmartintahoe @lantonha @EdTechAntics @EdTechGarcia… https://t.co/bFcmDmmd90]]></document><document><![CDATA[Online tix are done! If you want in tonight you better get there early because there will be limited tickets at the… https://t.co/eMWiukp2mO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't look at it anymore. #bad #slack #logo #splat 💦🍆 #android #samsung #homescreen | Even without the purple BG.… https://t.co/stPCGYpUkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpinionatedLab @ThisSteveGuy @LeftwardSwing @mnmanofhour Folks, in Eastern NC, it is a BIG deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An elected official speaking to the people she’s supposed to be representing. More than a little disturbing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless Sad but true.. so sloppy, so careless.. they honestly have looked like a young immature team the past two weeks 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I forget what I'm saying in the middle of a rant, no one seems to notice unless I stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting from negotiating perspective. Green new deal is unpalatable to many so why not make them pay a steep pr… https://t.co/busWcm91gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s clearly hard enough to get snow totals right one day out... so let’s not pretend like one deterministic model… https://t.co/qdcrH608YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishofBandW @_mario @nklongmire @CHSommers @USATODAY Plenty of men and women are in that role.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work craziness kinda helped keep my mind off of this.. but RIP to the Rave King, and one my greatest influences gro… https://t.co/5JUoR84lyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, probably the worst service I've ever seen at @PandaExpress   Middle of lunch, over a dozen people in line and… https://t.co/ZYMSl7c70v]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can concentrate on the past few months is money &amp; lifting. Something needs to change 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOS CUELLOS BLANCO FUE CREADO POR EL HDP DE GUSTAVO GORRITI CON AYUDA DE LOS ROJOS Y CAVIARES DEL MINISTERIO PÚBLIC… https://t.co/MY9AItd8LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewC95857546 @tarun26atheist @ERICTR0N @TheWestonMike @Soapbox_Atheist @ThinkAtheist If there is a scientific o… https://t.co/TKIjzTtebe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needed this... 💟 Back in India, Radhika Ennis was badly burned on both her legs before she turned 2. It left her un… https://t.co/MpxobMxttk]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUU WHOOP YG Playing from: E-40. ::::::: Your arrival was askew. You lacked common sense. Quadraphony had arrived.… https://t.co/OvAhLe50np]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylineZ_TTV No judgement here! Start with the prequels, then the classic trilogy and then was the new films. Also… https://t.co/ioYCL6P4Ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Member of Well Regulated Militia fails to safely store his gun. 3-year-ols is shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooking and baking for the Emmanuel Dining Hall in our SSC 100 and MAT 010 learning community! @ Delaware Tech SGA https://t.co/7lY9RYZsih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougBaldwinJr @playercoalition @JOEL9ONE @TorreySmithWR @MalcolmJenkins @USATODAY Here is a novel solution to an a… https://t.co/DnrGGZot49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackOBoogie I was reading this when you got Jo out the house and was like wtf. To the point I forgot to say some… https://t.co/lwAkEtUYLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintLouisWBB Terrific players and people.  It was a privilege watching their careers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Jose average salary: $84,229  $7019.08 per month  Well above the $6000 per month needed to rent an average apar… https://t.co/Jx8in2LqbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost What a confounded asshole in the WH? Delusional! Dumb! Despicable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Batista the perfect heel. Triple H heavy ass grunt was funny. He felt that shit in the back of his head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorr_harwood I agree but after what I saw yesterday has me thinking twice]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a player of value at premium position. You maintain all the leverage you can in a trade scenario. So yo… https://t.co/0RJSIfGjo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah but I guarantee those dudes can’t attack a cover 2 or decide in 20 seconds to go for it or punt!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faixa cão preta #oss #osu #cpmma #joshjistu #evolutionfightteam @ College Park Mixed Martial Arts https://t.co/SioQzWfn5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great event @munaacp! And congrats to all of you took home awards. May you continue spreading greatness on this cam… https://t.co/px7hihiDsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zaffino @KGWNews I'm loving it at Mt. Hood Roasters in Rhododendron. 5" of fresh snow and 34° https://t.co/rIvutyLCem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo el partido on mi hijo y mañana el clásico regio #ViernesBotanero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotSoUltraCapo I’m glad you’re staying positive. I wouldn’t be able to. Louisville will be an important part of ML… https://t.co/lMdqpxL5Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw I hope you get an opportunity to work with the Reps from #Mississippi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m 👀 @HudsonBooks timeline ... and see all these authors signing copies of their work at airports around the co… https://t.co/Y5JbtMNb59]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coroner has identified the two people shot and killed in Rock Hill yesterday.   Zuinquarius McCrorey. 20.  And… https://t.co/kvp8FvPBY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickHi2315 @badjamjam Got ME! They probably snicker when they look at their balances!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to a gutsy absorbed charge by Tiana Brown and some clutch shooting, looks like the Eagles are going to hold on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinterest has me doing the absolute most right now 🎀 https://t.co/vCh7hOaqNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you ever come up with an idea only to find out that somebody had also thought of it? Once I thought I had inven… https://t.co/D8YCzxCnFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HbXoXT4Npo You can get in touch with us via Att customer service 1833-554-5444 #attcustomerservice… https://t.co/YMdxBEYBXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over 2 weeks ago, Xavier was 3-8 and in the basement of the Big East. The Musketeers have put together one of… https://t.co/SNBB4bBWOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightOwensFight I'm Very Happy Your Gonna Get A Title Shot At #WWEFastlane. I Hope You Bring The Fight To… https://t.co/CFn6XRtHZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Office update construction has begun. #thisisotr https://t.co/sdaqRwo3HJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know why @TheDemocrats haven't made student loan forgiveness a major part of the party platform. It would i… https://t.co/jXTzstp358]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oddest ad campaign @BurnleyOfficial stadium.  Visit #uzhbekistan NOW! #COYS]]></document></documents></author>