<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@johnboosco I’ll be sure to tag you when it’s all set up. These tables are 💯!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is my Walgreens playing Amber on the radio #311 very very unordinary 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite number has always been #17🥰 My husbands’ dream to race has been the focus of most of our marriage.  I t… https://t.co/IDTA6cXNYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[how many times is God going to teach you the same lesson before you learn?🤦🏽‍♀️🙇🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_axxaa_ milk chocolate is so weird like it’s good but if I eat a lil it jus makes me feel weird &amp; white chocolate jus nasty nasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a beautiful display tiger sand shark, turtles, and big big fish. #aquarium #fish #florida @ The Florida Aquari… https://t.co/C5gV1hyjnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanRose30  Hi Rose! Just discovered you &amp; started following. ✊🏻💕✊🏻💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an answer to this question. I have been quite unable to sleep since close of #GC2019 and I am SURE this is w… https://t.co/ous2tmw7Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 illegal immigrants linked to Mexican cartel arrested in NC for drug trafficking operation, officials say  https://t.co/XhlxtC9PYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re the type of person who uses web MD’s symptom checker then it’s probably just anxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaylonRuiz “You won’t be able to use notes on a test in college” “they don’t curve exams in college” “you can’t re… https://t.co/rOteqUQ9U7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmgivingsoul @sorkKari @cazij @simplysallyh @suziday123 @Dracaenawines @Oberreimer @ja2cook @Cbp8Cindy @FinValko… https://t.co/EBwJC94wYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Pop-Up! 🌱 (@ Coliseum Nightclub in White Plains, NY) https://t.co/TSikUaNrcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @nischelleturner Well maybe the Adminstration could stop the promotion of the criminalization of homose… https://t.co/e1zjVsbIdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nakoontz @rhwiggins @CDP_Rad @CMGlastonbury @ASHNRSociety @phudge54 @Januarium @cmtomblinson @gmoonis @MedPierre… https://t.co/kGoWyn85KO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodgerFromYutan @AviannaNicole @HuffPost When on earth did I contradict myself or say I hated the liberal media? I… https://t.co/xtlIgh2PWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[...when you find your place.  No matter which PT’s I had gone to see I was not making any progress and then this pl… https://t.co/7yBhRJDmLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there really nowhere i can get my choice cigs and yerba mate in chandler. really . what do i fucking pay taxes for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! Keep it going all the way!! Continue on!! No court can stop it!! The American people want it!! Demon-crats/ a… https://t.co/23lFluEL2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone SERIOUSLY interested in an office manager position at a fragrance company in Williamsburg?]]></document><document><![CDATA[last game was coo, loved every moment. 💯🖤 w my brothers man season was fun 💯 love y’all boys rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SOXinTN @IB4UT2 @RandallCantrel4 @TonyBasilio I’m not from Chicago 😂😂 Another swing and a miss. I’m sure your imag… https://t.co/AFoIzka8Ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite part of the day is at night when Cesar rubs the bootyyyy for me to go to sleep 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me @ work "also see a doctor cause you shouldn't be growing when you cough" bitch disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Well put your life vest on stupid because the ship is sinking and everyone on Trumps Ti… https://t.co/V0Qjb7NzLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews You are actually suggesting that paying a living wage to an employee is socialism/communism? That it is un… https://t.co/BYnTBSdGEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edwin Gutiérrez  Coach-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +584145283218. Forjarse Purificarse y Brillar…Visión Sin… https://t.co/NLeVnMkagx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anwar and Conway research question: To what extent can public time-sensitive data from Twitter help us start to mon… https://t.co/e6Z5pQzZvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadowCellMedia @adambarnhardt You’re a rare breed. Most would have shook it off as being more of a true remake to… https://t.co/s2bLI1y36V]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key to living A cheerful life is choosing gratitude #shauntifeldhahn  #findrest #devotions https://t.co/D1f185Y7CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standamericanow @jjosephwilliams @NikkiHaley Exciting news! Will you join @SenAlexander and @BillHaslam in advocat… https://t.co/ww7Tp1tbpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1080Johnson @KamalaHarris Um there wouldn't be future bankruptcies from illness or injury and that's kind of the point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GOP @SenateGOP Time to #HaltTheAssault and #EndGunViolence #Tweetstorm NOW #Retweet Please @MomsDemand… https://t.co/3pG4HTCrni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noneloh @NatGeo U are absolutely right Nelson. Those crazy thoughts 💭🙃 #HappyFriday https://t.co/zfZh8VERoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live footage of the Jussie Smollett attack in Chicago https://t.co/YFMbtgE8ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[me on my phone at 3 am knowing damn well that blue light suppresses melatonin production https://t.co/HcHo8C5khq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Memaw02933680 @DarrenConnolly_ Michael Cole said "Dean Ambrose's future uncertain" not "Dean Ambrose is leaving" s… https://t.co/jnIHKFM6HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s coming down in Centennial, CO! @CentennialGov @weather5280 @ReedTimmerAccu https://t.co/H4uYAfwgyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re traveling around the league this season to tell some amazing stories. Have one we can’t miss? Let us know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely do not need anything. I was driving home and all of a sudden I was here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendrajessie 🥰 @followedbliss  Up &amp; Down Nights out 🤗⚡️🖤⚡️ https://t.co/JwHwfS345k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arthritis seems to be reason for Rams limiting Todd Gurley in playoffs https://t.co/MuNmFEJ9TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree! I have literally never had a boring or predictable day as a GP. In the US we also get to do many surgical pr… https://t.co/LQJvtai3I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleeOlivia Lemme know how that goes lol first hand you lose people doing that 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aoglasser @ETSshow @emily_fri @colleenmfarrell @laxswamy Here’s my proof of good life balance weekend activities i… https://t.co/2f3bSzlJ2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when I used to spend my whole day monitoring another girls Instagram, to see if we are still in active c… https://t.co/kqiiL74q4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun @LoveSTEMSD #backyard @SUHSD_STEAM hanging out with fellow #WomenInSTEM happy #InternationalWomansDay https://t.co/11NyUjK4L4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your tissues ready😭🙌🙏  You guys know I love to share success stories. But this one... oh lordy this one gets me… https://t.co/LblVqAu9MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandon_overbay @SteveScalise @realDonaldTrump So where were the Democrats on negotiating for the past 2 years oh… https://t.co/39pLvVDfxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melcastillo1977 We, as teachers, have repeatedly reported our concerns with this. Research seems to only be relevant in some cases.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Sports Ecard: 'Ryan Lochte, you go back in there and put a shirt on!' -No... #mirth #chuckle #smirk #playful https://t.co/vw2gV3XLDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't see myself spending this day with anyone else but you 💗  Happy Love Day, Sebastian. @ Broward County, Florida https://t.co/p5VrziuQWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDawnRaney @dbc_inc @burgessdave @burgess_shelley @tishrich @tamaraletter @TaraMartinEDU @iluveducating… https://t.co/hE3Mh2psrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re teaching them well which means there will be more 10 sec moments to come. Stay tuned!💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEST part of growing up in a blue state and moving to red state: I don’t need to call douchebags like @billmaher ne… https://t.co/HF8jvd98GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPS alert! DANGER, DANGER! #mymuttpepper @ Samantha Suite, Suburban Richmond https://t.co/aafh2l0Jds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we are waiting on mama to groom and bathe us...  #JadeAndBradyLomax  #PostMyShorkie #ShorkieTwins… https://t.co/TzYEbBSe3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I met a Tulsi Gabbard fan in New Haven over the weekend and I was truly befuddled. All I kept asking was, "WHY???"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to explain to Maya why her fish aren’t talking back to her at 8 in the morning is not really what I planned to do 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@classpass at LAX, flight delayed for 5 hours now. Really wish there was a yoga studio or napping studio that I can access with classpass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’est le 5e mois de neige... #hiver #Québec #Montréal #fatiguée https://t.co/kopdYByY5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Too many idiot people interpreting the law....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fasanomike @lmower3 Thanks @fasanomike for protecting Floridians from Big Business lobbyists who seek to eviscerat… https://t.co/09Cf8fogJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunhappyKat We were at Berlin last fall! My husband ran it. What a drastic difference weather makes, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 23 today! 😭💕 #sugardaddy #SugarBabyTwitter #sugardaddywanted #sugardaddytwitter #HappyBirthday #pisces https://t.co/qBrJRvKHl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of the week! So many highs and lows - choosing to end on a positive note 🧘🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah!!No more threats to the USA.  Trump has eliminated extremist terrorist groups in the Middle East-they’ve all b… https://t.co/O4Mus9qcDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️ I love my new watch #greenfordlondon #luxury #watches #rosegold #marble @ Colorado Springs, Colorado https://t.co/HYzDxVwSJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnetteProtz @Bridgettemurphr @TimCobbARI @Marmatt0303 @CherylFriese Of course, she did! She's great. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨JUST REDUCED!! 🚨🚨Please contact me for more information... let’s start the month off right heading into escrow. 🏡… https://t.co/w5FuZrpTeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCPolitics That I'd like to see, Ju$tin and Butts in a courtroom under oath  !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeymcintyre You will always be my favorite #BoyInTheBand  Much love always! Proud of you and proud to be a fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#comiendo delicioso en un #restaurante de #westhollywood #losangeles #california #usa .... #eating #yummy in a… https://t.co/ccsjnpdoH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for small businesses, particularly those in your community, to prosper.  Have I not commanded you? Be strong a… https://t.co/mELlAsyzc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IT_LEADS hi,how are you ? i sell fiber optic patch cord,drop cable,splice enclosure ,welcome u send us inquiry]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some comedy. Cat memes with funny sayings - is there anything better on the internet? #funniness #lol… https://t.co/xZmJ60UghD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoreacio There was ice on my car this morning ... I need that weather. Pool in the winter ! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Amen...Liberal Socialist Comunist No Democratic Baby Killing Party is DIABOLIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever Steph’s bro calls me sis I cry a little I love him and her whole family❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So twisted! We will #KeepGoing because the majority of Americans want safety and common sense solutions. Thank-You… https://t.co/7VUFoIkPXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#También #hay #mujeres #atrevidas #al #volante #dejemos a un lado el #machismo #trabajemos #juntas #mujeres emprend… https://t.co/wzonKfLxgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #ValentinesDay love isn’t new, it’s grown. Write it out because love never fails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😘😘😘 比心~❤❤❤ @vittawinbest  #bestvittawin #หวานของเบส  #vittawinbest https://t.co/Gy4cHQzgQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math isn’t my thing, but even I know what 100% means.  IT MEANS ALL OF THEM!  100% of Fortune100 companies are cust… https://t.co/YNkApImYvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyFox_RAH @GERONursing @nutriagelab might be able to give you some ideas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Originally posted October 2017 @Regranned from @nicrasenti -  Burpee pull ups. It's worse than it looks. But it wor… https://t.co/yJODjMNC0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[fina type this essay from my phone lol i knew i should brought my laptop damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thxs to @GRHSNews ELA teachers Mrs. Torres and Rowe for inviting me to help flip your research project on the Eliza… https://t.co/SZOiQoT6yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacramento!   But maybe we should tell Vladimir that McClellan Air Force Base was shut down in 2001 and now there a… https://t.co/sUWNuWMvka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryamMonsef @criseboro @mclaudebibeau Congratulations both on your new appointments from Education Cannot Wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DealNoDealCNBC #DealOrNoDeal Oh no. The $1,000,000 is alone. That’s dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever watch anything... please watch this... #trump #MichaelCohenTestimony #NotMyPresident]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @HireMeImFunny People prefer to earn money with the possibility of upwards mobility. The more taxes, and gover… https://t.co/MQfOr7h500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenNWCbus @TemeculaRises @TomSteyer Word from on the ground in 7 OH4 precincts-the key is discussion! We flipped t… https://t.co/rLCqPPpLfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter Hey @GeorgeConway do the country a favor and tell your wife or else she should resign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorFedeli @AutismONT You can’t seriously believe that!Changes to the OAP is nothing short of child neglect. We… https://t.co/hIBf38gHVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBOpi1 @shaunking @BernieSanders If I wasn’t interested in the truth, then why did I attend rallies for both of th… https://t.co/IdhMyFjcc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All smiles, fancy glasses and fancy face for Oscars coverage on @bttoronto Happy Monday friends! @ Citytv https://t.co/pQPxbepwfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think of this little bathroom remodel? Nothing I’ve ever seen in a manufactured home from 1970’s💎… https://t.co/DxUAmBnA4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/iItWqApxQl Man Who Prophesied Trump’s Election In 2007 Reveals 3 More Ch-illing Predictions'''Will ser… https://t.co/0XCqiiiD4e]]></document></documents></author>