<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Fr/Jv Bball triple-header at home today versus Portland. Freshmen Boys tip at 4:00. Jv Boys follow around 5:30 and… https://t.co/i3vCnpR5cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Eric Murphy- another former @RepublicanAGs staff member / Solicitor General confirmed to the bench.… https://t.co/pJ64bx2zfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louhaley @danapixie @mariodacat @StewBunny @ediesausage @SirShnerks @bluezed2003 @Thumpsanfriends @KatoQParrot… https://t.co/0ksAlXz3KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisGrutt @JamesCripps_ @BuffaloSabres Risto just pushes and shoves? 32 assists this season with 5 goals. If he s… https://t.co/Kbkqr3mNvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reflog_18 @holidayvalley The Wall Bitches....go, go, go!  Then do it backwards, drunk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the dude in the news said he didn’t know of evidence that gay couples (sexuality isn’t binary tho too so you’re mis… https://t.co/RSZZolY4ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madison East High School vs Badger High School in the Regional semifinal game. East is #1 in D1. @ East High https://t.co/VV5PHmboNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVDemForum @Arnold_August @danielmkovalik @ninopagliccia @camilateleSUR @ConsuladoVenVan @Tony_Tracy @venanalysis… https://t.co/VjxoPmFty1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Congratulations on being an enormous asshole. Your a boil on the fat butt of humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was blocked by @TSA @tsaspox @EnglandMichaelJ after on 6/21/2018 he emailed the media my #fentanyl warning from 4… https://t.co/AavzVNzoH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[as much as people hate on this new star wars trilogy i still gotta say i’m super hyped for the next one]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥰 We are in love with our new #justlisted Condo Downtown San Diego! https://t.co/Pngqd5WGkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldTakesExposed Trade happened more than 24 hours after 3/7. I mean... to be fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good data viz allows the user to make her own interpretations. It will never provide a single answer. Otherwise a… https://t.co/Wch5kUvFYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 4415 N Marlborough Dr #Shorewood #WI  #realestate https://t.co/wWdYVbvrhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis recuerdos de Facebook todo el mes de febrero han sido carnavaleando.. no encuentro foto sin maicena.. 😔💔... y no ha empezado marzo.. 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m traveling this weekend. Wanna know the worst city you’ve ever visited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerboE @meagankenrekt There is a board game pub in my town with a $10 cover if you play long games. They also have… https://t.co/n6hiYWVwcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NjnycS @KenzieReevesxxx @xvioletrainx That REALLY sucks... I was JUST starting to follow her work... SO sorry to hear it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseMaerker @Conacyt_MX El @Conacyt_MX se ha convertido en el consejo nacional de Chairos y Todologos...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filmmusicgirl @chenx064 @WeStandWithEvan @FactCheckU @4everDemocratic @Regan0002112 @steveio2 @nocovfefehere… https://t.co/5cJGSLC2nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allen_NeilH Those who die, die protecting our freedom and our Constitution. Ignoring the Constitution in the name… https://t.co/hte1ODkDvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart That's because...  NO one #UndertheDCDome will ever be held to account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ain’t even had to see the movie to know that shit was beautifully shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of pier 6 At Brooklyn, not much going into the port today! https://t.co/WdhV7akdNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaroUribeVel @santorendon  @mluciaramirez @gusgomez1701 @rabodeajip @IvanDuque @MariaFdaCabal @PalomaValenciaL… https://t.co/jy13n0APMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt00793038 @RamLover69 @barstoolsports @KFCradio I just found it under my fiancées name even though we’re both owners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy amanecí con ganas de #FolowBackGuerrero como ves @SantosLagunFans #Guerrero que nos siga #Guerrero que seguimos… https://t.co/EA6usSEgkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3P’s will get you every time!!! Piss, Poor, Planning!! 🤨  I’m on a mission to get back down to my fighting weig… https://t.co/yJYMsto2E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmeldrumJC @Coach_Terpstra One of my favorites. Really excited for his new book, The Infinite Game. I have already pre-ordered it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A valediction for Jeff Adachi, who defended the public https://t.co/PVMoOVv0xG 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF https://t.co/75CiFOB5wC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lugar que mais bate vento em NY. Se eu fosse mais magro, sairia voando dali. 😂 . . . . . . #BrooklynBridge #NewYork… https://t.co/ToJJzFzjU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusBeNyce People be eatin them Mfs wrapped in bacon and they still gross asl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dana White: Says Daniel Cormier deserves Brock Lesnar more than Jon Jones -- hasn't talked to Lesnar at all. Lesnar… https://t.co/8006nSgtBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[limo service near me #limoservicenearme #texinearme #sedanservicenearme #carservicenearme https://t.co/sYg5RE7hV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having good food will have you looking forward to lunch, hence making you try to work faster and accomplish all you… https://t.co/l24dDBVYoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @SteeleHoops leads Laredo Nixon 39-23 at halftime in today’s regional final.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoseOliva Appreciate your work on healthcare.  There is much to be done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@packetsniffer99 @TheEconomist It was Mogg’s idea to have a second referendum, one of his few, so let’s do as he suggested.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sexy neighbor’s well put together, slightly less attractive wife [sic], just rolled up in a model x. A) Fk you,… https://t.co/t5nqDxA5E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rabbit ragu with homemade egg pasta. I haven’t made this in a while. @ South Congress https://t.co/4MeExOatmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped host a youth engagement event today, there’s a 5 year old  kid and we’re working on crafts together when he… https://t.co/FCsQQjLbDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will this announcement change your shopping habits? #SLC #Utah https://t.co/OpgDkz0T63]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quotation, ‘’A great player, but an even better person’’ is used habitually. However, there is no better exampl… https://t.co/atixuMGIjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concert season is in full effect!! Happy Mary got to put another ✅ on her concert bucket list tonight seeing… https://t.co/D7HqASybsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good seeing the boys last night ✊🏼 @ Amen Corner https://t.co/nJAKc1ijCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @AniaKinski @CandiceDare @kayden_kross @IamPaigeJ @Cassie_Ibiza @TheRileyAnne1  @LighthouseAlice… https://t.co/NnJMafCu9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't seen those photos yet. But on Your recommendation I'll take a look. I'm Sure that they're Classic, Tastef… https://t.co/sQpiLgXZCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I let @Lorena_Guardado drive for one hour in Alabama and she goes the wrong way on a one way on the freeway!🤣🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm glad I got a couple of mins with @mandelash She basically told me that is all about content and document everyt… https://t.co/YSYAuCNsXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who needs to hear this, but in life people will try to do things to hurt you or try to take things fro… https://t.co/7UD7qP47Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now...the golden tones of John Rooney and the Missouri Valley Conference Tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj - Barbie Drip (Lyrics) https://t.co/3evGVOmqnH via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealjozvam @pauloquiros @pitrpatr @RerollAndy @FilmReroll Expert advice Joz I’ll be in New York City in Novembe… https://t.co/p4ZahpQuJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolGT @Adamkendama1 If we beat Clemson then just go ahead and crown our ass champions of CFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to know more about the creepy knife cart prophet man from #willywonka. What happened to him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continue to be immature with your feelings, you will get replaced. No one will wait on you forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take as much money 💵 as you can. You’re worth whatever someone’s willing to pay you. #MoneyTalks]]></document><document><![CDATA[02:54 Temp. 46.9°F, Hum. 68%, Dewp. 34.9°F, Bar. 30.26 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 175° 0.6 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BD12HK @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @CBSNews They are human just horrible, but they started in L.A.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallStRique Was thinking this the other day.  Hopefully he’s got his rhythm back by the post-season (if they get in)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to post this yesterday but it is proof that a great #puremichigan sunrise doesn't care about the 7 degree te… https://t.co/nE5P6et6gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cayenne in beast mode on the way to the gym this morning 💪 https://t.co/M7jSXISNUL @ Life Time Athletic - Cente… https://t.co/dmnMIYyIQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t serve a mission but I still try to never see my family more than twice a year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swindeazy I haven’t been since 11. Use to go every time. I have went and tailgated with buddies but, not to the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:35.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tropicpale Ale by @BooneshineBrew at @cobosushi — https://t.co/RQw4DkFvts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to a legend robbed of his vision. Sorry I couldn't get my video out for your birthday. Here's to you… https://t.co/gJg5LyQiXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Martinook (CAR) spots the loose puck and slaps it home!  4-2 #Canes, 13:22 to play in “The Music City”.… https://t.co/INo9fwyElN]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS HUGE NEWS: Stress Test Codes were just released and Zyphox once again has been picked to be the one to pass me… https://t.co/75Dwo0FwqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone plz stream #ColdinLA I promise you won’t regret it at all. I’m so incredibly proud of @JonahMarais… https://t.co/3bESRuYvm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[In literally every other state, I can take beer to go directly from a brewery. However, the greedy wholesale middle… https://t.co/6Ag9aRdStr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichKJr @ApexOnRacing I would recommend GT Sport. Out of all of the console games, GT has the highest ceiling in t… https://t.co/9IWGSIvdcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this item in my Etsy shop https://t.co/R4zcJBSrIE #art #artist #artoftheday #artsy #etsyshop #EtsySeller #etsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skills workshop  February 24th 2019   📍Keller Central High School  https://t.co/G9JOVBPxhW  https://t.co/Kb0YQnpMJt https://t.co/9YSDKchn1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great soccer facility!!  Love that most of our games are here this weekend!! https://t.co/rjX70puv6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man. Juan Likes Rice and Chicken was so goofy and sweet and wholesome. Loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraR77 @RARRRRR @sxdoc Should audit ALL voter rolls in every county...lawful, living, breathing citizens with pr… https://t.co/a6VNukmrwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @realDonaldTrump Or riders of public transit vote on the directorships that manage and fund that infrastructure?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplysales123 100%, is it enjoyable all the time? Nope.   But it’s the most valuable skill you can learn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent much of the evening organizing my library in a way that only makes sense to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pepe1807 @kunfupanda2 @ElRigel_ @germanamilcarsi @rlizarraga13 @Roberto47994229 @AnaGabrielaGue @ramon_flores_… https://t.co/CGLbvS93vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given that lying under oath to Congress AGAIN would violate his plea agreement, he seems genuinely remorseful for h… https://t.co/WtOt44UwpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResSports Killing a few minutes on YouTube before bed and came upon a rare Dan Antoniuk sighting. #xtreme https://t.co/Dugxbrs00d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we still expecting the Mueller reportthis week? Because I’m writing today and I need to know whether I should hide my phone somewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janekleeb @BradAshford18 Prepaid return postage on mail-in ballots seems like an absolutely valid investment in my… https://t.co/m2pa0QJ4Uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Any #government official paid by the #American people is over #paid. #Taxes is #theft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pushed this ship into pier 27 the other morning.  Put canvas out on the bow fenders so we wouldn’t leave any marks… https://t.co/YcfWhUgsPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at her with her friend awwwww 😂😂😂😂. We can play all night https://t.co/wvjioTy57S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really cool how everyone thinks they can guilt me into doing what they want and all but no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channel 10  NBC did a Story on Bill Cosby and 'MISSED the Con Job  the Inmates did on them. NBC reporters bought in… https://t.co/zY48iNDaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[people around me are put off if I say I enjoy shooting riffles, but I bet they wouldn't blink an eye if I said "I w… https://t.co/GowROamLdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Era obvio que el inepto @MartinVizcarraC iba a elegir a un CHUPAMEDIAS para la @pcmperu el tipo no tiene elementos… https://t.co/f4n1D7amj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAUANJENNlNGS @___hashbrown Y’all are making too many good points stop it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Friday night last night. Kicking off the weekend night out on the town. Celebrating my dad’s birthday! 🎂🎊🎉🎈🍤… https://t.co/ermXVoZ1Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening for Ozzy tribute band last night #Ozziethesportsjunkie #Chaotic #SarasotaRock https://t.co/cGxrWB67zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stories Like Passwords: very much worth reading again in light of recent developments.  https://t.co/79OQbuAcNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxFriendsFirst Good Morning and Happy Fryday🍟staff, crew, @HeatherChilders @jillianmele and @SchmittNYC Great job… https://t.co/fWdl1cwhwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maldita sea. ¿Por qué los malditos "opositores" no piden abiertamente una intervención militar? ¿Hasta cuándo tanta… https://t.co/KzVGZjISUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #Milwaukee #brewers team 1965-2016, position players.  https://t.co/4ps528uSTQ … … … https://t.co/qMag70HLQA]]></document></documents></author>