<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Que nuca volverás... que nunca me quisiste... se me olvidó otra vez que solo yo te quise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7horne_ Bro we down 1 man. We just got nothing from anybody other than RJ and Cam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA  It's rush hour your D line going to Gov't center is taking at least 15 mins. to pickup people in Brookline.… https://t.co/8JrLvP0MXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonequaMG @actordougjones @albinokid @may_wise @shazad @wcruz73 @ansonmount @alanvansprang @bahiawatson Awesome wo… https://t.co/lc0XLg247a]]></document><document><![CDATA[285 Fernandes  defeats Gashi  by pin in 1st  Njsiaa State Champion 285 Congratulations Lewis Fernandes Vorhees]]></document><document><![CDATA[These “Ask Me Anything” moments on twitter or insta.... I’m not even gonna fake an attempt because I doubt anyone b… https://t.co/RHwsQBj01a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What can you say except this guy is a BIG LIAR! I wouldn't trust him as far as I could throw him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am here lifting then hitting the pool for cardio. #faithandfitness #hyltonathletics #teamhylton #newlife #fit… https://t.co/nB31PMbbHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I probably ran a good 30-40. Kinda wish I would’ve kept count better xD.  @ComeToFrostbite is insane, let’s go Top… https://t.co/t2rHnJnuoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; I’m open to girls shooting their shot with me, but I won’t shoot my own shot. 🙃😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javawithjiva @mr_totte @AliciaKeenan7 That is a possibility.  Now I’m concerned that someone nearby is going to try to trap a coyote!]]></document><document><![CDATA[sNOw problem! #wahooligan #inmyelemnt #ownit #followME @ Downtown, Colorado Springs https://t.co/JyWDctgkju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not exactly. I don’t want them to see me out. I just want them to hear it]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some great examples of public libraries doing this around Alabama after hours...let’s keep this trend mov… https://t.co/02sjW09nyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferAnWorld #Occupy2DeColonize/RunningWolf ELECTED Mayor 2 STOP FUKUSHIMA (SEXY) /9th Annual 9-11 (was an INSI… https://t.co/rqdDBKYfj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arapahoe_Basin  thought you guys might enjoy this short clip from Friday morning first chair.   https://t.co/xU3Lk59pJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to keep updated on the next chance of winter weather with @megank5mem and @MichaelSeger  in the morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/uo5Fe3axJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You used to have to wait for a film to be developed. But it wasn’t just the photos we loved, it was the anticipati… https://t.co/YB473Yw18s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dc_mma  give  @stipemiocic  his rematch now!!  Stipe dominated that man who just took your bff soul!! #ufc #clevelandstrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carleecamlin Happy Birthday Carlee. Have a day that is as great as you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Max Keenan on advancing to the sectional finals of the IHSA Three Point Shootout! He beat 2 othe… https://t.co/PJzW2uhJBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASaunders_PGH @SynonymForWet I honestly think Botterill was THE guy. But he didn't have the title or the paycheck to go with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImprintedENERGY can we officially switch B in B.A.N. to C? C standing for CLOWN. all I'm seeing out here is these… https://t.co/JlaQgwD321]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe that Nicholas kid can come out and save @BraunStrowman #ElimantionChamber #WWEChamber #WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Incredible artist @iamlp got me through A Lot. If you are not familiar with her genius work. Get 👏 On 👏 It 👏. C… https://t.co/9Fc8f8V6ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrundle4 You dense mother fucker. She was bragging about being able to drive herself home DRUNK, not just 1 beer.… https://t.co/qn3n3dmcd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ship's tender dinghy, is totally something a boat person will say to you and expect you to keep a straight face. 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bygone era...but make no mistake: @ISUMattCampbell one of the best coaches in the Country for a reason...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pacers/Timberwolves Go Pacers! #pacersgamenight https://t.co/xGFaxYcLVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The night brings a different perspective to art.“ #WynnwoodWalls #Miami #Art #travel #explore #Murals… https://t.co/BCZHoRWWnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an honor to be able to open our doors to this amazing community! Thanks for joining us today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just saying he should be there go to player and as far as saying in my top 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monsterprom I have a serious question about Zoe, and her "eyes". Artistically the eyes on her face look very diffe… https://t.co/kLUolfYzP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyTheGiant @armano @griner No backtracking. I was legit ragging on my guys over here. But I do think there’s a l… https://t.co/3P59igOwkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflecting this morning on how many lives were positively impacted and transformed last week from our partnership w… https://t.co/6xeDTatOHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[How and when did Peoria, IL become the canonical reference for Everytown, USA? Is it still relevant /applicable today? Was it ever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bandit [upper-left] and Maggie. Bandit was rescued from being fed to fighting dogs as bait. Maggie was rescued from… https://t.co/KMCOZPNM3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsternks @renato_mariotti Democrats are controlling Trump and his stooges within the limits of the law! If you are… https://t.co/LrjWOkxoJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seungminkim @costareports @AshleyRParker Then, they went duck hunting. Cheney pulled out his rifle and everybody ducked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. If I can quote myself, so true!  Keep the good ones you have and recruits some more!  @CIOStraightTalk #STInights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched it all. (Tired)  Encouraged: by Dem women  Discouraged: by GOP proof that you can't argue w/fools   Left me… https://t.co/um8cE6pRYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VIXEN @TheVixensworld @GregLansky @AVNMediaNetwork @avnawards @AEexpo @RedTube @redtube1 @AngelDarkBlog @ButtmanHD… https://t.co/58euygTG8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caballitopinto Peter no crees que es bastante lo que @jguaido  lleva sobre sus hombros? Solo 60 días y el imperio… https://t.co/ovdJh4bgmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to watch Spinal Tap again...  'This tasteless cover is a good indication of the lack of musical inven… https://t.co/pvYq47DWk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miserable despicable human beings that would kill these animals. There will be a special place in hell for these ki… https://t.co/bFUEuJKuQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl hates watching basketball with me cuz this exactly how it be 😂😂🤷🏽‍♂️ https://t.co/tVCXXBBP9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarksReeseWIP @JonMarksMedia @Ike58Reese @bliv94 do you think Bryce will be at Carson’s softball game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdValleeWx Looks like a another pattern flip to what we saw a lot of the winter! Wonder if this is the last of the… https://t.co/3a75aMaN2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast working with the @nj1015 #morningcrew. Thanks for adopting me into your #family. Gonna miss these guys… https://t.co/iVWbq4nYiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sake’s get you GOOD too QUICK😂🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶🍶 . . . . @K_Lars15 🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AStineGiftPlan Coming to Benicia for the Walk 4Water. Met Pastor Ken on Sunday. Just had the US Trust presentation… https://t.co/CTyyk15HfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEMOORE1969 @ShannonSharpe Don't see color my ass.. Even i gotta call bullshit on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Thank you Hayley on Star Tours for reuniting me with my cell phone made my day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schott_free @AgdaCoroner Some, I’m sure. I don’t know about ‘many.’ The volume of vinyl sales (tens of thousands,… https://t.co/FqYlk1StiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah but dinosaur analysts don’t like the Canes doing this. Good thing the players, fans, and little ones like this… https://t.co/fUrbsJdKJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many phone giveaways he was a party to? #tgdn #ctot #bernardSanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[המפתח המ פתח @LIFE @54high @Wayin @KelloggsRDs @RadioSpecialK @PhillyStandUP09 @xFULLRED @rockhall) https://t.co/Jv2tKK8ym4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbdallahNATION Cool Abdallah and by the way my name is Kat and I really love to play Pokémon Let’s go Pikachu and Pokémon Let’s go Eevee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steph_A_Nanny @momjeansplease Hereditary Lights Out Babadook Paranormal Activity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Halifax the @musicatmemorial audition panel is heading your way today! Live auditions tomorrow, Friday Feb 22!… https://t.co/IbEZMW1YI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson it is a rare week.  I won all of the games this weekend.  I don't cheat on purpose.  I also will not… https://t.co/Zi4Zjl20L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSilverstein Raise ‘em....but if you miss the playoffs for a third year, choose your next ticket price announcement carefully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRongey @RandyKarraker @101ESPNFastLane @Meat101ESPN @bthompson48 She has been resurrected, much the same way the St. Louis Blues have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeeSaw is such a great tool for student reflection! @atimpd #edt602una]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇮🇪🍀🥃🍀🥃🍀🥃🍀🇮🇪 #irishwhiskey #greenspot #jameson #writerstears #teelingwhiskey #deadrabbit #redbreast @ The District a… https://t.co/WtOqF4cjPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlessandraLynnG Hi Alessandra! Seriously, this works:  1–half-teaspoonful salt in 2 ounces warm water; gargle with… https://t.co/l9tQmT3t7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miamicom @MiamiHerald The entire time I lived in Miami, all I heard was how great west coast FL (Naples/Tampa) bea… https://t.co/PA2B41iCDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VIZMedia Mr. Osumatsu for #toonami this April! https://t.co/hQkUMntaZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDabyss @FaithNaff @WhiteGuysTV Never dismissed any acts of racism. I just think we need to be very careful not to… https://t.co/tSIufGP90c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ODonJerek @TheNamesJeffrey @blacktanar @prxttyboyflacko @GilbertToves 💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time will be with you always  You treat with with lidocaine  A willing distraction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JStudjstruver Why do you try to fit your hand in every cookie jar at once?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump on Kim Jong Un during last night's Hannity interview: "He is very sharp," "a real leader," "… https://t.co/ewyXnylMcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought the Lakers couldn't play any worse .... https://t.co/TuJt52lktK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend waited over two hours in line in the pouring rain for pizza... imagine how much he must love me...  not as much as pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elevators at Montgomery Park.  #Portland #elevator #MontgomeryPark @ Montgomery Park https://t.co/Lzl0d1DSFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun begins to swell into red giant: 5 billion years   I-4 finished: 6 billion years  Sun swells into full red giant… https://t.co/1VECIo3iQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Addleben @YoniFreedhoff @WFKARS @gefilteria Pickles are a cruel mistress but a wonderful one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you go to @marshalls and don’t buy a new scented candle  did you even go to Marshall’s at all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to figure out the curves #TaylorSwift is talking about. She out here shaped like a butter knife.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So help me out here. At youth basketball tourneys, why don’t some refs allow siblings/other players a chance 2 shoo… https://t.co/ptEfHDrsk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is @peterwigggin when she has hiccups (also when she has too much tequila 😉)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter skies and palm trees on campus. #csusacramento @ California State University, Sacramento https://t.co/V6oLR9QNbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HughUnderPar @JuniorGolfofAZ @SWSectionPGA @yocgolf @ASUKarsten Hugh your hanging with a FSU Alum, the great Sean Ferris!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really reconsidered my whole life this morning when I had to get up to travel after only sleeping 3 hours...😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RecTecGrill @rectecgrills I'm living the RecTec lifestyle regardless of our crappy weather. https://t.co/IbEfSoZBEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#afterparty - Drinking a Peanut Butter Bananas Foster Forever by @CraftedMead at @blackheathmead  — https://t.co/MwsZSWVulC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like Kinberg took a bar bet to remake X-Men: The Last Stand, but WORSE. And that movie at least got some emoti… https://t.co/Hab6PcNtvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzo drops new music. @BettyWho drops new music. @SaraBareilles drops new music.  WHAT A DAMN WEEK. 🙌🏼… https://t.co/7t7BkDwp77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in seeing #CaptainMarvelPremiere? Why? Find a reason outside of seeing the fate of the heroes tha… https://t.co/7KlCVO9U7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizz_Bennet @LuchyB Y que dirán los Millenians cuando te puedes calzar un par diario o más sin tener que repetir e… https://t.co/pohRqFAIQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npr @LynnPNeary i would like to see u follow up with a piece on racism and racial unrest by racists of color like… https://t.co/UmZPj6dAII]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the last game of the regular season for @WarriorResults and @BlakeAthletics basketball on this Friday evening.… https://t.co/D4v2WBcTyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AdamSchiff , why did you delete this tweet? https://t.co/Pt3mqjfSOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hidden Falls Skate Park in Henderson, NV https://t.co/oyjVccvEfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ottawa forward young core / prospects : Tkachuk , White, Brown, Batherson, Formenton, Chalapik, Balcers, Abramov,… https://t.co/m4kCWNONVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump disabled seniors are being mistreated badly due to the war on drugs, doctors are refusing treatmen… https://t.co/Yc1MCyAJLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#inchrist #knowgodknowpeace @ Costa Mesa, California https://t.co/IiEWCdq4GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrific! Attempted murder of woman caught on camera! Feminists get involved! You or your daughter may be next!]]></document></documents></author>