<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your support and #solidarity #SaveOshawaGM #onpoli #onlab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelmalice @TomFitton Don't say that. This has to stop. We have to take our rights back..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocioCecil Wait,Idk if you’re running because that’s good,or terrible. Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump FU Asshole, your friends the Libtards will never succeed.  Stay put for 2020, Trump… https://t.co/yyodpi7EIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__lkh @FLEYELASHESUK I use a Lancôme setting spray and sometimes I forget to do it and let me tell ya, I can total… https://t.co/kq8yJffW0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻 desliza. Excelente nuestra primera #PoetryNight del año que contó con la presencia de reconocidos poetas: Od… https://t.co/Uf3WkFQcba]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way I spoke  The music I listened to  The way I looked  My skin color  My hair  My lack of fashionable clothing… https://t.co/VsRZ6krrzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every term I regret starting my projects the week before they’re due and the next term I literally do it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely hate Valentines Day.. it’s just a simple reminder of one of the worst days of my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great long weekend back home and had so much fun showing these New York girls how we do it in Missouri!… https://t.co/Q9qsOxewP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamela_alemap7 OKAY.. I just be like.. thanks for coming 😓 https://t.co/b1RkGQpU0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. Putting Hard Ass PJ away for now.  Revealing my sensitive side. I sure miss my old friends I made on here.  Whe… https://t.co/GkAdJ4byA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[20. A photo #fms_aphoto #fmspad #littlemomentsapp  Carpe Caffeine. @ Valentine Cafe Oak Creek https://t.co/Tth34BfT93]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our most important job is creating an educated electorate that fights for “we” instead of “me.” I have hope when I… https://t.co/xwUww5PjdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[me 🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️ hope to see some more HDFS majors/minors/cool ppl who are interested there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Civic Center/UN Plaza BART Station in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/KOijFupjRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome. Those cats know exactly what they’re doing.  Thanks for posting!  #Lions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is #RandomActsOfKindnessDay. What can you do to make this world a little kinder? https://t.co/5RjzFQtjOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want our Wasted Federal Money STOLEN for this pipe dream!! There again EVERYTHING DEMONRATS TOUCH IS RUINED!! Ju… https://t.co/vJ3hgMj53z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caristmas @iMakeShoes plz tell me “daddybear” is Hank’s text signature]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSIMS_6 @MK_McMaster You sit down. You can’t ever get pregnant. This doesn’t concern you until you grow a uterus and ovaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over here hiding Yo’s face with #richardgrieco realrichardgrieco  That’s a wrap LA - onto reno- home for one d… https://t.co/zDl5uzgwCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladava @RNBCHQT @chrisgalke1 @KarenCRealNurse @jdghitis @RobinTucker1234 @DeaGig139 Yes it's coming down pretty ha… https://t.co/8sBaouARgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four years ago...my how time flies! @ Fernbank Museum of Natural History https://t.co/XpI4t6euWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only crazy until you do it! ... we need a similar ad for #womenintech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okmaher You need a small whiteboard and dry erase markers.! And probably a visit to a coffee shop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I watch again in my block season 1 before season 2 comes hmm 🤔 ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy buenas tardes!!  Feliz y bendecido domingo!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/UFiLJreQfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriaanbacker @EddieDonovan @realDonaldTrump @doj @FBI President Trump is the greatest in many, many years.  Barac… https://t.co/Dq6RaBNWfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/UlHLIZLM1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[She my twin like we identical 😍💯 #youngdellz #youngdellzrianasfather @BrianaCaver @ Syracuse, New York https://t.co/4bdKgG2Uq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sticks and stones may break my bones, but words will make me think I deserved it.  Survivors of any and all forms o… https://t.co/giA3gCdstC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump You go deferred man 4 times. Haven’t had trouble with spurs since the end of the Vietnam war?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a part of me.  Congratulations!  Can't wait to see you in Orlando and Houston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DartfB3ider @FelipeCalderon Descalificar, es un recurso que tienen los que no conocen o no quieren conocer la caus… https://t.co/g55Q1JzLew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaCorinaYA Gracias por defender a Venezuela, estamos en deuda con usted!!! Dios la bendiga!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!! Dr. Seuss Day @CastlemanCreek @MidwayISD https://t.co/WQguXT1ioV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @EvanHarper9 love you crazy💓💓 gimme my sweatshirt back some time😤 https://t.co/67v3HmoIuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineBlau @DrKateJMiller Elaine, thanks for your reply. Unfortunately, I think some of this stems from our appall… https://t.co/KGsaT12gyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullthis @thedailybeast Then you have no moral compass but your own. You poor thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kken628875 @realDonaldTrump A dark day for America, when our acting president doesnt call out racism whenever it is displayed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Keep this predictor and dead beat dad in jail where he belongs. No sympathy deserved. His outburst with Gale K… https://t.co/4FO77V790K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BahrainiMehrdad Yeshua, SAVE Iran! Give them Your FREEDOM! You Love them. They are Your people you died for. Give… https://t.co/j7cRRu7rMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now coding through @BloxelsBuilder! @MsGuerrero2014 #BeAGreenDot #CodingCafe #ETrackDay2 @LandrumMS @KIPPCourage… https://t.co/aq0Cb4RiCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg that’s my husband y’all!! How did I get so lucky! 😍🤤 @ The Historic Pearl https://t.co/j5gjfbAgyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to start on my mini library in my 2nd bedroom https://t.co/S3dj1L87NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[this video is misleading. yes, this cat is reacting to thc, but because they ate an edible. irresponsibility is sti… https://t.co/Y0lPRbBwAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, I’m sick.  I couldn’t dodge it forever.  Is this what death feels like?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skippingstones LOL!!! Love it!!! Can't wait!!! https://t.co/mTJMZkpsca]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy at whataburger really trying to tell me my sandwich doesnt come with sauce.... like bro I always tell them no sauce are you new????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas baby! Another epic night in the books. . . . . #jt #manofthewoods  #motw #justintimberlake #timberlake… https://t.co/DWhRfssOaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5th Birthday to our Granddaughter Leanna! 🎁🎉🎈🎊❤️👏🏽 @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/6KmT1C4IlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m retweeting cuz I’d wear that taco onesie a couple sizes up. Taco Tuesday forreal. I’ll bring my own snacks thou… https://t.co/YOf5tXH7hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS Ya think ! Dirty money I’m guessing was used what is happening to our world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump An American “ President “ mocked a Senator with Vietnamese dictators. Sounds Trumpy. Thanks @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[summer vibes in the winter w/ my Garfield shirt 🤷🏼‍♀️☀️❄️ #friyay #vibes #garfieldfanclub #80degreesyesplease @ New… https://t.co/kIMhISy3uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to work at @CFISDWells with an incredible staff who celebrate students for who they are. I’m incredibly luc… https://t.co/6p79tn65dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I need to send a political contribution to Pine Bluff, Arkansas.  #Hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[💬 #ShestheOne who celebrated #ValentinesDay with the Seniors and love is in the air 🥰. Happy Valentines Day! Vote M… https://t.co/vWvmAT7Cnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss out! Spend Friday night with your friends, dress up and have a GREAT time! $10 gets you in...tables are… https://t.co/t0Pez25HTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that #pence may be dumber than #PresidentGropey  https://t.co/wgug5N7ztZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiKARE11 What a joy to work alongside you at two news stations! Your talent blows me away daily. Thank you so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like one of the most frustrating things is waiting for my LPC to go through, it’s only messing with my livel… https://t.co/IooddVwN0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neighborhood stroll #nyc @ East Village, Manhattan https://t.co/xCWHJbBdEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[my asshole phone updated and restored all my pictures with alec bc apparently they were backed up on my cloud 🤧🤧🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN GAME OVER: Chicago Police Reportedly Believe Jussie Smollett Paid Brothers To Beat Him Up… https://t.co/tvogFzpIvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/C5qohjLK4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fear and Faith fight for the same space. Each is territorial”. Beth Moore This picture is that of a floor plan to… https://t.co/khx3n5UFa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Duffy_theBear for the Valentine’s Day card!! 💜💜🥰🥰 https://t.co/GkCbN5Yxie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carnaval #ensenada en Ensenada, Baja California https://t.co/97rU2pLB25]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many amazing #stories and #blogs for #IWD2019. Thanks @bsebti @worldbank #SDGs #InternationalWomansDay2019… https://t.co/WPGCgbvpWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @LEGO_Group, We bought our nice this set, and it is missing one of the wheels to the bicycle! #help #41340 https://t.co/xQ7bcSj8Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoddessResists @adnilxa @ivyjofreeman @Jamiebabiez @american2084 @cornish1969 @CIAnderson3 @JohnRaimondo5… https://t.co/rtQZpuxx9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Feel Good Friday Shout Out is going out two culinary instructors who are making big changes and asking critica… https://t.co/PTGjAHySU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrobbin55 @QuancyClayborne Where do they reside, making sure to take that place off my list of places to visit!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow~I wish they would send these ignorant folks to another country if they don't want to respect this one!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just found a pic someone took of tayler holder at playlist and i was in the background akdks HELP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look at this legend for math class. Each pin is a different shape (forget the color) to represent A, B, C...… https://t.co/DsMDpQUitk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Recap: rnbtam Showed Up and Showed Out Saturday Night! Make sure you check her #single #freenow out and #support r… https://t.co/FRiDnoIx5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPug12 Hahaa aww, we know the feeling! But you sure look so cute in your sweater! ♥️🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please contact your Representative to urge them to vote to end this #FakeEmergency today! https://t.co/cuDx3FmGZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[CI Tournament kick off Friday March 1st @World_Nightclub with LIL BABY links in my bio for tickets or visit local… https://t.co/xliICfESel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meg me acostó borracha pa sacarme informacion de las rosas hahahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch seriously won’t leave me alone like why are working if you can never make shifts or always want to switc… https://t.co/nksPVGS0XM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@life_goals777 Ill hold a bit longer but that PR today altho had some good things in it was not strong enough to ge… https://t.co/0yd0oBzQFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @RobPolinsky from the @KSURadio crew! Thanks for all the laughs during Taste of the Town! 🍰🍗🍔🌮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @marcorubio @marklevinshow @AnnCoulter @michellemalkin @LindseyGrahamSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You must be nuts !! There is crisis when drugs and people are crossing everyday !!… https://t.co/C40mYQx8IO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful, like dancing wow! @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/wXCgTVMBQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[No gaters, no hurricanes and no skeeters (for much of the year) but real winter and great food (all year)!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notyourlizette What are you talking about? Her lipstick on the MAC US online store is sold out in minutes. Shut your lid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skeleton Keys #thebuxtoninn #keys #lamp #skeletonkeys #vintage #classic https://t.co/DqlhhjXdJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shannon’s topless in the backyard chasing the dogs around. Our neighbors love us lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting two t-shirts with two of my twitch friends for twitchcon and im so excited #greasybeans #danktank #streamtroll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arely_jaz Lo harán las que puedan, y las que no, seguirán exponiendo sus vidas tratando de hacer lo que consideran mejor para su futuro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lived literally right under this huge thing for years; a physical manifestation encapsulating the dreams of ma… https://t.co/j8XnaPEzKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holemac1 Yes. Solve that, THEN I'll be okay with free college. Not before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re going to get a manicure done, don’t sneeze into your hand, ya nasty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all go to a nail tech that don’t even give a fuck bout making your nails look clean &amp; it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crumbum52 @SketchyMars788 @ComingOutShyly If you do see them again, you definitely need to turn on your phone's ca… https://t.co/oP5XYuvCjv]]></document></documents></author>