<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Guess they are all attracted to the ethical and moral example set by Individual-1 or he j… https://t.co/9Q55g1dZLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[day 50/365 : you are in charge of your own life, don’t let anyone else have that privilege.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxSportsDrew @Brhea_BReport @ztilbrook @MonaCristo The birthing hips get me everytime @Brhea_BReport 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people I work with don’t know how to chew with their mouths closed and it drives me crazy. Yes, MULTIPLE PEOPLE. ADULTS. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s a good Jew vs bad Jew? While you’re at it, what’s a good Republican vs bad Republican; good vs bad Democrat?… https://t.co/ja71vdu1AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marcus_R_Fuller @StribSports @GopherMBB Love the way this #gophers team stands as brothers together 💛🏀🐿〽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[so u dm me my own photo with heart eyes but didn’t even like it?   electric chair]]></document><document><![CDATA[fun story for all yall, i’ve known of his account on instagram for so long but we met at my birthday party! ✨✨ https://t.co/SKh6B97Jzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live: Watch First at Five from WUFT News via @wuftnews https://t.co/JlglDoINCN Check out our @UF @SFRC_UF students… https://t.co/S7Od2ucD2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraFlowersE @hayden_pacl @JeremieLever @arghavan_salles @A_P_S_A @AlexSilverMSTP @careyjans @MDPhDToBe… https://t.co/xLcPgpr5VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shame on you, @SenFeinstein. What a disgusting way to speak to kids. They know that the future of our planet is mor… https://t.co/pK6TMR8HXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do #US #airlines fly @Boeing #737Max*s? There are at least 69 #737Max aircraft in service across @SouthwestAir,… https://t.co/BhCZcATdMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCVB No its embarrassing, and this team needs to clean up its act. We cant defend as fans at some point they go to… https://t.co/eMvt3h1zj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoodleNessa @twitweeting I would, too ....initially.  Then I'd probably shrug and eat it 😅😌😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollysmcdonough @transscribe @yashar Hahahaha 😂 https://t.co/6d4e5irPK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraaKW My really solid advice is to not use hot glue and that’s all I can offer you. She’s amazing though, you’re going to have a blast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to finally get out for a bit. We can’t be @OrlandoCitySC’s season opener but @bunmking and I are absolute… https://t.co/oqJQD0wbqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theboxershow Absolutely heartbroken. I loved him! I wanted to marry him when I grew up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to post a general statement:  If you don’t like me, that is OK.  If you have an issue with me, please m… https://t.co/8cWQTZ3iLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[excited for my nap during my lash appointment tomorrow because that’s the only time ill have to nap lolz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find something that makes your heart burn with desire and CHASE. THAT. SHIT. ❤🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello there Austin! Missed ya! 💙🇺🇸 first @sxsw sneak peak gig tonite at The German Haus tonite 8.30. See y’all there https://t.co/I1BbgkDrSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOMIE I SEND ALL MY FRIENDS NICE DRUNK SNAPS SND IM STILL SINGLE AF SO EXPLAIN THAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’s the weather in the 254???? I wanna get my sister some booties lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoT question: if the whitewalkers die in water, who went down and put those chains around that dragon to pull him… https://t.co/sL6OUGL3Ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[My band Carpool Tunnel playing at the Raytheon sponsored Girls Scouts in Stem fundraiser]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has begun. Happy Mardi Gras from New Orleans!! #MardiGras #NewOrleans #GreatestFreeShowOnEarth https://t.co/vzRO6OOw1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob4L Yeah that’s what BP said in 2010 when they dumped all their oil in the water what did ducks ever do to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mother says a student recorded her son in a school bathroom and shared it with his classmates. And her son wasn’t… https://t.co/44kZsrKBH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s me pulling the fakest smile in front of a Banksy. It’s a cool memory though, I’m glad my Dad was always cool… https://t.co/hkZAi5eNam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to see Bernie enter the race, but now that he has be prepared for a thorough Media Roots assessment of his foreign policy 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[If were on the boycott binge instead of #FireTuckerCarlson I say we #FireNancyPelosi #FireAdamShiff… https://t.co/r9mRbAuKOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to keep a cat from running out a door. A big world for a little kitty. Ideas? I am blind so can’t keep a look o… https://t.co/sgI4As9FFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems consider President unfit because he brought back jobs strengthen military builds wall to protect border, broug… https://t.co/Xh0z736M44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for @johnlegend and @LetsFreeAmerica support on #Amendment4 in Florida. More specifically GRATEFUL for lif… https://t.co/XMhyNeiIEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitallyDownld @Keirabisexual @mattdkerr @elbirdilara @CaNettoyant So you enjoy provoking people huh?  Shall I di… https://t.co/txWAG9Ol8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not stand people that have to share their opinion about e v e r y t h i n g other people say/do. Just let em live man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some hilarity. Random Funny Pictures – 65 Pics https://t.co/BN7oyEXYbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Impeachment is not enough, I want him and a Deadman Walking Pence to resign!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9s4COPs @Brian_Robison @tkeleiott @K9Telle @kkschiller @PattieAnn5 @sassysgoodies @LivePdFans @TaskForceRC… https://t.co/JvpDPDBKPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever I was doing this summer than had me glowing. I HAVE GOT to get back to that bc looking at old pics and vid… https://t.co/v3XgLqtcYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[States are failing on #vaccinations. Federal govt must lead  Scott C. Ratzan @HKS_BizGov Barry R. Bloom… https://t.co/auwuiwSOuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight #Stop2 on our #JourneyToSupportLocal checking bumpcitybrass and the big #13pieceBand laying down the #Funk… https://t.co/JRnMW0aE4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of #WomensHistoryMonth and #InternationalWomensDay coming up, @MoetHennessy recently hosted a tasting expe… https://t.co/UcriHlhpA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol.  😁The View’s Meghan McCain calls in sick after getting brutally mocked online all weekend https://t.co/HO4uq4787l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sullen_meiko @CarolineRaby @chantalkahle @cee_elena @ShannaSmlder @23__juju @MeffiMorningst1 @MorningstarFans… https://t.co/o8odUKYhGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleismyna2 @LadyTi88 @NO1GifQueen @hwivesfanatic I do not get all the feed on a lot of things. Only here and there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTrakas @bhsjustus Day 1 I have accepted the challenge from former student and now teacher@CoachTrakas to post… https://t.co/HTSGq1Dyne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate International Women's Day with us this Friday! The Women of TBH host a Rosh Chodesh Dinner then our follo… https://t.co/XQrluvmmO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reshmasaujani Please pause to celebrate all you have done ♥️Happy International Women’s Day @IntlWD @GirlsWhoCode… https://t.co/zCwe7ar9Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a kind soul to sell me a ticket at face value. This really upsets my plans for tonight which were going home… https://t.co/QKSabJyBs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payless closing??? Oh im bout to run up a bag on sum sandals in that hoe 😌😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[goodnight tonight was so much fun i didn’t want it to end i have more stuff i’ll post tomorrow &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MODSUN was done sharing @bellathorne pussy that was you yours lmao pussy mine is a joke . You guys just grew up it… https://t.co/qAJZBdaR7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marco! @tech_sps @jlittlef1 @chrlafferty @MrsCzak #techcenterrenovation https://t.co/iNKvGaoEZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pati_gallardo I'd love that! Thanks! I don't mind either way regarding my name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All i can think about rn is the video of The Jonas Brothers where they pick up a table, turn it, then Joe stomps in… https://t.co/tMN07mrWKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambertamblyn is everything, but that blouse on @TheView this morning?! YAS HUNNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband tried to get me the official gravity blanket for Christmas and it was sold out everywhere!! I still want one so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanlonwu That’s Santorums ONLY “defense” for trump. He’s such an idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_scottreid I would never compare colleagues to farm animals. But if I *were* going to, I'd get an agent to pitch i… https://t.co/56tiVL2DKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny! A “Billionaire grifter”! You have reached an all time new low with that stupid comment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suwareh_moses @CNN Born or not he was a President twice. That ship has sailed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsrisser Most definitely. We actually had more 5-7 last year. And a few of the speakers are secondary in nature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven Thought you were going to say the movie Hostel...but wait it was way worse than that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradenjohnson32 @2021FZS Congrats Braden!   Well deserved!  You will be missed on the FZS soccer field next year.  Good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scary but credible stuff. Anyone who is BFF with the evil MBS of Saudi. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for following me  I'm most appreciative. I'm very grateful. I'm sorry I can't follow you back. But I've reached my limit.  😁❤☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TALE2019 Setting the scene for free enterprise. Just heard the train go by as well! https://t.co/SXx4dQKO2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying breakfast out with hubby before I’m off to work 😊 @ Red Barn Restaurant - Towaco, NJ https://t.co/0hUYh6UZwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lectura del taller de escritura en español.  Reading of the writing workshop in Spanish.  lunicornsny 🦄🏳️‍🌈 📸 by mm… https://t.co/dgHmAPvHZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruthMaga @RichardTBurnett Oh my!!!! I hope nobody is taking her serious. What is her claim??  A bunch of nonsense!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@user14201 @itsmetoday1 @IngrahamAngle @Acosta Says who?  Do you have proof to back you up,  or do you just listen to Jim Acosta?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuddling in bed with my cats, cause im worth it!!! https://t.co/PcY24inYnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re never too old for Dr.Seuss . Had a nice discussion about themes and then read my favorite Dr.Seuss book, “Gr… https://t.co/2PYeUm4C0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra I'm f**king tired of people treating them with kid gloves.  They're adults, treat them as such.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Another pathetic lie from a master liar. Please Resign, we want our country back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my brother and I text about is @GordonRamsay and how annoying our mom is]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my walks around work I’m used to seeing condoms, alcohol bottles, weaves...but big ass crab legs?? Who the hell… https://t.co/9YK8TXnvWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen! Always Queen! Best face! Brilliant! #TeamMaura #TeamAva #GH https://t.co/H8JvQJLvdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breaking moments ago in the #RayquanBorumTrial — our @ColeenHarryWBTV says the judge has DENIED defense’s motion f… https://t.co/7Y8UAYG2Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FenchurchDent42 @DarlaShine It’s actually a real person- the wife of. Trump administration buffoon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThoreauSquad It’s cool. I’ve got my sexual assault survivor’s group therapy tomorrow night anyway 😵😵😵😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[breaking news, beauty twitter!!! olaplex has made another product for us to spend all our money on! https://t.co/d1bbzm1ULE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I started at @TuftsNutrition, I didn’t think a few years later I’d be pursuing my PhD in agronomy focusing on… https://t.co/vni79ciR3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeriLRyan Happy Blessed Birthday Jeri! I hope you’re getting a chance to relax after the move 😊🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repito , quién tiene a ese corrupto, mañoso, viejo cochino en la @FCF_Oficial , #fueraalvarogonzalezalzate]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking @RyanBeesleyFox5 @FOX5Atlanta @FOX5StormTeam monitoring severe weather #fox5atl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall this little boy post me as his wcw bc he broke up with his girlfriend 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @ChrisCuomo Maggie- remember when you and Mike were interviewing Trump, glanced at each other, and came… https://t.co/GwkWChpwUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Icy conditions could be a problem this morning. And it's only getter colder. Your full forecast @nbcwashington.… https://t.co/Nzhg0aVlmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[〰️ what did you want to be when you grew up? 〰️ I spent my whole life, from age 6 until I turned 23 hyper focused o… https://t.co/OGj74F9JWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalforNC @DugginsBetsey This is GREAT‼️👏🏼👏🏼 Any amount of #WASTE we can change and/or #RECYCLE Is #AWESOME 4 our… https://t.co/M3oIp36Nb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bout to make a another Poptropica acc bc I forgot the other 5 I had]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to continuously snooze some people on FB 😴 #bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHiltonx @MorganOrtagus @henryolsenEPPC @SaraCarterDC I voted for a strong President not a SAINT! I will vote… https://t.co/lu7kUYABhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t want this any other way. The most polite and biggest gentleman, the happiest but yet goofiest, the young m… https://t.co/Avuh07wLp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need 3 females that’s in Houston and wants to be in a section with me at rose gold !! DM ME !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabois @vkhosla @samir keith, loved meeting with you and appreciated your candor and feedback throughout the process. best of luck @ FF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the dog wants to go sledding too - Democratic Underground https://t.co/3clJoPDofR via @demunderground]]></document></documents></author>