<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LadyTi88 @NO1GifQueen @duchess1831 @dchinn2005 @carrie4502 @KKay7777 @wetbulldog @sprigwig @AuntiePegg… https://t.co/dtMDqE43BC]]></document><document><![CDATA[assumpt.jpg (4668 bytes)Remember, O most gracious Virgin Mary, that never was it known that anyone who fled to your… https://t.co/5U0uuMmAje]]></document><document><![CDATA[so w that being said, can anyone help me figure out the legal laws of smoking pot in a legalized state but in a ren… https://t.co/KBI7LxmxuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cyn93976850 When someone goes on the show, either as the Bachelor(ette) or a contestant, they’re subject to strict… https://t.co/Nv4vU3c6VW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democratic Party Attacks on Ilhan Omar Are a Travesty via @thenation https://t.co/XixpZVWlnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things change. And friends leave. Life doesn't stop for anybody. #lifelessons #behappy #thankful #quotestoliveby… https://t.co/WucDEJndgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will only hit you when they think it’s convenient.    so, I’ll respond when I think it’s convenient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumdogMilionair — for Halloween, you need to be Johnny Cage &amp; I’ll be Jax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who t** f*** is he.  Not letting HR1 come to a vote on the Senate floor.  Hes just as guilty of SUPPRESSING votes o… https://t.co/hWBuS15Zi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writing a paper on the legalization of marijuana is one thing I could honestly go on for hours about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned about some new resources and collaborated on some new ideas for teaching finance. #FunFriday  #BusEdu… https://t.co/Dy33kU7CbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Summer House Santa Monica in North Bethesda, MD https://t.co/lo3mNk2eLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexayall @kingno_ @Brand1fr @MoonSwag13 @Sneaky_Bounce I’m not crying...you’re crying....  👆🏼#WreckEm https://t.co/fSN0ojsxTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[KA had the best time collecting data as they surveyed the  @WilemonSTEAM family today!! Thanks @Tiph1227 for all th… https://t.co/4S7EkfQQMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns @Nickelodeon I've already watched it 3 times. The kids love it. You did an awesome job. Congratulat… https://t.co/YljS7KaKR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[random person: *tries to ruin my life* me, just trying to chase my dreams: https://t.co/fAdR369TuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it that I’m tired af but can’t sleep because my stomach still hurts Ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emma4Change Much love and respect to you, Emma. Take care of yourself. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEE1031 @sbg1 One never really gets away with it. It may appear that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching my son the art of photography. #sunsetcliffs https://t.co/rvfMlL9c3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday mantra to live by.....have a GREAT Friday #BeKind #LoveOneAnother ❤ https://t.co/HbzmaUwFj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photogrid #handtattoo #rosetattoo #realismtattoo #newtattoo #customtattoo #anotherone #tattoomodel… https://t.co/YQHCyQWB2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Seems to me it was the other way around. Who are you trying to fool?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely think I need to cut back on the wife things I do because I deserve a ring 🅿️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slfogus i’m sad because this means i only have one year left with you😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wishful_wink @bigangrylaw @GregNorberg Obuma tried but he did not have a Democrat congrees. They will nationalize… https://t.co/adv6uGceUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌠  💎iam.queen.alma  📸 lazyboi_photography . . .  Book a wearejerseydiamondz model today! https://t.co/NsYxFgkgcp __… https://t.co/0BbxxU2Jj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG this lady pulled up next to me and I think she’s the same thing.  🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third run this week, I am really excited to feel this good! #feelingood #running #runningmotivation #workout… https://t.co/7zTRtXFWpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This piece resonates with me. Seeing Kim and Kelly Deal in the “Cannonball” video, and Luscious Jackson open for… https://t.co/K2oAT9modf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giant Birthday S/O to this little Guy My Nephew A'mil on turning 1 today. God will always keep You Protected. 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈… https://t.co/GZZzuZczJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to hate the saying, "Love Yourself First".  Let me be clear- You've always deserved love, whether you love y… https://t.co/MTfcc3I7Tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you're tell me that not only do I get to see @joeymcintyre in @WaitressMusical this April, but also… https://t.co/nUIrmrr4KR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic mildly in love w/ this snap filter 🤪 https://t.co/1ljH6LfrsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/9pW8mUjKjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a physical affection type of person completely sober and when i have alcohol in me, i just want to be held… https://t.co/Q6z7bWHpsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The SASSiest look possible @khew885 @ Box Elder, Montana https://t.co/QdCuB1l3MZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[People have been telling me that the new dating app is just sliding into people’s DMs but like, how do you find som… https://t.co/uU7wn1YUDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Sheet Cake Cookies by @texasfarmbureau https://t.co/69G7YhjTZN via @kbogard]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking thru On Demand one eve...I came across My Christmas Love...and when I saw Bobby Campo was in it, I decided… https://t.co/CtaMXc5VdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ears/nose/sinus system is starting to act all the way up because of this weather and now i can’t sleep smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayRouseDC That pillar of virtue and honesty, Roger Stone (indicted liar), snuggled up to Matt Gaetz, the congress… https://t.co/3ysPLAGraf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedDoberman @Cass_C7 Breeder Is Shutdown, ended up w another Dobie Girl❤️.  Sat in back seat n held her my Lap for long drive home 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveL324 @SusanChatzky @arlantrip @MattWalshBlog And the 3 houses are his maids that he paid for... so na-na-na-boo-boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up on #TheOscars2019 this morning in between live shots and our morning photographer just asked if I was o… https://t.co/VF04Q8dNSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is for my grandson Jonah, I love you &amp; miss you!! @ New Braunfels, Texas https://t.co/4Z9Zfkd483]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all of this time, I am not ready to go back to work and I still can’t wake up on time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a "sfw" version of Doves in the Wind, do I dare? Lmao its almost all edited out but still]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EnoughIsEnough #GunReformNOW #SensibleGunLaws #VoteForOurLives #VoteThemOut #MSDStrong #ResistHate #TrumpLies… https://t.co/2gFeSJgCc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futbolfan1999 @lyn_cade @Bravewriting Not deleted. Twitters random block game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the little-known benefits of house-sitting in winter....morning shovel workout with music❄️🎶🎵… https://t.co/8gdJcqakaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your friend is a keeper when she volunteers to pick your kid up at 3:00am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers are really coming back harder than anyone could’ve ever asked for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroVioki Dale pero que diga "Que conste que yo no queria." https://t.co/7sOjj2Du1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom’s been wanting to get a green parrot and already has the name picked out for him too 😭🙄😩😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a thing or two we don’t have in Utah. A parade where crowds compete for the honor of a tossed bedazzled sh… https://t.co/WNJ4McgNYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got trapped into clicking on a link for a $500 litter box and unfortunately I am going to be bombarded by this ta… https://t.co/ocKbJUX1ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t trust the nigga as far as I can throw him &amp; I already tried to pick him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 @trailmaster2213 Yeah is that right? We really arent that dumb and stupid anymore! Once upon a time you… https://t.co/gg0nESlfLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of phone do you have?  What do you love about it?  What do you hate about it? https://t.co/qEQwbtzpqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chasemadgamer @KitKatBrothel @BunnyRanchNetwk @MadamSuzette @Dianneassistant @sagebrushranch @LoveRanchNorth @bunnyranch Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myFM989 Roads flooded all over Long Point. How many are closed? @NorfolkCountyCA https://t.co/NTYROtE91W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing my tia so happy is literally everything. That woman deserves the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[rachaelteboshair did more than just a thing with my hair 🙌🏼💁🏼‍♀️ #newhair #newhaircut #easttown… https://t.co/v9lEpgVaH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna attend this one on thursday.. time to grill truth, ethics and research to them. hopefully their perception of… https://t.co/2eiXbWqEFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleyydag @NetflixLAT Porque no te llevaste a Slater o a Brandon, señor! Porque a Dylan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clintus By is Youtube being stupid? Comments being disabled is even hitting your recent vlogs. Even your vlog 2 da… https://t.co/MSKO4CP3dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnexpectedThingsAboutAdulthood You can eat cake at 2 a.m. and not get in trouble. https://t.co/1nHNFzmhyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coolcatcassidy @Lin_Manuel Omg right!!! I WISH I could reach that level of elegance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Marv coming back next year? The Reb’s have won 17 games so far. What’s the word? What’s going on?? I have no ide… https://t.co/HQcvcIeJLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeauxColonels @Nicholls_BASE 🔥THAT’S MY SON!!!⚾️ What an exciting game!!! The Colonels were on fire🔥 So very thank… https://t.co/a8dPkUHEbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite ride at union station is the one where people can’t decide how much line they want want  to wait in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇 We Need Better Answers on Nutrition.   Nice piece, includes: ‘Personalized nutrition based on life stage, metabol… https://t.co/CPyjq2xHSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's all get behind this. Energy from light - imagine. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azqueenmama I feel bad for him, but they are glossing over how evil that woman was. She had so many people killed… https://t.co/RgREUYmXMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Miley promotes Pizzagate and Pedogate think she is the A**hole for the perverts why are we concerned… https://t.co/OVgvWRFwRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gracie5111 @jason_vally Megan speaks out of both sides of her mouth...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Sloss  please tell me you’re going to put X on Netflix. That was hysterical! Come back to LA soon!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter Happiness is where you find it live life because you have this oneI hope you have a great awesome amaz… https://t.co/yijS8cwgk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[More pics from the @spurs game! @ AT&amp;T Center https://t.co/5QZyujNBvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soIonis @yashar This is the saddest thing I've seen in a very long time. Love and empathy's unlimited, uncondition… https://t.co/2gCs8xHZbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is my 10 year college class reunion next month? 😳 this must be a mistake- I’m still 19?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young mothers... if your baby daddy cheated on you once before, he WILL do it again. Save yourself the pain y BÓTAL… https://t.co/QxCFefjJbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[you people posting beach spring break pics are being really inconsiderate to those of us sitting at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[yah well the other day I confused my cell phone for a mcchicken, he ain’t special]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown aka Mr. Big Chest to be traded by the Pittsburgh Steelers to the Buffalo Bills tomorrow morning.   #NFL #AB84 #BillsMafia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donald_j_putin As usual, John Oliver explained it, and how terrible it is.  They were definitely not informed abou… https://t.co/2QBuwHroUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love bumping into my #MWMTL ’Media Women Montreal’ Conference partner at #GlobalTV. Tickets are moving, so be sure… https://t.co/p9gg3O9v92]]></document><document><![CDATA[And some nights I get to work with a legend #JimHill @cbsla #cbsla #kcal9news #sports #sportscentral #lakers @ Stap… https://t.co/j8AIhiiyfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine*s Day Y*all! I just want to say sorry 4 any1 I may have had to push away today. This was a day I ha… https://t.co/Ia88MQ86AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today during Frieze Art Los Angeles Lady Rocket Foundation also presents Pawel Szanajca Space Mistral Collection An… https://t.co/1h8LlaGTvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @1jimmer What goes around comes around.  Nancy has no control over her gal pals so she throws a hissy fit.😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great day 🌍. Remember #Jesus  Already #planted this #Diamond 💎. Dream  On these books 📚. ☝️😇📝✍️ https://t.co/RtNiCUTjuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 69 days away from graduation and I still don’t know how to make a bibliography without noodletools]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfGodAndMan Fine. Fine. I’m out too for today. Secretary needs a Dad Break and I can assure AnyOne that ain’t t… https://t.co/CQTzyOG23z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brandons a #groovy 60s #speakeasy in #hollywood hidden at Labrea Brew #amaro #spiritsforward #herbsandspices… https://t.co/fLiadK5YuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Some people will say anything for there 15 minutes of fame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland’s been so successful at safety interventions that bikes move 4 times as many people as cars at some inters… https://t.co/OwwXWyvYMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got the cutest little forget me not tattoo today 💐 https://t.co/6QLDWIiBWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean I look young too. But I look young and my age. Depending on the hair style lmao 😂😂]]></document></documents></author>