<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Inbox: @SteveKingIA announces his 4th town hall meeting in #IA04 in 2019. It will be at the Logan Community Center… https://t.co/9bxiBMofQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePME @fantasynational Me if I get a lineup with Burgoon and Taylor through https://t.co/M4Eliakvkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdstalnaked @katy_fit @RichP222 @Mr_Spikey_Head @LifesStyleBlog @A_verynicegirl @MrsTyler78 I actually put a lot o… https://t.co/B52SxnFhp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This scenario is the truth in every nation that is communistic  And socialistic Nation. All anyone has to do who do… https://t.co/D9Xer5x6Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheriff Baldwin has ended the Snow Emergency for Franklin County. https://t.co/g6Zmk5RyYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks w/o TV. Finally got a new one. Too damn exhausted to set it up. Wondering if I missed anything... I only… https://t.co/gVMAUSWhLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[”If the Democrats now start moving down this path as well, then American politics will truly descend into a new dark age.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI: unlike little Cesar's, Domino's, Marco's and Chuck E cheeses this school pizza actually has sauce on it. https://t.co/Vlb9vzIFPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKevinBrady Because only morons and scammers talk about the average. If Sheldon Adelson gets a 40 million dollar… https://t.co/3FB6HXHait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodikantor Don't forget Native Americans, you didn't pay anything, just kill them, that's Capitalism in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickZircher I love that line and say it all the time, in character. My late father loved westerns, and I have r… https://t.co/zQZbBuOJTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump holds Kim Jung Un higher than a murdered U.S. citizen breaking his Constitutional Oath to uphold and safeguar… https://t.co/zFLqpEU638]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeDraper1 Worldwide the organization requires “Safe From Harm” . All adults volunteers and employees from Sunday… https://t.co/u6Ued0Ctg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the always-great @AirCanada service this morning en route to @CtrPubSafExc for CFAI Accreditatio… https://t.co/PnY8k1pGca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBreslowWKRN @WKRN @StewartCoEMA How cool you guys found plants.   Nah I’m kidding you should be ashamed and embarrassed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So loving the service,staff and food at @YardHouse in downtown Burbank  #HalfYardOfAleAnyone https://t.co/b8gOCDwyr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now @RuKCMO discusses how @KCMO partnered with @UMKansasCity to develop regulations for the sharing economy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwainEvent Must really hate Tennessee to sacrifice tournament hopes in order to keep the Vols from winning the SEC… https://t.co/VQVLjqaanc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sergiozaragoza @yahirmusic @menshealthmx No es el caso, este es un caballero! Y pues esta mamado!   Dedicado y dis… https://t.co/CDdAmUstna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving around today on the MoVi. • • • • #ac #assistantcamera #cameraassistant #1stac #1stassistantcamera #filmlife… https://t.co/n3tOMfkvCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Superhero 🦸‍♂️ status ⁦@kaj33⁩ Abdul-Jabbar auctions off NBA championship rings for STEM education https://t.co/EENMHAlQZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseSanchezMLB Great signing for a team that will turn heads and be more than competitive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalljones Petey Pablo did 5 years for armed robbery before he got famous, and then went back to jail for trying t… https://t.co/v4ijz2d10J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rusty_pennies @rachaelpacella @TedNesi Truth hurts sometimes. The fault lies with the madman that attacked them. I… https://t.co/0fBWiEED43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber @RealSaavedra Why do the Dems feel that tearing down America is a good thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist I never understood why people asked for more followers on this site]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @MacyKennedy22 @NatashaAdamsCWH @AlexandraSCWH @AngelJonesCWH @jadastevens420 @KristinaRosexxx… https://t.co/y8yL6TeK2d]]></document><document><![CDATA['Palace of Vivec' #digitalart #Illustrator #landscape #Creative #art #artist  #ArtistOnTwitter #iloveart @bethesda… https://t.co/S3qoQMCSsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt @amazon The @NYCCouncil just kissed 150,000 jobs goodbye. What will @NYCMayor say when Nashville, TN an… https://t.co/gqesZdFAHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Trump Prep: Kim, start the Denuclearization program immediately. Kim: First you h… https://t.co/eUTxsmPzO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Bernie’s announcement at a McDonalds on Georgia Ave. All minority patrons. not a single person watching ex… https://t.co/mr27HHbztv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@childofthewild7 Bus 🚌 driver always made fun of cause I would be asleep before we got out of town.😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warm-up drawing WIP #wip #warmup #drawing #underdog #cansonxlmixmedia #ticonderoga Done in a Canson XL MixMedia ske… https://t.co/FoPPF0fYQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day from the @t_testrote @ Stanley Hotel https://t.co/g7SGXtWLya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n0ahkats @BleacherReport What should have happened... https://t.co/UvWM4qf01l]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady right now on @TheLastWord is a sign of why Dems need to focus on the 60% of voters who aren't a Trump sup… https://t.co/tvqTX3X31a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also problematic is the fact that Charming, as well as the story logic of #Fables itself, tends to conflate his sex… https://t.co/LoCRkHCF9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to come to tomorrow’s matinee of Hello, Dolly! in San Francisco with me and my aunt tomorrow I’ve got a bonus ticket lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine #CreepyUncleJoe so the left want to now openly kill baby’s, sell out our country for votes and now… https://t.co/vmDtu2yrpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desusnice @SHODesusAndMero @AOC ???????, ALEXANDRIA, DO YOU?  I'VE GIVEN UP THREE BUSINESSES TO SUPPORT YOU DURING… https://t.co/bFEnimdWng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally never used you and you were the only person I had sex with in 7 years. I never admitted to any of that. Wth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, that's what it feels like? @ New Haven, Connecticut https://t.co/mMhPAfsOHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EtherAmy Just like Brian and Brain are not the same thing... the apple doesn't fall far... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam,  Since June of 1996, Cobalt has been my home away from home. It was always my safe space. It was my constant e… https://t.co/TON7Nd9mJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report of a large group of people "yelling at each other" in the parking lot of a Bethany apartment complex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the last day of #MPower2019 and man has this year’s class been outstanding so far!… https://t.co/K7HzQ8pLHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fetrow (106) Win Fall P1, DeLawder (113) win 4-2 @GAHSAthletics @GHSWarriorZone]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a blessing to be home yesterday to be able to welcome my first grandson, Samuel, to this world. #grandpa #pops… https://t.co/2CN7tTpyvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to recite this in an #improv set tonight, so you know, #dreamsarereal. #jaws #GOAT https://t.co/bFPgAa9kpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that’s a suicide and a potential bomb threat at @MCO in the last month. C’mon people, do you know how many famil… https://t.co/6zSMZCTWKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the FUCK @EversourceCT Are we ever getting electricity again you guys fucking suck your name should be… https://t.co/HhQyRE2l8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[que brisa foi essa q eu comecei a pensar no meio da aula KKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEsamparish @toejamandearl @wweppvhistory @MelindaBlue Anyone else besides us three? Scammer told me there were four]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moejoemoe1212 @shepherd_kendra This would be me if I tried to drive for longer than 2 hours alone lmao https://t.co/MBieca6ayq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ID was happily and heavily used this weekend 🍾 https://t.co/Swin5uUZvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[BC had this in hand as the 3rd period winds down. That eliminates the Terriers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Facebook is your only control in life you need to rethink why you’re living.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdoyle4479 @cathmckenna Their single use plastics.   I'm doing it for the children.  For lent.   For climate barb....err Cathie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially the ones that look good. Shit really erks the hell outta my nerves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPUBLICANS, sacrifice our children's America for the greed of the 1%...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come meet adorable @KikiCali at the Lone Star Spanking Party! Registration is now OPEN! https://t.co/1nCNxdudcg,… https://t.co/mmspmVsfZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pocos días para que termine el invierno en el hemisferio norte la masa de #hielo en los Grandes Lagos no ha dejad… https://t.co/H5RDgZBcjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revised per hint. @OneMinuteBriefs  @dalger2001  #BUNKBEDS https://t.co/GT4WNLrx4e   #creative #advertising RT https://t.co/erztTKBBc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peak anxiety is being so anxious that it’s keeping you awake and then wanting to make a tweet about it but being an… https://t.co/VLp1a4ChP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it interesting that people who want banks to be regulated don’t believe that social media should be regulated]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JBtheEmcee is about the love of great families, positive party environments, and draped as #ValentineHeartRedJB it… https://t.co/XWDwppaU9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last chance to try the @TasteofBurl Prix Fixe lunch menu at the Greenhouse Café! Enjoy Greenhouse Garden Salad OR S… https://t.co/Y4ungIJIB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd @MollyJongFast Is her actual job just convincing people the stupidest chain posts on Facebook are real?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Download @bestfiends  this game is awesome. One if the best I've ever played. Actually the best by far. ♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's merry. Over the Hill, Getting Old, Senior Citizen Retirement Humor - Old age jokes cartoons and funny...… https://t.co/h5z3aeiiWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@element_n82o How I ironic, you are forced to give money to an insurance company for “in case their is a blowout” a… https://t.co/Od0zE9UNO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nieghbor next door Nieghbor In the back  can not handle why we scream for Vengence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBBonFOX @umichbball @TexasTechMBB @ZagMBB @MSU_Basketball @NevadaHoops @UBmenshoops @BoilerBall @MarquetteMBB @UHCougarMBK Musselman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unyshek @AlitaMovie We are having a semi-343 showing at @ipictheaters on Monday. Wanna indulge again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love every season all year long except pothole season. #DodgeDuckDipDiveDodge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que alguien destape la olla del “porque” la compra esa tan comentada cuando hay tantas cosas más importantes para c… https://t.co/2pe7PQO0Es]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Opposition leader Juan Guaido returns to Venezuela after tour of South American nations (Reuters)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *exists Random white girl at my school: “so like is that like your REAL hair ?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiliBowlNomNom You only need to read what has already been abundantly explained to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This card is good. Let’s see what happens. #ufc @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/4CNHFnCIva]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Maine too. The parties can send you all the junk mail they want and you can’t opt out.  #mepolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my kimmgunn75 #bestiesforlife #foreverfriends  #friendssince12yrsold #30years @ Clearwater South Beach https://t.co/lRdBUPp3fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DeathRocker #DevilWeed #GRMBLGRMBLS #Music #Electronic #Alternative #Rock #Industrial #Shoegaze #Goth #Punk #New… https://t.co/I6lDAurtq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squidbilly929 I doubt it. I think they’re basically equivalent to squirrels in America. Except our squirrels aren’t jacked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkSeriousFace My god. My wife got bored after 10 minutes. A couple drunk dudes tried to help. But it’s a beach a… https://t.co/eQQYgScnOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#healthy #personaltrainer #gymlife #healthylifestyle #enjoyinglife #gettinghealthyandfit #gettingstronger… https://t.co/pQGhvBWktl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ttaryn96 @DanJRScott @BayleighDaily We will stop following , once we find where all the money they robbed for the… https://t.co/EhfRxlLDND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhshanti @kristoncapps @DavidKlion I mean, is it your experience that @eb4everyone are market fundamentalists and… https://t.co/zGPafyOnGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiderAnalysis we dont need any ex broncos/ravens.  back end of career.   we need ROOKIES.  lets build something gruden]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Medford Driving School Brooke is home safe and sound after her first 3 hours! Thanks @SharonBrescia they… https://t.co/hudUBB6971]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitneymuseum #andywarhol #andywarholart #andywarholfromatobandbackagain #andywarholretrospective @ New York, New… https://t.co/FxXz48ZhWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out not all of the constraints where connected to the saveLayoutGuide but instead to the contentView. If that… https://t.co/s2L1E0bZw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los mandaste no mi borrachín con todo el dinero que te robaste estás pagando a estos pobres que por un peso hacen l… https://t.co/SsKo3PkK5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyValentinesDay to all of the #WestwoodRedhawks out there (and to YOU as well!)!!! ❤️Here’s hoping that you get… https://t.co/yqDgQVEe6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious accident in #SouthRaleigh on Tryon Rd at Lk Wheeler Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grabbed everything then went to the end for my backpack. That went fine. I am 30 minutes from boarding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to motivate and introduce the Vision of Vida Divina to 600+ people at Apollos 2000 ! Wish me luck! This is ge… https://t.co/dkTxOb9pty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AOC    You’ve got to admit the “pompous little twit” line was hilarious...and not really inaccurate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay @Patreon, this is ridiculous. I opened a patreon link, but there’s no open in app button, and if I search for… https://t.co/lSdG6kSf27]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what’s worse: This petition or that dudebro who started a Petition to have The Last Jedi removed from… https://t.co/f8lQBz8XFA]]></document></documents></author>