<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the #ML1 @magicleap @riozilla @rabovitz 😍 I can’t wait to build out compelling social spatial computing… https://t.co/chsSGaeTgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the #AlesiaCBride in couture gown of her dreams designed 30 days before her wedding! Our team of bridal mast… https://t.co/va5VW9XyJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day friends! ✌🏼🖤😉 Photographer: mdanielsphoto  . . . . #valentinesday #likeimgonnaloseyou #booty… https://t.co/GoVrIpiyrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum @Wait4It494 As we were discussing crew yesterday, the general public has no idea how many people a… https://t.co/NqEJi4wOgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can't stand these dead cold weeks of winter. I feel like it's a waste of life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is fucking stoked at work right now because we all just looked at our bonuses 😭😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay!! See you all tonight!!                 #Repost @GreatFaithC3  Join us tonight at 7:30pm and connect with women… https://t.co/iuPLbCXkxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney breakfast beers - Drinking an 329 Lager by @goldenroadbrew @ BaseLine Tap House  — https://t.co/R5cWEiJp2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ElEquivalenteGringoDe Alberto Carrasquilla @MinHacienda es ... @AlbertoBernalLe 🎭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deplorable_Man @Rysa5GoldRing Wouldn’t it be considered an act of God?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verbocarne Make them laugh, sweetheart. And be broken. Ladies love broken things they think they can fix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that bankofamerica is the presenting sponsor of the Vincent Van Gogh exhibit! A must see! #MFAH @ The Museum… https://t.co/S09UJQ5UYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshAngus @guardiannews And pop without an Iggy in front is just pop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackvoices @TMODOM @astrostarbright @laycien @liligil @LittleMissFlint @kiernamayo @JackandJillInc @MidgeEpstein… https://t.co/ZZxvFbVQWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my friends are different , I don’t see flaws In my friends . Vibes , energy , personality. That’s real ✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraSewellTV @realDonaldTrump @wfaa Border security is not a national emergency. Gun violence is a national emerge… https://t.co/syunbPYNSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eedwardsellis She just wants attention.  Meghan has no real opinions that do not differ from the standard republic… https://t.co/FRcqgOI0V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ostendorff @EMjennielle I think the point @JonBoeckenstedt made is this: If you can not talk about the core probs… https://t.co/LCYP2COVGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz I’m an old flight attendant and I would have written this note to you as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcycology @CamGuthrie @PedroGryphon @cityofguelph And bylaw enforcement can be a source of revenue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs @tenzingmckenzie Remove the Republicans corruption from Senate, replace Trump, then the Viper Pit… https://t.co/POHZUafATi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I played Cocky Asf by Megan last summer for someone and they didn’t get hype... this is when I realized I needed to expand my friend group.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshTAdams14 good luck!!  I will be in St John’s cheering on Canada! 🇨🇦 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardCC and met inspirational students who will be soon be completing their BSN and then applying to @JHUNursing… https://t.co/eqvspd4GIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, My Little Leprechauns! I hope you have a wonderful day full of Shamrock Wishes and Leprechaun Kisses. https://t.co/sqdPsVQkYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like airport departure terminals anymore, they remind me of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for this piece. Shannon shared my girls’ stories, because that’s an actual portrayal of what choosing life… https://t.co/ukM2mVsljo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got drunk and tipped my waitress $100 and chipped my front tooth so badly. I’m not drinking again for awhile I hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m beyond happy with how life is right now, I definitely  am not looking for anything. It’ll come in God’s timing.… https://t.co/O22bpnz9ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDiehl20 @Unveil616 @_DarkMoonLilith @BestNotBroken @realdannimorgan @FarFromFinal @FallOfTwenty7… https://t.co/9f6m9tVnmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Wow, 4 all the people who believe in this hoax I really feel sorry for you! I thought ur meltdown was b… https://t.co/zTImcQ1Gak]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pretty sad that I can’t get the tattoos that I want, because of the career path I’ve chosen 🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great turnout tonight at Blogging for Thought Leadership. Learning lots of valuable tips! @jswomentech #blogging… https://t.co/338bo2cCeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @jessicacline23 (get_repost) ・・・ @ Warren, Ohio https://t.co/NKdZZ1qouF]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIP &amp; Artist bags Thank you!  @bocaresort hashtag_country oldcampwhiskey  You are the best❤️ . . . #country… https://t.co/HsYuvFcAm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlancollins WOW!! You are up early!  Please be careful and get some rest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GRWM is on my story now 📲 coverfx power play foundation • @tartecosmetics shape tape concealer • @rcmamakeup no col… https://t.co/zx5d1OpFMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw someone post on Facebook “if only the government funded adoption like they did abortions” 1 the gov never… https://t.co/tWqZONKdjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always an excellent experience to attend and speak at the Women in Leadership Conference, and to spend time wi… https://t.co/iZgLnGBMxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KizzyBits It’s super duper cute!! Not too short in the front, which is how things get awkward 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to come together as one people keeping our eye single to fighting evil and corruption wherever we may find… https://t.co/LaWNfvzGme]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m said to see the Kaleidoscope food go because it was a easy lunch spot. But excited for the new building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_Luvs_Us @Jimmysimmonds1 @Jilliemary @KarenSLeonard1 @ClockworkHamma @roads2 @AnwarManwar004 @Iluvinspireu… https://t.co/ytB31esbcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u get a chance go see him! ♥️ wish I could! 🌴Cat City 23 February! 🎉 #pm37 #feb2019 #musiclovers #youngtalent @… https://t.co/hsDsrXtnvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a tour of the Wildwood Grove construction at Dollywood https://t.co/XFvaQ97DCE via @knoxnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[uhhhhh i stayed up till 3am not realizing i have fucking work rn. im honestly gonna die today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MenTryVideos https://t.co/ujPArWaqfP you guys need to watch this channel. It is sooo funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmightyMXTPZ 🏚💎💰 Be My Host For My Next Tape Coming Soon!!!! I won’t take a no 🔥‼️💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 @Eva99279633 Yes!  I often wondered why they never leaked. Now we know why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I freaking hate going to the dentist and having to catch up with my favorite hygienist while her fist is in my mouth🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[#everywoman who #fights #t1d either as a #warrior or as a #mom needs to be tagged. #legit #type1diabetes is… https://t.co/853QtyGDC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies of Cinema is going to Austin, Texas for the weekend! Can’t wait!! Made me thing of Slacker (1990) and Richar… https://t.co/3DEyxjDb45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BewzNewznVewz I just read about this, seems like a major drawback to the diet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsudol @DrJacieMaslyk Exactly but today things have changed. Many students that may not be strong in math but are… https://t.co/NPXRBcMzEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch doesn’t even realize how toxic she is to people... I’ll sit back and watch though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeybagovdonuts Yes. I have two granddaughters. One is seven and one is two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisAmerLife That MSG story kept me driving around just so I could finish it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Coach @cnimmo and @wbgbasketball!!  Years of building a culture paying off!!  👏 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to having respect for your significant other? People these days are so shitty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Tammy doesn’t break Lip’s heart because y’all know he’s a super simp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping yourself &amp; your mind busy is good and all until the shit you been avoiding hits you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This event is sold out but join me online to hear strategies for analyzing your opponents data. Excited for stimula… https://t.co/IGC55Z6HTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDisability @robertwickens Keep fighting for gains Chris. You are great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreybowles28 @johnlukedaidone @TrueDetective @HBO Thank you for the information. Interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so bad at relationships, after 3 months their constant presence annoys tf out of me; being questioned bout everything- EVEN WORSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happens a lot. I went to a nat’l tournament with my 14U team and in a room full of about 60+ coaches only abou… https://t.co/T1K8yMUfXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump RUSH IS A DRUG ADDICT.  ARRESTED FOR IT..... Like most of your close friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abby_sherlock @michaelaaann @SabbyrinaW @100Thieves Damn. ❤️❤️🥰🧞‍♀️🧞‍♀️🧞‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How long has it been since someone touched beneath the surface of your skin and captured the attention of your soul… https://t.co/LqtpaHBTjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVEG001 @Astro_Eustice @cristy_hamilton @KellyKorreck @NBC10_Kelly @NBC10_Patrice @Beth_Lizet @Hadrians_Gate… https://t.co/RJNvK6XMBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to every person who has ever told me I can't. You are just another reason I will and I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_chi_town_eb @MeeMichie @Cofe6370 @Naahledge @12Chains @divateach37 @Imdatchick1985 @BIGJAMES_2 Not me I gotta m… https://t.co/auWa964W1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate to admit it. I'm gonna watch this play out but as much as I hate James Kennedy, I am on @TomSandoval1… https://t.co/3BJxiSdxnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kody on Sister Wives said they want to move to a conservative state but a liberal town [so their family will be acc… https://t.co/mXH70CrUxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Frank from Granite Countertops and more, we appreciate your business and friendship, look forward to more… https://t.co/J9JBlIbzjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZENLTHZ @Grahamy911 From getting an asus monitor haha I think. Idk she gave me a link]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccislamabad  #DEVELOP_E12_ISB ASAP @ImranKhanPTI @mohrpakistan @ePakistanToday @PAKSupremeCourt  @mophrd… https://t.co/vq9AL2XVBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/YBSwk2Q2hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepped and ready to volunteer at the snack cart and NOT be tempted by all the deliciously yummy options... (Rice K… https://t.co/VyLMH1IPpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[alllllll i wanted was to go the Dreamville festival in April.. maldita pobreza https://t.co/XX3N9Rphzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson Really wanted to go see #CaptainMarvel with my daughter. But with all the #feminist #SJW propaganda behind it I might just pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDB_AZ @seanhannity I know it’s not shutting down the Government. Have you seen what’s in the bill? Everyone wants… https://t.co/1kIUMoB0FI]]></document><document><![CDATA[He who dwells in the shelter of the Most High Will remain secure and rest in the shadow of the Al… https://t.co/FFSWoMkoZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace solecito. Frío pero solecito.  ¡Sí son buenos días! https://t.co/XKbU8R59dZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeybear85 @hooleil My running list has included most of these, too, but I did *not* know about kaffir! Glad I do now 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brox2bChuck @MarkLazerus Ex-Yotes: Murphy, Perlini, Strome Ex-Hawks: Hinostroza, Oesterle, Hjalmarsson, Panik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.... not a lot going on around here. Should be a fun few weeks. (@ DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Newark Ohio in New… https://t.co/ldD2U2nHcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better to kill an innocent by mistake than spare an enemy by mistake.  - #PolPot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg thank you 😊 @Kimberl38218406  thank for your help please let me know if you have anything ❤️😇😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typennington @JeremyParsonsTV @DougDesignsReal @RealPaigeDavis @andreaboehlke @peopletv @TLC Hi Ty I can't hardly Wait xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CthruHD how are you ever gonna get a follow back with a name like that? @thenickgass]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyWomensDay2019 Wishing you all continued strength, success, and sheer happiness! #makeupbymimitran… https://t.co/hqOu0HbNVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si alguien me pudiera hacer el favor de arrancarme la tráquea estaría eternamente agradecida]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vivi made Abe Lincoln at school and then created this. @faitsclass #BengalPride #TeamOrcutt  #TwitterBattle19 https://t.co/BXymCJhMpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjoyner1010 @xtinatkacik Ha! No problem. I figured such recipes exist. I confess I recently was looking up cake re… https://t.co/BzmznlIJlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time for me to face the facts: I am a cat lady without any cats. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtwarming 2019 @BellAdreal @Samuelhawley20 @WC_Athletics https://t.co/4ZAG9BruCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching all these little junior high kids walk into the Y &amp; realizing I used to be one of them 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twood20122 @1woodardkay It’s definitely the other way around bc you’ve always got some dumb shit to say lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SciATM so if farmers only grow commodity crops because of farm policy - why does CA grow speciality crops? Fruits,… https://t.co/4Il5rrAaOF]]></document></documents></author>