<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Let’s please wait a year before we attack green crap! Like President Trump said!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree with what you are saying ... but... the cheapest ticket last for the NC T Duke was ~2700]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMYLYNNnj @ProsAndConCons Yeah it really was. I just loved the idea of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of my vacation! And after that meeting I’m more determined than ever to stop working for the fucking man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorWhat1983 @MrNiceGuy18_58 @GeekToMeRadio @UpToTASK @CBNostalgia @GeekVibesNation @WriterStreamer… https://t.co/GFpPURqzgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KaceyMusgraves is the GOAT. Ok I'm exaggerating.  Her doing a song by Selena and me actually enjoying it is impressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha yup. I dislike this song  but whatever lol T - Pain back in the day #BuyYouADrink I’m not in jr high anymore s… https://t.co/LVTcyZP7PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devin_Patrick_ @Abdul_616 @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Oh the words are breaking people's bones.… https://t.co/rREi9t3ZEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Robert  @tommydidario  @GioBenitez  @NicGuaderrama  #GoodMornimgAll😊😘😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudes at the mall already bothering me about dirty shoes. I don’t need any help🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiniebeany Who is this dumb dickhead? Brainwashed idiot🤪 https://t.co/N2qfk1zc9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel free to share! A few of our adoptable pets that we currently have at our shelter. We have plenty more dogs and… https://t.co/zaoXl3LUEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@810varsity @skylineproud @PlattsburgTiger @PlattsburgHS @NPNowZenner @SJNPSports Is it working?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mantenho minha opinião, Jardine saindo, @rai10oficial deve pedir o boné também. Uma vergonha . #fora @LecoPresidente]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my brother for life @CalebKellems hope it’s the best one yet 🥳 https://t.co/jRP1JdmHxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futurepundit Computers do too much of our thinking. We’re doomed when they do all of the learning. @mims]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathantolbert :) My rule is two a show: Thursday night performance and Saturday night performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastel with kellyeden.. shocking, huh? 😁  #kellyeden #johnremus #throwback #pastels #pinkhair #tattooedgirls #👙… https://t.co/g64OmgKyEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Special Hoperations by @FatHeadsBeer/@barleybrowns @ Johnny J's Pub &amp; Grille — https://t.co/tDsOc5NT43]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY does every Uber/Lyft smell like a can of Febreze exploded in there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_mito51 I just put $100 in Nuttings pocket at 7Springs. Good thing it’ll go towards getting MyHeroZero at skyblast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[humor for me today. Done with finals ... #CollegeLifeMemesM https://t.co/8EAQTNsur6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pike Family Nursery - @pikenurseries in Marietta, GA https://t.co/zeOxLxYxcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathmckenna Mom .your chidren can buy house $1 200 000. and get $14./ hour.but from the own windows can see not wo… https://t.co/YDNhTXVMFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finnish Government Collapses Due to Rising Cost of Universal Health Care via @freebeacon https://t.co/GM449L6Btd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilsonCalvert I mean, maybe that's nice to have, but again even today HD barely happens on HD capable screens. And… https://t.co/C9Inqf3R0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/8/2019 - 19:51 Temp: 58.0F   Hum:  90% Wind: 1.0 mph Baro: 29.875in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.06 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion and RJ 1st game vs. UNC... I’m thinking they combine for 60+ and win easily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog “Hasta Cuando” by Tejano artist David Lee Garza Y Los Musicales and True Grit by the Coen Bros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Jes_Lyn_ @2012popper Truly sick.  Where is his family?  He needs to be helped]]></document><document><![CDATA[People blasting Trump about signing some Bibles, would I do it? Heck no.  But those same people didn’t, nor have no… https://t.co/tQFowbJq3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I reckon, I liken' your lichen.  #lichen #cheaha #arizona #azmortgage #ahwatukeefoothills #azhiking #arizonahiking… https://t.co/wq9A9x0NDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[(@ City of Coalinga in CA) https://t.co/6cM6rku1Mr https://t.co/P0UuS0IPwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm.  If there is a conspiracy, it pretty clearly extends in time all the way through to the early days of the Trum… https://t.co/T37ZLAbDw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are lots of weird things about living in Hell’s Kitchen, including the horse that won’t stop fucking whinnying outside my window.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @ashbrauer with get_repost ・・・ @larrybagby Happy Birthday!! Xoxo @ Valley Village https://t.co/D7ff3TlLXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrr42_dap Engage is not what I’m referring to. The DEIFICATION of any race is unacceptable. Period. There’s a diff… https://t.co/tMeOUWHPuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ "Abortionist," aka a doctor who knows what the fuck he is doing. You are disgusting people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveMaze_ @SmallRigChina @SonyProUSA So good! What I want is one that gives you 2 resulting shoes. 1 where the sho… https://t.co/wsgWM00JG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[more creative energy. painting my 🚀 - a present I got half year ago! https://t.co/hlylSj49Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adripalaciosbb @spencer_kain you’re not old enough to drink what the hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy @TheHumble_21 got his bread -- but hate it had to be them. Lol Congratulations, homie. 💡📈]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: Advice: Love is not a weak word. Love is strong and will always contribute to your success! Never be afraid to… https://t.co/J7UcA5E7NX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadreDelTweet @iAlexVilla Agarrando la peda en familia con canciones de Jenni Rivera.🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired of being ignored and left feeling invisible by you. I just want your love and affection. And bc you ne… https://t.co/fon3s0dd8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @JosephConKarne @realDonaldTrump Your freedoms have been attacked, don’t you get it. Yours!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer me puse un calzón de patitos que me regalaron en San Valentín y me preguntaron que si eran patas... por estar sobre los huevos 🥚🥚😅🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6, 1969: @NASA Astronaut Dave Scott enjoys the view from the open hatch of the Apollo 9 command module.… https://t.co/aR5EFv7eAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley home set to break area record and fetch $140 MILLION https://t.co/cjECdDoScQ via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday sent these #emojis to #mytribe #imfascinated on #flyingthroughtheair with a #bowandarrow #😃😂😃😂… https://t.co/ZlY5BKvA8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sup 😋 @Shineys_ @blvssoms  Boston ?🤔 we could all sleep in  same bed let’s cuddle 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cases resulting in discipline would be assigned a score value. After breakpoints were assigned then suspensions etc… https://t.co/wdgAr9JsO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT hace tiempo y alla lejos, los tiempos de la #Scorpio79 Dj de la epoca Ah mundooooo..  Seguimos igualitos mi he… https://t.co/ZdmGHzozMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sc08960854 @BobBrinson1 @RNinMI @Danie1607 @DFBHarvard @QmagaMike @mymynags @misspunk63 @cali_curmudgeon… https://t.co/48pDrzRzC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Look at all those little dopamine squirts! Addiction and teenage brains don’t mix very well... #JustSayin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday February 22 - A.M. Cheat Sheet:     Steve King: I Don’t Need to Apologize for Race Comments;       Smollett… https://t.co/bnK7GfXnlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty morning. #ftcollins #frost #colorado #fortcollins #fortcollinscolorado @ Spring Canyon Community Park https://t.co/I14gDP4AaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[(استثمر فشلك)💪🏻  لا احد منا معصوم عن الخطأ، وإذا لم نحضر أنفسنا للإنتكاسات والأخطاء، فسنصبح أشخاصاً يهدفون إلى الكم… https://t.co/hBlGxueqOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks like it just made its way to the top of my reading list... after I finish @RichardRohrOFM’s “The Univers… https://t.co/P4FTG1pw83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgiarrusso82 Please don't take this wrong. I am amazed at what is going on right now. #but it's still just the reg… https://t.co/iIRSpEQIAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davecahill Podcasts app. I’ve reinstalled it about 7-8 times because eventually it gets into a state where it refu… https://t.co/JIkhopQOuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow has stopped on the West Jordan Bench. 2”+ and melted water a heavy .65”. Impressive for my weather station in… https://t.co/JzK3CMlBNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimsVanDerBeek Momoe Nakanishi. Wait. I think I am doing this wrong. https://t.co/x7cCE8AUG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am unsure if I like these or not... Will keep y'all updated. https://t.co/YAIWQnPbm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cheers my friends #wine @sansliege @ Sans Liege Wines https://t.co/1JdyeEKGhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luke_toups_23 why didn’t you do this last night? It woulda looked way cooler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiFlameFighter @CiciBettaCCMe YO WORD is there a heart tonight!! Stand up! Lmao😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s absolutely necessary that we discover the commonality we have as human beings and begin to live in a world th… https://t.co/hQQa1gLCbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that's her idol dance let's hope she doesn't find another one 😎😎 @aubrybracco @survivorcbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @RealTT2020 @DoingRight1 @TropicaldogMosy @garway95 @nancy_hamm1 @John_R_Berna @galacticaactual… https://t.co/9I96apwxyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If half of #MPLS stays home because of snow again this week I’m moving to the Yukon. #MN #Snowmaggedon2019v2 #putyourbootson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorMBTosi @RADocCorrea @BrassWeb @JMMillsAuthor @edjlazar @sandybarker @NurtureYourBook @jmescoda @RedworldToys… https://t.co/l4ESxYIzW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJMcKean @shujaxhaider I LOVE Townshend’s work on songwriting AND performance. So excited to be seeing The Who aga… https://t.co/L6EpAmoUpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGodfatherMoody Racing was better when fans had less info and talked at work the next day about what happened lol.… https://t.co/iIYJciCuX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randyollis Dropping my mom off at the Indy airport and her departure is delayed (due to fog, I assume). Any idea if/when the fog will lift?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsvaccaro @BroncoPartybus Yeah that’s about one year in to our QB of the future and a whole new regime 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hello there!”  “I HAVENT SEEN A COMIC BOOK SHOP IN YEARS!!!!!”   It’s been 3 years and I still haven’t figured out… https://t.co/tFMwjItkmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaShabad @Bencjacobs @NewsHour @JudyWoodruff @sarajust Thanks Rebecca!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BallStateMBB @BallStateSports @TaylerPersons8 @Treymoses24 Just got my tickets for Senior night and I’ll see you a… https://t.co/bphe671Sfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InSpiteOfTrump vows to pray with @realDonaldTrump in the hope of resolving the dilemma, thoughts and prayers @ChrisCoons 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[this what i don’t get bout white people bc you clearly see this mf soikng but you just gone expect her to stop for… https://t.co/r8xS2Fk4UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ONLY #HOPE we have in #America is the #Gospel of our Lord Jesus Christ! He loves sinners (and Senators) He forg… https://t.co/F6SVt1vZkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorful 90’s Main Street  #disneylandafterdark #disneyland90snite #disneyland #dca #disneycaliforniaadventure… https://t.co/a5mxPPXuQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morenitomarcus Yeah especially when you’re seeing results. Just so happens that for me they’re really miniscule bu… https://t.co/hLfXWBaiG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Push yourself past comfortable.  5 years ago I swore I’d never do another marathon. I lied. I didn’t do as well as… https://t.co/RCFaaohXP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antihero_kate @ChiSportsHomer How ? If you give them a break you have to pay for it with subsidies to the companie… https://t.co/3nm4tX05ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Not coming out of your pocket. Easy to throw other people's money around. You are ignorant. If not ignorant, your a liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeopleofLeeds @guerrillagirl i've always liked england. i'm not an anglophile, i don't romanticize it or put on an… https://t.co/iGP03kQAD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_alexandriah @pretty_boy_zack I ain’t no big baller like tht idk wtf he talkin bout 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonThorne_RPP @oaarchitects @jen_keesmaat @GreggLintern @CanUrbanism @BrentToderian @jmfplan @alexbozikovic… https://t.co/6d1kUL4seo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now we are going to be outraged by the already well-know racism, homophobia, and misogyny of an actor who gave a… https://t.co/IvtQzmlRQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pyramids by Frank Ocean. #lasvegas #tradeshows are #dead 💀 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/YsjdME8OsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brooklyn ⚡️ Thanks for selling out the room and making us feel welcome last night. Onward to da city of brotherly l… https://t.co/CjvEEbcVTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! 6pm @WickedWillysNY in the heart of the Village! I promise you One Great Show! #whereruplaying… https://t.co/acUwS3XJjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Soros is funding the Ass Of Congress A.O.C And she wants to tax at 90% the millionaire hand that feeds her. How… https://t.co/zHDE8OMhzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with SG1 10x19 “Dominion”, it’s a shame that we only got a few episodes with… https://t.co/74QOtkzTYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well all this Fame and movie stuff is really weird hey there cutie wow you're so cute I wish I could be with you fo… https://t.co/PWWIHqJix4]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH AND TOM DOWN THE STREET DROPPED OFF SOME PAINT FOR PLANET RICK. SUCH A SPECIAL PERSON. THANK YOU TOM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@threatsr @JustfiedByFaith @PstAdelokun @InnocentByabag5 @ledrew @Believer037 @des_mel_trc @thankyudearlord… https://t.co/iDOR4lMI4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scout_Finch @cakes_iam Because the media is terrible. Another win for Trump.]]></document></documents></author>