<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[U know its beauty when her best curve is her smile -Fabulous @ Hampton, Virginia https://t.co/RY93urMeAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CupCakeLady1313 @KGonYT @njfarmerwife @CMANGO @Pixxydoodle @nasyryus_hill @4judyblue @DannyLeBlanc24 @dega_boy_87 Tya bestie 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally dressed in the lego primary colors during my trip to #legoland no shame!  😁😝😉 #selfie #dailyselfie… https://t.co/AdBxiXGQuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicoleevents @alixrose @SeattleMaven @VinoSocialNancy @MailePRMedia @OfficiallyLJ @madelinemoy @clairemccool… https://t.co/hKDT6ahWJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So touching. Thank you for being there for Alabama, Mr.President. We are PRAYING for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shake it off CAPS and go kick some ass tonight! 60 minutes of hockey and you’ve got this! ❤️🏒❤️🏒 @tom_wilso… https://t.co/ZgDiWbAeyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHLifestyleTrav @euroventure Absolutely this. I have carried on only for over 10 years now, so it can be done! #EUROVENTURECHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Are you truly developing yourself every day, so you are not a lid on someone else’s success.” -@hollypriestner #XperienceGrowth #KEFR19]]></document><document><![CDATA[re watching Gossip Girl. and realizing how badly Chuck Bass influenced my taste in men since I was 15.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Donald Trump is the greatest scandal in the history of the Whitehouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missed @AjohnBuckley live tweeting tonights @PureWGNA. Maybe he was too busy working on his b-ball skills for the… https://t.co/ZEnnDcfBOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuxSco @gatita_bonita_s @realDonaldTrump @AlecHagel https://t.co/Cr1OCIP8iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaG7985 @kaylaabiancaa Buahahhahhaa yes! Why is this Myranda &amp; @kimberllyguzman !! Her &amp; her wepa moves!! 💃🏻💃🏻☺️👏😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s teen Deb and 2019 Deb’s daughter are both heartbroken over this. Thank you for the memories, Luke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer Skills challenge 2.0 @ESPNNBA #NBATwitter #NBARisingStars #nbaskillschallenge #nbaontnt #headtohead… https://t.co/lwkRbvK62p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealUglyTru2 @ABC I’m thinking of the children. So, I must be way of bat. Plus think of all the Soc.Sec. losers… https://t.co/jHQtZsCrA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penblogger @GhostOfTick @Diaper777 @SeniorBoobies @HavokHawk @LeonWhi63670221 @WillTrumpYou @Atheist_Dragon… https://t.co/OjUzlDdOAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No entiendo porque el color del pezón de Andy Benavides les parece tan relevante?????????? Parecen niños chiquitos]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve spent $300 on concert tickets this past week and I have to buy a $270 pass for my train tomorrow and I’m tryin… https://t.co/VlZp6paYDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 If it killed hamberders and Diet Coke, then it would be a national emergency.....so pissed off with this… https://t.co/YxZ6GYrxwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco https://t.co/GYNDGBHeOW please I have absolutely nothing right now 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is definitely something I need to be more conscious of. Sometimes my temper flares to quickly and I always reg… https://t.co/DTXFVTH7Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ways to help our girls handle the stresses of teen neurodevelopment ttps://www.kqed.org/mindshift/52994/how-to-help… https://t.co/ftYG1JIHfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnip2020 @TuckerCarlson Can’t wait to see that. Let us know when you’ll be on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi I am from the great state of Minnesota and I begging you to please find a way to reign @IlhanMN in.… https://t.co/AVucajC6Rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Softball+Snow+BFFS=Bellarmine Softball ❤️❤️❤️ @ Stacked Pickle https://t.co/bBShxoevrT]]></document><document><![CDATA['Grounds for impeachment’: Kellyanne Conway’s husband shocked by reports Trump tried to punish CNN with DOJ https://t.co/iNLoy3QacK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@and_whatknot 😂😂😂. Tbh I expected nothing less once you said Patriots earlier. You’ll still be fine. People in LA s… https://t.co/XjC4ETNkJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaniemarie_4 buy the person sized ones. they’re half the size of a normal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Job #shedcaptain Keith @ 6568. Thanks for the partnership! #LeadsInSalesWin #ShedConfigurator #LeadsContest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like it takes an hour to get from Latest tweets to the Home Page?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to @SaintSluggo! Everyone shower him with good wishes and vape juice. https://t.co/L9Vhika2vL]]></document><document><![CDATA[4/20 Kapri Hernandez is hosting a trap and soca brunch with 2 hours bottomless mimosas and ting with all types of f… https://t.co/DMofHFtDHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laura24fan @nation_myers @JudyJ31830202 @ToddTPrice24 @JLee418 @Chrisracefan1 @chevychevelle48 @43324FAN… https://t.co/REqDndtqvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_owens O‘ CHarley’s honey mustard is 🐐 on their chicken finger salad!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it’s been a whole week since you have left us. I still keep thinking that your at home looking out… https://t.co/adqKmJVlxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chalkymacalpi @SassyCassyCat @_thecatsays_ @JoyOfCats @brian_blackcat @BartimusTheCat Gots it! 💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giants spring training ⚾️🧡 @ Scottsdale Stadium https://t.co/pTwzah5fGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JonathanKent_ Our Daughter doing her thing!!!  Your a Special Daddy!!! #daddysgirl #honorrollstudent #princess https://t.co/UVTuEUrmCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smartalek180 @JkwalkerAuthor @Fremdschaemen76 @NightlyPolitics @svik232 I am a registered Independent. I cannot vote n the primaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont want to brag or anything, but I’m really stupid https://t.co/jGOPPZLaLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making people smile &amp; happy.... is honestly the best feeling in the entire world! :) #HappySunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franklin19788 Pinning ZERO hopes on GOP in general  (aka "Dead Party Walking)  But eventually (as happened with Ni… https://t.co/36JwF7OqD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvgraz You might not have to worry so much about Meghan McCain as Joy Behar - and Whoopi.  There are mean white Re… https://t.co/nElYTfi3RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at home having a real live alone party and practicing my twerk moves:]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't like getting involved in this kind of petty crap, but I'm tired of the bulls***!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joh1Joshua @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Why? Because he’s a racist pos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you the kind of willpower it takes to get a wendy’s salad while brandon is getting fucking CANES. this is bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robby32099 People who hide behind a key board are weak. The only way they feel important or a sense of power is by… https://t.co/xxIysvIinT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bowdoin steamroll at #NCAA sweet sixteen round! These woman got game on #InternationalWomensDay @BowdoinWBB… https://t.co/uNiULTFIfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvgraz @HillaryClinton The Goldwater girl is 100% WallSt corporate owned. NO Hillary. No queen. Democracy Bernie all the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[titties out like blaka  broke bitches watch out now  your pussy basura  my pussy horchata 😘😘😘😘  #drunk https://t.co/8DeQ2dECtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been so 🥶🥶🥶 we tend to hibernate when we’re not working our asses off 💪🏽♥️ SOLD in under a week for FULL list… https://t.co/EE1ZcrRPP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[An early birthday card from one of my clients. And it's hilarious. michelemnyc #myclientsknowme… https://t.co/kOCCqIVDgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hellboy919 @kreepazoidkelly @90sGirl_Sydney @carpenterisgod @JulieCarmen3 @staciwilson @DebbieRochon… https://t.co/Xv7O5zVYd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast "I have a real soft spot in my heart for librarians and people who care about books." --Ann Richards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Pg 1 of 2 Nancy? Isnt that calling  the pot black? Someine exolain to me, that when… https://t.co/GoD8lwhLHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christi77929362 @DoingRight1 @WinkWinks222 @RealCandaceO https://t.co/dVu5WyDGD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s comparing MLB streaming blackout rules to the internet in the 90s... Oh, you mean before the idea of streamin… https://t.co/dyCZsBcfpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @HCSDSELDirector to post the cover of 7 books I love - no explanations - just th… https://t.co/dJvNgG233v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADeplorableBeam Wow! Very interesting info! Am I surprised? No. But when I hear "transform" that is a trigger word… https://t.co/nwhmaXKbTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my biggest regrets was not being CENTER barricade for weenie roast...my ass would’ve been on that stage sing… https://t.co/V7zqndf91S]]></document><document><![CDATA[My subconscious is Anna Wintour level style..... and she is easily underwhelmed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i should be leaving in 5 minutes yet here i am still snuggled in bed w Cal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought myself a box of macaroons for Valentine’s Day.  And I’m only giving myself ONE DAY to cheat on my diet.  So… https://t.co/ehLsT9WWl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever known someone that doesn’t like you, but watch your every move and copy your style 🤔😂 weirdo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @LFFStadium the hallway under NE terrace was a nightmare. Took1 hour walking through it for 3 of your staff to… https://t.co/5R2yf7fAvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PabloJoseHR Yup, y por 60 a~0s se ha quedado todo asi.  Nada ha cambiado desde entonces. El invento del ELA echo p… https://t.co/ockC38bH6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiamPayne @svandoorne #FanBoost #stoffelvandoorne https://t.co/NuA8xxsDU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to work with such genuine people, if it wasn’t for Karen I would still be looking for my car/ not knowin… https://t.co/EXRbCfEfnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperWiki Can't be wind, a wind strong enough to blow the swing that hard would have the trees blowing also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally agree a #publichealth approach will help.#spsm #ImpactedFamilyFriends #AAS365 #AVoiceattheTable… https://t.co/m6qRmeER7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really want a good scare out of me make a movie about big bird..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does #loneliness hurt? Isn't pain supposed to be a biological warning of danger? It sucks, but it's not actuall… https://t.co/Jy473C20Zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGANuggets @freddyrace14 @__CassidyRae__ @establishmentno @Finn_American @DogsBCool @NikkythaBee @bromsisa… https://t.co/okP12s2eIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MouseWorldRadio @matthochberg @mjcranston @LenTesta @MikeScopa What is Tax Writeoff for $900, Alex?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SynicalOFCL @zochada @itsavarose_ Keep on trying to explain/justify the shitty behavior and I'll keep on telling y… https://t.co/9flnYJJjp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than $500 to go in @WavyWednesday_'s Kickstarter!  https://t.co/1pTrWRiVCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCChicagoMed The way you worded that sounds like his gun came straight out of a horror movie.👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engagement strategy - Antonym dominoes. They love to learn through games #bettertogetherhenry @WCE_HCS https://t.co/wunFZzPM4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrath_of_Comm @SimSam541 @skewermann @SkipperToo314 @skousenisdumb @SLReaves @SMChalut @SmithTuri @SmotherEinstein… https://t.co/Av7FDGokL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Many MANY will die at the hands if a government bureaucrat...]]></document><document><![CDATA[92. Climax at @TIFF_NET definitely not an advertisement for LSD but just as messed up as you’d expect from Gasper N… https://t.co/6eZvGhnX2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and you best friend of 30 years are hanging on to the tea @JeffreeStar spilled. #SorryNotSorry… https://t.co/gF7hCtprO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inappropriateKM When I saw Jaehyun and Exercise  as hashtags I knew I was done for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fostering fluency and creativity with Reader’s Theatre. Proud 1st Graders! #iginspires https://t.co/6J1biI8fFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsimsphd @IRLhypeMANdy @nmmarino @sarahgollust @Oakes007 @AKAbariotes Indeed I am. See you and @polyscidoc soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give the gift of life today from 10am to 3pm.  Bethlehem Baptist church Ridgeway,  SC. Donors get a free tshirt, sn… https://t.co/ywt2YWzRAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INFPRebelSoul Well, where I lived a majority of people were catholic.  It was pretty obvious (that everyone fell i… https://t.co/eYYOsfkc0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[i spent 30 minutes vacuuming the entire house yesterday and told everyone to knock off their feet when they came in… https://t.co/yRaICmc7oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I shouldn’t give a fuck but WHY ARE YOU SHOWING OFF YOUR BOYFRIEND AS IF HE DOESNT CHEAT ON YOU CONSTANTLY b… https://t.co/c9fLe1yqk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[AT YOUR ATHLEISURE: my favorite function-meets-fashion hybrid brands of the season are on @sophistliving… https://t.co/jCeXr0pnKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a cold morning for soccer. #brrr #cantfeelmyfeet @ Cartwright Park https://t.co/zbB4cpoOAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone in Lakeland is looking for a roommate or anything to rent a house or apt let me know!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew if anyone I should’ve woke up it was my brother 🤦🏾‍♀️ didn’t even get to say anything to my step dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 @BraxtonLabs @bodyfit67 @cellmavin @excitedtofeast @afrobeerchick @PeychoJoe @bertrand_boily… https://t.co/lQh4kR4NYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieALewis This is why I follow you, you get so much accomplished with a smile on your face the whole time! #gettingThingsDone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteelCityChess @dvesean River is probably dangerous from all the excess rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy internet friends day to everyone, especially my best friends in green room hangs(: (i only have content with… https://t.co/wnNHiJHtwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my baby Gabby with her cute self. @ Macedonia Baptist Church https://t.co/w3alYJcrJl]]></document></documents></author>