<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tcarp1616 Concerned about the people being ignored...How about Hilary winning the popular vote and losing the elec… https://t.co/2E8xbMkCFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[After just one minute into the second half, Kentucky went on a 7-0 to increase its lead 44-31.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atltid @EricGQuintana @JoshB914 Never said anything behind his back... All to his face 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: The @PHMirage bounce back for a 5-3 win over Mound Westonka for 3rd place in the MSHSL Class A Girls Hockey Tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[50% of Oregonians trust their financial welfare to credit unions who deliver $1.8 billion in economic impact to mor… https://t.co/pLeYP13Oto]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT Stan Lee's Kamikaze show. First time in LA and the show was super fun and i got to meet Stan thanks to… https://t.co/SHERgeHkfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Product Specialist - https://t.co/3cRdXy5FUM #ProductMgmt #TheEmpireState]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StreetsDept @ccdphila @Brulee_Catering That doesn’t address misinformation most people tweeting are incorrectly re… https://t.co/qEZSxP7YwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandyLeonxo Happy belated birthday, you gorgeous woman you! 🥳 Hope your day was as amazing as you are! 😊 See you a… https://t.co/5SVRvKZLgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sssnnooooppp @jaydeefung @bionicanadian @samyliam19 @zenzurzb24 @InvajyC @p_ganzel @bhatanagarntn @OohLaLaLina… https://t.co/W4XLkN6UXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachpaige30 @ToshuaL This young lady had caused me more headaches trying to figure out how to slow her down that… https://t.co/P4Chh1fkUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like waking up at 6 am and not being able to fall back asleep 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m almost certain that every time I go to Fort Mcdowell I’m the youngest person in that building by at least 40 years😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like y’all don’t understand I gotta work so I don’t have time alone is the worst.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport He didn't play vs the Warriors to save the streak and lost it to the Hawks lmaoo 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the government knows that it can get away with everything. That's absolutely terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @TuppsBrewery @beerhunter74 @beeryeti @cedarflats @RJellyman @mtravis63 @Karithna @Beerislove25… https://t.co/zJGQYUBczM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans will continue to get shorter relative to other countries. Height is the best single overall measure of th… https://t.co/ZetGOwmXmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida Síguele Pedro rascándole los huevos al Tigre...... https://t.co/JSb3iMRZQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember being ON this during my #Mizzou days - it’s an honor. Congrats to the students and good luck with the BE… https://t.co/sg5MHa47vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xDayaannax Ya sea una u otra no importa (Aunque el tatuaje duele más dependiendo del lugar y la inyección no) 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former @RVC_Athletics All-American on 🔥🔥🔥🔥!!!!! So proud of where she came from to where she is. Keep it up… https://t.co/QOxBfiAwq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight in Akron OH! Let’s make it a sad one 😎 2.24.19 #makingmusic #basmentshows #sadmusic @ Akron, Ohio https://t.co/wuncxKivg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donle… https://t.co/EjUoteLamA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Patriots are the most openly pro-Trump team (owner, coach, and starting QB are all known supporters), and yet t… https://t.co/glB8igRhhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lshookkent @scamptres1 @splcenter I don’t block people because I believe everyone should be open to opinions other… https://t.co/5TKiV2HRRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KingJames y el modo PlayOffs pa’ cuando 🤦🏽‍♂️ https://t.co/H9MiCKmlPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to early crap lol. Pre-season rankings are complete trash and anyone who puts any stock into em just fuels the… https://t.co/UI9gA32mRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started playing Gnog on ps4 last night. So many knobs to turn and leveled to pull, all very polished and juicy. I’m… https://t.co/896LUHQ7UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early jolt bitches! (@ Starbucks in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/WvuwSL23fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillyScope I'm sorry to hear that Jilly...have they been able to find it yet? If they haven't  found it yet, I hope they find it soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @steph93065 @SecNielsen How is it that no one thought about this possibility before using the dogs???]]></document><document><![CDATA[we need to help farmers manage their woodlot. with a cost sharing plan to keep the woodlots in place -dave ferguson  #inthezoneforum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travisdhanraj @VictorFedeli @fordnation Some progress for sure, but more needs to be done to fight the deficit and… https://t.co/ipEwwDCVxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pray for our waitress, Christy. She believes Jesus is God, but has never trusted Him to save her. She is str… https://t.co/K9Fg1QjiED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyNemmity Watch Regal v Goldberg. Goldberg was SO STIFF!!!!! Regal tried so hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I CANNOT HELP to do the things I don't humanly have control over and just once in a blue moon (or less rare than… https://t.co/M47eudHcPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[25’ Maxi Urruti is down grabbing his face as they check for a head injury, play is stopped.  0-0 | #HOUvMTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police: Woman robs, kills man she met on dating site https://t.co/Tk4MmxflxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like they are bipolar Targeting me as if I'm someone else both my hemispheres work in unison. so they can exp… https://t.co/nbyrKx8wVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrishowrad He wears the blue and orange sunglasses all day everyday in his eyes the #isles do no wrong, b/c they… https://t.co/20JIdFvqVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reread the first volume of @MarkWaid and @ChrisSamnee's run on Daredevil and this has to be considered one of the d… https://t.co/KKDay4Tt8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/vbIsdQ8IzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having the Typhoon. Passion fruit and mango juice with a touch of orange and.....................  rum of course! https://t.co/EGzE7XQo2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theempressnic That is easy. Many Black females are mean as hell. I fought hard to keep my daughter from being real… https://t.co/EWghsEtQeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoulders and triceps this morning, 1 meal in, no infra carb shake and felt really really good so decided to push i… https://t.co/KihmNxPYQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anotherspaniel Thanks. And thanks for keeping an eye out for the article after our discussion last night. Congress… https://t.co/m3DeyaiJb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauty and brains!! No wonder I married the woman you introduced me to!! #BuildTheWall #incrystalwetrust]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods LOL… I think at this point Mr. Woods we should launch site to raise money right now to buy another… https://t.co/KFtNRRLBPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night 😴 Men of Troy! @mg_cronin put them down quietly. @RazorbackBSB wins series opener 6-3. #OmaHogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was younger I feared change I held on to jobs, people, relationships/situationships because I was comfortabl… https://t.co/LOQLGCBLQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLPitts Matt Lauban was tracking it, saw a pretty big debris area in this one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dorsey in tight end market.  Demetrius Harris, whom he signed as an undrafted rookie in 2013, bears watching. Tall… https://t.co/Ut2bJ6jR9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovestubbles It took me a second to recognize you without a blue or red shirt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally finished The Originals and I just can’t even deal with the emotions 😭😭😭😭😭 https://t.co/6oMZYju5g9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothin but respect for #DeanAmbrose and what he stands for. #Professional #Rub @ReneeYoungWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see the @AMCTheatres Empire 25 on 42nd street is still committed to having the dirtiest theaters in Manhattan...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#picoftheday #greatfishing #bookthetripofalifetime #Venice Guide Service (504) 481-7529 https://t.co/ARKVNSmqj4 TAK… https://t.co/GpLzaYuJne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its always “wyd?”  ... never “do you wanna come hit it from the back?”        😒😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__misshel hey. idk if you remember me. I see you doing big things hopefully all is well with you. keep grinding go… https://t.co/x7RXZhZWxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely agree. No team at this point is better. Bandits are outstanding on offense, defense, transition, and goa… https://t.co/zT9rOJdW0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliazapata20 @AlvaroUribeVel Raro; ahora es cuando este "testigo" viene a hablar? aqui hay gato encerrao, chivo… https://t.co/FHDlv2aCt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What drives people crazy is knowing that their are voters out there so disturbingly stupid that they voted to elect… https://t.co/xEh0Xtyq0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered my tam and gown for graduation and I could seriously cry 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is for anyone who might be looking for a welcoming and affirming Christian church. @churchclarity can help mak… https://t.co/GZZlF5MQdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[life is too precious to waste doing anything less than what makes you happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[contest won't affect the civil lawsuit he plans to file in federal court in the next few weeks against Akron and th… https://t.co/Ciq3PQo78I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmicoHoops The game and whole weekend...except for 3 pointer contest was bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 4:23 AM and I just beat the machinery boss with my last bullet #RE2 #accomplished]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man that’s how everybody living unless they got BREAD!! Mfz definitely roommates and some more shit here it’s the l… https://t.co/vZzMHSAhfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarSShakir @IfNotNowOrg @hrw Very simple. HRW should hire someone without a history of partisan anti-Israel advocacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARTIST EXPOSED: Annabelle Heart | dumpsterscore Solar-powered Sewing Up-cycled Fashion Designer Maker | Craftsman |… https://t.co/sCRmccNXdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bammas wear one turtle neck / gold chain and blazer combo and think they know fashion lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AM800News @WETransSupport What evidence do they have that this was politically motivated?  These break ins are usu… https://t.co/0qmxUthRmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its really hard to get my boss to leave work. He hates his wife and homelife(so he says) and would rather be here.… https://t.co/B0Q0kXLXNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Lord,  Today bless this week ahead of me. may I stand solidly on Your promise, that all things work together f… https://t.co/0pEl2snzwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody:  neil degrades tyson: Today marks the end of another month which actually holds no significant astrological… https://t.co/3uF7uUlfCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t imagine fighting to make sure something like this continues. What the hell democrats???]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the other networks are completely incapable of asking tough questions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 30 minutes since the time change and it’s already messing with me🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RejRoyal Military or not a grown man not bout to yell at me in the shower for no dam music.. y’all catch me when I throw on some gear]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Feb @3dThursdayLegal lunch @PackardPlace_  with Beck Insights presenting. https://t.co/tGxdVrBDM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah 101 &amp; got a hot mouth with all her sense &amp; still make jokes about her boyfriend in England.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBu74794060 How ever it comes out, the unity that will result will be the reward.  If that unity is with God’s… https://t.co/SknDl6FPt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren This country is turning out doctors, lawyers and other professionals who are so deep in debt that their on… https://t.co/qHSOb1JyJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptureYourMind @marshawright https://t.co/eRXp3N57Ro Her life arc is as compelling as her best-selling novels. Ca… https://t.co/kmhv7K9Ko3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osoriochong A que le temen a que los encarcelan a ustedes en el PRI, a mi no me preocupa un mando militar...que le… https://t.co/woLyQ0KLkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Their Own Words:What It's Really LikeTo Be Black In CRE https://t.co/sil9R2ysqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Work harder.   Pffft.  Transgender only hurts women.  Isn’t progressivism great?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the end of our USA adventure in Texas and looks like we’ve saved one of the best for last. Houston is a great… https://t.co/03maufZwsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino YES DEMS ARE GOING TO WATER IT DOWN AS THEY DO WITH ANYTHING THAT MAKES THEM LOOK BAD....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day all you tragic lovers!  Kiss each other, through the veils... #valentinesday #thelovers… https://t.co/eKKRALaix4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Jurcik Auburn still has games in Tuscaloosa, Lexington, and a home game with UT coming up. We MUST win the ot… https://t.co/aBiGfd0WAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Bruce. It's a great group, no question. I'm happy to work with everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DonovanFentonNH introducing HB520 to require places of public accommodation to install + maintain at least one di… https://t.co/ac8rSpPHdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[New band, who dis? #shotoniphone #productred @ Alpharetta, Georgia https://t.co/xYErBeIIyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW your @GOP is so scared of a member of congress 2 months into their 1st term - you start a super pac to “get in… https://t.co/rF0xhh473M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocking! NEW Revelations on Obama's Birth Certificate Full HD 1080p https://t.co/xXYRY886Ga via @YouTube @Alyssa_Milano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to hearing Urb drone on about his health issues before his inevitable return to coaching.… https://t.co/CZOjcRpSws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN loving DictactorShip. @IlhanMN loves #Socialism. @IlhanMN protects the murderer #Maduro.]]></document></documents></author>