<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @KyleWorkman95 @ZeroBlog30 @hanmiller123 you in the gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article from @Mike_Shapes on why every Friday the @ShapeHistory team work from home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremycargill72 @yachtrock @seaoffools78 @D80David @djsun25 @LibbyCudmore @GoatsYachtDJ @TheSnerly 🔥🛥🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the children, we must do better. For the children, we must fight harder. For the children, we must protect them… https://t.co/9sTsB1LqvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFSFCEE @DrFullertonMPP @fordnation #FullertonFails is a great hashtag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, I got a chance to visit the second biggest fish collection in US. This is an amazing place! @UF @SFRC_UF… https://t.co/wwmu1Ijtyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Stanton: fog, 48°F 93% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1018mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your fishing with the legend tidechaser101 Steve Wicks you catch big fish 🐠 ladies night matrix mini with a mo… https://t.co/tVATTOXfmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@centsible Trump seeks new momentum by lighting own farts in wheeled office chair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshD926 After living outside of Indiana I can honestly say buying bread and milk ahead of a snow storm is A very Hoosier thing to do !]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s now up to 8 known linked attacks by same guy in South Philly who raped a woman this morning after trying to ra… https://t.co/gOCg5asiTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretWeinstein Glad to see the promotion of ultimate I’ve been playing since 1976 I am thrilled to see its growth u… https://t.co/22w5Z1mbGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gee thanks DTF for another great night.. stupid guy right here ran the red and t boned my ride.. smh..… https://t.co/IukLv1PbDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid performance from start to finish and to hopefully get a huge road series sweep with win tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerrizor And I’m totally serious about painting my AR pink, and putting that Hello Kitty (Hello Frank?} skull on i… https://t.co/T1loLDLHBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#chocolatecoveredstrawberries  #yummy #dozens and #dozens #comeandgetem #happyvalentinesday❤️ @ Jay Bear Bake Shop https://t.co/NUueWIs9Ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATHOMEActivism @ArbiterAnubis He should get a spot in the debates as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveGuest @steph93065 Wow The great CNN does Cohen all day with zero reporting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardBarrow_ @samutsakhonjeff @thai_watch @RichardBarrow 275thb in US. Not sure how accurate. I've often conside… https://t.co/nJeHgTZRKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Suggestion For The West Main Street Parking Lot &amp; Developer Allan Cadgene! #iLoveCVille #iLoveVa    https://t.co/s423vCPTQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nightmar1sh @shannon_mcgrew @SugarMyntG Around Halloween time they have cool events and on Halloween they usually play the movie :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to say I’m enjoying Umbrella Academy but I...just...can’t...stay...awake...through...an...episode.  M… https://t.co/nZnTibEoaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPerksGillespie @AMDAFoundation I wholeheartedly support that initiative!!🤣🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[भजन संहिता 122:6-7   Hindi Bible:    6 तुम यरूशलेम में शांति हेतू विनती करो।     “ऐसे लोग जो तुझसे प्रेम रखते हैं,… https://t.co/bmeQBxoWsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Firestorm753 @amandacstein Tell that to Connor McDavid but yes agree. I’m blaming vodka for my comment:).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone on the Red Sox seriously looks to be in amazing shape. I’m impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #SupplyChain jobs like "General Warehouse" at ProLogistix in #GrandPrairie, TX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FarmaJanes If you can, turn down the dial on the asshole and if you need a reason do it for your kid. Unfortunate… https://t.co/87Nhxs6CIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz Try taking a walk down the street of a major city in this country without a bodyguard without a gun se… https://t.co/9iePAfU5rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The axis of evil in the House of representative are these newly elected #Democrats #AOC #Ilhamomar &amp; #RashidaTlaib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening up an entrance for my first run of the year in #palisades @sugarbowlresort Stoked to share so many options… https://t.co/wvBqMP7bOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las universidades deben de pasar de formar para el trabajo a formar para la vida. Celebrando la historia, imaginand… https://t.co/uOwTjMOWzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be me tomorrow! Too many cases, not enough time! https://t.co/k5qJVbMi21]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goofy ass dude was complaining he wanted more money, so he did this bs even though he was making 60-100k an episode… https://t.co/6q1Mh7XGMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No @NHL club plays @rushtheband Fly By Night! Good on you, @mnwild !! Goddamn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denschaal @gtconway3d What do you mean you are out of cheddar cheese?! #FAKENationalEmrgency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pimentel_paul @jesusmur123 Shit be stupid af thinking you will carry two these hoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotARingRat We're getting Wrestlemania 36 here. I've already started a savings account for the weekend of April 5t… https://t.co/no3Riiim7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay bih iz yo burrdayyyyy! Doing big things this year, plenty proud of you 🎂🎉🎊 @ Hallandale Beach, Florida https://t.co/LjNa1OGo1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly some days I can be happy as can be, most days I just don’t feel like myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @LambingNaomi @LiberalsAreDim @CelMar76978805 @Logan19682 @MAGA_RABOH @HNCurtiss @m4evr4gvn @PersistOrg… https://t.co/tdRVzeN0Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I was sitting here complaining that I’m broke and shit but then I got a bomb ass idea to put my titties on a s… https://t.co/p67usxRoTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballchickie Well… At least this is the correct spelling in the United States.😊 https://t.co/ftOxLmUbWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be invited to THE UA ALL AMERICAN CAMP!!@DemetricDWarren https://t.co/latKVE1sQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stripeyskunker I never took chemistry but I know two are sodium &amp; chloride]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good! Great night! Now sleep then on to next destination tomorrow. 🎉🥳🕺🏻🥃 @ Javier's - Newport Beach https://t.co/SGUK1ObIJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricksterps 2nd best round goes to Gatti/Ward. Ward grew up in my dad's hometown in Lowell, Mass and we followed hi… https://t.co/ep3Uu18uYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbarapla @polpla11 Every right to be! Amazing try. Great effort. Historic results. Goes to show you that with th… https://t.co/nZ6iSMZzUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Yeah, and Fox News is fair and balanced and loaded with liberals. STFU you whiney little bitch. Seriously just STafU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turtleturret12 @sdamned That's a great looking package!   The stickers and extras make it lively and fantastic.  E )]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at VON Canada? We're hiring in Belleville, ON, Canada! Click for details: https://t.co/n2TOLT5bUn #CommunityCare #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgdmd1 @LionsRoyalty I wouldn’t put it past BQ to trade back from the number 8 spot to acquire 2 more picks (2nd,… https://t.co/6REDMe4onH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frozen ! Contact When Ready To Order Email Us dfinelifestyle05@gmail.com or call/text 914-246-2597 Or What's App (9… https://t.co/M4DmpKe5l4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prageru Inconveniently that all happened more than 75 yea a ago. What have you done for me lately? I know! Gutted… https://t.co/dOAEKfQ4qM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnivDeTodos He oido algo.  Pero esa Academia me recuerda un poco al cuento del ruido del arbol que se cae en el bo… https://t.co/0nfq4STAlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like going to the symphony to hear your high school student perform with the BSO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#monday #mondaymotivation #morning #morningmotivation #nyc #artist #art #artistsoninstagram #visualart #birds… https://t.co/roJrf0ojsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 sisters were tapped into honor societies yesterday!  Congratulations ladies, we are so proud of you!♥️… https://t.co/1lRt3zy2UH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I don’t even look the same from 2/3 years ago https://t.co/B0SAltypNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting v very excited about a project that rbarntt and I have coming up with @pinehurstresort this month.  Wha… https://t.co/RSCVRWD6j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOLFonCBS @CBSSports @genesisopen Fixed it for you. https://t.co/HEMDadlMIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #FunFriday and I’m so excited that @VickiBarbolak is joining us in studio @WHORadio @newsradio600 ahead of her… https://t.co/wzEV7q7bcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine , the @SenateDems are all 6 cans short of a six pack and must be stopped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertoblake Don't use apps to automate distribution to all your channels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what the critics are talking about. Captain Marvel is great. https://t.co/QuYmcGiyJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESGtransparency @blackrock @BLKBigProblem Pull the golf ball out of the blow hole!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackson Pollock was really in his bag when he made this https://t.co/pwfTF0X9hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[...throat and then slowly burn your worthless soul to a cinder with the tip of a heated sewing needle before the as… https://t.co/08uVUQN5Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurSchwartz @DonaldJTrumpJr You mean like the way @DevinNunes leaked to the Daily Caller for this article?  https://t.co/7lwNBmgw2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManaByte do you know if Endgame has been screened? I was told that it has.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champagnennuts Last night at the game. Ty caught me after Rondo’s 7th 3 in the 1st 😂😂 https://t.co/zg16IC6uuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indiaairstrike is it a political stunt? Take our #TamilAmerica #TamilAmericapoll https://t.co/Yz0xbs92Yf… https://t.co/cos5cz7oWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faith__mercury Plot twist, cause we’ve already talked about getting married so 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP, Lucy Stanton (Day Sessions) passed away on this date in 1910. She was the first African-American woman to comp… https://t.co/cPAZ5JHXE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must drive a stake in the heart of this stupidity which endangers public health.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But Thats The Lords Day... Double Time And My Bar Tab.. Im There https://t.co/UuK7UfZjbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walgreens should ditch tobacco and sell fresh produce instead #nothappyorhealthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyrone345345 Black crime in this country has always been given more time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I normally shake of colds like bullets bounce off Superman; but after almost two weeks of my normal diet of wheat g… https://t.co/Wym9k7SpWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cory Booker is the dumbest Rhodes Scholar of all time https://t.co/zftWiC8Q8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get em today @Eric_Cerantola4 it’s time to show everyone a real Bulldawg on the mound!!! #OMAHABOUND!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbuck13502 WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother interviewed by Di… https://t.co/M7vy57hirH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biblecia I'm no longer on Facebook, been done with them for 3 years now, but will continue to follow your great content here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heart3626 @Denbar64 @Cant_Read_Maps @DianWChain1 @Corde61944395 @andyguy @TertiusIII @Jesus_is_G_d @commonsensejan… https://t.co/0C1jWGJFZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Marbles Jenna the whole video @ 5minutecrafts: https://t.co/sGROyORQ82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Installation complete! #taitcommunications #acrylicletters #titansigns @ Houston Energy Corridor https://t.co/R2hQqt0ek4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay away from negative people they have a problem for every solution‼️ -ALBERT EINSTEIN The Genius]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daherrin7 @GeorgeTakei It’s more than shameful, it’s a shining example of the narcissism and “me at all costs” min… https://t.co/eDJSHsIhbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tequila's Mexican Grill &amp; Cantina in Clearwater, FL https://t.co/vdgW7oexQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elevators: floor 6 and floor 1 Me: pushes down on floor 6 Elevators: 6 goes to 1 and 1 comes up to 6 Makes sense..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Obama judge, #Trump judge, #Clinton judge to hear border wall emergency challenges. It will be interesting to see… https://t.co/YNPFPzlIti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreamy, wonderful vibe last night from #halfwaif, #whitneyballen, and #pickleboy https://t.co/0aoxHU2krA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPP_HSD How are they able to speed in the left lane if he is limited to 105 km/h as per Ontario law. 5 km/h is tec… https://t.co/n7LEpJlupr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #vinyl record calendar is like your third hand ... scratching platters into the wee hours of the night in a… https://t.co/l0Eytuup8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakerFilmRoom Pete, I’m so sorry. I can’t imagine your pain may he rest in peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landaeta_javier @krampaw @orbnord @ninopagliccia @SenSanders @ConsuladoVenVan @Redconaicop @camilateleSUR Your acc… https://t.co/8ZMN4Sbhod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Zack Snyder! #ReleaseTheSnyderCut https://t.co/zh6YX3R6Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PupDigger @Venusdenko @thatitalianbear @roidpigXXX @ReallyDavidEego @TheoRossxxx @pdxBearBoy @AnthonyGinello1… https://t.co/yAwxaAVwDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was one hell of a good time. STOKED for endgame! we’re rooting for you, queen @brielarson ♡ https://t.co/H33r1IJalJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBeautBobbi @xpressfighting I'm sure I can swing that. See you in Brazil.]]></document></documents></author>