<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wow!  When did we break 2400?  #Exonerees #WelcomeHome #wrongfulconviction #innocence #XONR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT’S Girls District Basketball will be played as scheduled tonight at 5:00pm. @LJLadyMules   Due to forecast f… https://t.co/haifqxj8Mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad and want to cuddle with my dog but he’s sleeping in my moms room :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s have another look my Vintage Friends at all these beautiful pieces!   Please let me know if I missed anything… https://t.co/kpZDS9DeI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si me sigues buscando.. tal vez terminemos juntos.  Eres una tendencia clásica. 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkshine_spy Maybe, that’s because they don’t want to catch the next grenade?..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGDsquad wow , I’m a bit behind and just saw the tumor guy did the first time yikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s always going to be one storm that’s bigger than the storm you prepared for. It always comes down to level… https://t.co/s1lqCZHW6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ Put your money we’re your mouth is. I don’t want mine going to abortion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanfoland @Microsoft365 I love the PowerPoint search function! @Microsoft365 has done such a great job keeping Po… https://t.co/wU8JGw1DKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving away free tickets to the Grand Prix today pull up!!!! 7274215325 @ Chief’s Smokehouse https://t.co/ag60TRSZcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FareedZakaria In depth summary of life in Saudi, terrorism and killing...all in the name of religion and beliefs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Mary Kiffmeyer says the work that can be done is done for the night but laments that the House wouldn’t agree… https://t.co/IOdR73FXkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn , someone is secretly telling on me . Let me know if it works or not 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackInFullSwin1 @CheerFessions1 i loved that bc a team is a group of ppl not one person,, they are all incredible athletes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janaeritter15 I told you &amp; @lesliee_nicolee that weekend at Boggs I was feeling a little off😂😂😂😂 here we are 👶🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz @screamandletyou Pearl Harbor and 9/11 are in the rearview mirror.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely have to come back to @mrbsbistro before the end of my trip just for the Crawfish and Grits. I’ve never… https://t.co/4IKy0Dbw7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to go buy some plastic wrapped cheeses and start carrying them in my purse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devere09 @freenaynow I think Terrance was being Terrance and messing around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cab driver last night told me he spent years as a cargo ship captain and sailed all over the world and never fou… https://t.co/2JxRBj3JNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 @CIAnderson3 @Beaskind2 @beccas1434 @bfosterls7 @Black2thBone @BlkSantaX @BLUEinRedAZ @BobScarberry… https://t.co/hawoxiZiym]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get ready for work 10 minutes before im supposed to go in and i wonder why im always late ?!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FanuelMuindi @AdrianaBankston @LettersPreSci @phd_fashionista @AlyciaPhD @biochem_bri @LizNeeley @Connie_Chow… https://t.co/kmILPKqJ7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGirl Mondays@RBar 460 w.34st@10av Hudson Yards"10pm-4am" https://t.co/yjbSnwvv8i Fab Girls https://t.co/IDy5lnJsWR… https://t.co/LhGoPe0jc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use my @Wonolo referral code JASMINE1382 and we will both get $25 when you do your 1st job &amp; get 5 stars! https://t.co/J866FAtVym]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex only taught me how to love my new mans right and spoil him like i should 🐻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am still holding out for all the facts and then I’ll decide. What about y’all? #JussieSmollet]]></document><document><![CDATA[i pulled down my memory box to put the set list and tickets away from the last two days and now my bed is a mess of… https://t.co/nlprBpObwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been out of undergrad for nearly six years and I can still spot someone who used to be an RA/ orientation lead… https://t.co/wbO29XknZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelonelyisland who's the best person to reach out to about interviewing the Lonely Island for Forbes magazine? Wo… https://t.co/9ygLhyR0ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skylar and Raynes birthday party! 🦄🎉 #skylar5 #rayne1 #family @ Statesville, North Carolina https://t.co/0EWpemeJ26]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second #Pixaloop. My friend sent me this photo from Snoqualmie falls so I had to add motion! https://t.co/thsk6vXhnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who have a tough time letting their childhood go: I’m trying to declutter my closet (Saturday night turn up,… https://t.co/E6rgurMXuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This still leaves a lot of questions, though. Like, do projects have to have every single req marked as a ✔️, or ju… https://t.co/GgXyGACHJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 How much you wanna bet he knocks his wife and daughter around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UGH!!! 😭😍 I was checking in at DCA and Ms Patricia with @SouthwestAir was so impressed with my swift checked bag ad… https://t.co/S0mcnzbujS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianPalma16 Bronfman and her family have a lot more money than any of the other defendants. A few thousand dollar… https://t.co/OoYZp5FmJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy even with how our preview trailer turned out. Well worth the wait as I knew it would be. I can’t wait for… https://t.co/iGRfWbQSBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[THON 2019 is going on right now at the bryce jordan center on P-S-U's main campus. It’s an extraordinary event, rai… https://t.co/QxsR8fLpIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 GROWN SUCCESSFUL CHILDREN &amp; MY FIRST GRANDBABY CHAPTER 45 💖🙌🙌 https://t.co/EChUlhAcEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, tonight I made out w a stranger now I mc at IHOPe . Yes I might bi drunk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadeDeGood @41actionnews I don’t really care about the name but what is the cost to this change?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are car parts so expensive 😒 my car needs something so small replaced and that part is overpriced 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is talking about multiple Posie kisses and as much as I am going to love that. I can’t wait to hear Aria,… https://t.co/ZQGCwgAptj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TM2LeahDawn girl abbie grandma say crap start drama with your fan saying that you lie I dont think you are I am yo… https://t.co/0D9mmAN5fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wahlbonkers @DonnieWahlberg I so need to find out if I get it on dish I have to admit I love my ID channel but loo… https://t.co/BgugUY48gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vasamarief I would LOVE to show you butttt, I’m too embarrassed &amp; it’s the internet 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some things to watch on Netflix/Hulu that are like true crime files and what not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robin_schuh @hayes_melisa @Jarrett_Lerner Us today https://t.co/r6Tldb8V26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum @realDonaldTrump Amen, young man! Thank you for your service as a LEO. So glad you're awake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acakes421 Wow. You take care of yourself and your baby. Do you have family or a friend you can go to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Nouvelle Orléans. Son ambiance festive et musicale, ses rues colorées, sa forte empreinte française, son brassag… https://t.co/qmMRy4GI97]]></document><document><![CDATA[They that fled stood under the shadow of Heshbon because of the force: but a fire shall come forth out of Heshbon,… https://t.co/f2oAkvnEml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTM3 Anytime my son has played another sport he has gotten injured.  Our motto is “get him back to the football field where he’s safe”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day 17 years ago a SUPERSTAR was born and we named him Jadien Auntrell Smith. I cannot express how much you… https://t.co/G0MWWg7Oww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chef Jamie McFadden shares his love of #chocolate, and favorite dessert #Recipe with @OrlandoSentinel… https://t.co/UJge54HXT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdBernardMusic @AnneChabot1 @beyrima Oh, THAT old canard dragged out AGAIN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of every storm shines the love of God.  I seriously have no idea how I got the heart there .. lol need lessons… https://t.co/wN9j0aaYzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silueta de la baja Sur. @ La Paz, Baja California Sur https://t.co/4dGYr8p0eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can time just stop?! You’re growing way too fast. Days away from being 6 months! • • • • • #babyboy #love #sun #son… https://t.co/DTzFmnKL87]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know me you know how much I love tequila and mezcal. This mezcal is a celebratory Mezcal distilled with a go… https://t.co/lLzLJMdEEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home is where the heart is. #homeiswheretheheartis #hearttattoo #michigan and #semicolon #notdoneyet #depression… https://t.co/A1kLvhsx3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed Morning! Walking in the authority that was given to me by my Father🎉 His Word is True❤ Have a God blessed d… https://t.co/HJYM9uWl4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is jolly. Funny Yearbook Quotes From Seniors – 25 Pics https://t.co/uEWlActJEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 at a new random pharmacy. I forgot how long it takes you to long into a new computer 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zhaabowekwe @bleeker185 @EgSophie Far as I’m concerned he was enlisted, trained. I thank him for his services even though not deployed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonBergerCM It was great to finally meet you! We all quickly became one big @GannettFleming family. #joinourjourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precisa-se ! Adulto responsável,para tomar conta, da conta do presidente, no Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find top Remote Monitoring telehealth software in USA Call at +18444455767 or website: https://t.co/bwRMhmcTnA… https://t.co/Xde684kKLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub Beautiful!!  They don’t look like they are in their 90’s.  They are a beautiful couple ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @TheodoresMusic  -  This Sunday is St.Patrick's Day. The Sunday Sinners will be celebrating… https://t.co/FOinuhBC69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy Lantern Day, Happy Chinese New Year to our International Students @PSAltoona ! #WeAre 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bathroom with a glass floor over abandoned elevator shaft. Would you want this bathroom? @ San Diego, California https://t.co/hyRqdPcQYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorR30488127 @james_mccoy_t @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @TomiLahren Me too !]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Foster Wallace’s legacy is outstanding.  His writing extraordinary and stands the test of time]]></document><document><![CDATA[please lord, free me from the LA school board elections https://t.co/0m9Ti6lnKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #GOP needs an example of what happens to Traitors @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @HouseGOP @SenateGOP  @SenTedCruz… https://t.co/y9MlnueWQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyWantsBetter @NightlyPolitics I never vote for anyone, I always vote against.  - W.C. Fields That is exactly how… https://t.co/f8zKD33fVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buffer splashed on my cheek at work tonight and I just want to go home now.  😭😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irmaroxas3 @francisG_power5 To forgive ...is not that easy...but possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rivival Hall, Hamilton, Cindy's and Ramen San = sushi, drinks, amazing show from 12th row Orchestra, rooftop bar an… https://t.co/BCKjrly3IH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section V Boys Basketball: Cal-Mum beats York for Class C3 title https://t.co/5nos5BAxub via @DandC #localjournalism #basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puglaas says she believes that when Butts and Telford speak they speak with the authority of the Prime Minister. W… https://t.co/0VjqIpdAKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 You’re all over the news, Matt!  Lol. Idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darryls75888475 @PPCNorthVan @MaximeBernier @peoplespca Well for me it really is about the message. Been adovating… https://t.co/waZtIEZ2je]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also feeling extra grateful for the roof over my head, heat in my home, a full belly, and a warm dry bed to sleep in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashvilleSC @ConnorSparrow24 What else is going on?! 😂 https://t.co/9d0PoY11Tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio I  N  T  E  R  V  E  N  C  I  O  N           Y  A  !  Venezuela 🇻🇪 lo pide a gritos]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far, Amazon warehouse hasn't let me down. I pay half the price for good products that come in damaged packages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraTheLocal Omg great idea!!!! I didn’t want to bombard her but if she asks for more I will definitely send that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌊GOIN DUMMI @1future 💦 Hair / Makeup : ME  Casting : @mremills  Producer : @monicalawless  Director : spikejordan… https://t.co/xyrjLGlLDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosieOhDonald @pianopsycho2 @AOC Adjectives don’t require capitalization, and punctuation should not have a space in front of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My second graders using Google Classroom to answer questions about their reading and reply to each other as digital… https://t.co/3O3JmeBQ5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ex taught me one important thing and that was what I actually deserve in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found an old playlist on my phone that’s literally just the entire Apple Music 70’s soft rock playlist added to a… https://t.co/a57QidNQXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full disclosure, I dropped the ball on live tweeting yesterday afternoon, because I was juggling the Monsanto trial… https://t.co/u52E2hJrc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkStateAG Great work from you and your office. Now let’s get a conviction!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One sign of intelligence is knowing when you’re outmatched and outwitted. @IvankaTrump would be wise to not get int… https://t.co/prE2mWy1R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingBous @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump Because he has a hard enough time keeping track of all his daily lies to keep campaign promises!]]></document></documents></author>