<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[it's funny how the white women who constantly claim Bernie Sanders and "Bernie Bros" are problematic have records o… https://t.co/ui6UUPofBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitching Change: FIU relieves Everett Hurst, now pitching for FIU #37 Jose Machado. #FIUBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you know @GottliebShow Paul Pierce was first to suggest Lebron sit on the Jump or ABC pregame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyChri5 @MusicLinkUp He is one of the coolest cats in America love this guy always have always will]]></document><document><![CDATA[My soul cranves yours boo I can't wait until u get outta jail but in the mean time let's do what we do best and mak… https://t.co/MfkzECpFGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 23 by @HeavySeasBeer @ Bryan Park Bar and Grill — https://t.co/3UJcfzbcXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebalintREP @PavsCreamery @amatasREP Or Cuyahoga Falls. (I have to get there.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at America Gardens Theatre in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/1ipB05RS2S https://t.co/W4KKEOm9bN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! Dawghouse Saloon at 6. Writers round and I’m using a cool new toy tonight, come see how it goes https://t.co/idOOnXKt64]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 Essential #DigitalMarketing Tools for #Internet #Marketers [Infographic] https://t.co/JCdGxFOYJo via socialmedia2day]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the fast and furious movies. I don’t care what you say. Those are some awesome movies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamSwift_1 I will definitely keep my eye out. I didn’t know he was down here, you grabbed a good one coach. DM me… https://t.co/mtveqrypq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halloween_1014 @EnzosReviews @KirkMcCall3 I fucking hate hugs. https://t.co/IGUdJ7wjBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[life is about balance. sometimes, it’s hard for you to find the balance between things. like work and friends, or f… https://t.co/TNweRLtXBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Springfield, MA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/CDN4u9wlrG #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some wonderful photos accompany this reporting Guy Desrochers ordained as Alexandria-Cornwall auxiliary bishop https://t.co/Zie6D5Npgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacopo_della_Q And those weary 5 brave souls who escaped on last intact lifeboat, vowed to never book another "Gam… https://t.co/aBy4DRUZ9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that being said do not I repeat do not get it twisted that just because you I’m there that you will be a leech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇲🇽 Describe tu #bigbangchihuas2019 en una imagen: no sé diga más! #sermedicodelarisaesgenial Una de las mejores exp… https://t.co/13a01b5SqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach K is a significantly better recruiter than he is a coach and this game proves it once again... y’all aren’t r… https://t.co/fXiv6H3Es4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauBistro @nobby1955 @Quarterback_USA @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Your insane, people flock to California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey look it’s me. I struggle to talk to people at events I’ve talked to many times before. WHY, ANXIETY, WHY?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me da una pena atroz por la jani, yo la vi en Netflix y me gusto ene su rutina]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being bold enough to send yourself home early, while your Cast are working 12 hour shifts. https://t.co/VTaTGIs8Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tschwartzzz @thejoeholmes @crosssports We don't want you at our race tedward I don't care if adults have busy live… https://t.co/9BAcUCefDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FundyBB @CamManaraze @HaaymanHarold You weren’t there. You don’t know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_dunlap tell people to turn around and go home if they are trying to go 28.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has shown how important the issue is to him by spending a lot of his own money to help improve the lives of othe… https://t.co/S1XmGUwI1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been asked to share the advice I gave to someone stepping back into pastoral ministry. Most of it will apply t… https://t.co/4WZEC5cbGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ObamaScholars. At @GWtweets this afternoon, I was sharing and answering questions about the @ACFE_Group's strategy… https://t.co/BKDyOoglVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much I want to do this spring and summer! Have to make it up to Grand Rapids to see my friends and go to Nashville! I love traveling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel's opening weekend in China will likely surpass Wonder Woman's lifetime gross in China.  Disney (and… https://t.co/oF2bYdpbIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeWilson Really? You have no evidence. I bet you, if you read the surveys from the folks that live on the port… https://t.co/mgB2XYh4H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited about new movie premiere is The Upside (2019) at Cinema 6 in Stephenville Texas. This movie The Upside… https://t.co/JgYLgPnoOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oBetoGuerra @alerrandroA44 Isso não é nada! Manja essa minha aí ...Vê se aprende com o papai aqui https://t.co/N0QRILTNcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punker_irl “It’s OK, I wouldn’t remember me either” by Crywank always puts me in the feels :// but it’s so good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking through The Art of Tidying Up, and the first step of the first category is to put all the clothes in your h… https://t.co/t29nE78aeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Angela ❤️😘#birthdaybitch #birthdaygirl #betterlatethannever #tacoparty #nationalmargaritaday @ Super… https://t.co/huqNp9BMio]]></document><document><![CDATA[iirc, Michael Jackson just did the regular voice, and not the “lisa its your birthday,” as paying MJ to sing for th… https://t.co/HxqZ8ScwVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HermannTLombard @wolv54b1 @Weyerbacher @CurseOfOak @bodyfit67 @zappafaye @cellmavin @excitedtofeast @afrobeerchick… https://t.co/v1rmxQM3Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen @RealSaavedra Couldn’t read it all. Often at Twitter war because the Left stands for things I hate.… https://t.co/JewUQMU2bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast According to the law, he is innocent until proven guilty and will have his day in court. That’s in t… https://t.co/hGEqFbyTpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yunartowijaya Mas Dahnil dibilang bodoh ama yunarto 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 Terlalu bodoh sih ngitung nya]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to buy some Rose Gold pink Headphones for my special someone:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“After all, when we open the Bible, God opens His mouth...” - Warren W. Wiersbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[....Confirmation!  Let’s Do Work!!!!  #PUSH #DoWork @ Boca Raton, Florida https://t.co/5FuEd1yYsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboveThis666 @FatboyEarlLewis @PeteThamel @ChrisBHaynes @DanWetzel @YahooForde @YahooSports Yeah, but one horrible… https://t.co/TxvHWz4oqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USRoute41 @chigrl Yup...miners getcpaid, auto gets a write off or even a subsidy (thus they make $), green peace i… https://t.co/99peRB5hfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MccloskeyElijah finished with 14 as he caps off his great career with 1,222 points. #cghss]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I think of the Goodness of Jesus and all He’s done for me, my soul cry’s out Hallelujah. I think God for Savi… https://t.co/pF4zJRuRTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GardnerKSPolice I conf re hen   yaT faTher acTs   &amp; aJre yI na re fenT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeEmanuelFox Now, Grand Jury on FBI, DOC and Hillary. Congress has no power (nor the will)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still feeling the L today...  Love our team and hope the guys respond and throttle Vandy by 40.  #GoVols]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Eleanor Roosevelt National Historic Site https://t.co/yas2qYS0LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triponshroomish @zedwards41 @ShroomyBloom @RealKentuckyJoe @finebaum @KySportsRadio @CFBPlayoff Why ? what? you got something to say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @GlenBonney I’m with you. The Republicans in office are horrible for not protecting our Potus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear real estate world. If the category of best clients - I’m happy to say that I am the winner!! One of my clients… https://t.co/NrFxDqkzzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night's @Coheed show proved one thing to me......all concerts should ban the use of cell phones  Trying to wat… https://t.co/7CyqWTtoS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @mr_graba to to post covers once a day of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I'l… https://t.co/ltrE5i3Wcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[⛽⛽ 12903 W Magnolia Blvd, Sherman Oaks, CA 91423  https://t.co/jEX4i5YoIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago @BurtonABC7 I must agree he deserves whatever is handed down. Congratulations to #ChicagoPD for smelling a skunk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jantonioruizh El apellido de la Gobernadora es Pavlovích no Pavlóvich, saludos hermano desde Hermosillo: Jorge Barra]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You weren’t made for this world kid... the quicker you learn that.. idk you might turn out kinda okay” - my co wor… https://t.co/WSbumpXxfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daviddoel @TravisRuger @RepBarbaraLee She’s going to run the harris campaign in CA. She didn’t capitulate, she revealed herself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinLimMagic MAGIC IS REAL! We were sending all kinds of good vibes to you! You make us believe in magic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Section331 Maybe he traveled forward in time and watched episodes of Lucifer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakecronus @NoTechBen I don’t understand this at all. It sounds to me like you are saying that if a guy is good, w… https://t.co/mWlMcBHYxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @VP @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @GOP @DevinNunes About the same pence is a racist bigot and just as QUILTY a… https://t.co/DPjUtl6vvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonLitt @sabrinamoves if i get the Up elevator, when i’m on the other side I’ll send a sign if it’s true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew50095058 @JamesMAGA172 @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @patton6966 And to think they pay this clown for his priceless insight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APompliano There’s absolutely NO WAY we are wrong about #bitcoin.  It exists and will always serve a purpose.  To… https://t.co/tKkykct31Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayTembs @CraigHospital @MartinTruex_Jr @FRRacingTeam It was fantastic I was a little bit concerned because I didn… https://t.co/o6y9KAVOeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich 1500 EST. You all seem to agree that the big bad guys were in the FBI. That conclusion doesn't set up… https://t.co/MUbSl1kMYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching basketball (for the first time this season). A @ChipotleTweets commercial comes on. Why? Why aren’t y’all in Chattanooga yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaMariaMoraMa5 @QuesaVerdades @lopezobrador_ @TwitterSeguro Exactamente!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up every morning regretting not having a full sleeve on my left arm yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalieStandridge I TRY TO FIGHT FOR YOU EVERY DAY. I TRY TO PROVE TO YOU AND SHOW YOU JUST HOW MUCH I LOVE YOU. u c… https://t.co/6LLr3AtXMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Injectable, long-acting PrEP could be next in combatting HIV https://t.co/OzqamC7RYk via @washblade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusingsByGritXO The Dems are the leading cause of abortions not the #ProLifeGen #Patriots https://t.co/KwdmnxR1Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__DestineeLynn Literally one of my closest friends because of laughter alone 😭but this shit is funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BernieSanders - your grammar is as bad as your economics. https://t.co/NjG3bMgbo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ClassicJeff I figured you’d get it. And hell, it’s even old school for me. https://t.co/sJeOCiS0yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of SHARK KILLER https://t.co/lgADBD2p6s @tjoneswriter @Mestat5 @ScottFloronic @ReedsHorror @truebloodoll… https://t.co/q2m1EfxNTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Canucks complete a very meh trade. Gagner 1 yr left at $3.15M. Spooner 1 yr left at $3.1M ($900k retained by #NYR)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day beautiful people. If u don’t hear it from anyone else. Just know that I love u!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearcatOnBeer @EpicBrewing I wouldn’t use the jackass music.  Good job of not spilling a drop that I could see. 👍🏻@BearcatOnBeer @EdGrohl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trukitten Oh Al c Baldwin is brilliant!  Trump is so mad at him and SNL.  He’s such a cry baby taint licker!]]></document><document><![CDATA[… Am I more than you bargained for yet? I’ve been dying to tell you anything you want to hear Cause that’s just who… https://t.co/21SJfja9Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron realized what could have been during the all star game and came back to reality]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just get random ass piece of dust in your eye? Like what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Administrative Coordinator" at Transwestern by asking for referrals. It's a great w… https://t.co/LJOT9ZbvOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferrochae según tu, tengo que leer solo una corriente ideológica? eso es propio de fanáticos https://t.co/9wsorP8jSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerturnermpls @KeyBankCtr @penguins Yes - a huge fan since I was little kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Children Believe by Gold City https://t.co/HihFXutHiZ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen here, if these are some of reasons y’all choosing not to fuck with something, majority of y’all are hypocrites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WContreras40 @ONU_es @AminaJMohammed @jorgeramosnews That's not even food at that point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetSpectrum Your "latest" cable box, prematurely released 3 months ago, is defective. Your employees know it,… https://t.co/6J0pUwdOos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toda esta semana llegaré temprano a la oficina, más por que pediré varias salidas ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[with my luck I had to ask.. porque pos “uno nunca sabe” https://t.co/6e5E1Ylb8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all some babies. I see Lebron move out of the way nightly! Too scared to be posterized. Giving Harden MVP last ye… https://t.co/z5NubUIOoW]]></document></documents></author>