<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Darkrai_10 30 MINUTES????? Omg. I’ve never seen CoCo yet so I didn’t know that zjzizjzkzkxkznc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where your treasure is,⠀ There will your heart be also.⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀ #engagement⠀ #engaged⠀ #engagementring⠀… https://t.co/U9mezdswHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump You thought the question was about Basic Income or Guaranteed Jobs and you spit out your talking points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaoZeppelin @russianmachine Hopefully not the same broom we are going to use on Pittsburgh this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavings #Starbucks @ Worcester, Massachusetts https://t.co/OXqTKFHRp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring well over 20 years experience in a variety of training and nutrition to you all! . DM me for details . Creden… https://t.co/uwv5kS9AO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 more days until the #WomensTagTeamChampionship become #ICONIC @BillieKayWWE @PeytonRoyceWWE #WWE #SDLive… https://t.co/c117RFqBeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every minute, 62 children enter a Children’s Miracle Network Hospital. I am trying to make sure that kiddos at stil… https://t.co/gxAJswGrhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Face it. Hateful anti-Semitic Representative Omar took advantage of an opportunity to publicly attack Elliot Abrams… https://t.co/BomQr2jxkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neithskye As advertised, he’s helping me watch Softball right now. Came in about 20 minutes ago. Luckily he doesn’… https://t.co/n51wZVlzQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an amalgamation of Frustrating + amusing + depressing. I should mention this specific lady tried to order 5… https://t.co/ds41fL7Ads]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved Green Book and loathed A Star is Born. There, I said it. Let the unfriending begin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veyon Washington is easily a 3 star CB. College coaches go to Okeechobee. I’ve seen corners that don’t even half ha… https://t.co/hEIhx5nKOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel! (@ AMC Loews Roosevelt Field 8 - @amctheatres for Captain Marvel in Disney Digital 3D in Garden Cit… https://t.co/y3p0Pwf2GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spit out my coffee. Come hang out with @davidlagreca1 and @bullyray5150 to see kids in jersey and feel your… https://t.co/993G9hYiM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[They tell their kids that children of colour should be treated like animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but having control of the pick should mean it's at least touching your stick. #Pens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manp It was!! (And loved those squishy buttons...but got the keyboard case for that Spectrum...!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s embarassing that you served a traitor and possible Russian agent, but much of the evidence was on the n… https://t.co/DFADbaEKRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you had THE WORST parents in history. #AbductedInPlainSight https://t.co/N61jgtR5Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SL1733 @realJediMan1 @AdamSchiff @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @LindseyGrahamSC @DevinNunes @Jim_Jordan DAMN GIRL...I would… https://t.co/2v4L5meE7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta @WilsonOregon All governments student loans rates should be reduced to prime rate, to eliminate any profit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CITIZINS alternate cover of @OffsetYRN Father of 4 #Offset #MIGOS #FATHEROF4 #citizins https://t.co/ja7N4SMIEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fourth quarter action. @Miles_wbb vs. @KYSUWBB  https://t.co/C52lSyXy4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[A must read. Stories and people like this are why I will never be able to understand or respect people who refuse t… https://t.co/Pd4Cu5GB3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky to know a few of these kids and a coach. They work hard and have amazing results. Congrats to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EarlHecats @GottliebShow Who's giving him $44 million to be the 7th pick? What fantasy NBA parallel universe are you talking about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cardwell_taylor @Dstepp0218 @bvrrd @Heynow01258131 @arielhelwani A nut shot or eye poke is an accident and possibl… https://t.co/RwAV51CM0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M2Madness @MrEarpLA We've got to get term limits. These career politicians are just sucking our country dry! They… https://t.co/rlWGNmTALJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Winfield_24 He’s not engaging in diplomacy. He has no allegiance to the United States and is profoundly mentally i… https://t.co/reRj5osLGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjon My sworn enemy is whoever insists on feeding the pigeons *inside* the Rosslyn metro station.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Rliah, you or your terrorist family can be trusted. Your trash and Americans don't want yoi around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching WATCHMEN makes me really really appreciate Grant Morrison’s homage issue in his MULTIVERSITY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Nah. Don’t come back we are busy making America great again .]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we wind down this very interesting season with this team, we won our game against Bonaire by score of 59-46. Did… https://t.co/WqcNaHtBq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brennaharriss Within a month apart from each other https://t.co/FnB0SWnB0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow cat... #cutecat #cats #snowcat #coldcat #cutekitty @ Rockland, Maine https://t.co/2EabUcN5pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll take "you got this Alex" for $2000.  Positive thoughts, good vibes, and prayers to you Mr. Trebek.🤞🏽🙏… https://t.co/oVlcGIgKZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/uDyrJs4Uzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @RicFlairNatrBoy’s birthday today so I’m trying to decide whether or not to “Woooo!” every time a player hits… https://t.co/n0uYCfBx80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jespernweigner I'm not judging her by the color of her skin but by the content of her character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCBrent1 @BiffInDelMar #Insult madness #Irie Craig remodels his cardboard condos by stockpiling shipping boxes from local furniture outlets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeresells I’ll never, ever cheer for this time to lose. Try saying that to a player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottFish24 I won 2 trophy’s ? Sorry.  I’m in Vegas for the weekend and didn’t see I won the first one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally every minute I read about something happening in hip hop culture. The news on @YNWMelly is crazy. I just… https://t.co/hmeyIdiMNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say you fight the hardest when you start from behind. Now I dream the impossible all of the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Pop Goes The Weasel by 3rd Bass https://t.co/1ipjSMgG9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Trump lies again. .Trump only care about money. .not we the American people. He has the mentality of dicta… https://t.co/8jdnaTTk7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#freestylefriday  views of #Manhattan #Brooklyn from my eye.   Through the chain link of the Manhattan Bridge, thro… https://t.co/cTBJTWpxSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laurieleepnp @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/sXOHnEvSGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting how the Congressional upstarts who are causing the most angst are buck toothed. Stop electing thumb suckers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This building is covered with different pieces #downtownabq #downtownalbuquerque #abqdowntown #albuquerquedowntown… https://t.co/1JaJuu3gIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryan_Hackney Or move a 6 pack of beer to the left to show massive water damage and mold on shelves touching the foundation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stmmpls Not positive about infant availability but Linden Hills Child Care is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je ne suis pas d’accord!!  Comme membre de la XIVème Brigade Internationale, mon grand-père Gui est mort pour les R… https://t.co/bmb5oLReDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wizards failed to capitalize the T'Wolves even when the officials miss some calls they still get owed by Derrick Ro… https://t.co/VzmIhk9Wzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faye Mcmanoman @FMcmanoman and Zarkavon racing today at @WolvesRaces. Good luck Faye! #win 💪🤞🏇]]></document><document><![CDATA[OG on 🔥 tonight with #Raptors running an 8 man rotation #WeTheNorth  https://t.co/BuBsj3392Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchooyah That’s when we become one world government. Nobody can leave that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who this lady is but I respect her, I feel her pain and I am behind her 100%. We have to illuminate sa… https://t.co/gRxBT5zhuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yodaprncss @Uhmanduh Ahhh.... I can understand that. JP has a pretty smooth roll over at the top with minimal to n… https://t.co/TtiwVLBmzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LALopezCelis Así es, estimado y filosudo amigo... de un polvo venimos y en otro polvo nos convertiremos... y entre… https://t.co/N42nEtExzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenneth_ferg @BWildeGlobal The problem here is that with 14 games left there’s almost no more room for losses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First the law suits, then the Nineth Circuit, then the Supreme Court? Am I missing something? Oh yeah! Now I get it nod, nod, wink😀😘😋, wink!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today has been a real Bitch, wow 😂😂 tomorrow is Valentine’s Day as it’s about to get worse lol where’s my whiskey smash 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Congratulations! Been clean &amp; sober now 17 yrs &amp; loving it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga @VanityFair What a year! And what a career! Congratulations Lady Gaga! Beyond well deserved! ❤🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some #Disneyland shots previously unaired 😝😬 #Disney #CaliforniaAdventure #HalloweenTime @ Disneyland https://t.co/Ry3FWTJCBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hello #nyc #newyorkcity 🍎 #louisonthefly #loves @ The Rink at Rockefeller Center https://t.co/HChA802XyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy Ooh, I hope I get someones  grandma’s Boniva. It’s my favorite flavor of Skittles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc7ashley #whatsbrewing The Iowa Hawkeyes Womens Basketball team. Megan Gustafson had 45 points in the Big10 Tour… https://t.co/KtKkkJ6dpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJohnsonLaw Good. There are so many reasons the world would be a better place if women were not subordinated by la… https://t.co/guXLb6eoO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@civiltalker @SteveDavisUCI @danrejto @DrKateMarvel @JosephMajkut @GHGGuru @MarkSBrownstein Of course. I was over-simplifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnahita @millanpatterson I never attacked anyone on the basis of gender. You are making it the issue. Try readi… https://t.co/18OLpqagI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters What the fuck does Russia have to do with Venezuela? This is some more of that Trump shit, isn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky Strike and My My My! have been my jam obsessions for the past couple of days ♥️♥️♥️ @troyesivan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @TheEliasRework And I would hate to see Cohen call one of his Brooklyn buddies to have a firm disc… https://t.co/3PPiIxzBXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little cardio and resistance training never hurt anybody... unless u did it wrong! 😏🤟🏾 GM great people @ Planet F… https://t.co/EhBbgGaZsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @CanesBaseball on getting the series win against ACC team. Let’s keep the momentum going! #GoCanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wanderingscottw @threadsofenvy @reavo7five @7FiveBrewing @GoldenMisfits @SinBinVegas That’d be awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[today’s tea:            )         )        )     )     (         )       )    _(___(____)____(___(__ _ \      my do… https://t.co/UScQCkB5QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly don’t know how this @Uber driver is going to find his way home... he almost got us hit 7 times in total,… https://t.co/jnnF9eAF6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when im asked to explain physical chemistry theories vs when im asked to prove it mathematically https://t.co/mG907KqZIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camdasilva @EvanonHB Wouldn't have this guy in my team if my other option was I final year Houshmanzada ghaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMTurbo how bout some Cold from Static X. My ears been burning to hear that]]></document><document><![CDATA[My official match card for the historic #WCWMondayNitro in #WheelingWV where @RealKevinNash debuted on 6-10-96. The… https://t.co/RajU3A5WXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the very best films this year! #neverlookaway had me spellbound. It’s a beautiful love story, touchi… https://t.co/ywZS7a9L3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how a song can take you back to a specific moment in time so thoroughly that you remember where you we… https://t.co/FosJxNYEja]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Person as a Disgusting need and is Self Loathing and Wants to Ruin Every Man Woman and Child " they can not Be "… https://t.co/srjL8Mq8ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 25:28  Verse Concepts  Like a city that is broken into and without walls Is a man who has no control over… https://t.co/znrRyQw6wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really wanted to go to this Muse show but im gonna have to wait til Austin next month!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great reminder that it’s okay to show off your passion and just be you. Be the individual you were created to be.… https://t.co/i4OgUzu6cF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoustacheRollie @Ken_Rosenthal Input and discussion are needed for sure. I'm not saying there aren't some things t… https://t.co/3pxJByXrLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mugsy_Moran1221 I like Lebron. He’s the greatest basketball player of all time. There is a time and place to celebrate achievements]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonTrombetta @StokesTeraye @giantswfan you wouldnt trade for Davis unless he promises he will re-sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahPrangley I think of you the night you threw up everywhere and @Courtybear1996 and I put a full face of make up on you 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great week my friends! Don’t forget to #StepOverTheEdge. https://t.co/GLb26cYCK8 @guiville @wyattpauley… https://t.co/pgOwkdGZCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[He absolutely puts his hand on the puck to move it off the line. That’s unfortunate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let them walk around looking like a wood tip black and mild if they want to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Spurgeon evening devotional teaching  Evening by Evening Devotional for February 14 https://t.co/9NNMUkS4cp #arcamax]]></document></documents></author>