<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Get this Indians slander off my timeline like honestly some of you guys got nothing better to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the only way to fully grasp the inexhaustible generosity of God is to look back, to recognize all of the… https://t.co/9HoCh0hSzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair Selma thank you for, well..being you.. I’m fighting Spina Bifida and similar but different. I’m a singl… https://t.co/wz8jbboggd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreeendonP the gag is to make people click my profile and discover me 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[DFW to BNA ✈️ (@ Dallas Fort Worth International Airport in Grapevine, TX) https://t.co/25oT42om37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone knows I’m late to everything. But I’m actually early for training today hehehe...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered a Prize Giveaway! - Baby Milestone Blanket  https://t.co/p1IAHb7TkI #win #Fishbowlprizes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hosting this awesome event with @oliviawilde tomorrow at the #TwitterHouse! Send us in some questions using the has… https://t.co/NNzeTKzPsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drew scorbunny in class but i was also taking notes so the entire drawing just got smeared to death :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the first day of the best time of the year! -Karlee Hughes @LadyCavsSB @CalvertSports @LLGCOACH @smsherlund https://t.co/tzVfYUUOpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did these photos for my mink lash line that I will be launching in May.  #minklashes #3dmink #imanigracebeauty… https://t.co/rnTSguQKPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heavensouth15 @JimBeaugez @KeithUrban @BradPaisley @lindsayell I simply stated a fact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody have those days that they just feel super out of place? Like idk what to do with myself 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marialantz7 I agree! We are starting a book study today (Fostering Resilient Learners) with 25+ admin, counselors,… https://t.co/DyqcWQ9vUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow a reminder to self to look that up. Your only human like the rest of us. Cant wait till you get back on… https://t.co/0jiqVPm8Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breanna_Merritt I feel like I probably know who you’re talking about 😂🤦🏼‍♀️ I knew this would ruin her business]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so goddamn lucky I have a cat who doesn’t care what I do to him. Pick him up, put him on my shoulder? Fine wit… https://t.co/tXES910VWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[MESSY MORNING:  @AmandaWGME has more on how the snow will impact your morning commute and when it will move out.… https://t.co/HtoFMwJ59I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birds of different feathers, in Florida: a Great Blue Heron, Sandpipers, and a Snowy Egret. #birdsatthebeach… https://t.co/loFA9zWGBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just don’t know how to feel about all of this, and it’s all my fault I feel this way. Don’t let a grudge and your o… https://t.co/6057Tz6igB]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the incredible, strong, empowering, and super fun women in my life - THANK YOU for being you. Happy… https://t.co/uxtreLjyza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theredberry80 Oh yas! Kinda late but i love it. I always watch Cdramas &amp; Thai 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuctupMike That’s wrong.  Hope you get to spend some time with her soon. 🧐👩‍🦱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medieval Time’s 🏰 🏇🏾👑💙🏰 @ Medieval Times Dinner &amp; Tournament - Baltimore https://t.co/0NynISZlxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RFerriAuto RACING with #FERRARI returns to @SROAmerica to defend Championship in 2019. @NorrisMcDonald2 @jpappone… https://t.co/iG0aIPd8Il]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q facilidad la del muchacho para estresarme, pero q facilidad para quitármelo😩🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nottheribbons What do you see happening with SPN for the next few years? I was surprised about Arrow considering i… https://t.co/4pWjZlWa7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for a Spring #FashionShow💗🌷🛍️ Excited to host Apr. 12 with St. Peter's @quintewest #Catholic Womens' League… https://t.co/cGrdYZcR53]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are two types of people in this world: The ones that shake their fist at God in anger and blame Him when trag… https://t.co/ZX8EGykClk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a tummy ache from too many sweets today and my mouth’s still numb and I just want a nap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy behind me yells loudly during TO...  “Rose you owe me travel expenses.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to disagree with you Christopher,  if it’s something that is untrue , written and can be believed?! that is… https://t.co/3uIzj24qVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night. Garage Sale Weather Permitting tomorrow and Saturday from 8-4pm.   See pic for more information and add… https://t.co/1KeRDH9aLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Agree with ruling and waiting for Trump to follow suit.  Wolves run in packs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐝🐝🐝  nwfgs @ Washington State Convention Center https://t.co/yrcVHZMhHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP I owe at least $5,000 this year!  That is an outrageous amount and not what the president promised.  I really w… https://t.co/GMuoWsNUTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[holy shit ur blowing up! and for good reason, ur killing it dude😭 miss u sooo much 💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @putinsclown @nytimes @DavidBarstow @susannecraig @russbuettner Oct 18]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was gonna say computer science at first, but now that i think about it, probably music composition :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[E·mer·gen·cy: a serious, unexpected, and often dangerous situation requiring immediate action. synonyms:crisis, urg… https://t.co/pLGGrGj96L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix is getting rid of Vampire Diaries on March 1st and I literally have 10 more episodes to finish with the show so now I'm stressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Need2Impeach I Like the rhyme, so sad that it's true. Trump is a bad man, we all know that it's true! (Sorry, I'm… https://t.co/pvFe2TfOY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, That was a first. Got a text saying that the NYPD was in pursuit of two suspects on the @FordhamNYC Rose Hill… https://t.co/bjzURAz9iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d watch as she walked the floor and would pray out with tears. This was my norm. I thought she was praying for us… https://t.co/DhZDETmWIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Just another day in the @WhiteHouse. One day do you think the WhiteHouse will be painted gold?]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i had a dollar for every time i heard “i thought you were gonna be a bitch” i would be rich]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can we shape the creativity of our students and help them grow in their learning? Great techniques to use with… https://t.co/meI7C6uPQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/27/19. RIP to Marilyn, beauty tragically gone too soon from this life. A talent like no other. This song speaks t… https://t.co/H9D5krM5z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volvo to impose 112mph speed limit on all new cars from 2020 https://t.co/w1fYy1SyDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No You Are the Disgrace to our Country, we were great before you even came on the scene, go back t… https://t.co/O8an9u9FE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I predict he will be out before noon today! Don’t forget: 2 systems of Justice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorneliusTanks2 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump You are so right. I have family that left California, after living th… https://t.co/xkKj5gLPEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kadenwilliams_ And.. Some heart relations are more pure than blood relations... #family #alwaysandforever #igotyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW VIDEO IS UP!! An unboxing March’s boxycharm!! @boxycharm direct link in bio to watch!! 💕💕… https://t.co/7Nm948avdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m no canine expert but that was ONE FINE DOG. #justiceforburns #shouldabeenthedachshund #WKCDogShow @WKCDOGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[also, why can't I find any #peachclub pullover sweaters anywhere online :( help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLessard Seems like everyone knows more about running a country than the idiots that are faking their way thru it now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newest edition of “Dogs while housecleaning warren county” : This is Wilbur. He’s a good boy. 🐶  #marissabowers… https://t.co/mePkNaZteW]]></document><document><![CDATA[tinder à Québec c’est juste des gars qui vont probablement au festival western de St Tite à chaque année]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited! I just finished week 4 and earned my climb sticker! I have committed and climbed. Next is to conqu… https://t.co/Ttqawa5V2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear every movement I make something in my body cracks or pops. Going up the stairs...pop... rolling over in bed… https://t.co/5x7eeielkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iPlayMarioKart I just want 300......ok maybe I want a lot of things but 300 is close to the top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hooked on TEXAS...UT here I come!!🤘🏼🤘🏼#ut23 @ The University of Texas at Austin https://t.co/EPYLSevXRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of Fintech... had the opportunity to spend the past few days with our mobile app developer @BannoJHA… https://t.co/CR1VUWhATC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been this happy in a very long time. And I love the fact that all of my true friends can see it and support it. 💕🤟🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelGotti5 Oh! My! Hell!  He really is crazy! All he has been doing is insulting you and anybody standing up for… https://t.co/bI32T6Uk3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[but also none of them understand that I just...haven’t gotten a grade less than an A in college (let alone in my MA… https://t.co/flzM0OnLKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EwdatsGROSS Wait omg ????? Congratulations that’s amazing &amp; so exciting!!! I hope you have an amazing time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might of hit the hammer on the nail with this.. cause a lot of ppl don’t know how to except LOVE 💕..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland  I dunno if a special prosector can blackmail a US President but he is AND I know Letterman's EXTORTIO… https://t.co/0I43wfCR7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelAguirreA Al igual que tú y que yo, no hemos sentido lo que es llevar un hijo en el vientre, pero sí, alguna ve… https://t.co/V8UCfRk6ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terry’s birthday dinner @haymakerbar @ Haymaker Restaurant Co https://t.co/81doPEon9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleHamstra @Jennifer_Hogan @self_compassion @tamaraletter Thank you so much Kyle! I felt the same way!! #RisingTideRadio]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever wonder how different your life would be if that one thing didn't happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when you’re laughing with someone and a few mins later you just look at them and then y’all both just start laughing all over again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Britney! Looking forward to working with you this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the most amazing time at Amazing Skin and Wellness! Thank you for taking care of my skin! Feel amazing now! C… https://t.co/idmSEbDEqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing my first craft show this Saturday. I’m nervous but so excited to start up with my little business I’ve been creating! 💙🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Do you figure it will work for you like it does for that steaming pile of hot garbage in the white… https://t.co/IpHeFXFgFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DokctorD @Fox_jx @TheTNHoller Here i am arguing with a stupid bot..i really must be tired..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacePupSilver Panel 1, mind flayer discovers there's nothing to eat in the barbarian's head; panel 2 he goes for the wizard instead? 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 He can go to work and earn the money.  I'm not willing to loan him any, not from our country's coffers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 8 | a scoreless frame sends the Tigers to the 9th with a 16-7 lead @CoMoSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Spring market looks like it’s going to be busy! #letsgohousehunting #investinrealestate #iwannabeyourrealtor… https://t.co/wynW9IgiFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbouzy Aunt Sandi said you are welcome to come over and have a play date with us. We will have your back and cheer… https://t.co/CyxEVNxa9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrMixon   I will never ever EVER forget Mr. Khasoggi.  Oh dear did I spell his name correctly?  I dearly hope so.… https://t.co/XeVwM4aXyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrunkMcSaucy @johannhat Wait, I didn’t know it was possible to be adventurous with ketchup. How many kinds can the… https://t.co/s6R2VsBA6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches ask they friends, "You wanna go the bathroom with me??" And they friends be like, "yeah, I wanna come spy on you."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC  on the real how do we fight this amazon deal. I legit had a guy in my Facebook a... white man, newish to the… https://t.co/9dprzucnzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with Lilo &amp; Stitch #yummy #superfun @ Disney's Polynesian Resort https://t.co/fns228s5kB]]></document><document><![CDATA[to Congress, to the American people. You’ve been like a rock, a person sailing against the wind.” https://t.co/bPtMFliH8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I will never disappoint you, but I will disrupt the enemy’s strategies against you and speedily come to your rescue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My perpetual dammit-why-is-spring-soccer-in-NM-always-so-cold face, going on 22 years now. ⚽️❄️ I swear, I’ve been… https://t.co/rh5TXgDLm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSchollmann @StopTrump2020 Up until the election, but if Nancy don't want to be President it goes to Hillary Clinton!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas is jacking off while DRIVING LYFT, WHILE A FEMALE PASSENGER IS IN THE VEHICLE??? Lyft seriously lets anyone… https://t.co/xWgBj2rnZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see a #westwing character shirt for an upcoming election like- “Lyman/Young 2020”- I always assume the Lyman… https://t.co/SsAg7zmlM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lugar favorito. 🗽 (Después de AMSTERDAM) en Brooklyn Bridge https://t.co/8hyZSxg6Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “...yeah and she could do that til the cows come home.” @seancflanagan : “Ugh...you are from the Midwest.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelizlewis Do you realize that “conventionally thin” people also have judgement and glares because they’re “too”… https://t.co/jkzMYJxDbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So uh... #TristanThompson cheated on #KhloeKardashian with #JordynWoods y’all better be tryna be funny. Cuz I’m SICK]]></document></documents></author>