<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@eviimyerrs No evi no no if someone choking you I will joke them I donРђЎt want u to get hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can thank РђюThe Wonder YearsРђЮ for introducing me to this song, and Joe Cocker for giving it a rousing rendition.Рђд https://t.co/Dzc33O6m8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuSchwag9 @camallen1010 @grahamgmen WeРђЎll anxious to see Cameron and The Purdue Boilermaker make an impact next yРђд https://t.co/fr66XKbhMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormandeauNewsw @JazzMinella @RobinRLevine Boiler crossed off NYCHA spreadsheet in order to present revised ConsenРђд https://t.co/RXN29NhynX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My future wife is probably on 14 hour car ride to the beach right now with 3 of best friends and about to get trashРђд https://t.co/WGuVrP1gIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump This country is great at throwing people in the cross bar hotel for a bag oРђд https://t.co/JrrAKgRzTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an adult is realizing that you have to do whatever it takes to make it in this life.. at some point you haveРђд https://t.co/bYH48AFlVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When this song came out and to this day IРђЎll sing my little heart out ­Ъњю­Ъњю­Ъњю­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another highlight from last year was meeting JB Smoove. Funny dude. Really nice guy #comedy #work #DenverРђд https://t.co/Id2dp2wdeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Consensus on Global Bariatric Healthcare https://t.co/9BsOzUFk16 v├Гa @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[PAELLA &amp; FRIENDS #happybirthday #paella #wanderlust #chichi #travel #luxury #worldtraveler #travel #eventsРђд https://t.co/KgrJwocVLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always looking for opportunities to highlight and showcase Atlanta. Room full of potential investors. #GrowAtlantaРђд https://t.co/b6VJTw2bda]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best place to watch a beautiful #sunset is on the #arthurreveneljrbridge in #charlestonsc . @ Charleston, SouthРђд https://t.co/07P3eCuMAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Noticias710digital radiomambi710am @rodrigoduranh @nelsonrubiotv #EEUU #Trump #Venezuela #MiamiDade #Elecciones 20Рђд https://t.co/jsTOyV56Or]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewKocher TheyРђЎre the arm version of cankles. Forerists? Carpulnas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprisingly, yesterdayРђЎs stream on YouTube was a lot better than I had originally anticipated. Even though I didnРђЎРђд https://t.co/kM1NvsoZOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did Brian Elliott manage to look like an aging Colin Hanks without looking like a current Tom Hanks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBENMO I like both, just grew up playing outdoor, so thereРђЎs my bias]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game tomorrow will be at St Joseph 6pm varsity only. Sorry about confusion was wrong on our poster schedule @TitanUp_RHS @rhstitanbasebal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarleyShimkus Pork chops &amp; @kraftrecipes macaroni &amp; cheese ­ЪДђ ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ @KennedyNation @IngrahamAngle @EricTrump @CarleyShimkus]]></document><document><![CDATA[­ЪњаNew Listing!!­ЪњаРађ 515 SE 74th St., Minot ­Ъї┐ 1.55 acresРађ ­ЪЊЈ 4800 sq. ft. Рађ  Give Neil Gush a call today!Рађ Рўј№ИЈ 701-340-17Рђд https://t.co/fwS6AuW1zD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #longexposure #night #nightphotography #light #dark #streets #streetphotography #canada #ontarioРђд https://t.co/IYUZeiWecZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieFratto @davidrgoldberg @eclaireoh We donРђЎt use the РђюMРђЮ word in our family]]></document><document><![CDATA[CC Sabathia┬аOK with starting season on injured list for Yankees https://t.co/JHUOBJcxWD via @Newsday]]></document><document><![CDATA[H&amp;M will be closing soon, so IРђЎm glad I went and snatched up this cute scarf, yes gawd! #fashion #gaycuteРђд https://t.co/SsoRW4W3Ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msloobylou Hah hah! Well, it makes him look like an insufferable twat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ThatРђЎs the game. Tough loss by the @aafstallions. Should have won this game. Had momentum until the end. #SLvsBHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @CandySpangler. Fantastic school librarian, wife, mother, and WMU director. She also makes sure I never go hungry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSKYWGN His family has stunk up my home town with the family business  . Damn clam factory has an awful smell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFBEditSupreme2 Clemson vs Bama and Georgia vs OSU would be the best semi-final games we could get.   Clemson, GeoРђд https://t.co/kxQVRTE4X4]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC Рюѕ№ИЈ Chicago Рюѕ№ИЈ Omaha   #WheelsUp #MarchTravel https://t.co/tyInSEn8R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[His plans for us are better than we can imagine! @ Wolfdale, Pennsylvania https://t.co/Kqa2KgAfa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thomas et Scott en t├фte ├а l'Omnium Genesis https://t.co/KcEd03Qyk1 https://t.co/AQ0Ou2ejeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think itРђЎs funny when people declare they РђюdeserveРђЮ things in this life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Council is proposing a public hearing for the fiscal year 2019-20 budget at 4:30 p.m. March, 6.  Citizen Marv Van RРђд https://t.co/GgsrI9khjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontneedthisrn Sounds like something a stuck up central student would say ­Ъцћ­Ъцћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo.  Absolutely not.  No. Nope. Negative.  No shot.  Nah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wklj All requiring follow up meetings as critical members were not present. ­ЪЎЃ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico look up the KKK and Jim Crow History of the Democrat Party! https://t.co/nyF2mdsdmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyChiefStaff good to see you, Sir, @ArmyWP_Wres with our Superintendent Darryl A. Williams. You brought us luckРђд https://t.co/KeS354qSHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jivanalfaro How is this even a debate? Hands down Twizzlers and anything else from the brand!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueMystery Not GOOD or EVIL... GOOD AND EVIL  THE extremes of each only further The DIVISIONS  THE NEW paradigmРђд https://t.co/dtNy1OFVK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Culin crossed 15K. Time 01:37:06, pace 10:57 min/mile, est. finish 11:38 am https://t.co/GSNt4N7nwP #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expensive surgery needed by London mom not covered by OHIP https://t.co/AmksazBqli]]></document><document><![CDATA[mCNBCnow People are getting this #worldwide ­Ъїј ­ЪЉЅ #cut the cord Рюѓ№ИЈ #enjoy life #no contracts #save money ­Ъњ┤ #anytimeРђд https://t.co/XnY5KQmbgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANelson25380005 @realsaltlake Follow me.  I am following you.  Click on the envelope and send me your full name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what going to college means... itРђЎs not about the money. For the guys that always talk about the РђюmoneyРђЮ anРђд https://t.co/HmzmxvITQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @starrphmom @marcorubio What it says to me, is that we are a godless and immoral nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDaulton @NBAVisions hahahahahaha better than Ben and Ryan. What an idiot, watch more football]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putinsclown @GOP @HouseGOP @SenateGOP Many of them cannot imagine or accept altruism as a real human trait. They dРђд https://t.co/8JAtmWMFM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feliciasonmez @mikedebonis No balls.....if you truly believe abortion is murder then charge all involved with First degree murder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 90 year old mom, Donna! Amazing. We had SO much fun this week, walking (and RUNNING ­Ъў▓) through parks, shopping,Рђд https://t.co/EqEKShYf2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones Is anyone surprised? Their oaths of office are meaningless to them. A voluntary pledge was just "red tРђд https://t.co/joXpKVip3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up. Crush it. Repeat. Yeah... that really is what it boils down to. . . . . . . #crushit #successРђд https://t.co/hq9CKvdaPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless the Phillies who are about to ruin their franchise the same way the Angels did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumbtack Tries Bridging the Benefits Gap for Gig Workers https://t.co/IfFVr8qJzu #tech #business]]></document><document><![CDATA[new month, going through all my tabs. clearing them all until thereРђЎs only just one. Fresh start in the AM ­ЪЎЈ­ЪЈй]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a DreamWeaver Wheat by @TroegsBeer at @reclamationbrew Рђћ https://t.co/7BA5TEFTW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can Disney completely have their stuff together when it comes to EVERYTHING but ESPN?]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Chicago Police say #JussieSmollett has been arrested. In custody.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeAndersonFF @TerryVelcro @FantasyGrafix @HunterGibbon @WestonGibbon @TheVinStrokes @hrr5010 @artcots24 Thank you Jake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate You dont put ketchup on an omelet bar.  If they have ketchup it should be on the table. I used to raРђд https://t.co/IdMrY5TCge]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PghPublicSafety - More pictures from the Baxter Street #fire in Homewood. #WPXI #PGH #Pittsburgh https://t.co/40NI6Ns3xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pregnant lady at the park just yelled, РђюWrigley, Chase, Camden... itРђЎs time to go!РђЮ  I wonder when Guaranteed Rate is due.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si tu novia no te dice eso es porque el vato al que le celas es m├Аs mejor que tu en el aspecto de muchas cosas ­ЪЉђ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HATE the Keto diet РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ Well, like IРђЎve said before it has its time and placРђд https://t.co/7Wcaenm13i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiftyfiveangel @SenFeinstein RBG hasnРђЎt departed, but she isnРђЎt here, in a normal way­Ъци­ЪЈ╗РђЇРЎѓ№ИЈРўЋ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running: a supposedly healthy thing I do all the time that makes me want to die while IРђЎm doing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎve been watching this rivalry since I was a little kid... so pumped for Wednesday 9pm ET. #UNCvsDuke ­ЪЈђ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingdomMind321 @_mckenziexo @mrFOAMERSIMPSON @kustoo @MikeTheCompass Amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations amigo !!! ­ЪцЎ­ЪЈ╝­ЪцЎ­ЪЈ╝ Come celebrate with some margaritas, today is #NationalMargaritaDay KeepРђд https://t.co/pjJ3PJtec9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sauvin Faire by @ThirdWheelBrew at @ThirdWheelBrew Рђћ https://t.co/332y0UGp3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NWMZgMx1Pm We canРђЎt say this is the last big Galaxy S10 leak (thereРђЎs still a day to go until Unpacked), but here it goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also when it comes to the trolls out there, people who will actually call you names and offer no kind of constructiРђд https://t.co/vOm8lXfKGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is she still walking around after getting someone killed? #JussieSmollett https://t.co/K4kI9hndLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROVIDE  . . Рюќ№ИЈIn a world full of Рђюsolution providersРђЮ, what makes you stand apart from everyone else. How do you pРђд https://t.co/0w3E8GeX2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[That derailed westbound train is still here at the Westbury station. @LIRR says westbound trains will run this mornРђд https://t.co/43s4iTf7Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the next couple of months IРђЎll be ramping up my object oriented teaching. Watch this space.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Zaddik OK so yeah she is a bigger star but my thing was why WWE let her come in and jump to the top of the line.Рђд https://t.co/jVkhho5d0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know IРђЎm late, but I JUST saw #GreenBook ­ЪЉЈ­ЪЈЙ­ЪЉЈ­ЪЈЙ­Ъјъ­ЪЊй https://t.co/b5u7xmeYQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh to the days when I had hair and was young!  Now I am proud to be older wiser and bald! https://t.co/PRw9kym5bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusksFUDetector @timseymour @eddiemac3356 @skabooshka @Latrilife @PlugInFUD @TeslaCharts @GrainSurgeonРђд https://t.co/IUc50ZArpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no dog in the fight since @DaleJr retired but IРђЎm rooting for @chaseelliott and @dennyhamlin tomorrow sinceРђд https://t.co/HyUjeZHWDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your car detailed today! https://t.co/YzD8CM8PgL Dm for pricing and availability today! #Wash #Wax #SealantРђд https://t.co/Ok25ba1rZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACH0N3y @animalcrossing All the items I got were dupes. And all of them were 3 star. #disappointed https://t.co/C630nQRrmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just amazing... Respect to Carey Price... Class act!!! Just no words.... #CareyPrice #Humanity #NHLРђд https://t.co/sE6iIP2KVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @CNBCMakeIt ThatРђЎs ridiculous. HeРђЎs a great man but I hope that money went to a good charity. He certainly doesnРђЎt need it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder why I even bother sometimes. IРђЎm living the wrong life. IРђЎm in the wrong place. I need change, ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tax return hitting means I can now eat out without experiencing existential dread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No significant snow is coming for our part of Indiana ... everyone can relax. #AnotherOverHypedWeatherCast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badjamjam Then it's up to us Canadian to add SUPER UNLEADED gas to the flames and not let the SNC issue flame-out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoldenmuzzy @BrooksRoland82 Yet no love or mention for Hart. Best player on the runaway best team in the league #KucherovForHart]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys have earned their standing. Averaging 28 matches/guy, the workРђЎs being done. Reaping time in March shoulРђд https://t.co/4fiZb18KBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AurozOgra @WBG_Cities @UNESCO @SamehNWahba @Ede_WBG @100ResCities @UNHABITAT @Mayors4Climate @c40cities @ICLEIРђд https://t.co/GGUcjtsVcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @JohnKasich Will Kasich run in 2020? Would he run as an independent with another candidate on top of that tickРђд https://t.co/KhtqLXvD6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GOAL... log an workout everyday this year...­ЪЉї­ЪЈй On track Fam...­Ъњ»­Ъњ»­Ъњ»­Ъњ» Jan-Feb2019 #nike#applewatch#activity @ JacksonРђд https://t.co/VmPlGX10zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess theyРђЎre still salty about the Fyre Festival. https://t.co/WIxkw2c9B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rfosterFTNT YesРђћ arthritis and other issues.  Definitely look into it.  It fixed me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dicho y hecho, a los primeros que votaron, les iban a dar una patada en el trasero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Need a Song ­Ъћі Tag someone ­Ъћі doesnРђЎt matter the genre #tripptalk . . . . . #music #free #songs #rapper #rappersРђд https://t.co/vTKIrH0U4B]]></document></documents></author>