<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VeloBusDriver @kgchalms @kcmetrobus The last southbound is a 41, scheduled at IDS at 24:53. The last northbound is… https://t.co/lDlKuwyii6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did you hang up the portrait from the auction?? Did you give it to your North Korea buddy as a gift??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your dedication as a trainer to give back to others #travelingman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gol de Amaury Escoto y así lo celebra el Diego #HazlaDePez Vamos 1-0 😊 https://t.co/6RCrXi7yaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've gotten this in my recommended for as long as it's been up. Almost every day, every week, every year. I've seen… https://t.co/pu54FZHE0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/4R3uUJD9S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I prefer to find the room in which I'm the dumbest, then become a sponge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got out of #FightingWithMyFamily its a good movie... if you can ignore that fact that most of it is fiction. I… https://t.co/K1brQzuQZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking on the whole family in a political argument https://t.co/GxHrecws5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click this link and signup for a great opportunity! https://t.co/38jvc9ul7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to UO’s @benjaminwnelson! The 2018 APA Dissertation Research Award recipients https://t.co/Itb1gTIO0I via @APA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancnluc @realDennisLynch @BarackObama You better start doing some research sweetie, your ignorance is showing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David confirms this way of looking at it, saying that the one who trusts God to do the putting-eve…… https://t.co/1yAYTRR2Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #Washington, #DC  (with special greetings to @WNCathedral) https://t.co/MIZUzJ1k8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImBrittanyEvans Teens having sex? Goodness gracious me! I have the vapours. https://t.co/GlFgCqfa7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmanderz We can only hope or else.....  Judgey Bear takes his job very seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gotta be one of the longest crush ever  if i ever get to bust it’ll be the longest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natural Southern States Classic 🙌 . April 26th and 27th, 2019 💪 . Pro Qualifier 🏆 . Liberty, Missouri 🗺️ . See you… https://t.co/At1H7MBG0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[La cosa es por dónde ver el partido hoy de la @ldacr?? #CentenarioLiguista  #QueLindoSerManudo  #TodosJuntosPorLa30 https://t.co/ppsVeMA4rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpearson3031 @TheRynheart The real question is what's up with the people that support these corrupt people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @sahluwal’s Tweet: https://t.co/tqzcO2gSw1    We have to stop this practice and hold those responsible accountable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabbie_goo Your new profile picture is probably like an 11/10, just sayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @TaiyakiNYC - Miami in Miami, FL w/ @passiondrink https://t.co/xpdW39nAe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murray State is doing in Evansville what Kentucky does in Nashville. Just waves of blue and gold everywhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bwgoldspoon1 @williamsmth66 @NBCSCeltics @Raptors You gonna be sad again this year 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHillMedia @DisneyDishPod @DrewTailored I stopped at the Frozen II or 2 spoilers section. Is it safe  to proceed… https://t.co/AyrsyWp194]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Ferrin @1057TheFan @Orioles @masnRoch @tinytimjones @masnOrioles It’s that new replacement surgery bump !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muppetfrenzy Agreed. I'm a really good cook but I'm a trash at baking. I can make biscuits and really bad challah… https://t.co/s0SLZqOFo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep smh someone put me in a sleeper hold till I pass out, but tuck me in though.. I’m not tryna get sick again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dys_les Hi, Leslie: The headline has been changed, however, Twitter still posts with the outdated version. I apolo… https://t.co/eGOuWhiXhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KimJones PreFall ‘19 collection @dior x #lavishlifeofjay #paradigmluxury https://t.co/QNB2INwhfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marvel 9. When he decapitated a man with a car door because said man disrupted his date  10. When he blew up Hell'… https://t.co/wFQ2LybJKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DashieXP uhhhh you got a DeLorean ma boi or nah 🤔 https://t.co/cwCpRda4Ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I had a dream that I had a company that would always try to replace me with someone who could do I b… https://t.co/F1h543RgnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tezjones29 @WithConnie Happy 30th Birthday Martez Jones🎉🎂🎉 30 is a young man but they’re being killed at 14, 15 et… https://t.co/4eVt5ND40f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me win this awesome giveaway from @GunWinner https://t.co/WKLCjB4QEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connectingSW Ravens cut Eric Weddle: 3 big things (via @footballman58) https://t.co/Pwvmp3gcd0 #Weddle #RavensFlock #NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re waiting for the #mail 😂 #taxes Good Morning! @ Conyers, Georgia https://t.co/i1aVmcnRSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Try not to get hit on by any trannies.” Really, @jccronin? Bigoted language like that makes me want to abandon you… https://t.co/8SvPYS93cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I’m still not convinced I’m going to LOVE Red Dead Redemption II, I gotta admit this game is utterly gorgeous… https://t.co/zb8VbWzQWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrapieLLo @jguaido @AsambleaVE @LuzMelyReyes @EfectoCocuyo Y cuando le dieron a @MariaCorinaYA y a @JulioBorges ?… https://t.co/wVlgmEDmRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSimmons   So how do you feel about your beloved NBA players having the same leaderships as President? Only abl… https://t.co/S0B5xFJzvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[As one who has (unfortunately) unthinkingly praised Finland’s education system results in the past without giving t… https://t.co/pmp4vrfann]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orlando_Larry52 FSU game 2016.  ESPN game day and Lamars breakout party.  Stayed 4 hours after the game tailgating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deeSilas_ Fr you supposed to match each other fly but not by wearing the exact same thing like lil kids 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could be a move honestly. I can just send them a link to my shirt when they annoy me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've opened negotiations with the New York Times over an Aus football product.   We've reached a major hurdle over… https://t.co/h307rv82Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattklapper So what your saying is Hillary stole the nomination from Bernie Sanders to save democracy? Interesting very interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve gotta have absolutely nothing better to do with your life.. To do this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conéctate a nuestro servicio semanal ahora.  Te puedes unir a través de #FBLIVE o https://t.co/8zsAIA7xWc  #aomiami… https://t.co/wBZ4WQZkys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting to listen to Korra herself fight for the greatness of Korra. Thank you @screenjunkies @janetvarney… https://t.co/r23b93LhQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why on earth does @mitchellreports give Chris Ruddy @newsmax the time of day? Just another trump sycophant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Lani the goodest girl in her birthday hat https://t.co/olBLyDTMuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[that “do it look like i give a fuck because i dont” vine has been playing in my head all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreybojorquez You must be a good man..... there must be a common attraction..... but it's inside what really counts ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Meller @AdamAAbdalla  There once was a man named waddle  He was pretty enough to be a model.  But he retired… https://t.co/OuIBviYJvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We gave each other high fives 🤣🤣 We had too much fun at @WaltDisneyWorld  VIP Event for @Passholders https://t.co/FbrYAG00gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre sean persistentes, si en verdad les gusta una chav@, no se rindan! Porque TODO lo que vale la pena en esta… https://t.co/fNA3UgTTTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting that good word in this morning at A Change For Christ! 🙏🏽 Thankful for another day that was not promised to… https://t.co/clz17ah2d2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDayCobra At least you know when you make a mistake and take responsibilities. Keep on doing what your doing  👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amuoralzg @mattyglesias @jessesingal A necessary starting point for the leftist position, but not really an answer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jared Kushner needs to resign and then be prosecuted for lying. #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s almost tournament time, @CoachLadner. i’m ready. @SLU_Hoops   #RIPOldCourt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeofimoLopez where can I buy some merch? I want a cap just like the one your pops always wears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing will happen to her, when Democrats are in charge. Look at Virginia. And shame on all you Republicans in the… https://t.co/6OsgpFAS8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I sit on this plane ready to be reunited with my amazing family and take a short 4 day break, it’s a great time… https://t.co/Y2hOs9TIkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAindex Did she really leave to escape the taxes or did she leave to escape @AOC ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@souljaboy Me too check me out #THINKFAST now streaming everywhere https://t.co/citLlkifMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 3657 Birchwood Rd #Saukville #WI  #realestate https://t.co/KLm0qyOJkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyricspoetic That was Jada giving a teaching moment. Teaching without chastising. Jordyn thought she was agreeing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBR4EVA @JeffreyTheGreek @TimSherry12 @slmandel @BruceFeldmanCFB While Nebraska, delusional or not, expects champi… https://t.co/GtLhV6S9GI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cluque33 @GeorgeEsGenial @DeniseDresserG Sobre todo en un día donde se conmemora la lucha contra la discriminación… https://t.co/2efEL0Zzrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHortons Been there done that, thx for the refund, but no thx for doing business with you anymore. And I STRONGL… https://t.co/Sj1I82uVGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a party!! My good friend and student aleksander.flores made his American Ninja Warrior Junior debut with a ban… https://t.co/LuiINMMlH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I can’t believe I lost my AirPods smh . It’s rare for to lose my things .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceyEvansWWE Your daughter looks like she’s growing pretty quickly...catching up to her momma soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just uncovered the memory I repressed in which one of my first grade classmates dared himself to rub his own pp on… https://t.co/5jBZDQjgsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homie said “your dead to me” because he heard his crush is crushin on me 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bklvr14 @Kahil @williamlegate He stood in one place, the Indian approached him and got in his face while lying abo… https://t.co/q1UslMnkLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caveat: The truth, if knowable, which, sometimes it is, may piss you off but will really set you free, even if it i… https://t.co/cr2r5U79MM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofWalkerMI  is pleased to have Oscar repping our great city!  He has jogged more roads with his mom than just… https://t.co/1NpRdNNTev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @Thaworden11 To be fair it isn’t illegal to sing in public. Selling without  a license is. Yes I know the… https://t.co/ZUdnwHAPma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReluctantGOPer @GOP Because we live in a democratic republic and what the other person said as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/gCDSY4Ui07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HutchVNL That hurts to think about 😅😂 I saw some light on the horizon for y’all though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju ask him if he spoke with roger stone, or anyone in the trump family...  step up Manu!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepublicanFraud @the_real_LAFord @ByronYork you are pathetic Troll and I'm done feeding you have a good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Puertorock77_ @SoulKingLives @BrokenGamezHD These systems are to similar for excuses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennwhite Sort of at random this book both does and doesn’t include a MAC in its designs. Here, he’s forgotten abo… https://t.co/MPuacOiLWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, but don't touch. Touch, but don't taste. Taste, don't swallow. John Milton  The Devil's Advocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[THINGS. JUST. GOT. INTERESTING. Our Redeemer’s takes a 42-38 lead over Bishop Ryan into the final quarter of this s… https://t.co/cDqd0X9o0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Leavitt Four time felon needs to be locked up. Paul Manfort did not put anyone’s life in jeopardy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mucho Yalitza pero le haces el feo a la mujer indígena que te pide dinero en la calle, tengan tantita madre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning. Zen Garden. Simple little recycled wood turned into Found Art Candle Holders. #foundartbytjd #wood… https://t.co/hIaj2SSJbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevorwoodart @rustedsprings @Crogthefrog @SjwSpiderman @renfamous No but i will check it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you shittin me!? I’d be crazy if I felt this way about Latin Trap when there’s artists out here like Daddy Yank… https://t.co/yNHjnyjjzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megan7oneill @stackjo @davidmweissman but now we know Trump wants Bernie to run as an independent. That's the bigg… https://t.co/Ye2umvRatI]]></document><document><![CDATA[im going crazy over your album. thank you momma @solangeknowles #WhenIGetHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RL_Miller @SenFeinstein I don’t think anyone thinks that a national carbon tax is the exclusive solution; however,… https://t.co/3UEp1dJ30w]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey vato! #DonaldTrump #thinks we're stupid! He thinks we would try smuggle drogos! United states! What 4? we get B… https://t.co/22bFNkZBr4]]></document></documents></author>