<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[love is on its way is one of the greatest jonas brothers songs, try to fight me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carjjc2 Republicans always spouting "fiscally conservative". I've never seen it in my lifetime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP On the road to the #Hitler regime! They want to legalize marijuana so most people will be high and not realize they are no longer free!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurahbaeza No sé por qué me molesta, de entrada no me halaga. También me pasa con el cabello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeWebber9 @shanedawson @JeffreeStar @ColbyBrock what did i just click on oh my god]]></document><document><![CDATA[the guy was a liar calling Trump the choice maker of Russia that the Trump signed off 3 months after his presidency… https://t.co/5c4Ho7FjMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad we couldn't take a ferry ride, but we definitely explored a ton. :'^) @ San Francisco Ferry Building https://t.co/J7GLURawdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discussion in 9th grade English Mollie: it was Yorkshire McKayla: like the sausage?  Brody: are you talking about t… https://t.co/rPj2XLYvm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollylynn444 Being a good woman to your man comes in many forms, that is just one I like to do. Each to their own.… https://t.co/2vfT1joh7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elena’s gonna learn to not act like this and if I ever have a son he’s gonna learn to smack bitch if she’s acting l… https://t.co/sOsPifRtiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikiFirmin @RPD_Axel @PD_Drake_DC @DC_PoliceDogs @LancsPolDogUnit @polscotdogs @policedogunit @NSPoliceDogs @ERPDF… https://t.co/FkWP2eeF9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Get out the super absorbent Depends Donnie Boy! Shits about to get real!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraMiaSG @TheWiningHour @winegal57 @winewankers @DemiCassiani @RealWineGuru @Fiery01Red @Dracaenawines @jflorez… https://t.co/6o62XFUh3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[sedat pakay’s intimate portraits of james baldwin (at david zwirner for god made my face) blew me away. to be captu… https://t.co/aj6XwtZxEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Controlando mi mente y haciéndome mas fuerte 💪🏽  Controlling my mind and making myself stronger . . . .… https://t.co/ZII4mKALUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zandrous @MyFavoriteBeach @TheLoveBel0w @myawesomelife4 @CarneRoyale @AOC So you go to med school,  have 100,000s… https://t.co/fyOlHvQkRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Had One Job!  A relaxation therapy course is designed for counselors, therapists, mental health... https://t.co/5I1gcZq6Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this jolly there's something wrong with you. #humor #chuckle #smirk #humorous https://t.co/bG1x6Tr8J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[WaPo Issues Big Fat Correction For Big Fat Lies In Covington Catholic Kids Coverage https://t.co/8IJ386TLIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, we have to address the Homelessness issues!!  No families should be put out their homes 🏡!! Exspecally our Vet… https://t.co/3V6zJFxT4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have fun yesterday with my second family with my daughter aireen she came to visit me 🙂😁😃😄😘💃🙏 https://t.co/wJqvWhOrW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wicked74303 @broadwaycom @BeMoreChill I want to see Kiss me Kate. Lol!! Hmmm? I wonder which show that is? 🤔.  Wel… https://t.co/YPvhJrvBTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Alexander on transformative justice: Reckoning With Violence https://t.co/Q9pHZpHCSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles Hugs James 😍 text Tati I feel like she would know exactly what to say rn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg and Julián Castro came out swinging in the fight for 2020.   Get familiar with those names. They hav… https://t.co/7XCD8pLnUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  Me: I’m moving to California in a year!!!!!!! Fuck Maryland 💪🏼🤷🏻‍♀️⚡️🍍‼️🤧🤢🤠😱😱😬😂😳😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkUncleP @Pharoah_Gama @damn_ryte @TIMxMACK @ItsTheBAUCE It’s almost time my g’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does this color palette give us so many dreamy sighs?! Photo @emilieaphoto @ Ma Maison https://t.co/M8ZxWxPRi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #FatTuesday. We’re celebrating with @lowdownbrass band on @channel2kwgn tune in for some high energy fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Espngreeny It’s not your alarm clock, is you’re putting stroke that is prohibiting you from playing on the tour! #Kidding #Fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maleyna says it isn’t valid for me to change my name to Plato Basketball Justice. Is this a valid name?]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is tucker (for my new followers) he’s perfect https://t.co/oWfvrFAMX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josiah_nyale .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different kin… https://t.co/M0pqnJjaRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i cry at night thinking about how ill probably never be able to see post malone front row in concert ever again]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest review: #HumanAnimals produced by @arcstage. You can also follow @envirocontrolTO for "updates" about the… https://t.co/dOlMg0aln1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attract what you expect, reflect what you desire, become what you respect, mirror what you admire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kengordon @ZacconeMaryann lots of cool cars today. 🤙🤙 https://t.co/8MQYAergMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennifield @LordOtis_ @el_nashtified @a_boy_like_that @the_Ashytect @_chillara @salako_tcode @certified_empez… https://t.co/8tMsgRG2OB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nectarsleep I’ve tried that and got hung up on after being on hold for 20 minutes. And the chat is not working.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying la croix for the first time and people have such strong opinions on it. I DONT GET IT. Like it’s alright, bu… https://t.co/jFBtbSGmga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonag04 @VikingsELA7 @ElaRasberry this looks so awesome! Engaging &amp; something Ss would definitely relate to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan This is so AMAZING! Way to go MacKay! Way to go Scotland 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdriguez_jass I heard que la cambiaron. So it’s not the same mannequin 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohio50 @jw_gilbert @TheHerdCHS @chselksad @GWOC @JDabbs86 thank you !!! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankshyong My dad was obsessed with the Yoshinoya beef bowl! Tastes like this particular bian dang he had in Taiwan growing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBaconBlood Thanks LBB!! Can’t believe our kids are about to go to college! 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saying... y’all never left the select list of artists that I keep on my iTunes for my phone. https://t.co/hwS9GcCbvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuzElenaGlez muchisimas gracias por la foto! Muy guapa y super amable!! 💖 en Teatro de los Héroes https://t.co/Gh6s4JyXDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain Thank you for your factual perspective on Green New Deal. Need all views]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG the micro micro penises on the french men at the urinal scene in SE2 EP4  'The Sword and the Hand' @AmazonStudios #Patriot]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 of 4 little paintings of mother and child.  Great for Mother's Day. - #motherandchild #grandbohemiangallery… https://t.co/OZX0pWYlbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustafsonBrad A2: Most times students don’t know their strengths. I tell them. Then I set them up with opportuniti… https://t.co/S8hYcbx1GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turned the heater on in the house. That's how you know it's bad. https://t.co/XBIPyDWtc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch @realDonaldTrump You simply can not reason with a 2yr old special needs man/baby. You just ignore… https://t.co/SdI04WCw00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigsturmcoming I had a dream during my nap earlier we went on vacation to a remote island but you fucked up the pl… https://t.co/Xka5SMPY91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yychoeman @LauraE303B Always has to be a villain we can blame everything on. That eliminates the necessity of crit… https://t.co/8lAYD5xRoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieinjax I came home to Penn for cancer treatment. One year this month cancer free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beerhunter74 @badhopper @ManvsAle @mtravis63 @cellmavin @danmayer77 @ephoustonbill @wrayzors @JohanBBT @15jjc… https://t.co/x0VSMpqeSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @marcorubio I doubt it. He’s too busy kissing trump’s ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sedona &amp; AZ I am currently  booking the week of  3/28 thru 4/5! 💄 https://t.co/uLsbEk04XI #carriekacen… https://t.co/HSC1rbPxAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian @KrisJenner I’m a 20 yr old marketing student at UGA. Kim, your customer service and marketing team… https://t.co/FXvtOR0FAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juanbat2 @jaazieldizon1 @joshuatorralba U mean @dnllsalinas @daina &amp; me right????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@violets6661 @AllTimeHockeyFn he pulled up and i think i almost cried. then he came back outside and my friends cal… https://t.co/Ew5qcjOQHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu She came off as old, an aging dinosaur who needs to make room for younger generations and make sure her votes reflect that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zavier Simpson’s hook shot is absolutely filthy https://t.co/40mcc7ypPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing to do with politics."  He said Venezuelans "are being denied medicine, food and aid needed to live while th… https://t.co/0syulCiTwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtholfsen @MicrosoftEDU @MSFTEnable @hojusaram @kerszi @sdtitmas @RobynHrivnatz @KarenJan @MSAUedu @NccE Thank you… https://t.co/HlYPH8wHoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurniteGeorge @paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump I'm wondering if the $6.9 billion (I think) Trump asks for in the new… https://t.co/hbATOkBooX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening remarks from @PhillyMayor on the strength and success of the #Irish community in #Philly. @IABCNPhila https://t.co/RQmjvxMYJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who thinks it’s better to say more than enough than not enough??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will pass on spicy food &amp; scary movies but roller coasters is a must]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck @JCJCBaseball ! Keep on fighting for that W! #4-0 #proudmom #BobcatsBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are non color corrected stills from yesterday. 🎥 @pjdavs • @JonathanLondon says he’s not an #actor so I wrote… https://t.co/UHg7mTfZne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police are investigating a hit and run chain reaction crash that damaged these vehicles on the South Side. A descri… https://t.co/PDYvmkFutk]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHS Music Club meeting for incoming musicians’ parents tonight-  7pm band room.  Music Camp info and Band Tryouts/p… https://t.co/5ewqAOuJjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waking up in the wee hours of the morning: I need to get some more sleep before the alarm goes off   My brain: I… https://t.co/z2sHhWWwKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just performed live with Crystal Waters at the Atlanta Hawks basketball game ... OMG!! Tweeting so I’ll remember]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for my delayed flight to leave from #ROC to #DCA to attend the @NCRC #JustEconomyConference . I'll be there before lunch, hopefully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinahVP John Miklos has told me he stepped down because of all the critics. regardless he is educated in this fiel… https://t.co/M4ciKjwYQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a thrill to lead such a talented and engaged team of researchers in this important endeavor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al fin encontré 1 de las 3 franelas que necesito... #marvel 😍 en Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/ynLQGWb3hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to chuckle it off. #comedy #chuckle #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/KPO1fKVLsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls wit boyfriends are too main stream that’s why I go for the married 1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #ousd parents! After you support #Oakland teachers on the picket line take your kids to a local musuem! We love… https://t.co/44YFpd1EQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @NoLabelBrewCo @CatsOnTap @TammyJaben @RJellyman @badhopper @JonMontag @Stef_Pellerin I love passion… https://t.co/7EaCqzVOYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bballjkey Great job @spearj23 Jewel and @Tamiaj14 .   I’m wishing both of you the beat of luck and KEEP WINNING!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twinning &amp; wasn’t planned .... thanks backbone_dungeon_family 💯 #son #momlife #friday @ Dunwoody, Georgia https://t.co/MNEnTssR8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trending page called the Kardashian drama a “brouhaha” and I seriously can’t stop laughing😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Weak and spineless, unable to take a joke because he knows he is a JOKE. Seriously in a national e… https://t.co/Po8R9QhYMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garretdillahunt @UmbrellaAcad How interesting.....I was considering a Deadwood binge....... https://t.co/1veSa7BPl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bones_canada I AM ONLY FRIENDS WITH PEOPLE WHO ALSO SPEND WHOLE LECTURES DOING WEIRD HAND THINGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How early is too early to start declaring your daily idiocies as “senior moments” for example how I just thought I… https://t.co/BvwV1HfllE]]></document><document><![CDATA[💕🙏💕his love never gives up on us💕🙏💕🎶🤗🙏💕🎶 @ Sunriver, Oregon https://t.co/owbUw24yrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who got fucked over by the one guy she wanted? Lmaooo meeeeee 😐🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning my new commute to work and taking the 4:55am train just to get to OTF and to work on time🍊 🔥 🏃‍♀️ No other… https://t.co/Eni8IN6JgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSaraMiles_ yeah...my feet hurt and i almost sprained my ankle 3 times today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to ship! Perfect for your little sweetheart! Available as a headband or a hair clip! This adorable wool felt… https://t.co/suWnKUoMWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjkarcher @CanadensisMax It's too risky with ultra-conservatism in ascendancy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cirque Du CMOM Fundraiser was oh so fun! @EventsBeyondddd used balloons to bring each theme to life. We had to have… https://t.co/jAcqiMhXiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis come Alive viewtopic.php?f=11&amp;t=820&amp;p=8031&amp;hilit=Genesis#p8031]]></document></documents></author>