<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Les comparto la que fue mi sopa de rice noodles y vegetales de hoy.   #besis #NoMeGustaElPimentón https://t.co/42RYaHi9PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drpichel O es la verdad que todos los que no piensan como tú son imbeciles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve thought long about the DNC’s decision to ban Fox from airing the Dem primary debates. I think it’s a mistake t… https://t.co/OvxJ2fOuwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie My Mariners are up first @Katie and let the fun begin. I just absolutely love this time of year, I saw my fi… https://t.co/1Pxii13Fue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @bfouhy Oh shut up. Everyone on that list is culpable &amp; has info. You're acting like FOX NEWS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hiMc39GNfJ  Nom-nom  Biological control in #Texas  Awesome  #PublicHealth #Mosquito]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WordOfKo @MorganKolkmeyer @SouthwestAir @marcusleshock @WGNMorningNews Love to see the story when it’s up..no run 🏃 in snow ❄️ today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @reg1776 @slusk123 @JanRickey @ImabitcSumtimes @TigerLetsRoll @JulieReichwein1 @tnmynatt @Sekusa1… https://t.co/so3TwdIFNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieBowget @Chrispb131 @HackneyAbbott @sajidjavid She voluntarily left the UK, she wasn’t kidnapped or forced… https://t.co/GZl4kBCPre]]></document><document><![CDATA[might I add:  - I took a 4 hour nap  - watched a star is born - watched the reputation stadium tour  now capping th… https://t.co/tjAJ1IEMvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neesietweets Well we control our own destiny, when not under orders, he asked for it and hurt innocent people. I h… https://t.co/HqZoYJNd2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[W.F. West wins 57-43, will take on Washougal at 9 pm on Thursday in round 3 of Bearcats-Panthers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellJody @TimKennedyMMA One can look at recent history and see the effect of socialist change and what it means no… https://t.co/jQLKZm88Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RollingLoud we making the biggest group chat ever! Retweet to spread the word!!! #RollingLoudV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh my lead is pretty cool, it just pains me to see that I’ll be trying to take his job. :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Roenick @NHL THIS has to be your favorite goal ever. I know it’s mine. I was there. Thanks for the thrill. https://t.co/hawPw7g7a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Up, Up, &amp; Away by @2spbrewing @ Two Stones Pub Jennersville — https://t.co/VeAIgPlBTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#home #e90 #karamu #karamuhouse #216 #cleveland #ohio #love #quincy #musicislife #lifeismusic #plays @ Karamu House https://t.co/UtQlL9ruFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BrewMac @JodeciMManz Best looking raccoon is the lightskin raccoon 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martin_worgan @alwoodswork @JuliaHB1 @RJ_Banksy May I hazard a guess that you don't have young children at school… https://t.co/bybxms4GUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[He totally just injected that rat in the groin and the insects need to win now. #BMovieManiacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN YOU NEED ALL THE PROTEIN unisoyfoods veganstrongteam 💪 Come say what’s up to Team Vegan at booth 1425! @ The A… https://t.co/gnIlJ2GT0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly just want to do a sex toy haul LMAO. I know that’s so random but there’s literally a list of things I’ve wanted to try.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Fars_14 @TwistedJC @jenluvzbaseball @SaveByKorenar @WEINGERIN Thanks for the W but sad you had to leave early https://t.co/oI7bcEkBZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginabean72 @Post429Baseball @David_Bohr Yes. There is good history of youth baseball in Lebanon County, but it is… https://t.co/91218GhrTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenCoryGardner @RepPerlmutter  Please take note. Hundreds of thousands of innocent babies count on you to do the r… https://t.co/LBT1FmFYxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kickback #beer #margaritas #barbeque #vaping #music #food #academyawards #lilpeep #greatdaeg #paris #postmalone… https://t.co/RbmnBaUwwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/qXsrU7eTKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I identify as @Alyssa_Milano  I want access to your life, finances, and property! That's how it works right? I bet… https://t.co/Z7ppHwdjGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im convinced once kawhi sees all the beautiful women in Toronto during summer he gon wanna stay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodFriendedMe Our resident Queen and leader @AshtonParsley blessing us @ValorCollege with a sneek peak of this is a treasure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11brewera @NASCARonNBC @HailieDeegan @jaggerjones98 Only at a few tracks]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @SHardwork program is the REAL deal!#mudmade #sahardwork #texashardwork #family #hoopsonmission @ Alamo City Ch… https://t.co/LdLaq5Z5Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOOM...TATAR 🚨 @TATRR what a beauty goal to start the game 🏒👍 against your former team @CanadiensMTL let's get the… https://t.co/cdtBnmXFQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Firestorm013 @IvankaTrump Here’s a lovely picture of Benedict Arnold. https://t.co/MFMccrlrXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottcoulton @cnab_spec @kubernetesio @IstioMesh @Azure @DockerCon @containercamp @kubeconio In that case, it may… https://t.co/m2qncc9n4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_man6 People being lowkey racist and dont want to admit it,  that's basically what happened 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debiontheweb @lyft Was just in my first Los Angeles car chase! https://t.co/bhmqWxGFUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Everything is the President’s fault.  Just ask a Liberal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimJarmuschHair I legit wonder how many people who voted for him think he provided the singing voice? My wife's parents both did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randycorporon @nytimes Yesterday's hearing speaks for itself.  The Rep Party has poisoned itself.  Too early to ca… https://t.co/4AULOVLx5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omnia is jump’n 4 a Tuesday! #zippidy #vegas #omnianightclub @ OMNIA Nightclub https://t.co/TIYwMN3A47]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there’s two very distinct eras of Fall Out Boy. There’s an angsty music for teenagers Fall Out Boy and ther… https://t.co/7ypZqSg4PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimiescxtt Even my dad who like only payed attention occasionally was like reslly that’s the stupidest ending I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like this @mims analysis. Amazon decision to not do HQ2 in NYC could mean new #startups, #angel investors, and… https://t.co/ZpFVEymRQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kikegarciaadn No Quique ellos aún piensan que empataron porque solito fue superior, pero pues fue más por lo que d… https://t.co/wkY8UlcjHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @JamesBayMusic !!! Definitely worth the wait 😍😍 https://t.co/Q8TeixCbZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is a choice. Things in life make it difficult, but at the end of the day you control your own happiness❤👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Because they are mentally unstable oh look twitter banned your tweet go figure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are giving the government a tax free loan. #NotSmart #UncleSamThanksYouThough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yea, please get tuff with these Ca. politicians before they completely screw up this great state.… https://t.co/7cbhyBTXsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think all restaurants should stop giving straws with their drinks unless someone asks for one 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALX_S0UL Yeah its cool, just been going to school and work really 🤷🏽‍♂️ nothing much else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Lowe's? We're hiring in #LongBeach, CA! Click for details: https://t.co/gEjBVbDdk8 #Retail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cameron’s highlights from the AVC Tournament this past weekend https://t.co/qcTBwQYIJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t change who I am I js try to get better so in the meantime keep it moving or except that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikal @egernst @ccollicutt @cmsj @intel @katacontainers @dtroyer the community didn’t have the right information.… https://t.co/t4ystBdTCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookieRiverside The next time I hear some politician or lawyer remind us we’re a country of laws, remind them that… https://t.co/koGl1h68ZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAMEDAY!!   7A #1 Bob Jones (3-0) 🆚 6A #3 @HGHS_Baseball (1–2)  🗓 2/26, Tuesday  ⏰ 7:00  📍 Hazel Green High School… https://t.co/xR9djw5rK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fight continues, but one thing is true, The Stupid is spreading. It’s spreading quicker than ever. Plan accordingly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PETAUK @KatRussell12 So, you are against the Michigan Milk Producers Association (MMPA) ?  I am not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher I am happy for the new album but I have to admit I like your original material.Closer to the truth had some w… https://t.co/VOSO6J3TW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyCameron @thenatalyaco I YELL EVERYTHING SO THE !! WORK OUT JUST FINE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Thomas: The Big Lie About the “Science of Reading” https://t.co/RHZoZXMYbF via @dianeravitch This is fact, and… https://t.co/kDGmBQruah]]></document><document><![CDATA[... reconciliation and grateful in weekly mass 🙏🏽 @ St. James Catholic Cathedral https://t.co/peEhvkBubU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidOAtkins @DanteAtkins Watch Mr. Smith Goes to Washington (1939). Some things don't change much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having these #NXT stars juxtaposed against the #RAW announcing crew is painful. The incessant explaining and overal… https://t.co/Wo6fbbwZPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[All about perspective.... @ Knoxville, Tennessee https://t.co/E0GNbJKP7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full color #custom #printed #STICKERS / #Decals for my clients. #fashion #APPAREL #clothing #brand #shirts… https://t.co/1Olk5CF5Y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forest Hills NY Fri Mar 8th AM Forecast: TODAY Mostly Cloudy Hi 45 TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shane_holmberg @NickRekieta @CoolerDakota @MeReachingout @SSJLarryDavid @Fantmas3141 @ObscureAaron @renfamous Kumo… https://t.co/Z564dNdVWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[was stuck in a very scary and violent situation last night with a friend and I’m genuinely hurt by 1.) what happene… https://t.co/194dLx5sbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow the raiders look stacked brown cooper at wr and Mack leading the defense for them 😉😉 @NFL @WGR550]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGianaris You lied about people on the street thanking you for killing the Amazon deal? Who celebrates killing TWENTY FIVE THOUSAND JOBS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctrBenway @9toed_Viking @texbrodave1 @nonya_bidniss @udarnik @marymjoneil @Kate_Amara @WTEpaminondas @aarostew… https://t.co/gyvL5CvMjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsbasiltime Is this Android update the redesign that iOS got a few months ago? Or are there bugs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Actually I’m more interested in justice for the American people #Lockhimup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BucketHeadDyn You're a legend if you solve this ".... .... Raven 😏"  #LOYALSQUAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Leffe Blonde / Blond by @Leffe @ Royal Caribbean Symphony Of The Seas — https://t.co/iZrHyBQwkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyCarrBrokeDown Dude AB didn't shred anything lol , he's played almost every game the last 5 years, where was all… https://t.co/SVKQTOlGcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I don’t know what it is with San Diego goalies but we keep hitting the nail on the head with them. Jeff Glass… https://t.co/SDH7b8LrU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace I never realized until today , when I saw them in action , how truly lame brained Jordan and Meado… https://t.co/qUJzavTqkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had @rhj_24324 temperament. Always cool, and collected on here ... bravo man, always classy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 20th Birthday Angelica!🎂 with Baby Adam celebrating his 27th monthsary, too!🎉🎁❤️ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/fWZnMjda4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estarLA @netflix Omg. It’s the best!  I wish there was another season #midnightdinertokyostories]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasonGemmer @Charger0843Rion @highbrow_nobrow Not really. Dems want to see Jr., Jared, Ivanka and Trump in jail. No deaths, just cells.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that #PlanetEarth has 100 lightening strikes per second as observed from space. That’s over 8 million… https://t.co/S5f0umRBXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the best run, well was a run/walk, but i got the miles in and moving in a positive direction… https://t.co/Yzed0VukGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw I don't think Trump can manage the government and get reelected. When are we going to start talking about… https://t.co/ILP78ZktIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a good 4 am start to your day!  Debate: #earlybirds vs #nightowls.  I work better as an early bird. Wh… https://t.co/m3T2BhWcEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is the only thing that has gotten me to smile this whole week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deojr1965 Well Donald - The government is getting involved because #FDA has authority to regulate #ecigs. The Agen… https://t.co/h3J96mK12a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gerald Butts is a bad liar with a hilariously bad cover story. Claims they moved JWR because they needed someone qu… https://t.co/AJ3dCLyQ8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cincosayshsport @ALawRadio You directly attributed to him the status of “victim of police brutality “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoopOnNRA @AOC Here you go.   I’m gonna keep posting them.  There so many https://t.co/uSad74iiVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my ppl have deep issues. Don’t mean they not my friends or our dynamics changed. I love em the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexaLonestar @Trump454545 Ridiculous. The groups that are organizing n paying these caravans need to be prosecuted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump U forgot Fantastic President of the United States of America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngriestPat @MightyKeef oh my god the room will be on fire this time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying hard not to discuss the birds and the bees with an iguana. @ Ocean Springs, Mississippi https://t.co/dTTkYYrlgK]]></document></documents></author>