<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Her impact on this world was great and wide. Her impact on me was immeasurable. #TeamJodi #PikeFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunkybun @PopResistance @lilith2u @buell003 @Communista2 @KittyBhagat @haloefekti VT is legalizing- state is so da… https://t.co/vpJpMZVUMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbelievable!!! When will Bad Behavior by a Republican have to Foot their Own Legal bills? Wealthy Donors paying it… https://t.co/amBMHe2Crd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joebonsall @AMTShows @oakridgeboys Joe!!! I totally LOVED  your impromptu on My Radio Sure Sounds Good To Me tonig… https://t.co/9hVUHn1Rte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @julianzelizer @CNNOpinion Good distraction 👍 https://t.co/xxSbhYKnyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephGruber Safe travels and all the best to you. Sorry we couldn’t make it yesterday as we were still on the roa… https://t.co/r4kRLuE4AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful way to start the day! #FridayFeeling @USAsunrise @EarthandClouds2 @EarthandClouds @ShareALittleSun… https://t.co/FG8oQ3EoFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway, here’s another incredibly ridiculous foodie video. #foodlove #TikTok https://t.co/Rn0LHkQq5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you've never run out of room on your staff paper and tried to extend the stave into the margins freehand... you're a cop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D10Peacock @bryentravis They sound  great!  Way to go Peacock Choir! 🎼👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricShapiro3 Since people keep liking this twat, remember she won by 3 million votes and she handily defeated Bern… https://t.co/Xm9WrUd1NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my boo enjoying a cool Jazz concert dinner #thepressroom #portsmouthnh #jazzdinner #lovehim @ The Press Room… https://t.co/2jfAZxsYGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye, yaaa, ya me harté de las solicitudes de amistad y ninguna es de mi bebé @nickjonas , agregame bebé, te amo😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petitevanilla @bhatbhabie Extremely unfortunately I do not have whiskey either 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard the rumors. I watched her cringe as she sat in the other side of the church. She was absolutely beautiful.… https://t.co/0RimGSkuny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNCtarheelfan I’m excited to see all the NXT guys.  Most of my favs are on Raw but I’ll always go and support no matter the brand!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope everyone is ready for @5boymom to withdraw her amendment on @jrajra’s SB 167 in the morning when the… https://t.co/eufTaL7A9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko @syyddaustralia @lil__chewy remember in dahlonega omggggg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MShakeFactory @SouthSidePgh @6Schultz6 @penguins @penspartners Gina Natale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley @BWilliams @11thHour @NicolleDWallace Thanks. I wasn't going to watch but now i will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RODEOHOUSTON @TpTroubadours I will ditch a wedding and drive 3hrs if i have to 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump May the Lord please open your eyes and heart to see and receive truth.  He is the way, the Truth and the light.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@internaltopo Is reality objective and outside of everyone’s subjective experience tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try to avoid posting too many ‘look how freakin cute my dog Is’ pics and videos.. but this continued behavior whe… https://t.co/nPPooVwqnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like a real bitch when I say something without realizing how privileged I am to be able to do thin… https://t.co/c9UMzeFtvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JStrawd1 I have been blessed of a son that I have been given as a gift.. but oh man!!😂😂 at 14 I sure Hope that my… https://t.co/KuXxHNhejL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seokjins_sky Oh okay, okay *straightens my back and makes a serious face*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Jaxsen!!!! 🎉🎂😘💙  (part 1! haha 😂) @ Main Event https://t.co/b4px7gqH0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 It can only get better from now Eva!! Off out to do the Laundry and hopefully have the Laundry Room to myself 😊😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyphy_republic No I get why you said it was a no brainer to support teachers but I don't get the usefulness of say… https://t.co/M268Ch01Ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioDawson This is such an awful bill. Brought by “any excuse to screw Boise” crusader Kike Moyle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yassss!!!! 😍🙌🏼♥️✨🥰 @jakemiller  @pandoramusic #latenightvibes https://t.co/NbT5S9h83X]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ❤️ in Tennessee, my granddaughter Laci. Getting a pick me upper before school☕️ https://t.co/3wwrcMm5yC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MortonAlex @DannyShawBBC @sajidjavid Nope. Have you seen mafia movies. Children avenge their parents. It will be l… https://t.co/iZDqfHOoL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frito Lay: Add pet suffocation warning labels to your chip bags! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/Tsv8b1aNll via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pamela de antes con tres caguamitas dormia bien  La pamela de ahora con media cuaguama anda bien peda  Que paso… https://t.co/a4r56KWgqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attended a great workshop by the United Women of the Arts entitled “Pitching for TV and Film with @tyjohnstontv”, F… https://t.co/Z1pk1yr6kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom just got home... all i hear from the garage is mayores by becky g playing and my mom singing along.. 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[trao3 sitting beneath the best background ever #tennisraquet #surfclubfourseasons #springbreakmiami @ Four Seasons… https://t.co/wpeWpSFMW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t even realize “A Little Bit Longer” by the Jonas brothers was Nick singing about his diabetes and that just hit me hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarpad @iamjohnoliver @LastWeekTonight Not you! Happy 4 year Anniversary of #akf. Jared, you saved me! Thank you!!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Me Play: Max Payne 2 Part 6.8  #GameOn https://t.co/BWFTtLGr08 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surfspies @AOC No, AOC hubris is beyond the pale. It's similar to the arrogance of the 5 time deferment President,… https://t.co/78nFhi51qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like nigga you still gay. He bitch you out the moment that dick pass the second hole. Go sit down somewhere. But ge… https://t.co/LVsdp78Pt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charles_gaba I had to read that three times until I  (sadly) understood what they did 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to shout out that the @LGuardiansComic Patreon with colored pages is gorgeous and inspiring!! Definitel… https://t.co/y81UXLGc9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMonteroOficial @patriciajaniot @CMonteroOficial Gracias por su paciencia y su gran apoyo por Venezuela! 👍🇻🇪🇻🇪🇻🇪]]></document><document><![CDATA[def we need to talk then they hit you with the “in person” then you think about everything you’ve done since birth… https://t.co/P7OYEHiQZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're vacationing in Orlando, you should definitely consider adding on a day at Discovery Cove! This all-inclus… https://t.co/455SNrY3jX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy VRalentine’s day ! We got all Tiltbrush brushes right.  From #vrolga and @AryanBehzadi  @ARize_AR… https://t.co/OuCDoCP8Vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because goat cuddling works up a tremendous appetite. And pizza. #goatcuddling #bluemoonandco… https://t.co/84HgkTVVtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I often have crazy messed up dreams. Anybody else? Tell me about a crazy dream you’ve had that inspired your wri… https://t.co/bY1YZGIFsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought my first and last beer tonight for @garthbrooks, I am for sure more of a tequila girl 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 18th birthday bestie @tpermillionaire toby and i hope 18 is nothing but the best because if anyone deserves i… https://t.co/htz1pRNJJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[who share diagnostic-quality images, virtually, from their offices, with specialists around the globe, for multi-di… https://t.co/SE69PqXA4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reviews are in: “the best example of an interactive toilet experience I've seen yet” https://t.co/xh5DkkbMXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika @JoeNBC OK you two are the wisest most prescient and amazing twosome ever. Now shut up with the self congratulating sermons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I am in shock. Of course I had a crush on him during 90210 this isn't supposed to happen. #RIPLukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultabeauty idk if someone stole a bunch of your stuff and stuffed them in my hair mask or what but this is wastefu… https://t.co/HJQ9zfZfst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo much fun hanging out @Lukes32Bridge @DwntwnNashville here from @california #Californians are here for… https://t.co/5kaJ5nXK0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Advocating the wall is hitleresque and should be explained.   #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #Mar-a-sh*thole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn my mom fried chicken last night &amp; I remember I can't eat it today...Damn start of lent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLHarrison1 We had a beautiful red sunrise - which, of course, means storms to follow. Oh, well, it is February!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HereInMalibu Omg it is alive here in Red Rock conservation area! Snow melted into peaceful streams! Nature at its… https://t.co/vnCLytrXLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready to be home and see my family and friends! Missing them like crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[By taking a break for the entertaining subway heist The Taking of Pelham One Two Three in the fine and erudite comp… https://t.co/NuElfRRYse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Georgiepm Shut up knee tat, why don’t ya leave him alone and go DouBLe fiSt some more beer to post about u uncultivated barbarian]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I was too drunk to collect my money yesterday so can y’all Venmo me for the tacos :’( the total was $63 bis im a… https://t.co/1yw7tCNRuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinamash @TheRickWilson Why don't you just say it? "They are failing their oath of office; they swore to protec… https://t.co/4OA018bEzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwikWarren Aunt Jemima has more dignity--and I'm referring to her old image, not the "modernized" one that's on the pancake box today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @juldelatrinidad there’s no badder bitch than u, not even carlos https://t.co/hRt376RoVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS wow, Michael sure has a lot of paperwork to hand over to the committee! Wonder what it is?? Individual 1 cur… https://t.co/trbkwSxuKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My discernment says nah! Shirt by unpopularapparel #eastnashville #bluelips #chinesebang #muralseast @ Nashville, T… https://t.co/tbKzMZyFVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissieEvert Pedophilia has nothing to do with normal sexuality and allowing priests to marry won’t solve that particular problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitajap @annefleagle Hypocrisy is calling someone obtuse while calling someone else out for being rude!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastislife @peterjhasson he also didn't say that the reason anyone is pro Israel is that Jews paid them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything that God will do for you on earth will have to work through your mind. It is in your physical mind that… https://t.co/ffhHqxFxQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[parking in Germany can be a bargain, but there's no right to (free) parking. Cities that establish successful parki… https://t.co/eGWb6LyYsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oliver is soooooo fuckin needy, he keeps waking me up because he wants me to cuddle him -.-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly No. It has been declining for years into commentary not fact based]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the people saying 50 min... praying for you! #IRatherWaitUntil6pm #Or7pm #NoKidsLife #HISDAdminChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we appreciate ' You look great, though' - just don't. #psa #wedontlooksick #msawareness #multiplesclerosis… https://t.co/tKAy2ZVFCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know people always say, "This is my year," when they have a birthday, but I really feel like this is my year 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the Federal Assembly without referring to the case of Baring Vostok.  European lobby groups release statement A… https://t.co/vcn1ZekNMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache I agree. Not normal. You go Bryce. We are behind your efforts. Blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in Riverside, CA? https://t.co/x6XCdS0B04 #IStandWithPP #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Conley @KIRO7Seattle They wanted to take down the big guy in Calif., so the let these women lanquish in hell for 3 fucking years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPR @Robert_Townsend loved the interview ‘...like an eagle among pigeons... live in ur power”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever want a shake that taste like you are drinking whip cream straight out of the straw go to the @culvers o… https://t.co/ilKzUR6EJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoHauteMamas1 @wccoradio @DawnStebbing @LauraWCCO Just tuck the bags down into your boots so no one sees them and gets weird about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day for Wetumpka HS wrestling. Three State champs and three medal winners. In second place as a team right no… https://t.co/kmx6oeh19g]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a comedy fan, don’t be a BEACH!! REACH @UndergrndComedy this hump day and join the fun. I have a feeling… https://t.co/TNjxpu1E0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kacheling Probably, test for everything but this president only shares bc what he wants and he lies about that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like talking to my friends until they ask to hang out... https://t.co/LpUis9UzjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanfinneyAlan1 Just texted you with my phone number now here is my phone number 6146866915]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alxiaflor_ If you was really about this, you would’ve @ us fr not subtweet https://t.co/5gSyJEXHuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably not a story that should get lost in the abyss...seems we must come together and somehow right these wrongs… https://t.co/RUkSHSTfwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr You had 2 years of MAJORITY rule to get your vanity wall done. An illegal power grab by a wannabe dic… https://t.co/Wpox3FWU2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannorwood16 Currently making my list... I am shook reading everyone’s responses to that thread 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michiana educators are getting students excited about reading by putting books into the hands of thousands of kids… https://t.co/KpJRlAavrz]]></document></documents></author>