<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow They need to make an example out of him or her or it, that kind of BS will not be tolerated and th… https://t.co/6oA26LlwyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd swear she has a sister, equally strong and beautiful, I see regularly @FishsEddyNYC (I'm too intimidated by tho… https://t.co/6UZoOjgKem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BAYLEYSBALOR @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE @TripleH https://t.co/p7RtH6kO5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi. yes it’s me. welcome back to my channel. i hid in the storage closet at work for an hour and cried. life is going good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paris has the Eiffel Tower. New York has the Statue of Liberty. Now, Los Angeles has a statue of David Beckham, com… https://t.co/7KZeR8uPq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all most St. Matty’s Day. @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/cUC0ddxrql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingOfRolexes @VikingsGraphics He had the worst line in the league man and comparing him to Ponder is absolutely ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Twitter is a public forum, conversations we have can be read by anyone, certainly more than just the t… https://t.co/IAKgQn8ojA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HELL4SL00TZ I’ve watched and analyzed the trailer at least 5 times already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melystica Send thanks to (now twitterless?) Michael The Jung too 😂 when’s that collab coming out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We actually pay these idiots you know they are not doing anything there in congress except taking up space and stir… https://t.co/Myv9Fibq5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been rocking my Klein the last couple of practices.  Hands down my favorite guitar. #kleinguitars… https://t.co/HPKDYZ6mZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a purely math perspective, the Dems should run a candidate who can carry rust belt or a superstar who can take… https://t.co/wHOs28eEaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProspectsBraves You remember how Folty started off hot in 2017 and nearly through the no-no Then fizzled out the s… https://t.co/hYfLTKx5Pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birsic Spot on, Brian. And talking through ESG filters seems to be an accessible process. Starting with #impinv ca… https://t.co/P9X05fuhs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grecomeco23 @ChemicalAT @SGVNSports @Tarek_Fattal https://t.co/SKu35YCGzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happybirthday  mom ,,,,  As i try to write something and express what i feel , tears are dropping out of my eyes,… https://t.co/5vjq68cFqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been so busy I haven’t had much time to talk to nadia and it was so exciting hearing all about her day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FANGORIA @HereditaryMovie See @MurrellDan she won best actress to bad not an Oscar #oscarfortoni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL Ben you think OBJ gets moved? Hearing any other names on trade front?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water still above walkway. #tomuchrain @ Smith Smile https://t.co/HmEMPcTL8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking the picture of the Episcopal Church of our savior, it dawned on me that Rock Hill has something in common wi… https://t.co/XcZSY9P3pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦍As you thinketh you becometh...You are responsible for your state of mind. . Emotions come into play daily. Some d… https://t.co/HmWRQ4Z3nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall i swear you don’t have to go to a big school to have an opportunity💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPaulDelgado @NinaPietrasanta @AspireInskeep @AspireLAschools considering science curriculum for next school year https://t.co/ThFW4Ho3lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I saw Michael "Red Hulk" Malone starting to emerge after that last 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buzzbrainard @SXMTheHighway I’m still requesting to get @LaurenDuski on #OnTheHorizon. Buzz artists like Lauren ar… https://t.co/sfEn684ryd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 congrats on the deal Bryce.  You now have 330 million reasons to be nice to your fans and sign some autographs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could the position of giant spheres of hydrogen and helium undergoing nuclear fusion 500 light years away... influe… https://t.co/VtoeTJrwsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright a @pantelis_xidias. Sighting!! That was fun, am I right?? Uncle No is on our side. Bring on Creighton!!! #dpubb #PlayingPossessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushJohnNabors Makes me more excited for 2020 bec we don’t have to force the position on KJ if he’s not ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EduQuinn @sambcoltrane @mj_lee I was a decent high school student and didn’t receive a scholarship. I didn’t work… https://t.co/BY7jodY0ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@levynews As I hope Kerr is telling the Dubs now: The Warriors just beat the Warriors - the Suns just happened to be the beneficiaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayHairston @LEGDAYGaming @DallasFuel @EsportsStadium @FrostbiteCospl1 @overwatchleague @PlayOverwatch… https://t.co/rKMqzhz2b2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video update: After Maya's birthday, we're still collecting! Please DM me if you want to help for info where to sen… https://t.co/aqRBPwwL29]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sliceofheaven #ishouldnothaveopenedthebag #maggiehasacold @ McAlister's Deli https://t.co/byY4Tbutbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Than You Can Imagine https://t.co/asRWNFQngS via @YouTube #writerscommunity #writers #quotestoliveby… https://t.co/8q9eUB4yyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[could you IMAGINE having as much money as he does and not giving a fuck 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many people will make a video like this? 🤔 I was speaking how much I felt about @PostMalone and his music helps… https://t.co/Gg5gxG6YB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarTrek @ansonmount @thejaynebrook @startrekcbs @StarTrekRoom @StarTrekNetflix @SpaceChannel What IS that smell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This family sure has folks triggered. Maybe folks should actually learn a thing or two from them instead of hating… https://t.co/xVsZr6lKIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems For some of the people opposing the HQ2 project in New York, Democrats and this young girl Ortizia-Cort… https://t.co/viTDqMSEoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcgayle I haven’t been involved with the company for over 2 years, but I’d reach out to Qualaroo customer suppor… https://t.co/24EUzvMq59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speechboy71 And she is EXCELLENT in a town hall setting; she listens well, really engages with questions, and trul… https://t.co/Kud38t6GPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffLieber 100% true.  You’re a one-man film school.  (Of course, if you wrote comedy I’d be a lot more negative.… https://t.co/qUc3Ia0Gqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @tedlieu @IvankaTrump @IvankaTrump Good thing you never mentioned fashion photographer, pedophile and frien… https://t.co/8WehF0gr7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start sending subpoenas now. Don't just request, DEMAND. I AM TIRED OF PLAYING NICE WITH THESE ASSHOLES.  Former Tr… https://t.co/UQN5b3jzuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red School is cool Procrastinated on my essay I'm such a fool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mika the wall was deemed needed under Obama. What changed now? The grade of steel being used😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13Tmueller Ya just a warning on liquid plumber and the like they don't tell you but I saw where it melted a pvc pi… https://t.co/h6bYKLvtVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamShatner Big fan! Ever been to Kingston area, say @LOYTWP or Amherst Island? @CJAI921FM Sunday Night Live… https://t.co/1kMmm3iztj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/shKI1tBI6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE KING’S ARMY UPDATE:  Scott after 1 week of dieting and he is already showing me vascularity and noticeable hard… https://t.co/DAwdy0kowP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra I keep going back and forth between infuriated that she's an elected official and "wow she's so stupid it's hilarious"]]></document><document><![CDATA[My God I can’t wait for Capela to come back. Anyone over 6’8” just dominates us in the paint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada Thanks for putting a smile on my face today. Love it!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Michael tried to be a "bad boy" (eg "crotch crabbing," edgy :Beat It/Thriller" videos despite the lithe ap… https://t.co/Tu1GmkQ4F7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trolmalpagado Están pero bien tontos si quitan la Fórmula 1 se ven esas carreras en todo el mundo para que conozca… https://t.co/FMPcmmO1lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad it’s raining today. After those two days of sun, I was afraid we might go into a drought. #SoTiredOfTheRain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, is @ChuckECheeses even going to respond to being called out on their bullshit by Shane?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @garway95 @sickofbiggov @RockSlithers @gmanlook @ROHLL5 @bull_pamela @DirkPitt1352 @Bob72270 @MG62967… https://t.co/qisRdyNIOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingDarius85kg I love you thank you. To be more specific the site itself was the issue. Not finances. I was trying… https://t.co/9ydEr1pAU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not the puppets we should be watching, It's the puppet masters who works behind the curtains and allow people… https://t.co/8ed5Roejnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What hurts the most is that after everything that happened you just  stop caring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HARD WORK ALWAYS WINS! .. One thing that time and time again predicts success is fucking hard work. .. The simplest… https://t.co/BvO7gDYHv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoChilds Veronica Vega's version is called "pay me." It's a bop! https://t.co/M2tvSuif4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[TERMINUS MÉTHANIER DE 9G$ AU SAGUENAY. Un projet "sale" selon le titre du Devoir! 8M de tonnes de GES! L'usine de l… https://t.co/CH0zmkEpvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Fight EXTREMISM of #Capitalism AND #Socialism.  Stop the greedy 1% from demonizing a healthy mixture of t… https://t.co/YoxHSGVtD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pooraggies @1stColonel Another aggy theory shot down, over 90,000 in attendance https://t.co/p0K1pSIhYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hadrians_Gate My guess is that’s a rare occurrence. Why did only one blow apart?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlMacLeod66 @CupersLee Still not even remotely interested unless the return is a younger Phil and then some]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffAllen71 @dfitt08 @BruhReport @NCAA True. Title 9 plays a huge part as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a panda as a pet. I know it’s a terrible idea, but I’ll still pretend  it could happen one day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amazon suma a exCEO de @Pepsico, @IndraNooyi , a su directorio, y se desempenia como directora de la Junta Directi… https://t.co/CFV0Wm6jhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!!! Everybody in South Florida should stop https://t.co/b50tHLE5bW and try the #crabcake #bltsandwich , this is… https://t.co/zHLDMDJ4GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALWAYS PERFECT PATE’ #wholeheaplife #diginyall #nola #delicious #travelfoodie @ Bywater American Bistro https://t.co/lQx0Re5OPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me behind the bar this weekend at averylounge!   #averylounge #downtownsanjose #sofadistrict #southbay… https://t.co/NKsJDY72BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKaralous @SenWarren @EricLesser You're using the term Pocahontas as a pejorative that makes it a racial slur.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only CNN can know how heavily they should lean into that report but it should be discussed with the context Barr’s… https://t.co/lqKajn7uBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend: Daniel when we get here don’t be extra and loud  Me: https://t.co/zS6pDviXIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nadabakos Russians? Go to any left wing health food store and you get bombarded by anti vaccination stuff. This ha… https://t.co/bkCZUXI2QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmidi @RandallAGordon @solrivalsgame Yup we are under my LLC TallGames Studios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlairKamin @chicagotribune Did they add some bathrooms to the Great Hall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrutliff7462 @Hunter9David @kcamp3 Shoot a 125 deer in 40 of 45 yrs and I think that be more impressive than 3 170… https://t.co/PP8vUF2E8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH I LOVE YOU IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE. UNDER TRUTH GOD AND TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST. SO OXYMORO… https://t.co/9DJUD6MhhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @MikeWitko51 How SELFISH of Hillary!  SHE wears lipstick.  Why can't OTHER pigs?  @DonaldJTrumpJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Manhattan looks best from #Brooklyn @ Williamsburg, Brooklyn https://t.co/lSpjhCcgt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching 1993 Royal Rumble On Demand.  Miss commentary of Gorilla Monsoon &amp; Bobby Heenan]]></document><document><![CDATA[members on BOTH sides of the aisle found many of your answers to be unsatisfactory, incomplete or contradicted by other evidence,"]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Disbelief” 02/24/19 Trb 420 days! @ Flint, Michigan https://t.co/xQlSsMTOQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidOAtkins That’s not even close to being true. I’ve never worked for a member at any level that didn’t do this.… https://t.co/dRPr5Vxill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAtHome For me, more like, "Guten Biden!", a fun little farewell statement... 👋🇱🇷➕🇩🇪 ('Been saying it every… https://t.co/JXkwsiyPQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SleepyDeeee Trueeee! It will never go away as long as stupidity and free will exist so will racism unfortunately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBush727 I live in Nashville but went to Smyrna because it’s less of a wait at the county clerks office. Go to Wal… https://t.co/3CmK6Brqef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eighth #Sunday in Ordinary Time — “It is good to give thanks to the LORD, to sing praise to your name, Most High, T… https://t.co/3tHWypThnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBInani @mmtanner55 @FlyoverCulture @AOC @EcoSenseNow I don't think he's all that conservative. Just a realist whe… https://t.co/bt1B6Rtfkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg Saw you on @Morning_Joe . Really liked the interview and hoping you go far- republican from NC who i… https://t.co/kvOdpGu3Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2018, the U.S. economy grew at the highest rate in 13 years. Democrats want to stop our soaring economy costing… https://t.co/Gk1qsrR9NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brinkong @javicverdolaga @juandig14 @JJTrellezV @FOXSportsCo Un equipo de suplentes jajaja pero su tromba salió ma… https://t.co/NcIPxU116l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KNICE @coachmicah @Applebees Man y’all making me wish I would’ve cut up now lmao]]></document></documents></author>