<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[oh so this how we rockin now? Bring that same enery when yall get jumped next time]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Maid of Honor at my wedding to Bride!  Love you, dorseyhadden!  💕 @ The Nest at Ruth Farms https://t.co/Flhdexm5Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch a replay of this morning’s @IBMResearch 5 in 5 Science Slam. Already up to 1.4 million views! #IBM5in5… https://t.co/4ydWvJNNlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Delicias del Mar in Santiago, Nuevo León https://t.co/Yi0XuMW9Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LGE_Basketball wins the first round of the @OfficialGHSA State Basketball Playoffs! @ELHS_HCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Owls score the first 5 of OT then USF answers 3 plus to go Owls by 3. Shizz heads to the line to look to extend to 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasThunderman @alexrstockwell Hahaha of course you do- you’re the biggest @BachelorABC fan I know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had one of the scariest experiences of my adult life.   When I take Emmett out on his walk before bed, we al… https://t.co/ejM04ZsYmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[somedays i wish i went to school closer to home so i didnt feel like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I came to eat sushi for lunch and the guy was walking towards me to take my order and this old hag kept yelling… https://t.co/z4IqGbXxDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregnant from rape - Extended interview with Jennifer https://t.co/q0uSSmlL3K via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a quick stop to Newark Nutrition before class 🤗 https://t.co/G43VEyBMh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes #inners This administration pushes the divisive boundaries daily. So much gets underreported or ignore… https://t.co/80uiZjSKgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKAY, snapped myself out of my morning slump and ate lunch/did my makeup (actually came out on point) now I’m ready to be productive 💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perusing in pajamas. 💛Harry Potter #reader4life @JParkerBES @LaurenBaileyBES @MsCruisesCrew @FCSBES @FCSchoolsNC https://t.co/3WxBeEScfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meal prepping as an adult is Starbucks at 7 am &amp; Dunkin donuts at 12 pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary Oh Lindsey! You were biased towards him at that point in time too; he was and is an… https://t.co/6Ouuvggx0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts! BIG FACTS! I let shorty disrespect my mom once, you do it again I’m cracking your 6’10 foot ass even if i go… https://t.co/g9x15O1yIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiancaaaSays My girl lives 10 mins away from Disney. Somewhere there lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissagrelo @YourMorning @KelseyMcEwen Chris Helmsworth/HulkHogan =less clothing on as well! ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5000RoleDuval @DCPSTurnaround Look at my student 6th grade student, helping tie the 5000 Ties for his fellow Role Models. ❤💚❤💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MundoC13 #PactodeSangre por que se tardan tanto en subir los capitulos a youtube me tienen sufriendo 😭😭 como puedo… https://t.co/o58xvMWCIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letambitionwin the person who made this picture... the flavor is there https://t.co/SSmyQDq8SI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S1Your @HauptmannHansa @LadyLovesTaft @ajduggins @notabattlechick @waitmanb @HellOnPaws @Doctrine_Man… https://t.co/i7Mwld2rRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annika_Kraft I got a stable job so HONEY I’M COMING TO CHATTY (eventually... I need a paycheck or two)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi guys, want to share you my Youtube Channel Really hope you can check it out. I have lots of videos that you may… https://t.co/gKZdlsMmVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wrote a review on https://t.co/GDqcxPtCHe https://t.co/4ZcQEi45Vj via @yotpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @realDonaldTrump Not true. His highest priority is making money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronmurray11 Curious. . . Why do  you have a neon green circular sticker on the back of your helmet and no one else does? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's NoChill Earpers!! #WynonnaEarp #FightForWynonna @IDWPublishing @IDWEntertain  💜💙💛💚❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all of these mathematicians!  @AngelaAbend @Oceanside_NY_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtinexcess OMG This photo is amazing literally sums up my adolescence]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be wanting to dress provocatively then my insecurities be like nah 😂😭😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muslim aggression if unchecked will find its way eventually into your neighborhood. England used to be English. Thi… https://t.co/HHA5fnhTCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews And Obama didn’t have every single network in his BACK pocket and that is not… https://t.co/B829EprjoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the top excited for my favorite TSM!!! Congratulations @Brandon_HDI proud to call you my leader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ej315 @hendee_ellen @CharlesEsten @conniebritton @mleitten @Allyallpgh @BrittLynn2531 @brooksiew83 @megweiss13… https://t.co/KRzCoXlj5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbbcoachmartens @StMUmbb @StMarysRattlers @StMUwbb Because the girls bus always smells better than the boys. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are the missing Page Strzok text messages they just don’t disappear and where is the DNC server and the Weiner laptop]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quieter you become, the more you can hear. - ram dass #teampixel  . . . . #myunicornlife #discoverla… https://t.co/FViDjHoTzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginatognoni @JoshuaMorrowYR You are definite fave of mine, now and going back to oltl !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[like some dude just said he doesn’t have any respect for me because I said that women should be equal to men and sh… https://t.co/8MD8FIfYSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bijancbayne Of course so important https://t.co/3sIhsillLE #History #OTD #OTDIH #twitterstorians]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out how you can partner with Charlotte Works to empower our future and existing workforce!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @LincolnsBible Let’s say it out loud. When all is said and done we will find out that Trump is one o… https://t.co/l3LpuLwosU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilPirochta Thats why i deleted my facebook. I cant handle the idiots there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After hunting far and wide for a garbage can in multiple airports I now understand why ppl stick their gum random places]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really try to stay super hydrated during the day, but I guess it does depend on the person as to how much water y… https://t.co/a40m0ngbcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Babies in cages. Record deficits. Tax cuts for the 1%. Lies. Treason. Repeated attempts to deny Americans medi… https://t.co/D86sC77GFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk i think she self made yes she had other advantages but she made her business into what it is like Rob had the s… https://t.co/qfSFcenja5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFantasticIan Yeah we know. I wish we would put our marketing behind Bao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @GhostAdventures like you got me in chills😱🖤💫 https://t.co/2jyLakmVL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part of being an adult. You can sit on the counter without getting yelled at!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethanyAlvarez3 Aw, ok. Thank you!! We’re flying in tomorrow and coming back on Monday. So I’m only taking a carry… https://t.co/GtCKtDti8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 8393 Pinto Drive #LakeWorth #FL  #realestate https://t.co/uhW1UvuV4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpPastryPlate So, if he doesn't spill the beans on the really awful stuff, he might get to live? Or is he hoping t… https://t.co/HrNqL8UDIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPLagerfeld a true fashion genius and icon. This is a huge loss to the fashion world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deddieromeropr Deddie muy mal de ti el que te molestes con España por exigir respeto,hay que ponerse en el lugar d… https://t.co/2ttvcG5zPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #PinkShirtDay !  Wear a rosy shade to cheer up a full February day AND show your commitment to a peaceful and… https://t.co/zgT28a39fL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trying to be extra at @Starbucks but: iced, grande, skinny vanilla latte (non fat milk), light on the ice ❤️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lradzins Do it! And I have no idea. I barely have room for a decent grinder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remi🐶💙☃️ #weekendvibes #snowmuchfun #snowdog #littledogphotobomb #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy… https://t.co/87a4DVeMTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mondaymotivation 💕💕 from @goldengoddessNC  . . . #mondays #mondaymood #monday #mondaymood #quotes #quotestoliveby… https://t.co/ggRbgfRdfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakaktaSouth @notcapnamerica She has such an awesome laugh, too! I want to be listening to her give a SOTU!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyhendo15 @shallam14 @Luda_Lundquist Well that explains why i don’t know what it is.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoDavidson7 @AnnCoulter I just took her comment as facetious.  The Dems are always criticizing why Ivanka is a Tru… https://t.co/YAvrZYq6OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissGigglesss_ The custom matchmaking games were a blast! Thanks for hosting these and I look forward to more of t… https://t.co/tYpo4IpNDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen Feinstein Dismisses children pushing for #GreenNewDeal: "You didn't ... https://t.co/UVXdZp6hBX via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH, IT IS ON TONIGHT!! Tonight’s special guest at the #probluesjam at @thecountrynash is beloved Nashville organ ma… https://t.co/E4PN1YgPpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bestowed my entirety to this person but lust steered him away from realizing my devotion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMiller3039 was as good a coach as he is an NHL goalie. He coached @MSU_Hockey camp in the late 90’s/early 2000… https://t.co/xIrO8vfTWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Lowes Home Improvement in Lexington, SC https://t.co/GRzhzFD56R]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little overcast, but can’t complain about the view! 👌🏻 @ Four Seasons Resort Scottsdale at Troon North https://t.co/T4r2qnMgY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m giving up Halal food/Pita Chip for Lent so rip to 95% of my meals I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews How disrespectful! He’s been threatened with the I word s… https://t.co/z6XC6szAe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  66% of Americans DISAPPROVE/OPPOSE National Emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_nsg92 @CandiceHere_ IM SCREAMING. Adding it to my stock of amazing gifs (featuring Candice)]]></document><document><![CDATA[kordell left for work this morning and T and i have been snuggling since 🥰💜 https://t.co/SWWIZZ9ABj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1120Eclipse Thank you, she has been also fighting breast cancer for a couple years now. She is doing well but she’s also in her 80s!☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo Oh gosh 🤭 John,I was going to ask!  What was that absolutely adorable critter?  I would have try to catch it… https://t.co/8WRD5Oa7oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s not allow  #JussieSmollett take away from #BlackHistoryMonth #MuhammadAli]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what point does ghosting become acceptable? This guy keeps asking me to hang out and I was super nice but super… https://t.co/4oFwKOAV3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re squeezing every satoshi into our #latam expansions @AthenaBitcoinAR @Bitcolution but we WILL, again, be suppo… https://t.co/7WDJPZf3wT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Let me get this straight: 1. Pulling out of Syria. 2. Pulling out of Afghanistan. 3. Graham is wit… https://t.co/0Q6HlguRbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time of year is so strange and full of nostalgia... it's begging me to pick up my tarot cards again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who does stand-up comedy in the shower for 49 minutes at a time??? Just me, okay..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadaMoments My take on JWR is that she is unsuited for Federal politics. I admire her tenacity and intelligence,… https://t.co/FqUtfxItBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The gluten flowing through my body just feels so good right now” - @TheRealTPizz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home based lead exposure over many years can lead to negative health outcomes including heart disease and premature… https://t.co/3a9fawqLMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cannot believe that i just bought tickets to see the loves of my life. IM SO EXCITED AAHHHHHHH @5SOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @dog_feelings W a Valentine’s bow from the vet https://t.co/HC1UW6xQ4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoopiGoldberg Hoping all is well, sister gir ... take care of yourself out there. Don't be a John W type... he sa… https://t.co/BwYrQKtBug]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skin then just say fuck it. There is nothing wrong with cosplaying super heroes of impair colors. Just don’t change… https://t.co/AjwUUrErWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever see a meme and find it hilarious, but then you see it again...and again...and again...and you wind up hating it? 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlehummertwo @ABC This murder with a badge is still alive and the same can’t be said about the young man he bru… https://t.co/RhaOko6Hvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddlovato I love you with all my heart forever, thanks for being who you are, i’ll never leave you☺️💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherylunderwood Thanks for the vodka tonic laughs today, Sheryl. I lost my mom a few years ago and didn’t I’d ever… https://t.co/SQ6sMpyltN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewPelkey I was thinking of changing it to Lake Effect Consulting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big good luck to some of my favorite fishes!! Go do your thing in the Ville tomorrow and Saturday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Another thing,  have trump release his taxes,  come completely clean about stormy and other women he has silen… https://t.co/I9qtp5kb6H]]></document></documents></author>