<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[DJ Mike @mikemor14291639 @Rockets120 AttenDANCE Bash #AttendanceMatters @McAllenISD https://t.co/3Kae5CG40J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ADubInBaseball ... paving the path for the next generation.. and making a difference in our community.  G… https://t.co/ttt8RLY8Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you are ok with Robert Kraft patronizing spa full of victims of human trafficking and arrogantly thinking it’s o… https://t.co/HXBeUM42CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so happy there is a #HyVee across the street from @maitrainer 💙 I told their Dietician that my clients ask me t… https://t.co/saK9aH5yWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's the real bigot  "The real antisemitism is on the right"  "The Islamists are the real racists and sexists"… https://t.co/nVaJPD7LOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glaad I had to show you the APPALLING place I just passed!! I am in SHOCK!! Part of me wants to bust every window… https://t.co/DOJ8XuTaxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched this 100000 times and still don’t understand https://t.co/EH7JqiqnQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Contrasts at Dries Van Noten Fading summer flowers struck the designer as the germ of a collection. How… https://t.co/18gzsp0yPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3ATxHsBaseball  Lone Oak 10 John Tyler 5 HC Josh Cuellar’s first coaching win]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #FoodieFriday here on #GoodDayMaine   I’ve never had oysters but plan on trying them for the first time later… https://t.co/ZEGZlFw2Tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riche604 @lizzie20114 He’s not on Steve’s level.  But if Steve refused to leave Sheree and I was left to only have… https://t.co/Q4zTgnhJ5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when the women of Texas Southern succeed. Like there is literally nothing that we can’t do 🤷🏾‍♀️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying goodbye to dizzie715 was tough today. This woman is good for my soul. In all the years we’ve been friends, w… https://t.co/8EhbGHnsRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FulbrightTeach @ECAatState The Fulbright TGC experience will change your life and your classroom! Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceartas @HRC @ButtockPennock @UMChurch Heated and emotional subject these days, but it seems we’re getting closer… https://t.co/rxtYrD4CvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked at tinder again for the first time in months, and was instantly reminded why I told myself to stop that to… https://t.co/G1opnaQ4rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[• mardi gras with @RepublicNOLA• 💚💜💛  @Herobust  @Ghastly  @Midnightasaurus  @downlinkmusic  @Klutch_Music… https://t.co/L2ARRxOFh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCDFW Any particular reason I've been watching non-stop NBCDFW commercials on your stream for the last 27 minutes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNYtv Jake is incapable of taking it easy on someone I love it. Also he’s so adorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToughGuyMankas @Tonithecat32 @vroberts9 @BloomNight2 @lynda3035 @fluffybasil @deborah26449389 @sharon_cantley… https://t.co/QHn9Qtjnur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakepenta @spenceriswhite @Dfrench_ @madluttrell Or everyone in the pics for this article, I’m too down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those on the Left shouldn't watch this, b/c you're either: 1. Involved, or 2. You won't believe or understand. Thes… https://t.co/mnUkKUoytS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just saw a guy’s bio on tinder that said “not looking for anything serious, just eternal love and commitment” oh… https://t.co/AZ6oMJgAdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing even for a few minutes a day makes a big difference. #thisischeltenham #mindfulness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHSCounselors40 @sandyhook @MHSComets @MasonSchools Thank you! I’ve always believed in the power of a well worded, hand written letter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 wasn’t the best year for me. 2019, you’ve been a blessing. Coming home to my room with flowers and balloons is just great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day to showcase @boisestatelive @BoiseStateCOEN PhD programs! See you at dinner :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The avett brothers got me sitting in my parked car singing my lungs out]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the umbrella academy. I’m not familiar with the premise but giving it a try. And I just don’t get why there is a talking monkey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maroon 5 - ROAD TO SUPER BOWL - PT.2 https://t.co/yEoqGYbLFa via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews They trusted this guy???? Nothing about his candidacy screamed trust but okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @JONWBRID Trump believes and defends -Putin didn't interfere with our election or use nerve agents… https://t.co/LGQFRAnSTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaroleTBeers Thank you! Getting back into writing post-op was much harder than I thought it would be. Sending you strength and words!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Environmental scorecards out for 2018. In WI @SenatorBaldwin making us proud with 💯rating! No surprises with a depl… https://t.co/Cyiq8TmILk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No leadership problem is too big or too small for God. Ask for help.” - Judi Cotignola #pfwomen #leadership… https://t.co/kuhEygrsnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my Sista Girls 20th Birthday at midnight and I can’t wait to embarrass her 😭💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t never have to make it out of this MS mud, don’t open your mouth to speak bad on my home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if between now and August I’ll create anything meaningful or worthwhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_reyes @ACEatND @padreFJ I believe that @timothytwill does some impressive post-production work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready to “Think Big About Your Future in Communications” with @flahertyrob ? In just 15 short minutes, he w… https://t.co/3pqoKlTQlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg these “permission” moments NEED to stop. Come on Bachelor.  #TheBachelor https://t.co/lLGjcB4Gst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARSHALL_KING @JuanCarlosCNN @CNNEE Los “expertos” de Hollywood a veces premian por estar bien con los afroamerica… https://t.co/rZqwV3wPg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaturner @CNNSotu @jaketapper This is going to be fun. If you criticize Bernie or question him, attack attack. T… https://t.co/s1qMdE2HMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I work so much that I just need to make sure I get at least one hour of irresponsibility in a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dog doesn’t like me and it makes me sad the other day i tried to take her off of a virtual stranger’s lap and she growled at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny part is your son/my ex is being more civil and understanding than you. A almost 50 year old grown up child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were there tonight and saw what you saw....that’s me defending my family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me trying to thrive and be happy:   My anxiety: https://t.co/XGDf24ZHdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan We do know he was not doing it as a joke.  Clearly, he is not the type.  More the weasel type.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone in the Huntington area needing/wanting a roommate let me know! I have a friend looking for a roommate asap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... a cool little birdie with  🔥 purple hair 💜 @angie_easley told me that these awesome CenterStage rockstars 👇🏻… https://t.co/DcSlacwkFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland UPDATE: Roads around Calumet Refinery reopened to traffic in Great Falls https://t.co/cdsWt548f2 via @GFTribune]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingSeun3 @rainlogos happy for you 😇❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ hard work is always noted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_JKern Makes you just wanna say...augggggggh! https://t.co/Ybe0LgteKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's my challenge to nurses today. What radical collaboration can you create to transform health? Do share...… https://t.co/eW8J2tpl1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottBaran31 If it’s any consolation… I’ve lost a few for no apparent reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Training in 4 Days Baseball Enthusiasts ..   ♥️💯⚾️♥️💯⚾️♥️💯⚾️♥️💯⚾️ https://t.co/0XFxzvyunx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rai reading my DM to @ClarusPlusPlus : Who is she?  Me: my best internet buddy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatsKitties I wouldn't touch it with a 39- 1/2 foot pole, but a bit of buttermilk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encanta este día, me encantan las parejas que en serio se quieren y se presumen 😭❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched the new apartment building across from the bar burn down today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CRsoprano @AlanTheisen @mezzoihnen @CRsoprano, these are killin! Bravo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been experimenting with my nautural hair by puttin in no product.  I love the feel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! So many aviators coming together to support #lgbtqYOUTH 🏳️‍🌈 Hey, Ts - do you know any 12-16 year olds interes… https://t.co/nFLDcFvVHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STMPioneersPBIS @LCPS_PBIS @SterlingMiddle1 Aww...Ms. Bartow! Please tell her I said hello!❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to donate money to a broke college student so she can get the new @TheSims expansion pack/ Sims 2 u… https://t.co/mB1vYxyvpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angela681417 @Viviane6677 @Jose93571656 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen… https://t.co/mBoZB7cz0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart hurts so so much for the person I was at that time. and I get so emotional on the other side when I recogn… https://t.co/4KzXvK9KPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the dudes sitting next to me they were like "fuck I'm going to cry before this even starts" at the stan trib… https://t.co/cnNbNsbCh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@72cricket @sannbs @ChicagoPenguin2 @MrsSpuds @BxglL @sharon_schwan @CSonafelt @RidenerTina @ACog1984 Keep it coming 💛💛🐧🐧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenEKrall @G_Schleeter @DrKels50 @ike9_Eagles @AldineISD @MsDYChaney Thank you 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the type to get some shit like banana pudding cereal then wish I bought something regular like fruity pebbles. Every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stormdk24 @kingfish7418 @SethAbramson @realDonaldTrump  I’m Republican. I DID NOT vote for you. You shame America.… https://t.co/JHsm5HeObp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist The republicans have set such a low bar for decency, you would have to be a mass murder to drop below the average.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRAFFIC TRACKER  Yikes! Major slow downs on the Beltline from the winter weather. You’re going to have trouble in b… https://t.co/5rpzivvLkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAKING US HOT INTO THE THROWN ROOM OF GOD - https://t.co/7QatvnyB6W https://t.co/api4qq3KUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter This I Believe, &amp; I will not give up my gun no matter what laws are passed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling out, maxin, relaxing all cool watching some #Letterkenny with my all dressed chips and actual puppers sinc… https://t.co/yCsLK71HAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeingLGBTQPod We think #LGBTQ artist should definitely get support from the bigger prides!! We’ve had the pleasure… https://t.co/BYWgHV1UeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a lot I didn't learn in school that I needed to know, I'm sure I'm not alone. The more you know about the h… https://t.co/H72o66z0FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau, my how you've changed - https://t.co/9Yk0NxPIVr https://t.co/FLCXOcCQ6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Patrick Dempsey sing at five points cafe in Sayville NY https://t.co/ZJ9zC4ouvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Sorors are better than yours...My Big Sister Terrie put a smile on my face with this beautiful surprise yesterda… https://t.co/uq1CQeTidJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinopillow wow what a sweet and thoughtful birthday gift. also... happy birthday &lt;333]]></document><document><![CDATA[yikes people are asking questions apparently they do understand whats going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump No, he's doing worse! Threatening a witness, selling off United States secrets, and in… https://t.co/jLVJkpCEML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maggarooo @BarefootKb @HounddogZenith Maggie, I didn’t mean at all thIs pup was to replace your hubby, Hound dog Z… https://t.co/igjVaHwKdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monmouth/Ocean County Administrators Meeting. Discussing latest news related to standards, assessments, CTE and oth… https://t.co/G43WliwcDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karina_hines First thought that came to mind when I saw his ranking, like WHO does that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt Namjoon, I think this is a nice addition your #Rkive https://t.co/iQFn75kw63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisakers @MDCudaback Is Ki Yang the roving ambassador to the @GOP ? She’s positively ubiquitous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neokogirl2 @ThreeDailey My daughter (who speaks 5 languages) swears duolingo is the best... She will graduate bein… https://t.co/K9QA7vEDi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to spend the day at @TysonFoods talking #boardgovernance with one of my board members and @BoardSource. https://t.co/lUA357ErIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my nephew Ethan! Hope his parents @TrungMCao1 are getting him the puppy he wanted #nephew… https://t.co/kibBAcoQLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bayern are like a superhero movie where the villains always win and everyone dies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!! In this stressful end to the quarter, it's important to remember to take the time and do something f… https://t.co/8bKM3IYCO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix I was watching Hawaii Five -O for the last couple weeks. I was through 6 of 8 seasons. I watched it until… https://t.co/FtsSnNB64m]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Red Carpet for the launch event of movikarma !! 🙌🙏 With great friends and talented people.  AMAZING PLATFORM… https://t.co/gTcVBkmIx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realize you have no battery left mid conference call while near an Apple Store...cut to me laying my head… https://t.co/AFTtzbrIjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This r Kelly shit has me at my desk crying real tears y'all are dumbbbbbb]]></document></documents></author>