<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lose and Loose are not the same words I’m just saying  That’s all I had in the original tweet but hold on let me re… https://t.co/MHixOOZp5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama, Hillary Clinton and Obama administration have Benghazi. #Benghazi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram… https://t.co/li8NJVrp0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escandalamx @belindapop @yahirmusic @montanertwiter @LaVozTvAzteca Viejaaa ridiculaaa..... Me cagaaaa la gedionda esaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @andersoncooper America knows the truth. Democrats suck!! Everything is a 100 percent better now than 2 years… https://t.co/fL93DsmvVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachMoss6  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd hey chuck - next time you schedule jim jordan you may as well put up white noise during that time. you’r… https://t.co/capk3RbZXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my Wife @haleyrosekiller 📸: @michellexstar venue: #thestanleyhotel @ Stanley Hotel https://t.co/DKzeiNf9Gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[They missed @PointFarmsPP! We discovered this little gem after missing the booking window for the Pinery 6 years ag… https://t.co/ma5EIZOqzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 I work at a high school with plenty of great stories, count me in please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next witness is John Harris, Mark Harris' son, He has been a assistant US attorney since October 2018]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avalanche Why is Nemeth playing over Graves? So stupid. Thought we were going with the youth movement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all a Chinese hoax, Said a Turd that likes to boast He’ll go to jail with hopefully no bail, But the mammal’s… https://t.co/p068Zhvyt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IshtarCommander I’m fine with these figures. Worth every minute. https://t.co/dUwGrns9eG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading that Kenny Lofton thinks he’s a victim of PEDs and should be in the #HOF. No fucking way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveAction Planned Parenthoods new President says abortion is their core mission and they aren't backing off. https://t.co/awgmMjVxxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briseidac881 Maybe to show &amp; explain to her daughter that she’s need to make the best decision.. Real happy, not fake happy. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t help but think about my accident when I saw this picture. 😊 https://t.co/ucvA7alXjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prison4Trump @jack @Twitter @realDonaldTrump @JoshMankiewicz @TwitterSupport Fine line between following and stalk… https://t.co/Tkxv8tJKC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @nctbrewery (@get_repost) ・・・ Enjoy a mixed-6 or stock up on your favourite with a $20 6-pack sale on IPA,… https://t.co/qSWLUgyQKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samsung just canceled my order for my phone because I was getting shipped to my current address, not my billing add… https://t.co/t2Lqq2mSLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thehomiesrepresenting  Notas do velho na sala: A imagem captura os sorrisos depois do trabalho, depois do suor, de… https://t.co/VrwjT9xlMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Benny! Good luck this weekend! Can’t wait to see you and all the fellas this summer! 🤠🍻🏄🏻 https://t.co/WhlZjOG4Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one bites the dust! Just rented in the #SouthLoop in under 2 weeks. Thank you to our client for trusting in… https://t.co/THiU5IbPv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched a lot of the replays of the dunks. I thought it was pretty good and entertaining. I can see why people do… https://t.co/7T4FRduN0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscars are always dumb, but god damn this is pitiful. Everyone sounds and looks like they want to be anywhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickClairmont1 In what way? These people may not be able to travel, but they are still home with families and capa… https://t.co/rO07BGs5ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marty_rodz Muchas gracias e igualmente para ti saludos a distancia ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods In EVERY INSTANCE the #MAGA hat wearer is THE VICTIM!! Wtf is wrong with people’s intellect!? That… https://t.co/o4uOLVhK5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner (@ Cafe Zupas in Phoenix, AZ) https://t.co/8R8lM8LDtV https://t.co/DwFQOsGVPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a BraufactuM Progusta by Radeberger Gruppe at @radegasthallbk — https://t.co/Qt1giQqTXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning on @NBC10 #sunrise, we’re continuing to follow this developing story that is now considered a murder i… https://t.co/mbgGvfjxSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to signee @andrexallen on winning another regional title at Arizona Western! Winners win! @UBmenshoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/WQytO7TxRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must admit that hearing Alex Trebek’s statement today brought me back to thinking of this one from April of 2005.… https://t.co/w20NqvPD0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceMonkey111 @Miss_Sadie_V @polls_about Yes she is her name is Feisty Rose and her pretty face belongs on a pack… https://t.co/3hfTgQmzFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe you are a FRAUD! It looks like You conspired with Russia on Uranium One, on the Fake dossier, with the FB… https://t.co/Y3pUENqlhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyrone_Calloway Congrats!!! Great player, great team &amp; great school]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose we were due to lose but against Arsenal is a tough one. Gotta move on and keep focus laser sharp!   #ARSMUN @ManUtd 🔴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoveling around the doorways at work reminds me of how powerful snowflakes are when numerous, so a task I abhor is an analogy I adore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My soul thirsts for God, for the living God. When can I go and meet with God? Psalm 42:2 NIV https://t.co/xGHKcxMw09 https://t.co/obdwM0WfAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just picked up a little magazine called @Cosmopolitan only to find @emilyjoypoetry’s moving story. Proud of you! https://t.co/t8jPI3dEbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering how @lansingschools would be impacted by the new state budget? Hear it from the top!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter-Spring Cara Half-Marathon Training Program initial long run #cardiorehab #runCARA #caratrained… https://t.co/cLOl7BBkhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5redpandas That is genuinely dystopian. And you know not for nothing but shit like *this* is what we need function… https://t.co/AhH6jRmDop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsntDaveOne @BravoTV I am so dead 😂 💀 Are they still relevant?... https://t.co/eHp5qeMrLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @BojanglesMuldo1 @HouseDemocrats @realDonaldTrump Eric, do you want to run ? https://t.co/cnS1QAckUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doraz44 Not sure Antoine is big enough to play the 3. He and JQ should be the backcourt imo. JRE Swider And Bey wo… https://t.co/D0LEhdY36z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I’m going to be honest, I respect the streak so damn much, because that is an absolutely incredible thing that… https://t.co/iA2G6NtfcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfarm22_ @baileym818 @farmer1279 inexistent? Is that Spanish? #Idontunderstandyourwords]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFunkypants Yeah ive felt a bit limited on how i can code things in godot. Seeming less and less an issue with unity]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fan Controlled Football League recently added Marshawn Lynch and Richard Sherman as its first 2 team owners and… https://t.co/IollIqxu39]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BackThereMonday check out this #originalsong &amp; #follow these awesome friends. https://t.co/sMispeez2V… https://t.co/4CRakpwp9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is all republicans have to offer. No good ideas only demonizing and lying !!!! Watch "Sebastian Gorka Desperat… https://t.co/wsht6j49VV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Frank.  You need old New Bern / Clippers  teammate @AlstonNorwood running with you.  Guess they didn't wan… https://t.co/KvtqAchu5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apollo Rocket  https://t.co/OPnQakSb50      .  #saturn #apollo  #nasa #houstontx #houston #texas #rocket… https://t.co/l7GYEDLvpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sergiosuiloo @Imagen_Mx @beltrandelrio Varios programas te vas a hechar jaja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILikeConcertsTV @Y34RZERO @benshapiro I'm laughing so hard I'm in tears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diego_solares73 @MiserableSDFan @monkigrass @Padres_Farm @TheChamner Plus I got $20 on it and the guy I bet is a K… https://t.co/aLqeGw60eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flood My Wrist is now streamable everywhere🥶  EP coming soon   Art by myself   Produced by @MalikRomello   https://t.co/07eT5ZDVOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanBlakestad @TmanSpeaks @dez_blanchfield @UofA @PwC You gotta share what you learn. Wanna guinea pig my upcoming blog on the DX topic?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aubrey He’s marginally above Tulsi (because I don’t think he’s actively a Russian asset) and behind everyone else. Gross.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Instagram timeline right now legit only consists of "🔥🔥" captions and dope gamer pics of every Gears pro on the… https://t.co/GjqXeXjqlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber @lyft @RODEOHOUSTON @SylvesterTurner the pickup system in green lot is a disgrace and dangerous. Should be fi… https://t.co/YnGPqIpQ2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump still doesn’t understand that he’s the only one who believes the garbage he puts out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me with @BMitchliveNBCS @JacksonSports on @team980 talking @WashWizards @TerrapinHoops 2:30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Storm Watch for New Richmond  https://t.co/NaEw0ZxWPv  1Weather for Android.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6623 is ready to drive #just149. #PCservicesWE @DianeLizette @wendyofthewest @OrmondLsormond @stacie853… https://t.co/wXqQQiMc6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/RdxaiSf8j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedEyeRadioNet The lyrics to #Imagine are the @communist_party manifesto. It's one of the most insidious songs ever written.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DanielK8 @SeannOverman @ShantellShante7 @LikiAndrea @EveryisL @nina13239729 @Anne33148385 @DRIVargasC @tom_savino… https://t.co/hWYcye5bCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiaTainaJ1756 @NiaJaxWWE @FightingWMyFam I have a huge crush on nia jax I am a huge fan of her and she is woman… https://t.co/diXlMHI12R]]></document><document><![CDATA[These scenes in Madrid each time @realmadrid has a big game never cease to amaze me. One of the best fan bases in w… https://t.co/BYBDLldQfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win Your Weekend, Earn Your Week. #thinkfitness @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/607RztwFrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SexyNinjaPowers You’re kickin it with us my dude! Let’s make it happen 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope theres at least an afterlife. Theres so much I wanna talk about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joellecasteix well written and informative piece on Child Victims Act. @protectnykids https://t.co/lBkFnQlNsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrkToLight @MuellerSheWrote @DebPietschTTM @jentaub @realDonaldTrump Excellent tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SubvrsiveHippie @BernieSanders It's info from Bernie himself. Bernie didn't vote for anyone until he was almost 40… https://t.co/hEFRvK0L7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Regal_Beagles @MichaelRapaport Of course folks who look like they wear MAGA hats dont care.  Dont be mad. Go rape sum1 like u usually do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texturizing the hair defines the placement of your highlights. Gives hair color and high lights a pop #hair… https://t.co/GYUX2uu2ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were having family game night before mex and everyone in my tiny ass apartment is goals 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The love and excitement for Baby Metzger is very much alive and well after a weekend spent preparing for their arri… https://t.co/4RVLohIDd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to drive with my knees has been one of the more beneficial things in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the new “Mad Maxine &amp; Beyond the Thunderdome” starring MaxineW as Auntie. Pelosi as The Blaster &amp; AOC as The Master]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelasthotsauce @trnrtips So have i... so weird right.  Dems protecting the country,  Reps protecting the president...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amatoronto @RevivalBarTO Would love to get back to attending AMA events (enjoyed the ones I went to early in 2018… https://t.co/pT4AMzcwlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's see if @LouisvilleMBB, can bounce back against @ClemsonMBB. #Clemson #Louisville #ACC #Cards #ncaabasketball… https://t.co/CkS5lpycEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Envisioning celebrating with my wife at the rate kids move out there parents home these days https://t.co/TMfJCVwbnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard ready to face @CNN tonight. Watch @CNNPolitics in action as she is asked gotcha questions all night,… https://t.co/4EZmDc8DrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarayA61 I’ll post a video or two about some exercises that can help counter those discomforts! I’ve got you! 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codnacho @JamesCurle I think Keatts is doing a good job in Raleigh, but the people calling for his head already ar… https://t.co/E660hZZLUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, nice music on a Tuesday! Great way to start the day! Go Vikes!! https://t.co/52yXaAhdFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrCarlosLHCSD @DrC_LaHabra @LHSchools @TeganLHCSD @TeckerSheryl Mr. Morales and Mr. Martinez thank you for inspiri… https://t.co/ZSkoo3tldk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadler1969 @PowhatanFundLLC @GChernack @celtics Usually the best player wins and that’s probably Kawhi, but that’s… https://t.co/K2Lb3KsOiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt some type of way at the beginning of the match with Pep not going with the players who got us to the final.… https://t.co/YDLW68xkAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BritishArmy @butterflybooks @NAM_London Brava #BalanceforBetter @BritishArmy  #GenderBalance @HeForShe #HeforShe… https://t.co/EfFnvZ6A5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorahODonnell @GayleKing You promote promiscuity and immorality on a daily basis, and act offended by R.Kelley. Yo… https://t.co/Z8JYmqz5tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jewelia_G I hope us Texans can figure out a way to remedy that mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AManill @kengurnick @longenhagen That phenomenon is likely due to two factors: UCL injuries are often cumulative,… https://t.co/GADQ606dEM]]></document></documents></author>