<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I get to see FSL tonight and you can too! #FreestyleLoveSupreme on @TodayTix! Enter here: https://t.co/Ysghl6eFhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCarrey Why soooo much hate and negativity? Please join erase the hate. Love your work. You crack me up]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t think Dyer Maker and Tangerine are two of the best songs ever then go play in traffic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown #austintexas from the hotel rooftop! @ The Guild Hotels https://t.co/kDYE6ymOTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bryce, as we start our descent, please make sure your seat back and tray table are in their full upright positions… https://t.co/er0gCcGVCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esos volantes del America están por quemar al 4to delantero en América. Los secan tanto de oportunidades q piensan… https://t.co/uGadt5pDqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You don’t think George Washington wanted to bet a little ball” -@BarstoolBigCat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValdesMenendez @nataliauci16 @DiazCanelB Hijo de@puta asesino https://t.co/XbraPKtNkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[El matutino de @CarlosLoret es el Alarma! por TV. #8M #AbortoLegalParaTodoMéxico]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking away from my phone then all I hear is “I’m thirsty” https://t.co/oO2gGcdcYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texconserv @ForHD65 Dang Rossy poo blocked me. I’d love to read that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UG Comedy Show Tonight! $4 Heinekens ALL NIGHT LONG!!! 8:30p drexlersnyc  Everyone knows it’s a Marvel of a Comedy… https://t.co/JTNjSZMWpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being the best at getting better is something you can take with you everywhere. It’s a path that lasts forever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random question into the void but I don't understand why Kap settled so early... the longer it went the more info c… https://t.co/bMDYFALxbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@banaszak65 @_StandForTruth_ @reachjulieroys @jamesmacdonald @HarvestBible1 Sir, I have been serving as an Elder in… https://t.co/3sD0QewlZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see my hometown mayor on @colbertlateshow tonight. I've had a @PeteButtigieg quote pinned to my profile… https://t.co/0VAHjeu3Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Yao's Restaurant &amp; Bar in Houston, TX https://t.co/Apv8BpkRIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA I linked my account everyday before the streams and I didn’t even get the kits..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LedyardNFLDraft You don't know how being in Las Vegas is preferable to being in Buffalo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moments like this make my work with @Vol_FanHQ and @VFL_Films so much fun. #JumboTron #tvdirector]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Democracy Now! Thanks for 23 years of non-corporate influenced news!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankFigliuzzi1 @MSNBC We need to change the dialogue from... "Trump disagrees with Intelligence chiefs"... or… "T… https://t.co/lj7Wbo5ceD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warwick’s David Hnasko advances to the 170 pound semifinals, decking Etown’s Javan Thomas in 3:01 at Sectional Wrestling. @WarwickWarriors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thereaalc @almondmilkhunni Mannnn, when you wake up and can barely open your eyes and you gotta try to fight your… https://t.co/aNB5emTVrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Death Day tryna be on some Avengers time vortex quantum realm shit lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume @jmartNYT He’s a leftist not a journalist why would he find something wrong with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experimenting with multiple mini paintings at one time.  I’m really enjoying the creativity inspired by doing minia… https://t.co/UBpfxAXUIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to AUS (@ Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County Airport - @dtweetin in Romulus, MI) https://t.co/oQxki2nXqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summers Interlude x Drake was something insane!!  I just wish he would’ve given us more with that interlude honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDonline Well I hope the thoughts in this article are found to be accurate.  I’m not so positive I have to say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[But nothing will happen to the female that falsely accused him and cost him a shot at a professional career. This h… https://t.co/dt5pVbY4LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes She’s an anti Semite how many times does she have to speak against Israel for you to realize it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The GOP has documented evidence that Stacey Abrams has traveled outside of the state of Georgia on multip… https://t.co/7G5frG2a4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE DID IT!!! #54mins #walkrunorscooter #nevergiveup #DrToldOurFriendSheWouldntBeWalkingAfterCarAccident #GodatWork… https://t.co/rYgHe7eTr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyVslater &amp; @DarnellMayberry were great and all but they didn't have Stu. @maddie_m_lee wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all in on this, but I’m more interested in who is playing for the Monstars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring It 🌞 🌺 🐦 #iloveflowers #ilovegardening #imsoexcited @ Beach Condo Association https://t.co/wvtIEiTXYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[No JOBS there EITHER 20,000 jobs for the month of FEBRUARY Well only 185,000 were expected Inflate it like your INA… https://t.co/qs4lUpesI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nightmare result of US-NKorea talks: Bad deal, little change https://t.co/koMz7lEFcm #FoxNews At least THERE IS DIALOUGE between Leaders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Carrabbas for coming through during the clutch yesterday 💪 https://t.co/EykxcGLo5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump God you are a fucking moron. 🤦🏻‍♂️🙄 @realDonaldTrump, you’re the racist fucker who likes Russian w… https://t.co/JXoixVAirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never even met him and I miss him. Rest easy king. Boy, we can sure use you right now. #MALCOLMX  https://t.co/8IW17ZDpN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHutchingsFTW The Royal Ontario Museum! You can learn more at https://t.co/ge0p9neZvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw this clown in jail with Don Jr. Another Trump ass clown https://t.co/We8x3oGQkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Program contacts of some of the festival organisations in Volusia/Seminole/Orange Counties in Florida. @ Orange Cit… https://t.co/b0H1RNF0he]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow If I was Amazon I would tell them to pack sand. Get rid of your morons like AOC and we will think… https://t.co/S2uIGAwsPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve set my watch ahead. I’m now....in the future (by 19 hours). #InternationalDateLine #vacation #Sydney #Australia]]></document><document><![CDATA[help i’m in a hole of listening to old smell bands from the early 2000s. actually don’t help me. https://t.co/WOvaFdqhm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bfet09 @Kybaseballclub @UD__Baseball @tatescrbaseball Congrats Bradley.  Wishing you all the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was GREAT to host the Super Bowl LIV champs!!!  @JamesConner_ juju @livmiami #steelers4life #steelersnation… https://t.co/GvBCn7xYDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussellANjax @ActionNewsJax Been here for 3 yrs (So Mandarin) and have been downtown to take one daughter to an in… https://t.co/EZ8dHl14El]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardonMyTake @BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter Name a more iconic trio... I’ll wait. https://t.co/FxV484QUXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterMallouk I never really cared for the cereal but I’m interested in trying it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StumpyHobbit @FilmInquiry @filminquirypod @imdbjourney @MMandOscar @MattRSays @NextBestPicture @KevinRBrackett… https://t.co/bLMVwhUBCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, was anybody mad when we didn’t get Amazon? Nope. Quit carping about Sox Management. They did their best. Mann… https://t.co/fHty9QjyI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWE Thursday Night Main Event Live!  Mohegan Sun Arena At Casey Plaza! https://t.co/gU9YP6Xt8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/16vU0zGT3m It seem that PELOSI has flip and gone CRAZY losing CONTROL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sara_Tonyn Only two things I do know about throwing underhand: 1, It's a more natural motion for the arm than over… https://t.co/UDu2FMcFEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get in your car and the talented @GabbyBarrett_ #ihope comes on the @SXMTheHighway on… https://t.co/fJvq7LiQBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Verse  Exodus 15:11 11. Who is like unto thee, O LORD, among the gods? who is like thee, glorious in holine… https://t.co/tcLswnGkVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to look really good covered with @PredsNHL Gold in about 10 months.... https://t.co/sGzCXhWpFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump In the end it doesn’t matter what a person’s politics are to you. If they’re either more powerful… https://t.co/4GaWMFfMZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOtherScottM @TheMovieKit I think the answer is very few. I can think of only a handful of freelancers and one o… https://t.co/O0m8jdJLtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pikachuliu for future reference if anyone brings up Title IX as to why they can’t pay players:  https://t.co/cTe7NfBOAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kimchee yelling at Terrence will never get old. Also, I love working with @MichaelMusi so much! #KimsConvenience… https://t.co/SVPhPBS8mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyStrang Article 1, Section 5, Clause 2: "Each House may determine the Rules of its Proceedings, punish its Memb… https://t.co/NagD2jzHSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHolder @brianrayguitar He should not occupy the White House. He’s a fraud.  Indict, convict, and imprison. He… https://t.co/QUHjHa8jwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@be_katz @RobMills91 @johnwintertweet I mean we're doing that wrong too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnakeTheJake21 @LoudCityPhotos @russwest44 @okcthunder @RealStevenAdams @spidadmitchell @rudygobert27 @Yg_Trece @utahjazz 69/4/20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@getFANDOM I keep getting #SamwellTarly come on 🤬 https://t.co/2lTLHewtMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘She’s not cheating on me yet’- The @SethKush Story @DrewOnTheRadio @TheJohnSenning]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now the waiting game begins. Praying the surgery goes well for my dad 🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[First #Sabres Facebook Live in the books. Thanks to @JMackeyPG for asking a question. Give it a watch:  https://t.co/6Zf88CSZWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaePhoenix @PamKeithFL Scientists get so much more done when they're being paid by private companies. The only pro… https://t.co/lujW9xxu1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you arent cool with @mlow_beats then you sus af thats a mf fact lets go]]></document><document><![CDATA[i stuck those circle batteries in my ears and thought i was charging my brain. 💀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto a es Tuitel PR en video. Dos tipos agarrándose a las pescozás y el “somos adultos” equivalente al gato de la p… https://t.co/LWOPOYt7od]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LavonteDavid54 It’s like forgetting to press send and start telling everyone you sent an email!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalvinRidley1 come visit us at @MountParan in the #ATL #riseup #RollTide]]></document><document><![CDATA[East GR leads East Kentwood, 31-26, at the half in girls districts @FOX17Blitz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alezander You know them white ass kids were asking to get thrown again😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@True_2_thebigbl @brauf33 Dont disagree but Kentucky should be 3rd #1 considering they beat UNC by 8 on a neutral court]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Friday evening at home all by myself... this is weird 😍 prepping for the week ahead with some fresh juicing while… https://t.co/KAWUksXju5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Chardonnay Barrel Aged Saison by @MapBrewing @ MAP Brewing Company — https://t.co/QfDTdSZZZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Petra_Kvitova @BaraStrycova @DDFTennis I love what you both bring to WTA!  On and off the court!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senategopfloor Baldwin (D-WI) Bennet (D-CO) Blumenthal (D-CT) Booker (D-NJ) Brown (D-OH) Cantwell (D-WA) Durbin (D… https://t.co/hz9qeAjaHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a playa vista resident, I’d like to say that the old racist white woman is the only one who is not welcome in ou… https://t.co/TOKEMFHvsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its As long as I am honest and stop being too silly. Try not to confuse the ones I want to impress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is strength in suffering, there is power in being overlooked.” -@TDJakesShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhuntingtonn You gotta point its only the ones that mean something. Thank you j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi  It’s apparent that you’ve lost control of the Democrat Party in the House with so many members thum… https://t.co/g4Ma8eGuzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got all my people with me I see whole bunch of green &amp; gold in this thang....Zwolle made💚💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video of the incident will be uploaded to @LRpolice ‘s YouTube channel at 4 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s  #DrSeussDay Grade 4 @GCPelementary @MrMillersClass2 https://t.co/Wo8KMHf0Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 90’s kids will remember this  A Goofy Movie - Eye to eye https://t.co/8zW6S33CJc via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[All 4 Aurora public highschool basketball teams will be playing Today at East Aurora. This city is a basketball com… https://t.co/pZGSYueTX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Capgemini My advice to my daughters will be to focus on what YOU want to be, not what others think you should be.… https://t.co/JtTDPvFhH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loathstupid From what I understand the guys who built the place were drunk 75 to 90% of the time. This whole house… https://t.co/JEmB0fm3HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiply . . . #waynetennant #recordingartist #montrealer #portraitmodeling #face #singer #songwriter #closeup… https://t.co/SNtQ9nF3JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman On his long list of accomplishments was buying an election for the presidency with felony bribe… https://t.co/RitK0gRUJI]]></document></documents></author>