<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mane started reminiscing about a old Louisiana nigga ...got in my feelings ....but ohh well . New adventures]]></document><document><![CDATA[But they must be having a grand time because they still support DickHead-Moron Drumph.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says “Girls Brunch” more than wearing my big black hat and combat 6 inch heeled boots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #QA jobs like "Deputy Director, Principle Scientist, Swiftwater, PA… https://t.co/osJPWRqMOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PAPowerWrestle @MarcBillett @jasonmbryant @WillieAtFLO @KnopsKnotes @Mr_RHolmes @LeboWrestling @SprintCarUnl… https://t.co/GKoBE2rmzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I8uridea4brekki @EmilyGorcenski The point is, you should stop talking out of you’re arse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, pretty sure Spike Lee was cosplaying as Stan Shunpike on the Knight Bus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alienvsrobbins @joshuaclov3r my fave fox of all time https://t.co/LXiabo8SUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArchivistsRock Probably for the best since I think you would’ve ended up enjoying Adam and they killed him off in… https://t.co/Isp6s711Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everyone can just say a small prayer for me as I start this A&amp;P2 Lab practical that would be great !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be there with my friends, let’s fill those seats!!!  #MovieGoingMatters #indiefilmsource @BarrymoreFilm… https://t.co/exnVp8Wr8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think the Left will ever accept their defeat by Trump. I think it’s hilarious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but this warped lineup is gonna give me the opportunity to see so many bands I love that I’ve never had the chan… https://t.co/iYnF0exXlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reflection of pure love in the middle of confusion. It’s the movie, and it’s the life we all live in. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to start decorating for my 👑 dallas_ytismything birthday pool party 🎉... had to start the gift 🎁 table off wi… https://t.co/QK0aErSHrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layman terms of Friedman’s second law of media communication is  Smaller audience—more complex message Bigger audie… https://t.co/UaOf9HbHhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[• this is the end / this is not the end •  (Gungor End of the World Tour feat. Propaganda, The Brilliance) @ Subter… https://t.co/dduOQZF29p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse me? Are you my mom? No, I didn't think so. Please take you and your... https://t.co/U9Ts1cLQtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homemade pizza. It's tasty! #wwfreestyle #ww #2ingredientpizzadough @ Pensacola, Florida https://t.co/0rpRZjoAds]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cranberry muffin isn’t bad,&amp; I don’t fuck with cranberries like that lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows made a mockery of himself yesterday he has a long history racist comments about Obama , We need to… https://t.co/uLqITAmGKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asdrubalivan Animo. Todo pasara pronto y Venezuela necesita gente talentosa como tu. No desesperes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 1000 amazing people give their personal time to make the Sporting Life 10k a success for Camp Oochigeas a… https://t.co/U3EnLu8BwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Budgam #PakistanAirForceOurPride #PakistanZindabad #PakistanStrikeBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[It deadass amazes me how I can go from talking w/ someone every single day to not speaking at all. Smh. Shit is beyond baffling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyYoung63 @glibcf Weird how you went in the Farrakhan direction and are also not taking a Jewish person's feelings into account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the problem… The parents defending the kid’s disrespectful actions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Love is eternal and so are you! ❤️😇 #soulcoach #angelreader  #mariapeth #happyvalentinesday @… https://t.co/rDhTdUyeft]]></document><document><![CDATA[The speaker is cutting off a bit of a shouting match between the premier and NDP MPP Catherine Fife, who was saying… https://t.co/Bq3BIKWDQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlestforestr Congratulations Lacey.  That is great news and is well deserved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's what's up!! its.just.maddy_4  #25MadyM @ Colorado Springs, Colorado https://t.co/zuWOxBNYy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a sad situation.  A husband went to his wife's place of work and killed her.A patient with a CCP shot the susp… https://t.co/c3HcYwZ1X8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pentagon may tap military pay and pension funds to build Trump's US-Mexico border wall https://t.co/ywMbDl0s4m via @businessinsider]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpmomof5 I am not saying I am onboard, it sounds reasonable and fair. Democratic Socialism is another big step how… https://t.co/i5cDAYK4tJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJenniMurphy @DonnieWahlberg Yay Jenni congratulations on overcoming that fear. I still won't talk in public in… https://t.co/NOg5SE9t7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I was walking past this man and he held up a snowball and was like “friendly snowball fight?” NO THANK YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's an illogical and non-reality-based argument in the first place, but it's also politically counterproductive! What's not to love?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reactivated FB yesterday, already deactivated that crap this morning. 😂🥴I just can’t take it. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHe11789025 Thank you! I do! And incredible grandkids, too. Bonus this trip —- time with my BFF!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We started playing Rock, Paper, Scissors to decide who has to go to the store on our days off. So far I’ve only had… https://t.co/pvMCYH367g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@82nd13 @norcalbbgm @butchbaccala @_JeremyBooth @JasonMcCuistion @CedrickHarris11 @SBetkey @mactiner… https://t.co/pKV1RBFztB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinUnderwood Hang in there! It will be a wonderful #Boskone and we’re looking forward to it, even if I am leaving… https://t.co/6ZZyciqwux]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Selfies of the 1630s’ #ifthisisntniceidontknowwhatis #rembrandtselfportrait #artinstituteofchicago @ The Art Insti… https://t.co/RBpN46Rvp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hedgearoundme @Blavity I believe descendants of American slaves should be in a separate category like Native Ameri… https://t.co/CO8rkuMny6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @NASCARtrackside @MattHagan_FC @KyleBusch @MW55 @CoreyLaJoie @LeahPritchettTF @HailieDeegan… https://t.co/yHLuUSCCwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinsonWoodrow @IsoaG @HazzellU @PamBGreen @SusansMusicPg_2 @SugarJunkiesUK @TheSunDogs1 @BsThorsen @MahoganySzn… https://t.co/9TmLdqjxA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun to watch @TCUBasketball WITH @conbrochill12 @tcumbbm   #GoFrogs https://t.co/suJ5LkqYJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer  Win $10  Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,  Sign Here:… https://t.co/7JsfIaopg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟Playdate with me! 🌟Learn how to set your pendulum to access information. 🌟Find out what you can do when you do not… https://t.co/Ed0p87iimv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting Like the way you slid that cake* business in underneath your fries manifesto. *we can do better than… https://t.co/LJ4RDfwFGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST SOLD!  Happy to announce🙌🏻 closed sale at Desirable Bal Harbour. 10275 Collins Ave APT 928 Bal Harbour, FL 331… https://t.co/PTugXvGK0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[and taught in public schools of OKC for 41 years. She introduced Negro history long before it was acceptable for cu… https://t.co/vgeX0dedpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naiyorkcity Definitely!!!! I’ll dm you my cell now. Let me know if you’re in the DMV!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yikesks So many yummy choices. I think I’d try the Glazed Coconut Carrot Bread first! 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apayne @kainagata No, the DRO from Elections Canada counts the ballots in the presence of scruntineers from each p… https://t.co/FRekZIRBG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 @Brandon20472428 @1pissedPolack What the fuck happened to her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuxlonLLC @bookmebrooke Thank you. I live Cuban thigh highs and stockings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EndlessMidnigh1 That sounds cool. Mine is a series. It's just too much story for one book]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KdSmith65 @Whataburger Maybe they’re trying to save me from heart disease ✌🏼✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderfully Wonderful Things That Are Turning 100 in 2019! https://t.co/ns9eRVEV7y https://t.co/wH2klrDcJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to you all  I hope you all have a wonderful day https://t.co/2i4HOfYi1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌞Saturday, February 16th.🌞Enjoy the weekend!🌺🌸🌈#floweroftheday #flowers #roses #hillcountry 🌈🌺🌞 @ Bee Cave, Texas https://t.co/5NjPfZfBRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @lexusknox on their 25th anniversary! I had a great time celebrating with Mr. White,… https://t.co/7RdaHQ6UtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when the person most important in your life to you was a complete stranger?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSylviaGarcia @HispanicCaucus @HouseDemocrats @HouseJudiciary It is not an anti-immigrant agenda! It is an agend… https://t.co/QzaIKFHg4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaronCorbinWWE @WWE @FightOwensFight @WWEDanielBryan Troll level 100 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading in from Santa Rosa island. The weather was really bumpy and windy on the way out but turned into a beautifu… https://t.co/V0FpNx1Z6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley I voted so hard they gave me two stickers! https://t.co/XT97ahUvGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in the hell can Congress allow this asshat to represent us on the world stage? No doubt he should be impeached yet he holds us hostage!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @nytimes Yes it is! A lot of food and most of other products I use are packaged in plastic. I'm not Be… https://t.co/QioXi9w6os]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Actor: Rami Malek (ughhhhh, honestly it should be Timothee Chalamet who CRUSHED in Beautiful Boy a year after… https://t.co/doiAbUxGvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cfahooligan He’s one extremely unattractive, but wealthy, guy.  She’s clearly in love with his $$, not him. 🤷🏼‍♀️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy the game! Enjoy your teammates! Enjoy your time in the game, with your teammates, your coaches, it ends quick… https://t.co/9FTLA99D1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPAmericanMom "Leftover funds".    With everything needed for Military and their families (housing, med Bill's, e… https://t.co/khN2HuFAYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annehayhay @Aibek91 @MyFavsTrash this would be tight but there’s only one shoe added in the end lol it’s not a pair 😅😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkartista @vicementa new generation @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/m64auobVv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said I stopped goin out but really, I’m just waiting for the warm weather again so I can be half naked again in p… https://t.co/UYf9pCuJIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve woke up EARLY every single day I’ve been off and now I can’t sleep. 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch “Amazing Experiences for Girls: Powered by the Girl Scout Cookie Program” on #Vimeo https://t.co/JpyE65hpqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheeseonurtaco @BritaUSA I bought a Brita water bottle and haven’t bought any plastic bottles or drank and soda since 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud to have healed and beat the timer on a +11 Freehold last night. Hopefully I get to run the +12.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Leesie!  She played her heart out this season for school. SJS took 2nd place and she made the All-Confe… https://t.co/GfQeqeihBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent over 5 hours making my sister a cake from scratch instead of doing homework. Now I have to pull an all nigh… https://t.co/0jFB3IwdXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#parents #recherche #cannabis❓ @rclalq @FRAPRU #cannabis #logement @francoislegault  @CarmantLionel  @SJB_CAQ… https://t.co/EPaepYZHLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaNicholes Back in my day, my dad in Michigan shipped truckloads of hay and straw to Arlington Race Track.  M… https://t.co/1InvmtuQDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway fuck ugly old men and goodnight to women, specifically women of color, ONLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bourbon Street / French Quarter https://t.co/fBC4n0fHv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[me &amp; Heidi planned a trip to Oregon and planned to sleep in our car one night and its snowing so we had to cancel, im so sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[His voice is so iconic and his humor in such a dark time is one to be admired. Prayers up to the GOAT of game show… https://t.co/1xUe8elrGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy story! Multiple car jacking attempts and terrifying experience outside two Saanich businesses but bystanders… https://t.co/iWcxRIRUiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @FiveThirtyEight Well we're certainly not going to let to them take our voice vote away and this is all happen… https://t.co/lOVtj8U9Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HFTAlert I understand your point. Thank you for your thoughts on market making.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glowing like never before.✨💕 I think it is the braids ya know I feel like a different person with them on my head😂… https://t.co/0fw8lhPYVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC You are embarrassing yourself, your state and your country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the feels 🥰 seeing images of @KamalaHarris taking time to share a meal with immigrant families at La Casita de… https://t.co/gs2J3YYmGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q: how do you make a soccer mom angry? A: what doesn’t make them angry? The real question is how to keep them out of everyone’s business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book your @AirCanada to #Japan! Count down starts from today, #500DaysToGo, till #Tokyo2020! #FlyTheFlag #AirCanada… https://t.co/1xNulvzrNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[a second mattress to alleviate his back problems.   Wednesday, Feb. 20 Putin weighs in “Good-faith business shouldn… https://t.co/xq4urXb3vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @realDonaldTrump @CNN Do you think 45 is bright enough to know he’ll lose but that he can tell his base tha… https://t.co/npSmVAH27D]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls selling highlighters is the biggest makeup scam. lemme put y’all on.]]></document></documents></author>