<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Upon further thought, maybe chosing to do my weekend homework between 6pm-2am Sunday night is unwise. In other news, Beat Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time eating @KSBarAndGrille Without a doubt the best bone in wings I have ever had! Are they always this good… https://t.co/nGZYCqGlRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHOtheCALL No way 😡she encourage people to take trucks and run us down in parks and anywhere 🤮stay out too bad Traitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing the trout don’t mind a little rain. @bennettspringOA https://t.co/KzV3ZEaEN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay #Abetterway great balanced team we have at @BlueSnapInc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t vote for him, but shame on anyone that wants to deligetimize a guy who wants to help the country because he… https://t.co/N6PzBu0ZFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this is the Swiss Army Knife of rap songs. Wanna feel hype? I got you. Wanna vibe? I got you. Sad? This… https://t.co/RTCugMtwXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are truly some sick individuals in this world! I couldn’t even imagine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradA53472906 @IsleRacingPP @gabe_prewitt @Dailydoublesw Thx Brad. Feels good to fire away and take a shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mcgavockairstrip #nashville #sunrise #picoftheday #sky #beautiful @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/YSokQCAIIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Chicagoans! Early voting is open. You have until Feb. 26th to make your voice heard. Get in there! @ Chicago, I… https://t.co/2wNttcqo6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGHtransit I love public transit bc they are reliable! Money AND time saving too!! #publictransit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t expect you to have some sort of sympathy towards this mans situation cus your name is Sheryle and that s… https://t.co/X5m4zODsfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeaseLax wins in OT over Buchholz 8-7. Jacob Gmeiner with the OT winner! @LaxNorthfl @FloridaLX @lax904 @wwbrown19 @BrentWoronoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora resulta que trelles no queria tirarle al cruzazul..si es su pan de todo el tiempo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strength training split by @Chrisfittt - @Chrisfittt   @Chrisfittt @Chrisfittt - Building mass is a little differen… https://t.co/FHBGgxvjN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_a_w_a_n_n_a @CunningSq16 @Steelerschic85 @pam_brundige @bfosterls7 @jhgurf @jawofsteel2014 @tharpel @ninampls… https://t.co/JrkrEWAEnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The third act of our podcast is here! We hope you guys enjoy our conversation on the next recession, automation, li… https://t.co/o4XOhNcEHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S. So I opened up GarageBand on my iPhone and wrote a song with the virtual piano. https://t.co/eMybp8IBA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnny_Cage22 Mane you know how that shit go. Niggas can’t resist designer shit, therefore they’ll always do slick… https://t.co/FmU5PJeGVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacCountyDA @YouTube Thank you I enjoy your podcast very informative and I love the tweets about the criminals tha… https://t.co/I7rT9iD8cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaOsteen @VictoriaOsteen Hey...Good Morning and Happy Saturday! Thanks for sharing. Prayers you, @JoelOsteen… https://t.co/78ed86cpjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cool. Have you seen, @brandonleblanc, @LauraCatPJs, @donasarkar? In 30 years, maybe someone will unearth an old… https://t.co/8BPwIsZLQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dramatic plot twist involving the actor. Our @Miguelnbc story tonight: Jussie Smollett arrested for orchestrati… https://t.co/UGfxR97nsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIGERWOODSRENEW Let's get one last birdie. Too many missed short putts this week. ☹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @UGAWomensTennis showing off their new @ITA_Tennis National Championship hardware in #TheSteg.… https://t.co/IPxBhzfzVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pleasure, and thank you for being a critical component in uniting #LittleRock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossUglem I’d rather see Armie Hammer. Both are 32 and very good actors but Hammer is 6’5” and Richard Madden is 5… https://t.co/vFTztmyyGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt @POTUS @SecPompeo @AmbJohnBolton You’re playing the MSM card?  Really?  In defense of this mentally def… https://t.co/4yMiprIqcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I learned yesterday that everyone at the top 60 🏀 workout has a picture taken in an all star jersey so they have… https://t.co/GQd4ouVuwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pence now talking about President Trump’s efforts, says it has been “two years of action.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frank_WTAM @ChrisBeeble Quit being a buzz kill Frank, enjoy this. SUPER BOWLLLLLL SUPER BROWNSSS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerrySinDFF I think you’re reading my thought wrong.   I think landing spot is a terrible way to measure value.… https://t.co/KexTd0rFqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was actually on key, -@WayneDawsonFox8 on @Kristi_Capel's singing just before coming back on TV. #Fox8Quotes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southern Oregon is seriously such a damn rad place. My favorite annual “I need to get the fuck out of California fo… https://t.co/nl136yUJyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedLieu @StormResist @POTUS Please Donald so much could be done for America with those funds. Throwing it away… https://t.co/7qcmn8maNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you pick the right people and give them the opportunity to spread their wings, you almost don’t have to manage… https://t.co/fgkdVOuVpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He’s Going to Fieldstrip These Guys”: Inside the #Trump 2020 election Campaign’s Wild, Attempt to… https://t.co/bAR0xmjUT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaganMediaBites I think she was promised her freedom if she just showed up and kept her mouth closed like a good h… https://t.co/8L1HjIXazL]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Bruno Ganz. Your portrayal of Jonathan Harker stays with me. #BrunoGanz #WernerHerzog https://t.co/g72yGYtbN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRichGannon most content fed to you by The Algorithm is faked in some aspect.  redditor ties his dogs neck into… https://t.co/Cf4Gq3YZ3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThreeCalories Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my autho… https://t.co/5pDImaeECA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #Indianapolis / #Baltimore #Colts form 1965 on.  https://t.co/G9y9USJ0U6 … … … … https://t.co/cBLiMHQl3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holly_Love2 @marklevinshow He needs to actually do some work for a change]]></document><document><![CDATA[***Price Reduction*** Contact: Friedrich Hinterberger, PA Coldwell Banker Boca Resort and… https://t.co/TJV1rvqcYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk It's American taste. Put corn syrup in ANY food and it will sell. Putting a ration on sugar would do wonde… https://t.co/i32gUdIyTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like Thanos deserves to become a verb, like “Don’t try to Thanos me”, but what should it mean? When someone… https://t.co/worviHNR5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveCliffJensen You’re a trip... how you expect to close doors playing games lol 😝 Y’all are nuts 😂❤️ #OnlyLove 🐾… https://t.co/UO2Z7LliuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had this ad come across my feed on FB. Notice anything?  #Bernie2020 https://t.co/DNRmQQIJ48]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cracked open a beer at the same tempo as the song I was listening to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home Grown Mixtape Vol 1 Exclusively #Spotify on Spotify https://t.co/PHGQJgh6WP @ Muzic Empire "You… https://t.co/74XbTBHFO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling into Friday like.  #MBTA #RedLine #FridayThoughts https://t.co/DNJI4jAkTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goknickstape Quickly and quietly help her find a place to dispose of the body.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ree_emily My advice would be don't co-sign it unless it's for a motorcycle.    Motorcycle opens all kinds of doors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum @GetSpectrum your digital adapters are crap.   Please Wait. I’ll try using that next billing cycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know an EASY way to find who you know that’s attending #SXSW⁠?   Go to @Twitter search, type in #SXSW⁠, fil… https://t.co/uNy9QJDvPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @julianzelizer Brian , all of a sudden the wall is not immoral.  Just think the Dems approved 55 mile… https://t.co/iEy8O9c0LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Far from an overreaction, I’ve seen plenty of stuff traveling with women for work that made me fear this exact scen… https://t.co/oyd4FMv8Ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVToronto It's bs they're not calling it for what it should be a terrorism attack frig]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT BEGINS: California Gov. Gavin Newsom Announces Plan to Sue Trump Over ‘National Emergency’ | Sean Hannity https://t.co/V4eR3OyXNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NigeACT @farmingforever How about defining your version of a #GreenNewDeal  and use support for it as a litmus tes… https://t.co/AGbsaY3tXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be prejudice against a fetus &amp; label it "not human" is a double standard, because everybody once was one.… https://t.co/GsKdKNQQho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Btw Abigail votes that I stay home with her forever. https://t.co/39rcy61DRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaac Hernandez(game winner) and Gustavo Aguilera (2 goals) are all smiles as Arlington beats Godinez 3-2 in the se… https://t.co/vBXIrHczzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers knew we’d be living underwater in the year 3000 because of rising sea levels due to the polar ice caps melting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lana_jaee True but like we all are also trying to see this masterpiece of a show as soon as possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slipknot @VOLBEAT @GojiraMusic @BehemothBand @KNOTFEST Austin TX! GA🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bugl3t @Lifeisamitch @billmaher Your not staying focused. POTUS leadership is exemplary. He has created booming jo… https://t.co/NJ81JAoJj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackKingston What do you know Trump reportedly paid an army call girls to stare at his hair. Don’t remember you commenting on that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikerubymusic @tyejamesmusic   #teamwork #newmusic #letsgo @ Hollywood https://t.co/0CtNW9xDTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sharon82819258 @topher331 @CoryBooker You understand it would take Trillions not millions right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited #Bills this week. Would have been a good get, especially for this price. Really good blocker. Former Pats D… https://t.co/xmAVZ7lrLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Junior Day invite, University of Tennessee -Martin. Thanks @CoachKBannon for the invite!!! https://t.co/ziuroSD0vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NFL how is Robert Kraft still the owner of the @Patriots? He should have been removed immediately, what he did is… https://t.co/aHvsRFCn6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BlackHistoryMonth #MalcolmLittle aka #MalcolmX Keynote Speaker Nation Of Islam also assassinated on this very Day.… https://t.co/RiCc5VkkZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeofferyRogers Nope, it’s only about 10 percent of my actual job in the newsroom. I relish the quiet nights when I get to write about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's running so much better w this and the new spark plugs https://t.co/PGnBzS8TbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pope Francis ends landmark meeting by again calling for ‘All-Out Battle’ to fight sexual abuse within the… https://t.co/HBsrZpx8Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneDennis34 Smart managing if you ask me. Although Tommy Tilma was left waiting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetaStreeta @bokamotoESPN @BlessedMMA @DustinPoirier @MadduxJae We want tony]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had nightmare I was in the White House with Trump and he said that it was in bad shape because they weren’t maint… https://t.co/4yMeO3TQPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeMolishh @OldPlugMurked @KraftyKur @deeblain @Maxhell_AMEN That’s ya mans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people post quotes with sayings and shit like everyday I don’t understand that lmao chill out b nobody is. “Th… https://t.co/Bx0c9gVI1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reciclan la ropa en #ESPNam? @AdalFrancoESPN trae el mismo suéter que traía Paco Gabriel el día de ayer @cprocuna @ESPNmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with SG1 9x04 “The Ties That Bind”... I forgot how funny this episode is. My favorite… https://t.co/k1BWCcfIyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of Trump’s trade tariffs,  farmers, who typically vote republican, must take government money in order to s… https://t.co/5xkHHch8OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Racer_BA @3Skulz @DLoesch @KamalaHarris @NRA It’s the most preventable except maybe smoking deaths]]></document><document><![CDATA[FAMILIA TWITTER-el sistema Gobierno en Mexico-establecido  por DON MANUEL LOPEZ OBRADOR-esta ya en los Paises Latin… https://t.co/6UzdEaZkRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a dying network this is like an afters where people are staying around way too long  So I’m just going to h… https://t.co/nrdQFchbC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoApp Went to Buc-ee's last night, Went with my buddy here. https://t.co/NvZedfA6QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSandersEdu @Belouga_ @mrsmfranco @rdickerson2 @bfureighEDU @missbritaustin @MrsKennyPRS @MrsGEdu @lcglassford… https://t.co/hgUhpjS7ZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight class from Rome. And I will politely decline, keep my agenda, and ask myself why I’m so bothered by Pogba… https://t.co/VJP1mIMWrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A canine cure for the mid-winter blues out here @UConn #mush! 🐾 https://t.co/UccUZlJqyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 years of results, 21 locations and 66 reps. ALPINE G241-S is proving to be a step above the rest and even the sta… https://t.co/cw5L4PxmQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickwallace7 @CodyMullins34 We have more nattys than most of those programs. All been pretty close together. We’re… https://t.co/WOioDCi0de]]></document><document><![CDATA[He doesn't understand hypocrisy and probably denies everything he said anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New family member #Optigan We are going to have so much fun but I got to bring it back to life first. #composer… https://t.co/tZn1j7diw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGreenbergSez @yalielkin And back up her answers with Jew hating Jew groups. Oy vey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austintexasgov @MayorAdler joins representatives from @Ford @ridespin @TechCrunch and @CityofMiami to discuss how… https://t.co/ZltvkJaNam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarsynElledge3 @KarsynElledge3 Hey🙋...Good Morning and Happy Monday! Hope you, @jelledge81 (your dad) and your… https://t.co/8KVOftb6Cn]]></document></documents></author>