<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Half Moon Cay, Holland America Line's award winning private island!  This is one of those places that it's always h… https://t.co/yFRdHI8mtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is sorta urgent: does anyone have paypal? pls dm me if u do i need help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayne_brandt @TheGoodGodAbove Exactly. Thank you.🗽#Resist.                 #VoteBlueNoMatterWho]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newmexicoskies #newmexicotrue #wagnerequipmentbloomfield #wagnerequipment ...Nothing prettier than CAT equipment g… https://t.co/l8JM49Ck7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever go somewhere and someone just stares at you like they know something about you https://t.co/LQK5F30Ctt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin You’ve been through hell and trauma losing Joyce and being terrorized by the man in the whitehouse. T… https://t.co/g41yMDBP15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScaryJBlige_ @RoyParret @Alyssa_Milano What asinine is you skipped over the part in the article that says “over th… https://t.co/S7WRr0hVDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing out our #solarpowered ovens as part of our #ebdteems fourth grade unit!  Can the melt a S’more?  Collect da… https://t.co/U7WyS70f2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good pre-expo #marathon fuel with this #Anti-inflammatory menu at the keynote luncheon by @TheDoctors Dr. Travis St… https://t.co/iGO8NyTeeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachcrazy70 @RikRankin Nevada, New Mexico and West Texas are hideous. Except for Taos. Beautiful there. Remember… https://t.co/Y6jP0dNc9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NemoV8 This infighting must STOP! Divided we are weak, United we are Strong. Please anons we must stay United.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_reinaaxo Girl I don’t remember the name 😪😪 I bought them con las Chinas beauty supply store 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start the week the right way!!! Monday to Friday happy hour 🍹🍹🍹 4:00pm to 8:00pm ^ * Happy hour at the bar * ♦️ SPE… https://t.co/V4HQpTxYJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnlyAngel2013 This is such a beautiful thing.  I love to see what he see when he looks out at all the love for him… https://t.co/t7ITsJEOhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @hultmark_mark Are you freaking kidding me? She didn't know this would traumatize children?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tombstone1954 @AMMOCOLLECTORR @cali_curmudgeon @jonz970 @AW95NJ @Razorsmack1 @DaveSchreiber3 @StoverLove @garway95… https://t.co/AqR9xXcSbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl used to wear padded bras and sit with her boobs on the lunch table]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un beau portrait de Magali Charbonneau d’@inovia, qui était au #ForumCCMM #IA de la Chambre hier. #FemmesenTech… https://t.co/pD30kw11t7]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the fabulous Paul Groves for Das Lied von der Erde @nashvillesymph . Has an amazing week! Thank you! @ Nashvil… https://t.co/wyJ3cTp1bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly impressed with the customer service I received from @emmaemail. Y’all are killing it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the privilege of working with Lionel Richie the other night. Private concert for 120 people. What a great show!… https://t.co/VHxgtrrQTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreenranger_ Second of all, why am I wasting time while he’s getting piped from the back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vou dormir na sala de espera mesmo, pq ainda falta 6 horas pra Carla chegar]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚔Tallmadge | Tallmadge Police: 7 hurt after bike goes into stands at Summit County Fairgrounds https://t.co/zAu2c0vocl]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was telling jenna how i bumped my head and there’s a lump and her first reaction was “are you sure it isn’t tooth… https://t.co/ZuPWCKfM2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Pena de muerte a Maduro y Diosdado en cadena nacional. Gracias!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is officially Stuck in my head. Thanks @halsey @travisbarker @yungblud 🥁🎧 https://t.co/TFyZrk0MJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjoneskerr @jaymeamann @AlexDe_Luca I have 5 releases at my desk. Plus at least 3 more that I can think of off the… https://t.co/PBpEpvQAVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are driving to or from Tooele, you will deal with some snow. Here’s a look at the drive on 201 &amp; I-80.… https://t.co/jCTFrU83ak]]></document><document><![CDATA[New to Dallas and found out @tseguinofficial and I have something in common. LOVE Dave N Busters!!!!! #amazing Need to go to a game now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take time to stop by to reconnect or meet us for the first time. Lots of fun and chances to win! @ARAGlegal… https://t.co/IN3gf0b8oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday sucked. When you wish you had that one person there it would’ve made it so much easier]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @Twitter how long do I have to wait for an Edit button? It’s 2019. Pretty please!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NIHDirector please outline in Twitter format what NIH does and progress has been made to fight various type of can… https://t.co/V4woU6UzGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole thread!! I’m dying!! And desperately trying to come up with an amazing one! 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annie Lennox, Ed Sheeran, and More Team Up to Get Everyone on Board With Feminism https://t.co/cKE86nFy8q #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Bite your tongue! Or you thumb. Or your phone. Or your keyboard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyMen0705 @lentzadam533 @YanksGalaxy28 @abc13houston @NYCKING @NYCKNP @TheEsquire212 @ZionMonster2019… https://t.co/zNNMiokdTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhiramduncan Rebekah and passengers seemed very thankful and positive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brigittbrien @Paigeota We shall see. Oliver will accept her like he does all of his family. She needs to push past… https://t.co/o1Dv9Zpqq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPOnYourRadio I'm  never pissed at you. Just cause i know when you're wrong and debate you a tiny bit doesn't mean… https://t.co/jlge9J0NhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to live life on the edge this morning and wore a green dress knowing I’d be in front of a green screen. Wil… https://t.co/4dgUMmZGlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who needs to hear this, but go get ur nut and go to bed. shoutout @Logic301 for being sexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Knew these would come in handy! @LisaMCollard https://t.co/kRFpeOXQQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tricking my brain into thinking this is the sun. https://t.co/SoDiruasOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️ PSA: ‼️ I have an EXTRA TICKET to KACEY MUSGRAVES @ Houston Rodeo TOMORROW NIGHT if anyone wants to go w me 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallbrary Me too. Along with everyone in my family. Intermission and I’m a puddle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dianne Feinstein's Husband Wins Near-Billion Dollar California High-Speed Rail Construction contra… https://t.co/HLmYxOwcwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how we all knew Iain wasn't going to go yet we are all surprised hes not there....]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang jolly. 22 Gifts Your Teen Secretly Wants %u2014 for $50 or less! https://t.co/tjNcJ8L4mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodySIO I somehow keep forgetting that I’m seeing you guys in a couple weeks. I’ll be minding my own business and… https://t.co/VQIbjX4ETc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @Itridpm @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn @Msgargoyle13 @NOW1SOLAR… https://t.co/vGmxQJci2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something a 3-year-old told me while I was changing his diaper:  “I am a pirate.”  *points at penis*  “And this is my pirate ship.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@U_S_C_R_E_D_I_T Word "barriers" in your letter to the editor is really wrong. My Medicare has Requirements. Barrie… https://t.co/zyJVqs4v4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javachik I thought the Leo/ Goodman pairing was an unexpected stroke of genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made myself a treat for breakfast but now I’m afraid I’ll never be able to afford a house ☹️ #Millennialproblems https://t.co/9dckCrSDMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Thought you could go after the big people, well girlie they are stronger and richer than you and can figh… https://t.co/9z245oplAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the new Magnum is as close to Hawaii as I'll ever get...(sigh)😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life Goals: Make enough money to buy a Christmas Tree that requires a ladder.   Note: buy ladder if this happens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSalvi59 I love him...i follow him on YouTube.  His stuff is still 99% spot on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think you know what entrepreneurship is? Lady Gaga has something to say about that. @heathriel https://t.co/UfzDFVNRTJ via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[To just see baseball. To sit out in the warm Florida sun. To spend time with Dad and @julieswims02 and to bump into… https://t.co/TapwQgmcrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you already doing well?⁣ ~~~~~~~~~⁣ ⁣ Sometimes my journals feel like a nauseous overflow of reiterating a… https://t.co/uZF9rwA1WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanson Brothers is playing at work and I don’t know how to feel about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Arizona ??????? Somebody upstairesvhas been trying to send us messages from all around the world. People aren’… https://t.co/PLlfHfWFFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett The hate monger is finally awake https://t.co/zgnegGEEvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornach1 @wackyvorlon @RueNahcMohr @GuildOfMakers You should! That's a gorgeous clock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump Wow, that's amazing. You didn't show the thousands of protesters either that were t… https://t.co/PkCxe1BwqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Cheatham County Lady Cubs!! Bringing it home again 61-48! Regional Champions!! 🏆 🏅🏀 #ccchs #ccchsshowingoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy (Belated) Birthday to the BEST university!!!!   Such a beautiful place!!!  #Home  My bday is the 15th.… https://t.co/NaHjYlOcFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[fun fact: since this tweet, new jersey has had 70 degree weather, and a school cancelling snow storm within two wee… https://t.co/ZHtAeFV4Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA Overturn Trump’s declaration of emergency &amp; get him OUT of OUR White House NOW‼️📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣📣]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the snowstorm, #Seattle has never looked prettier. ❤️ #city #cityscape #downtown #sunset @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/7JEXPcZtIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so blessed and thankful for @Anthonyshane420 even though he can be a fuck at times, no one will ever have my back like he does ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHSMEETSAYA I got to see them in Chicago last year so my dream came true 💜 just wanted you to know how precious th… https://t.co/4C2A6wbwMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quienes me conocen saben que cada 8 de Marzo, desde hace muchos años, comparto este post con el fin de llevar a más… https://t.co/LCoHyHMPvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AndreaRamos_ Her recent is like 6 months I think she dropped out and she’s my age actually not yours so it’s prob… https://t.co/CYSIWnbUyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimnguynn I forgot my umbrella I’m coming back tomorrow to get it since it’s Lina’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b1k3man_773 @777089965g @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump Too bad for us he didn’t go😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeThangs @starwriterlv @missdarma @GlamourNMetal @Dinelle_Fuller someplace that isnt snowy and cold 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kological I don’t have blind spots or double standard like you. You are a wannabe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El tren. Los autos. La lluvia. La montaña. Todo perfecto. R580 https://t.co/QCt1vSWFFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leggings Styling Tips for Plus Size Women https://t.co/68IJjcdwcY #ChinaLeggings #ChinaLeggingsManufacturers… https://t.co/hHEiS0vJjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @LindseyGrahamSC you stand for nothing except protecting your scared a$$ from whatever they got on… https://t.co/440H235nuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJeromeTrammel @rkelly Now sashe’ away! In my #rupaulsdragrace voice 🙌🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words can’t describe the feeling I get when hearing “Don’t Wanna Be” thanks to OTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinstrasser SARS? I watch GH now. And loving @thejonlindstrom s/l. I’d need a #dool history lesson. I have missed seeing you on my tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcorr54 @fabulavancouver Yeah, I was looking up some reports and the increases seemed low in comparison. Ofc, aver… https://t.co/J5UnFEB3Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta delete this for a little bit, trying not to get out of character 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY, March 5th is our STEAM Night from 5:30 - 8:00 pm. Enjoy a family event with hands-on STEM activities. Free P… https://t.co/RPhIquTVFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news4buffalo The parents say they instill their values upon their kids; what values? Has anyone checked out the pa… https://t.co/J6cwggi1WW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is sad but he needs to condemn such behavior. Otherwise he’s condoning it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Children of God! Have a beautiful and productive day. 😘 https://t.co/jva6QytZLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish someone would have told me that it was okay to not be fine sometimes. Thanks to @TheBloggess for sharing t… https://t.co/1FGDnE4K04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between Douche Jr and Douche 3 there is barely a single brain cell. #Pendejos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in NYC @i_love_ny 🗽♥️ @ 34th Street–Penn Station https://t.co/H1m0U97975]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Black by Popular Demand’ SHIRTS ON SALE!! $15 due paying members, $20 non-due paying /staff. DM us for more info t… https://t.co/EwIL92MGT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earthtohaleigh I get the depo-shot (have since I was 15) at PB and I don’t pay anything with my state insurance. A… https://t.co/xUeBG9wffA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now abideth faith, hope, charity, these three; but the greatest of these is charity. 1 Corinth… https://t.co/Ox64O5r7aR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would’ve been a lovely tradition to start back in the day. Why did no one think to do that?       Ohhhhhhhhh]]></document></documents></author>