<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @galacticaactual @Krm1285A @tweets4poppy @CocoKAG @Bigbillshater @phnixus1 @roderunner01 @BenJackd1… https://t.co/zsCKoTrSak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intili_h @MsMollyRachael @ArdittoKime Looks like we may need to relocate that wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @PAStatePolice Forensic Unit for sharing the valuable work you do to fight crime. The @OctoraraLearns Hom… https://t.co/LXVb3LxoJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t he the hypocrite who believes Russia is paying Trump and Rohrabacher?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vrooommm I'm in heaven. The heads up display reminds me how badass it is. #manual #7speed https://t.co/raSuGbKes8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSeattleWeather After one hour @WaWxChasers @lbc_weather @BenjaminJurkovi @ https://t.co/rBBtanhOcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me n my lil guy tb4, thats my dog foreal, s/o my bros stitchedemxtixns  fir the dope gear @ AMC Movies In Columbia https://t.co/EOTlQQ5ehi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out at @Lutron HQ. Learning lots of cool things with the rest of my @Graybar colleagues. #LightingControls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since were all going to die in 12 years, no point in the Dems showing up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chill Out, Gary! Neighbor Goes Ballistic After Snow Lands On Property https://t.co/5H9nwyVql2 via @YouTube.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcsowriter @SparkleByMonica @sparwelten @BooksPromotion @Beterov1 @The1Shez @prochecksports @toddsparks1 @Spicy707… https://t.co/saraEM3i7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrooklynVIII Irritating af, no doubt. But at least you're not in Jussie's situation. 😉  https://t.co/FqhIiXxWvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Luka for the Mavs tonight, damn. Guess I'll find something else to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late post because I’m terrible at remembering the dates and always use this photo for reference. Booze free for 3 y… https://t.co/2tx1HKkeZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet on Brady to be the first to be nabbed in a prostitution and human trafficking ring. Dammit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Where did you dig up that poll? You will not be re-elected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dyeager14 getting us ready for a great day with great emerging leaders! https://t.co/QpNIDNeJ4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[White House vows to shed Obama-era policy of 'cowering' before North Korea ahead of second Trump-Kim summit  https://t.co/cWLXk5wkLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no... not again.    #Magrathia #lifetheuniverseandeverything #hgttg #hitchhikers #hitchhikersguidetothegalaxy… https://t.co/WbpHtTlgjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a reason Kyrie left Bron in the first place 🤦🏻‍♂️ @BraydenStarnes9 @cojack2323 @BrycenStarnes]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is overdue, but I am so glad to hear it now. Gentrification is what I mentioned to him when I shook his hand a… https://t.co/khqhoXS5Is]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾: Adam Echols opens the game with a single, but a pop fly and double play end the inning  Madison County - 0 Walnu… https://t.co/CLsG7KSvsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, @Ebron85, Shut The Fuck Up, You Sucked In Detroit…   https://t.co/6kiWYrsql8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate covered strawberries are a part of a balanced breakfast, right? Yeah, I thought so too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr @TheeJamesPond I’m proud of what you accomplished behind the wheel &amp; the way you conducted yourself. #ChildhoodHero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennylattimore #kennylattimore #kennylattimorelive @ Chrome Showroom https://t.co/bzHAABHTq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a loss in OT, @RStanleyNHL doing post game with @deannakaytv. #NHL19 #smashville https://t.co/MGskf07FPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked up hypocrite (see also ludicrous) in my thesaurus and found ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long overdue time w a great friend and leader. Thanks @larsleafblad!! To be continued. Soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyGraceffa @EscapeTheNight the flat tire was a scam this is a hint. there’s gonna be another season of escape the night 😭😭😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clscottfamily No worries I like them both man I wish we could keep them both. But I happy with CW man! They just asked my opinion man👊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got these awesome light up tip jars made. If your interested hit up boogieswoodworking   #jessedeestrada #dj… https://t.co/S1zsBQviyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slytherins in the basement of Hogwarts being the worst house https://t.co/q3pnwKDT4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pilar66429233 Muy buenos días Pilar y feliz viernes saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProTVSports @SliceOfSully @STEVEBURTONWBZ @NHLBruins Pepperoni please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLBlackhawks @mitchell_ness Watching the game from my barcalounger in buffalo ny..could use that shirt cause its freezing here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarikCyrilAmar @AviWoolf @egavactip @JYuter @JoshuaTCharles https://t.co/rXeC4lGpEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunkerGear_Gal I sure hope the tank is down low byt otherwise pretty sweet. Run it with a twin with big pumps for… https://t.co/1OtX2wg5at]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house @uofmemphis for @GovBillLee 's State of West Tennessee Address. Over 400 have shown up to be a part of… https://t.co/XxVUdXtfV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started #TheMaskedSinger on #Hulu. I really love the Bee! 🐝 https://t.co/RpIwFfWDjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, #SpikeLee never mentioned trump. LoL thats how we know he’s on the side of hate not love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@living_marble This is, conclusively, the only good idea on twitter dot com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catsnotababe “I wish I was born in a time when whites had more agency &amp; blacks couldn’t do anything :////“]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hungry for the #word https://t.co/p1ZbgBxIKb #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/jaPdElla4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods To have Hillary Clinton run again would be like manna from heaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uniradionoticia @CIAD_CONACYT @lhuesca @SoyUnison @ColSonora @victorspena Buenos días estupenda probadita.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetarotlady Well dang it. I went in search and found no such word exists in dictionary. com or google. CRAP I was… https://t.co/zqzRK6A6uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velocipietonne i'm miserable and trying not to fall asleep in my cereal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excelsior Bravo 👏🏽 felicidades señora una rata menos solo así vamos a combatir la delincuencia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey uh @THQNordic , I really like you guys and I'll support you, but this uh.....8chan thing....  Could you please… https://t.co/kFcPiuT61i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump Wasn't Hillary supposed to be in prison by now? Lol. That's right she is innocent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do like the idea of diverse Finals matchups, but one cluster field of 16 to get there isn’t for me. Especially wh… https://t.co/1DHInNHhE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Custom Shower Bench https://t.co/7NoXN2DvfQ via @Kennedy1724 #columbusgaluxuryrenovations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teens are now getting high off of vanilla extract.  😑😑 https://t.co/ebUwLIm28H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnapRaise_Juan @SnapRaise @PCreekbaseball @MCreekBaseball Thank you Juan!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KazzraCSGO @AFDeSports Hope they’ve done their FG research then and found some local help outside of my usual local teams with experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce Hornsby, The Range - Mandolin Rain https://t.co/azu88E9dQI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @CavinderHanna,  @CavinderHaley, and @wadebrynn for making 5A all conference teams this season!🏀… https://t.co/9Rg2PfDSCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonjour_jamie 1) Her family says reporting about her condition has been misleading. https://t.co/t6FsvmbVW7  2) Wh… https://t.co/vjT14WlN4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheapAssMTG Draw format doesn't mean that you draw 100% of the time. Just that, more often than not, you should ch… https://t.co/ATBzCJtqwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @WhiteHouse BPTH. Money #busy #CaptainMarvel #LANYINMNL2019DAY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our brothers and sisters at #CPD lost one of their own today. Please help out if you can...  #CopLife @ Hamilton Co… https://t.co/StU9o8dy7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diamonds and Triangles A view through a garden shed at Ringwood Manor in Ringwood, NJ. https://t.co/x7r0ark3p3… https://t.co/RSQlMlaRa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1868Weekly @BB_Brigade I'd like to point out @Reno1868FC remains winless in season openers. #facts #ForCounty… https://t.co/txkw8KxlZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castleberry: Transparency isn’t required by Amendment 100, despite the arguments made by those opposed to letters o… https://t.co/I3giigI21C]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFTER CAREFUL ANALYSIS THIS LEGAL CHRISTIAN MARRIAGE IS TOTALLY LEGAL AND CONSTITUTIONAL. BY THE WAY THE THEME OF T… https://t.co/O5Y67kHN8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SplitSeason1981 You’re welcome! It’s hard to find the right audience for that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was in H.S. his supporters stood outside DMVs. My dad told me they were “libertarians and don’t talk to them… https://t.co/t63j3VK0sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6 of 7 of my challenge from @ScottMirkesOHS   Mere Christianity   This book was eye opening for me in my faith… https://t.co/fsinXXHl1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Almagro_OEA2015 @OEA_oficial @pacoguerreroa65 @brendaindc @gerardodeicaza Solo confio en resultados de elecciones… https://t.co/VmNj0sgO0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bootsie5 @cent_new @JonStall2009 They say provocative things to try and put people on defense while they keep poun… https://t.co/S5ywOy4fSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the remix to ignition 🎵  This man’s going to prison 🎵  He’s throwing tantrums and crying in interviews on tele… https://t.co/ArrjwBuwam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes Or, here's a better idea: Improve public transportation options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickieStarxxx1 @freja_noir What a fucking moron! Tats are great and love to hear about plus I have a tad bit of a… https://t.co/6hXR5eZfPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardiBStats @DailyCardiB @iamcardib This was the best part of the Gram]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Felder didn’t fuck Vic up but I think he got the job done #UFCPhoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this age of Trump derangement syndrome, victimhood is the new street cred.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@occasionalell Math Blasters or Tonka Space Station might be your first but I figured those are too mainstream to be right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HankinsJocelyn Good for you kid.  You take shit load of victory laps in your life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The school district twitter page is averaging a new follower a second...it must be snowing... https://t.co/7PpXLWY8l5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatorsTF @AndrewSpiveyGC @FloridaGators @UF @SECNetwork @SEC @jbird_18 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[hockey picks were ok today 3 right 2 wrong i am i little late tonight and just doing my picks for feb.23 right now… https://t.co/GNoqZ7kc2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was fortunate to see @HamiltonMusical in Columbus on Sunday, and still have the songs looping in my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#strawberrydonut via @lacma @ C+M Coffee And Milk https://t.co/CLMvCxKhAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrB135 @RepAdamSchiff the  term is now used as a weapon not only by the political Left, but  also  by far too many… https://t.co/dmnWGrnwEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler I have nothing against liberals but the Democrats are no longer liberals in the tradition of JFK they… https://t.co/c5GT1Ey9nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m not 28 yet. Gotta wait til 10 am pst since I was born in Sacramento and I saw that in my birth certificate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosePaliza @PRM_Oficial Pacto eléctrico. ?  Para dejar firma en la constitución de un problema no resuelto por el… https://t.co/YL8ATaWrgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking time Away from twitter.I am emotionally drained anxiety gets the best of me.I have said more than I should.… https://t.co/tB2hAMSujm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning (@ Highland Park - @nycparks in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/9PHVCyf5pv https://t.co/SkaiFBn8zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom You might want to actually read the contract and the revised 2012 amendment.   Cali has violated the terms of the grant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me having a job while also wanting to  check out all the hate tweets I got from #Gators n #Canes this morning.… https://t.co/o55P9ewUez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je suis plus grand que ma maison!!! à Chicoutimi, Quebec https://t.co/TUzIJ4BfQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petershk @EpsilonTheory Nah, I've luckily been pretty happy most of my life. https://t.co/JE16nrucoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I forget the paper I needed to bring to the doctor concerning the refill on my Adderall that is suppose t… https://t.co/SCfX8C1JTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmmmmm  I guesss us ... never mind 🤦🏽‍♂️  #Survivor #SurvivorEdgeOfExtinction #Comeonjesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to start using my backup account. May make it my permanent account. May not accept everyone though. Follow me @mjm3763]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExpansionMx Se empieza a ver a México como una copia del gobierno chavista sin pies ni cabeza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are OUR  superpacs? Did our focus (Correctly so)  on aiding house candidates hurt us in fundraising for natio… https://t.co/qtgy6l9F4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dameshaw11 Yess even me the same and especially my family with the talent and gifts for real]]></document></documents></author>