<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I still gotta come up with about 25 more pairs of snow pants before Tuesday. 🤨 I can do this! It stinks to be calle… https://t.co/TDmdXWGKsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this college thing so stressful?!?! What even?!?!?   #Isabelleisnonexistentforthenext4years!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[he told me I reminded him of someone, Snooki from Jersey shore to be exact 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosewind2007 @Alyssa_Milano 👆🏻is hilarious rosewind. Hilarious. Stick your head back in the sand please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyMrBass @squiggsquigg This is all I can think about. https://t.co/i00IQyDbzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the weirdest things about wedding planning is you end up finding entire sites dedicated to porta potty decoration]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a wonderful 40th Birthday! Thank you to my friends and family for all the wishes! But the icing on the cake t… https://t.co/uW4x4N4u78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patriots, it looks like the Paradise, CA fire was to steal gold. Paradise has a gold mine underneath. A dew laser w… https://t.co/DMNoT8gLa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a new meaning for the term BACK-TO-BACK...  Georgia women's basketball coach gives birth less than 12 hours… https://t.co/WLOKzgaAmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#totalcardiofix✔️ TODAY IT TOTALLY 🦵 MY 🍑!!! But I am feeling great! It’s been a productive day! #trustingmyjourney… https://t.co/IlEMMJb8Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlramsdale_law I got home late and there were Hershey’s Kisses on my pillow. They get it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QMillz21 🌈🔥💥☄️⭐️🌟🌎🎡🎢🌋🚀⛽️🗽🗿🎯💎B E S S 🔮⚔️🦠🧬💊🧽🧬⭐️💦🤠👾💀S I C K O🤮🌡🔑⚰️🏺😈🐍🌪🎸F R I E N D🧩💣🧿🛀🏽⚜️🌀💤📕📆🧧🧼📸🦴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tigrayrocks @angelgirl1976 Vicky are there any events coming up next month that we could go to you go with you to? Can you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alysonfooter @Esther188rod  JUST NOW AT 80 YRS OLD ALYSON THANKS I NEVER CAUGHT IT  BEFORE HAVE A GREAT EVENING ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just came across my recipe for NC macaroni and cheese casserole. You are right @ShannonBream flowering dogwoods do… https://t.co/S2EqXMWZXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how there’s times I act like I’m in a relationship yet I dam well know I’m single 👀🤣💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers for common sense to rule the day. We need to secure our borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for this guy!! He’s been reposted by Will Smith &amp; Post Malone. My spirit animal. #MikeIsTheMan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me rn. “God done sitttin’ in heaven, he thought of every godamn thiiinnngggggg”]]></document><document><![CDATA[humor at it's best. OMG! these are hysterical! we have a ton of toy soliders around. Toy soliders for Valentines... https://t.co/CkgyLp9Oeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Waunakee, WI! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Inventory Receiver at Remed… https://t.co/ANFr1gxAcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Yoongi, one of the most talented and hardest work people! So much love sent his way! 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValeriaBrownEdu That kid’s teachers should feel great about his ability to differentiate between reliable and unre… https://t.co/WdLkUI6E7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendellGreer So I’m like oh shit I ain’t following her I best follow her back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, he's jelly. Oh, this is the perfect Joker plot. 😂😂 #Gotham #AceChemicals]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band is about to play their last song but The Tabernacle is nowhere near empty #JOUR3190 #RKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jowrotethis Is there a Rob Lowe thing? Please tell me there’s no Rob Lowe thing. I get the Aziz issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @realDonaldTrump This is fake and I never retweeted it!! Twitter!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You should have been there when it was NOT an Amazing place! And knowing how stupid you probably w… https://t.co/9l1PCUI0SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPD102Pct @NYPDONeill @NYPDQueensSouth @NYPDnews @NYCPDDEA Rest In Peace! 🙏💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed I’m missing daughters tonight. Please come back around to LA! 😭 https://t.co/KXa4tEYxYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can hear dial-up internet sounds floating through my office space and I’m not sure what that means. Is this someo… https://t.co/bNLUYLREiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you liv!!! ur the best friend I could ever ask for, I love you too💙💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you check out YouVisit? I’m finding schools don’t know how to promote their virtual tours when very few people… https://t.co/kA9DMvtjwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a a GAB invite @intheMatrixxx @Jordan_Sather_ @prayingmedic @ThePatriotHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bromanconsul @DrunkestLibrary I just need a small mouse. I’m not that great at my job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally love my dentist, all the ladies were ordering coffee and insisted I get one bc Doc was buying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuppaaEvelyyn We ready for the NC adventures 🏆 https://t.co/CU1MB7zGSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We'll be closed today March 10 between 3pm-5pm for a private party! https://t.co/wDtvWgHYz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome sermon this weekend @RevAdamHamilton . Looking forward to next Sunday's sermon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mplsmike_d Thanks! Weird that your car is the listening environment you hear it - I’d expect headphones to provide more detail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny how when anyone tells me things now i immediately assume its bullshit. sorry but i have an constant internali… https://t.co/R55x29AO8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking HATE the fucking post office. Fucking nasty ass pieces of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope you had fun while your bored lying immature ass lasted. girl byyeeeee :))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greysaddicted4 @gopogo12 @OneDayAtATime @everythingloria @netflix Nice!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Logan0291 @MavenOfMayhem Logan🇨🇦, thank you!!!! These are the pins that I do. My website is… https://t.co/8Iw3r0ngck]]></document><document><![CDATA[If parties were like this&gt; I went to school with to many rich kids to not have experience one of these 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelMcMahan Catch me looking really skinny the next two days then !😘 might have the crumb I saved for later for a light snack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrispychicken3 @jakequery @Schultz975 If that happens, then I demand to come in-studio to talk about 80s bands and boobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherTDay Wait so I  get to sit in a quiet room by myself? No kids? No dirty house? No laundry? vs. electric sho… https://t.co/OoOPGAv2XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to deliver these handmade journals/sketchbooks that Art Club students created for the Children’s Attention… https://t.co/dYBFpidOiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyCliff @TradeMark297 @THC_Junior @sjgolf891 Is it illegal for people hire lawyers to sue for slander.  Threa… https://t.co/LYL1ifwYfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every bride deserves to feel like a queen on her wedding day! Our designs are guaranteed to to just that! Photo the… https://t.co/R0kQd7H0nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonLionFineArt @grandmatojosie1 @SpeakerPelosi @sfpelosi @TeamPelosi Extremely talented.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daishen’s 🏀 IQ is off the charts — his court vision is STELLAR — if you haven’t seen him play in person you better… https://t.co/uryrCi3ISJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular sports TV opinion: I HATE hero shots when play is live. I don't need a close up on whoever scored running… https://t.co/80fmITZtEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright ima delete all my social media wxcept my finsta so if u don’t have me on that bye i’m #cancelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here just thinking... I went from foster care to being one of the, if not the, first black training manager… https://t.co/ZRivElSP16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLAMonline No it’s not! They get paid millions of dollars. Fans spends hundreds of dollars to see them! It’s too m… https://t.co/yvBB46CsbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @HallieJackson @PressSec totally ran out  of excuses, so just flailing away there.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[The very fact that supposedly reputable news organizations use the juvenile term ..and derogatory in nature...… https://t.co/tasqERGCwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaCharles88 YES! Philly is the best place to be a postdoc. Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When there's a lot of love there, there's always a path and possibility towards healing.  I really, really want t… https://t.co/iGTXA1ozdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[???? People associated with the Clinton’s almost always “kill themselves.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So honored to be chosen as one of the 2019 @QueenBeeHalf Ambassadors!👸🏻🐝Excited to work with this amazing group for… https://t.co/BpL2iax549]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna know how long my phone has accidentally been on airplane mode for LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically, "Baby Santa" is the favorite Christmas song of my three year old twins! #laughter #chuckle #grin #cute https://t.co/q5eocxaV0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm super hella Excited!!! I just made my brand new furniture purchases at #AaronsFurnitureStore!!! They get delive… https://t.co/lvQpuDkguW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be on this panel to tackle this important issue. Keeping kids safe and making sure they feel seen, heard… https://t.co/4YKwnnDNr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it highly disrespectful that I have yet to have some sweet shit like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whodidthis 😂😂😂 #lol #timallen #eminem #slimshady #timshady #timinem #random #randompost #subday @ Anaheim, Califor… https://t.co/oIRJTSTBrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterGleick @HarriHaanpaa @KHayhoe @DoctorVive @FrediOtto @SISeneviratne Sorry but that’s not the issue. More than… https://t.co/ab5PPqt9PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @LincolnOPS misses you too Sun Commercial! HEY KIDS JOIN STUDENT PUBLICATIONS BECAUSE @GayleRobbins MISSES US. https://t.co/3tPMhOai78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriguyHFX @CBCNews Did you check with Dexter? @SHO_Dexter https://t.co/GNpvp33EIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans I had a dream we were hanging out at the @hauntedmuseum .. I didn’t want to wake up 😖 wahh https://t.co/5JlnvTMXra]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fertsquirt19 will definitely be used heavily come growing season '19 💦💦💦😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of times my dog has heard me say “Yuh” to myself is embarrassing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justincholbrook @SonjaSantelises @BaltCitySchools @Owl_b_TorresEdu @Leanne728 @MarkLewisLUM @raleshevich… https://t.co/IoTSvj8PMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supremely excited to have #timeisthekiller on #TheCaseAgainstAdnanSyed @RainJPhoenix ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me bañe como marimar ya que la japac aun no arregla el tubo 😤 y soy una de las afortunadas 90 colonias sin agua...!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have been able to work with two of my former Captains! It never gets old hearing praise regarding “my… https://t.co/e9r1gwE023]]></document><document><![CDATA[So damn heartbreaking!! And irresponsible humans are the ones at fault!! This poor baby needs his earth angel to re… https://t.co/zPtJDXpxdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chloe was nice and shared her cold. I can't sleep, mind's racing. Decided to reorganize Christmas stuff... we have… https://t.co/Ufeefbs6eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bailee sprayed my brunette dry shampoo onto her hands then rubbed it all over her face. She genuinely looked like she had a 5oclock shadow 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very exciting opportunity for our #OCSB Student participants! #ocsbdl #partnerships #ocsbBeCommunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElisaSDavis @jbfc_ny I saw it yesterday and loved it. I am a big fan of The Lives of Others so I was curious about… https://t.co/uzecqCgJ3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhaliMac Lmao! For the record: I was in a different room and thought you were joking about ACTUALLY breaking your toe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The JB's - Doing It To Death https://t.co/2Tf15SMH7l via @YouTube: James Brown: “Doing it to Death:” The Sounds of Blackness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#neflscottishhighlandgames #CaberToss #PureStrength https://t.co/nEFRyGkjis]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd grade studied how Native American groups adapted to their environments. It’s time to present design projects on… https://t.co/vkc1BbgOwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know I’ve been helpful to others and/or made a difference in someone’s day each day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[so my phone auto updated last night and i lost hundreds of my photos... anyone know how i can get them back or am i just screwed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emporbooty @RedQueenRising @EmilyGorcenski @Donna048 @I8uridea4brekki @BrokeNotWoke1 @helenstaniland https://t.co/5i8Fu3vIjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I got a rejection letter from a guy in music. For a work gig. I laughed. #greattiming #HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should probably save this for morning,but anyway Good Morning!  Enjoy this rt of a girl doing her dance]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOMELESS...  HAS BECOME AN EPIDEMIC IN US.....  Highest VOLUMES ARE DEMOCRAT RAN STATES( DONT VOTE DEMOCRAT)  WHY..… https://t.co/0DXd7x4DQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Esoterics_ It isn’t your boyfriends job to make you feel good ab yourself though...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope @JTark3 gets a postdoc in Chicago cause honestly that was the city that most resonated with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz Hearing you're thinking of voting against POTUS on wall, hoping you're not so foolish to do so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberthrush @SnezanaJevticBg Good. They made it to the water away from that pesky crow or raven.]]></document></documents></author>