<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[MY ROLLIE DON’T TICK TOCK but it’s because I think it’s broken. Been wearing it strictly for show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @realDonaldTrump Trump is the most powerful man in the world.  Why can’t he have McCabe arrested?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChloeNooga Does the #NOOGAtoday have a print edition or is it all online. #Chattanooga #nooga]]></document><document><![CDATA[AW HELL YEAH! WERE GETTING HIM DURING CONCACAF! I KNEW ALI COULD DO IT! #GloryGloryTorontoFC #TFCLive #Pozuelo… https://t.co/QKVkWm1bo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bauer's 66 1/2 Grill &amp; Skillet in Modesto, CA https://t.co/UJfGPTV1le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joesaward Joe, they say these are the best drivers in the world.  .....and I have a full assortment of large bridges for sale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[12. As always, it’s all in good fun with tongue in cheek. 😎 🎷 🎶  THE END.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teddy Pendergass was that nigga. Don’t you ever think else in your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckessinger65 @MizzouSoftball Thanks Cory - I’ll be back before y’all know I’m gone. #SECspeed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightningVacc The words of a whore. Maybe give up being pompous as well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackFord @thinkprogress So if LGTQ is a religion, do I get tax exempt status when I buy stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @GOP I'm glad you asked that question. Because every time I read a tweet from a member of the GOP c… https://t.co/XArqRRpm6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glowlikeleroy Me going to my bag on water break and grabbing a Pepsi https://t.co/J4MjAf4wTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The late 80's were perfect for those awkward family photos.... #throwbackthursday @ Easton, Pennsylvania https://t.co/rYRT1rfFS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nature  checking each other out.  #deer @ Amelia, Ohio https://t.co/Kt2aZBHPcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that my taste in music is so diverse! One second I’m bumping chente then switch up to country then to banda… https://t.co/vynxNdcD0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many @GhostAdventures fans think @Zak_Bagans should do his own reality show? @Zak_Bagans you should do a realit… https://t.co/evDeS2gFvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Till we meet again, @WhatRUTinkin.  Will always keep the memory of going to a Brewer game and meeting @PaulDier.  Was a great day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paris__G Good morning Paris! Is there going to be a Spring this year? 😳😂😭 https://t.co/RhaHDt1Qyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Thank you Sarah for putting up with the thoughtless comments from the media and tweeters… https://t.co/jwGKL6MECf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianmele @jillianmele Hey..Good Morning and Happy Friday! Great job on   @FoxFriendsFirst @foxandfriends and… https://t.co/kLXBk5vjeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow because he knew you were stupid and would give it all away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@composerose Yeah I went to some unofficial stuff... but like I know there’s a screening of “Us” here and I don’t k… https://t.co/7Y4BdJpljq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a retired city police officer, 70 years old... He killed my dad...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#conflict and #climate risks and economic uncertainties arising in recent years threaten our ability to progress to… https://t.co/MqGLc8aZPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulldogSenn officially ends their season losing in the IHSA first round playoffs to @NilesWestHoops 91-53 https://t.co/0kvr8vkCbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@666MEGAWATTS I was too old to get into that by the time it got popular so I didn’t even watch it haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hoppy White Wheat by @BreckBrew at @theviewhouse — https://t.co/mHAJQgrDxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up never knowing this wasnt a common experience for all Americans.   (The first time I saw the macys parade… https://t.co/6aMvua1G6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball also uses its farm system to actively not pay some of its best players for a very very long time. Don’t gi… https://t.co/HGgxxIlTrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so focused on recording for TMF and practicing on excerpts most of last week that I completely forgot to look… https://t.co/CtHRpmR5PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packing up Chroma Paintings headed to Washington DC. #coporate #corporatecollection #washingtondc #nationscapital… https://t.co/Xi3e199L63]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally just started rewatching twin peaks 30 minutes ago, I checked twitter during a bathroom break and have s… https://t.co/9Yjhf7v7BJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slideshow: A Visual Guide to Atrial Fibrillation https://t.co/yiPHEiz9aw  from @WebMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Night with 2 points is a great night!!! #JoinOrDie PLAYOFFS!!! @BarstoolChief]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinskyleigh Alpha meet X-man Orange Omega. His special power is the ability to manifest the 7 Deadly Sins at will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me being confused when ppl called me a fag in preschool cuz I already knew I was a girl https://t.co/StIU3Oa8Pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀I take this as Gronk definitely coming back if he’s going to work out with Tommy!!!!😊😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most major California reservoirs are near or significantly above their historical averages as of midnight, 10-March… https://t.co/gV7R0R3FQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvnelson @mitchieforshort @hnnhjey That’s pretty affordable. I think I have to do it. Lol and since we’re here...… https://t.co/yWNjoF9Hhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else feel hungover with this time change? These are getting harder and harder to adjust to. #timechangesucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We’re happy for you, Don. Of course the Republican Party isn’t what it used to be now is it?… https://t.co/ek0ARLqhsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF for some reason Zion doesn’t play Saturday he doesn’t deserve to be Player of the Year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[what inept signature is this? It’s a fucking microwave. Art of the English language my ass. Dolt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this.  Perhaps we can squeeze something in tomorrow? 🤔 #relationshipsmatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela blackout will have lasting impacts. For example , Venezuela lost almost all of its present industrial alu… https://t.co/FvAubX9w2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad god invited those things called drugs. 🤪 I’m in real pain tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dogturd3 @catturd2 How so?  Prove it, because this Cat has a huge head start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catalina03Anna Sooo good, now give her Thanos!!! https://t.co/fDDafzLDBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willwilkinson Do you think that electing Lincoln President was a bad idea because it made enemies out of people mo… https://t.co/A7n3KuVrKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speedfreak228 @AR72014 Mine has never had any of those issues lol. Just as smooth as every single iPhone I’ve had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrabant3 Washed up alright, sorry for the misspell... you won anything lately? How many games you play, any points in the big leagues?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theryanmichael What he did during that era was incredible. No one came near his numbers. I wonder how he would have done on the Niners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[dis nigga was doin roids while he was in miami. they did a study and the side affects include balding (ik yall senn… https://t.co/2HPrYIKBH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATTCares I attempted to make a payment via bank draft 2/6. The system said there was an error so i paid by debit c… https://t.co/82So2Ajh5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bullshit is now on the democrats plate. The Senate is crrrently investigating the origins of the Fake Russian d… https://t.co/zqXeeSPl0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my sister comes home and we can kick it. S/O to #SoOakland for putting on an excellent event @ Oakland,… https://t.co/VFK8qKy3nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bingham beats Copper Hills 46-41 for Class 6A girls’ basketball state championship, via @sltrib https://t.co/ols7ObxvbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't wanna work! I just want to bang on the drum all day! #PresidentsDay https://t.co/JGX4FWEzc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this edition of Thursday Night Tailgate with our guests: @LeonardMarsha70 @tonycollinsbwyb… https://t.co/1yncRvVIxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cville_Sports @RossviewHoops Wilson Central vs. Lebanon at 6 Monday. Second straight year 9-AAA sweeps first round of region.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put you in the flyest gear and make sure you alright! Only if you promise girl you try no games 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell someone “I wish you nothing but the best” that means we’re done, it’s over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodzillasHeart @LifeLesson617 @iLnatyy Y’all started, don’t blame Lance  🤣🤷🏾‍♂️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_juel @merovingian2069 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump I think you’re confused.  President Donald Trump is a l… https://t.co/W230wTQgYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kansailarkin @freedomisok @jondutoit @Cernovich @StefanMolyneux for some background, I was their DP, who didn’t ha… https://t.co/kkcZ8G3xKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's what happens when a puppet follows a dictatorship. You are in office and acting like your daddy will not wor… https://t.co/vQubzhyLc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who ever has me make a wedding cake for them from now on will need to agree to these being the cake toppers.… https://t.co/oNt1NKRJfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's that time of year again in #Indiana where we play Drunk or Dodging Please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joel Embiid is currently speaking to the media here in Philadelphia.  Said that his absence over the past 10 days i… https://t.co/TlwWrTTo22]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBK: Congrats to our Northeast Inland All-District AP selections @zachgeiser5, @Cline3_JJ and @KingDomer21 #TDR https://t.co/3lvxOiHjSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEPCOT Here is everything I have on Lighthouse Point. I think the key difference here is the location isn’t an is… https://t.co/S6BU7C4rDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferjo1977 @ArbraEden Ok, but that’s not what the call for service indicated. It’s not like cops were just in… https://t.co/1iVOl8onDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooksyFL @DAWNIEB @jrdup21  Follow Logan Brown Catcher Atlanta Braves Needs new gear for Spring Trainning 2019. A… https://t.co/1nCD18tH9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo lo que siempre has querido esta al otro lado del miedo.  -George Adair  #sugarmill #california #wine en The… https://t.co/OM0idBEAjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet maple and malty aromas and flavors. With a English note. Smooth and tasty. - Drinking a Maplechusetts by… https://t.co/5XJYjpRo9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Synaptic Misfire by Cliffside Brewing @ Cliffside Brewing — https://t.co/naSu6UoSDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ 🖤Repost @HFRmovement ・・・ The dots will connect. People are watching even if they don’t say a word, like a photo… https://t.co/IVqg4BrhfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, to be quite frank I enjoy dunking on the olds both in real life on the basketball court and in the tweet-o-… https://t.co/wcMPsq8RP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamstue Because Berube seldom, if ever, announces the starter the day before the game. And - Allen has been playing well in past 3 starts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Não é fácil e demora, mas é necessário. Quanto mais jovem tu começar mais fácil será.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaWSB @wsbtv Don’t worry, they’ll go to the Roach Motel and those numbers will start to rise again! #stinkbugluv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJ_GIA Valid points, but don’t you think she’s going to get one hell of a contract here real soon after this tournament? I do..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved it like always @daniellaperkins @AmarrWooten @owenjoyner @dibenedettolexi @savannahlmay @IamLilimar… https://t.co/6TiwZvg6cB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having lots of problems with websockets today, and it’s more from just configuring Apollo + RxJS to play nicely]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penelope7usa @AnnCoulter Democrats believe in change for change’s sake , i.e. we should scrap everything that the… https://t.co/bT1R2bWCtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yula_ro @haveibeenpwned @1Password Can't remember when I last did either but I was sharing more for other people t… https://t.co/jxp93C7AVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XRobsPunchinBag Has your favorite actress in her second movie! (was filmed after, but released before her first) 😂 https://t.co/kZ8khFZxUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we look back on our lives, will we remember the things that we got?  Or will we cherish the magic moments and… https://t.co/aRqGhwlssL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nyquist getting the exact same return as Zuccarello and everyone is losing their minds not sure what you expected f… https://t.co/iiSAySAyDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anyone in the world supporting @pets DUMBASS during this absolute PR nightmare?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @EMluvsPibbles @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/pLqNCxXAvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlayZeKyriarchy @unicode Good question, there's this existing petition, and I'm not sure how/if @Unicode takes in… https://t.co/E8B6tfuQDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast...  Choose to LIVE... YOUR CHOICE... 🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️… https://t.co/OmdFFG8y0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo somebody is feeling SASSY af today on this app https://t.co/OQxpQ0u17S]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK: Dalton vs East Canton update #NorwayneDistrict #TDR https://t.co/4r79ORXntx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waconia3 @deaconcruise @WeStandWithEvan @MrsPerrin @desertdave2012 @Regan0002112 @HSchouten @MarilynCapps… https://t.co/yYWHTWFDVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobandtom Tom needs to dress up like Gerald Ford, so he can trip on the airplane stairs. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougdirt24 For whatever reason Cody doesn’t have the right “stuff” to be a starter. Just leave him in the bullpen… https://t.co/HKTWkV5tWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMelendezCelis @aaronsalomong BUENA DECISIÓN ESPEREMOS NO TE VAYAS CON LOS CAVIARES DE GINO COSTA]]></document></documents></author>