<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HollandTaylor @MsSarahPaulson Writing a memoir w original music.  I'm gonna change the world and help abused child… https://t.co/xWPz4Bri9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum Oh! Terry! How absolutely fabulous! Your child mist ne so thrilled getting verification of their t… https://t.co/gPFACqTWyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zyanyamelo @NoFascistLies @drewcatmorris @jjz1600 Speak the truth, Melo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzzfeed’s @peretti - we have ever been more connected and yet feel so divided #SXSW2019 https://t.co/95XSIOG4Pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dKAYsDays I keep hearing people say how great he is but I just hear a Biden/Bernie platform coming from a younger… https://t.co/alSkM07vtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @skyboy123 @FoxNews Stormy should sue fox too, obstruction of justice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that this morning’s sunrise does not define itself by last night’s sunset.  ― Stave Maraboli So... "Rise u… https://t.co/3p4IvtC8Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Explícame porqué me levanté después de tres horas, mi nap era de 20 minutos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got some time to actually celebrate valentine's day with the homie 💘 #q45..#chilis @ Chili's Grill &amp; Bar https://t.co/WjXgtQPpbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband and I said the same thing at the conclusion of the Chicago PD press briefer.  Plus the Police Superinten… https://t.co/oH2m1bskGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm guessing back then, he didn't have persons of color in his family and friends circle or at least wasn't thinkin… https://t.co/lyzaMmbvCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a bubble on a cold day. #bubblelift #skitheeast #itsokemotime @ Okemo Summit https://t.co/TRcu5nPro1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Следующее фото - апогей. 2.2 унции. 2.2 УНЦИИ, КАРЛ!!!  Наверное, они количество травы делили на 10 под травой, так… https://t.co/LtTpnIqAc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What is the consistency with which it's being implemented from school to school within a district, and within the… https://t.co/TJ2NZaHelN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RallySXSW The world would be healthier if...We got our kids vaccinated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a nightmare about high school and what seemed like the apocalypse, woke up feeling like I attempted to run a ma… https://t.co/YdJwApffVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/Tbk0m37w7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙄 I don’t like barbecue so I’m not shamed that I am only familiar with less than 5 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Constitutionally elected not stole 2016 ones as all Congress knows and is in… https://t.co/0x8aez8GQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manthatsbruce Lmfao bruh they be asking if I’m Jamaican or Nigerian cause when I be like “I got 3 jobs” they be li… https://t.co/VGNQ5wB6lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m adoring the little flower animation that pops up when you heart a post with #Valentine 😍I purposefully sought o… https://t.co/j6GeUJJ7v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve: I love you Me: love you too babe Steve: I love pub subs too  #supportivesteve]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realize that the thing you thought was an amazing ORIGINAL idea has already been done https://t.co/4HO8kswOo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week was such an emotional roller coaster for me to only realize how blessed I truly am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zbranner70 Can't wait to see you!!! 💜 Kick some booty, have fun, and keep grinding!!! 💜 LOVE YA BUNCHES!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream compliment would be “that was so funny that one time you were so funny on SNL”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLenaG @jdillardwright Yes! There was so much positive energy in that room yesterday ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️Thank you for comi… https://t.co/nkK6iCNJwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly She’s not very good at her verbal skills either😂 ahh ahh ahhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @morningmika @Morning_Joe where is candidate @marwilliamson ? #Marianne2020 https://t.co/nTzo1uaPAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobMayeda This warm air is heavenly, such a tropical feel to this storm 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happytuesday😊 #stluciecounty #portstlucie #homeforsale #realestateagent #realestate @ Port Saint Lucie, Florida https://t.co/XdTgWKszfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for tomorrow at 1:50 pm as I walk out of Craig-Lee and STEP tf off ric campus for a whole week. I need this spring break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to wear a full face of makeup on an international flight? Flight attendants do a lot more than serve drin… https://t.co/glRoCjXjnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatDoneyNBC5 Your positivity is a great reminder for all of us, Pat. Thank you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump stop supporting the NRA if you really care about Parkland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Textearle al novio “amor te hice cena” y pum enviarle una foto de la QK depilada y mojada y adicionarle “carnita su… https://t.co/cSyiCsPJ57]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t have any time to be wasting. So you either with it or you not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @BMahmarian @IlhanMN the Gov't during that massacre in El Salvador was a dictator military group called Ju… https://t.co/9F9PxUkOmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @SenateGOP So much for the oath you took to defend the U.S. Constitution. Are you pussywhipped wusses… https://t.co/yLnRO4VOuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ante el ataque y arresto del reportero de @elnorte emite la Red de Periodistas del Noreste y la Asociación Estatal… https://t.co/F7OU9FMuPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if it’s lunch time and there’s a Golden Corral within a 30 mile radius you can bet on that too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comment a rapper that’ll kill this!🤔🤷🏾‍♂️🔥 . . ✅Download this beat “PORT OF MIAMI” today! Click the link in the bio… https://t.co/em6x2jKzGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank goodness the ☀️ is going down !!! It was a hot one compared to our #weather Monday in the 210 !!! #dragracing https://t.co/1ib4g2Hvl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Monday Morning! There’s a new traffic system to learn here at @KDKA, but @CelinaPompeani left thorough notes.… https://t.co/v92wPfMXJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Duck was poppin in Kingdom Hearts though, he was a gangster ass duck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldMasterGamin It’s not my favorite because I feel it takes too much of the coffee flavor away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I I love this song to you sweetheart I will buy camping I love all your songs you can't make a bad song sweetie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @tattoo_ryan at sanctuarytattoo207 I have an amazing new hand tattoo. I absolutely love it and couldn't b… https://t.co/Tt5kwM5FZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digitalcloudgal @TechWorldsHalf @laurenmaille @LornaGarey @TechnyGal @TamaraMcCleary @khalihenderson @JolaBurnett… https://t.co/bNKtR3ix6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @BernieSanders wins the election next year I'll be very happy and my faith in humanity will be restored]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm too the point that I'm seeing ppl true colors.....if u like cool if you dont plz dont bother with me....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K3ZLYN @Kat_Travino It would be so funny Sanem provide the bed sheets for rope 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jhanedouze Ah!!!!nou mèt dil sa nou vle, Jomo pa lach menm jan ak Titide non! Enmweyyy nou mele 🙆🏾‍♀️🙆🏾‍♀️🙆🏾‍♀️… https://t.co/70LtEP9t6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine we’re all barbies in someone’s bigg ass play room and we don’t even know we’re being controlled, when ur sl… https://t.co/EA4Pjy2AnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runningdogwood @KamalaHarris Absolutely nothing Tracie. Because every cent you earn would go to “free” healthcare… https://t.co/isdV8815Cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i've had a lot of people who have enjoyed the few songs i've put up ask me why i don't release music anymore. it's… https://t.co/qJmfhF9vOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelDazeco I had the same thing happen one morning! I was so embarrassed. I was told later that some establishme… https://t.co/5n0BsdQn1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinivanAdv Your welcome!!! I'm trying to remember that my attitude is all my doing. 😄😄😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThatSkyTho #EveningSky #CloudsIllusions #FederalHill #InnerHarbor #BlessedInBmore @ Christ Church Harbor Apartment… https://t.co/tRMSIosJAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse Italy just had a Parade dedicated to Trump. Europe loves him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stew1453 @nytimes I used to get sexual notes in school from unwanted males.  Same as sexting...except on paper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWImpalaOwner @ItsSam1983 Mmhmmmm what if say said something like idk oh you need to fly for the next case]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetsyDeVosED @POTUS Just how are you protecting our most vulnerable students by funding schools with my tax money… https://t.co/3xmnkK6mgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard for me to face people from high school when they remember me and I cannot really remember what I did last… https://t.co/m6Q97me7Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first ever @folkalliance showcase was fantastic! Thank you @musicontario and @ottawamic for putting together suc… https://t.co/yC0FsMUNEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have soo much stress I’ve had a migraine since Saturday... yay college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: don’t sign up to play travel hockey if you don’t want to travel or commit to ALL of your games. Freaking sick… https://t.co/CiCgcbKZ88]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belters are a big player in the Solar System after saving everybody’s ass.  Woohoo. #expanse https://t.co/1OflZ8gOeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Holden crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 02:01:47, pace 09:37 min/mile, est. finish 9:32 am https://t.co/96fbNxWeeP #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyChannel plays all these movies like beauty and the beast and stuff but never The Little Mermaid 🧜🏽‍♀️ 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[si se humillare mi pueblo, sobre el cual mi nombre es invocado, y oraren, y buscaren mi rostro, y se convirtieren d… https://t.co/vqkaezVvxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackintel1 We had only 1 grocery store in our town We would have to drive 30 minutes to go somewhere else that st… https://t.co/6mcdRmWeLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it might be possible to have imposter syndrome and not realize it right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise to whomever started this sing- along. Someday it’s bound to be me (if it hasn’t been already). #Robyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auroberjo Paul’s Pastry shop sells them year round in case you go into withdrawal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TJ Tacos... (@ The @ScoreboardName in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/4Uf3HI2I7E https://t.co/yAMbwkqwx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really was one of the most fun I had in the Stu since arriving in L.A! ☺️ Thanks for having me @BrookDLeau ❤️ https://t.co/oCzLN0aZ9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been weeks since dean cut a real promo and i’m dyingggg to know what’s going on in his head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newtral @UniNoticias @jorgeramosnews Eres un perrito bien ana steadily de la oligarquía @jorgeramosnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremySoers I can’t, either!  Someone mentioned coffee &amp; pizza..can’t do it.  I think I’m skipping lent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[January 26, 2018 was the best day of my life but that’s about to be replaced by May 18, 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was walking on the sidewalk and a man said “ on ur right” so he can pass and he took me by absolute surprise so I… https://t.co/SfXDEFj2Cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s @regallakeland starting lineup will be paying tribute to @flamengo and the families who lost their love o… https://t.co/0DYK0XGe59]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 3 Common planning times and meeting times 3 to 4 times a week. Teachers need time for conversations, gathering fe… https://t.co/6O9K59dpZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[been spending so much $ it’s making my stomach hurt . Look me up under compulsive shopper 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksucats85 @larryelder @JussieSmollett @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker They have no thoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer It might be a good day to have Panera or a pizza delivered]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donnie Wahlberg On The Making Of New Kids On The Block’s Video For “Boys... https://t.co/EohqjGMnqv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry mama i can't turn the other cheek, they wanna knock me off the edge like a fuckin widow's peak]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in Tolland or a neighboring community, TFD would love some follows.  Only need 5 more to get to 2,500. T… https://t.co/AzqNeiAhFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARESH_22 @SarahJazz17 @AnnaCAAlves17 @jill_magnussen @RoseThompson29 @Lucyalmeidas @CamillyVanovich @pkamla1… https://t.co/Xw5zczZMEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC That is the kind of judge who would say, "there were very fine people on both sides".]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚧Con Sue Photography and Design🚧  🚧Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚧  🚧This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/iygLzdfjNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to celebrate Virtual Education Day in Texas with @PSO_Texas #ITrustParents #schoolchoice https://t.co/aNPInT396L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poweranddivine @marwilliamson I don’t think the corporations that sponsor the news shows (via commercials) would b… https://t.co/ye8ORRR5C6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_HolySmokes 2 incomes is better than one y’all like basically married 😭😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screw that! Sunlight is the best disinfectant! These victims deserve this, at least this! Screw Alan! Not one word… https://t.co/UEzO79UJfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarsonhq @brielarson @captainmarvel The week the film opens ❤️ will be at https://t.co/UFgHDimm8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok world I got an extra code for @Doki_R6 so you all can stop blocking him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Gods is back today. Aka a so-so-show-I-have-to-watch-because-the-book-was-EPIC. Very ok w/ it. @americangodsus]]></document></documents></author>