<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DailyCaller Then let’s get the damn thing up before the demorats yank the money out of his hands and… https://t.co/qQdzUQTVrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire An icon? I had never heard of Jussie Smollett until the day of the attack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[...Even medical procedures can't keep me away. I had an endoscopy and I was volunteering for kids that night. I had… https://t.co/tM3vK35hjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing stresses me more in medicine than renal physiology. Here today, gone tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you or someone you know is considering suicide, please contact the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800… https://t.co/E133LddfIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuaweiFacts People like me that use  independent research from the internet appreciate hearing non US sources repo… https://t.co/PSb2mc2NB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamtheBullFAN with Bauer a free agent after next year, they should probably trade him because you can't afford to… https://t.co/n8pOoC4YPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is cute. SHOE QUOTES - or cartoons in this case - Red Soles Rule! - #Fashion #Quotes #NICCI... https://t.co/KUp8jNn1Xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[IU Definitely has a chance to make the tournament.  The NIT tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGoldwater @markpoloncarz @NYSEandG 100% what you said. It wasn’t that windy, their equipment should be able to handle this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww shit the plot thickens😩😩😩😩😩😩🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/3ACAxfuSuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmegsterr @Tanner_Joyner21 i’m literally so drunk hi who are u again i’m squinting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's my report on @Southwest_MBB's 88-58 rout of @CoxMill_Bball in the NCHSAA Class 3-A West Regional final, with… https://t.co/iFjF9SJ48V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to @EKConsulting @EKBranden - what a great week for you to start with us! https://t.co/crXSKPdfSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO imagine not being able to make the playoffs with lebron on your team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcrom1 @smittygrrl My great, great grandfather died while fighting to end slavery. He was shot in the left should… https://t.co/JUGkVyRS4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVatWork @OtherFBallPod @QuakesEpicenter @ColinEtnire @ChrisWondo @MLS @Magnum702 Put me down as SHOCKED this article would defend Wondo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nine2stein @felixpotvin Don't have a 2014 Classic yet, sadly. Will get one eventually.  I don't have Mo because my… https://t.co/VBWacH2ddm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ad_tommo I’m so sorry to hear this. It saddens me of the loss to your family. But, she is no longer in pain and sh… https://t.co/kYvn4UOO36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out WORLD here comes Shaniya Perry!!!!! So happy to be mentoring and coaching this beautiful young lady! She… https://t.co/LiMb0VtZjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good choices @TheOGc1 Richmond is going in with some energy, attitude and fire🏀🏀🏀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a plan and everything, I’ll create a brand like no other. I’ll partner myself with the Goats @KidCudi… https://t.co/7bFEmWlFMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awh I have tons and tons of pictures with my brother Lucas, I love how we’re soo close. I wouldn’t want it any other way. 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD1 Honestly wish I can do that, friend. Most I can do is work via Facebook Messenger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadmoiselleClel Actually I'd be interested in trade and narrative NF. Up for a discussion? Marcgris@gmail.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, even though it was all a little shady, I can get behind this logic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedoghouse47 Agree ! Iran not to be taking lithely and they know this other wise they will with the Israelis went… https://t.co/36SsTAq7KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mal influenciar a mis amigos para que gasten la misma cantidad de dinero que yo en pendejadas pa no sentirme mal cc @guzman_rober4 😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg can we _please_ start having basic moderation in group meetings??! Being active in politics I got used to “Robe… https://t.co/0Nse0OWlhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wisconsin-Milwaukee get two runs back in the top of the 5th inning to cut Arizona’s lead to 6-3.  Labaut has given… https://t.co/sqI5qDMG77]]></document><document><![CDATA[▫️▫️▫️▫️▫️▫️▫️▫️▫️▫▫▫▫▫▫ #portraits#portrait#portraits_ig#pixel_ig #portraiture#expofilm3k#portrait_perfection#stre… https://t.co/SnkGLLqWOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this #fieldwork photo because the plastic sheet that was snagged by a tree branch and blowing in the wind bl… https://t.co/RGEXfa6ubk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your promotion of Clean Coal is killing us.                             Clean Coal… https://t.co/Tbz7XulmMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to go on aim chat and pretend to be celebrities and people would either call me out or deadass think I was Miley Cyrus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaddenX @Steel_Curtain4 @AB84 Let’s start a service $34.99 we’ll have a random illiterate homeless person read… https://t.co/PPGUO4fMYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brandon_Nocaute @jiltedamericana Jones sure as Hell ain’t coming swinging like a wild man though ...but I’m still… https://t.co/lYp5TSnwTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutlerRidgeLAZ @homerun0620 @HeavySmoke239 @SportyMama @kellycanes @kelly_deezcanes @RobertPerera5 @NYCanegirl… https://t.co/cy2xEdsww3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddieonfox But they shot it in Syracuse so when theyre at the War Memorial he's is one of the refs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've began on a new journey. Yes I met with @lsarsour and I can tell you she is not the person that the media portr… https://t.co/xQsUqy7h6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ll still more time to get my DM for hire service thought out. I want it to be as well prepared as it can… https://t.co/2pe9S7kaVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zimm2213 @PHLSportsTlk @football_Kelly If you read the article I literally address all of this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[One is not born, but rather becomes, a women - Simone de Beauvoir. Happy #InternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul McCartney don’t give af about me. Just because he is an immigrant doesn’t mean he cares about me as a Hispanic… https://t.co/6VyAmUj5RB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyJohnsonNews Also...if you think that top college athletes (football and b-ball in particular) aren’t being compe… https://t.co/l7nxMvhfkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a real thrill to share the State of the County with my son, Eli. Having spent my adult life in public having… https://t.co/I7xdppt5FD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ New Braunfels Railroad Museum https://t.co/JoJWweAjoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettAthletic made it to Iowa City, Live play by play tonight on @qcsportsnet pregame begins in about 5 minutes  Li… https://t.co/PQxcSEyNgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had lots of fun in Daytona this year with the @krashindustries team! Can’t wait to come back on that amazing ski… https://t.co/0rh49CgeE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@da_tells @_JIMMYHENDRIX_ @jackieaus @newyorkval132 @LylajoyRose @Okie08 @trumpifiedterry @kathy101252 @KenPicciuto… https://t.co/sglkTiPeQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi @SenatorSchumer  @GOPLeader Now it… https://t.co/BvQ200hztE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional - Coaching, Mentoring, Training and so on...  There are many occassions I am asked for my "professiona… https://t.co/xwSHfWAWHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonESawa Sharp individual indeed. Has a degree in economics, but doesn’t understand economics. She’s the Left’s… https://t.co/sfWmBKKhqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katherinelegge Jeffery esptien driving for auto Nation now https://t.co/MakqOG5Xdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look crazy but I’m warm. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/Hranj83dkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkThEwizz @LAFC @LAFC3252 Great to see you on the field. Looking forward to seeing up here in Seattle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, now. Musician friends...I'm thinking I need a musical blurb for a new podcast.   NON boxing podcast...  Know s… https://t.co/V2FUaFjkkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am feeling 2️⃣2️⃣.  #timeflies #birthday #pvc #22 #plumbing @ Franklin, Massachusetts https://t.co/n6mMslosV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Too bad, he won’t win the battle. She and he are enemies of America...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcwashington @erika_news Temp.going up to 34* so that would be all rain but the ground temperature  would be less… https://t.co/wtCTLpOX1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinmack You are a damn prick. She was raped and almost killed in Egypt covering the Arab Spring you POS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeAbert @RachBlevins Here's a list of all the Putin critics who wound up murdered https://t.co/epguce3F3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Big Head: In the Kitchen.  This week we find Big Head in the kitchen wishing the was food in the pot.… https://t.co/6CHKRIIJpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWFriedberg @ml_barnett @jayhancock1 Regardless of the short-term system-gaming from payers and hospitals, I like… https://t.co/Oa7MrOvcik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frekiwolf @SkinsFlwTrain Wow ... and here I thought I was the only lost soul who risked my marriage trying to just… https://t.co/dmMFGISDwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@friendsfcollege so it would be awesome if you came back with another few seasons!  #FriendsFromCollege]]></document><document><![CDATA[You vs. the guy she tells you not to worry about @THON @THONwardState https://t.co/0WpoCZnSfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[At The end of the day it’s fuck what y’all think... just worry what’s best for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must be a billion fathers and mothers  that led to your creation yet none of them left you an inch of land on this… https://t.co/JZzESPOW5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren It wasn’t a military weapon and it was a gun free zone. Fact-99% of all mass shootings happen in gun free… https://t.co/2UFTBUZMva]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watson at Maltby closed, couple of mangled cars (OPP did let me ride past) #guelphride]]></document><document><![CDATA[BGIS CNP helped student celebrate National School Breakfast Week with real race/pace cars #StartYourEngine… https://t.co/S2CYyKJaFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmcgphotos @adrianweckler Do you have T-Mobile there?  As a yank we get free data international data. Worked in Ch… https://t.co/CPujhzaQA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinrhodes @TexasLonghorns Anytime sir. Glad you like. Thanks for babysitting Grayson lol. Safe travels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plaisir immense aujourd’hui que de participer au séminaire de @vi_boucher de @RDandurand à @UQAM @Pol_droit_UQAM; p… https://t.co/ByXqbjm9E8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillLeeVovers @w_terrence @SpeakerPelosi And how would you have felt if President Obama’s, or any other president,… https://t.co/lujXQahLQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[At a rock music show, seeing Mother Mother with @Bees_Beads I know little about this band but they seem enjoyable. https://t.co/B4Elt803iG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá: Si sigues faltando vas a reprobar el semestre  Yo: https://t.co/AgzlHCEsYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look in Jacksonville Jaguars locker room @OrangeBlue760 #DUUUVAL https://t.co/BhOGC8muwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boost protein with blueberries and bananas @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/sQhv2zX5cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azsportsfien It's annoying but at least our boys are on their minds, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auroraathletics @BoysTallmadge @BenedictineHS @GreenmenNation We're working on it. Gotta meeting tomorrow. We'll iron it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come say hello!! (@ Bamboo Beach Tiki Bar &amp; Cafe in Fort Lauderdale, FL) https://t.co/uh65vpam6D https://t.co/iwHUpufBod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Can’t think of anything that would bring me more pleasure! Junior is a piece of shit! 🌈❤️🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[when FDR betrayed the forces of freedom and allowed his pal "Uncle Joe" Stalin (FDR's fond nickname for his other c… https://t.co/GTfBIzBWu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jboyette88 Exactly. So regardless of what he does in the combine, flexibility will be  a question with him until w… https://t.co/EtYKIFJdT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder the Lions Have 0 super bowl appearances and are the only team in NFL history to be able to say that… https://t.co/a0OX3gaeWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShondaCromer2 @GopherFootball Great things are coming for these young men. RTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro his tactics were spot on today. Change formation mid game def helped us]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see why this scene was gif'd. Well done, internet. @ The Matisse https://t.co/rlf1602Xdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xavier_Hockey has 2 more games left to play this regular season. But tonight, the seniors played 1 last night game… https://t.co/yZwexuxEWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisH59386592 #theVenutiTHEOREM  This post  written pre President Trump. Convinced that Obama would never step d… https://t.co/KwtSr0jHE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Jacksonville, NC job and click to apply: Logistics Driver (Eastern NC) - https://t.co/tzRGWK3tFE #Transportation]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why the girl i wanted to get pregnant is pregnant   this some bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samesfandiari @warriorsworld I asked for a load management tee and he does the most as per usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @Chase announces no more funding of #PrivatePrisons. Calls on @WellsFargo to follow suit. Marketing ploy? @Chase… https://t.co/L6nzId6JdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might actually be a good year to be a padres fan fingers crossed 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell you how much I love the fact that this crown of thorns comes in two sizes. https://t.co/SEXIFCUHVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregPaul58 Whenever you hear a politician using superlatives take a cautious step backs. They most likely have no… https://t.co/pf4uUd4Z0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DepressedDarth Maybe a joint Vader-Kenobi stand alone movie? Better than the three originals of course! And heavy on the Vader!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:56 left in 1st half, Luke Maye has 8 points and the Tar Heels have raced out to a 20-9 lead #DukevsUNC]]></document></documents></author>