<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_aprilolvera @aubbbayy I really just watched this like four times I’m crying dios bendiga a tu madre 💕💕😩😩😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise That’s because that particular practice ended with the SPARTANS!!  You Asshat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[📌🙋🏻‍♀️ Who is ready to buy or sell a home⁉️  🗝 This market is HOT! 🔥🔥  ☎️ Give me a call at 251-463-5414 and let’s… https://t.co/3KBM3aIz5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbieH22571300 Thank you Billy ! Her comments mean nothing to me ! She is so ignorant ! I’m a Bimbo ha ha !funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 17 year old boy is having a baby and everyone is commenting “sa srecom” and “opa mali samo tako” are you kiddi… https://t.co/deywf5vvfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[how you go out with somebody and talk to them for days an then have a crush on them that’s so annoying I don’t need… https://t.co/9tqSNt6F9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in Ann Arbor, MI? https://t.co/F4djqG8cb7 #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateCasey @BravoHWFanClub @JenniferAydin Has she curtailed the adult beverages that make her act awful?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my second graders said today: "I never want to get married. I want to live alone with some cats!" #CatsOfTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a #chef , people ask me, "do you cook at home?" And I say that we split it up.. The truth is.. That esug615 is a… https://t.co/yaIo3fUhjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeahDayanara Fuck no hoe im cute and jorge going to look just like his momma sexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister says that our door have been opening by itself randomly on the nights I’m working the overnight ahhhhhhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timthecripple @CraigRSawyer EXACTLY...and the criminals just keep on running....FREE W/ ZERO CONVICTIONS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psychiatric Hospitals became Prisoner of War Camps for an untold number of American women.   Some facilities induce… https://t.co/j2zT9GOhfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimruehl I’m guessing you’ve read the Elizabeth Cotton book that @lauraveirs wrote? Not the same thing of course b… https://t.co/OXpsbYCQ2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarakate0110 Truth! That’s why you don’t let those people bother you! Stay Strong!!! 😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men think they can talk shit to me and I won’t say anything............ surprise...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me tomé dos antigripales vencidos, si no vuelvo a molestarles la vida es porque me morí.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what the product will be but Thrive + CBD sounds like a good thing!!! I'm freaking excited! https://t.co/vftpAqBgJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA BÚSQUEDA, de Blanca Miosi @BlancaMiosi https://t.co/ajvzZe7ewq  Un boy scout en la resistencia polaca sobrevivió… https://t.co/IGuLkxmdFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that this appointment is really happening makes me soooo happy 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hand Bags, Evening Bags, Tote or Wallets. WHERE? myboutique.yourownstyle #handbags #wallets #shoppingnow… https://t.co/cwjCsgg4Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog He is no longer the smartest man in DC....see tony kornheiser]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mind is on to the next event.... What will April bring??? Let’s talk about sex for sure! Just a brown girl on a… https://t.co/wTJo3fdVW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[im kinda hurt im not gonna hear the entire version of llegaste tu. @CNCOmusic fix this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I eat it is the food that is scared. - Ron Swanson #parksandrecreation @NickOfferman3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samkirilo09 Good question. That’s what I do, and so far no one’s told me not to. Yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be reading a tweet and it just flips away to an advertisement????🤔🤔🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hersheda You will totally relate to this kid. “Okay, okay, okay.” Love. https://t.co/F09vIee2wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I modified a trapezoid table to make a standing desk thanks to inspiration from @lsdevargas. This was a fun Saturda… https://t.co/IeF8AllQmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureynaaa Exclusively ONLY for the Air Force Bro . Special Collab with Nike]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to SFO. Baggage claim and yoga room. @ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) https://t.co/qJ1NhSPx9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful site visit at Bristol! #sappstaffrocks #SAPL https://t.co/XiGPWsztdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there is also good things happened when he is mad because he was able to do stuff that I usually do for him. Thank you God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe so the rest of us would become alarmed and moved to take action. However, it is not for us to understand God;… https://t.co/vucJeSxNPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @HillaryClinton Don’t yell at me over this, but I don’t think this country is ready for a radical… https://t.co/5CGqxJMvFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[my managers such a goof. he spent the whole day referring to stephane as “master bait”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xadditupx @NVoluntaryist @MrDapperton @Ancapikitty @HoodieDemon @morganisawizard @I_Am_Reason @MAG16231910… https://t.co/y2klHB7D0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embrace life's enjoyable experiences. The simple things in life are often the most rewarding when you fully experie… https://t.co/sUxOBBMkc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelpreaching Two things: 1. Thank GOD he was not in Blazing Saddles - I love that movie! 2. He was a TERRIBLE ac… https://t.co/FJGfesm7Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que perro 🐻 cuando suben algo hace 40 segundos y ya lo visteehhhh nmmmmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 3?  In Seattle, you’ve got 1 garbage/non-recycle, 1 recycle paper/cardboard, 1 recycle glass/metal/mixed, 1 fo… https://t.co/N2WEKeyhO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patnutana @journo_dale This is unethical and deceitful . He learned nothing in the sandbox.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZucklesOfficial @Misfits @GoodGuyFitz @TobyontheTele @Zuckles @iNOTORIOUS @RealMcCreamy @SwaggerSouls @Samalingus ily baby 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t date or marry an Aries man they are self centered egotistical assholes who will only hurt you and abuse you this has been my PSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Bellingham !!! I will be out in the streets Saturday afternoon handing out resistance cards and talking to peo… https://t.co/5xU77BJCUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerrmace And as time goes on... a) the best pieces from "new music" will become standards you gotta know, and b) h… https://t.co/PTqi7kftgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, stupid, outside at 7am on a sunday morning, on daylight savings: where the fuck is everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jazzed to hear this hero tell his story- I read his book as was inspired #boilerup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @davidsonbhayley ! I hope your bday is as fun as you are! party hard ! ;) ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i24NEWS_EN @mikeymusto @DavidShuster I knew that was coming...next it will be blamed on a mental health issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puppers and doggos enjoying their morning commute! Enjoy this warm fuzzy and have a great week! #HappyMonday https://t.co/QjzWs5NLqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathDenisNJ A2: I often try to mix it up...brain breaks are nice-I’ve been challenging my students to take a break… https://t.co/cKtYrWIYpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw this profile of our students on @WFMY #inclusion #UNCGCampusClimate  https://t.co/FA92DFncmf… https://t.co/LhTnteq9fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DidiYueyue09 @zooeycide @mayanglo Ayyy oo ,nakita ko na thank you, yun ba yung may 7.2k followers , may close grou… https://t.co/GMZ2jWJj7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found a new tooth in my mouth i had no idea one on my wisdom teeth had come in ..... I’m tripping out right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanw68 @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump Even worse, he wants to be one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the rewording of questions. I’ve asked, “What questions do you have?” because it’s better than the old, “Any q… https://t.co/T5YCf3yNPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahwaugh20 @CIAnderson3 @ItsMeCandiceCat @PollyPapaya @RexThomresist45 @og_dbl_lo_g @tracyb12371 @callkurt… https://t.co/mbRxV4cSaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homomeansnevada i did this at 130am last week and I still hurt from it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BEST true crime podcast out there just dropped some new info! My Monday morning routine is soooooo weird!!… https://t.co/r3M6VqcYvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[LET'S BEGIN THIS DAY WITH A HUGE A R⚡O⚡A⚡R  FOR DOG'S MOST WANTED⚡ AND WGN. @wgnamerica #DogWGNA. THEY ARE ON THE H… https://t.co/AgtTmpdQoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[both of the kids i babysit are sleeping this hasn’t happened in MONTHS i don’t know what to do with myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how EXCITED I am for that day to come that I’ll be DONE with this annoying semester!🤗 #overschool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatshisname7 @suea1978 @AmericanAir worst airlines ever the rudest airlines in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING A house fire breaks out on Fairfield and Hewitt in Evanston.   ▪️10 people, 8 children, evacuated (none w… https://t.co/rWayIVGvh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @WellingMichael @jguaido @CNN Yes and they don't know how much that hurts the majority of Venezuelans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydhuisman If you are making me nervous. I have no idea what you are doing to your Dad or @kjhuisman 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibyshire It was lovely. The focus was pulled away from our ohana for a bit (don't wanna spoil too much for you), b… https://t.co/AOXogsx3jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave the diversity and individuality of the regions, grapes, and wines. Opa! 🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remartin53 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroderickGreer Exactly. Where’s the mugshot? He’s a murderer not the sweet college boy next sore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terranhabit Omg. I just googled Amelie. It’s totally in my que. I knew I kind of dig your darkness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @Liz_Rochford🥳 Thanks for everything, from teaching me to ride a bike, to being a great teammate, an… https://t.co/7BOkAgShRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the heck did I get myself into???  @BAHSTigers #dodgeball These kids throw hard! 😳😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being an adult means I can eat ice cream for breakfast and no one tells me I can't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox doesnt really like you Trump but the little people do..start paying more attention to your true soldiers..]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m teaching an ice skating lesson tomorrow for the first time in YEARS and i am so happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash OH, Please, is she an idiot or what. some staffer wrote her script, she hasn't been in politics long enough to know anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how difficult life gets, the important thing is to live it with hope.-- Topanga Matthews ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful day to celebrate Mrs. Judy Baker. @ Ashtabula, Ohio https://t.co/l3BNiKKI2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlohaHa59067534 @jakelew75666768 @harjo111 @Aug1405 @PayItForward213 @kaci150 @TankIncU @SealeyGerald @AsiaTater… https://t.co/qJLGLZNtaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely a righty. windy but beautiful. #soccerdrills #muddyshoes @Sweatcoin #TuesdayMotivation https://t.co/BMLnIU9Whh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you live a life of good design incorporating #efficiency and #beauty? @ExpressiveAge https://t.co/AkqV5e9QVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adorable Prince Bei Bei, Queen Mei Xiang &amp; King Tian Tian!❤️🐼🐼🐼❤️3/7/19 https://t.co/fxAFNQdwwJ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[You in with me on this?! @kcusick20 @EducatorWilcox three days late but still worth it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someday I’ll get on my soapbox about why calling yourself trash for a fandom drives me crazy too, but probably not today. Maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#righteousglassrig  #sold here made in cali @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/zjPI9bInmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have nothing against our President.  In fact I think he is the best we have ever had but I do expect complete hon… https://t.co/cNlUHBrgwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[At first I was like, “How sweet, he made a playlist of me,”  but then..... https://t.co/Da6BgFDgXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuntLulie @ROBENT805 @Alllwftopic @woozleweasels @alexespind @Backstorymom1 @NavygirlLaura @CeciliaLisa3033… https://t.co/BAOiddeR7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamaraMcCleary @JolaBurnett @TechWorldsHalf @digitalcloudgal @laurenmaille @LornaGarey @TechnyGal @khalihenderson… https://t.co/28bAnhMvn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love luke hemmings so much and he should love me back please and thanks :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turning 20 in a month and I still don’t know what the fuck I’m doing with my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day dreaming about warmer weather and opening all the windows in the house, come on spring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed @friendsfcollege has been canceled. Do reconsider, @netflix. The 2nd season exceeds the 1st. Also, the Atlan… https://t.co/SatuMcAw3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow please have this amazing and smart 8 year old future scientist on your show! I will be there in the a… https://t.co/erXLPzlWZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vangsness I really like your character on criminal minds but let me ask...drugs coming across border are deadly. S… https://t.co/ADkqm4xPhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/zGxaVfGcHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luv_A_LEXI Of course he will or he’ll get hit by a bus after he make his will to our kids.. lol]]></document></documents></author>