<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes @ckchumley @WashTimesOpEd All the welfare payments  for  decades  needs to be counted as  payments rendered]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's March! Time to drop our new Burger of the Month! Thanos! . . . 🍔 Thanos is a half pound Burger served on a bed… https://t.co/r45sFYCgCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[All it was doing was keeping people from being able to appreciate two very unique and talented women who contribute… https://t.co/HJSGmMXyeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ja4jamaicaJames @SInow @AdamSchefter Yeah and Brady's willingness to take low pay helps that. They go after positi… https://t.co/zwOE9hvGfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[next up. #h2ography #saltlife #wanderlust #liveauthentic #cloudporn #outerbanks #water_captures #vsco #iphoneonly @… https://t.co/ADt4y3aQJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevie Newsom’s murder on ‘Set It Off’ is one we don’t talk about enough. Sad and unfortunate. Brotha just wanted t… https://t.co/GMQlFmP4HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TheEllenShow for supporting survivors! #leavingneverland https://t.co/Tcwf7kfTxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesMen_3 @Coachlazar AWESOME great people !! #GoEagles #GoNuts #SursumAdSummum catch them before they go, greatn… https://t.co/XGtEb6wWRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ram_rossman @JeffPassan If they’re incorporating a clock, yes it is changing baseball. What’s wrong with a pitcher… https://t.co/LzKZPnjGCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHasselgoff He took Eric Snow and Larry Hughes to the finals don’t tell me Brandon Ingram and Kyle Kuzma are worse than them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelers It’s not too late to rescind the trade and let Brown not show up and not get paid. Oakland’s offer is insulting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassieFambro Sam was an amazing guy. I ran a scheme he did for sr that wasn't used in 88 but told me what it lead… https://t.co/paVFK6h6AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisreyes06 Whoa sorry for the stupidity lol but Anthem is a narrative? Haven’t been fortunate enough to get the game yet haha 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HabitatForHumanity #BuildingHouses @ Mableton, Georgia https://t.co/kVPGun7FeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen Prove Peter swore...none of us is perfect, but this man had lived with the incarnate God...if that e… https://t.co/SQ4Zj4AI1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I see any of the people I follow on Apple Music listening to the Lil Pump album when it comes out Thursday night… https://t.co/RriqAt2SGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cherry Stout by @BellsBrewery at @walk_ons — https://t.co/apRT3hOYZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollieYacano Like I said - SO totally on your way 😂 Girl’s got to have some priorities in this life. Decent caffeine is top among them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mck69zie What trips me out is their instagrams are all like California model pictures and then there’s that one pi… https://t.co/ZYOJjDPEmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Correction: Russell Westbrook is a member of the Thunder and not the Sonics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk FOLLOW Me so I can send you some Vids of my GREEN Rotarywing for E.V.s! Or see them on YouTube! Under My Name!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankDElia7 @SusanBordo @AwardsDaily @JW4Hillary In other words, don’t give us polls that aren’t right now. Plus,… https://t.co/a2NrLD5cGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going to be a lot harder this time around for the @BernieOrBust people to try and say that the @DNC "rigged" t… https://t.co/U6stzO78lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[And finally we have three!  Only took him 4 hours to get ready...seriously, 4 hours. @ Sugarloaf (ski resort) https://t.co/LKQzgEFD0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it’s been over a week since I thought about @stoolpresidente’s toes getting dragged up the stairs o… https://t.co/Kv8RQqvhRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discover more ideas with Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest....It's all about you. 250 million people come to Pinterest every… https://t.co/ELAwyz3gy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family across the street just arrived home. I must stare and bark at them. https://t.co/AU3XBjnkCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good finale but not great. Some really touching scenes particularly with Roland and the dog, but it all came down t… https://t.co/w5Zqc66dop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justo lo que no quería oir, por culpa de Lainez metieron el 1-3, ni modo Diego, toca levantarse #MushoBetis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HQNigerianArmy N Army stay away from election polling booth if you dont want to be accused of Meddling or interfer… https://t.co/yT5qHTm3pJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LifeCare Health Partners is hiring in Denver, CO! Read about our latest Healthcare job opening via the link in our… https://t.co/Q3T2X4y8Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Coffee Coffee Coffee  Sixth City Cycles on their one year anniversary today at 4193 Pearl in the heart… https://t.co/53bkAEJ3Ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singletrigrero1 Pana los "servicios swinger" no existen, son voluntarios, gratis. Infórmate. Tu lo que sueñas es c… https://t.co/OhANvSLIel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the one in the middle making the funny faces. Tonight was dope. Can’t wait to perform again! #slocomedyfest Pho… https://t.co/jLlc4ErFAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raf! Looking good mate! #EsriEPC #Esri #MainStage #DroppingKnowledge https://t.co/HbBvmo8usx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's getting deep out there in the hood! @ Frond Road Cul-De-Sac https://t.co/vgyGA0FyIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all in ok Keith he goes to duke and he lives in a trailer park do it for your family! #Duke #SurvivorEdgeOfExtinction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaBanksWWE It's sad to see so many wrestlers wanting their release from a company that's been around longer than any company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleWhittaker In my 37 years of work in the academy, I never encountered a more capable, smart and wonderfully eng… https://t.co/ErKWWpFwLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samrae999 @vlexramos Like I stated about social security. It was supposed to build revenue because when establishe… https://t.co/mHbTMCBGB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[El nazismo Catalán sobre una muchacha de #EspañaViva  @__ayduchis__ @LuchyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunset from home. . #myindiana #picoftheday #indiana #indiana2019 #iphonephotography #igersindy… https://t.co/RDlRqS3vxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyLance MLS uses these games as preseason warmups. :-/ ill never understand not wanting to compete in the CCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods he did a great job of staging the "attack"-two people got paid to stage it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hisaraskinner Thanks Sara! Great commentary. Love having you as part of the News Channel 12 team. Up next... cats… https://t.co/sNj2J5uSGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dreams are like an SNL episode random skits that have nothing to do with each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fried to perfection and finished with fresh chili oil, our Hot Fried Chicken Taco is a bite you’ll remember. Join u… https://t.co/I4jzj6kapa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great day and enjoy a Mocha 📷📸☕☕  #photo #photooftheday #chicago #chicagogram #photoediting… https://t.co/7ZgyE0XmV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detroit is an amazing city. It also definitely needs saving. If a premier watch factory opens up in town, it’s prob… https://t.co/9f8ZEabHaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boban Marjanovic is available tomorrow. Brett Brown is happy to get him back #Sixers https://t.co/scL7ROW6yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm unclear on why Smollett chose two black men to portray racist white supremacist Trump supporters in a fake atta… https://t.co/YPgUgRfKcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 14th Street/Eighth Avenue https://t.co/EKAxzCCMej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LethalMILF @Angel_Wicky_II @sametmax4 @zupergeil40 @BigJuggsWorld @AmateurVibes Beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, @realDonaldTrump is showing how he knows absolutely nothing regarding trade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetBenMax @chriscoffeytalk @ShaneGoldmacher He’ll get a challenge, but it might. K go anywhere again. If the lef… https://t.co/w2Gu5jMB4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnlee333333 @Jeffrey86437753 @SenFeinstein @realDonaldTrump Corporations should pay their fair share of the burd… https://t.co/PI7t31c8Uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@im0genx We’ve switched the indefinite article to “an” because it’s been so butchered haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Take the Cannoli by @FourFathersBrew @ LHD Tavern — https://t.co/wy3v6udwrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaiPan_StraunCo You still don't know what you're taking about. There's literally hundreds of types of breads and p… https://t.co/SdH4BShsOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 9 yr old and I just @MarieKondo ‘d her sock drawer. It’s a start.  :) Thanks @netflix and Marie-San Gozai Mas...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki_Skywalker Your father is a national  treasure https://t.co/QKn0HoGq8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[List Of 10 African Innovations For February 2019 https://t.co/dpAafnGW1c 🛑AFRICA IS ON THE MORE IN INNOVATION.👍👍👍👍👍👊.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ouchinagirl @DaRealGrizzle @BernieSanders It’s scary to see how his message resonates with so many Americans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielnazer However, because we've made life such hell for brown people and so cozy for people like Manafort it'll *feel* worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBradyWalz They must’ve been creeping on our thread the other day, Walz!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrivetoHarmony Opposing band director probably rushed the press box 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vckscria @ItsKrissy @chasestrangio Loyalty to what? Do you maintain your loyalty to white Nationalism?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_daniiielle Well, guess it’s time to update the ol’ tinder profile then since you’ve confirmed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve read comments about he Aussie Army losing a fight to emu’s. I need details about this story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder I won’t be streaming today or next week. I’ll be testing with the rest of #teamcfb for the Mythic C… https://t.co/uyiOBbpjS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MAGA by selecting and surrounding himself with the best and brightest never before experienced by… https://t.co/Vl8XjIJobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pantherrants @Tjonesonthenba They are closer to the rest of the West than they have been in some time. They are no… https://t.co/XZ929GWqpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @realDonaldTrump And Mexico will pay for it! Wow! Never thought Trump would be able to keep that promise! #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Angels Seniors! Thank You! 20-4, Keep it rolling.  @mgersh2405  @shelstad_  @cjoh1612 @HolienThor  Diego Thies… https://t.co/Y4FPd2m2Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sure would make me pretty happy if I did get to see you in person again sometime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this is the most unpopular of unpopular opinions, I really love Wanna Partner, the season six finale of The… https://t.co/zJC9dNCOD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarieDesh1 @guttybruin @gatewaypundit From the beginning of what? She wanted to saddle us with Christi-cream and t… https://t.co/9iwMjcJxav]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you always gotta tell the ones close 2 you 2 support you then you are wasting time. Sumn I learned over the years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstover7222 @_ThunderNation @okcthunder WTF ever he isn't playing good tonight so quit acting like he is]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2021CheerleadingProspect Anna Hamm had a great time at Univ of Georgia Clinic. She had a chance to meet with the H… https://t.co/rBa2oH51J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHSghockey_ prevails in double overtime to advance to the state tournament for the second time in three years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEEI I tried listening to @MutCallahan this morning.  I can t do it a anymore. Went from must listen, to a boring morning show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC How about your options to try and create fake news and lie about what you never found in a Phoenix air… https://t.co/FgvSAVyKSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[[Sunday Schedule] Feels like we’ve waited a long time to say this again - it’s RACE DAY! #FirestoneGP https://t.co/EdmFzJNTek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the good guy.      Suspect kills wife at dentist office before being taken down by bystander  https://t.co/J9gJjiOcCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim, Please, Please, Please ... take your new-found friend back with ya. #NotMyPresident]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is too close to the first white jerseys #MNUFC had and this hurts cc: @EPluribusLoonum @FiftyFiveOne https://t.co/RNkMNLlInz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartGrist That's from Starship Troopers. An amazing film. Paul Verhoven is a genius. #Catitstu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVP_DFS Tried your MMA on Sat. didn't work out. Love to win and see what you can do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But, take heart, because while so many scoff at the idea of life at its most vulnerable, He who is both Author of L… https://t.co/rNpvD7vznT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the 1998 UNC v. Dook game and noticing how UNC tradition has continued through the years. Glad to pull for… https://t.co/svWYzJCN8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fauverlaw @StarTrek My first episode came after I watched the first five movies.  It was summer and I was allowed… https://t.co/21bnmjO3tD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are my feelings towards hand shakes after the match. I’m not in the ring to be friends with you; I’m in there… https://t.co/9R9Hxh199p]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/ba61vhqv3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Giants One of my favorite players good job Hall of Fame you got this right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinephile24 Oh god the way Walbrook says "Clive" when he takes Livesey by the arms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC The REALLY CRAZY THING about “THE GREEN NEW DEAL” is that AOC might be considering “IT” as an a… https://t.co/SIerHjv8Eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do y’all think is stronger?? A military grade tank, or a hydroflask??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you been in love before. If you been in love with me I know you still love me more. I just knoww.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PilgrimHockey and WW/EWG are knotted at 1 after one period in Game 2 of the Boys Division III Hockey Finals. @BeaconCSports]]></document></documents></author>