<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#chicago @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/PpZAQiUR2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanjp1979 @SHO_Shameless my reaction to tonight’s episode #Shameless https://t.co/G6UaNLOH5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsverAlexander @Red_Tanager @scrowder In the use of lethal force, see, e.g.,  https://t.co/RYUo8ACC8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Goodmorning from the middle of nowhere.  #Beautiful , right ?  #Travel #getoutofnyc #newyork #ny #visitmaryland… https://t.co/4OSDa9J9xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wind and 🌧 rain is coming down in my part of #Tucson #azwx #winterstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISPPutnamville Just bump it over a lane. Or slow down. https://t.co/KpKmmUM4oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonniLaurie @Tonia8675309 @SaneSophisticat @jam266 @Jimmy43754220 @62WalterP @stuffbusted @politiolyc… https://t.co/yUtCUoUMik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo I hope I make it this time. I went to see you in Vegas but l got kicked out. Fml I lost 700 bucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@endwomanabuse Always a pleasure to represent my membership at this incredible event! Thanks for having us on behalf of local 101.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterwashburn Give yourself time to calm down and then call. Even mediocre teachers are still human. I'd love to… https://t.co/59rJvvWyMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I remember GM took bail outs from The Government..... produced cars that no one wanted.. you can’t fix bad mgt b… https://t.co/hSiq9svrQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Rehearse Your Past Victories” Think about the giants you have overcome to get where your at today. Check out today… https://t.co/msMQBiedSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dabynsky Geez Dabynsky take some baseball bipolar meds. Injuries happen, last year we got ours. My thoughts are th… https://t.co/P4CpUYnY7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKLUBER @AGrossNewsday Dal Colle played great with Barzy. If Beau hit the net more often, it'd look even better. E… https://t.co/Y7a5yRn2Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMaroonV Those were faux locks (a protective style) to help treat my real hair. Lol I had a head full of hair though ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only value in Yang as I see it is that, since he’s being ignored by the DNC it undermines them to get him onto… https://t.co/89xHscuk62]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever try to talk shit to you just know that I used to consider Jason’s Deli an upscale dining establishment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is local government trying to handcuff this industry with archaic policy and regulation?  What can be done abou… https://t.co/Io9NMZKeV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Are you worried that our President: 1. has legitimized Kim by praising a murderous dictator; 2. is s… https://t.co/fl7ZNG1Pzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coinniss @sethquimby1 @gonnabechef @SenMcSallyAZ I completely believe her. I can’t believe she ( and @joniernst) d… https://t.co/UeVnRdEx4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I am thinking that Ivanka would do anything for Daddy Dearest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[[driving down Atlantic Avenue]: I’ve made mistakes there and there and there... and there.  👉🏽💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Smart_Liberal @nofunnate @charliekirk11 [Only one side hates America]  Look at any recent study by Pew Research… https://t.co/Jpco76ZW0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me on Instagram! Username: mossow https://t.co/Y6puoC4BvR https://t.co/WGYCnDV6uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met this girl and then we later started talking on FaceTime. Conversation going good and she asked me do I watch… https://t.co/RP93AwBoe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berdyboy47 @wilsonabrokwah @youneshh Let’s just blame Kepa for missing two penalties as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJEnglish The UN Charter reads in article 2(4):"All members shall refrain in their international relations from th… https://t.co/xpoMSEgL1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[315- Even though it’s not an impressive number, I can say this is the most I’ve squatted in a long time. I was alwa… https://t.co/ii5S3Vollb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got a fever. And the only prescription, is MOAR TERRAFORM.   Having too much fun building stuff lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Resident_fan @ResidentFOX I kept saying the same thing. I see honhe rattles Nic and I do NOT like!!!!! I no likee at all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[rent is only 175 this month suddenly i love having a water damaged room]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malbeckford I don’t think of you as a fool. I see that you’re an educated person with beautiful intentions who doe… https://t.co/p240G62Y3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 May the memories of the joys she brought you soon outweigh the pain of losing her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OllieTurnbull @GenIntact @NSPCC If you have to have it removed due to medical reasons, that is still unfortunate i… https://t.co/00Y8ne1mzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT 🏌️🏆 Arnold Palmer Invitational Presented by MasterCard PGA TOUR tournament event at Bay Hill in Orlando, FL fi… https://t.co/qXrCS83Yjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to papi! If you could only smell through the screen! Buñuelos pa’ los sábados! @ Dunwoody, Georgia https://t.co/zcvBB9YdDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matvelloso Look at the rake on that front end. Practically makes it a sofa. And all those over the top curves. Ew!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewR_Physics I am so cautious about taking lessons from there right now-it seems a mess. Although horses make m… https://t.co/T5dKcCmaqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Danner This is exactly my perspective. Plus I like a beer bar culture far more than a brewery’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CriticalRoleSpoilers - Campaign 1, Episode 114  The difference between the elation of Sam using the level 8 Counte… https://t.co/IG1DQvaxMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton A monumental idiot. She should sue Boston University for negligence in giving her a degree. So sad that… https://t.co/UwJfvSVaiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LantermozRory @Susanjmccann @kalimullah2 @arunbhar @manuParshwal @bynsny @saefqureshi @123_4Access @ReikiArthur… https://t.co/x8Te8e4kd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg My heart is with you today. Jaime would be so proud of her dad for fighting to make our schools, o… https://t.co/TgIKgsWNAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same Bills fans who are happy we didn’t get AB will be applauding the Bills’ “progress” when they go 8-8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe Bryce Harper was texting Mike Trout and told him to leave his wife so that they could start a romantic relationship in Philly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigCaplan Anti - Jew bill. Won't do any good. You can't change ideology. Need to pass a law banning Muslims from office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njterrie @grammy4lphhl @Catlady628 @criteria681 @kimmybeaa @pinewoodsdojo @dorisat58862534 @DarCie287… https://t.co/1EObAxVQgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You measure the size of the accomplishment by the obstacles that you had to overcome to reach your goals. —Booker T. Washington]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BemidjiState hockey, prolly send offers to Casadonte Lawson and Cameron Lantz from Greenway Monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyandrocles Just get back to it tomorrow. One bump in the road doesn't mean you turn around and go home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayOverwatch really really wish I hadn't bought digital. So wish I could get my money back. Can't believe I spent… https://t.co/o6dOSx97G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of the trailer for the movie Breakthrough is when This Is Us lady says about her comatose son, “Yo… https://t.co/H4ivyJkk1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I trained a little with UCLA's men's crew (I went to UCLA for college), but never rowed competitively. I row indoor… https://t.co/TMSIAYPu6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlm901 @Joverrated_ Dude I've had some heckin' bad luck getting Countdown repeatedly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerrydulac How great would it be if the #Steelers backed out of this trade like AB with Buffalo. #JustSaying. Sinc… https://t.co/tIj2QmEmv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[my followers/mutuals when they see me making a long tweet ending in “—“ or “...”: https://t.co/4t2WnVHo03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanholobeats I hope everyone fits when you do your set here 😂 this is going to be insane in April https://t.co/sXgmXavOmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payton Anderson moves on to the wrestleback semifinals for the Red Bulls and will finish in the top 6 at 145 pounds. #MSHSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts @JussieSmollett @danabrams @sunny No news here again, still...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is your attribution click or view based? what window? did you have multiple touch points (ads, email, post cards, S… https://t.co/xrUTOyzLWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to participate in Judge @Lina4HC #CivicSaturday #TalkingTransition on Children and Early Education at Hester… https://t.co/eUXMFGAPyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_boro @PenaltyBoxRadio Not up yet. Will be posting later this morning 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh4Miller Congratulations folks!! Working on 34 with the world's most tolerant soul down here in the SC Foothills!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stig_Ofthedump This is basically like a crude lensbaby, but with a multi element lens. There was this commercial p… https://t.co/0bvwIIamej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo solo digo que despues de este 14 de febrero les deseo, Ojala Les Baje A Todas 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHES A FUCKING JIMMIN STAN FAN ACCOUNT FAM HER “HUSBAND” THAT SHE TALKED TO ME FOR AN HOUR ABOUT WAS A FKN KPOP STAR AND SHES A FAN ACCOUNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtistIzzy Can't wait to see you return on the podcast , something I can't really  say for all those people so hap… https://t.co/cn5kDk7cbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bartoneus I ran PF so that an unconfirmed crit was max damage, and a confirmation meant max plus roll again. Was popular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/TFLRA6GBpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday...let’s do this. #CountDownToVacation #NewProfilePic https://t.co/ICf0AW9NhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me as I watch the Cohen hearings. #michaelcohen #dumptrump #fucktrump #trumpsucks #thegopsucks @ Scarborough, Maine https://t.co/6WtQl6RzyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prior to joining AHIP, Jennifer served as Development Director for the National Housing Law Project, a national hou… https://t.co/sf0Cm8ibpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha. Don't you dare hide your excitement for #boruto Viz Media😅 https://t.co/i70RtzfNRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 years ago today @SimoneSello introduced me to speakeasysage. Well, I could never have anticipated THIS. #thankyou… https://t.co/ZK3cPJHe2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracy505 @ChrysMusician @schwaka_ @candikahne @CallMeLuis @RealSaavedra No more federal dollars? Does that mean we… https://t.co/OBgBuGZHsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce The older I get the more strong I become in my conviction to like animals more than people....… https://t.co/eZb1zY7JXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_henley @Charlesh1972 @mrjefffostermsd @davidhogg111 Because parents never go out without their kids. Maybe y… https://t.co/PIk2tgSLqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can forgive you for lying  I can forgive you for hurting me  I can forgive your mistakes   But I will NOT forgive… https://t.co/GC7IklnXpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot clock winding down, @_Sydneyisabella sets up her screen and drives right into the Dixie State defense and fini… https://t.co/wMYvzpnTSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantistevanRyan @DiinSilversmith What I learned from someone raised in polite Southern society is that you start t… https://t.co/76Ubdd7Rqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nmRSnuRHKl No one should be attack4 what they believe.But🤔it look like was stage.The punch look more l… https://t.co/i1voX6o5RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @deray @KamalaHarris Wtf is wrong with folks who make up these false claims about other ppl, can they b… https://t.co/JHzJwwxoFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 285: Unsettling Part 1; Pennywise... #pennywise is probably the one character that I have the most #funko varia… https://t.co/IiOG7Llf8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceGillispie5 @Deterrified @Wallstreet1975 @TBTimes_Rays They didn’t make billions by making bad business decisi… https://t.co/aPLuYd1HUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOSS: We need to talk about your theft of computers from the office.  ME: Oh, wow. I’m disgusted. We could be talki… https://t.co/Y5rxhMapHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathTheKatholic @pierogicore Prostitution seems possible.  Good info here.  https://t.co/fMbLCqFTue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm mostly introvert, quiet reserved and not super chatty or complain about much. I do my job right and super frien… https://t.co/njImU6h49d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka No she don’t...you just stand anyone that’s more popular than you .... not to mention much more intellegent]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pun #puns #punny #wordplay #stickymoments #comicstrip #doodle #postit #webcomic #funny #jokes #comicstrip #comic… https://t.co/ziGgkrefhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@36Angeldb @IWasHrren @AOC Is her nose growing? The only scientists that are allowed to have a say must be in agree… https://t.co/jskE4P6XZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either Mete will never score a goal in his NHL career or he'll score 4 in one game :)  #goHabsgo #almostMete @GagnonFrancois]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personal Philosophy:  "Take one day at a time. Do the best I can. And trust in Jesus!" #Slamism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baynecolon @leafyfiddle13 @theoneringnet Thank you. This is like the sun rising in the north. The world, and what… https://t.co/8dsaycsWLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Atrium Hospitality team! See our latest #Marketing job openings, including "Assistant Banquet Manager", vi… https://t.co/cAeUY4RCn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJakiemiec I feel like his tax payments adjust for the state they play in, maybe I heard that somewhere idk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two things:  1. I farmed 63 Lightwyrm’s Glowscale 😤  2. Rodrigo sucks.  #DragaliaLost]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m a triple threat 1.) I play A guitar 2.) I have TWO lamps in my room 3.) and I am a THREE out of TEN”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Manzzz &lt;3 enjoy ya day fam! Owe you blunts and beers when you touch back to ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normthompson213 @FernandaSHD1 @CJcoates4 @RayLay04 @EmgeJim Come on back we always have a spot for you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to see my sister @LBaby1230 kick butt on live PD very soon can you imagine her myself @FCSO_S6 and… https://t.co/QT8WShxeiZ]]></document></documents></author>