<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why y’all hate Valentine’s Day so much? Why y’all so bitter? Valentine’s Day isn’t about being in a relationship it… https://t.co/joXUW0VJSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @realDonaldTrump, the kids at #StudioMariposa made you a gift! #NationalEmergency  #BorderWall https://t.co/ADG7rmeDAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[El lugar donde nací... y tantos tristes recuerdos tengo. 😔 I was born here... and I only have sad memories...… https://t.co/uVkjpYHwON]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still holding out hope.  Are we still good people @amanda_tierney9 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn everyone in Tulare County really went to those one trees this weekend huh, ive seem like a shit load of photo shoots there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrantMeredith @QueenWillRock I have seen that film 5 times in the theaters.  Great film.  KISS and QUEEN are my 1… https://t.co/vHxF96nycI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGNSV_ @sunterra1014 @zaptrapped @hardhouz13 @NotTooFondOfYou Need 3 originals G https://t.co/LK9PdKOved]]></document><document><![CDATA[He didn’t think he was making enough money......now he really has something to cry about🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at my grad school research topic area like... 😉 https://t.co/klVpyyv1t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If not for #Realtors... How in the world would the general public know to turn clocks forward this weekend?… https://t.co/euBZRoGwcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard 2 people have been cured, soon we won’t need AIDS UNITED. President Trump said it would be cured within 10… https://t.co/nMiCtOTOjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[AEF DC EAGLE CAM 2.5.19 FINALLY! DC NEST GOES LIVE https://t.co/pC2zoL7KpG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRHand808 @bekinddotcom @TeamPelosi @YAppelbaum Well,  you don't know what you are talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhiteHouse Plan to Sell Saudis  #Nuclear Technology May Be  #ILLEGAL  https://t.co/IJwKiPnll0 via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a shockingly good florist with very easy-to-use online ordering in my middle-of-nowhere hometown. And for… https://t.co/IneMGkBKI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha ha! I don’t know about SJV or RBC... prob Manasquan / Pt Pleasant back in the Mabrey-glory days 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sake_tasty @ephoustonbill @SouthernStarBC @TheStraightHops @RealBMaxwell @badhopper @lhtetrick @qblacklock… https://t.co/r1Wh7dX966]]></document><document><![CDATA[@april_deniece @acmecatalyst @samirose817 @VarshPrakash @sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein She crossed her arms in a trumpi… https://t.co/w5QRuJMkBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Semi precious stone Sterling silver rings. My grandfather would take my mother and uncle rock-hounding as kids and… https://t.co/SLhIwlTXiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hispanics that say they don’t date other Hispanics because “they’re not their type” but primarily only date white p… https://t.co/2UkmMmCGdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to when I thought I was going to live to the year 3000 and live underwater #iykyk  @jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thensls Columbia University Gabrielle Feldman Washington and Jefferson College]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had plans with autumn today and instead I decided to stay up until noon crying and then woke up at 9pm. hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[#church #praising you each and every day @ Shoreline Church - South https://t.co/qFH4D86jZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msshanitarenee Why did i login on the first try? It’s been what 15 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_DeLoach @AnnFisc35587367 @candacecbure Ok. But Im not sure why you think she may have lost her faith or drifte… https://t.co/ItpxWc0jVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[8泊10日の舞踊研修旅行に行ってきました🇺🇸  初の海外で終始緊張しまくりでしたが、無事に帰ってくることができました✈️  平日はPhiladelphiaにあるThe University Of The… https://t.co/SuAQVTA2fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a campus full of bucket fillers!!! @Horn_Dream_Big @tejadaaliefisd @BThomassci https://t.co/8IloL92zRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @POTUS @WhiteHouse You are going against the middle class,these people are not Trump's you are going agains… https://t.co/jK6cEN7Mgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS. @brendonurie would ROCK it his way. #P!ATD @hellosarahurie Elvis Presley - Bossa Nova Baby - Remix 2012… https://t.co/Rmt6GUOFlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m crying real life tears because they’re making the greatest showman 2 and this is the best thing that could’ve ever happened 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday means comfort food with leftovers for the opening day of book fair tomorrow.   #homecook #sundayvibes @ Peto… https://t.co/5tCVUHnxbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OU7C4ST It won’t let me download movie maker says it was discontinued in 2017 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHSsportszone @Mandarin_hs_fb @FHSAA We @DuvalSchools will be there cheering on the Mustangs!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[elected officials are communicating policy stances via in-the-moment memes👇 the way people communicate is changing… https://t.co/GfsawjLXla]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Calm, 6”x 8” Alla Prima painting as the sun sets... . . . . . #pleinairpainter #allaprima #oilpainter… https://t.co/ZU4PTh3q5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakeyraqwhitney I’m just saying. If someone killed my brother, mother, grandmother etc. it’s either me or the gove… https://t.co/PpAGJ8ISWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jspalding79 @B3KeithG Seriously? Cal can’t fart without it being national news. You think he paid Anthony Davis an… https://t.co/FDspbirEJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Fatal Pedestrian Crash🚨 Lanes are closed on I-81 SB between US-30 and PA-316.   We are headed to the scene now,  s… https://t.co/nIid1CWLdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby’s fly like a jet stream, high above the whole scene, loves me like I’m brand new ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellsiteGeo @tectonictweets it's definitely not! But it's where I am currently situated, and it doesn't seem very… https://t.co/5mlTiyhvFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erin Express Bar Crawl ☘️ #landsharksponsorme @ Cavanaugh's University City https://t.co/BkKrwitROr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A simple way to say Happy Birthday.  Thomas style.  Because what he wanted for his birthday, was an actual $100 bil… https://t.co/SGOCsklg1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Z3RoForksGiven @DonnieFire @suzystays @h8Wankmaggot45 @Kimmerella16 @gramV319 @MissGFYCuffy @ExpectoResister… https://t.co/HFu5XJVMAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love me some @thevirtualsavvy. Check out this blog post from her on how she breaks down how she went from nothing… https://t.co/t0KTlxmWUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx @RhianNAEYC for your leadership. It is mind boggling that preschool teachers are compensated half Kindergarten… https://t.co/tnZaKBWF1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suppose this #PaidPuppet will conspire against herself, being that she is "as powerful as a man"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephLaberis @my2k It does depend on the animal. My dog and cat are snugglers. The kitty sleeps next to me like a… https://t.co/4TVEoZPtMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_Thompson He was using his indoor voice when he should have been using his outdoor voice. Maybe he thought f… https://t.co/HWKoX81uMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Grease one and two are just noise. Creamy is better. Skittles are gross.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we were all laughing at Gruden when he traded Amar Cooper but now the Raiders will likely acquire Antonio Brown. Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NattiNatS_Duros @NattiNatasha OK......pero NO......no...y No....k tu hermana sea la queen y k yo no me boy a ir...… https://t.co/wxc3iqjsqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working until 1900hrs. (@ BlueCross BlueShield of WNY - @bcbswny in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/syNQvnPPAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[does someone set off fireworks every night?????????? morgantown what tf is this sound???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomledo Right wing evangelical voters support Israel because they think their state will play a part in the rapture. Not kidding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Blessings Worldwide!!! #GodUp Do Have An Amazing Thursday On Purpose #DC #Amen @ The Keels Mansion Roc… https://t.co/Pic3ALvvb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes money to make money! Grind now. Shine later. 🤑 . . . . . . . #letsgo #letsgetit #grindmode #grind #hustle… https://t.co/LZ6H30Qy8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey yo! I'm in this! Second act @IanInsect directing! https://t.co/qMoKR7dos8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourAnonVzla Esa es su opinión, por encima de él hay un Presidente llamado Juan Guido, quién apoyado por una inmen… https://t.co/maE6uaWa67]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing is I don’t even where makeup but false lashes.. ye it makes no sense to me either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you tonight at mayfairhotella @ The Mayfair Hotel https://t.co/PNAnO4nKWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us @OscarsGrill on March 19, 6:30-8pm, for our hands-on "Taxes 101" workshop presented by Senior Manager, … https://t.co/OvPqVjJIXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared Your anger is not misplaced. However, you are talking about a race in Mississippi and as a southerner… https://t.co/vlt3VWgt8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggsacks One time at Taco Bell I sat near a couple romantically nuzzling each other until I looked closer and reali… https://t.co/xIByB5GIfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention dudes in tech: It's not a good look when you are in Slack groups focused on getting women/nbs hired but y… https://t.co/mMiVbN08jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My egg donor pisses me off so bad that I had to delete her off Facebook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Urunderarrest It would require HONESTY. Something this guy can take or leave apparently. It was NEVER about Ben. I… https://t.co/EVslPMQ0Oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am new fan to @whydontwemusic and I am so happy to have joined this fandom to hear this incredible new sound!!!… https://t.co/GFjVstOrG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on now: @LRCADC monthly meeting! Right now @PepcoConnect rep. Mr. Cole is explaining the Capital Grid project… https://t.co/GWDawkqCez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Theresa got to see @SpaceX launch this AM. She had no idea before visiting FL that spacecraft were even stil… https://t.co/XthJ09o2qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live very near to Houston My 24 yrs old lives in Houston Omg 400 firefighters is 400 to many what about rue next… https://t.co/OiRVR83KFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[you need to check out @AndrewYangVFA and his Freedom Dividend https://t.co/KRdCOv8OVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymotivation_uk @cdmeditation Thanks so much for the RT and for all your amazing support! You and @Bigdirtyrock are greatly appreciated! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[The marketer in me wants to see the luggage brand and hope that someone sees a promo opportunity 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! I-15 SB closed around 1300S in SLC. Updates starting at 4:30AM @abc4utah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #OliviaColman win the Oscar then give such a wonderfully honest and normal speech made my night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Absolutely. If I get the chance to meet him; hope I have my Bible with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMarcusP I'm sorry but did you miss the 800% inflation, no food, aid being blocked, people being beaten and kille… https://t.co/1UXhFRGAtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to hug you one more time... still my favorite thought... I think of you, I just can't talk to you I m… https://t.co/50nr7lOOeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously???? @Chewy @PetSmartChariTs @PetSmart Well Companies.......Whatta got 2 Say/Response 2 THIS???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Glass House for You Me at Six in Pomona, CA https://t.co/BDeAd7oUI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ultra-hydrating cream immediately replenishes moisture for intensive skin improvement and all day smoothness a… https://t.co/q9qFrTznH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sprite @TroyGrantMusic deserves the most shine in 2019 and beyond. https://t.co/fCN47o3Im6 💜💜💜🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir we’ve been on the ground waiting for a gate at @DENAirport for over an hour. Can we please get a gate? SW flight 1106.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me when i’m high &amp; scavenging the kitchen and housemate gets home https://t.co/twb05uSkyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This past week and this weekend have been so stressful and it’s starting to show on my face 🥺 I need a break...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It isn’t even 9:05am and I already cried bc of @bassnectar, @TWLOHA, and @Electric_Forest  😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out @hinge #founder Justin McLeod with @BurtHelm at @Inc #IncFoundersHouse. Here for the business advice,… https://t.co/qTShlNw6yK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win or lose, work or play. Blessed. @lakers with my favorites. Both #stephenasmith and #markjackson in the house. T… https://t.co/7Z3bb2yJKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[･ ｡  ☆∴｡　* 　･ﾟ*｡★･ ･ *ﾟ｡　　 * 　 ･ ﾟ*｡･ﾟ★｡ 　　　☆ﾟ･｡°*. ﾟ *　　ﾟ｡·*･｡ ﾟ* 　　　ﾟ *.｡☆｡★　･ 　　* ☆ ｡･ﾟ*.｡ 　　　 *　★ ﾟ･｡ *  ｡… https://t.co/jawQccBEPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickGriffin @The_Jenius @always5star @CultureTrip @miliman12photos @CharlesMcCool @DarleyNewman @discoverhk… https://t.co/bAqlB5hB3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WebbAdams3 @DougJones Look we are never going to agree. You obviously have a problem with Dems and liberals and fi… https://t.co/Poc5r3MeUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onedirection you really gonna let the Jonas Brothers reunite before y’all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House on this GORGEOUS DAY!!  If you can’t make it today,  call me for a private showing!  281-382-8755.… https://t.co/ZHnyZwjVy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #security jobs like "Loss Prevention Detective - Oxnard, CA" at TJX… https://t.co/n79dTHk1uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's only been 55 years since the Civil Rights Act of 1964.This is hardly even someone's lifetime. Systemic racism… https://t.co/5Q1PURNJsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivycherries Goal is to move in, in September👀 I’m trying to save $3K for downpayment and a month of 2 of rent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustWinks @headdock I have joined many groups. I have rallied in 2 of the 3 DPP rallies. Hoping to make the CDC protest in June, too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I made the mistake of Googling Warren Jeffs. OMG, how could anyone defend him?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been feeling well at all and I’m extra sad bc I had to cancel my trip home for the tourney]]></document></documents></author>