<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Last night I realized to hit a new and heavier PR will require a spotter. This photo captures me doing 355lbs witho… https://t.co/HfcpBLNAYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[They will do something...maybe not anything major — maybe something major. Trade deadline!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is a perfect example of how important it is for the entertainment industry to listen to experts. Too mu… https://t.co/MrWyflqTYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Ms Sabeti, if you give a shoutout to our stats teacher Mr. Schmidt, we get to negotiate our final. If you come… https://t.co/iLK0S9uM8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenho @ABSCBNpr @ABSCBNNews Those people are posting rude pictures on Twitter. Twitter is a professional soci… https://t.co/s2T3sl9RtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhaedraParks @ToneKapone33 Hopefully one day you will return to the RHOA. With @Kimzolciak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the new Profile Preview feature on Twitter iOS because it now makes me go through an extra step to see the i… https://t.co/SKNJtOfueF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If she does nothing else, @AOC exposing the little bullshit that happens everyday in Congress, the actual mechanics… https://t.co/f3DRNpJFyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHLHockey @brock_mcgillis @ErieOtters  @SpiritHockey  @FlintFirebirds   I’ll FaceTime with any one of you until I… https://t.co/diYoH7XyGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll Have To Dance With Cassie by God Help The Girl https://t.co/SXbCufXVYp  What can I say? I love indie film musicals.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m guessing @kyliecosmetics next collab will be the “Kylie (x this bitch out of exsistence) @jordynwoods palett… https://t.co/ljmN5dObRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain legit starts glitching out when I try to wrap my head around this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Atlantic Prep Athletic Conference playoffs next week. #hockey #FlyerscommUNITY #Philly #Commish #FlyersCup https://t.co/VGpxM5WTz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this ghost town I found in Montana. Or Idaho. Or Wyoming. Wait, where am I? Hashtags below: . . . . .… https://t.co/gAirjd22fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianeason It’s a tricky dilemma. CU Boulder in state tuition is about $11k year which is actually not bad. We nee… https://t.co/P7qVUcROwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyBee1 @LisaTalmadge @szwest1 Maybe we need to forgive and firget. I said similar things to you in the past;… https://t.co/BeCm55dU8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDLG515 @NYSPHSAA Just spoke with coach and yes it was a tough spot but they are here and ready to go. Hopeful… https://t.co/hlALWc4cyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber Said the lady that has been handed EVERYTHING during her life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up for a frac at the Andrew Zulch 1H, thank you MD America for the work #gunnelsandson #mdae… https://t.co/IMUcjyHFhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I behind on this? On Friday, a ten year old girl explained to me who ‘Momo’ is. I’m just now picking up on it an… https://t.co/ORdSyDvUW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother-in-law i_hafoka is the man and THE number one Jazz fan. So when I was offered courtside seats tonight, i… https://t.co/h3rJmc14nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Reasons Your Outbound Strategy is Failing https://t.co/0k7N2dH2Ws via @dpriemer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again. Your opinion. Or mine mean shit. They pay a pro to make these decisions. And we need to judge his tenure aft… https://t.co/gD9j2FQ9c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[$EFR.TO triangle looks bad.  Only hope of a false break down.  #uranium https://t.co/UrfzUostTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quant I through today: Easy Breezy Quant I today: https://t.co/mtoI35E0NF]]></document><document><![CDATA[On @AlaskaAirlines headed down to @Mariners #SpringTraining with my favorite co-pilot. https://t.co/xpu2YtLMOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BathforEurope @AngieMeader @EstherMcVey1 @ledbydonkeys @gavinesler @IanDunt @_Britain4Europe @BestForBritain Not sure what it's about!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nerlens hasn't had the best game, but hes playing some good defense right now during this comeback. Leave him in! #ThunderUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Democrats haven't got a clue for success for America They're liars for selfish ambitions!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidwebbshow @charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris 100% agree. Would have been a significant cultural moment (and a stunni… https://t.co/RzFdIH86pX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have watched how i met your mother multiple times but this time through for some reason it literally has me CACKL… https://t.co/PjBAaBjQLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EastCarolina New Student Center is revolutionary!! State of the art 🖼. @ East Carolina University https://t.co/2HlYPCXW0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raging_Red @LisaMei62 Imagine yaself one of a CPL ppl in Boston 5days ago, wasn't not on the news, its just in sch… https://t.co/wklpyFmBah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylebuchanan If you go to Christchurch I've got a good Kiwi friend there who will show you around..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GKMC18 @taylorfor20th @Winwithwillis @Callowayfor5 @UgoOkere40 @TStamps37 @Mariafor49 @CDRosa @_MayaCamille_… https://t.co/LGjmvsQKx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will continue to move in silence it shows the fakes from the reals step back and reevaluate your life and you’ll notice it trust me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom That's why the schools are overcrowded you IDIOT, AMERICAN families can't grow cause you let the thug'… https://t.co/k3kTZWEaaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straws.  Seriously?  This foolishness DOES ALMOST NOTHING to change the planet.  #clueless]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were like what are you doingggg you’re supposed to be defending Nathan. NAH KENDRAH IS MORE IMPORTANT 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Dude just run for el presidente of Mexico already u obviously love Mexico and hate America. You alread… https://t.co/fqZgYrX2N8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanPlanteKUSI @LaPlayaHeritage Turn it into a bike/walk path with stairs to beach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichJash @shane__lewin Florida was decided by less than 1,000 votes. Even under the most conservative assumption o… https://t.co/8fSkAXa1Nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I finished scandal for the 2nd time. Still shipping #Olitz 5ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dilanesper @jonathanchait @EricLevitz @HeerJeet Non-responsive.  I agree with @HeerJeet's tweet in the spirit in w… https://t.co/nxz2BjXNOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtsCountryXLI @WorldWideWob You dont even need to be a superstar. #brewer https://t.co/S4YNXD7WoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d never thought about this - why is normal for supermarket cashiers to stand in the US when they sit in the UK...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sainted_corpse @GiggukAZ People can't even define/categorize the current 'breed' of "anime" and and you want to br… https://t.co/dRhg5Ch6Pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  its the end of supply side economics.. tax cuts have always killed more competition as more and more Mergers… https://t.co/5BOWcEmhrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthem was the last game I played last night and I woke up this morning to my ps4 stuck in a power cycle reboot int… https://t.co/0b1jZneR70]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some hidden gems on the Appalachian Trail. Despite doing it largely in the winter and being faced with th… https://t.co/CEIesTjfNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to that time I tried to channel Eleanor Arroway but ended up nearly sliding my camera off the hood of the… https://t.co/82mwb7OSmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMccafe Westminster Confession XXVIII: 6. This is just part of it. XVIII explains the position, but this may be sp… https://t.co/GoVGsIY7wC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteBlackburn Im with you on that Pete, gonna be a great game none the less!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread is 50 tweets but worth the time for those that have not read or seen Cohan’s opening statement. Thank you… https://t.co/l70BvICwy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must read. History, folks, history. Thank you to the great @BillyKilson for the share.   #JazzLovers #jazzhistory… https://t.co/GhwSV1v0xI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beware of @AOC and @IlhanMN ! You can’t defeat a great country from without until you first destroy it from within.… https://t.co/TdIFnGbKRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[DESORDEN ACTIVO:  SANTIAGO:- Sin luz, sin placa e implantando el orden cerrar establecimientos comerciales de venta… https://t.co/cQx0TZKHH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cirquelar @tanyaofmars Well, y’all done good.  I’d give everyone hugs if I could.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up and seeing Bernie is trying to bring socialism into America again https://t.co/9cu8UKzpii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abragwell This cat was watching the right channel… https://t.co/JAK1x55ypf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow @presidentsday How about best fictional presidents in a movie role?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmbfnews I hope he’s just doing that Challenge they said teens are doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When i bought an Uber using Uber cash  I truly realized in 20 years i will be pledging my allegiance to corporation… https://t.co/35987IZBUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiotrZychowicz To byl stalinowski oprawca! Zwykly psychopatyczny bandzior pokroju Abrama Tubery ktory po zamordowa… https://t.co/0AZojOYIAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Margaret's Boy is also in way over his head - ButtSvengali will feed him even more outrageous pap from outside the… https://t.co/kqX9sPZo7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Glad the truth finally came out! This is how you find racism in America - you manufacture it?… https://t.co/A5FYaEDhMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib hope this message finds you well. Figure this would be a more direct option to reach you. We work wit… https://t.co/MSaqWdBaE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't that the name of the song in the movie The 'jungle' King hoda matada, what a wonderful phrase youre no longer… https://t.co/38QqB9KQFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonKnoxx Funny stuff, great pacing, very natural speaking. Good eye contact and you can barely notice the red… https://t.co/zaFrllR29q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nilfa07325044 @TejanoToscano @jaxlee101 @DineshDSouza The jackass is running up a Trillion dollar deficit. He is r… https://t.co/63UslWagun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUOwlsDaily @APTop25_BB Our fans do whatever @UCFproblems asks them to do. He tweeted "rush the court" or somethin… https://t.co/ae699piuGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredBrooklyn @sairasameerarao 😂😂😂👏👏👏always keeping it real!  Thank you, sir! https://t.co/TsiW4kKlsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: Timeout Lady Warriors. Cardinal Stritch leads Sterling, 60-53 with 2:43 left in the 3rd Quarter. #swordsup #kcacscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing today for our next battle! Plenty of fight left in our Polar Bears! Need PBN to show out Tuesday night!… https://t.co/U3tgKl1Fya]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many English words can be formed from a set of toy alphabet blocks and what the percent likelihood is… https://t.co/9ANYR71OXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've entered to WIN $175 in eShop cards from RGT 85, and YOU should too! https://t.co/TzUm6UAFFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[See. Now “Can’t Sleep” is stuck in my head. Let me turn on some Usher real quick. 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisonia @cory_harris I kind of talk about it as nauseam but I’m doing just ducky. Thanks for asking. #ImpactMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a five minute replay over two tenths of a second to slow down the momentum of an exciting game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleChaps @katebarstool nothing wrong with a little fart box tongue punching... but dont blame your partner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaCoulee They had no clue. The terrible quality of writing displayed how they had no idea what they were doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just coming across this thread now. Worth the 2 minute time investment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best things in life are unseen, live each day to it’s fullest... https://t.co/58TBZuSM9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSandraGal @CallawayGolf Enjoy and have fun in Thailand. 😍😍😘😘😁😁🤗🤗😊😊🙌🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t matter what you’re going through, I promise you @OfficialTLC has a song you can relate to and give you a litt… https://t.co/9H4NgqnbSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men vs women... who’s better? https://t.co/bao725N6eH https://t.co/sHekcVR7v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doodlebobnewt I can understand that but hit is quite a stretch he touched him it was innocent and the kid will rem… https://t.co/DNBwEKaJRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherRohde1 @TaxReformExpert @mitchellvii Our present system--in which a small # of private individuals own the… https://t.co/3goEMPhzhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindymccain @ChrisCoons @SenThomTillis @SenJeffMerkley @SenMarkey @marcorubio @SenatorSinema Cindy, do not be over… https://t.co/iaOTgKUhQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TisPiece Thanks! Yea, this was my second attempt and I just can’t get it together 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But how many pain pills was he on at the time? Hmmm? #FakePresidency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Josh for hitting Platinum! You Rock appreciate you Rocking freight team every night ! #VOA365… https://t.co/5Dq5ExIXxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearsonNate When you’re Coach EyeWash all you have are anecdotal and subjective observations and since you don’t K… https://t.co/dDqYaXWAWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Weeknd sings this and y’all think he’s a lyrical genius but a female rapper pulls the same shit and you slut sh… https://t.co/4InfFCjFA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile Good thing I checked my bill.  Have been slammed with hundreds of dollars of "usage" fees on my mobile bil… https://t.co/KeywKnEslY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like Kanye rn except I didn’t fuckin support trump or shit so idk y tf there is such bs boycotting going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@957thegame @BontaHill Forget you. Not your money. Not giants decision. They made offer. Let’s move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanbender There’s no space to invert the FBs. There’s also minimal width without them playing on the outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just based on the fact he’s playing center instead of first his WAR will be better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost the NBA All Star Game 153 to 161. Try for yourself! https://t.co/wWNbfWYI8T]]></document></documents></author>