<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@drvox @c_arise Yes they will get left behind. The number of people in the US that are using motorized carts due to… https://t.co/zuO3GMP6oY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t fucking come at me trying to defend assault bc I’m fucking tired of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Ball family y’all watching on Sunday?? @SHO_Shameless @Lavarbigballer https://t.co/4F69kuUJus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kecatlin @kc8apf Drop vague references to contributors "proving themselves" before being allowed some responsibili… https://t.co/OedwEw7ez8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remember that 2 can play this game, and I will always play it better. 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Donate, donate, donate.🧥🧤💞👖👚👟👝 Do some #goodinyourneighborhood! 🏙👨‍👩‍👦‍👦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pell24Pell @WhitlockJason Oh ok... I can see your point to a degree...I don’t really give a crap what he thinks ab… https://t.co/Onwq77v0jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg this pink hair and lash combo is FIRE AF I wanna do it but with blue 👼🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: if you don’t see me again and its after 11pm...I’d come check on me.  Dad: Amelia I’m tired of this don’t fall… https://t.co/wwkvd5ALHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigues sumando puras cosas hermosas a mi vida. Gracias por todas estas emociones y sensaciones. Te quiero bien, te… https://t.co/MHAXU0ahvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought people in Congress were supposed to vote what the people in their district want and not what a bully cong… https://t.co/SD5Z3VwfVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamecockWBB WAY TO BOUNCE BACK ON THE ROAD AND GET THE DUB!! VERY PROUD OF ALL OF YOU!! # OWNIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Paul Godard, DDS u didn’t ask 1 question! U continued to browbeat Cohen like the other R’s making fools of thems… https://t.co/lhu50YUQ9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLeeBraxton @my3monkees @DouglasWarsko I don’t think a miscarriage would come out whole like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...I just got really emotional. I was not this emotional about it last year. Maybe because I was in a better pla… https://t.co/T41Gmvf7RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Thank you for your leadership Secretary Clinton. No matter what your political views are today-not be child deserves to die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailed it Corey ..why aren't arrests being made? Isn't that the job of the DOJ? #DonaldJTrump #RobertMueller]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting a video from @sebtsb last year to meeting him this year💗🥺 I couldn’t be happier! Honestly I didn’t expect h… https://t.co/dnjMtSU4Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my classes overlap concepts! Currently in my West African dance class I’m learning “the stick dance” wh… https://t.co/tOLdID4Inr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So powerful of a #FANBOOST endorsement that @svandoorne is a top Trending topic in the US at 4:30am... nice work… https://t.co/899hFuuCxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RandomActsOfKindnessDay  "Kindness never gets old"  Dress like Grandma or Grandpa day at school. https://t.co/exQ6dvqEWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean...🥰  #smitten  #engagementphotos  #friendsinlove  #couples  #centralpark #nyclove  #theknotweddings #hanbok… https://t.co/YZUuEhUwzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudeRedfield No, just the inches - so we are 1/7th of the way to a new record ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body Language and Medical Analysis №4221: Why are Donald Trump’s Pupils Intermittently So Large? by @DrGJackBrown… https://t.co/YXZKuDE0C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven no but I have to admit that if it's like this year's every year now I'll continue to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesjammcmahon @NME Well good luck with it and thank goodness for some small bits of awareness-raising.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why be there for someone, who doesn’t appreciate you being there for them? 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatronBullets you have inspired meh to betta an better threw my life i have been threw a lot of shit myself as thr… https://t.co/dXNi5g89tY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a meme folder with 124 memes on my camera roll is this why boys don’t like me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw WTF? Where are the guys in the white coats? He needs a straight jacket &amp; a padded room!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, I made a lopsided king cake for my daughter’s second grade class here in New England (thanks… https://t.co/EuQHEtOpTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @Nicklaus4Kids Thank you for all the  unknowledded work you and  our President are doing t… https://t.co/sbFMWgSXOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanhawkins67 Thanks for the follow #GoCubs #CubsFollowTrain looking forward to your tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrk_Immaculate so you couldn’t tell me my nephew be balling like that 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #marathon last weekend! The Alamo Marathon was awesome and I ended with a PR by 23 minutes! #running… https://t.co/mQ87Med8RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Human by Darkwater on Amazon Music https://t.co/mcYYUtbmv8  Its finally out. Check it out. My friends awesome band.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RageBot5000 What qualifies as a sin According to this arbitrary survey?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving through the mountains in Colorado, even in the middle of the night, is by far one of the coolest experiences I’ve had so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I watch a documentary that takes place mostly in LA — no matter how dark the subject matter — I find mys… https://t.co/d8pO9KN2fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMsCase It’s always so interesting that those sweet little affirmations come when you need them the most ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comer hot dogs, ver series malas y reír hasta que nos duela la panza, quedarnos dormidos el uno sobre el otro. Porq… https://t.co/CXCTzWHrL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a day late, but why is black history month the shortest month of the year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake This narrative of embracing falsehoods is truly bizzare. Unfortunately, today we are all witnesses to t… https://t.co/1Ohgozpvtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyB_Simcoe Only if you put LBJJ on it and have it ready by the weekend for the rest of the post season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got the same awesome #parkingspot today! The closest I can get to class. I'm so smug. #easilypleased… https://t.co/arhPueBert]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I am wide awake again because the babies are kicking me from both sides 😩😭😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ if it ain’t worth a second chance then why was it worth a first chance? “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Ok, Girly, We appreciate you want to be Nationally famous BUT, hopefully, not as a moron. Do consider… https://t.co/Miv0jCJeZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first time trying #BurgerBoy #chocolateshake #workingman #burger @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/Bt8sQO5dxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshRamsay Too bad we can’t bring a sword to the shows. Also, here’s my rocking chair from the 1820s. Who knows ma… https://t.co/qle23bjkbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, Gogel. You've outdone yourself! #patsselfonback #homecooking #nomtastic https://t.co/N9CSNb6KDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are nacho lovers, we are nacho friends @ The Teragram Ballroom https://t.co/G63oMHHyAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so sorry for my cat because he didn’t ask to come to this world and be annoyed/loved all at once and I JUST… https://t.co/MLMyaqeN84]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather have snow; she’d rather wear cut-offs. https://t.co/pTUKJWaiKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode #4: Talkin' Bout a (Sexual) Revolution  https://t.co/bESH3R7D0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagocircunt please @ the homosexual who was playing Zelda in the background of this video. I wanna ask him whic… https://t.co/Nnp8c7EkLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FabulousFifty ❤️@StephanieMcGo16 @SharonTowler https://t.co/rRRaSmpxc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday, gorgeous peeps! Make it a great one! ♥️☀️ https://t.co/WYMVZO3kKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother gave me a bottle of vodka for valentines and now the entire family knows I have a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate missing #AXSChat.  My week is not as rich when I miss people like you @KimPossible1809]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help donate to Fame “Lady Crush” so we can reach The Summit!! @UltimateClimb https://t.co/H0iXhWadyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d nor is there one who has fully stood up to hm and said "the wall is fake"]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother: it sound like you were saying supercaliFERGALICIOUSexbealidocious Me: ....I don't think that's.. right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKONOHIO @AdamSchiff @FoxNews @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @marthamaccallum @IngrahamAngle @foxandfriends Look at… https://t.co/m0V9VJdzA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pr26271 @BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump He needs to pay attention and to a Intelligence briefings, but instead watche… https://t.co/74Dr32KE3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just .@MPCelina being a boss. Thanks for being an awesome role model for young women getting into politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blackbird singing in the dead of night  Take these broken wings and learn to fly]]></document><document><![CDATA[cheating is not, nor will ever be okay. if you support it in any way, you’re disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorFedeli The only person who made them languish on fhe waitlist is your lying buddy @MacLeodLisa who’s going d… https://t.co/UoOiiVST51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Scottish warrior Sam heughan/jamie fraser Credit to tanyatartaruga  #Outlanderseason3 #LoveForSam💖 #Samheughan… https://t.co/FzeZJsY44m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygagaph Have you listened to the latest @ladygaga #MotherMonster inspired #WhatsYourJerseyPodcast 🖤🎙🏈 #Ladygaga… https://t.co/YHBvQeYbqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenHarley @saraclark @jennstolen @davidyunker @obsolete29 So, so lucky! 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ty2010b @theleakymind @LilithLovett Maybe replace "work" with "side tasks" or something of the like. There- entire… https://t.co/tYqG8khEBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSkutack @aaroncarter @aaroncarter I was planning on meeting you in person in August however Flint Michigan is als… https://t.co/jTTmkEPWPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a drunk @GuinnessUS sales rep tell me to go fuck myself (while flipping me off) after he says that George… https://t.co/Xk5JWoZuf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!! GREAT job last night ladies! You should all be very proud of yourselves! 👏🏻💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaximumCortez chicken nugget review is %100 correct. @Wendys tops the list and spicy @BurgerKing nuggets are weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawdustcitybeer Yay. Hopefully there will be Princess in the fridge next weekend when we will be there!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkwouter Sorry. Spent time watching him instead of worrying about grainy video in the sun. Maybe later this spring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m craving a peanut butter and bacon sandwich. And I don’t know if that would even be good🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDi12324775 @4evermccreerian @mantond @Mccreery02 @ACMawards @ScottyMcCreery I do know that God will prevail f… https://t.co/IQLSL5jIfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is within her,  She will not fail;  God will help her at break of day.  Psalm 46:5 NIV🙋🏾‍♀️💃🌍  #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG this Alan Jackson wall plaque is EVERYTHING. https://t.co/Nbs9vKHiGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF. WAY. THERE. (and still serving looks 👀😂) I can’t believe I’m #20weekspregnant with this sweet baby girl of mi… https://t.co/RWWfo2o27F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjl Agree we need to have enforcement mechanisms to drive policy, but why not move to an aggregate sharing model w… https://t.co/bodzFAC2Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran into my fave year of the pig Twitter account n I'm in luv https://t.co/AgpkE7iXDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Spider-Man! #marveluniverselive @ Verizon Arena https://t.co/QXZYVMGLRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you walk into your first CORPORATE YOGA studio!!! 😍💕🧘🏻‍♀️   #yogateacher #meditation… https://t.co/jTgdREyRtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd grade Lady Rangers are scrimmaging Perry Central tonight! @FPLadyRangers https://t.co/GtB9quEy5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hussiresvlog @heaathhussar @zanesbubba @euphorichussar @Heaths_peskie @tooafrid @msglasswoman @MariahAmato… https://t.co/GaCS9Duukr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Order your favorite looks from @gucci ‘s Spring runway collection today at https://t.co/aLvagQNj5f . #Saks #Gucci… https://t.co/EjJ8XMDWXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t unusual behavior for Republicans. They oppose Trump to such an extent that they deny his legitimate emer… https://t.co/srQxzEC02s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an #AmazonGiveaway I just won Coogam Rainbow St.... Check it out here: https://t.co/QciWxBBGWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Rep. Espitia! So thrilled for you AND #teamjulian on a fabulous hire. Your star keeps rising!… https://t.co/W9AVCin3WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love watching her get new skills Now to get it really good and then move it to the floor  #BAmily #PHANTOM5R https://t.co/IMxHJFCSxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a special birthday celebration!! Can’t get over how much love was in the room. #LYLYW #birthdaylove ❤️ @ The B… https://t.co/LjcAAYS97o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dogboy48 It is honestly entirely geared towards golfers of all ages and skill levels, with some points geared spec… https://t.co/jIUPvZG2dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Innes434 @LouSchoolBeat Maybe, but KERA was inacted because of state supreme court ruling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta Yes! Thank goodness this flight is as slow to board as my #Boston flight was!Clearly we won’t have an on-tim… https://t.co/Nmtf0vzTBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbslocal @kevin_nealon @DJ_Sixsmith @CarolinesonBway @ManWithAPlan I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Wo… https://t.co/RhcfYrvvWj]]></document></documents></author>