<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ConservativeTht @kaci150 @marklevinshow @DennisPrager @MedvedSHOW BAD ACTORS ON CENTER STAGE IN OUR GOVERNMENT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cute is this cutie! And get this. She's in med school!!! The pics were a must. How could we not?  . . . . .… https://t.co/Ngp9FbXY6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor keeper. ⚽️After a kick to the head at soccer, trip to the ER and stitches, she’s on day 5 of concussion pro… https://t.co/XcqGhGT8Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gumbygotguns @BettyBowers That woke me up to a living nightmare. Thanks a lot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Alex left me to die!!! So not the best boyfriend on the planet at the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up a Stromboli from Fiorella’s to be breakfast &amp; lunch and maybe parade food. #starving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stuartbrainerd You did not engage arguments offered, instead countering with silliness anyone with a search engine… https://t.co/8O9A2F0GqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad,sad,sad. Hilariously sad examples of toxic masculinity. Why guys? What are you trying to prove anyway? Or impre… https://t.co/0iPUPDQgpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprender a decir “no me merezco esto”. No me merezco que me traten de esta manera, que me respondan así o que me ig… https://t.co/dfh4F9g5R0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton, its a fire hazard to light candles and leave them unattended. Praying your room doesn’t burn down #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeDe, you are a sunshine boy~🌻🌻🌻 Really love u~😘😘😘 ️@titlekplee  #กลจของตต  #titlekrt  thx 原始素材 from logo https://t.co/Qvdmn1duFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler You are such a two faced.  You said Trump could fire Comey and now you say he was obstructing justi… https://t.co/Bx6cBPR0PT]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is watching right Babol @mainedcm  / Maine Mendoza  #MaineBDayIn3Days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridge2tabitha_ Me in college complaining about my 2 classes a day, after spending like 14 hours a day in the band… https://t.co/QTtRLFnHL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThiccVent @ChaotixEDM I seriously felt bad for the pleco bc of its environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will certainly help me be more effective - Great info graphic: Tired of wasting time in meetings?  https://t.co/AaQQxJXIGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBurnet79960811 @MSNBC If you actually had a clue about why the electoral college was created you wouldn’t make such an assinine comment!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it turns out, The Lion King is a LOT more emotional under the influence of wine]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my #cat, #nachocat is a real monkey.  Climbing shower curtains is his Forte.  Once he gets to the top he likes t… https://t.co/YRQ1cNT7sN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a cloudy day in Orlando so I felt this quote was fitting bc I feel my mood matches the weather but I have to r… https://t.co/qBvEjTDsBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @Wendys likes this, maybe we can get 1.00 from 10,000 followers and reach my goal of 10000.00 for wounded combat… https://t.co/UN74ILiu4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catalyst's exploitation of patients to raise the price of a life-saving drug from $0 to $375,000 is making them suf… https://t.co/ews43gbcY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annnd, the annual excruciating tax info gathering is done. I don't mind paying (reasonable) taxes, but this process… https://t.co/ypZwy0dNnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love playing with inspiring skies and this morning, it was so beautiful taking off from LAX! #skymagic #LAX… https://t.co/MBHz59fYSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to @Sherrichill for bringing lots of smiles today with lunch! #lovetoleadhere @CobbSchools @Comptoncubs https://t.co/7PDVm5rUt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the smallest things sets A.J off, he needs to stay single &amp; seek a Psychiatrist or a Psychotherapist #MarriedAtFirstSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloorItLk @Maureen11869591 @MindingMeLk @evelynmcmkting @pocaproductions @Sinead_od1 @DonegalWB @aechambersnove1… https://t.co/dK8ceXcPqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is so difficult  to find a pair of decent jeans that don’t have huge holes in them?!🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you, I worked hard for this award. I’d like to thank all three of my big ass water bottles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #6 I have  accepted the challenge from @Esl_Excellence to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or rev… https://t.co/8UYufDptMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Sorry dear but today America will unite and take in every word of Cohen's testimony. Your loser father… https://t.co/mRILw0qQ1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited that Ms Olivia will be a future coog @UHouston  #gocoogs @gwschattle281 @BaylorGirl2003]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best Coaches I have ever had 💜 #CrossFitGames #InTheOpen https://t.co/2vKQs4AvGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson How do you sleep at night? You are one of the most horrible people in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_J_I_1 @WickedWalnut It was only supposed to be six to begin with, but this actually explains a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough loss for C1, but great learning experience. @queencitymutiny #betterneverquits #painistemporary https://t.co/XpgmqSopUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[NUMBER 18! ✔️  °o° • • • #princesshalf #rundisney #nuun #asics #run4Dad #rundisneyfrance #castletochateau @ Epcot -… https://t.co/gi1mPGlK0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haitch_Kay @TakiTonfa @trilllizard666 Communism only works for hive community creatures like ants and bees. And hu… https://t.co/NCAm8WZWTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets now on sale for The Smallest Parade in the Universe March 2 at the Key West Theater.  Artist-designed float… https://t.co/QsXKfu5wLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another story I had the pleasure of writing! If this bill gets passed, it would be very interesting to see what bec… https://t.co/8fsWzD99cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[dang mine always try to scare everyone into not talking to me for selfish reasons smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numbers 32:23 says YOUR SINS WILL FIND YOU OUT. Whoever did this needs to pray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pranks #laughter #laugh #smile #hilarious https://t.co/vfJl6VuqFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11dmshhs @NBCThisisUs @chevrolet I think Nicky is important because he brings things full circle. He knows the “pr… https://t.co/25k3d3iD0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanderpumpRules @LisaVanderpump I’m going to Ceasers in 2 weeks can’t wait to visit the garden there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisOpfer Of course you meant “@jaclynmdiaz and I have the scoop”. People are getting that wrong all the time, in… https://t.co/l7FBtatLhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much thunder in Playa Vista. WHERE AM I?! #thunderstorm https://t.co/5NER3Li0sX]]></document><document><![CDATA[as someone pursuing public health i’m disappointed and yet relieved I will never be out of a job]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to remember this today! "Therefore encourage one another and build each other up, just as in fact you are do… https://t.co/79IfUzrM9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Says the guy whose harassed so many others. Even his own schools.  You seemed to have taught it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love getting images back from my weddings! How gorgeous are these shots by @emilyklester 😍😍😍. . . . .… https://t.co/Qa9zVOsLU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgrate_ Eggs with syrup | Hot Chips with White cheddar popcorn | Lays chips with ketchup | Ham sandwich or Hamburger with chips on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neither Do I !!! What are they THINKING WITH? ... I don’t think it’s their brain/head]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says I want to go for a run more than having 6 nine year olds in my house chanting songs I’ve never heard of. Send help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaylenDuke Actually no.  For all those who have experienced racism or prejudice he has to face the world and the j… https://t.co/vfUUasDGe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southshoreline Is there going to be any special advertising for Star Wars Convention Chicago in April?]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE CANCEL SCHOOL WILLIAM BLOUNT IS NO LONGER A SCHOOL ITS A PUBLIC SWIMMING POOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest things are happening in these next couple of months and I am so freaking excited, I can’t stand it 😍 #comeonjune]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a song to sing, and it’s a song about hope for you,  it’s a song about faith.  I see all that you are going t… https://t.co/r4e8I3z61M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that I became homeless again and honestly that's not how I wanted to start my week...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My ex legit calls me and texts me everyday.. why did god give me good pussy”😭😭💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take note, this is a HUGE reason why @CoachStephens_ and the @LadyPioneers_ are playing for ANOTHER championship to… https://t.co/7eLNN08HX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurisuS @FireGoddessB @BubblesResists @gff122106sjp @lisastark351 @cruxie @elena_center @ZPoet @Molly66810832… https://t.co/u79XzQJ2ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i could do cartwheels i’d be doing them right now https://t.co/dHpbY1V7Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[My late friend and neighbor initially got the death penalty in Mississippi for working in the civil rights movement… https://t.co/ZrZzv2Q9FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_SKG_1983 Ya he says shit like that all the time and global warming is really sun spots]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAGG IS LOOKING FOR LOVE... @GCSPCA is here on #GoodDayCharlotte to tell us about this sweet pup and how YOU can g… https://t.co/FQEFrldJ8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, I also have #lupus. I am sorry about your brother.  We are trying to improve outcomes for all of us with… https://t.co/z1YSkZHl1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Characteristics or strong mathematicians is the same as strong readers.  @mfannie #WSMI https://t.co/kmDVmkhYsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh great.. Mika's daily lectures aren't enough for ya, if you're a young woman, she'll be publishing them in a book… https://t.co/11v4yOQfBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabmartinez Bendiciones Pablo, gracias por éste medio que te veo desde Brooklyn, NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay Today ,I am making herstory.  How about you? How are you celebrating YOU?… https://t.co/CkZh5A9nVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job to our girl basketball team, dance team and cheer leaders team ! Go COBRAS ! @BocaRatonMiddle https://t.co/uLg5sRtvGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dasenbrock12 ...and you're a wonderful coach.   Remey has learned so much from you in the little time he has had with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akgonnella @CongerKim Yes, I am still searching tap dancing videos... Tap dancing for beginners! https://t.co/p9pdtu9wEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hblackburnnn @carlisle_brooke @YoastAric What’s good with everyone rn Jesusssssssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day, I’d like to celebrate the female who inspires me the most. #daughter #InternationalWomensDay19 https://t.co/7z8HjsXnOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissyElliott Yes absolutely true I get anxiety, bad to the point I feel shortness of breath]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts BUT REPUBLUCANS PROTECT WIFE ABUSERS! They refuse to sign the VIOLENCE AGAINST WOMEN ACT! So tell me… https://t.co/j94pwk1Xlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @downtown_austin Getting here early in the day for breakfast brisket tacos. They sell out.  https://t.co/d5iast4fTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaMDO1 I would go bc you hit the two week mark and things could be morphing into sinus or ear infections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @WSJ Preet.. can you clarify why Managort was in solitary confinement? It seems harsh to me. I would appreciate your input. 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Slow news night? Cannot believe you are spending so much time covering @JussieSmollett More #FakeNews I have a… https://t.co/2QjYWBOttO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The customer service at this establishment @Budget is 10/10 on Opposite Day. I wonder if they are going to help us… https://t.co/OXj3S2cULg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Schools can engage partners to make sure students have access to mental health services and that their nutritional… https://t.co/G7gUKEhOY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Madness kick off! Who will be the MVP? Let’s learn! #CCSDMathMadness @ClarkCreekSTEM @iReady @CurriculumAssoc https://t.co/RyJ9pb8HN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CARINA rescued  by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Po Village #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea   Breed: Jindo Mix  To adopt C… https://t.co/xkC6ICMTZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my favorite Ole Miss Reb! @JustDeW_itt12 #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen hearing: Cohen says Trump instructed him to threaten people hundreds of times  https://t.co/vmGmM1kNpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[New research has found that doctors specializing in cancer treatment aren’t as well-versed in #trans health needs a… https://t.co/cXDyR1mnsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna say I was awake to witness the time jump forward and I also would like to say it’s rude asf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie_Leigh_ Regardless if people would buy them you should start either way because getting yourself out there is… https://t.co/4cT8qMKmin]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6UkX8dT9Bg @Ashton5SOS u do look like shaggy u should consider it full time #iHeartAwards @5SOS #5SOSFAM #BestFanArmy 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom: “you were the hardest kid to raise, and you’re still just the worst child I have” OKAY JANE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RecomiendoLeer El FARERO,   de Pino Naranjo @Pino_Naranjo https://t.co/oqqCff50MN  La mar y sus hombres, el amor d… https://t.co/Q8Zk47pos1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about your #plastic use, dependency. Try one thing, then another and another. Challenge your lifestyle. Turn… https://t.co/OeSfs6t5lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need winter to be over so my battery stops freezing plz and thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how someone can y’all so much mess about you and still be on your line, smh. 🤦🏾‍♀️ girls and guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*In MedSurg* Me. López: what can I do to help you for the exam? Us: do a review like what we need to know specifica… https://t.co/LEtb3GwtGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we were rattlesnake munchers and museum delinquents 🖼 🐍 https://t.co/3Zi9NdkQox]]></document></documents></author>