<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just got my tax return in so it’s time to buy something super fuckin ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuritacarpio Si no es problema de Salud publica, porqué invertir en abortos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_B_Crumb Yeah. I’m surprised. Have to expect them to lock up didi soon also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @Bill_Dance1 has a Twitter makes me so happy. Top 3 greatest legends to ever make a Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyrich1 This is such a glorious Russian disinformation play. Will we ever know which “journalists” were compromised?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @DMRegister Iowa Poll is out.  A lot to digest in the approval ratings.  Bloomberg net favorability -11, was +9… https://t.co/MxsvtPfXsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revolvermag It’s not been recent but Rush was best show I’ve ever been to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostKarin Just add a couple cats, and you have all you need to ale anywhere a home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2016-17 sucked big time but made me better than I thought. My ability to search for a job and overall resourcefulne… https://t.co/XgKQc6FROM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my beautiful wife and kids @lindseycbeck Emory “walking bucket” Beck, Bennett “Mr.Clean” B… https://t.co/tWM2et5Slg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @TuckerCarlson He did an excellent job and it was absolutely the truth. He is among only a few that actually tells the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solangeknowles I JUST WANNA WAKE UP ON CP TIME https://t.co/1sfxVvbVaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyJamPed Either then or now 🤙                           for me? I make mistakes every single day so every ‘failure… https://t.co/cY9QT86KmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullyray5150 @BustedOpenRadio @davidlagreca1 The Hardy Boyz  Tommy Dreamer  Rob Van Dam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please let President Putin know that we appreciate the suggestion though and we hope he will support working within… https://t.co/VMayZLMf7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarnTheWorld Got any real-life spy games? Covert CIA missions.... stuff like that??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Every time I see Gaetz on TV, I wonder what kind of constituents would send someone of his ilk to… https://t.co/7tlkfYhxjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leegough1 @DT2ComicsChat @Kenwar950 @Sric360 @SoloDoloGamer @JamesGavsie @elisebby01 @EByzio @The1stBAT… https://t.co/ZsfEQgDkyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@60sPsychJukebox @uncutmagazine The founder of Aural Innovations, a knowledgeable writer I never met, wrote the fol… https://t.co/YOpqMC0DUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @aarrrgggghhhhh3 @jade3457 @philemon_owona @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch https://t.co/3myC7rUhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #StarWars friends check out this awesome new podcast i found strong in the force these two are! Listen to Ep 4:… https://t.co/Lr5WaMaar3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was one piece of information I would have preferred not knowing. Ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roleplayers_TV @WyrmwoodGaming @r_a_salvatore No love but much in the way of desire and lustful obsession💯🕸🕷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostRoz @partlowj @NickMiroff @Fahrenthold The Trump Crime Family has a hunting lodge - perfect. Is it in Apalachin, NY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So beautiful I don’t know how people can just kill them to brag about shooting a giraffe and or elephant. They make… https://t.co/ft9vz30FCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willchamberlain @PoliticalKathy They are just as bad as the rest of them I heard them speak all they wanna do is r… https://t.co/hCd9H9lra8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets A tactic used in North Korea, China, Nazi Germany. Jail those not rolling the party line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes for the truth about socialism, the peons and not the leaders or dictators know what it is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImAaronBro252 Probably get better service that US Cellular any day of the week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutnumberedFNC Why do you let Marie Harf Get away with out right lying]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION ⁦@ShopRiteStores⁩ Customers!! 🚧🚧🚧🚧🚧🚧  Check out ‘Specials’ on the Cereal and Sweet Cakes Aisles...  ... B… https://t.co/wl62DhvWxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Andy McCabe! Yes!  Why does the president of the United States and everyone in his orbit have an abnormal amoun… https://t.co/07825cLFTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathieDello I have had one since age 20 PERFECTLY positioned near my hairline, that sticks straight up. I know I a… https://t.co/hySsffWLQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Rosey. You will be maximizing your day with 2am wake up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[49 shot attempts for Boston (26 on goal, 9 blocked, 14 missed net) to 23 for Ottawa (14 on goal, 5 blocked, 4 misse… https://t.co/R4pwNbRXSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellemx_ Danielle , te ves preciosa y espectacular como siempre besos 😍😘😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically fuck the new Puppet Master. I will never watch another one. @fullmoonhorror @shudder did you even watch t… https://t.co/iSrJOPR6P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me at my open house!!! Dm for directions #therealtorjohnv #townandcountry #realtor #morenovalley… https://t.co/JMyaLhQnT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@podcastnotes @naval @nivi "the harder I work, the luckier I get". (oldie, not perfect, but true).  So many "smart… https://t.co/P6TfH6Qvfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boy_myth_legend I am so sorry about your loss I lost my dad almost a year ago I understand the pain he will be in… https://t.co/TZDzzrJiJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a cake - it tastes like victory!  Thanks Julie and boys for the great birthday...and to everyone who reached o… https://t.co/qh1so4qSWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[great 🍎 @9Artemi ! thanks. i called it and anxiously await some #bucciovertimechallenge gear @Buccigross https://t.co/TZpD8IanI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 It’s so true. Bron 😂 please 😂 stop 😭 ... 😂  Also, you can tell LeBron is no music guru simply by the odd ways he’… https://t.co/5HAXlmeGN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am ashamed of myself for looking a man in his eyes with this face “🥺” and telling him that I want his nut on international womens day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The K9 is Summit and her handler is EMS Manager Andrew Holcomb of the SFDPH EMS Agency. @sfdph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennesseine @BernieSanders Bernie and nonBernie supporters must keep their eyes on the objective of unseating Trum… https://t.co/WXbx9LR3Lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We win by forfeit and are in the playoffs of the Intermural league... lol.  🤷‍♂️😱💯 https://t.co/u2OodqBoC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[promo me?? im ryan, he/him i love overwatch, OWL, homestuck, kpop, nintendo, mortal kombat, kingdom hearts, and a l… https://t.co/cdm0Ttlkq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having to watch #UKvsUT on DVR, but PJ Washington making Admiral Schofield  look more like Ensign Schofield. https://t.co/TTXESQlflf]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point in my life,ive given up and since im going to hell  anyway might as well enjoy the trip gping there.… https://t.co/qpFbTlb46p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm Bob, if Alexis’ football form was a middle school aged teen, you’d be going thru it’s things and wondering if it’s on drugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TragicLoss your  ig brother has lost it @TheHaleyBaby your on my side on pizza what do you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend: *hands me the aux chord* You’re not gonna play The 1975 again, are you? Me: https://t.co/tfYcDR0bTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwltvweather A most heartfelt tribute to all the Chief Meteorologists of @WWLTV Channel 4 #EyewitnessWeather who h… https://t.co/k6PUzYT6GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think America loves the "N-word" now wait until they find out it's gender neutral.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't decide if I actually like our new primaries... kindof looks like everyone's walking around wearing black vests from the back. #ATLUTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some big wet flakes in Ballard. Radar looking nice! https://t.co/C3hVBjq05W]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AceHardware, is there a way to add rewards points from a previous purchase if I just joined the rewards program once I was home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[currently my to-read pile. will try to push through most of it tonight. also will try to tweet thoughts about some… https://t.co/wIzT33d2m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adams just stepped on Favors' foot and fell and Gobert gets a foul cuz he was standing there]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been a problem since Obama to get the fuck on going somewhere and learn some shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipcoffey Chip, they just announced 22 fatalities in Lee County, Alabama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joek726 @DNFWing @NTRA I heard a rumor about the solution and i think you’ll find it’s MUCH better than the curren… https://t.co/snmLNXVtBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DitchThatTxtbk @craigklement @SEANJFAHEY @wizardwarren @jmattmiller @emosier3 @CoachJonCraig @MandiTolenEDU… https://t.co/5BRb7VVnDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfChrisMJones All. The. Time.  I find myself constantly asking them, “Have I told you this?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acebannon I don’t even know what that is.  How old were you?  What sparked your fascination with muscle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CanJamSEWinter - Drinking a Straight Outta Middletown by @eqbrewery at @triplecrossing  — https://t.co/zYi4TvJ2j1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CinderSlays I appreciate you! Not saying this because you are a Clemson fan as well either 🐅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisparente @SamBoik @everyday_show I think you’re most happiest at the age of 2 and 75 because your only concern… https://t.co/IpC52YpSHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they come with you they'll come, if they won't then they won't ... keep doing you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregaming for DKM tonight!! - Drinking a Baltic Brotherhood Baltic Porter by @huttonsmithbrew/@Craftybbrewery at… https://t.co/RC1vwWOdEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went for a belated Valentine's Day brunch in NYC today. It was all delicious. https://t.co/hrpNYXlHbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ Ben Simmons just change your fucking shot. Your free throws are so damn bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMPACTWRESTLING @SantanaLAX @Ortiz5150 @PENTAELZEROM @ReyFenixMx @Konnan5150 https://t.co/1QTf6ecO4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKYBOIMAN50 @ChrisSeelbach @700wlw Did he share any "deflective" comments?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louis_seube @BrianCorley13 @BrewsterMac @john35592542 @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Obama was a failure.… https://t.co/cHPV2x2pqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was debating this as my response:  This isn’t even remotely true 😂. $900 billion is roughly 5% of GDP...if illegal… https://t.co/n54Ywe2jF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you make your apologies if need be and clear the air with those you may be at conflict with, for you NEVE… https://t.co/rqm02Y0vSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draco_Rider @bkbkb79 @jax_persists He doesn't need a reason, and the reasoning you just invented is a product of your own paranoia, not his]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexFischCC Thank you! It’s not Daylight Savings time people hate, it’s Standard Time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another major study confirms no connection between autism and MMR vaccine https://t.co/IsA1UomZKF via @TheWeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to Target and Costco this morning without having to use GPS. #GreatSuccess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicolex723 LMFAOOOOOOOOOOO guess I was talking to a wall yesterday ... thanks for the ted talk tho 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JP_856 @SportsRadioWIP Ohhh, you’re trolling me. Gotcha. Nobody is this dumb. Good one. Got me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are very generous with our money.  Have you ever paid employees from your own earnings?  No.  You haven’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Segui a dica que vi por aí sei lá onde de escrever um resumo dos meus últimos 5 anos na vida profissional e o que q… https://t.co/Fspj64E3Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda05352402 Thank you! Rough flight through the storm but finally landed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/EOHTTqYXXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek @BMS_Arianna I got playing “doctor” with the neighbor girl at like 6. In 6th grade my buddy T… https://t.co/6HLNKCXlDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I've been a little tired lately. I'm either driving in my bed or sleeping on the streets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronFontana @HOMAGE @KatieAnnFontana @EastonTownCtr Im talking about both of you!-)+ #AllFour 🚺 🚹 🚼 🔥☝ 🌟… https://t.co/y6Mw6vDuQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats have the power to block funding for this small but still significant diplomatic initiative. Here’s to hop… https://t.co/bT8x8TsUGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shame Mane can be so inconsistent with finishing at times because on his day he’s world class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC MAYBE SANDERS SHOULD GO AND SUPPORT MADURO AND COMMUNIST CUBA !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotsProShop Yes, that's the case (Mexico). Thanks! I'll contact them ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s the BOSS? Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides! @walkerfordco fordperformance ford… https://t.co/NA0Fs7xI5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official - McKenna’s behind the wheel and I survived.... Great job Mac! @ Lancaster, Pennsylvania https://t.co/v3EVRdVQY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WHEN YOU CARESS HER HEAD, SAY THANK YOU, TELL HER HOW BEAUTIFUL SHE IS AND MOST IMPORTANT. . . LET HER KNOW SH… https://t.co/xR10yFS0K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rayados Vamos Rayados,, rumbo al clásico Regio,, todos somos el resto, en la vida y en la cancha, sin violencia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christopher Alan Pallies better know by the ring name King Kong Bundy has passed away at the age of 61! RIP… https://t.co/pXOzx2UEoj]]></document></documents></author>