<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@thatgalcaleb this reminded me of you and William Carlos Williams https://t.co/WOaCOMDN9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @RussVought45 Nice try, but this is bull crap. He wants to cut enviorment protection even more so his b… https://t.co/nqjjDv1zYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good #SaturdayMorning, y’all! —A Hawthorn bush (I think) in bloom https://t.co/xISgqhwbBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what Xavier Simpson is going to buy Cassius Winston for Father’s Day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Song For A Whale by Lynne Kelly | Book Talk https://t.co/fToFCV6r0z via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not too often that you get to watch your newscast twice in 12 hours... https://t.co/BudLVjpngE]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF👏🏼YOUR👏🏼FRIENDS👏🏼LEAVE👏🏼YOU👏🏼ALONE👏🏼OR👏🏼LET👏🏼YOU👏🏼GO👏🏼HOME👏🏼WITH👏🏼STRANGERS👏🏼WHILE👏🏼YOU👏🏼ARE👏🏼OUT👏🏼YOU👏🏼NEED👏🏼NEW… https://t.co/VhnEw2PHZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VelshiRuhle @GarrettHaake @EvelynNFarkas @KellyO @mjhegar @RepRoKhanna @JohnJHarwood @MSNBC Remind your viewers th… https://t.co/iYhcC8Ntto]]></document><document><![CDATA[My liberal guilt is never higher than when I’m sitting in my home office responding to email while my housekeeping… https://t.co/nI49ZSX7XO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the sentence next week will help to compensate for this week's.  I hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly... Bruno Mars, John Mayor, Harry Styles, and Ed Sheeran are probably the most talented people on the plane… https://t.co/giC6UA4s0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paceamoregelato I think I have one of these on the shelf if you don’t want to wait...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a group of contemporary dancers try to break up a bar fight was the cherry on top of my night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[these cars stay passing me and getting mad like if a bitch can afford to get another speeding ticket]]></document><document><![CDATA[At $12 a pop, I wouldn't drop my vodka soda either! #iamup #Mavericks https://t.co/2mcESIZYLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LingZhiTweet @mmpadellan Do you understand the level of anger rising up in this country against Trump and everythi… https://t.co/Oei7PONFyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk like you mean it. #mirth #snicker #grin #cute https://t.co/Hpn2jdSoYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColnJav86 @BebaDril7 @Anibal_da_G @Miss_Higgi @MMViverito @JumaaneWilliams @CidEloisa @TeamCucusa @AngeloCas1ano YEAH!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you taking the ACS-CCSE exam? I'm here to help you study. Reach out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que será de “calle y poche” cuando se separen o durarán para toda la vida ? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday.   #happyfriday #relax #enjoythesmallstuff #weekendvibes #takethebackroads #buyyourselfflowers… https://t.co/s2YB9L5Ouy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love waking up early to soak in some sun before work! ☀️ #Floridalife https://t.co/eruVZ1QbSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Stoked. Can't wait to get back home and clean these up tomorrow then get some tires on them. #zauber… https://t.co/9hb2UKOU8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove by a deer laying in the middle of the road still alive after it got hit by a car and almost called out of work cuz I was too sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnwoolf @DoingRight1 @bigleaguepol Punt ur balls when u get to prison because that’s where ur gonna end up at]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi listen to the song Take Courage by Lindy Conant if you want your life to wrecked   “There's a "yes" in our heart… https://t.co/0TOmermgD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeLDuncan If God is not sovereign over all things, including adversity and suffering, then He is not God. In o… https://t.co/FgGPKJf8l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cafezinho após 12 horas dentro daquela lata de sardinha! #orlando #miniferias #carnadisney #orlandofolia… https://t.co/AnbZU4KHOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boxter me despertó porque escuchó un ruido en ma cocina, no descansó hasta que fuimos a ver que pasaba *se cayó la… https://t.co/rpwvfN5W68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OLDFLACO @MABob1 @TheSteveKon @ChrisBragdon @sappermartin @Brenderm1 @secretstranger9 @trumpAngel45 @Sy_Crux… https://t.co/hCOWP3HpNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent video of citizens in Iowa trying to walk to the store for supplies. https://t.co/jKpgq5QuQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saraadactyle I don’t get paid til next month but I need some color! The last time I had my hair done I did a littl… https://t.co/Ky9cgbzRwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successfully accomplished Rise N Grind.... now time to go have Breakfast with Ana then work....   #OperationMomBod… https://t.co/rj6Jk5Vk7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WISH_TV I can’t say I wouldn’t have done the same. Maybe not the exact same thing. My husband had Dobermans when m… https://t.co/EoIXk8DzdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baue0160 @SapientHetero @Billy0623 @charliekirk11 Hopefully It’s coming to A FBI agent near you!  Comey, McCabe an… https://t.co/6tHa3hQ3Pz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career Day @GrayElemEagles. Learning about becoming an Emergency Medical Technician, Emergency Medical Driver, and… https://t.co/Z4zcnVs18Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entre cada célula viiiives tu! Todo lo llenas tu! Que vienes y pasas como un huracaaaaa-han.. tu!tu! Total y pleno… https://t.co/6WmB7tzUUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part of grad school hasn’t been the workload or stress (although both are difficult), but adjusting to… https://t.co/rqrhbq6HwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers @JKCorden @latelateshow I absolutely loved everything about this!! Also, can our fandom name be called the #FamJam? 😄🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cera has been hanging out with Ryan way too much she’s for sure scheming on him and all his belongings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers @realDonaldTrump Make sure he wears shoes with good arches. Helps with bone spurs. https://t.co/ePhtD6Jee8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @11madisonn !!!! Hope you have an amazing day!!💕💕 https://t.co/zQk5BK8d7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair as a youngish person with a scary diagnosis (Parkinson’s)  I wanted to share this with you ❤️💙 https://t.co/x1wD2bi2Ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craiggroeschel I have found the perfect combo! @craiggroeschel leadership podcast and @Bose frames 👏🏼 throw the oc… https://t.co/aqLHdWRDEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt We need Medicare for all. The job of the government is to protect its citizens from dangers both f… https://t.co/imdsDENEQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get alot of compliments on my hair but the best one was yesterday when he said it looks like the reds growing out… https://t.co/b7ifwivNXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That wasn’t the point— how she treats her staff was 😐😑 Mind blowing how people fixate on a stupid detail and ignore… https://t.co/pneRsFqZWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDX_zombie My daily struggle. I told my friends if they see me with pizza, slap me in the face. https://t.co/poJ5MlVOJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally cut myself off at 9/10pm (somewhere between those!) and still managed to get LOST at mgm... last night wa… https://t.co/4Hab8zwP1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheri_lynn95252 @RoverDov123 @Bren_O1967 @DrJimmyStar @greg_dabbs @DavidDiehl20 @KFearri @petergraigs… https://t.co/k9VYRv3pEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xstitchyn426 @mikebarnicle @realDonaldTrump But he DOES know how to lie and con still so he's useful to Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I discovered the #ASMR movement and videos.  WHAT IN THE WORLD, Y'ALL??? https://t.co/VuwVOuRo5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA uber drivers always take the “backroads” aka dark alley ways and tunnels and it really :$) makes me feel some kinda way]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Sunday....and my dad is wearing one of his long sleeved shirts that he usually wears to work  "Dad, get some s… https://t.co/HpEP6XZo2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. You get to sit back and make fun of everyone who doesn't...  You're welcome🖐🔥 https://t.co/rKxnqD9KLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I so sincerely 🖤 everyone and also #TheBlackAlbum! 🖤🖤🖤 https://t.co/nM8SUxzgbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRnDCSportFan Sure dude. 2017 report said Nats are moving on from Bryce Harper. 2018 Bryce said I’d love to stay i… https://t.co/sKrmhAcJY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthurq @CrazyCancerLady @LovlyKatieLumps @WhereDoesitLead Your very welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[But without faith it is impossible to please him: for he that cometh to God must believe that he is,…… https://t.co/dPcfiDcCEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamentMyIcarus Wow! He did not understand your body language.  He sounds like a creeper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love vampiros, I love tortilla de maíz tostadita con carnita encima y guacamole, I love México.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat is catty corner.  😉  #crazycatlady #catsofinstagram #catsoftwitter #gingercat @ Gulfport, Mississippi https://t.co/PRVBpRgXgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to getting almost 1000 new like on Facebook in like 3 days!!!  @Twitter fans where you at😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what a Monday morning is all about!! Thank you God for all my blessings!Rend Collective - Counting Every Bl… https://t.co/14I1AnjKF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskVelB I’ve never experienced it with the thought of someone else in the room. Basically my mind will be FULLY co… https://t.co/rfNyrpQQgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephengdavey @NYT_Crossword I don't think you could clue 118 as a 5 letter word even with a rebus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to take my annual crying pic w Kinley on her birthday which is now today since it’s after midnight!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenluluthepug The noise is so scary and your other puppy had you in a vice grip with his knees that you couldn’t… https://t.co/Z3rN0mwK2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Segunda cúpula de Donald Trump com Kim Jong-Un disputa atenção com noticias diretas de Washington que são desfavora… https://t.co/zx32aJhPNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews @CBSNews Enough about Smollett!  You need to be talking about the plot to kill legislators and jour… https://t.co/tIie8CL59c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complete me Father... Leviticus 25:18 "Accomplish my precepts, and observe my judgments, and complete them, so that… https://t.co/2OIepxLHYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta talk about it so we can change it. Happy #IWD2019 ⚡️#WithoutThisWoman #BalancedForBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[ethan hawke was there for nothing last yr and now he wins and he isnt here he hates me huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so only one girl gets his virginity and the rest get sloppy seconds? #thebachelor https://t.co/NVtCH05Pzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay now my boy @DJKASTONE about to go in on @EBROINTHEAM @HOT97 !! Oye what’s gooood Kast uno?! 👋🏽👋🏽✊🏽😎💋💎™️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How proud I am of my sweet Ellis! He is now the voice of the 11-2:00 slot at the UofM radio station, The Jazz Lover… https://t.co/I5qoGTSwfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Waiting for that to come slithering out if the woodwork, D &amp; S.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC That is because he has no clue. Is still in office because of voter fraud and voter suppression! Trump obvious… https://t.co/LCFH83Pp6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IiiMorring Thanks so much for watching! Yes I’ll have to check it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IG is about to crash with all the Las Vegas snow pics being posted ⛄️❄️ #DesertRats]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I have to wash my hair....again https://t.co/q3ZUa31aWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw my baby @Emmawith2ms and all her bffs who are so welcoming to me, as I stepped into the house party. She has… https://t.co/Z63QDwk6bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your client gives you less than 24 hours notice to push out your project, it’s a 4am coffee with whip kind of… https://t.co/i7ipdCj0nV]]></document><document><![CDATA[... *grabs popcorn* .......... ANDDDD IT CONTINUES!  Thank you I need this distraction while I get a root canal or… https://t.co/QAaMbaHTFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you missed the Oscars last night.... 🎶🎵 #LadyGaga #BradleyCooper #Shallow #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3Lduadkv3R this best have order be fan of her https://t.co/n8KZHqzQZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning to this guy passed out in my lobby at 2AM and this guy passed out in my lobby at 2AM only https://t.co/9xIZM5HHhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about this Thursday.... @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/tNpy4uRR8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArchivistsRock How have you not moved south yet 😭😂 I love snow but this is too much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought yesterday was Thursday all day. Pretty rude it’s still Thursday 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mardisgras #silverhair #over50 #youtuber #comingsoon #sephorasquad @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/oLvxJmeSjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the mood to do karaoke which is strange because I have bad stage fright]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a good surprise!! (My mom is pretty great and pulling them off btw...) My bro was able to make it here from Ca… https://t.co/cBOBACvfK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[اب انڈیا ہمارے سرپرائز کا انتظار کرے: DG ISPR ببر شیر ❤️💪 #GetReadyForSurprise  https://t.co/xr26Pz5cAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo un chingo de suerte pa' que me escoga la gente para marcarme en la peda en plena madrugada]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now they’re going after Trump charities and never a word about the Clinton foundation 🙄the left has finally dri… https://t.co/sKntv26v70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Who's writing her material? She couldn't pronounce Contra...does she really know what she's talking about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big state, big statue, from the “Fragile Beauties” series @ Stephen F Austin Statue https://t.co/v9BHhEwqoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnitude 1.8 #earthquake, 24.8 km NE of Eureka Dunes, CA https://t.co/Chyc7hu1u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um, so it’s 2:13 am here and I just woke up over a dream where I was best friends with @KDTrey5 and he FaceTimed me… https://t.co/FZJltXR7Lm]]></document></documents></author>