<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Daniel Strum's SH goal gives @SHS_CBNAPuck a 3-1 lead over @PHSScores @NewmarketMules . 7:18 2nd. @FostersDailyDem… https://t.co/eiGwr4udoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Back2NaturalDoc Hi Gillian! This is HUGE! Congratulations again on this feat! I screened it myself and really thin… https://t.co/zigTqHVY9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brighton should have been down to 10 inside 30 seconds. And then he goes and scores the match winner. Oh, football...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm annoyed with the people saying NYC "lost" Amazon when 1) not one Gd thing is stopping them from coming here lik… https://t.co/eTfS4JTdau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meesismijnbroer Good Morning Sem! *Happy Thursday* 😎👍 https://t.co/PgQFE0F3dX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad place to spend a birthday — St. Petersburg, Florida 🎂 https://t.co/ljWbp0X6nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @AceHardware employees for taking time to teach kids things. Today we watched the paint being mixed. https://t.co/3TIZiTGawu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I’m watching Terrifier, and it’s actually pretty creepy. The most terrifying looking clown I’ve ever seen. https://t.co/QPDU0eVA9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[✅ Insistir en la idea 4-3-3 entendiendo las características de los jugadores a disposición. ✅ Cuando el equipo atac… https://t.co/Q7Byss9jHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruPharaoh JFK is pissed that Repugnantcans sent a self-confessed traitor and rapist to the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news, @casforachange. Your chances of being in a school shooting are ridiculously low. You’re way more likely… https://t.co/ORgYKjuIcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im excited to live with these beautiful babies again in a month. https://t.co/lpnCVFHN5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaForAmerica HUGE - VERY DANGEROUS!! RUSSIAN WEAPONS - MUSLIM Islamic Centers being used to cache Russian weapo… https://t.co/EFDfpgoHmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, am I crazy or did @wilw eaton have a cameo as a blue alien on tonight’s episode of @TheOrville?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Colbadilla Cast Iron Pork Chop on top of a bed of spicy sauerkraut - Variant  - - #sauerkraut #porkchop #dinner… https://t.co/2dKhJBGV72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosVerareal Siempre hay ilusos. Lo q nunca esperabamos en USA.  Nepotismo corrupcion y possible traicion.  Pero hay obtusos e ilusos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raludwick So true. Also so many of these providers are so stressed, overburdened and worked, and paid poorly too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many great visions on this road... This was only the beginning... Great moments ahead  #MensPhysique #Physique… https://t.co/yZIvLW3nSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick up and back flight today to serve my Alma Mater @lancasterbible. Excited to see my youngest @Brother_Ave.… https://t.co/P572j0eJiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidR10 @bmproenza @FutbolPR @recreaydeportes @tabpr @FutbolPR_ @juanbfutbol @DeportesEND @UnivisionSports… https://t.co/rfTEM1z1ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConceptualJames Yes, that is the problem. Regardless of any theoretical merits or destructiveness, this is a relig… https://t.co/1BLsGYLqOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried streaming tonight but my internet was not cooperating. I will try again tomorrow with a return to RDR2. Sorry everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mention people scaming claiming to make Dabs from your weed and actually stealing it and using garbage in it… https://t.co/ct05xdSTLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicbyglc and I met Mark Ibanez and Jason Applebaum from @ktvusports! Great talking a little baseball and hockey… https://t.co/BkwhEBWXWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda miss NYC before each subway station had WiFi. There could be a new Pope by the time I reached my train stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Churriosity (2018) by @thebruery/@horusagedales @ Stouthouse — https://t.co/73WaZCvvZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karl_diesel I would hate for you to ever go thru what I went thru this morning.  I couldn't breathe for about 15 m… https://t.co/WRzbYajInv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swhiteCMS @trhart1 @alicekeeler @marktavern Thanks. So, to me the policy is not so much the issue as its implement… https://t.co/TDK3Zpio5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home bound (@ Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/huknSkq59x]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love you @ladygaga   When you get knocked down, you just gotta get back up. No problem, sis u got this https://t.co/KwfE4P1p0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Android Is Helping Kill Passwords on a Billion Devices https://t.co/7oWEzIusLP #security]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Tesla Model S Tesla Model 3 Tesla Model X Tesla Model Y https://t.co/2MJKKyR8oJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y si haces la primera llamada a los campos tétricos y te regresan tomando la segunda oportunidad. Y cambias todas t… https://t.co/x5qp6RhV7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC  your SUPREME LEADER is NOT most people He believes he can do anything including shooting someone… https://t.co/MayrzkOpwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hnl_8 No no no no I still remember one of those scary pop up videos from when I was around 4 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I never got on the Bernie bandwagon. I just don’t think he gets POC and always points to what he did in… https://t.co/s0XyDcMsV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dude_mark I think I may have accidentally screwed things up while trying to introduce Chantal to the Offspring...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait Cool.  Now the repetition seems preening and clueless at the same time.    https://t.co/sJIA8vXoxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christopher Lee has a small but great role in SEASON OF THE WITCH as well. I’d completely forgotten that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Henry looking good n the pre show. @superkickingit @SATPOD @smarktodeath @SuplexCityLimit  @DrHugeShow… https://t.co/zEbR5VxQdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story broke while we were on-air. We spent 30 minutes power ranking the soups best suited for throwing. So muc… https://t.co/F6wuw46rO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more you pour into something good, the more you will receive in return. If you’re not getting anything in retur… https://t.co/fsEOOCBc6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beauties_Angels @GaryEll85341441 @autumnfallsxoxo @DjDarcieDolce @ScarlettSageX @JaydenCole @shylajdotcom… https://t.co/2ATHNq7Hmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juice WRLD is just a wannabe Chris Brown... equally as bad of a person with worse music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@930VM @thomas_mulford @SuzRiebold @LoveBling6 @WeWhoWait1776WW @JENsen4Truth @MrsMogul @Dollfinish… https://t.co/YKKa182qaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/BrsRCGVirR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got my shit rocked tn and pretty sure i have a concussion but it’s fine im fine😂🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s only so much you can do to help someone but if they truly don’t want to help themselves there is no point b… https://t.co/jQwdA3x5G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#People #Pictures #Portraits #UnknownPeople  #LuisFelipeGaspar #LuisFelipeGasparRetratos ​  #Mexicali… https://t.co/eSpsaELODg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have the opportunity to have quite an influence on those around us on a daily basis, making others stand out and shine ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey, sign the Rubio-Sinema letter to join @RepPressley in the fight to protect #Medicare #PartD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaCarterTO Hey Melissa and Happy Thursday From my alternative music station 😘😘💖💖💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes As a LGBTQ member, I feel you are including me in your wonderful family 💋💋💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Way past time for you to stop lying but that day will never come. Those of us that despise you and… https://t.co/4lQkU5ReWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2018, we added automatic bank reconciliation and certified payroll reporting to #Sage100cloud. If you missed the… https://t.co/o1CNAmWKOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVietor08 @charles_gaba I honestly don’t think this will make a bit of difference to anyone at all at this point.… https://t.co/lWqYgypdiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExpansionMx @ExpEconomia ¿Escucharon a @lopezobrador_  lo que comentó de que se van a perder $25 mil millones si n… https://t.co/1PEnJyFtJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer- Intimacy with God that leads to the fulfillment of His purposes  @DanielHenderson #Prayer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraNTrier @JessLConnell @jenb Hopefully it was el dente https://t.co/R89kHpmwOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Beer Alliance Derailed By Bud Light Super Bowl Ad https://t.co/JegbHTipFY via @AmericaCrftBeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winefriendspod So...graphic design? That’s the hill @cwavery is going to die on? Really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReduxitSpem @smfehir Kinda hard to give a guy a ticket in one of these loaders LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Mariota can figures things out and the significance is on the IF. Then Humphries is about to thrive in the AFC S… https://t.co/oEa45wekyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: California’s ambitious plan to stop deadly wildfires may not be enough, experts say - San Francisc… https://t.co/bQpjyvCfit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here comes the X Division Champion Rich Swann as he's getting his dance on that's a great way to ease the mood #IMPACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackDyerX1 @toucanstiki @igaypalmsprings @ILoveGayPS @aebn @JRLCHARTS @XBIZ @Str8UpGayPorn @porn_actors… https://t.co/nrFMl4kldX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraJaneGrace Vs. is their best album, by far. Never even thought of the Fugazi comparison before but that is so on point]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's possible the April patch will remove buying weapons and ships and make them free.   But I love playing as… https://t.co/YkGMWj2K2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonLemire And Mueller report will be released while they are gone.  Isn’t that convenient?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Jordyn, Davia, and Celine. Y'all are the best friends a person could go to an after party with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kira_Media @PolitiBunny @TwitchyTeam It's been going on for 3 days. Did you just notice it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveTheRox @nickgroke 💯 percent. I think there is a quiet optimism it gets done just because of how Rockies have h… https://t.co/zm0LkYKSbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#riseandgrind   Committed to being better then I was yesterday.  Something strange happens when You just keep it fl… https://t.co/PEYTHCa6x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jckarter @macshome @slava_pestov @lapcatsoftware @stevewoz A0++ would buy again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s interesting, I had no idea my FB review was going to automatically post to my Twitter account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmasnaynay @GamecockBasebll Inclement weather for the night that’s why u should never give tickets away with base… https://t.co/UiXO6Z6P6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Public Enemy Number One is Trump trying to Unmake America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs Im CIA John f Kennedy jr from marilyn monroe Mortensen and JFK born Sept 9th 1960 CIA sealed iowa fa… https://t.co/pL56ScoWdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shauncore I’ve been cracking up about those chickens coming home to roost. What ticks me off is that I just barely… https://t.co/csZINNxJYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU to everyone who contributed and made this trip possible for me! 21 days until we depart for Switzerland,… https://t.co/ccgtELhWEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[They can put anyone at the top, but Republicans are who still wolves in a sheep's clothing:  Pure bigots without an… https://t.co/ncMJpsq6Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC The Democratic Socialist Party has to get over it you lost the election]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonxx01 @MelodyMarksxxx Sweet sexy hot lady you can tease me any time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Lord I AM not worthy to receive you but only say the word and I shall be healed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I disagree. Turning a blind eye to the acceptance of anti Semitic (and make no mistake, that’s what t… https://t.co/18IHorH4b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like they really missed an opportunity to get Seal singing “Kiss From A Rose” 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fireworksfriday Canada Day 2018. petrieisland @ottawacity @nikoncanada #d750 tokina_global #tokina1628… https://t.co/Ya1Qf2dM5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Very frustrating when we can put men on the moon with precision but cannot straighten out this horrib… https://t.co/tli03yczod]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my standards aren’t that high living in Jacksonville but fuck this is bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPJArt @NoRibsNoRice_ People are acting surprised that he’s slow, when he’s got 5k throwing yards and 130 rushing… https://t.co/41L79lDAOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its almost the year 2020 and yet people still drive at night with the headlights off #nashvilledrivers]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Americans, as well as those Americans living elsewhere, had hopes for a solid economy. Trump exploited their… https://t.co/5nWOSJGtex]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have moved onto Big Lebowski. A cabin in the woods with a wood stove burning is probably aesthetically the best c… https://t.co/g13ma5r7Z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been struggling to find a good pair of headphones for years. My ears are different than yours. Question... #airpods… https://t.co/euzcHaVsXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicacpm_ @pamelavillalobs @jotajotaoi Oh demonios, éramos mucho y pario la abuela.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on Mercari! Montblanc Doue Steel Rollerbal... https://t.co/RSCAMwnXje #pens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackie Robinson was the first African American to break the color barrier in professional Baseball. On April 15, 20… https://t.co/CTxGbIP01r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@o_tricky Cleopatra is lost too other lost souls https://t.co/mEWjiOSJbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGalvano @FLSenate @stmcocathedral Best wishes Mr President for a great session]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @AOC To be so ill-informed and yet to be so self-assured. It's quite a study in psychology. She not… https://t.co/YQYC3Zuees]]></document></documents></author>