<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@iDarePhillips Lol. Bruh. Lol. I'm not doing long distance abeg.  Bye bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandoubeda Lindo andito échale ganas, me ubiera gustado verte en mty ahora qué viniste 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWBDimash #WorldsBest @WorldsBestCBS @dimash_official   never heard better singer then Dimash https://t.co/zlAbJupJqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I am admitting I have a problem... the problem is I like to eat. ALL. THE. TIME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day ❤️ @pgervia @MsAshleyDubois @MsMathnik @SueM_MHS @sueabes1 @MHSBromley @mikemcraith… https://t.co/kLSVzFbLt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Kind of SILLY since it's only 6 people but have to say I AGREE with them   Go Away Joe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! @Cultural_DC ask @jenniferrubell questions about “Ivanka Vacuuming”]]></document><document><![CDATA[People calling me ma’am is so weird. I am but a CHILD! Someone call my mom, I need her to pick me up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz If you’re telling me that Vladimir Putin and Hillary Clinton teamed up with Christopher Steele and the F… https://t.co/FbpNEeUrWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews This is less about CPD than it is some sick mo fo doing what he did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyFranHey @FriendZonePod I’m listening to the episode while I’m on the train to work. Me and my gf will be intere… https://t.co/eeeVMEt4Yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@221beees @inevitablyjohn1 @LoveBug54 @astudyinsnoggy I do have a candy bar from London 🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/jslAY1Mbmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel bad for you if you don’t get a Dani Frani dollar store valentine gift every year like the true homies do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Blinders convenient blinders she’s poking her own eyes. SMH. But then again who cares she’s foolin… https://t.co/AbFcwyIfdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using the “people need jobs/need to eat” rationale for murdering wildlife is pathetic.   Why not show fisherman how… https://t.co/VnotJqnSxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have *very* limited availability for @NUMensBball v Minnesota tonight! Come to the ticket office to get tickets… https://t.co/sv781VzQcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s a may baby. so i might be up against a taurus or a gemini and i just. idk. i need to get the day....and time..… https://t.co/fFuywAPIsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[the heat funny movie quotes - Google Search #funniness #snicker #grin #hilarious https://t.co/Xcs9AbNuQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to also vote #iHeartAwards #BestFanArmy #BTSArmy @BTS_twt @iHeartRadio https://t.co/AMusLBhGRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDONeill THE FDR DRIVE ALL THE WAY TO HOUSTON STREET, WHERE I HAVE BEEN MANY TIMES.I WANT TO ALERT YOU OF A POSS… https://t.co/WyfzGrQTWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually, I see our Deer twice everyday, but have not seen them since early yesterday morning‼️They  know to come to… https://t.co/JZtq72MvUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say your neighbor does THIS to his/her house. What do YOU do?  https://t.co/JcljVkiczP #KHOU11 #HTownRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_ShaManagement @IGotPeace @impettyasfuck @500Ells I love how all she needed was 1500.00.  I was like this child i… https://t.co/DbV5IuTVT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at NYC Chinatown with @yipsdragonstyle Wing Hong Yip's Dragon Style Kung Fu &amp; Tai Chi Club celebrating… https://t.co/aBSSzmNi41]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so incredibly honored and grateful to have been selected last night as the NACURH Advisor of the Year nominee… https://t.co/8gPmK5CjKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me tonight at 8pm at Avant Garden. I will be performing an Egyptian dance. This is a rare No Cover show… https://t.co/tPLkfB43LH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I saw this now so can play it on repeat in my head while taking my exam I’ll surely fail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theomilll Not with him. Oh wait, we had a good one with Buffalo and he stopped that one. Keep him, he would probab… https://t.co/YBBD94ABD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview with the sweetest sugar daddy charleslongstudio in @bombmagazine Spring 2019 — #youngjoonkwak @ Dylan's C… https://t.co/ip25jkkjxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My “Jack and the Beanstalk” Story Book Character Day https://t.co/OeqlMuqmi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Robert Clotworthy fall into the money pit?  I don't recognize this narrator.   #oakislandcursers  #Oakland  #CurseOfOakIsland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Impolitics Lindsey Lou and John McCain are the secret everyone knows about]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whooo!! 19 hours of #intermittentfasting today at work - effortlessly. I love her feeling when it just kinda happen… https://t.co/lRpispWdfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning Shane told me that I might be smarter than a “normal monkey”, but not smarter than a “smart monkey” ..… https://t.co/RUnJNvCdpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/14/19 💝 Baby Constance was born and I became an aunt ❤️ Weighing all of 5 pounds ❤️ Welcome to the world Constanc… https://t.co/5zZnPJK2q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can call me fat but at least when I get dolled up I’m actually cute... you on the other hand still look like a monkey 🐒 oo oo bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my fucking god my stomach hurts so much I’m convinced it hurts more than labor 😩 i wanna cry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning beautiful sweet humans! Yup, it’s Monday morning ~ no way around that. The good news is you get to mak… https://t.co/v4DYStLOKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally just keep getting better and better in my craft and it’s making me feel unstoppable]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are the most basic girls with no style RT this like this is literally me u wish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScheinandSchein map viewing party. What an incredible place. I now love MAP. https://t.co/Fz4w2aNbMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por ser dia del amor y la amistad, verdad A. Guardado? https://t.co/J5x546u1QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing support from the city of Bernalda for the IIS Bernalda-@GuilfordCollege cultural exchange. Just 5 weeks unt… https://t.co/gd2hMqFz9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most unlikely duo since Martha Stewart and Snoop Dogg —  I give you @AskDrRuth &amp; @MrPeanut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Lafayette Springs, Mississippi https://t.co/m3Z8xlGwfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Antlers celebrate a win against Madison and Amber's18th birthday. It's been a grueling weekend of softball. On… https://t.co/EpovfMyvfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cute little spider built a web over a week ago by our front door. Even with all the wind it's still holding st… https://t.co/2rPcxN7zH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud past A-Lister giving this a #shoutout for @CITmagazine Get yourself nominated - it’s a great accolade to be a… https://t.co/hDzeBqNJ5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1RealBadMan Fine lol. The rich side bitch bc lowkey means single lol AND if I’m a “main” that means he got hoes. C… https://t.co/wvcPNqs4le]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @musiclovingfish just looked at each other in confusion and mutual amusement 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liltaquiito @joshuarabina @supnesss @baerriito https://t.co/N2o8Z7nFcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoltonElem RockPaperScissorShowdown#hoops#gameboard#PE❤️ https://t.co/PNrt4WdNCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Why would that surprise anyone?  The Perfect Back will force change so “Medicare for All” will likely not be necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoveling weekend.  Share, like and vote!  Online voting in this link https://t.co/atYPbgrufX  Apply in the bio lin… https://t.co/hV2zvdAI45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNnenna Always seeking ways to enrich the world.  God bless you both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weird_Dana I will be the tree that bends in the wind...lol 💜 https://t.co/GbrezaIr6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heart goes out to Ethiopia 💔   No survivors from Ethiopian Airlines flight crash  https://t.co/tyZuNA3uBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we ever colonize Mars there will eventually be people who are anti-Earth or Earth deniers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Describing my brand in emojis: 👙 Resort Cover-Ups  🚲 Beach Towns  ✈️ Travel Tees  🧢The Coolest Hats 👗 Sunday Dinner… https://t.co/cKbQwKrHf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyTrask @DukeJack1 @MarksNewDaddy We’ve always got your six @AmyTrask Raider Nation⚫️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There you go with your  #Iam5yearsold bathroom humor again. #SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the world ends in eight days, how is #5 58 years old? #UmbrellaAcademy https://t.co/qXqr6qIdn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWATWritersRoom I am worried about that too. Deacs could need some SWAT POWER for himself with that shady dweeb!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great experience at #SXSW Wellness Expo! Stopped by the @CAULIPOWERED Veg Out Lounge to #JointheVegolution… https://t.co/XvJIXpTRfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I not only was very blessed to understand from afar off the importance of being worthy of self but to feel security… https://t.co/AhRPxWj7t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stromer19 ties it with a PP goal!!  #Blackhawks #COLvsCHI https://t.co/okB9PDciAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[May you all enjoy good cup of coffee on this cool Saturday morning ☕️👠👠🤗🌻🌎😊🕊 https://t.co/vCeS7Biu7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let’s cut lunch funding for kids who might possibly only get their meals at school because there is nothing at h… https://t.co/ZZXScqLHCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asleepynin Right?? Like who the hell threatens a creator who’s work they enjoy for free?? That’s messed up. And it is super creepy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IUFoundation @IUPUI @IUPUIGradOffice @IUPUIGPSG @IUPUIEnglish Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorDude90s Best: One and Twelve Worst: Three and Ten https://t.co/QY2wevtDE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day being a big kid!!!!   #universalstudios  #magicalday #rides #thesimpsons #studiotours #dispicableme… https://t.co/f1hi5qD79c]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i get stressed out because  i don’t have anything to stress out about]]></document><document><![CDATA[apple called me in to try out the iPhone 95c ... I’ll be the first one with this dropping 2020... #bigflexin… https://t.co/wAayMmZI6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when i thought 2019 documentary memes couldn’t get any better 😂 https://t.co/byPV5R9VRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaxbeachmarsh @JillWineBanks I love Jill Wine-Banks.  I hope you are right, but a lot of replies (including mine)… https://t.co/Nn6ao3QOT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[What could possibly go wrong with the idea of giving everyone the power to make their video posts look like real ne… https://t.co/EfEJVolF05]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wine budget used to be about $7 a bottle.  Now it's $12-14.  And I feel that's an accomplishment. 🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyhumpday🍑 #friendsarefamily #❤️❤️❤️ #🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈 @ City of New York https://t.co/8wuftnm8n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forced myself to eat with chopsticks today because I would rather choke on a noodle than ask for a fork in a Japanese establishment 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash What sacrifice did he make that was his choice to take that knee and he receive compensation for it this is totally a joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramy @HIMANSHU @hulu Oh cool another brown dude’s perspective on the growing up muslamic experience why don’t you… https://t.co/eH0uJERtcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeDaveHageman @IBJIYONGI Yes and Jews are socially conditioned to be Zionist. They have to push out of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacques_balayla @AirCanada @AirCanadaRouge You officially have good Karma coming your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GypsySmashley @jendruns @JPMusicLuvr @ThisIsRobThomas Sorry to hear you feel that way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to keep it short. Thanks you all for tuning in, should be back on tomorrow. Hosted @Raptor208, He is a good f… https://t.co/W5BStcSxuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frosty's Baby Picture rustic board sign - Christmas Holiday | MyRusticBoardSigns - Woodworking on ArtFire #mirth… https://t.co/Hx9Xr3CY6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean Clearance sale:  Trump Ivanka Junior Eric Pence and mother Trump orgy err org]]></document><document><![CDATA[my old manager may have offered me a threesome sometime in the future and best believe I was so mother fuckin happy… https://t.co/sugXtIZSpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truthandfiction @marcorubio It’s a blatant display of privilege for you to stay there as a freelance journalist af… https://t.co/dB87loqJGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyAkzam @JoyAnnReid @KamalaHarris @MSNBC You can't be serious Or can you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's take some solace in this disappointing sentencing that Mueller confiscated tens of millions from Manafort. That 🍄 can't give back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[02/17/2019: 2019 Pan African Film Festival Fashion Show. 🙂 So proud to have been a part of this. @ Baldwin Hills Cr… https://t.co/Uib7Z6C1RS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_nors No more daily emails with excuses for being late?  Or A/C that doesn’t work on half the band buses?  What will you do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9Cool17 Thank you for your service, Neco. Run free over that Rainbow Bridge🙏❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_astro_babe @NomikiKonst @HumanistReport she wont answee questions including did she vote for Hillary or trump or jill stein?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmeinvasnshawty I got a depression spell if u need it n we can go do sum grounding as well I’m praying 4 u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The time in history the lights went out in liberals.. and they were dark along time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenNollWeather @kateejavier @NetsOnYES @BrooklynNets I hope it was sweet and full of love ❤️ 🍓💋🌹 thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Us: Rename Manhattan’s Wastewater Treatment Plant as the Donald J. Trump Sewage Center - Sign the Petition!… https://t.co/gXPSarG5xO]]></document></documents></author>