<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Well, here we go again...snow, snow, and more snow. https://t.co/g4JQCBvjS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet the @Lakers pulled it off smh yall really jocking @JHarden13 like he has rings. I'm mean he good asl but still… https://t.co/Z9PWtgG4rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Santorum’s commentaries and political “insights” are a total embarrassment. Why CNN continues to pay him, and… https://t.co/Bgc9ho8Ieq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it winning financially? Yes of course. Can’t blame him for taking the $. However, like Cano, this isn’t a winnin… https://t.co/LSXS8SclTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is automated in the lab so really all I be having to do is put the specimens on the machine lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsHackCA i’m almost positive they will bounce back and snatch the Rockets hearts out of their chest https://t.co/fus1StPYvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I lassoed the moon. Tomorrow, I will concur my insecurities.  What’s your plan? @ Union Square, San Francisco https://t.co/yMjBjwWfHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ain't like @NellyFurtado fly like a bird. SHE'S ACTUALLY SINGING ABOUT BIRDS #HeadAboveWater]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow House can vote for it all they want Senate will shut it down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnHHeberlein Vår "demokrati" är inte värd så värst mycket om politikerna gång på gång hittar vägar runt det som v… https://t.co/TCJDqdETRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook stories did one of the most amazing things this morning, sharing this throwback with me.  . . . Hows your… https://t.co/j9Y5nr02qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling over this year as Seven Stars. 🎖🎖🎖🎖🎖🎖🎖 #bigbanksabe #sevenstars #caesarsentertainment #lasvegas #nevada… https://t.co/FmMLdahgIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 minutes until our weekly #teachpos chat. Hope you can join and bring a friend or two.  #masterychat… https://t.co/3dsaN2MCjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakerevans51 @Tyler_Thomas5 @eeelzz I hear he’s leading off with Midnight sun. We should probably get to the chape… https://t.co/jPQb0cakSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The unveiling of the new Columbus @AFL team is getting started. https://t.co/oILDaj00CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[MICHAEL COHEN el que hasta hace poco fue el hombre de confianza de .@realDonaldTrump declara hoy ante la cámara baj… https://t.co/ihfWEWMMnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to reconnect with our yoga community at @EarthBoulder tonight (photo from Nov...)! #yogi #teacher… https://t.co/VvKoaLJbbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan No affairs or scandals you say? 🤔🧐 https://t.co/4xJ2XmPtgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone thought that #IdrisElba doesn't want to play #JamesBond? I think he has hinted as much. Craig will have… https://t.co/jFbCka6Gsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sullivan's Steakhouse - @sullivanssteak in King of Prussia, PA https://t.co/FX8A2JZfmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS @LouDobbs Coming from the man who has made bogus claims, backed with zero evidence, since the dawn of Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-0 on the night with two impressive finishes #teambambam #attindy @ Kokomo Event &amp; Conference Center https://t.co/5UudJEgXYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap!!!  So many great 80s/90s sitcoms on the @Roku Channel app!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Gristling by @relicbrewing at @tipping_chair — https://t.co/aGkAMmLKmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it better to wake up in the dark and try to put kids to bed when it's still light out?  Personally, I'd rath… https://t.co/RhcCDGgJtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for some clothes that allow for freedom  https://t.co/RG9HI63iZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWA I’ve done it and I’m not even a pro. You can get some easy money and some recognition as a player. As long as… https://t.co/h79bCz3iY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you have never gotten hit in the face with a snow ball by your dad and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, the thing that pisses me off the most about that is that @gordonhayward couldn't even send a thank you note… https://t.co/FjRySZ2STB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@milwaukeedpw Commissioner Jeff Polenske just issued this statement on the shooting. @WISN12News https://t.co/uwTQrnPAMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂Hahahahahahahaha!!! 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/QFHUrpwx94]]></document><document><![CDATA[The women of the FMH Foundation presented Odessa Arts with a check for $50,000 yesterday. Not bad for a day’s work.… https://t.co/sP4A2Kc45M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imthegregger @SteveWestly Not talking about colleges. The conversation is around k-12 public schools. 2nd Universi… https://t.co/NBV6GrPpYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma have to hunt me a josh Johnson when I get back to Rockford, biting the hand they fed him. Got me fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[El ganador de botin de oro.... intentando detener  como sea posible ... detener a el eterno, y único, botin de Oro!… https://t.co/mAGkHAV0hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving away Mets Nationals Spring Training Tickets today in the 5pm hour on @SportsRadio1560 Who wants to go??? https://t.co/PsIMlgOrDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbattalio It’s pretty clear that this person has no idea how academia actually operates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kielbasa_Posse @Kentucky_65 @V4Revenga @TrumpWinning2 @dbred309kool @RandPaul @realDonaldTrump Again wrong, law en… https://t.co/FOPfEPLLyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you not following @EFCYGaming yet? It's been one hell of a ride growing this esports organization! I would appr… https://t.co/oe1VydHyvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican opposition mounts against Trump's emergency declaration, could trigger President's first veto https://t.co/YOHWzk8kQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Podcasts: basically a radio show, a large part of the point is that you can do something else at the same time. #APSMarch]]></document><document><![CDATA[KAYAKER SAVES STRANDED DOG: ‘Bosco’ ran away from his #PalmBay home when a neighbor lit off fireworks. Missing for… https://t.co/wn8GpfNcFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariohezonja @brainsfordagame I’ll take the guy who can shoot 3’s and layups and actually get the ball in the basket]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nocentino @SQLvariant @jsnover Technically it’s the same functionality as corefx uses ‘open’ under the covers which pwsh relies upon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a safe Carnival everyone. Models: @JECapone #NYC #nyc🗽 #NewYork #BushwickCollective #model #fashionmodel… https://t.co/DWyF3drvNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longislpatriot @ABC7NY @LeeGoldbergABC7 @AOC Shithole? What Long Island City are you talking about? It’s the most… https://t.co/Ow6menwIiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay you do not need to call me out like this buzzfeed https://t.co/hqTvVI4fUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsTalkTigra @kyle_scanlon04 @tgshepherdvan @LetsTalkMock @bodgei My thoughts EXACTLY. My head canon now is that… https://t.co/oTDkauvFGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keanu on his ducati... keanureevesph @ Bedford, Massachusetts https://t.co/AwkkFJqYmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jttbiz Half the time it plays out of one wear only and I have to redock them. Sometimes they sit overnight and don… https://t.co/Kb7FgSB6fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woodland killed this weekend. Can’t get out of bed. Send help 😂 for real though it felt sick to get sideways 4th ge… https://t.co/nG64p7FfjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[running thru this juice wrld album n wow lot going on but do u think after he namedropped ‘pinot grigio’ in hear me… https://t.co/YM2OjOCAkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pat Morley kicking off the men’s retreat at Covenant Church in Naples. Live, Love, Lead: Finding Success That Matte… https://t.co/OTkICQ2zBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Haiti #Ayiti #KreyeChanjmanPaw #AyitiNouVleA @ Wisconsin https://t.co/tFv7bAyJGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveKingNBA @ScottHoward42 That would be Sarver-esque but I am much more confident in Kokoskov than James.   Has a… https://t.co/Ef5OHGOcYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helpsavecahokia Glad You’re Following The Roughriders! https://t.co/LNuSNGcPhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias The 🇺🇸 spends tremendous amounts from #education budgets supporting corporate entities, and our % cha… https://t.co/lregtMUCwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhaledBeydoun All Totalitarian governments are evil, because there is no check on what they can force you to do or… https://t.co/tJTBZ7gyOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dschatsky Now that you have this idea, you see evidence for it whatever you consider.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doc Emerick doing the #mshsl Class AA state championship game. What a treat! #TheTourney19]]></document><document><![CDATA[It cracks me up scrolling through our Amazon and target wedding registries bc it’s literally me and my Pinterest board in an itemized list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicamhayness @zoeymarie01_ Haha we would be so funny so dumb hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrawleyPDX @doughboyspod Yeah, that’s nice, Andrew. Hey, get a load of @nickwiger trying to figure out how to pron… https://t.co/a5iI1E3P0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is incredibly sad.  It might be impossible to find a better golf writer in the world.  Even with his old schoo… https://t.co/kBzfXJ8c5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all get on everyone about tipping (something I agree with) while wearing firsthand brand name clothes made by people making slave wages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepChuyGarcia What are you doing to address this problem?  https://t.co/gM3GrEwdvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan ComonMan ! @MarthaRaddatz Still Crying 😢 💦Over @realDonaldTrump Elected By WE🇺🇸63,000,000 45th🇺🇸@POTUS… https://t.co/fxrb8OUsFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest in Peace HERTIS JR. 😇🙏 @ Beecher, Michigan https://t.co/8UnNAfTUt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vrushalmp @CBSNews Doesn’t exist? You think if Joe Schmo has 5g that the gvt doesn’t have like 20g... general publ… https://t.co/30mRmoWdTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gravity_levity “The universe is infinite” kind of feels like a heat check by scientists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @jack there hasn't been one thing, not one thing done to fix it. It's worse than ever before. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw 3 busses pass as I’m walking to the bus stop. Ended up being 15 min late. I decided to skip to get ahead on HW… https://t.co/hhyFL8gzPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a Chick-fil-A commercial where the narrator pronounces “pillow” like “pellow” and it makes me want to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien necesita cupón de https://t.co/O36Z7Jjbuy ? Es para qué no se desperdicie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LimerickSage @AiG So what? The absolute certainty of death does not make facts go away or bullshit the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More #familyday w/ a little something to keep dad happy @ Mont-Tremblant, Quebec https://t.co/X5l8R8YLFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riding @Amtrak back to Boston with my new travel buddy @Comey #abookaweek https://t.co/lqgdDsLTga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like fermented raspberry sherbet #DrinkLocal - Drinking an Ice Dreamz : Raspberry by @alsofhampden @ JD's  — https://t.co/stQZrYomVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump You, Miss, should resign. Donald Trump knows no hate, except for the hate forced upon him… https://t.co/gnqayvwn6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[the countdown is on! our 4th annual #MM2008CurlingBonspiel is THIS Saturday! 28 teams, over 150 participants 🙌🏼🥌 th… https://t.co/ccu4nm2Mqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearn talks about Lemieux in this interview. Around 19:30-20 min mark of video. #boxing @PSTM09 @JasonToufexis]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VamosRayadas (@ Estadio BBVA Bancomer - @rayados in Guadalupe, NL) https://t.co/8M2nTYjCMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WideRtNattyLt Oklahoma didn't inbound it until there were 29 seconds left. The five seconds doesn't start until th… https://t.co/BXDS6ZwidM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re always in control of two things your effort and attitude.   Let’s get it today🦈 Up Up Cronulla @Josh_Dugan a… https://t.co/OnyF9P3ZC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSaenzPhillips observes @HISDMultiPrgms Gina Lerma-Avila discuss the ESL exit criteria during an individual studen… https://t.co/nyAK6yOZoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also we do have our heritages...we have clubs dedicated to Italian Americans, Irish parades, German celebrations...… https://t.co/bElmKYHcUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Redding isn't in southern California! It must be that college education! #TheWeatherChannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeynight Although coach Babcock said it best” he must be pretty good to be so hated”, but what a bunch of crybabies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PdpAkwaIbom @OfficialPDPNig @IEmemobong @PDPNYL @akaebube @Hailfinger1 @voteandstay @enoidem1964 @TonyeBarcanista… https://t.co/dy3Y3wUeiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see the @goodyear blimp I expect it to say @icecube’s a pimp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@storminspank It. Was. Rutgers.  Hawks knew they were pissed and wanted revenge.  So sick of excuses this late in t… https://t.co/6XBCp4O6B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Boone said that it is “highly unlikely” that Luis Severino will be ready for Opening Day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Davies wrestler is the 160 pound state champion. Congratulations Kolbe Booker on earning a state championship #NDPreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does God light my way, even in dark times? Someone out their has a testimonial just as I do! @ Downtown Long Be… https://t.co/1IyoovjYoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Drives over 12 hours from SL to LA.  Also me: Listens to Harvard EdCasts and reads articles about undocumented… https://t.co/gmnu8wg7Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mardi Gras Bock (2019) by @TheAbitaBeer @ The Whiskey Jar — https://t.co/IHwcMzvhDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar Love how the Trumps live rent free ( something you socialists should love. ...free stuff) in your heads… https://t.co/GdfkjvKQz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have work in the morning but I have the audacity to still be awake. Shouldn’t have taken that nap...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTLAMorningNews The good news about all the rain is, thanks to the Dems in Sacramento building all those reservoir… https://t.co/cX0BE8k3xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spruce Creek has already committed four team fouls at the 4:45 mark of the third. Hawks still up 38-28, but lots of… https://t.co/dFi4pdxaY2]]></document></documents></author>