<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Showing his young lady's LOVE...beautiful. The flowers that followed was everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMRnewsdirector We are in Clive. This pic is our kiddos Tenny (5), Ty (8) and neighbor Ethan (8). It’s the perfect… https://t.co/h8L6mGGf6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @sobriety23 It’s is not broken.  It was constructed to do exactly what’s its doing. Oppress and destroy… https://t.co/vJGyPRZpYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lazyditzychick @sha54111 @SenSanders @ewarren They were weird. She didn’t say she didn’t want single-payer or that… https://t.co/tJExMbDbHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliceLfc4 I’m late to this but in addition to the ladies who’ve already been named, I’ll add Katie Ledecky. She’s… https://t.co/F1YGgtLEC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet again @BTS_twt 's  #Jungkook continues to be a huge global influence as this ADORABLE little cowboy turns up to… https://t.co/P5CG6rY57U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kipkazi_koech Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ #us #uk #nz #ca #dating]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 5th grade teacher had 50 rules that were posted across the walls in the classroom and i used to laugh and talk s… https://t.co/uUnFfa0d3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to make more visits to cigar Sundays at the @DC_Eagle https://t.co/9g6Bu114Za]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatTheFFacts That my friends is called #survivalofthefittest 🤣🤣🙌🏽💥 https://t.co/eQnAGvUnlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantylercohen Says he grew up poor, family owns a bell factory, got bailouts]]></document><document><![CDATA[The war in Afghanistan is 18—older than the new wave of Marine recruits fighting it. https://t.co/xXP8exB9L0 via @WSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exhausted after #day3 of #SXSW but I got to meet Willie Nelson himself as he was walking into the theatre and Woody… https://t.co/JyI0pk5rsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I stated yesterday, if anyone wants to assume something about me, pick an argument with me, or threaten me, I wi… https://t.co/pspySfIXzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a full service shop, with an ASE Master Certified Technician. services we do are: Engine Work, including: He… https://t.co/JLBTMzPdkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3) Being an effective communicator/collaborator, being flexible, understanding one’s audience, etc. can help #GT s… https://t.co/UpzcW4dhSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a great Worcester moment #BirchTreeBread #CromptonCollective #SeedtoStem #BedlamBooks https://t.co/kY76DaDcf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling happy about four @UCAComm students competing in the @ucacareer elevator pitch competition today. Way to go,… https://t.co/8J7HvowEyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland! Thrilled to perform at @albertarosepdx on Sat Mar 2  with my band, @RiseUpBand (Hamilton Tribute). ✨🎶🔥 Pi… https://t.co/ab9lOWfBPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Oh Lindsey‼️@LindseyGrahamSC   Oh Marco‼️ @marcorubio   Oh Mitch‼️ @senatemajldr   Oh God‼️ @god 😂😂😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Photo Bombing Bitch... #pssywells she ruins Everything #timpalazzola #billyfrancesca https://t.co/pzim3cEqMJ https://t.co/yxVJSpDP9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Justin talks about me during his own interviews, it makes my heart gooey 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get a text from me at 2:30 am, don’t worry I’m not drunk, I just woke up from a nap I was supposed to wake u… https://t.co/4AXxvPfqRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicahGravley @douglassentinel @TSpigolonNBR @AllenPeake Way to go! Proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History February 24th On this day in 2006, death claimed popular actors Don Knotts in Los Angeles and Denn… https://t.co/TqnwPqkeEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder to NEVER judge a book by its cover...  #latenightthoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrea loves playing in the snow ☃️ #snow #snowday #noschool #winter #winterfun #funinthesnow @ Cortlandt Manor, Ne… https://t.co/Y0Pw0ynz7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[. This past Valentines day my beautiful cousin, Samantha was in a horrific car accident. She broke her neck and is… https://t.co/MEueZkHR5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maria52580 Maria, I am so sorry. I’ll email asap. - Christine from Aura]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you read so much, they ask. Bring your warm milk and chamomile tea to the living room at 3:30 am and find out. #weehoursreadingclub]]></document><document><![CDATA[myles and i literally grew up together and it’s so weird to me that we are having a baby 😂 i can still remember all… https://t.co/kuJuAc6fBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Beautiful models brows micro-bladed before and after @ Reclaimed Beauty https://t.co/xOKyfRESkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you saw me on the dance floor last night... that wasn’t me. idk her lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two bottles of wine in less than 24 hours, I’d say I’m doing pretty well 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majorleaguepins @AwrdTravel101 @Hotel48Lex Pretty sure they’re talking about Expedia, Hotwire, Priceline, etc - no… https://t.co/D13NMaimkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my GoFundMe campaign: https://t.co/La8JPR03f7 @gofundme https://t.co/JB4SW2jbyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @BenSasse @WSJopinion So disappointing to see you pushing this misleading narrative. Shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilianaSnchez9 @JSaintPastour @mimiros9 @delosangelesbe1 Buen inicio de semana  Lili y amigos ❤️ https://t.co/bodELjTTHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JP_Rosenbaum I knew Colton was a horrible decision.    That’s such a childish reaction.   Lame]]></document><document><![CDATA[All made up in his disturbed very ill mind. And maybe one other location.😎😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxrushden it didn't go unnoticed! 🇮🇹🇮🇳 And yes, you and @bglendenning have the honour of being our group chat pic… https://t.co/aB83eoApVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes living the dreams..... The two Georgina’s 🤪 @ Hollywood Hills https://t.co/B4K2ZeEzOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see what this coming season brings. I'm already excited and it's only February...LOL.… https://t.co/H7gZJLhYfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Tommy Hilfiger look like a poorly dressed Huge Hefner? #OscarsRedCarpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I ❤️Ruth Carter and Spike Lee too. The jump/leg hug ofSpike/Samuel Jackson was pure joy for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJonair @KindaNerdyNews @ktayers @JOHNAS_URLOVE @LadyPodSquad @transformers My brother still sleeps with his pillo… https://t.co/qHPmDXQVgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 13 year old self is screaming but y’all couldn’t at least get someone who looked a little like Harry Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[☃️❄️☃️More snow today @ Dakota Dunes, South Dakota https://t.co/h8lU4NUvzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[a few weeks ago a dude and i were butt ass naked in his bed when his roommates came home at like 2am and decided to… https://t.co/FBjEHYxuLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandadeibert so here’s my first attempt at stand up in hopes of landing a job https://t.co/CjDWgzSHyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdmjjmegm Can you Tweet without name calling ? Or is your point only made in kindergarten warfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[The launch of our new one hour morningshowca in the books! The team (minus a number of very important peeps who are… https://t.co/VYKuLAKOgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s clarify how ppl are feeling about the #AmberAlert:  It’s ok to be mad about a very loud noise *before* knowin… https://t.co/hq90tuzx4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesFourM ok..listen..when u r linked and your brain actually is able to understand the language your lovely prog… https://t.co/cksmU6cJlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I think I love Mr Lynch from Massachusetts! He read the gop a few home truths!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic thank you to the talented @skateforjake for making me look more beautiful than I am. https://t.co/kKMF7xmZL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies lies.  You should be ashamed.  L… https://t.co/h6EIdyNTZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The filter doesn’t like me today 😏   Nonetheless... HAPPY TUESDAY 🥳 https://t.co/qbFq9qzMzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kendall_Perry I have sling and roku and I literally never touch the TV I know someone burn me at a stake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was FaceTiming @Tonithenonphony at Target and she said “wow this is the most I’ve been outside in weeks” 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliaboone But I love it when it's golden! I used to think that's why it was called the Golden State!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ze best thing in my life accompanied me in working at The Pyramid tonight ^o^ #BerryHappy #HappyMardiGras… https://t.co/K4dqIDwVzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dahile00 @TheSWPrincess @1Jedi_Rey @B52Malmet @TrinityResists @EmmaFrostResist @DebbieDoesTwitt @NatCookResists… https://t.co/NyC0J0UrDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[During #LasallianLent students learn what it means to be without, appreciate simplicity, and understand why we sacr… https://t.co/7KnBrFlGxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep singing! #JohnSchneiderStudios. #BosExtravaganza. #MavenEntertainment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forever_cal Oh, man! I don't think I could handle that, they're biggies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convos I'd like to have w/ local officials: How will changes made by @celliottability affect how my family gets car… https://t.co/112pSoOguU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwjwtw1997 @PowerLisaDoyle Trump cannot laugh at himself...to me, laughing at yourself is sign of intelligence. Tr… https://t.co/NWHYEUnqKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber has the heat on full blast won’t turn it off and won’t let me roll down the window...ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They ARE the far left 🤣 Don’t worry Mr. President we got your back!🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adeline is up cooing and talking and smiling like no other. Wide awake. It’s 4am... but im not even mad about it 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[two days after joining tinder i’m about to meet up with this random guy from colorado lol i love this for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex Week is from February 18th-22nd and they have a lot of events to talk about topics in gender, sex education, se… https://t.co/E2VvYKdW20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s GO Tre Williams @ayTrizzy Minnesota Gophers commit and the Wasatch Tigers @WATigersBB !! @GopherMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlpierce @MattStout07 HEY...that is an insult to @primus !!! You take that back! 🤣 https://t.co/tCJegYgjZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Sorry about the accident and your https://t.co/KD84Ax1PBw know I'm an old lady but think you are amazin… https://t.co/QoUmiVpVAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finchbro So ...  Free-Market anti-Globalist Canadian Nationalist  or ...  another Crony-Capitalist Corporatist Liberal-aligned Globalist  🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama  implanted 70,000 Muslim refugees In Minnesota and now Omar is in Congress! Investigate Nancy Pelosi ties wit… https://t.co/wiqOlT2tYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What they don’t tell you is that all of the behind the scenes work of making democracy happen is the trillion paper… https://t.co/SP7bZVW2fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I tried to show one of the girls I give lessons how I used to pitch and all 5 balls I threw went right i… https://t.co/mW1eycYQBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling myself on a Sunday Evening. #feelingmyself #curlyhair #hairdid #ididitmyself @ Napa, California https://t.co/NXJXlhuK7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you find your person there's nobody else you want, nothing else you need. https://t.co/4AAcE7ZIDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my bestfriend, i miss partying, i miss drinking, i miss cocaine. The good old days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Ha ha ha! Delusional. Oh yeah, you have great instincts. Remember Al Capone’s vault!]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who ask how others afford things have to be the tackiest I’ve ever met 🤧🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[S1E33 #MeteorGarden2018 just wanting to hit Ximen in the throat for hurting the cute little cinnamon roll! #XizeWu… https://t.co/XRKMJV039j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid at the gym: your stares and attempts to get the cute girl doing her plank to notice you are giving off a rapey… https://t.co/uYeIsLo5Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linda36322803 @cristinalaila1 @KamalaHarris And what exactly have Trump supporters done? Exercised our right to vo… https://t.co/2PCaoY1f52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JooBilly @DavidCouchAR @AutumnDamnIt Because there wasn’t a link to donate to a generic Cotton opponent? Folks fel… https://t.co/D3k6AxvCT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic problem solving with higher level questioning on display in 2nd gr at WES! Ss collaborate to solve a mult… https://t.co/2TdFtd4g7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a lo, it's a lo, it's a lonely weekend It's a lo, it's a lo, it's a lonely feelin' without you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFranklin2017 @Cheryll1950 @nbcsandiego Let’s start a fake investigation..spread a wide net and see who we can cat… https://t.co/DlihSi0xLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@militantangleno @victoriabernal @valleyrelics BUT! They just moved (to Van Nuys)! One less reason to go to Chatsworth, honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day will have to wait until Suge is done with her nap ... @ Geneva, New York https://t.co/Sz8UsJSbX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadiesOfLivePD @LivePdFantasyLG @Sgt_LarkinsGang @IndependenceGr1 @LivePdBlueLine @DonnaJamesRye68 @CrownNatalie @LivePDKennyCash Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougProp No words. 🤗(wish there was a hug emoji that wasn’t grinning).]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How does Paris Hilton know the queen????” a legit and genuine question from @laurynnestelle ‘s mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[hearts upon our sleeve is super underrated. everything about that song is incredible and it doesn’t get the recognition it deserves 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[as robots take over meanial tasks, the value of people is going to be creativity. @reagankayk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uncle, who does not have a faith nor attends any sort of spiritual services, always told me growing up that ever… https://t.co/RdvObShWmg]]></document></documents></author>