<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How in TH were enough people stupid enough to vote for you that u became POUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not need to eat like I just did for it not to be a gym day today smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Ervin go around following Sox fans again? Did I piss him off. @ErvinSantana_54 follow me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half: Sioux City East 30 Lewis Central 22. Jaleque Dunson leads the Raiders with nine points. LC has been paced by… https://t.co/BJKuCPeKB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What he really meant: Thank you for hosting my distraction from the Michael Cohen hearings and the ongoing Russia i… https://t.co/LYafapznSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The face I make when I’m trying to show empathy https://t.co/ySUQkTv8t9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a man from the @USNavy came into my job looking like he was ready to defend the world from the aliens from In… https://t.co/e7Qc8kibtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spiritual food for the mind, body and soul. #teamramsay #iamronramsay #ilovegod #passion #passioncitychurch… https://t.co/ntnZYrIunW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthew_goolsby @erosegolden @KamalaHarris You didnt decide to believe this, did you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing Carrie @carrie_edu this idea for a #FormativeAssessment using @Nearpod modeled after @Twitter, a… https://t.co/OY3QzEUfIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD @realDonaldTrump @POTUS THEY'RE DOING THEIR JOB UNLIKE THE REPUBLICAN LEAD RUBBER STAMP THAT WE HAD F… https://t.co/WZI08d9TUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetsDaddy2013 @ernestdove @Mets Yeah and trust me I’ve gotten in my fair share of disagreements but lately it’s ju… https://t.co/r5nBHVIbwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left Eye was a master at telling stories and painting pictures through her lyrics. This verse is still legendary]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3_Olive @TheWestate @F3theFort @F3UnionCo @F3Area51 @F3MintHill Just glad you are part of F3 brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please go subscribe to my channel on youtube I have tons of fun videos and plenty more to be released soon! Thank y… https://t.co/v1hvvhAYWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sung_minkim Catcher at home, bucket in second base. How many baseballs can they put inside the bucket in X time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big time person and professional. Super proud of her journey! @CPMustangs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intersection lights out at SM and La Cienega. Need traffic police there ASSP! @WHDLASD @WehoDaily @WeHoCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ju5tM0nik4 Monika, Yuri and protagonist got married. And That made me cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kipsy1979 He’s a small horse. Can’t race him that way on mile track. He’ll be fine...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman is #amazing. 93 years, 11 children, 11 grand children, 14 great grand children. My #heart is full. ♥️ Ev… https://t.co/jpMszASGzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine network television airing an award show that no one knows personally, yet people care enough watch. Weird don't you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning...Wake Up with the WORD!   #wakeupwiththeWORD https://t.co/qAf9yItsNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CahnEmily @POLITICO_Steve Monday 11am-1pm range is the best time. Literally just had this conversation with the ma… https://t.co/bF1HE2iynN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulBrown_UK Sounds like a plan. Tell Zane to go donate. Lol   Seriously was not expecting a second surgery for 20… https://t.co/OptEgjrGWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[didn't think I'd spend my friday night having an existential crisis but here I am 😝🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeylaSeka Oh no!! Nightmare scenario. Apple should come up with a Find my Airpod feature. 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chemistry between @SamuelLJackson and @brielarson off the screen. Looking forward to them on screen in… https://t.co/otco4qx6b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[WET 🌊 SPLASH 💦 MOUNTAIN FOLLOW MY LEAD  PUT THE 1 IN 1 OF 1 ✂️♻️ what could have been but never was but may be some… https://t.co/fqQwObkpKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@purrpetua @TPointUK The EU is merely sticking to the agreement that May already signed. What you want, I’m afraid,… https://t.co/Hsg64W2PH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bo-  what do you want most now? C- this calm to last my life time Bo-  I think we can do that C- don't treat people… https://t.co/wFDuN23pQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walkathons and Other Athletic Fundraising Events Continued Revenue Slide in 2018 https://t.co/BsP5yuFjfF via @Philanthropy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary boy I'm a mufucking Twitter vet https://t.co/ZZoU0pCoe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverPD01 @SilverthorneCO Wait I thought Mariah’s “moose” was at home lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday The 2017 Diocese of Trenton Boys JV Champs. The @SCSprincipal Boys JV Basketball team. https://t.co/P6V0ftrEnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking to @RepAndyBiggsAZ office about issues that impact the cystic fibrosis community.… https://t.co/rbe7u8fJIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[[Bruno Ganz in Wim Wenders' 'Der amerikanische Freund ' (1977) https://t.co/8MCBFAY2tG]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FdeBoerofficial @ATLUTD @DEalesATLUTD @BocaBoca3 On behalf of all #ATLUTD fans https://t.co/9jLGKgVvnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure Nick Boyle is a fine blocking tight end, but this has to be the most unnecessary press conference in NFL h… https://t.co/Nu88YGeoAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/KjQksIUGKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#babyKai loves her some gtskombucha Trilogy😘 @ Live for a Living https://t.co/gwQmV9aKto]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mv1d1adCla Saudi MOH 6-7 Mar 2019 https://t.co/Tq6olSmnKV In past 48 hours since last update (#MERS-Co… https://t.co/tfmu0W8A34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune to Channekl 69 News at 4pm with @JimVaughnWFMZ @Melanie_Falcon and @Joy_Howe on my BIRTHDAY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be the best reason(s) to go to bed early on a Friday night: up alone, cup of coffee, comfy chair with snuggli… https://t.co/pwXpNqk9fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fiddlestix7 @BlueSteelDC @admrablsnackbar @Cakedaddy4ever @SallyAlbright @pamwallace @MSkotnicki @LexAlexander… https://t.co/hwKSUw6qyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SVM_X But if we’re talking about welfare I don’t think people should be giving money to buy beer and cigs ... simp… https://t.co/Kk6meQLx5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hjonschneider @J3Adams For a second, I thought you were referring to pulp fiction. Specify!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#McGill #Montreal #mtlmoments #mtl @mcgillu @McGillARTS @Montreal #downtown #campus https://t.co/KIgBj5Mxjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Imran Khan Says Pakistan Will Release Indian Pilot, Seizing Publicity in Showdown: From the start,… https://t.co/iYWZ5kMVgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SounderBruce That was actually what 5 years ago this week. Largest mammoth tusk ever found in the region!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyfuller @rahulpathak I think plates are 2-7 chars total (including spaces) in Cali. I dunno about WA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@not_a_pog @sgtjanedoe If I actually reenlist before Sept it's for the discounted @WaltDisneyWorld tickets - my son… https://t.co/Z8PWTgfgvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although it's also Chuck Norris' birthday and he once said he was voting for @RonPaul . Good choice. Would have bee… https://t.co/QZGAKzessO]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV boys soccer - 48th minute  goal Plano West Wolves McKinney JV Lions 1 vs  Plano West JV Wolves 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitkat57 I was shown...  Pouring rain Cenote fills, Purified Love Seventh fold!  Record breakers In your log, Stil… https://t.co/twRmpocfqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @dsupervilleap @AP @mikedebonis What is Trump going to give away at the summit with the murdering dictator Kim Jong Un Florida?]]></document><document><![CDATA[FX Friday: 5% off all in stock effects pedals today only. #uhlikmusic  #FridayMotivation #pedal https://t.co/L4jPR3VEUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris And who is gonna pay for it. You talk a lot of shit about this and that but don’t explain how to pay for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton Desperate people trying to escape impossible living conditions. They want to give their families a chan… https://t.co/8HIG9UoU8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESbeINSPORTS @JoseHDonGoL @Jaimefmacias buenos días desde phoenix Arizona rumbo al trabajo viendo el máscon. Slds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonteMcNaughton @mkbartz Sorry and “troll” trouble are big at our house but it’s checkers here tonight https://t.co/d6M17ii7jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need awesome songs to celebrate your loved one? Why not gift your Valentine with my dear friend Marcelo Lima’s new… https://t.co/8YvX82cqR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckphotoal @flterp @700poems @ChrisJZullo @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump It's cool that MAGA-Jihadists like to at… https://t.co/tQ1R6v3lIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_nickrichard I don’t blindly trust anyone in life. The offense had been a train wreck for 20 years. They have zero… https://t.co/24sGQjzFod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoundsnColor @RealCandaceO @AOC She is telling the truth. So are YOU acting racist against Candace?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob5Chief Cekam na pozew od Lecha Bolka Walesy UB eckiego kapusia i kompletnego kretyna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life would be so much easier if I liked soy milk more #veganproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchellGreen @AaronBlake Don’t worry @MitchellGreen about agreeing with fatso, compulsive eater CC. It is what we… https://t.co/WMqDiqo7Sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're thinking about Lasik, don't second guess it and just do it. Its life changing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donlemon is your head so far up your own ass you will never correct the record in the #JussieSmolettHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnieJohnson I listen to your show whenever possible! I learn more from you then I ever did in NYC schools! Lol. Enjoy your Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIPMorningShow @KevinCooney @AaronNola027 @Jeansegura02 @gabekapler @JSalisburyNBCS The thing he's missing,Middlet… https://t.co/qaDhvThSlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panthers RBI @bxllaaaa17 @KeeganLanzerio @PaetowSoftball @madisonhaileyyy #PaetowPride #paetowsoftball #tournament… https://t.co/RLXrrfz0xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjaninemorison @realDonaldTrump Thank you for continuing to prove that all the demon rats are completely brain-dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an iStout Affogato by @8wiredbrewing @ Stouthouse — https://t.co/xAgRgqL094]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVVnoticias maduro estaba muy callado ya comenso un ataque sicologico para demoralizar al pueblo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineLamarre Le système est vraiment plus malade que toi 🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigpapi343 @WatchTheBreaks @ClubOneOfOne1 I'd kill for just one he's my dream autograph sadly I'll never be able t… https://t.co/nkmWdvTySB]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of #CelebrityBigBrother2’s finale, here is my @CBSBigBrother all-stars cast! @MrPEC_Tacular,… https://t.co/FA48pYHDWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hannahmpait OH YA?!?!? WHAT WILL I PUT ON A RESUME: can style a wig pretty good, is a people person, knows a LOT of Disney trivia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tx_pierce @NYFRANK27 @drewcotner Or you simply are surrounded by dedicated, good players.  Vast majority of kids o… https://t.co/nUiODf79oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sure @realDonaldTrump would call this FAKE NEWS as he takes Kim’s strong assurance that he knew nothing about i… https://t.co/VASIFy2vGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeachThatAsh I’d do alright with the hiding and scavenging for food/supplies part.  The gun fights, bow and arrow… https://t.co/F0u2wZknIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really excited to finish up my @sudhirvenkatesh book #GangLeaderforaDay and then move on to @mrjasonowilson… https://t.co/8LVEDHyKEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Antonio Stock Show &amp; Rodeo https://t.co/tYKPIPtXeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeejBug Yes! It was the sort of green even mild wouldn’t touch.   Also it was a very even color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fatNIXON and China trade Just in case you missed it  tRUMP spent 8 billion in aid to farmers (WELFARE) because of… https://t.co/tCKXEgSb7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW //// Classic Wines Auction - Winter Winemaker Dinner Series with @synclinewine https://t.co/RmTfzVKjjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wet_pterodactyl @kevinjonas @nickjonas @joejonas I know but I already know nothings gonna beat it, got a summa vibe]]></document><document><![CDATA[15/ The higher of the powers has spoken, and has demanded, not asked, these things be fulfilled and they are to be done immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANOTHER YouTube movie about my @Lowepro Protactic 450AW! We’re talking about the gear I travel with, and the bag I… https://t.co/2Bi0prNxGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@get4208 @RealMattCouch @realDonaldTrump @EMPIREonF0X Oh brother!! Self Created Victim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drummond_of_DFS He looked healthy but seemed to be Coach Bud almost using him as a decoy. Didn't look hurt but the… https://t.co/1QuEpkdHie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been loving @PlayApex. I think it would be great of they made some comics of their heros. I'd read a Lifelin… https://t.co/nae7i7Bi04]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InfinitePaintingDesign #WoodArt #WoodCreations #Art #Abstract #AbstractArt #MyMichiganCity… https://t.co/CECNWryOXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[this new juice wrld about to bring the henny gawd out of retirement for the weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethkroll Cold wasn't an issue! More challenging was the 8 ft sheet of insulation, which began creaking/popping in… https://t.co/wgRX8BM5k9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronLangston22 @AuburnBaseball Oh yeah. I’ve been pissy all weekend because I couldn’t watch it. I refused to pay… https://t.co/zdZITpWnYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y mosca, te ponen en unas “Listas”, con nombres degradantes. Son hackers Rusos contratados.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mihotep @castello2 I definitely understand your view @mihotep. But you certainly know as well as any that the… https://t.co/Y5WPb7zOWf]]></document></documents></author>