<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Closing lunch and keynote for Indiana Campus Compact 2019 Summit.  @RoseHulman we have a lot to learn from our ICC… https://t.co/UiHzSjPG1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @LindseyGrahamSC #WorstComedianEver! #Ironic, jokin', about somebody, who won't have a #JOB, but a… https://t.co/lujIKcxAP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look at my best friend @PinknWhiteBat12’s fan art from @rabbidsofficial!!! #RabbidsFanArt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cl… https://t.co/GlgZmV1sUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruh roh. Hang on Lola. It’ll be ok. #winterinwisconsin #lola #snow #february @ Lolas Garden https://t.co/JLBEuUqEZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the 3 boys who said “Lemmie hit that” to me in the target parking lot... I hope you stub your big toe on a brick while barefoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about buying some Trippie Redd tickets I might have a free one left 🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[$20,000 in the hole and sad to know that I’m better off than most people the same age and still won’t be able to pa… https://t.co/eUu3LSwTOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using “part, part, whole” as a strategy to solve our missing addend word problems with a partner. #WeLoveMath… https://t.co/E1APBAVCkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIackPplVids One time this happened to me and my dad made me go back and pay them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Feel sorry for whomever has to work with the dude holding the can of baked beans. 🤢🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean Stalin was as brutal as Hilter.  He had no issues starving, executing, and burning his own cities.… https://t.co/P0KWVSKhVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is right around the corner and our Marigold Totes are in bloom! 🌻  If you are going out to dinner or headed… https://t.co/bFrz1HN7oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is worse than expected. There is supposed to be separation between church and state!!   From Discover on G… https://t.co/wK20wmkEuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Couldn't  they release him and take you, Pence and McConnell? #HappyDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Sussex God! I can’t believe the state of UK journalists. Just a little bit of research and a little less arrogance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nightbroother What can I do to help you?  Can you call a hotline or a family member you trust?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Downtown San Francisco in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/8i7UK5I9ZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If youre funny and make me laugh until I feel like I cant breathe, you’re mine. 🥰 hit my line]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bakit laging Yolanda Funds ang hinahanap? Bakit hindi hanapin si Peter Lim at yung mga drug lords na pinatakas ni D… https://t.co/US1ghOhtVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickLewis13 @yolakin @clenglish @kim @AugustaGolfGirl @heykim @allaboutirma @teeco71 @lilsouthernlady @NatalyinAK… https://t.co/4ZMtM4omQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ladies aren’t ladies and pee all over the lid in public. Y’all are gross 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @DollarTree in Hanover, MD https://t.co/QZ6ivFmYVI https://t.co/b7z1gWpfAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You might be interested in the VR experiences in our Nearpod and Discovery Education resources as well! Can’t wait… https://t.co/rYaBKfYsIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jikookmiin___ Hello my brother. How are you? One thing I want the true, can't stay in the hospital all the time. I… https://t.co/RMA4XNiSyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 🎁@tperez3826 #GIVEAWAY AT 1,000 FOLLOWERS, WHICH WILL BE REVEALED AT A LATER TIME.🎁 . jeffreestarcosmetics launch… https://t.co/jcfLCn9v8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Easter bunny has a cold and has forgotten basic math again🙃. Maybe coffee will help🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/o65Vqj2dqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elaine72948039 @MSNBC @MalcolmNance @maddow @senatemajldr @POTUS Amen to that! Now we find out, Trump wants to giv… https://t.co/7pOWCjCp8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may be because I’m sleep deprived but these hometowns have me crying 😭❤️ #bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know you’re tired when your eyelashes start doing the clicky thing whenever you blink]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all broken. That's how the light gets in. #playyourhand♠️♥️♣️♦️ #lookup✨ #attitudeofgratitude💫 #itsalwaysnow… https://t.co/aatYcn8jwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beegsi_ @MrMaker14 No it wasn’t. How dare you disparage someone’s name who you do not know. How dare you infer any… https://t.co/oVrxEyNkKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God these 2 young men finally found their truth. After watching how can you doubt them???#LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 day work/school week followed by a 3 day vacation - I can do this https://t.co/rxTrqwKilq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had charcuterie for lunch today. Also for dinner at least 3 times last week. Do what makes you happiest they say 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YT_Reagan please go through that interview with the two young ladies dating R. Kelly that's #2 on trending. I want… https://t.co/Xjcvz2nayj]]></document><document><![CDATA[First team to win 4 consecutive MiAA titles!! 💚 https://t.co/ATvBMm7le8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte I’m with you! The fee to just just apply is around $900.00 total.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow @andylassner @EdGlavin @MaryConnelly @kevinlemanII @coreypalent @pommyrantz 😂😅😂🤣❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[INCASE YOU DIDN’T KNOW: abortions ARE NOT federally funded and defunding planned parenthood will only prevent women… https://t.co/xgRzeTHFDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen has already been tried and convicted. Republicans continued effort to discredit him instead of addressing his… https://t.co/hwL2ytuzb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DubaiCheckFraud @adamegelman @RubensteinAdam Examples please of people who have been silenced]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PCs dropped the ball when they took over. There was never any watchdog put in place to ensure appropriate spend… https://t.co/O4OB8iGJ9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of mourning what could’ve been, I’m going to celebrate today bc I know I fight to make sure I don’t get to… https://t.co/lGmk5dPw6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahmarjr I’m positive you never shared this with me!  It’s soooo good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seriously ??  #mysaintpaul #twincities #mpls @ Highland, St Paul https://t.co/W9rvSuMr5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genwhypod Yeah I asked a couple ‘hard’ questions and she skirted around them. I wanted to believe. What kind of person makes that up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory That's nice. Now let's see him stick with that break and actually, go up against Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano I see all this support for the very thing the African American and African American Islamic Communit… https://t.co/uZhF3KXBf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tatiana just had a very laud #Zumba class 😉 . Similar to @AOC. Funny 😄.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #InternationalWomensDay, I want to thank all my sisters for inspiring me to keep up the fight to protect ea… https://t.co/cRtpRT983X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men are so quick to blame a woman for why they are the way they are. “You’re supposed to mold me” FIRST of all, thi… https://t.co/0aFy2I6Hcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[There may still be snow on the ground, but horses are shedding out nicely 👌🏼 https://t.co/mWSLF37jxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st Week Spring Break Miami Waves https://t.co/6q2tWjvXn8 https://t.co/7kkQcEjbYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little sister day today 😍🤗 So glad you decided to spend #springbreak here! Love you seeeester! ❤️🌊 @ La Crema- Tapa… https://t.co/qQ80oZX879]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zthunda Tbh I prefer them in solid colors. Can’t do the pattern and the ombré ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EwaGoszczynska Yikes you’re brave! Too much restriction in natural ROM - be careful! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJThompsonmusic never disappoints! Great tunes and great beer @TownBreweryCa https://t.co/aJ9YgecIAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @GovChristie @JoeNBC Steve Schmidt did NOT say Trump could win. You don't remember 19 Oct 16 on your s… https://t.co/nxNiampB2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peace out, Palm Springs!! 🌴 ready to get home and snuggle my boys!! // I just want to say THANK YOU to everyone who… https://t.co/vM5D9hQZ3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes in Life, it’s best to always be observant of everyday life challenges. For, know one knows what tomorrow… https://t.co/T7KWy5fMJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_of_Europe Why so much migration? Why aren't these people staying in their own countries?  Why aren't Muslim  peo… https://t.co/7X434BAYqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenkuntzGP @MVPAward @allinison @okkiwiflyhome @betsyweber @krosvold @SQLMelody @KellyLappKane You are incredible… https://t.co/SoNaYOyxxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to work on something pretty magical yesterday with the horticulture team at the Conservatory of Flowers. We c… https://t.co/O74vFGzQrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarie Burton comment on Danneels post is best friend material at its finest. https://t.co/L0INCvmVpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: I think Joey was so much better for Rachel and Ross was horrible for her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis you rub my back and I will rub yours with a happy ending]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your bass probably doesn’t need to be loud enough to rattle my whole house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGHolmgren @TheAuthorGuy @IanAMartin I’m hoping it’s Secondhand Souls - the next book after A Dirty Job.   (Be a b… https://t.co/C4yKiqhUUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ve been stacking the deck all offseason to make a run for the NL east]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRIVERS!!!! START YOUR ENGINE!!!! 🚗🚙🚗🚙🏎 @NASCARonNBC @nascardaytona @NASCAR #Daytona500 https://t.co/It1PNmRjEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RtweetsG 😭😭😭 it's a lot of money but I'm sure it's worth it for those who can afford it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am deadass serious If Seventeen were to ever an LA show, I will pay for someone to come with me and take video be… https://t.co/M9PsGhPT1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t even tell what song this was but I sure was thinkin i’m cute uh https://t.co/kcJiojMKYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll open them all, but I’ve repeatedly warned that if you show me a creepshot I’ll expose you publicly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatcha doing?  Me, too! 😁😉😳😆😅😄😃🤣😂 🌼 🐝 🐸 #hey #whatchadoin #blessed #youareloved #mysuperpowerisprayer… https://t.co/zN57bL3p1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeChainSA Killers of human human being babies https://t.co/dQymQK9EL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asleepynin Yeah, it’s absolutely  a bizarre and hostile way to interact  with someone you’ve never met in person before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I find the motivation to go to a class that I hate, and a class that is having a quiz that I’m not prepared for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so done with people who have big ass egos. Your exit out of my life is this way 👉 https://t.co/cQTQpvrdbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel Has Already Pulled In $160 Million Opening #Weekend https://t.co/74otxCOqwU via @HotNewHipHop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdlogg @BibRave @3dotjuan @BrendaRuns @jenn_savedge @HoustonMarathon Especially is there is a pub crawl involved! #BibChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[my family and sibling of@course!! they helped me get here and still do, and i miss my kiddos every day and i love t… https://t.co/nNYrywOvm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost everyone I dated in the past is either engaged, having kids or divorced...  Bullet dodged https://t.co/HHqIDTPxv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lou_S_Stools @Andy @NeNeLeakes That wig was everything! (almost as good as her court jester one)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get It! Getting real Cozy tonight #RevolverBarWeHo #billyfrancesca #RevolverBarWeHo https://t.co/xwJYqfbzra https://t.co/5RGPq4En1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sararrowsmith NEVER i could never!!! i should have made the tweet specifically abt girls without the H in their name]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aviatrixt @kylegriffin1 @GovRonDeSantis cc: @AGAshleyMoody (Again, an attempt 🤷‍♀️)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So stupid. You can’t have a problem with Klobuchar’s anonymous staffers complaining about her yet support Donald Tr… https://t.co/E71UuWFRN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chancetotravel @ThestoryofJS @Sostraveluk followed! Excited to read about your adventures!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to our Pisces cat Gala who is 15 years old March 8. We got her from the Humane Society when she was… https://t.co/TxkKELm1CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RescuingDogsVE @MARIAACLIFTON @ClaudiaMRola @EllenRitsos @pocs80 @MIBFBI @ThreeDogsNappin @chortletown… https://t.co/9wIXfSSbqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bored. 😏♥️  • • • • Choreo: @mrhamiltonevans 🙌🏻🍍 Song: #breakupwithyourgirlfriendimbored @arianagrande 🎶🔥 Dancers:… https://t.co/Gdt1pFWBgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Republicans are trying Cohen. They have data and facts from Cohen. It’s about what he knows and he is the one w… https://t.co/7bBRDisbtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:45am, I woke up with the feeling I missed the ticket sales here in the US now I can’t sleep. Let’s spread po… https://t.co/4VDOmxUlhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Всемирное общество защиты животных: Запретить медленное убийство северных оленей в Уфе https://t.co/zlKIW5gUyn via @ChangeOrgRus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellelamar @Karoli @MSNBC Yup. Find a way to let us keep some beef and we good. https://t.co/yU0gHnDLzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clementegelo gaga hindi naman pweds usa to ph sa tinder. need pa mag bayad sir hahahahahahahahahahaha 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNerdsmith only you will appreciate how awful this whole thing is. https://t.co/rWSxQllyB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[311??? Adtr??? BLINK 182?!!)??(  Frank iero???? Gkassjaw??? Man o???? GYM CLASS HEROES??!!!  THIS IS FULL OF RICHES… https://t.co/qpvsvpUi93]]></document></documents></author>