<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jasonbirch @Esri Ohh ouch! They must have forgot the most important thing from the 5 rules of dodgeball... DUCK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDPomp hate to see the talent leave, but someone else can inherit the problems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValeriePrimros4 Remember Jesus was God robed in a body of Flash, but now he is ascended, therefore he knows, but t… https://t.co/mKaCpXIxZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d hate to die young.  like if you die at 40, that obviously makes when you’re 20 half of your life, but odds are… https://t.co/qzi3n7IXXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Comfy Chair by Eppig Brewing at @tigertigertav — https://t.co/R6eiIj7AAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlockWriterstm @theintercept @briebriejoy 1.3 TRILLION dollars to give 30 million people $400k a piece when that m… https://t.co/z1V5mO4Ef5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude passive aggressive nature is truly aggravating bro YOU’RE the reason why]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was attacked by two vegans wearing pink pussy hats, they were yelling”we’re with her this is hillary land” the wh… https://t.co/gtWaVgmnd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agentcurieuse @Comey Do you know Mueller’s past at all? Look how many lives he ruined before this “investigation”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at the future schedules I still think Davidson wins the conference. VCU doesn’t have an easy schedule the r… https://t.co/axQ8u0KDGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Central Coffee Co. Southend in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/NsJnU1ULNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadfowler I hope this is the soundtrack for your event: https://t.co/WmDA73vfM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On March 2, 1962 Wilt Chamberlain set the single-game scoring record in the by scoring 100 points for the Philadelp… https://t.co/NI7u6Yq0ZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[a few photos from my wedding this past weekend 💍 https://t.co/KsRUoODvte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brownandgold89 @NBAOfficial My argument was the Harden was right to challenge what he thought was behavior not fit… https://t.co/ciQC72ajjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The North Koreans are playing the psychological game with Trump. I was watching footage of the Trump-Kim Summit 2 a… https://t.co/7ahb0NrbpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just when I was about to fly off into a raging tirade about this dumb bag, and how they could have put the pape… https://t.co/q7rEtYKuJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing DO vs OLU or DO vs HB would be like my two worlds colliding at full force.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSANOWFOREVER3 @SarieAl @sicat222 @bubasl @awwadsalotaibi @Abualfawarss123 @Headsnipe011 @SecStudiesGrp… https://t.co/dITAvfhby0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Willard on a 6-0 run to start the game leading Madison. Lady Flashes are tall and athletic! #njhss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLAMOURSHOWSTAR @chi_townkid77 @bigeventny @laguardiaplaza Nice addition! Looking forward to meeting her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeshua_porvida Love you sista you made me smile an an I love the way you can so effortlessly bring Glory to God 🙌🏼… https://t.co/LNmYjvePmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice job Carlos! #DRCrystalAwards #LifeAtDiamomd #floridalife https://t.co/liADUJzan2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HISHEIRESSANDCO @4wardCity @ElevationChurch @JesusIsTheWay_7 @JewishTweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarloColaiacovo  @FirstUp1050 that first idiot that Ron Hainsey leads the NHL in +/-.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealDeljoo Happy Birthday Brodie ! I didn’t even know! Enjoy your day homie ! 🎊🎉🎈💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see @BigWos is out here going wicked hahd on the Daily Ding to butter them boys up before the Boston live show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle All those years at Fox really sharpened your ability to lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokerCookieM @WWLP22News In my opinion, 16 and even 18 to me is still too young to vote to fully understand everyt… https://t.co/oBVKu7w949]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife: “Where is Cardiff?” Me: “Wales.” Wife: *Googles* “It’s in Wales.” https://t.co/IkyotwIJS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejandraoraa Es positiva, la tensión es necesaria es tiempo de decisiones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wagner ain’t pass Bron the ball then tried to dap him up but Bron wasn’t going for it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaidersBeat It was a great trade. Cooper was a moody malcontent who had a horrendous work ethic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣 &amp; my bih talking bout she gone get a Girl n leave me 💀 Have fun with that👌🏾👌🏾👌🏾👌🏾😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinbkelly @MarkLayman12 @DineshDSouza They don’t teach that in Klan class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @elonmusk, is it possible to refuel on the drone ship and launch to land back on land instead of having to tow it back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another magical afternoon at Disney’s EPCOT. The 2019 Flower and a Garden Festival is just spectacular as always. T… https://t.co/4dKD8zuiOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inge, es de @TigresOficial la carta, rescatelo y a banquear...  no vaya a ser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judas Priest’s ‘Stained Class': The Album That Redefined Heavy Metal https://t.co/hiPDrxggH4 @Loudwire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OzziesPOV Only in #mtl does a blizzard make walking on icy sidewalks easier thanks to the snow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see a graphic novel that’s kinda like Bleach, but instead of spirits it’s like the embodiments of negativ… https://t.co/ISW06cBUws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanElizabeth I'm so thankful that you are! I'm a Nerd/Geek too! Do you like Nintendo and PlayStation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the one-way chemistry between Christine Teigen and Walter (Owen’s grampa)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @LAGOP @SenJohnKennedy @WYGOP @SenJohnBarrasso @SenatorEnzi @PAGOP @SenToomey @wisgop @RonJohnsonWI… https://t.co/SnxbQiDRqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball Senior Night = Butch Reveal 🙌🏽 #GoCougs https://t.co/BAqeq2paGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he got 50 guaranteed to play for the giants and was bad, they'd obliterate him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ENighti Ghost is bad..Provy is bad..JVR is bad...and the list goes on..it just doesn’t mesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhilRL @nfrealmusic @WittLowry @nightlovell @guccihighwaters @softheartmusic @FROMIVANB @RyanCaraveo @luke_reelfs_… https://t.co/ge6ZTjIXV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jebidiahjohans1 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Notice what. That you can spell stupid. Seams to me, you need so… https://t.co/i8VZjBnpB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Ethiopian Airlines flight with 157 believed aboard crashes minutes after takeoff from the capital:… https://t.co/QUBCyyKbZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyLevi I just wanted to say I really appreciate your openness and honesty about your issues, your vulnerabili… https://t.co/vgRZDn3wfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComeAtMeBreaux Velvet is the warmest material known to womankind. Do you like sweating? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s pretty funny coming from someone who dodged the draft with a faux medical condition]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire drive to pick up a friend there was a couple in the car behind me clearly having an argument. Though I c… https://t.co/tt4wwCVR8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotJerryTipton @_iJakey How is this prediction working out now. What a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boricuaskye5 I understand why you hate this SL but Jon Lindstrom is knocking it out of the park]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tapley_kate @meowitsbrenna @chelseabeth11 @theKevinGarcia_ Oh man could you imagine? I’d never leave work lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my brain’s default setting to assume everyone’s parents are divorced]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princeton Tourney - Red Oak 8 Frisco Lebanon Trl 6, Red Oak 6 Celina 11 @5ATxHSBaseball @4ATxHsBaseball… https://t.co/0H0okIBSgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariannelaurens @podcastDAB @mtlabitibi @919sports @slipcoquilleJC @DLCoulisses Merci Marianne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does this make me emotional? I didn't even know you existed until now 😭 #ThanksOppy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLAlumni @HockeyHallFame @NYRangers Also a Stanley Cup Championship with the 1990 @EdmontonOilers. One of the fin… https://t.co/In4aI6KPVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie-I got a boner reading the Song of Solomon once. Is that what predestination is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primer Tiempo @ElSalvadorFutb 2 @GuatemalaFut 0 #futbol #soccer #salvador #guatemala #canarionetwork https://t.co/6wZjI3BBPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My awesome library @nypl  #library #books #nyc #Manhattan #NewYork #newyorkcity #explore https://t.co/1TtjPlqBI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in headlines that Adam Silver is going to hate: “How former ref Tim Donaghy conspired to fix NBA games”  https://t.co/xOoFMRVpA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @IlhanMN She’s a Mole! We all better wise up before it’s too late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the mouth of the deceiver.    Obama can say it,  But Trump can't #BuzzVideo https://t.co/QBg7wZKRs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up in Walla Walla, Washington, the home of Adam Goddamn West. I wouldn’t stand a chance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felippe_Hermes @JordanFariaLima @_BarbaraBB_ 😂😂😂 https://t.co/cs4um799SN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinicioSenador @LeonelFernandez No Vinicito no discutas eso a FRANCLIN no lo defienda .]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Republican Party does not represent what the United States looks like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Branching out. (There’s a joke in there.) Seeing gretchenrubin at the @cuyahogalib in #Parma tonight with my Love,… https://t.co/nn0pV1oos8]]></document><document><![CDATA[IS YOUR CHECK ENGINE LIGHT ON?                    PULL UP!! #autoservice #autorepair #autoshop #asecertified… https://t.co/FeEhNAIokT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion I disagree with Krugman on many issues but he brilliantly captures the MMT sophistry when he labels it… https://t.co/vMbq5LJHAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bking7878 @JMartZone Nothing over the top on senior day! https://t.co/nw6qYSdsvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the squad! Came this far, might as well WIN it! Either way it goes I’m proud of these guys for represe… https://t.co/Pn5TCaEcdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanmfrost @GirlScoutsUSA I imagine it’s like recruiting, get them pledges bub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liquid Courage Comedy Club (@ Somerville Brewing (aka Slumbrew) Brewery + Taproom in Somerville, MA) https://t.co/2GaYoBLls0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new #sofa we bought for our #newapartment @westelm #newfurniture @ New York, New York https://t.co/ZFeX7YbIpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope @SpeakerPelosi and admitted criminal @SenBooker , are paying attention you do realize we have more authority… https://t.co/4WJVZHn8Dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[today’s  coffee:            )         )        )     )     (         )       )  _(___(____)____(___(__ _ \     Vale… https://t.co/WMeO6BTNM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrashStl @Musial_Suspects Ah, great minds right.   He makes me not to worried if we don’t resign Ozuna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Molly hit me hard af yesterday I drove from the plaza to food4less in the e. Felt like a video game. Shit reminded… https://t.co/B44xMexCFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fort Myers takes over San Antonio TX! @ Knockout https://t.co/jNzaSBJeq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Bart told me in 8th grade to major in Classics. I took her advice, got a PhD in it, and now I follow in her fo… https://t.co/7MaJPoue7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Myriegypt @frandevox @carmencalvo_ Juasjuasjuas....la esposa de mas es española????...hay otro por ahí casado con… https://t.co/voyUb6obt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[realshit im too old to be wasting my time on anything or anyone that won’t benefit me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t mind the violations...... he had to get away.... #brownsvseverybody #browns4life #createyourownlegacy @ Beaut… https://t.co/kfN4viyKr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought daughter first pair of stilettos! 👠 #singledadbliss #fearandlovinginjersey @ Willowbrook https://t.co/hVWelnWodZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bunch of people from clarence going to GU next year... the Corigliano and @SwantekCam effect 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieSwagRight @MahgdalenRose You are all fucking soviets. Can't lose ya. About fake news. Its in ya schools, not… https://t.co/M5E0XEruHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianpaulhaigh @JamesMelville You saying that things that were promised to happen after you leave haven’t happened y… https://t.co/v3bL2Lei0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic panel including @jedidiahyueh sharing insight on micro / macro innovation. Apply the beginners mindset an… https://t.co/ruPhMkdnS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to turn off the @BuffaloSabres game....no hope on this season #Sabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Article on my latest single @areasonabletrth  https://t.co/WPdfY5cWhY  #pop #rap #TheRecipe #birthday… https://t.co/zKX2ZQGlsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timothydclark @RiotRMD Blacksmith and Rivensbane?! I still have to do Scourge. https://t.co/SXPa1IUBOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy March1 Day!! @Cm3465 @MarchiJ @LisaMarch1st @N_Marchi33 @Steve_Marchi @anthony_marchi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, John Miller and John Barron have told plenty of lies as weird as this. We could stay all night making a t… https://t.co/8rFKVXpKup]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand what’s wrong with restructuring a contract. Players get old. Players get worse and no longer wor… https://t.co/7Q2SXncgjv]]></document></documents></author>