<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not having to worry about if your getting a Valentine’s Day gift or if you needed to get someone else a gift  &gt;&gt; #singlelife 😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Look, it was WOMEN who brought it to this point. Libs. Certainly majority. Most of which also protes… https://t.co/fpsbNqZBdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You really BELIEVE YOURSELF! #25thAmendmentNow  #FakeTrumpEmergency  #SoSickOfTheTrumps #NepotismSucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @StewartMidcoSN crushing it today! (&amp; every day)  Keep up the great work!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked out of my window and beheld the poor, begging from house to house with children in tow. “Over here!” I sho… https://t.co/vhn3VUzyAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynKY1950 Antonio he is really creative, we do everything.  My daughter had JRA as a child, now lupus, never let i… https://t.co/3wZrnJd8tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico The #metoo movement is a disgrace of Feminism. I say this as a survivor of sexual molestation as a 13 yr… https://t.co/dGitZOZhKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmen_leannnn Me last Sunday when 5 assignments and 3 discussion boards were due at 11:59pm😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenoBiscontePA Um I’m sorry but @2DMpod came up with waterheads first. Now I love you two so much but I want to gi… https://t.co/g9YptJQ6ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all! Do you like my more cohesive style of Insta posts or should I go back to making them more haphazard? 🤔🤔🤔 https://t.co/kopJBgVSgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristopherB070 @nofussgourmet @DivaVinophile @FoodTravelist @eatandrun @BonVegetit @monstervoyage @foodiamo… https://t.co/Znt4bD2BwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[New fav thing: watching Buzzfeed Unsolved while I workout - love learning about demons while they escape my body]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to scramble and book an earlier flight back because I originally planned on working from Tobago. Since every si… https://t.co/wQQZuothFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[never seen a tweet more relatable to you two @WyattErzen8 @Jacob_WlIkinson]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no reason to be confused, she said it. Hence the reason why she apologized.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlaBorras @katieworth @frontlinepbs @GroundTruth Congratulations to you @CarlaBorras!! And thank you for all, x1000. 🙏⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abmoore1 @Christa0003 @2_legion @benshapiro Aldo Nova, Life is Just a Fantasy... first time I got high. We wore that record out that night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh y’all is 😴😴😴 on Life Waxahachie! 😮 They have the complete package.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Fordham confirms that Trump team threatened the school if his grades became public https://t.co/WYaiY6cCrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BerniesBurgers @localish @ABC7NY You’re welcome!! ☺️  Your Bernie Burgers, 🍔 sure do look 😋 really tasty!!! 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to record ADR an hour before delivering a project and you don’t have any of the right equipment or a… https://t.co/IrtpvhPByP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lazonadeportiva Weather is better so the smile is better too! https://t.co/ZTVnvFf7wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t come in to work today. In case you haven’t heard, the Jonas Brothers are getting back together”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kasich4Indiana @BreatheNewWinds @WomenGreenForum @RonFinleyHQ @green4EMA @suzfrankCA @Frances_Fisher… https://t.co/kfujThvfI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[New 🎊🏡 #home for sale😊🎈 418 Tulare Ave #morrobay #california visitmorrobay @morrobaytravel #carterandco… https://t.co/5TEmarh1Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Xi is tap dancing 🕺 right now at least he has a negotiation tool to counter trumps idiotic trade war 🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[95% of the will of God is already known, and it has to do with who you are, not what you do or where you go. @georgeowood]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I’ll get it...someday. 👀👏🏻 #wheelies #agirlcandream #goals #riderlifestyle #honda #scorpion #grom… https://t.co/BtISKGb4sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomLowe82115133 @ambcottrill @uniotoapm13 @emily_lane11 @jerzipaul2311 @FisherJocie @AmandaMcGlone2 @Halliepink8… https://t.co/F4Y8HZLRWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#noho #manhattan #justwalkingaround #newyork #nyc #ny #strangerthings #skulls #history #travel #rings #dark @ NoHo,… https://t.co/NYdWoV1HDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My room at my dads house was lime green then after the divorce I got to change it to aqua blue and at my moms house… https://t.co/OwmTdR5ZXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime “no respect” is said I can just picture Michael Scott saying it https://t.co/DebAHsxmNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 5th paragraph in. No Facts to back the Collusion.  We can “say” anything. What can you “prove”]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity is good for the soul. #funniness #chuckle #smirk #ludicrous https://t.co/OcdBvvlXmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[D’ya Think Ray Romano Loves Ramen?  #FaceSwap obsessed!@faceswaplive https://t.co/XailT4AiJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAceTJShow When are you giving away Pink concert tickets in Birmingham AL????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Isn’t it interesting that he WAS your lawyer and on the Republican Finance Committee???? If he’s s… https://t.co/BqL8ZrxVLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirCanada @showtime411 This whole thing could have been avoided if @AirCanada would have valeted or gate checked m… https://t.co/ipc5vq8J3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @jamesmurphypdx Who payed for his golf simulator? I'm sure tRump didn't...oh wait it was taxpayers right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti  Question: Ms. Daniels received $130;000. Cohen said he was given $35:000 a month for 12 months. T… https://t.co/NMv9vroWNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clarissa_xplain @techsavvymama @lashawnwiltz @orangetheory @glamnellie Yesss abs and squats are running so close i… https://t.co/MQhMoSq7A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @maggieNYT I was so hoping this story was actually not true. He should be impeached just for the comments about Otto Warmbier]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Footage Of The TPUSA Berkley Incident https://t.co/zxy4lkJW8C via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN if it was the end of the war (basically Christmas + New Years x10,000) and I was that nurse I’d completely und… https://t.co/yeHRWHp3AA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask Bryce about the quality of Philly’s fan base after he wears a Knights jersey to a Flyers game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my man doesn't sing It Takes Two from Hairspray to me at least once, it's not meant to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyKubrick @zenslaya @valentinavoight Oh not even jdm is way better looking and I would know the difference, just… https://t.co/78QlVHLvg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A classmate trying to explain Pokémon to a very clueless teacher is a big mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomeB4Dark @thekellyfrances Just looking at that... https://t.co/xYC4k7kt81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered that I still have to name these babies... 🙈😐😂  #pregnancyproblems #halp #SaturdayMorning https://t.co/1nIJiZN4XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature 🐇 Wow 😯 that’s some hugely beautiful,lovable,precious rabbit!!! 🐰  Adorable ☺️ ☺️ video of both!! 🤰🐇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccascott1496 @sowie_boyz Is THIS why I’m being weird as shit and crying every 2 seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I so appreciate all that you do but you must feel covered in slime most of the day. Question for R’s are al… https://t.co/2EzcSN67xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Arc of Northern Virginia is teaming up with Dulles International Airport, United Airlines, and airport partners… https://t.co/oiuBRpFHNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sport empowers. See it in action with the amazing work being done by @FreeToRunNGO   #run #freetorun #sport… https://t.co/F1bTtPWjU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much i could say, i be wanting to vent and go all in on you but i dont.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lionel killed it last night. Great show. @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/ewahysvxsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh so this is why @pmccormick021 and @hennyyyyy2 slept in till 11 today 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish the politicians would concentrate on padding the public schools cash flow vs the private schools. Mak… https://t.co/mOLilFILNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just admiring how your hair flows in the wind with the windows down. I love the car rides with the music blasting a… https://t.co/oZdeslM98p]]></document><document><![CDATA[u gotta b at least 50% black to say the n word sorry i dont make the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supermathskid @JimMFelton @paperghost @bexin2d @Luiseach @Astro_Jonny @tommyhale91 @davidallengreen Jesus! Off the… https://t.co/JhReaH8b1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥I can’t WAIT until those immunity deals are unmasked and blown up. Let’s do this. Whose behind doors number 1.… https://t.co/k70PvdYDob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever think Frankie Jonas feels left out? They always get back together and he never gets to join]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super fun weekend with #upsamaskom  in Vegas! 😄✨🌈 📸: Ken and annvifuller  . #fremontstreet #fremontstreetexperience… https://t.co/ghwjPOFEmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[والدراع معروف طبعا بالنسبة لهم الإخوان هم الدراع انهم يشعرون بالخوف من من سجنوهم وقتلوهم لعنة الله علي السيسي ومن ي… https://t.co/KX7Zl9ufqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13PhotogRudy @13PhotogWillie Ay, ay !! Ese es mi Amigo Rudy profesional !]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the many factors of the racism and misogyny that @IlhanMN is facing.. its simply because w/are not used to s… https://t.co/eFcN7B6kfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really feeling this article on money and going after what you want and sending money to family. Read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALT_uscis Where did this happen?  Do we have names of the woman and her husband/boyfriend/whatever?   They ought t… https://t.co/bq0TtDtPVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorWoggon so excited for you! Malibu/LA was one of my favorite solo trips]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues bueno nos sacrificamos en Sultanes de Monterrey https://t.co/kPNvm81bCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you guys ever seen @brendonurie make four peoples’ lives all at once? I have. And now so have you. 🙌 https://t.co/SbUIFJ2OWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Misspiggychop @Lilmisty84 @ZellnerLaw @lloydbassII @MyNameMe99 @2Kkozz @TManitowoc @quantum_quasar 😂👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA She never should have been elected at all.  No one should be in  U.S. government who cannot, or will… https://t.co/j4s0YuMHA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KdotJohnson_ k but right now I’m worried about building an empire while you’re just watching Empire]]></document><document><![CDATA[This person on Instagram has me laughing 😂 #90fiance #90dayfiancehappilyeverafter #leida #trash #phonesex… https://t.co/MKaA3jhDdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the coolest booths at the @TravAdventure is the City on the Side #motocycle tours! Get a tour of #Colorado m… https://t.co/ArVW44RvX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toookan I got like 3 and only one is slow motion and they are staying in the vault forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top notch meal @cheflisadahl &amp; hiking fun! #Sedonabeauty @ Sedona, Arizona https://t.co/NEcFYD02kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kymadds Omg it happened to me when scrolling through Twitter I did at least two double takes from confusion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perorationer @hopedowdlist Can also try going into the ocean for a swim. Ring will slip off in the cold salt water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burtmeek @CKBiomechanics @KamalaHarris Again, they don’t. U can’t get chemo for cancer or preventable treatment fo… https://t.co/NPefhijmY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lube tubes and country music bingo with my best fraaans. 🙌🏼 @McFresh_Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wh3UZPPaJX "Ces consultations surviennent un an après qu'un accident impliquant un conducteur d'Uber e… https://t.co/bE9Sac1zdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY SISTER GOT INTO THE PT SCHOOL AT SAC STATE!!!!!🤩🤩🤩she gon be a doctor🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋Sealed with a kiss!  💋This is my favorite lip plumper/color right now from @revlon it keeps your lips so moisturiz… https://t.co/SpPjhEK7yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#failedpugselfie olive.edie.pugstein @ Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts https://t.co/hue7mEychv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstonex2 That’s what I thought. But I know sex is different these days and people are into different things so I d… https://t.co/P1mLNnsOf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask the survivors of the shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School in more quiet moments about the awful yea… https://t.co/H8VaQCMKwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing in life is dessert! #tourlesjours #matchagreenteacake #mangocremecake #sorryredribbon #sweetendings… https://t.co/ewqUSyNrK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA I guess if you cheat to become President. It's worth it. Good luck America. Every election will be like… https://t.co/QOGE06xDFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllentownPubLib Nothing is more exciting than walking out with a tote bag full of books!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yasssss!! #clespraytan #norvellspraytan #216bombshell #euclid #smallbusiness #tansafe @ Bombshell Beauty and Spa https://t.co/d33ozo2s4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I would love lip gloss. I’ve always preferred matte lipsticks. WELL. @patmcgrathreal was like, “Hol… https://t.co/HLKvVCuZp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh shit!  Completely forgot about that highly important meeting that could change the world. Distraction is so easy… https://t.co/w5dbQ4du3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heyy_ItsKristen Thank you so much! I love my new lifestyle! I’ve been making a lot of changes and I feel so much better about myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 🎁@tperez3826 #GIVEAWAY AT 1,000 FOLLOWERS🎁 . touchinsolus is now available at @ultabeauty. I LOVE their No Porebl… https://t.co/B7drs364uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coezycoe @BrianTengMD @SWexner @ScottRSteeleMD @HolubarStefan @AmyLightnerMD @PhilFleshnerMD @amirbastawrous… https://t.co/cRkrat9Te7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Freeport nonprofit is working to raise money to help those in need get through the rest of the Maine Winter.… https://t.co/uqjxPKtFLT]]></document></documents></author>