<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MaggieVA44 @TheThomasGuide @secupp Ahhhh, are they having fun without you and your cats? They can't do that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me enjoy my beer, that i didn’t get carded for because i look my age, in peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rob Zombie + Marilyn Manson Announce 2019 North American Tour Dates https://t.co/AmXi9Owvqa @Loudwire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @TomiLahren @AnnCoulter @IngrahamAngle @seanhannity are all brainless trump ass licker that couldn… https://t.co/LS7LIV3y97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right on target Sir,hate for POTUS    have them loose their common sense,because of the president succeeding in bri… https://t.co/NdiJMwmFBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[for the first time in 19 years, I have remembered it is ash wednesday and have not wondered why there are grey crosses on everyones forehead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimIrsay The Patriots Made All The Right Changes ever since Their First Superbowl Appearance in January 1986... Th… https://t.co/99a5C6ImfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This show low key had me wondering what y’all other nights be into.  Fuck wrong with y’all 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolynplease I had a very hard time not laughing. I felt bad because they were an immigrant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drewmin72 @kenjeong yeah me too, I wonder what that would be like, yeah amazing, I am a big fan of Ken's since I s… https://t.co/BQ4a6QAysi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microsoft is sending me two XBOX ONE X dev kits. https://t.co/HHs5kdPHg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cultivation Classic judging process begins... #Oregon #cannabis #CannabisCommunity @East_Fork_Farms @wweek https://t.co/wsHaRr81Lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you lonely hearts on this shitty #ValentinesDay here’s a heartwarming story of me embarrassing my youngest d… https://t.co/Zxw0zlCoKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[No iba por ahí el cometería mío... el punto es ..que ambos no han jugado bien partidos que han ganado o, que hay ri… https://t.co/7Co4aeIkBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grammys Get Awful News as #MichelleObama's Appearance Could Have Actually Hurt Ratings @MichelleObama https://t.co/rL7fvveT2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelinaSummers I agree Races yes, Religions yes, Tennessee fans maybe lol, political ideologies responsible for the… https://t.co/5e1rOtx6b4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can only give empty promises for so long before nobody believes you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RastaballsOPG @stephan_xo Me:  My bank account : https://t.co/1cBCTOUEZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why people keep quoting this tweet with a list of events that are happening around the world. Y’all do realize… https://t.co/Y9YaOXqvpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddieonfox Ah okay! All good. I was finishing up last weeks episode this morning and loved the second period cover… https://t.co/E21MHQN0Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent my son a pic of me on the water catching fish today. He sent me this pic right after and it hit home. Refuel… https://t.co/R4otTXlrnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstonJeffrey @KathaleenHarpe9 At times I worry about 2020!  Not because of @POTUS but just the ugly haters called… https://t.co/xayd43oe2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sr-  what kind of studio do you need? C- depends on what people will pay for Sr-  that makes sense.  Would you turn… https://t.co/AEjaor2cX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ship is repeatedly disabled and distressed, but always back up in full working order.  Where are the spare parts coming from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be determined in prayer takes discipline and a love for intercession. The Holy Spirit leads us in prayer, and He… https://t.co/HNUOEcf5oR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyL66 I never even came close to saying anything like that. Where on Earth did you get that from? Your assumpti… https://t.co/ApykkQlRvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DavidMiller_ @C3Conference @EdYoung @claude_thomas It was so fantastic having y’all here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boosted_Busta @JodyDWright @MerrisBadcock @WPTV @WPTVContact5 @RyanShomo @varnadorewesley @samj1293 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my man @EdKiernanNYC enjoy it brother! #MUC #alumni #thoma]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok people - want to transform Thursday? WATCH THIS and prepare to die laughing - from our fave genius]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cawayee @lol0ptz @katieguo I actually this was gonna say “turning 24 soon but just took an L” when I saw the sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elohimmusic feel better beautiful!! You’re amazing and deserve peace and happiness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[good day today @KyleKashuv @KassyDillon @DonaldJTrumpJr https://t.co/aSty9BW2MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko please make one of #AngelaLansbury as JB Fletcher from Murder, She Wrote!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is an entire other world once you see it, hear it, and live it in person]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessphillips is just the bees knees, the business, the real thing. And if Britain’s lucky and/or smart, the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[I signed up for @HiFiveUp! Can I just say how good it is to have a soul like @HelloMelanieC building with kindness… https://t.co/BXprh37jRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @Ivanr_HD From little marco's BIG Mouth, Another EMPTY threat!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judybeansdeux @kwilli1046 Weird question but ok..  my stance is that both of them are wrong and nobody should ever… https://t.co/CTxh9Nwp6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am blown away by @ChucklefishLTD and Wargroove!!! This game looked awesome when it was first announced and I’ve w… https://t.co/Eo3rHXxcaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroTransitMN  "Hypothetically" if we get a foot of wet heavy snow Saturday into Sunday morning is there any reas… https://t.co/nAfcVQL4qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boredsuch Yeah, they're the most acclaimed amongst the audio enthusiasts. Supposed to be the more "balanced" one.… https://t.co/RkdTCghbJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #internationalwomensday with this #FBF. Thanks to all of the amazing women I work with who inspire me,… https://t.co/cSbZ30TZfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikos39617878 @Harlan It is easy to point the finger. And if you said socialism is a mental illness I would agree… https://t.co/mJq7If15rZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is Dave Matthews starting to become ironically cool this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go see it before it’s gone again and definitely check out the soundtrack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @ChamberWichita for the opportunity today to discuss important issues facing businesses across our sta… https://t.co/hRNdIyuigR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitch_Lion815 @realJBA @AvalancheTwitch @BeastCaucasian @KingSchaffy Have a little more respect brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @theblaze @WhiteHouse I would still bet a paycheck!!! Stephan Halper and Joe Pientka ARE THE KEYS to unl… https://t.co/ycSry1Y1jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan The good news Mister #frump is we'd be happy to fund the walls that are closing in on you ! ! !… https://t.co/FsVOptHivV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ki enfomation ki bon nan 2 a  #Carel Sanble se Ginayiv tet dwat li ye #Duval 👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Godfather just got done with this week's episode containing his thoughts on seeing Captain Marvel and the contr… https://t.co/0axhJChvfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Agreed Ms. Milano.  I wish I knew how to convey this message to our elected representatives in government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is dumb cause education isn’t a tangible resource like bread or food that needs to be made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NorthKorea the bromance with Kim hasn't accomplished anything it would appear]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your an ARTIST, TODAY is YOUR lucky day💚🍀!!! Follow me for a follow back and maybe a collab!!🔥🔥 All independent… https://t.co/47Ry1b7hN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troyboi’s -Grimey will always be one of my favorite songs. Easy top 8. So dirty and live is even better. https://t.co/cVU9GYTO7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: @MHSLadyHounds leads St. Pius X, 20-19. Serena Sundell leads Maryville with 14. https://t.co/9xJfbGGgV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't misunderstand this is serious stuff..however This beats any amusement park ride! https://t.co/irijv2PBpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump KEEP UP THE INCREDIBLE WORK!!! I DON'T CARE WHAT LYING MICHAEL COHEN SAYS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZubearAbdi Lmao I’m still tripping off the screenshot intro you posted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Lizzzy @Wonderfullycre1 @inecnigeria Not one seat in lagos house of assembly only (APC.) One party state is n… https://t.co/2N5XGfyY0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giannis - MVP PG - because he doesn’t travel  Harden - because he travels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the Panthers release Munnerlyn is the BEST news I’ve gotten today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @AOC Leo borrowed huge amounts of money to build St. Peter’s and fight a war in 1517. He had inherite… https://t.co/G49KpijNmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXL @sza @Kehlani @ellamai @JheneAiko @kodieshane favorite female *artists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubasl @KellZillaMae @Turki_AlOwerde @sicat222 @SarieAl @awwadsalotaibi @Abualfawarss123 @Headsnipe011… https://t.co/BhmHPohqua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sophie_swaney A couple of the tagged ones would be great. But I would kill them shit bags for free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from @emmillerwrites about the fallout from yesterday's UMC meeting.   https://t.co/LAcsRvSrMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually never go to Wednesday Night BET but just might this year. Guessing we will get 2 good games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadDogRadio Has been s soap boxer!It would have won a Oscar in all categories! However not the best song! It's not… https://t.co/lCERnof2PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaBoz28 @Ramcgreg @vivahate46 @benshapiro You need to reread Hamiltonian history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Does that include the illegal money your paying your bo? Ethics violations hopefully will land your a-s in jail. #MAGA2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who could video this, and not help ‘ get your fuckin head out of your asses !😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHSD155 Fun to be part of such a great event! Thanks to all the @CHSD155 parents that came to learn and share more… https://t.co/mLf5owbE1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Neat looking old Locomotive, They had a class about them that the diesels just don't have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cduhigg Hbs 2015 here. 3.5 years out of school I can tell you there are people in my cohort who already feel this… https://t.co/3x0DrBslyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really @russwest44 you’re such a pansy. I would punch you in the throat if I had the chance for your idiotic though… https://t.co/D1YdSZFzSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @POTUS #TRUMP @realDonaldTrump your mutual love ❤️ with  #KimJongUn 🇰🇵 should be all that’s needed to have… https://t.co/7uAptZxxsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami Marlins lose another game today vs St. Louis Cardinals. They have only won 2 games so far this spring training. #MLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldenmeanpk powercirclesecurity @CuzzinDre_ jprincerespect zoetharoasta @ Oakland, California https://t.co/XzYV2XSWn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacMemo @Faitelson_ESPN @1AlfredoTala @rodrigosali29 @cochorios15 https://t.co/NaNnB2Zvg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dangd3si I been doing it since the beginning of the year😂 y’all caught my wave in all honesty😭🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday March 6 - Today In Politics:   How Trump’s high school hid his transcript;      Michael Bloomberg decides… https://t.co/WMMnckr0Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman initiation! April, Ciara and Iliana! 3 a.m.🤣🤣🤣 #fish #WFHS #Coyotes #ladycoyotesoftball @ Wichita Falls, T… https://t.co/WUzdGiH2zz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomcliffordcfc @hazardeden10 Now they want Klopp as their next manager]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @YhsBucks host Pierre, with the winner earning a trip to state. Game in 5. Updates to follow. https://t.co/6olOYMRTW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LockerRoom101 I tried to nap. Didn't work of course! Still debating if I wanna drink or not? Making it more compli… https://t.co/3cgZu7Jfpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLydecia @Suns Yes they do! Some nice R &amp; R and a couple days of meaningful practice! #timetorise]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING ~ ASKING 498,000.00 ~ Hasbrouck Heights, NJ Beautifully remodeled brick single family home on a 51 x 10… https://t.co/F5QOrbp5TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could I leave the man beyond the skies upstairs out Its a blessing thank you God🙏🏽💯🙌🏽👏🏾 I’m blessed #Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Oh shit. @aoc is gonna piss off the boomer snowflakes with this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrible and useless statement. This is the entirety of it. https://t.co/RD9A9eu6wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't have to search for the good if you're surrounded by genuine people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @KellsBellsSC I bet that town is better off now than when a Democrat was in office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanna , sorry for so rude , never pull your pants down until I say .O.K , I understand your a women]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbbecker19 While this is true, I’m ok with that. Us men have been praised since the dawn of time, while women have… https://t.co/LoqG7p7oc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp @Betsy_Manning #CPAC  It’s no longer conservative   It’s how Nazi’s communicate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy anniversary my love 😍 gracias por soportarme estosmaravillosos 11 años te quiero y te amo 😍 con todo mi coraz… https://t.co/1cwa3diF6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeThompsonOE @OxfordPolice Thank you. Please forward to Lafayette County to initiate the same program. The amoun… https://t.co/VIl6yyRpBn]]></document></documents></author>