<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This guy wrote a book on how Hillary lost the election. It was so full B.S. and he's still at it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[While binge watching Grey’s Anatomy for the up-teenth time, there’s always that one episode or one scene that will… https://t.co/lyJyN3aA4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜💚💛Everywhere else it’s just Tuesday.  Happy Mardi Gras!💜💚💛 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/pG8YAUOScn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drew into top 8 of #MTGMemphis with @kjvsthehighway. He's sweating his breakers, but hopefully we get two Bearded Dragons in top 8.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I gotta stop watching Facebook vids before class starts that’s shit has me cryin wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shotwithsoju I’m like a really big fan. How’s ur day? Did you have any good food?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby sister is officially a mommy !! Welcome to the world Easton and Oakley 💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susanperchede @777089965g @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump Every outlet had Hillary winning remember. They had Kavanaug… https://t.co/kpvpVvyErq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311 @NickHexum @pnut just got out of the show!!! So much fun. When can I own it friends?!?! I need it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @MichaelsStores does this not add up to 70% off?? Every weekend I’m confused by your emails https://t.co/bsiefKgemI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep telling myself I'll delete Instagram but getting dark patterned. You apparently can't delete on mobile? Make it easy to unplug, dangit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIssyvoo Mandatory positivity is a neoliberal, dehumanizing approach to emotional life. Victim-blaming and gaslighting all rolled into one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to personal reasons I’m deleting my Twitter. 🖕🏼 https://t.co/9NQxhcaWAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is so bizarre to have people that harassed and belittled and bullied me expect me to want to be their dumping gr… https://t.co/Hey7Tb3LbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csunorthridge why is the library and gym full of high school students? Like, don’t I pay enough tuition already wi… https://t.co/FrJCLp9aoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#findlife #spirit #❤#😂 #theway #benew #believeonthelordjesuschristandthoushaltbesaved… https://t.co/YfMt8E0X60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu @orange_parrot19 I challenge @FLOTUS to stand up for the migrant children terrorized at our border-… https://t.co/SNwBWwjZE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaBelle_Cat Your welcome LunaBelle for the follow,your a beautiful kitty and congrats on that many followers!!!😸… https://t.co/YOWEt4UMFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Bob McGinn.  Met him at the Phoenix airport. We were on the same flight to Vegas.  Have to say I’ve had a bit… https://t.co/UCO8ZqAUf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sure thing , Spanky. How about we ALL explain what has happened.  Except THIS TIME you can’t say “… https://t.co/1Jt0nufXCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyOnAir @emilyrosefry My ex still has me up on hers. While cheating on me with who she’s with in her new profile pic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeesoul "May as well give up, Rex...you know momma said not to cross the road. Now git back in the woods before the fur starts flyin'']]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have to post about my boyfriend every day for him to still be in the picture. Just know that we’re happy 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fair, you really know how to make me cry when you give me those ocean eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scheana Next time you're in nashvegas I got you. Your sister in green!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uepcsonora @Chaposoto @michelleriveraa @rquirrin @TribunaSonora @marcelobeyliss @megavisionmx @hilarioolea… https://t.co/UYJ1m6i8O3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckRossDC Maniforts job was to organize and hold the delegates. He is good at that. He did it for Bob Dole and others. No Russians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've reached peak hand size, lifting, squatting and jumping season. My mute button will be getting its own workout this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanFraserDR @COURTATDIAMOND @MalbonDavid @DRIguy2017 @bscotthart @TammyDRI @nanperusse8 @Shelley_TeamVB… https://t.co/MnYmhQkHHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even get a nigga to take me to the movies let alone my nails done 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanChiarelli @hoctorthelovedr @MSNBC When you consider the nature and scope of this investigation 2 years is no… https://t.co/EsA9Ox8DKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody said if you’re good at something, don’t do it for free... &amp; shiiiii that got me thinkin lbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerrydulac @PittsburghPG I don’t have a good feeling about Steelers going forward. I saw so many problems in 2018:… https://t.co/0f5UkGjgg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #SHAZAM movie looks outstandingly good, the visuals are on point, it has humor and heart, AND talk about that k… https://t.co/IR1FD3yfz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cain_nate I hope every one of these evil Democrats are haunted by the screams of those poor innocents the rest of their worthless lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion : entertainment journalists should only wear black on awards shows. It’s not their night. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[More fun pics from a great night for an amazing kaws!  auction_for_a_kaws #greenvillesc #animalauction… https://t.co/IQAmyKpie3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystaljadepark We try to tell our stories as completely as possible on the platform as we find audiences don’t co… https://t.co/z1v3U5M90u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld No, stupid E Entertainment made them stupid rich for nothing! #stupid #RealityCheck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t do much today so if I owe you something, it will be tomorrow. My hips and hands feel like I’m 40 years old… https://t.co/a8mlXKV8KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BornIMusic glad to see you made all your sets at @dejavoom! I was the girl that helped,I’m assuming your manger an… https://t.co/bp7l6HbPu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_patel @jenkready7 There’s potential, but we’re feisty enough as it is. That’s my concern]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BernieSoBlack he tells Black people there's no need for identity politics and we should just focus on working clas… https://t.co/nK9DSq6eLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OaklandRJ @takebackousd @OUSDNews @OaklandEA From the healing comes strength, the road toward justice is filled wi… https://t.co/AQOi3j3Okw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HCHSPTO Thank you!  Shout out to our third lead Kristy Giltner, along with all our other wonderful volunteers who… https://t.co/ydXCmsAQgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[fucking sucks watching someone you love go through something and not being able to do anything to help]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been three weeks since I last ate beef 😬 I’m trying to stop eating pork but whenever there’s bacon involved I can’t control myself lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls who brag about being with, or brag about being able to steal another girls boy are easily the most trash huma… https://t.co/3IHcmRCPHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sat morning breakfast with the fam. Challah french toast time! #SmellsLikeCinnamonInHere @MoreauSue https://t.co/RzVsPqvIfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting in becoming a rep for your class or college? Interested in running for an Exec position?!?  YOU!  Who?… https://t.co/H91esH3Smk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You’re an idiot but this is still shit, agreed. Damaging and horrible rhetoric.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to hear 'NANA!!!' when I walk through the door to see these sweet faces tomorrow ❤️❤️ #twinsiesturn3 https://t.co/KGaGlsIJ6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be an age limit   like there is an age limit to Vote https://t.co/A5om4M4KuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @garthbrooks brings out the ultimate queen aka @trishayearwood to sing....😍👸🏼❤️🤠🎶 they are so perfect.… https://t.co/GkpXR1QruA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyelance I would love to!!! Tbh i know nothing about stuff to do in austin despite living so close]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I first started fashion school there were girls in leather shorts and I thought to myself, I could never be co… https://t.co/v4YaGnJuqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JABell27 @NationalHistory I used to judge at all levels.  It was such a wonderful experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaFibonacci @AndrewScheer Health care is much more available there than it was prior]]></document><document><![CDATA[soy la única que tiene una cajita con todas las cartitas y detallitos que me han dado!!?!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entomologist in the Physics house! No, I did not accidentally answer one of those predatory meeting invites. I’m ac… https://t.co/3WKzPUQflW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have great peace in not having to worry about student safety today. These roads are downright deceptive this morning. #blackice #KCwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at White River, Ontario in White River, Ontario https://t.co/BYBml3kZvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimCanty1 @ImLiveRT @KrakenRum Followed back! I'll definitely check you out next time you're live!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She didn’t get to eat! He made her pour her heart out and then didn’t feed her. I hope that limo driver takes her… https://t.co/2THuwbzTPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissHannahMelia @Michaelj2805 There have been lots of times in love scenes in romance novels (gay and straight) where "tummy" is used.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Circles! White satin matte glaze with black and blue brushwork, fired in gas reduction to cone 10. @ Greenville, So… https://t.co/LDfeQNBTBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve done nothing today and I can’t stand it. I need outside or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaroJewels Tagging @GailMcHam and  @linds0120 to #win this gorgeous Heart Padlock Pendant #giveaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomaskenn is sharing the history of #SB168 and the detrimental impact it will have on our state. Tune in to the pr… https://t.co/QF1mgR3DRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from my teacher friend  @MrsArciaga   to post 7 covers of books I love — no explanations,… https://t.co/QAnDok9zoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @CtCathCorner Then why are the still investigating Russian collusion? The Democratic Party just invit… https://t.co/sTFzehOcQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok update, the 6 people I see on a daily basis know I want a dog... we discussed breeds...things are progressing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrissyBritchez ❤️❤️❤️❤️I understand. I lost my mother too. It is so hard to walk this life without her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This discovery of a 30-year-old Apple IIe computer is a real blast from the past  https://t.co/MvRPtYnCJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I learned from my yearly #tradition of attending the @LiveKellyRyan #AfterOscar show 1) Who would have guessed… https://t.co/XZs2ijJ7ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_karilis_ @LarissaNY_J I wish I had like a b cup dude I’m tired of mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hump day! (@ Tarc Bus 25 East Boumd in Louisville, KY) https://t.co/pEDbGpkXJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok goodbye y’all i am going to drunk cry at some animated shorts n be back later w my oscar pool thread i luv the spirit awards good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fashion nova is trash. I understand some of y’all want celeb looks for a lower price but they are ripping off desig… https://t.co/EukoXjaIHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm touring the e-sports training facility. Their team is #2 in Canada. https://t.co/XsbC57gC0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaMarcille I’m a big fan of you on @bravorhoa and I felt so much for you with the loss of your grandfather. 💕 But… https://t.co/DfF0nZK74y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raque_rocky @Yael_Averbuch Thank you @Yael_Averbuch  for posting this and @raque_rocky for retweeting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2napier2 @USWNT It’s Jill’s world and we’re all just living in it. https://t.co/GjC7ggZA4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe you still have the audacity to talk down on my name... after everything I did for you. 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@autenticslav @ElTio_Moy @alexacb999 @anmc17_ @Aylinmichel99 Ecuaciones diferenciales chingonas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s 7 mile run took me on a nice loop around Roosevelt Island. #morningrunviews ☀️ https://t.co/fO2bIYNPIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN This woman needs to resign. She’s stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Remember 56 -60% voters are already against the wall , then every Contituionalist, eve… https://t.co/aFCdQSVPOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a girl's day out! #makeover #Iove 💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜 https://t.co/rnHL3AGTAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owillis I honesty believe some white people will always vote for hurting others but the don't understand what goes around comes around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CostasMandylor saw a terrific film tonight.. “Cliffs of Freedom”!  Costas, you were  FABULOUS in it!! Also lucky e… https://t.co/qKQF7ntjpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of Birthdays to my beautiful Mom.  I am so blessed to be her Daughter.  I Love You, Momma.🎂🎉🎊❤️ https://t.co/mwUtvx0cUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alf_y_jackson @jentrification @BrianBrackeen @iRunWithLula @deongordon I told you not to go there 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[📸 #BehindTheScenes:  On Set at the Black History Month celebration at @AndersenCorp!  Emmy award winner, T. Mychael… https://t.co/0HnVHlI12J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Children’s Mercy CB Rehabilitation Clinic in Overland Park, KS https://t.co/qIbVm4fF74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaRHelm @beroe We should chat to see if I can help point you toward stuff. Depending on what you’re looking f… https://t.co/AhJ5pDslmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been searching for a song for over a month now and i finally found it today. i’m overwhelmingly happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah! That quicky was like an hour and twenty minutes long!  ...The real reason day light savings was invented...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh @TrueFactsStated You were one of the pedophiles along with #Epstein  and #Trump weren't you? Yes, yes, y… https://t.co/fkKmx9kn9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who thinks that having a “National Women’s Day” is a little bit backwards when you want equality?… https://t.co/hEAhTgJEzy]]></document></documents></author>