<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MimiWaltersCA I am sure you don't care how much you screwed everyone!!! You got to help your rich buddies out! I a… https://t.co/EjrG3DjwRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚦🏮Street   #bayarea #eastbay #film #california #movies #disney #sales #love #fun #art #technology #restaurant… https://t.co/p8vP9xIkAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citizentvkenya This is one of the most incompetent Cabinet Secretary we got. His work mostly done by Dr Fred.]]></document><document><![CDATA['Canada is going to the moon,’ Trudeau says in major space program announcement  https://t.co/atwgULPsaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody need a contractor? These guys might be available!! 😳😱🔨🔨 https://t.co/9ZfRoeOOn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awonderland I’m flying to Texas to see @DaniCal1f0rn1a as my form of self care 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbucy57 @DanCrenshawTX But one without strings which begs the question of who controls who ... no worries Bernie w… https://t.co/xg6IGWMNfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #snowing in #vegas ! #mental #mental #chickenoriental @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/bl15rKpQxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Political bias is destroying people's faith in journalism https://t.co/iajKwgG1NY via @nypost. Brave woman.  For he… https://t.co/hrYxBgsPAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start listing the fist 500 items this week. https://t.co/MFuTGhn1HB #urbanpicker #helferstay… https://t.co/9u5sPuD41h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great letter by the kid and I love the @Qantas CEO’s serious and witty response.  I am sure that it will further mo… https://t.co/w0bk44tDSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[George David Banks, President Trump's former international energy adviser, is skeptical of that approach. "Any kind… https://t.co/OFRYvUNYNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTLug0 || 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The… https://t.co/EywdqFgUfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when the only ppl who ask to hangout on tinder are men and not girls https://t.co/aB0G8UO0fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbendery THANK YOU KNUCKLE DRAGGING DEPLORABLE TRUMP SUPPORTERS! https://t.co/gLx0j6uRbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skydart Buy a gift for a close friend that will remind you two of a positive life experience. Then you get to reli… https://t.co/EtG45VixLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston's next 5 games (4 on the road, 1 at home) are all against teams that would currently be in the playoffs: at… https://t.co/upEsdNVJat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiehannigan Yeah...I know better than than.  Being bald and extremely pale, I tend to get seated in the front ro… https://t.co/O9xhG0FD9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish @DsOchoa Pirro is in pictures with the massage parlors owner at Mar a lago.the one who is involved with sex trafficking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean_Callahan @RobinWashut It all starts with taking a non contact sport and allowing big men to push shove and ba… https://t.co/F5wsFkbt6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Apple Music playlist I've been curating has over 700 songs and is titled "Radio Station Seeds". These are s… https://t.co/TaRDsavMfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishrygirl @realDonaldTrump @GOP The king of debt will explain it away by reminding everyone of how much their 40… https://t.co/cpCFNZ0HnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDoctorHannah He’s the former (retired) chief of radiation studies from the CDC so he definitely knows what he’s talking about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said it taste just like a pineapple like she was eating a whole ass strawberry 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arq31 @AnthonyFlores60 Tenemos que seguir la PRECION y lograr que Maduro salga del poder y por fin Venezuela recob… https://t.co/n4Kz4mXUiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a property deal been in the finally for 7 months. In this little County called Beckham. City of Sayre. Looki… https://t.co/9ruCmWh4Dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's shoot was a different kind of shoot. I'm exploring and posting some of the snapshots. @ Phoenix Public Mark… https://t.co/wct1huzU9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Bibens is an American fucking hero. In his next life he’ll be reincarnated as a Bald Eagle. 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Democrat that’s not stupid.  Watch the MSM destroy her.  US needs to stay out of Venezuela, says Tulsi Gabbard -… https://t.co/wHDvmXX3yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro I promised I would start listening to the Sunday Special when @AOC grows up and comes on! #SundaySpecial @realDailyWire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislaxamana I really hope your “Chillax” thing is a joke. But if not, I hope you know how horrible it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK- Now I get it. Judge Ellis just sentenced Managort to 4 years in the NY District and next Wednesday Judge Jackso… https://t.co/CiN17DYCfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be back in Lodi in a couple weeks. See all my favorite people 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatMcAfeeShow @ESPNNFL @PatMcAfeeShow on the mcafee mobile would be ELECTRIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_Burkman jackie-youre tweeting duplicates again...thats no way to lessen the zipper comments!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The State Highway Patrol said this silver SUV slid on ice, went off the road, hit a guard rail and flipped on its s… https://t.co/1AsGDiAFPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I had a short day at work, due to rain. I came home to #paint and #hobby, but it was too dark and gloomy… https://t.co/oEfurwL4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defense was good in first quarter which led to some easy transition buckets. Also getting into the bonus with 2:16 left was key. #Flyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jack in the Box - @jackbox in Stanton, CA https://t.co/2wwYxu3h4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris These poor kids are so brainwashed.....Feinstein is a total idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson @JessieJaneDuff In case you missed my tweet - during WWII she was called Tokyo Rose 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhondaTheCat @MKGenest @PetraMcCarron2 You certainly do and I very much enjoy reading your posts. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBrookhiser Long was a very great worry.  We have had a few city-wide and regional Mussolinis of our own.  Haven't… https://t.co/yubUu82K9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I let someone in front of me while driving and they don’t give me a thank you wave https://t.co/lPbUsBiCLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@YalitzaAparicio solo por estar nóminada para un #Oscars2019 es una mexicana muy cabrona.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal @tazcj @USMC This becoming more prevalent in the Marines. Notice how many join right radical so called pa… https://t.co/j2Hc6Yaz0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be seeing my idol @NICKIMINAJ this Thursday ! God is truly real ! 😩❤️🦄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great spending time in the tv studio with my friend Addy Jolly from NFM Lending. Sharing our Journey to Success. Ho… https://t.co/mOKXXSJymz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday - Drinking a Voodoo Ranger Liquid Paradise IPA by @newbelgium @ Intouch Solutions  — https://t.co/S2beonOtMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Throwin’ Shade specialty cocktail is perfect for your #ThursdayTreat! It features a decadent blend of Gin, Texa… https://t.co/JdGcXj0PAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WorldBookDay on March 7th is a perfect opportunity to celebrate characters of color, says children’s author… https://t.co/y7dIurU8TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now offering royalty collection coaching services!! &lt;3 https://t.co/n8Js6XHWUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNVenusiii @MahgdalenRose Speech in ya center since 1791 Free press came 21 years before. Its in ya schools, not o… https://t.co/PoJX7lyFbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenShattuck @tanialittle I use mine for steak, roasted chicken, Mac and cheese, fried chicken, pizza, chilli, p… https://t.co/SYarWc3Wi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @JieMant2 Time for justice is nigh. https://t.co/10yVIuFHxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Speaking of #FakeNews......... "Are the Words ‘Fake News’ a Problem?" - https://t.co/NkOQiSqfqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetoasis_ @creolegyaal @OGFlash https://t.co/e6UFs9z4CT https://t.co/JMlEUn2wE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrisByLowes - We need to have a little chat about the message you just sent out on your app.  Some of the devices… https://t.co/Pd33Nykqtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmirAminiMD Sitting Congresspeople can/should/need to be primaried. If they want to save their money for the GE ho… https://t.co/LccRl2HbrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NianticHelp is it possible that we can get lists of what pokemon are currently in what eggs? It would make it a lo… https://t.co/uqC02HVufy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinkrease @mims We’re in a race to the bottom where companies cut costs, people have less money to spend, and th… https://t.co/yZOEtuZR4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Busch40723402 @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/9UcfS5kCOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran across these dudes @Jordandecatur10  @jdecatur07 back when they were in 3rd grade, fast forward to today and… https://t.co/MtUkd8j1m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for this madness this year?!?!?! #robzombie #robfennphotography https://t.co/8kIH9YmGPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems counterintuitive given his stats (if not his W-L record) are impressive...but I’m wondering if Magic made… https://t.co/0U2cN64Upc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your bfs son calls you and ask you to go over ☺️ can’t tell him no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayplaysthings @Polygon @HND_Overwatch Love you Jay https://t.co/c2Kei2xt4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAshenLuca I am a sucker for BBQ year round...steaks. https://t.co/GZ4meHSjlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[But y’all going to record the deer and grill him for clout instead of help get to frozen snow off his head 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@el___camino @KenJac I was ready to commit a felony the day they reduced the serving amount from 3 to 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenAffleck confirming that officially his not batman anymore makes me sad.  Fuck you @WarnerBrosEnt for messing everything up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmgentry seems to depend a lot on what Council allows them to do. Not sure what leverage Council even has over the… https://t.co/hSMgHoM29y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My world is pink, #pink #pinkart #myworldispink #worldpink #drawingportrait #drawing #drawingpink #art #arte… https://t.co/WEHivVz5zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cigar_General Had no idea the level of corruption. Had heard from many but dismissed much of it as hyperbole. Then… https://t.co/h2cHU1ruPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigfatsurprise Look how Big Food has changed — twisted— that word. It used to mean something like “containing vege… https://t.co/7tfxBKjqoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/LcJEl0Xvqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidKlion I joke about this very subject frequently and induce panic often]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grannyanon1969 @ehgreenie @TexasDeplorabl4 @galacticaactual @Carolyncorneli8 @OLDFLACO @cindy_nurse @EinsteinMaga… https://t.co/7r78EwmBta]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you trending for me is getting normal! 🔥 https://t.co/YTOev3NwgZ  #SamsungGalaxyS10 #SamsungUnpacked #mkbhd… https://t.co/7Edq6R6qbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh good. I’m waking up in the dark for work. Again. 😖😑#DaylightSavingsTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve listened to “a lot” by 21 and J. Cole about 100 times and i just now heard in coles verse that he talks about fultz and his shot 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDelahunty1 @AOC That’s today’s breed of politician! What ever it takes to buy votes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanCaro27 @Battlefield Everything is free now since people complained about DLCs.. now everyone has to wait for updates and new modes 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[One reason-- 5 G leadership --  why South Korea is well-positioned fo the future:  https://t.co/JLvTqT5snr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never thought I was a person who suffered from depression but as of late I’m noticing a lot of signs that I’ve… https://t.co/uO5maqXmS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariahsmom @WillyAthletics @Graham_Couch @hornetgrappler @willysection Good luck to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never delete a family members voicemail message because you never know when you won’t hear their voice again...👼🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[As they should. They also take an oath, which hopefully means something to them although it doesn’t to the Democrat… https://t.co/X1kTrEU69m]]></document><document><![CDATA[The FAM. #losbalcones #truecooks #cheflife #chef #chefhatco #kitchen #kitchencrew #secondfamily #workhardplayhard… https://t.co/yfv9x2Fjvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nishmanweather @Eweather13 Max gusts almost always overdone on models, but it's gonna be ripping windy tomorrow.… https://t.co/cKrAh72K2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth is we should have had this like 10 years ago. But still let's make it happen. Alternative energy from Cal… https://t.co/4XwvqVXQuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m closing in on 30. I’ve never had a girlfriend. I’m weirdly proud of that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainMabel @philsquidgharri You’re right. There are plenty of haters of white men out there. I’m just trying to… https://t.co/J3q8m2thSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gibson City-Melvin-Sibley is bound for the state tournament in Peoria after a 52-37 Class 2A super-sectional victor… https://t.co/1UmL9K7TNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massage parlors in Florida? So Hugh Freeze was just trying to get a Pats job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gaither4IL @politico his 2020 campaign , so far, has shown they have all learned a considerable amt. from 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BangaChaseDange @NBA @Hawks @ATLHawks @TheTraeYoung A great game. Hawks gonna be good in a couple years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealitySteve MAP-OUT  INFRA-RED  scanning     AnnuiTTiunnA          AmericA               🇺🇸 .....................… https://t.co/DLubhDRpYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My colleagues surprised me at work few minutes before our meeting @seattlecentral Student Leadership. Ricardo and I… https://t.co/zcb5LWzYfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Pharmacy Technician - Target Store" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these… https://t.co/IgqHLSeLBm]]></document></documents></author>