<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You need to be green-warranted. #insane #mentallyderanged The #gop leadership is failing this nati… https://t.co/GFqdpFE9el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRowan15 @MarkDice @PleaseNoStupid I used to smoke pot in college and listen to snopes.😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures from Am-Po's win over Allen. Lady Panthers now look to avenge a regional tournament loss to Konawa tomorro… https://t.co/ZZwJ1DYrHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me Barney Stinson because I’m the king of laser tag https://t.co/7Pgayu9Pui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullyPoseable @MJGIV79 @ItsANewDayYes @Target @HOVAAA @metsandnesfan @BillMiekina @FScopers @RepackAttack @Mattel… https://t.co/kK0UDmo4Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enough212 @LelenaPeacock @Mary86802059 I don’t blame you. I had similar thoughts until severe pain made me call an… https://t.co/tNSSLnGmU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gymnasium - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) - @bmccathletics in New York, NY https://t.co/N7WaKjJXfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[New tele deluxe neck for the #jazzcaster. Love the fat 70s headstock!  #telecaster #jazzmaster #hybrid warmothguita… https://t.co/Y2skQU3Cld]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got home from my workout, and Jas is in bed with her coffee watching the Jordyn Woods interview like primetime television 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DCEASED #1 out May 1st. Cover alone makes it a go get on #NCBD @DCComics I love you lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@achristineee_ I didn’t think my other friends would take it seriously because people should know he would never say that]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 Game Block finished 80 over Avg. 213  The Last Game Really hurt me https://t.co/YT93AWKK7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[At work. (@ Hilton Long Beach &amp; Executive Meeting Center in Long Beach, CA) https://t.co/DfxsX8uE55]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in: Former under-the-radar Colorado governor, not known for decisiveness on high-visibility issues, annou… https://t.co/ZR1knkeDn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @garryhamm1 @BreitbartNews ….like he needed to concede that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rljunior007 I am a South American Indian of Inca decendance, adopted by a Puerto Rican family and living in Boston… https://t.co/O3Ik4odfur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyBaggYo I hope we collabed on a masterpiece with a Fire beat behind us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidMajorMatt Walton is entertaining, Dakich should only get excited to get a NIT sweet 16 call.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally had oysters, scallops and lobster bisque soup.🤤🤤 I’ve been missing out #BucketList✔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rough and stuff with yo Afro puff @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/1gqQcUlktb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoooPe @RCTVenlinea Es falso, eso fué desmentido por Beatriz Becerra..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce @DickieV @BeverlyWilshire @chancetherapper I was thinking “Beverly” or maybe “Bev”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marigarme @PrensaGoBol @NicolasMaduro @DrodriguezVen @dcabellor Iba en comisión a instalar un equipo de comunicaci… https://t.co/mtPwFrCsyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pumped for this week! @jody_delicato @XKerrigan @SWHR33 @HouleHeather https://t.co/pkUgq7MEZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adeyanjudeji He caused divisions in the church, mosque, families .Everywhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what you were tryna say here usually I can piece it together lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, traffic was surprisingly light today for a National Emergency.  #NationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss @joncoopertweets The depth of hypocrisy is unbelievable had this been done by a democrat they woul… https://t.co/6nVbbBfslG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT @MUTGuru @EA_KRAELO @Sgibs7 @MaddenBible @Jstein2469 @Schautz47 preying that dalvin cook gets a power… https://t.co/Z5WRFFKe0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[He made that.  . . “All streams flow into the sea, yet the sea is never full. To the place the streams come from, t… https://t.co/1dommp0xHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn to appreciate what you have, before time makes you appreciate what you had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my grades are “so bad” that my mom deadass made me make a schedule of the month w all my schoolwork, my work, who i… https://t.co/lrQr98Rwri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theheatherhogan He’s really looking out for the fairer sex there, and shouldn’t he be commended for that? #sarcasm #PleaseDontHurtMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acousticnewsuk #Wales #Music #Bluegrass 🎸🎼 CLINCH MOUNTAIN MEDLEY at INTERNAL FIRE MUSEUM OF POWER. A tribute.  An… https://t.co/Gvd4HEty7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Salt1estGaming Totally agree. Have it on UHD and  watched it 3x already after the theater. Keep finding little things I missed previously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfonsocuaron recibe mi felicitación, Mx es un país con grandes historias y personajes, que materia tienes para de… https://t.co/3M8PkMpT1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miguel_Pizarro @cocasalazar @diegoscharifker Mi pana @Miguel_Pizarro estas poniendo la cagada!!! Lula dejo robar y… https://t.co/DFVbVTsytA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisfitsTamara @RealWraith182 Gal Gadot is 5'10 so I'm guessing 5'11 in shoes? Hell, maybe 6 feet. She and Cavill c… https://t.co/rsTV77G9H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayo_400 Appreciate Bro!!  I’ll miss the fellas but Ill be around. Keep grinding!! Hope to see you at that next level balling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Datruecdub Switch Juwan Morgan and Haarms and I would have been jumping up and down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SFO-PHX never tire of the desert . . #windowseat #worklife #newproject #phx #wildlandscapes #desertlandscape… https://t.co/HRRFhfZ8rU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftOfMainSt @cspanwj You’ll change your mind if the socialists take over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Met That stupid pop up to the pitchers mound killed Ike. Was never the same after the injury.]]></document><document><![CDATA[with every Philly sports thing thats good, something bad happens to the Cowboys. i love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiestaKey Dude!  Dump her quickly and delete her number!!!  Find a Latina! 🤔🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheetahBronze Oh really? I remember that song from way back...   More importantly, it kinda reminds me of us havin… https://t.co/DhBZRlY45T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acwhit @AshleyUnzicker PAPA: You like cheese Taddy?  TODD: Yes sir!  PAPA: Eat this. It’s Pah-mesan.   ASHLEY: Pop… https://t.co/5FUBoCJ45J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AutomationPanda @pycascades The importance of mentors/experienced folks to newbies. Just an idea that I thought ab… https://t.co/jtOY9DlIk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sramji Hey Sam, you coming to LFLS next week? Hope you and family are well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @thunderrosa22, @sammyguevara will be at @WithoutACauseWA in a couple weeks. I plan to wear your shirt to this… https://t.co/tSQCKYVJ7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because college sports fans regularly say good things about players on other teams 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @Sherman101Tommy If Obama had a son, is this what he would look like?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow @peteholmes really enjoyed this series. Made me wish I had worked harder at stand up. Well done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where the hell has @wingoz been since his Wild Super Bowl Rant @GolicAndWingo  👍👍🤔🎙️🎙️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepFreiberg @MichaelFreiberg Dude, he's a Commonwealth Games gold medalist! So in America, you're more famous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC “See spot run”  “Jack and Jill went up the hill” just to name a couple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington, who'd been facing up and attacking and scoring at will, settled for a jumper with a chance to go up nin… https://t.co/EvTuEPv8pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always loved the player interaction with fans postgame at the IIHF WC. It was a great connect and showing of respec… https://t.co/S2c104sqP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god Mexico controls our #NationalEmergency fund to pay for Trump’s unnecessary, racist wall. I will give Trum… https://t.co/WOEiUOQq94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not cool @SouthwestAir to cancel my flight 2 HOURS before takeoff and have no alternatives. And what’s the point of… https://t.co/NJ3NWsL3RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwestTarHeels Who's Elon Musk. Please answer in a form of a question plz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisWilliams @TonyTodd54 Oh I thought that movie was so dumb but I was trying to figure out why they call him cand… https://t.co/9TQW0mk7L4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKellyPxP @NCAA Reviewing the mistakes… good. Reviewing “OMG, we might possibly have missed something”… less good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarStecker ok, if you like superhero shows, The Flash, SuperGirl, Arrow, are good. Full house and fuller house… https://t.co/RBAwSQUPVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[He could go on Maddow like the others. But why do that when you got a cheerleader to talk with at 8? Chris Hayes to… https://t.co/YsEz8gdO2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let me get this straight. California was literally on fire and trump suggested they rake the leaves. But now he… https://t.co/HIZgXyFAYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've had six lead changes in third quarter. Elkins currently back on top, 36-34, with 1:32 left in the quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue got does your entire system go down? How do you not run a redundant backup on a remote server? #delay #delay #delay #Delays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Torres_Juaan13 @E19tuzo I mean if I go to a restaurant to literally just pick it up then no I’m not going to give any 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgarwright hey Edgar, I know it’s unlikely, but if you see this, medical bills from stage 3 Colon Cancer suck. A… https://t.co/JRpTmaVYyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jothebeast31 Well, turning himself into a Denver omelette on I-235 isn’t going to help that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeredJustus That's it? I thought you were coming strong with something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi  And he does this without much notice from MSM? Why; because they have chosen to normalize him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbathurst @Kugey @YogaArmy @annemariayritys @ThalaBeratung @terrinakamura @dress2win @BiggiPommerin @ionacrv… https://t.co/qHXHsRsI9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Write Drunk Edit Sober by Fat Orange Cat Brew Co. @ Edwards Lane Brewhouse — https://t.co/PaidBNeVEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liz_kuhlkin24 Norm has more heart in his little body than the entire tour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida no se puede pasar como el color de mi auto en BLANCO.... #acciona # ASSHOLE 😂 . . . #djentrepreneur… https://t.co/N1yZgA7lMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ight i was 1/3..... BUT my boy @hamidoudiallo WENT SUPERMAN MODE ON EM🤩🏆 #DunkContest @okcthunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Cecelia T. for placing 3rd in the Junior girls division at the district archery tournament this past we… https://t.co/sfwDlWWcDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#girlswithgoggles #Grantyourselfafuture #GrantCareer https://t.co/O2pe4YDWM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clydesconnect @DON_NO_BUENO @corbydavidson @JonWLawson @SportsSturm We are all monkeys homeboy  Some of us are jus… https://t.co/Ir4BTPmC3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Bennett scores for Biondi and its down to 5, 30-25 Mlk https://t.co/vRnJGcpYJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Edward's Sean Seefeldt wins 5-3 (SV) over Elyria's Peyton Fenton to win the 106 sectional title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.........we are not in Bavaria! We’re in Leavenworth, Washington. Fun!! @ Leavenworth, Washington https://t.co/TvPdmXzv7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah. I do this all the time. Even when I'm trying really hard not to.... #laughter #lol #smirk #merry https://t.co/uRhN5YzYU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog @maddow Such BS.  If you had even tried to find out what Hillary was going, you MIGHT have credibility… https://t.co/dMcNshI7vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What has she done for the city of Houston for them to give her a day lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWDanvers @The_Wotch @Foenix I think it’s pretty clear for all intensive purposes she is their version of the char… https://t.co/yP9XiRvgC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terk1 @GOPChairwoman @GOP @realDonaldTrump How about we let them wait in Mexico until their court date]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannywood Hope you have a great workout in the gym getting Swolen, Jacked &amp; Ripped]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpetrie8 Spot on... just pass around the 3pt line until we gotta shoot a contested jumper 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demonrats, only way you’ll get my guns is, well, you won’t like the outcome!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi China just approved Donald Trump-branded spas, escort services and massage parlours https://t.co/d90cncY6Ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just chatted with Charman Smith today. She has been freed and is safe in Istanbul. She will be back in Canada soon… https://t.co/X1hVorO9lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Royals can swing it...another 2 run HR in 6th. Devils need a rally, down 9-5 in bottom 6th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First, what is it. #securitization is a financial deal. Find someone to lend a huge amount of $$$ to buy the coal p… https://t.co/VPv7Ov7OSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve been perplexed by some of the photos on @BrianIsBeering‘s TL, take a listen to @goodbeerhunting podcast E… https://t.co/7G5SCSfT7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bomar67944074 Prove it! Vlog the whole walk and I’ll believe you. Until then, #FlatEarth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I’m late to the game, but I’ve learned the best way to communicate with my 13 year-old nephew is through @Snapchat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dearscotland @NotTheFakeWags @LeeMNichols @shawncollins @SoccerIsASport @TheWagnerWire @TheSmashSimmons @philwest… https://t.co/gprSfYfIm6]]></document></documents></author>