<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@theintercept Are you seriously campaigning for the ISIS bride Trojan horse mission?]]></document><document><![CDATA['Give it up!': 69-year-old woman attacked, robbed at her front door (VIDEO): https://t.co/ckuNMP9TGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triuxmph @thevelvetindiaa DonРђЎt forget that OprahРђЎs true goal in life is to be a movie star.]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюIРђЎm from PeruРђЮ РђюIРђЎm from EcuadorРђЮ Рђюoh so you both must know each other hahaРђЮ fuck no babyyyyyy   someone come getРђд https://t.co/7GNqmdXcRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Necesito el Рђюcon el te duele el coraz├│n, y conmigo te duelen los pies Рђю de mi vida]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys are really really tough.  Best of luck the rest of the way!! ­Ъњф­ЪЈй]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish I had the weather that everyone in the valley has instead of snow and-7 wind chills­Ъўц­Ъўц]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic @qjurecic Great article... You nailed it... Elijah was both merciful and graceful.. in a sad and complРђд https://t.co/oLazisRoVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In elementary school i rewrote the script in my own words for the movie Volcano (1997) and held auditions during reРђд https://t.co/nVxvZ2J33j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just hollereddddddd Nick ranked his Jumanji co stars and Kevin Hart is dead last... https://t.co/0V7g30Hp4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anoche vimos la primera parte del documental #LeavingNeverland por #HBO y la verdad nos sacudeo bastante. Su lenguaРђд https://t.co/91v9ba2iuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just gave Parker a cold shrimp and he about puked and now he wonРђЎt speak to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puffdaddyangel @saraeyajamai_ Me to but it got me cuz the whole basis of it is trifling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream I was dating Buffalo Bill and he kept accidentally trying to kill me, so I win the Nightmare-Off this round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wreckingkrew44 @Hsquad99 @RonMFlores @trigonis30 Yeah I noticed that too Ed ... I was like uh oh Pop Pop ainРђЎt plaРђд https://t.co/ixM6UPT2rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[i pray for this most recent one cause his ex ainРђЎt gonna turn into me just cause youРђЎre going back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetronelliMedia @hocejake Morgan who needs a boyfriend? You and I can recreate this tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beekaytulsa @crestreponazar I know of a department who didnРђЎt really have any idea about what to do with their curРђд https://t.co/zNuFX4cQcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMAGASteve @SidneyPowell1 The worst is yet to come. Like "London-istan." #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[ItРђЎs almost 3AM and I spammed Gio with videos of me doing my nighttime skincare routine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kekav23 @MarCuzz90 @Esai_Ponce I might work this Saturday. IРђЎm down if I donРђЎt go to work ­ЪњЂ­ЪЈ╗РђЇРЎђ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryUpdatesAcc Jesus fuck why NO UGH NO NO NO https://t.co/e39ZDC8qXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nonna with her loves #pandababyfi #elifoxprince @ Bellmawr, New Jersey https://t.co/4JNAGMDAkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #French75 @DALYNNCosmetics #eyeshadow palette AVAILABLE NOW!!! Grab our newest MUST-HAVE 9-Color palette!!! HerРђд https://t.co/XQCLvQEyhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_crownxroyal White ppl couldnРђЎt ride before right? DidnРђЎt something change in the last few years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Jim Jordan is the kangaroo court joke isn't time for him to be voted out soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally done studying for the night­Ъўг letРђЎs hope it pays off! It might still be 4.0 szn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainbraintrivia @Dame_Lillard I ventured out so you would know I was alive. ­ЪЎѕ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerriIrwin  Hey Terri check this guy out. I'm so impressed with this guy. He sticks right up for Steve.­Ъўђ      OzzyРђд https://t.co/PdSTjHErZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fythia @Loh Scroll through my twitter or hop over to my website or instagram to see my art! ItРђЎs all made with the laser~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beardfoundation @jessetyler If he needs a co-host, IРђЎm available ­ЪњЂ­ЪЈ╝РђЇРЎђ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a snow storm... finally! #snow #snowyweekend #snowsaturday @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/O2Croys7A2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @cindila2009 He already gave them everything they asked for. Yes Trump is a Russian agent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennifer_deG I just got up and ate 4am cheese like some kind of fiend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueyedproducer My grandmother was taken by schizophrenia. She was found at least a week after she died, partiallyРђд https://t.co/czLYs3PfrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tuesday #morning #carline #selfies garrettmorgan.pta @ Garrett Morgan Elementary https://t.co/mpxCHV8ZfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONI CLARK BOUTIQUE RETAIL THERAPY AT YOUR FINGERTIPS   #godfirst  #godsplan  #godswill  #torontofashioninfluencerРђд https://t.co/mKxvIl39M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you want to send me money so i can get my boobs yeeted from my body you can also dm me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up in the middle of the night to the answers my mind has been searching for! I've been worried about beginniРђд https://t.co/uiCKM5JEZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a beautiful Saturday night and IРђЎm perfectly content with staying in   ┬»\_(сЃё)_/┬»]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y U No Meme: Drawing.  So true, so true. *sniffle* https://t.co/1PJ46xNMji]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are still some fixer uppers available in the District you can flip.  Contact me for a list. #Deals #houseflipРђд https://t.co/MehGcoW1Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AoIhwMU8Ch and its ability to sync with Google Classroom is a game changer!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I'm telling you those Mickey Mouse and Bunny Boots are outdated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B said once that she got famous by talking shit. I love talking shit , so I felt that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alanjkaplan @trinkschiz @tedlieu @IvankaTrump Strange that they are all going to serve time for one thing or anothРђд https://t.co/dvzQU4921q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again, this is NO DEBATE . In n out is plain asf and canРђЎt touch whata AT ALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go game on. So far in the 2nd SFV west tournament I beat nagasiren (u.g.m.) and sevelei (g.m.) the savage necРђд https://t.co/GGCPSHvvWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao yРђЎall mad about losing greeters at Walmart? I canРђЎt stand them. Guess IРђЎm rude ­ЪўГ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judicial Watch Sues DOJ for Mueller Deputy Andrew Weissmann Text Messages Regarding Trump, Clinton - Judicial Watch https://t.co/OH6tFVu2yF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#reunion #Highschool #newtrier #bestfriends #forever incredible journey through life and #Carpenderia #californiaРђд https://t.co/wproRXEpPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i wasnРђЎt where i was at right now i would quit, this game / community simply isnРђЎt enjoyable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VMEA Orchestra Assessments 2019 in the books! Go NPS! @NPSchools @NAfME https://t.co/H8fCXDMK8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocked by the ending. Shocked that we went another week without the fence. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadresGeekster @elefantvanishes @RedTheTrucker IРђЎm just so sick of bullies!!!! ­Ъўњ­Ъўњ­Ъўњ­Ъўћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah , I have watched you your entire career and this shit with Leaving NV your actions show your not a journalisРђд https://t.co/P00goFKVG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLueCrew @abc13houston Good for him. ( I mean shame on him) seriously you should never lay a hand on someoneРђЎs eРђд https://t.co/BkNY04kHaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomidiezkith @gloriazuri @CamachoMamen @SyP_tve Eso me dijo la muchacha que creo el otro club que no es el oficialРђд https://t.co/wjxN1Pq9LF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllsportsTees @Wes_FGC @TomasAli14 @Ajepart1 @Just1StepTooFar @wbpictures Oh my god, can you guys please take me oРђд https://t.co/v7Lj6024fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah!!! They did it! ­ЪўЕ­ЪўЕ­ЪўЕ She was just too demanding and crazy for that ass! He was already booked on the 14thРђд https://t.co/MDSJCury6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NQL44FROxG  ATT Customer Service Number 1-833-554-5444: A Way to Deal with Your ProblemsРђд https://t.co/P0t5aE5yty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RodStryker Sir when they start doing it publicly it will be too late for them the fact some are hРђд https://t.co/D6v0ffy1YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're all a bunch of hypocrites, I guess they're all immoral then, because I guarantee you that most, if not allРђд https://t.co/niyLsbj0wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexkidman @harrytuckerr @charlietech @Chesterrod @tim_cook @HuaweiMobile Samsung didn't even do it first, as youРђд https://t.co/WOWTtccmc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrocr33p IРђЎm saving them until after I workout tonight but I will report back!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SheРђЎs so dumb for going over the fence and into the enclosure. Like wth did she expect to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brit Kirwan, Senate President Mike Miller, and House Speaker Michael Busch stand with Democratic lawmakers to ensurРђд https://t.co/DcwEXYZLkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had sent @MarineOf_God a funny valentines video from fb and he actually pulled through ­Ъўѓ­Ъўў love my husband https://t.co/9pzkWiICuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[ItРђЎs tomorrow from 9-4. We will be there with 8 flavours. #plain #raisin #pecan #saltedcaramel #cherryРђд https://t.co/YJODw1hse2]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's so much to say about Anet. They showed me my first MMO. They got me my first game partnership. They got meРђд https://t.co/atpiYR6UYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stranahan About as much as I trust his wife, so NO.Had POTUS kept his campaign promise that none of his children wРђд https://t.co/tdxS4Ip9Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alcohoilic Do I just stay out of it. ItРђЎs ruining way more than just their life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkpolaroidgrl Same here.  I bring an extra credit pair of panties downstairs just in case.  ­ЪцБ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night valentines concert.. fall asleep after 4 songs and go home at intermission ­Ъў┤­Ъўў­ЪњЋ #happyvalentinesРђд https://t.co/lqxUEHvDiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One massively delayed flight back to the US after 4 crazy weeks on the road for an exciting new project. Excited toРђд https://t.co/nFbewwpXTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our campaign is focused on listening, digging in on nuances of policy, transparency and accountability. This is howРђд https://t.co/k4A598oMAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[­ЪїИ To Bloom It May Concern ­ЪїИ  РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ I donРђЎt know what kind of week YOU HAD, but it canРђЎt be as bad asРђд https://t.co/q296mubsCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But what your missing is that fact that you did not say Kim ordered the torture!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!Рђд https://t.co/BwWd7TKExQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: never pull a 14 hour shift. A mental breakdown is bound to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterixxx @LexManos THIS! I also give the suggestions for things they can do such as start a lemonade stand, sellРђд https://t.co/mYWgswAh4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pthorsett IРђЎve seen students take it Into consideration when evaluating their compensation but most usually go witРђд https://t.co/M33rHdkfFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This picture was taken in the daytime a few days ago and it's the Sun..... We need to fight for the Sun]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a serious note.... IРђЎm wanting to get some more ink done, itРђЎs been awhile and a lots happened. If you know anyoРђд https://t.co/3ENgcdNUPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy's slipper us a good pillow #heistootiredtoplay @ Goldsboro, North Carolina https://t.co/taELtnyjIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabellablanc @tweetmommybop My sister has a cat named Killary. She is amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestonBergmann @ChallengeMTV @johnnybananas Okay...not sure what this means. I think my life is getting in the wayРђд https://t.co/mCHmFlnyD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my bby daddy like come the fuck home already https://t.co/01W864lidi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChesterEnergy @energysmartohio I have a Volt (my second leased Volt) and am obsessed with it. Handles great, has gРђд https://t.co/sY3lGbIpr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking in Smyrna: We just saw two young children carried into the back of this ambulance. Resident who just walkeРђд https://t.co/VdSOyhhqb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[tbh i only cut half of my hair off bc i wanted all the dye to be cut off but alas.. there's still dye in it :))]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the Petition: Enough is enough. Impeachment hearings should begin NOW. Рђћ Petition by Power to Impeach PAC: https://t.co/ItID6QIJul]]></document><document><![CDATA[FEARLESS: Lacking fear  ­ЪњЃ­ЪЈЙHOPE­ЪњЃ­ЪЈЙ  РюеI AM WOMAN: Experiences of Black Womanhood in America is a developing work of poРђд https://t.co/2RIsbM2O6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawson_tayshaun @nicolebyer @anxiety_amber You shamed me to protect her. I am a fat woman who was giving her a comРђд https://t.co/O7KoGdGFlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YouРђЎll find any excuse for your failed meeting. The homework should have been done and details worРђд https://t.co/one5wOrNXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EgotasticFT I'm already a crazy supporter. Patreon, paid comments, and I think the Jar.  Okay, check this out on tРђд https://t.co/WbaRHoCtSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --Рђд https://t.co/bQpYNZlfLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good night for the Farmers and for #hlgrider00, #ParisJC, #dingers https://t.co/bPU8EK94lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton I am sure if YOU ask it, it will happen...not, you are irrelevant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Difference when you get accepted to come to something and they donРђЎt cover everything. You showing us all of this,Рђд https://t.co/TCZFKDcgJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want a nice little third shift job at like a hotel or something .]]></document></documents></author>