<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WhatRU4USA @Hightailbfmc @HouseGOP No We think not living in reality and making false claims against us is an atta… https://t.co/Cdk6HdHSvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Crew at @YachtleyCrew #longbeach #yachtrock #yachtleycrew @ Alex's Bar https://t.co/h8O8tC5Oek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckynum13 @Hill52063501Man @riordainn @thejtlewis @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Because our country was designed for… https://t.co/Y2zCaWvQpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I think Manafort should get used to the idea that he's going to die in prison and rightfully so.  On… https://t.co/qITPIExJzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except IF @POTUS LIED ABOUT HIRE AMERICA, #AmericaFirst. @kimguilfoyle @DonaldJTrumpJr make sure Trump keeps his pr… https://t.co/At3EY7eKl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically how I posted this a year ago and I find myself in the same spot 🙃 https://t.co/WmJN8DkIUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 They'll call it fake news.  They're totally brainwashed that nothing is his fault and he's a great gu… https://t.co/uFzMMvtHXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaY1legwondr @coloradogal12 @spacecowgyrl @Carib_Dawn @flybaby014563 @EmluvsSPNMarvel @DevilFaraAckles… https://t.co/NRglIUV8H3]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN Will our lawmakers take action and declare this POTUS a national security problem? After he gives Putin the nu… https://t.co/81QztGbRqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when the guy at CVS says they don't sell newspapers https://t.co/AXKfvyxT8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of my seven-day favorite books challenge. Though no explanation provided with the posts, I’d love to visit ab… https://t.co/Q2re9xmbMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vegan life has been good to me....mind, body, and spirit https://t.co/nmPri7xhuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting so excited for this show! We got well deserved awards going to some amazing and talented people plus a… https://t.co/ROgPYfr5Qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[WH Lies: False Transcript of Pence's Words in Munich Speech, Indicated Applause Where Pence Was Met by Dead Silence… https://t.co/oAnPUGIbTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former McCaskill aide heads to K Street https://t.co/doLqBNQ7PN via @politico  Congratulations &amp; welcome to my ASA colleagues!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMotivation #mondaythoughts  For my seniors,  Graduation is coming! Keep working hard, your future is so brig… https://t.co/nQXv3hrscY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell I to often get my hopes up and then have them dissolve in thin air. This man has stacked his deck with… https://t.co/prOFazn8pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Structurally, it’s good that buildings sway a bit in the wind— but I have never felt it this strong. Surface winds… https://t.co/GE9vw7sDwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope your Valentine’s Day is as stinky as me! #valentinesday #sallylongdog https://t.co/B9hlWMKumf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theREALninamac I’m kind of freaked out by how many people have this same dream!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Men’s basketball team needs support from our Hornet fans! Let’s pack the NEST tomorrow for our last playoff gam… https://t.co/1Y6h3qENjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins @TheDeanAmbrose It was a hell of a ride.  Will miss the Shield.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discover a new way to learn Armenian history, a bright example of #children co-creating smart solutions for… https://t.co/MsyIdZEPY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliesaaab Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao and and Caraval! @SGarberGirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to get my eat on and maybe a few cocktails,lol.....#blessedalways #dayoff #justme #feelinggood #blackgirlmagic… https://t.co/kNVAj7W6yG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marzipan_heart I think I’m more side eyeing the dramatic presentation then the actual sammich which can’t be bad because cheese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaGPaley Thank you for answering my question, Emma. So how do you know it happened if it wasn't you who did it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let you pick by @ELHAE has been on repeat for days. Trouble in Paraadise is a fire ass album.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddyschweppe As I was reading your tweet I was like “man same...” then I realized I’m also on Twitter/day dreamin… https://t.co/4uM6x3rUZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@attaboy365 Some people’s brains are wired wrong.Malignant Narcissism cannot be cured. Those are the worst ppl to h… https://t.co/HuSLvtXpcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @nbcsnl Atta boy! Some can laugh about themselves &amp; enjoy the moment...]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC Rants After WSJ Writer Says She Leads Young People ‘To Take Pride In Their Ignorance.’ She Ends Up Proving Thei… https://t.co/HkAv1VnKN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[uh just wondering when the one direction fan fiction i wrote a will be made into a movie????? the clock is ticking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else did this? Because I don’t care who you are, you don’t put America’s National Security at risk! Names, and… https://t.co/PVySy57MYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraSeals4 @TawnyTwelve @TheRealDMNGZ @thedebbiec @Soviet_Cola @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS… https://t.co/dfQZvdj60g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgarland This is how the Infiniti War Avengers gets saved, also. The Avenger left behind kicks ass. Bravo, Eric. https://t.co/AvCDCR1vkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya naciste mi Bau ❤️@mariobautista_ #23VueltasAlSolMarioBautista https://t.co/Xne96bw7Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏒GO💛KNIGHTS🖤GO #michellesellslasvegas #goldenknights #hockey #nhl #vgk #lasvegas #vegasgoldenknights #goknightsgo… https://t.co/0ABH5RaYXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blows my mind to think about where i was this time last year... I was miserable,in a toxic relationship, broke, ove… https://t.co/HsvHcBZKwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineBemis2 @Shapiro_WTHS @ScottLewisITC @khoggardGRT @teacherasleader @hayes_melisa @MaireCervenak @_on11… https://t.co/TtdsGgf2et]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duh #Republican #Senator did any of you have #aneurysm ? Going along with #Trumplicans is a #DeathSentence I don't… https://t.co/zNgSUYXh86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaldwellElemen YAY!  The class actually cheered when my tardy student showed up.  They really want to get an attendance reward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having lunch with the #WMLearn  STAR Program @SalineSchools, discussing people who are #VisuallyImpaired,… https://t.co/QHzLxcuh3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[We created a Matisse inspired cut out to represent joy this morning in Elementary devotions! #henrimatisse #joy… https://t.co/6yvH5KGf94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surely it would happen if you continue tweeting and promoting it . That's way we have to be here for  " them ".]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend/next week is going to be lit af ... turnpike on Saturday then Louisiana for Mardie gras 🤙🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home, on the couch with my baby in our pajamas. I love working for a Bank ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Over Everything merch available soon‼️  #danisworld #daniellehutchins #familyovereverything💯 #familygoals… https://t.co/X0xVIL5jr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temple Civic Theatre has a busy lineup of events set for this weekend, including a #5K race, a volunteer outreach e… https://t.co/pMZadbz855]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronNicolaides Well said Aaron 🙏 I believe failure is our best teacher and what you’ve learned from your mistakes… https://t.co/VXSoxssZ2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRaulFlores @CleoGKlein @PepeClavijoA @DRG2000 @YesiSLP @FannyLouSandova @GuaracuchaFB @CASTORFAVELO… https://t.co/7yfLI7pqN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news: No junk food in the house when I get snacky after work 👍💪 Bad news: No junk food in the house when I get snacky after work 👎😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next auto parts guy to act dramatically surprised that I am capable of changing my own break light is going to get punched in the face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunnerGirlRusso I saw that. 😳 I literally get queasy when I just watch stuff like this. I’m talking serious vertigo.😲🤢🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok conspiracy theory: influencers intentionally keep their merch/makeup lines in low stock when they go on sale so… https://t.co/zkreVglhtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone has my voodoo doll can u pls kiss her forehead and tell her everything will be okay 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9CxahqMt… https://t.co/OE6xdBjjem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just asked my waiter “hi, we’re both single and it’s the night before Valentine’s Day so do you think we could get… https://t.co/YNLpEYB750]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks   to @J_E_Allman and @havrillaamber and others for working with our future  engineers! https://t.co/y0Trp7IV45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahhann615 @pdprints @InboxDollars @lrhannaman Awesome!!! https://t.co/geSOOFfxN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bfs brother tells me, "I can't wait till you get your phone so I can take up all of your battery using the wireless charging." 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruke7777 @CfcGiza @DemekeTesfaye @abiyetk እባክህን ያልበላህን እትከክ። እኔን የጨነቀኝ የናትሽ ደም መቅረት አለ። ከ tplf (666) ወደ oalf (666)  መተላለፍን ነው ለውጥ የምትለው?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy having fun!!!! #school6magic#somuchfun# @jmcgahan31 @oceansidelaxmom @StromerTara https://t.co/E8SnjPmhpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShemekaMichelle About 2 years in Prison should teach him a lesson &amp; Deter others!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you today? Talk to me, share with me how you feel blessed or stressed?  . #butyoudontlooksick #Lupus… https://t.co/7ZgIearSqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl ...... love her !  Microdermabrasion facial with esthemax hydro jelly mask.  Microdermabrasion is a minim… https://t.co/nZOefX39ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Tommie volunteers spruce up pet cemetery where beloved dog is buried https://t.co/frae1xN84R via @cbs6 .@PaulCBS12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hillary broke new ground, and we will always be grateful. The next generation is stepping up now,… https://t.co/PRdHvY0Iaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Sorry...meant Ron Blagojevich IL.  Jesse Jackson Jr got got almost same amt time federal prison as Manafort… https://t.co/C129m8Ya7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlWithGossip @vgunvalson @RHOC_KellyDodd First of all, @vgunvalson said, “I heard that @RHOC_KellyDodd  was doin… https://t.co/SyggHM6deF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTheRedCarpet @AlaskaAir Fantasy seatmate on an #iflyalaska flight would of course be my movie star fantasy husba… https://t.co/JKudB5O9UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[After my staples come out tomorrow I need to look at getting a good haircut. As can be seen in these pictures, my n… https://t.co/MmmW0Sijs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicoohai So cute!!! ;w; would u commission similar art? just thought i'd ask &gt;~&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmhgolf @MCFCDamo @piersmorgan @AOC  Actually AOC’s recent anti-corruption address to the House Committee Hearing… https://t.co/sx66AhtplC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or has anyone else noticed the media is no longer calling Trumpie POTUS or Pres but instead Mr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_kamara6 Awe. I’m goin to bed early after two days out sickie. Up early.  Alvin, brother, Put some great music on… https://t.co/FY8mQiYy8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ekbaney example of a true friend = liz  example of a back stabbing hoe=rylee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @AliVelshi @PittCyber @whowhatwhy @ChrisDeluzio 5/ ... get away with this because, again, the Blue Ribb… https://t.co/IKYvUGa5sA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checkout https://t.co/5f9WtqtANH! https://t.co/0uH1vwniBd #KeepMeClub.com # SharingIsCaring # Discount]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBLong Today is premiere day!!! 💙💛💙💛💙 #hstreads https://t.co/1PyxvDyddE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this. My cousin just finished his residency as a doctor and is having a nice wedding in Savannah and I have… https://t.co/X27rx3uDSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people always tell me I look like Anne Frank? And they are so shameless about it too it’s wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone is continuously doing their job wrong, and you refuse to tell their boss, how TF do you think it’s going… https://t.co/f0AUQ2jxq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born in Queens, Made in Brooklyn #NYUTandonMade https://t.co/jV9IHB78TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @POETreeOTIC @POTUS I was with my kids &amp; husband  We were eating popcorn 😊 #MAGA #KAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annaaaatee @EmDGat Except for Brandy will suddenly sing on her voice at random spots - but other than that. It’s a… https://t.co/xDGlm7gVbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nata1yyy @Rgmedina93 I was like this too! If you can force yourself through season 1, the rest is absolutely amazing😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2004 my niece was sent by #UnitedNations to build a Plumpy'nut factory from scratch in Dar es Salaam, Tanzania.… https://t.co/CxjyX3LhIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures in the 25th year of marriage: realize it’s Valentine’s Day while watching news early morning. Turn to hu… https://t.co/iFQaHydbSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaelieee can we just marry cute baseball players who make lots of money while we do ministry already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlDirtyCrumpet Right Dirty!!!!!! &lt;3 Miss your face BTW 😘😘 We should Destiny it up soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 @TheDemocrats It's so sad and Drs have to dance around this all the time. I suspected my Drs had to… https://t.co/ggzV6mVcHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesLaf38 @JiCLajoie Je suis d’accord ! Deslo et Hudon aiderait plus l’équipe !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southwest did me so dirty canceling my flight at 3am. good thing I was awake to book a new one, lmfao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the meantime I’m 😡😤🤬  on many levels and for many different reasons. A brief answer is my tax payer dollars is g… https://t.co/c7ryfLm5AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @NAllirog @RickHough5 @ekoziol23 @AnnSton49504512 @RonaldLorenzen1 @America10355477 @M_Livius_Drusus… https://t.co/yWqeTfrBtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeliverAlpha @realPitBullDog @1of1nero @Stefanburns91 @CBSNews Interested in the probability stats on the likeliho… https://t.co/E0h3XLh2o5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it wouldn’t be such a colossal waste of money (like there hasn’t been enough wasted already) I’d like to see int… https://t.co/CI3KIUewOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The recklessness of infinite possibility” 48x48”, painting and collage on panel #botanicalseries title from… https://t.co/UL7tlyciQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayeimajosy2 this was so stressful like I was trying to get gold vip and HSHXJX]]></document></documents></author>