<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Gots to give a huge birthday shoutout to my awesome nephew Sky! You are growing up so fast and I am proud to see th… https://t.co/FfXiNDAAl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers! - Drinking a DDH Juicy Bits by @weldwerksbrewco at @revisionbrewing  — https://t.co/MKEY7gOssI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking out my contacts at the end of the day is equivalent to taking off high heels at the end of the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red, I loved that you used b*tch, but had no problem with fucking twat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mystic Moon Juice by @FatHeadsBeer/@barleybrowns at @101BeerKitchen — https://t.co/LUctyHPMNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like how your grey hair is coming in.  Thanks. I earned it all myself. 🙌 https://t.co/WtckwJ0nEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey look everyone. Look at what my propaganda channel created for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysteryman113 @DGSkilla23 @MeganHickeyCBS2 @cbschicago I want to be really clear I’m not offering conjecture or hy… https://t.co/kGB0xNKz6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sick new drawing #art #drawing #sketch #scifiart #fantasyart #psychedelic https://t.co/oImwyOGZSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate_the_Saint I see @ChicksInTheOff in your wheelhouse if you have Sirius]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold winter days makes you wanna just live it through. ❄️🌧 #best-views #mountains #winter @ Oro Valley, Arizona https://t.co/uhqgJ4AyOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNSotu @HurdOnTheHill @jaketapper @WillHurd Jake,  just because Democrats have different ideas like reparations,… https://t.co/Cv1vVWTY8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlpalacios1962 YES FOLLOWED @RealErinCruz A SOLID CANDIDATE..@realDonaldTrump SEND HER A SHOUT OUT &amp; OTHER… https://t.co/9R8OmVi8kB]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that the game is tied!! Fragale hits a sac fly and scores Ortiz! 2-2 in the 3rd!! #FiredUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBoringJustin @MikeAnderson979 Sorry to hear that, good luck to mike in his future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesackerson2 Both Fall 2017 and this article from 2016 are before the MCC updates though, no? Where is the Fall 2017 number from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[hozier is a poet and a mortal god please m'am let me buy a ticket off of you for a reasonable price]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se que el tema principal es la ayuda humanitaria- salida de Maduro y su combo! Pero también he tenido esta enorme p… https://t.co/D4dNHcJykA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone prove that @senatemajldr and most of the @GOP are not working for Putin?  I don't see why Mitch McConnel… https://t.co/1FWIkhNsjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm using my Christian Psychic abilities to help the United States FBI and the CIA. From Christian Psychic, Angel G… https://t.co/y4EyYmjfpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcACaputo I wouldn't want to be in this place in a hurricane it would kill you just tossing you and your possessions around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody who missed Kids See Ghosts live at Flog Gnaw missed the experience of a lifetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the folks don’t know, dilly bar actually invented in Morehead. All those involved with the creation of now pass… https://t.co/dn5LIi9ZUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man visiting his country killed without remorse by this man https://t.co/Kcue78zdiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMiller3039 Congratulations Ryan! You were always one of my favorites. And you will always be a Buffalo Sabre i… https://t.co/h2w2FhAGSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@endofanerajc @morganisawizard Wait...are either if you secretly behind the Burger King social media account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargieSay99 @charliekirk11 @gehrig38 And sue his ass until he has nothing!!POS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That juice wrld autograph go dumb!!! &amp; All Girls Are The Same!!! I was sleep on him bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[People at times seem to discount the opinions and impressions they leave on children.   I still remember a Rod Serl… https://t.co/eJVPvPypLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickySmessaert Good Morning. Some snow possible here today. I hope you have a pleasant Saturday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toedoroe Probably not but it’s an interesting idea considering his package and connection to Schwartz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Desperate times call for desperate measures. That’s what true leadership is all about. @RandPaul don’t be a coward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes- but the thaw is on. If you think this has a happy ending, you haven't been paying attention 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCM1956 @inittowinit007 @Unite4Truth @CCM1956 you're very welcome have a great day 🇺🇸🇺🇸🗽🗽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch Can we, as conservatives, simply agree that some things just work and leave them the F alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @JussieSmollett Ummmmmm ,,,,,, not passing the whiff test]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when they said game of thrones be killin off characters.. they meant it. Lemme finish season 3 up and go to bed sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the use of Benjamin as a hired gun here, just wish he was used more and used more successfully as of late to… https://t.co/XOp4HxABRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BudaTxFrog @WhiteHorseATX @sxsw @dirtyriverboys @CrooksCountry @TpTroubadours I’m down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the discussion of bond for e-poll books continues, I’ll note that three of the four male NCSBE members are we… https://t.co/30dLnraJJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_bonifas @koinzangreg @NickFickbohm I read that last night. Scary stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not even morning yet and Fortescue already gusted up to 57 mph 🍃. Gusts will go up as the sun comes up and mix… https://t.co/cFPXIvXiol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you call a dinosaur that is sleeping? A dino-snore!  😂 #FridayFunny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senor Procurador,  Jean Alain Rodriguez: Quiero, por favor; que tome el caso Odebrecht con la seriedad que admerita… https://t.co/17rwP6rlSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan @EdLaborCmte Work harder or get a better job you should not receive more money if you ain't worth it.… https://t.co/JGJB2PcOvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I said , I’m on the same page as you . I agree with everything you’re saying . My dislike for the Democrats be… https://t.co/AtUhxnovwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlekope0903 Food pictures can be challenging at times. I Often find it hard to capture the true mouth watering deliciousness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found some @TeamLiquid fans hanging around in Miami. https://t.co/WDf2gNllYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonMartinCTV Dear Don, #CTV #DonMartin #MP #Canada #cdnpoli #Liberals #SNCLavalin #Quebec 💩 https://t.co/kqgrgwY64n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fstef92 @FThooligan Don’t talk about my Broz like that https://t.co/96FtVwxEXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I do, so why don’t you mind your own damn business there ninja gym blog or whatever your name is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wazie45 @madisongesiotto I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOM… https://t.co/volNBIHHAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wisconsin Governor Pulls Troops from Border https://t.co/2bm2zDijfw  Timing people timing, the Dems are in cahoots… https://t.co/k2CRHme4G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's up this homies, they try to fuck around with me... with no keys and no wheels🤣🤣🤣😈. Puppies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaBanksWWE Sasha and Bailey you two rock you are so out of sight and sexy and beautiful and whatever you two do… https://t.co/DxWJM0jeA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MailOnline What I don't understand is how these young but physically mature male victims don't beat the Holy hell… https://t.co/TOWqnU4hD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justindotbell @Coach_Rick57 @JamieShaw5 @MasercolaMiles You deserve it bro. Keep up the good work ✊🏻💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mobile Tax Services Book your appointments now! https://t.co/fkUY98wqQf https://t.co/rhX4iEYj4b You can earn $100 p… https://t.co/OPxPjZHQ77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeReinhold @KenCosentino @TheRealJenCandy Stripes is still one of my favorite movies. It truly is a comedy classic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LenierMesa en Vivo por 107.5 FM Gracias puncanapuntocom univision 1075amor  official_miami_vice  #hialeah… https://t.co/WxWCFepobc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2011DerrickRose @NJBall2K @BullsGotNext So we aint gonna act like they traded for Otto Porter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stats from today’s game against LC:  @Gohamjdub 27pts, 6rebs  @dawand_jones 23pts, 10rebs  @CameronMaul 11pts, 6ast… https://t.co/dIjg6o0wBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle and High School New Teachers learning about Culturally Relevant Pedagogy from Flavia Gordon-Hunter! We're GS… https://t.co/L9T10W3P9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicususa I noticed a moral decline with the introduction of Rush Limbaugh and the conservative takeover of Am… https://t.co/HEAo6lbTaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS:   Dispatch confirms a semi truck is stuck under the Lafayette Street bridge.  This is near Lafayette… https://t.co/VZj47ODObO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just went on a tangent about sports gambling strategy to my mom and and she responds: “let’s talk about something… https://t.co/gHu9YJY4qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @NicoleLapin @NicoleDarin @NicoleDenver7, @Nikkydwilliams, @JosinaAnderson, @Lnanderson,… https://t.co/BB0Uu5NGCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much do you really think it should cost for your #Charleston #Wedding #DJ ? No matter what your budget is, the… https://t.co/H5Gpp4XUOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kottke The departed might be my favorite too. It’s so fast paced and Leo is literally going insane throughout the… https://t.co/pF3mxV6aFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @tayhidesfromHR for the ticket to @KONGOS tonight. Made my week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonksMullet @Senators Agree there seems to be no good way say we “Sensfans” have no way to work our way back to be… https://t.co/FYBfLiw7Zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early light #greyfieldinn #georgia #goldenisles #georgiacoast #cumberlandisland @greyfieldinn @ Greyfield Inn https://t.co/FQbvWpq9oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartySmithESPN @ESPNMcGee #whatcansyallgot ever canned beverage needs these reclosing tops! Its 2019 and this is g… https://t.co/nUeVp6iXWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost got all those steps in at #CMUERPsim2019 competition ! https://t.co/InrFa9GPsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are like 5 or 6 women who never speak or respond when i attempt to be cordial but always manage to find and f… https://t.co/9vgPj2GMMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just what the doc ordered after a shitty week. Thanks b! - Drinking  The Grid  by @TripleCrossing @ Gerhart’s Garde… https://t.co/zbt0saVGCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aacro_x @_F1gure8 @NathanielBandy1 Happy feet Wombo Combo https://t.co/QT3qkQbcEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll give you two guesses which nonprofit. 😍 cc: @code2college #diversityintech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam_qu They don’t pay. Most of the time, the stuff is worthless and can’t be sold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taranis7303 @KyleRichards @doritkemsley1 Exactly. This is not the first time. I prefer to watch successes and good use of platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner Got it. We come to you whenever we need to know when Cohen is lying or truthing. https://t.co/vc36lSvAJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glorbs_ I really enjoy our relationship and that you don’t take anything personally ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrennaSpencer When I read "who the Son sets free is free indeed" in John 8:36.  God was saying He could so I took… https://t.co/UilgIkhwUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[6th Street in Austin, calm before the #SXSW2019 storm. https://t.co/vx2M3evhYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 10 of twitter teaching me more shit than my college education will🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefkeev29 @DavidHasselgoff Personally no but a lot of people on this app do. It’s a problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkidunn7798 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_UNISecrets Bro. If you have to ask "is it cheating if..." And it involves another person, err on the side of caut… https://t.co/ALPJHH14Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember this other time that @fafhrd01 tried to kill my PC? https://t.co/2zgxvQ4jCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News Quietly Ditched Trump-Loving Sheriff David Clarke https://t.co/pft7OxbPa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teixeira_dennis Aqui nos EUA geral tá usando câmera no carro pra acabar com essa pouca vergonha. Assim que é punid… https://t.co/WDG2fTOhiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hheever @Cultaholic @RossOnRasslin Hahahaha the belly button was the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worksalt @aframe If you're working with hundreds or thousands of objects, you should also consider merging them to… https://t.co/VLqDim9Cg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Google #StreetView Now Lets You Take a Walk Around the Large Hadron Collider  https://t.co/0zmkKAGKph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ben41080 @elderofziyon @mishtal Repatriation as part of a peace deal, not while leadership swore unending war. Whe… https://t.co/nlsF5wgBJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevsACatch I know it does, I just meant I always grew up with separate ones so when i realized how many teams did combined it was weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 5.0 mph W. Barometer 29.975 in, Falling slowly. Temperature 22.5 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 34%]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LasChivasPorEl6  saludos a NatyLopez más Rayada que la más Rayada del mundo...... hoy gana la Raya!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In commemoration of  #NationalNappingDay, come get rear naked choked, free. https://t.co/8AOmg8mlt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off presentations for #Toledo Smart Cities Hackathon! @ATT @JumpStartInc @UTLaunchpad @eriehack @TPSProud https://t.co/47wyHreCcC]]></document></documents></author>