<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Goodluck to Emma Grace and her friends at NVS Dance as they compete today in Hot Springs, AR! https://t.co/krTkhHgEkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Banking job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Teller 20 hours Derit… https://t.co/ZKy2dNk217]]></document><document><![CDATA[*AND* planned parenthood isn’t “jUsT fOr AbOrTiOnS” a lot of times it’s people’s only healthcare option because it’… https://t.co/qN3VwnRHnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo Doesnt new antisemitism act, etc violate free speech ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please before speaking on a situation look at it not from a birds view. Alcorn police do everything but actually po… https://t.co/6HbuEumUgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We took a cab to waffle House and now there are no more cabs/Ubers to get back home lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #IT job openings, including "Senior Big Data Ab Initi… https://t.co/8Cm1mH5Od7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 They have to have pearls to clutch in case anybody attacks the NRA or our fascist president]]></document><document><![CDATA[No intakes tonight so I’m going to shadow the NP tonight and get some tips from her on nursing 👩🏻‍⚕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS my brother dropped his new song and music video!! He was working on it while we were home for Christmas vacay… https://t.co/C3axcA46Vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJSwag32 I love you my sweet boy. My heart is so full when I’m around you. I’m so proud of the person you have become.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 has been the year of putting myself first &amp; I’m not letting that stop anytime soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Margarita Day, friends!  Come celebrate and #drinkaboutthis with us at Wild Wing Cafe in Anderson, S… https://t.co/zB581LMmGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SandraDShep, it takes all stakeholders to move the work. There is no “ I” in team, it is collective work… https://t.co/qPBuuYPadD]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you guys all watch the umbrella academy on netflix so I can get a second season pLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[we don’t stan people who are only there for you when it’s convenient for them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay!! Look who made student of the month! Way to go Isaiah! #ZayzayJustice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonithecat32 @deborah26449389 @1gingerbeauty @buddy_gizmo @EricaGoss @SoxandD @Kathlee54272830 @MoetBlindCat… https://t.co/lCjulDhj2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's quote I found fitting for both my daily photo, and for Valentines Day. My children are what give me the gre… https://t.co/DeO1lE1VZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you start shit cuz you’re bored yeah that’s the shmood rn bahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day driving since my accident whew chile. https://t.co/ojYi4BzO6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like such an adult. going to my appointments n scheduling them all by myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[For example, no one is driving around my home this week out of state. Except I see Georgia. Everyone is at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united I would have to go to FLL. When I get to the United desks, there is. I one there. I call again and after wa… https://t.co/TQqp9MfGZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucille Ball...I love, love LOVE LUCY!! She didn't let her looks get in the way! She... https://t.co/w4kfaCBeA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BQQuinn @SalVulcano Aw Brian I think he misses you! Trying to get your attention by pissing off as many gullible p… https://t.co/ov0263aaj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump Never watch any of the hates Trump networks. @CNN @MSNBC_Breaking   All fake news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skeezboi I’m going to go cry about this for 100 years :/ I think I would of had a really bad panic attack if I did do it anyways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Hardly a rip. IT was incoherent in her response as if congressional  interns and aides did nothing all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me rn at 6am, suffering from jet lag &amp; 2 hours of sleep https://t.co/8OSyYvoWlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the feature Jeff Riseley and @BrainStation!   https://t.co/vKMzwA1H1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is the opportunity for me to have Popeye’s for breakfast and it’s about to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurdsIVue @CLE_CLCFan Ritos in Brunswick is very good and no where near the wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jättebra grej i Chicago (kan gälla hela USA): vid övergångsställen som saknar trafikljus är det STOPPLIKT. Ett exem… https://t.co/xgDkitrPy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going back to work in a week and damn I’m not ready☹️ I already barely sleep, time to never sleep again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is getting married or having babies and I’m just over here trying to pick out a name for the foal that’s o… https://t.co/SXN3s0Nuuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWHAM @13WHAM My cousin is a certified breeder and she is always warning people about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg they kill it this song and video I’m going crazy here my childhood back here this made my day so far I hope the… https://t.co/5AYqe4k1FG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hashtagtom24 @MattDoyle76 2.5 hour weeknight weather delay plus street flooding around the city will do that.  I’l… https://t.co/TySX3f3NvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday Selfie!! I may be another year older; but I still don’t look a day over 19!! 😉🥳🎉❤️ #Boston #selfie… https://t.co/8qbeIQrdfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisBusch The new OAP can be likened to serving everyone a liver dinner and expecting everyone to like it when MO… https://t.co/htdW9fe0OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen 🙏! He’s always right on time. He never fails. #I’mMarinaYourRealtorandFriend #I’mHereToServe… https://t.co/tr59LolciG]]></document><document><![CDATA[i probably peaked academically in middle school which, to me, isn’t that surprising or upsetting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leah Bradshaw: In history, there are splendid tyrants and vicious tyrants. But, no matter the origin of the tyrant,… https://t.co/nAkgn7uhMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so they can indict for the first time EVER the Prime Minister of Israeli, but we can’t indict the POTUS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weimardoodle @RealMuckmaker Super bad face lift or two. Weird that she is so puffy. She used to look like Ivanka.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ears r ringing like I went to the club with a bomb sound system... but I didn’t. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias @ananavarro for reminding us that the true measure of patriotism is how much you love this country and all… https://t.co/z43oOf4iZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#toasted shipleysdonuts like memaw used to make. #foodporn #nomnomnom #BACON #sundaybrunch @abreg_1 even though the… https://t.co/dVBqop3OjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who thinks God is solely male and the masculinity is “superior” bc Jesus was man is forgetting the truth tha… https://t.co/j1fD1Jsmhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEO_Scan Passed that about 10 minutes ago... not sure how I missed the pole and wire part lol.  I saw a car into g… https://t.co/JKFSZD5GRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein So... you must mean Mueller too since he signed off on the illegal plea deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[visited my FAVORITE mouse pals today!!! too bad whit couldnt tag along..i know she’d LOVE to hang with them✨❤️ https://t.co/YIjlAgdMCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco Fire PIO Lt. Baxter: “We are at a point where time is so crucial that we’re not going to put a deadli… https://t.co/gvdIEbMyXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your friends don’t support you and push you to do your best are they really your friends?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I miss the 60’s, the 70’s shoot even the 80’s and 90’s in all those decades up through 2016 there was hope and… https://t.co/ha67FWDd1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomasthecat @JamesKerwin @thenicolabryant @DVDGeeks @JetForMe @KalofXeno Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house at Covered Bridge Inn last night! Good times! We'll see you back there on St. Patty's Day!… https://t.co/vGUmFzLCzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanna_turton They just seem like they’re always so happy together 😭 we stan forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredibleCulk PREACH!  #pedogate #pizzagate #childsextrafficking #HumanTrafficking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettShroll @AOC You are obviously still ignorant! Besides being a condescending jerk! Blocked 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troutslayer1448 @likeajboss @regrams @Emily_1448 @MariahYelle @qnguyen622 @Howard_JoshT @Tom_T1448 @VMjillMarch… https://t.co/hcXOYBJU7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brexit_sham @JustWhatNowWhy freedom to expand their land grabs. Rebuilding their empire is the end plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are the fastest track runner in school, you need the perfect fit shoes. not_sebas_tho #proudmama @ Road Ru… https://t.co/pytjcDoe0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonVivantGirl @StacyeBranche @AfroStateOfMind @karenhunter @SylviaKAlston @LoriShemek @drjoyce_knudsen… https://t.co/6qlJXvdjQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BComptonNHL FYI- whenever I say or read this word—- in my head it is same in the way Arya yells it out at Sansa 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/UW6NnJ5lf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lgibson12397 Live this. Having a way with words and writing poems ect. Is such a cool gift❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo I am a Floridian and I am pissed! How dare he !!! He needs to go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixers how he injured when he was dancing with all those white folks yelling the N Word he was great @JoelEmbiid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalKopan @maggieNYT He is of course correct, not@to mention it’s illegal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton Good! They won’t reproduce themselves. Now if we can only save our children from believing the insanity the left spouts...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackZagg My hip is hurting now. I think I need to combine running with yoga if I’m going to do this right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Really? You have to think about this? Roseann was canceled for much less. Can you spell hypocrisy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand 😂😂😂really, for real. You want the Green New Deal?? Have you even read it?? It would put America back… https://t.co/wuyrQbLgiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I hope the Sara Lee that we keep hearing about is the Sara Lee from the sandwich bread. Then we’ll have a lot… https://t.co/Suk4BTUHK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish i could jump up and down, bang on the sides of my abdomen to get my uterus to eject out all the blood like h… https://t.co/OJOcNs5Ue8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy!!!!!! Super proud of you! Successful player and even better kid! @_taburgess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convo the other day.  Me: Tom, could you please water my plants. I've been forgetting.  Tom: I already did yesterda… https://t.co/9rHnH2zSj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrArunaJ @acgme #representationmatters makes you wonder who the disproportionate toll of burnout, sacrifice fall u… https://t.co/p4vnN6G0gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This proposal has now apparently prevailed among the US bishops - and should be introduced to the will of Cupich an… https://t.co/VUCvSeQb3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raptormamacita Agreed. She was whiny at times and that annoyed me but I tried to imagine myself being at home and… https://t.co/1oAdQXkFPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been waking up with ice on my windshield in the morning and I’m not okay with it. This cold weather needs to b… https://t.co/NxJzCulAAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually accidentally apologized to someone in korean a while ago. .. the looks you get...... https://t.co/Nv7wnZ5Vyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too class tonight with this weather being as cold as it is or not to class?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birdieglad @AOL @Ireland0828 @pannlewis44 @abronxchick @veterans_i @KelliSmith15 @MarilynT4 😢😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[People gathered in the Boston Common today to protest U.S. intervention in Venezuela #HandsOffVenezuela… https://t.co/e7KU9wNmOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close encounters of the Dalmatian pelican kind. #zoolife #protectwhatyoulove https://t.co/jLnGZxZcLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree! My student engagement has been positively impacted through using it! The lessons are high quality, customiza… https://t.co/4UNxAlUDbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Infantry0300 So true. Jeffrey Epstein’s friend Donald Trump, with his sordid past and sick fantasies must be held… https://t.co/SnyNj1Tutn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Monday morning wishes for you. Don’t forget YOU this week! ☕️  . . Image via @SweatpantsCafe. 😘 #monday… https://t.co/WJRZ7mEUQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, lay down for a nap in the afternoon and wake up, SURPRISE! Its 5am! Jeezus, was I THAT tired????😦👀 #WhatsWrongWithMe ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soaking up all the sun and warmth we can! #sun #fun #vacation https://t.co/qnkFHGsszn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the tweet!!! While I work w organizations to design human capital management systems and am an HR profes… https://t.co/b8TezWXSwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[☑️ 3 receiving blankets done  ☑️ 3 baby quilts started ... Next steps mean lots of busy weekends...  🔘 3 quilts rag… https://t.co/GyjaX1f3IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow I can’t seem to get past the ages. Haunting they were not protected while these crimes happened in plain site.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya know, having my hours cut, did kind of coincide with when the cocky little child referred to me as a bitch.  I'm… https://t.co/wSDlOwo5rE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrYantzi_LU @ECHO_Laurentian @DianaCoholic Congratulations @DianaCoholic ! Seems like this is long overdue! You're a true inspiration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literature Circle Book Tasting - which book sparks your interest? @bernat_nicole #RiseUpRidgeview #KellerLiteracy https://t.co/6qv9ymfaee]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so happy. And I'm so excited to get started with my journey with Disney, because it has officially begun. 💕😭 @… https://t.co/cEmuAWNdXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @CindyHess65 They're smart enough to know that they cannot win any argument about policy or government… https://t.co/AvJXhkxi9H]]></document></documents></author>