<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Def agree 100% had our chances to win Forsure. Also had our chance to get ran on our home court as well. Just hopin… https://t.co/DAhwko1lv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man that wants you will never leave you guessing about where you stand in his life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobileUS I dream of a day when my phone #GalaxyS9 has an update that it doesn't change my settings! https://t.co/AmeunzchrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is ludicrous. How Asian Women Age #comic #cartoon https://t.co/v1uHvMDxBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungUS What's the best replacement remote for this tv model? https://t.co/96gl3r8wqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millie loves watching the sunset 😃 #Sunset #Capitola https://t.co/epybHwzplA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julie_kelly2 You need to look up coup. @Dictionarycom can you help her? Or at least try?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking @lisarinna. She is a GD national treasure. Can’t we get her some kind of award. Make up a title. Something people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGratchen @realDonaldTrump He kinda slammed a killer deal with Kim. At least he took him out to dinner.… https://t.co/QywifCp3d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations from your @TheMIAA Conference Partner @GearBoss_Wenger!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay Tuned is the best podcast on the internets.  Cafe Insider is the icing on the cake, totally worthy of your sup… https://t.co/0TTPgYkYa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Fall River, Massachusetts https://t.co/V6y4J8WVeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hassel_Chris I think Iowa may be viewed a bit more safety in the conventional wisdom than reality because of their… https://t.co/xxGmFORJhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_S_Hancock @MelissaBujeda @JSOPIO Congrats to you as well, Chris!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker, Taylor, taking her shots at sunset Saturday. #nh #newhampshire #newengland #northeast #whitemountains… https://t.co/hNZT2NjbI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lady on the GO train just blew her nose and it sounded like a cross between a trumpet and an angry elephant. Anot… https://t.co/qWNpSpwQGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I’ll be on the Grand Ole @opry tonight! With @Elizabeth_Cook. We play at 7:05 pm CT and will definitely be the… https://t.co/a9ORhKJ4P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me whenever my friends might need medical assistance after drinking too much:]]></document><document><![CDATA[On some nights like this, I just wanna text you, but for what? _Kehlani @ Club TIGERHEAT https://t.co/btCw9gupei]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Last Jedi was released more than a year ago there is still a contingent of people on this website who are SCREA… https://t.co/jXzECLT8DI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Your Trump Derangement Syndrome is usually ok, because it usually only hurts you and your sheep.  Ho… https://t.co/0DZ1uguNoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBrunoWSOC9 @wsoctv Congratulations, Joe. Your Mark Harris investigation harkens to Charlotte Observer Pulitzer… https://t.co/JV1bmfj0l8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad Max Domi is part of Les @CanadiensMTL!  This man continues to impress on and off the ice! 👏👏👏  #LGBTQ #Habs… https://t.co/1Jlv2WYWFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the artistry from our Hispanic and Indigenous culture and community. #xicoarteycultura https://t.co/QjVpv02HK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christy Clark needs to be prosecuted  and tossed in jail. It won’t be hard to convict. You just have to want to loo… https://t.co/yfCT1a2OWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to me, all who labor and are heavy laden, and I will give you rest. Matthew 11:28   ©TvBawDesign https://t.co/3LXwlCObOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lavishedgelivin @JohnLynch49ers Name a wr that would help jimmy better than ab? If the niners go 4-12 or 6-10 this… https://t.co/nVZaeOnf4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a “paws”to tell them we love these incredible young men and women! @GUMedicine @DiverseGUMed @GUAlumni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein He’s the father of Adam Sandler in the movie. The Waterboy. Dumb as a box of rocks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcthiessen He’s also far more unafraid of any political fallout to just say things on this issue others might have danced around a bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZuckerman So Harper wouldn't bet on himself after 4 years with odds Heavily in his favor. Not to mention livin… https://t.co/RMXds6dWrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeJon71906400 @Briana_Lee_xx She is not and i mean not in porn anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk any plans on making a Tesla that is winter friendly? Tesla struggles in the bigger cities mechanically. W… https://t.co/3KtloO59Ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchsilver @ItsMightyGoat Stuff like this only works in free to play where micro transactions fund the game, gam… https://t.co/UVlQg4HMDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Camanche 78, Wilton 48. Cameron Soenksen had 27 and Caleb Delzell has 26 points to lead Camanche. Jared Town… https://t.co/fvqavq2wzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[sheriff’s weekend is highkey the scariest thang that happens in wildwood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at markets as we wait for the briefing. Asian stocks extend declines along with US futures after… https://t.co/k2UNJy0K8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was like Mr. Wilson’s rare midnight blooming flower in Denace the Menace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this is the softball/baseball equivalent of the royal flush]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst show with the biggest bunch of freaks in the history of television!!!🔇  https://t.co/JRLilH0Zne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @LindseyGrahamSC Mr. Graham has uncharacteristically lost his pair... from belittled during the 201… https://t.co/vaPHi9HQoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Machomike60 Some , but I love life and always have fun and love to be entertained]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great! Check this out!! @stephanie101312 @HDKristofer @THDGorski @CowlesDoug @JimLamar1 @jmiller2110… https://t.co/jLrqj4zF5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball Roger Stone can try sign language in the meantime. The audience may be small though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbarro Trump National West Chester  On Pres disclosure he puts value at $50MM.  In tax docs - he puts value at $1.… https://t.co/ItgSKL5SNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMauraA I want to BEAT THE HELL out of that EVIL SOCIOPATH right now! 🤬🤬🤬 https://t.co/G4yWws2uea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookwormpp @RealJamesWoods when you jerk sombody;s head up to the snap position.. It ain't a pose.. it is real tim… https://t.co/OCRVfmr5ZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xio090876 Buenos días Xioma linda, que tengas un excelente viernes 😀🌷🌹. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FExpressionsUS If you need a coach, I'm semi-retired and have decades of experience with fresh expressions, going… https://t.co/Mu7HzxvYkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[One #Mets coach (and a few ushers) have noticed my @ColaFireflies jersey today]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many lead changes @LVMotorSpeedway in 2017..? How many today??  How many position changes from 2nd to 20th in 2… https://t.co/0ELsBcQCAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@protestona1 @BoseOfficial Y la opresión de la nación Palestina por parte de Israel es un tema vetado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @MindiMink @karleegreyxxx @RachelStarrxxx @Zoeyfoxx @SummerDayXXX @JillKassidyy @onlyjennafoxx @APOLONIAPORN… https://t.co/g7ijptsng2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kingdom Hearts III and Uncharted 4 both beat. No more PS4 for me for a little while. #headache]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJahvonQ getting some more minutes tonight, love to see that!   #PatienceIsAVirtue #FutureStud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Один из самых уважаемых современных певцов, композитор/пианист/актер и продюсер, "оскаровский" лауреат сэр eltonjoh… https://t.co/nbnHPrXZIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Chattanooga, TN? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/uCEgBZWx8A #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rachel: Federal Judge rules that the foreign-owned mystery company engaged in a court battle with Mueller does have… https://t.co/V5SAGYVbdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we now all just sit back and let Grimes develop at his pace instead of at the pace YOU thought he would?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucken identity theifs just like the fucken prediction I made seven years ago it came true https://t.co/ivhTeJ3JKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose when you’ve been wide awake since 2:30 you just get out of bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleMusic is there anyway you can sort out the @MarinaDiamandis and Marina and the Diamonds searches. It’s imposs… https://t.co/E9viGlYYB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Rian_Stone @deeppresence @RationalMale @ironshrink @EdLatimore @IvanThrone @joserosado He loves you more than any… https://t.co/lc24sCGFVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tuchdown26 @BeccaLynn412 @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian mus… https://t.co/hDOdMdjVPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brayden VonLanken, who will play on the line at McKendree, has pretty good footwork in the post. There could be a dancing future for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t deserve Deftones, new sound/mood goes for each album i love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to former Vol Fuad Reveiz, All SEC 82, Pro Bowl 94, his 71 Career Field Goals remains a school Recor… https://t.co/u9x5GtPJG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom And said, he likes me, I like him! Sick, despicable and disgusting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMahaney @Prudential Millenials are being screwed by the Capitalists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman along with @dog_rates and @Super70sSports yours is one of the best twitter pages]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to buy some new shorts! I lost so much weight that when I played today they kept riding down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercials are horrible @NASCAR @DISupdates good thing I have @NASCARAppSeries in my ear or heck I wouldn’t know b… https://t.co/P4zvfXu1im]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure whether I am beginning to be sick or it's just way too dry inside my house but my throat is scratchy and s… https://t.co/k1b6ehWEon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @StewartThomasD You are lying !!! IF YOU CAN LIE ABOUT THIS TOPIC ... PEOPLE WHO CAN READ ME !    IMA… https://t.co/vMSIqqcm42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elspanishgooner How are we still having this discussion in March 2019? Clearly Emery isn’t going to play Ramsey in… https://t.co/EPOWCo5Cn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making fun of John Elway is low hanging fruit, but I’m going to do it anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s out !! It’s out !!  @ThisIsRobThomas “One Less Day (Dying Young)” 🙌🏽 🙌🏽 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[this guy drake really left toronto cause a snow storm was coming.. this nigga my idol wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad the the Federal Reserve Chairman has to state publicly he’s appointed to a 4 year term and intends to fulfill h… https://t.co/fp3XYY2Es5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve19214431 @RE_Games @CapcomUSA_ Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music… https://t.co/pfwTkuIjGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda sketchy. Did some doodles @ The Art Institute of Atlanta https://t.co/zjgs3xmloZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[They really are not going to conclude that show? Smh... it’s a good show btw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hidden treasures.... many of which are also flagged 🚩 along the way so they can be identified later... students lea… https://t.co/Pw7g2bqKMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geheichou 2nd pic looks like you were wearing a straw hat and you turned your head so fast it flew off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Start investigating the Democrats how can someone become a millionaire on a govt salary. Please INVESTIGATE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioNovelli @AlbertoRodNews Que tipo tan gafo. Pobre diablo vendido y bruto, no se da cuenta que se acabo y que… https://t.co/paqdUPiCF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the nominees and winners. There were so many amazing and inspiring films released in 2018. R… https://t.co/YHeR988iuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGregoryRoseDDS First 20K write down of all student loan debt = zero for most Americans except the real high incom… https://t.co/kzfH63eWgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 King Of Rock by @OfficialRunDMC on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/jziV5WTYeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryaninteractive @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews That's an old picture. He's much fatter now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my family showed me all the values that I WON'T instill in my future family. breaking the cycle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blummer27 Do you know why Dallas Keuchel is hanging around Rice University?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else see that @espn #HQ @IzGutierrez is perfect for playing #BlackMask opposite of #BirdsOfPrey… https://t.co/yCsgt4jb0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[This rivalry only seems to end one way. Great win for our boys in blue last night off a well earned comeback.… https://t.co/WNAtRzLbqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas are losers no wonder women sick of y’all lmao. Louis loafers, suit nice and decent table but wouldn’t buy an… https://t.co/mauZiAohXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyaleighxxx U have such a hot sexy sweet yummy pink slutty pussy so hot baby very hot😍💋👅🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyJ_WOODTV @emilylinnert @daybrett Thanks pals, for all of the times you guys have let me share cool stuff for… https://t.co/nLQ5VgrBNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Old Florida Antique Museum in Hastings, FL https://t.co/atFUqk16zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[N4TRQ-5 Near N4TRQ QTH, Va. Beach, VA https://t.co/PBPtuqZ8lv #APRS 13b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock Around the Clock by Bill Halley and the Comets blends almost perfectly with Rock This Town by The Stray Cats,… https://t.co/WsjPEKN0Ft]]></document></documents></author>