<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Praying is the greatest activity we can perform. Let's keep our Lord in this struggle against Islam and hatred.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThreeFoldComics I've read Y the Last Man, Pride of Baghdad, Saga, and Private Eye. He does nothing for me. And he'… https://t.co/QqfKKgwMRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinparson75's sophomore advisory beat the snow and completed their service project Monday. Check out their Vale… https://t.co/ThMTf9utZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS         🎉 🌟 👏 🎬       to #LaciKay @lacikayofficial for 2 #Nominations from @yeaawards !!  1)… https://t.co/dQFlH3Bbzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HereForTheTea2 She and I had plastic surgery on her face but she definitely had it elsewhere! Her butt hips and bo… https://t.co/nKgMiUSGfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @thenaca... our @upcnebraska delegates are exhausted, but we had fun at the National Convention!!! We boa… https://t.co/XuQ5oVeexQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slapping someone’s ass that you don’t know and then blaming HER for what she’s wearing???? Disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he don’t want to party wit fat hoes he ain’t got to party wit fat hoes period]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailBenzler @DivaVinophile @SIPwinebar @GrnLakeGirl @jflorez @Fit_life360 @_drazzari @boozychef @sl2016_sl… https://t.co/jjL8dW9zY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why blur her face out? She wrongfully accused this man and ruined his reputation and probably his life and career t… https://t.co/TrY2niSSD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going back blonde next week for the first time in years and I’m so nervous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAPNorthAmerica @SAP @sunjunemusic Hi! Does this require badge or rsvp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH YEAHHHH!! Looks like someone was reading my Tweets asking someone to keep the Ruskies busy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not pumped for our future @ATLHawks, you’re wrong. This is an exciting team. #TrueToAtlanta]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so used to waking up early af for work now my ass can’t sleep in for shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are so unoriginal for hating on country music. You don’t hear me saying squat about what you bump to in your car, Susan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am just as nervous watching teams my kid coaches as I am when she competes as an athlete. 😁 #nerves #goLeopards @makdaddddy95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: just saw him ride in on the scooter and hide it under the stairs again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause yall so amusing to me, be so consumed with another individual smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this, because if you are dealing with mind, body or soul, you cannot fake it. Be real. https://t.co/zobaZMw4NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diane_Stewart @chrisalbano422 @JamieMBlanchard @lisarinna Their jealousy is dripping off them so bad it’s starting… https://t.co/f2WzGj7B3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limoncello sorbet with Deep Eddy Lemon. @ Frost a Gelato Shoppe https://t.co/fbDOi3IFvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Media, come save people from overdosing! Forget about universal health care. Media, this is your responsibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exchange between Kurt Lash and Norm Spaulding about how we’re using the term “revolutionary,” prompted by a Darrell… https://t.co/4RPavCWyaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett Is Arrested And Carolyn Bryant, The Woman Who Falsely Accused Emmett Till, Is Still Living Her Life… https://t.co/wRInlWzavN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was having a convo with my female coworkers about me giving my girl my extra pullover sweater and they were happy… https://t.co/tsHBf2KwRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I strongly support statehood for Washington DC, says @BernieSanders in #SandersTownHall. How to make it happen? "… https://t.co/7zA0PJbmcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettinaSumner I’m not spreading anything as fact other than my experience. It is a blind item but I have my reason… https://t.co/MwHUiSZxRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like this nigga wants to get locked up he practiced this out scene by scene 💀 great job to her I would’ve been… https://t.co/odYtNIy8yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching the chicago news conference @ABC @ABC7Chicago this is terrible im disappointed and sad @JussieSmollett wou… https://t.co/51yStS2ZYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @RoArquette @AOC @CPAC Do you renounce your christian upbringing? Everything your father taught?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csimmz74 Oh hell no sis, that’s just you. That’s not a cancer thing. 😂😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in a shit talking group chat w people I don’t even know and the only thing I ever say in it is “fuck that bitch”]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are very committed to serving CA transfer students! @CalCommColleges come so prepared and strengthen our campuse… https://t.co/sHFofM2d1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5SOS have a song called midnight, @SetItOff have an album called midnight, conspiracy theory future collaboration??????????? i fudging wish]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You never change things by fighting the existing reality. To change something, build a new model that makes the ex… https://t.co/0glvmPyWtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemetriaObilor @DemetriaObilor I am a Principal at a Dallas High School @IDEA_at_Fannin , I would love for you to… https://t.co/9YaBnUFsnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinScampi Poor Scampi.😿   Please give him a new one before he tries to retrieve his from Kevin. 😹😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly @foxnews Bill Mayer must not realize that MANY red staters no longer live in the red states because com… https://t.co/lgom6C7ljc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose your own @AB84 adventure, NFL press edition #steelers #bills https://t.co/t8PxiR4zD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home safe after the game, #LAKings Fam! So much to post, but it will wait until tomorrow. I turned on "Goon" and no… https://t.co/KcIHlDlNfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MississippiBlu2 Though in many ways I think of them more as reactionaries, like 18th-19th c monarchists, so rather… https://t.co/j0B5quWItE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltc_007 @KRenaeP @BrianMendler I agree. A replacement for behavior charts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now u heard it from ebonylips_ hubby... haters kiss cobra 🐍 @ Hyattsville, Maryland https://t.co/RRw7LymyO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workshop: Colored Pencil Painting Date: 3/9/19 Time: 10am -3pm Location: Seneca County Art Council, 109 Fall St., S… https://t.co/aBRHRTzwDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently waiting on my Ipsy pkg...like 🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼. Also live in central Washington where we are under “winter shut… https://t.co/lLxkd7GdWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulwallbaby this song rocks I am so happy to hear 👂  this new song!!https://t.co/2fSlK7w6RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i was in new york for a couple of days and im in love with it ☺️ bye bye new york :( hopefully ill see you soon. https://t.co/40Dkr03zM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeleStar11 @GatesRobin Now that's what we need..thank you..until there are ARRESTS...nothing gonna change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @JeanHaggerty1 Way to step up to Florida...you got yourself a good one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I urge everyone to buy Blue Light blocking glasses or include the film on prescription glasses! Every time I visit… https://t.co/i33399oVpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylStrayed @tumblehawk Feeling this hard today. Thank you for giving us the right words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend treats me w endless respect and kindness always and i sincerely don’t deserve it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicOlague @Worst_of_Crimes No es responsabilidad de nadie, cumplir los "sueños" de otros. Yo tengo una alta de pro… https://t.co/f3Q3tQfFKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extrañaba pintarme el cabello de negro 🧡 ¿no les pasa eso? Algunas personas me dijeron que no era yo sin colores en… https://t.co/hHiMVouNY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCChoops @byuwbb @shayleegonzales @TheAndyKatz Yes she is a scoring machine so glad we have her on our team💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Allen19 I do random things just because and deleted my Snapchat and ig, then I got to twitter and realized what I was about to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klancer1 Thinking of you Hammer and team! @UWindsor #yqg #hockey Go get ‘em!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardAmericas @emrazz Only if you're a dysfunctional 19 year old with daddy issues. Luckily once you become a grow… https://t.co/wEWC3Kfnc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raju @shaunking This was a CLEAR case of buying his decision! I bet they paid off the JUDGE too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is the best. Honestly. He’s amazing. But in the middle of the night he somehow burritos himself in our c… https://t.co/xQvVP1DJdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need a relationship with the Holy Spirit again. They have lost their moral compass.… https://t.co/SCZpr5uGAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got 4 more eps to go for Pinocchio! I need to know how this is gonna end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you want to build a snowman?? 💙⛄️ ❄️ ✨✨ . . . . #disneyfrozen #frozendisney #disneyfrozenelsa #disneyelsa… https://t.co/MEGStzcJpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroByTMobile Chris Hemsworth @chrishemsworth  would make the best pro basketball player! #TeamGiannis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ListMccarthy Again, you are generalizing. The point of social sciences (broadly) is to study and understand relati… https://t.co/LBwYgzIgom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcb97 Contortion training. I haven’t been trained for 3weeks.. due to sick 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanyaMudway @Madeleine_1115 Was Mark Hollis the singer for Talk Talk? It is sad he left this world 🌎😢💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmostShawn All of your plants are amazing, I am in awe!!! https://t.co/rfA01YaXxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whcurl @Stretchbelz And somehow she takes care of people for a living? :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sol1dus2 Check this out it is in your neck of the woods:  https://t.co/9JmvXxMZXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Saturday night ever!   I’ll show up up to a @aaron_watson concert in any weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[LORD, I just want to thank you.  I want to thank you for being so good to me 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community colleges are a superb option for high-quality education at a low cost. Check us out @TriCedu! Love this c… https://t.co/Dud5f7lacq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hugozapata486 @GracielaReartes @FerIglesias Repugnante es el régimen castrista.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCSCsocial CONGRATULATIONS Dr.Martin-Knox... I am so proud to hear the excited news....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Part of Kathy Griffin is a “Self-made” ??? Her filthy mouth 👄? Her Idiotic brain ? Or her stinky lung ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guys just learned how to use this whole location thing on Twitter, and I must say it’s pretty cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for appreciating my efforts. Tennessee is much closer to legalization than 3 years ago when I started lob… https://t.co/77AyfVHAIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tenacious_inc  I know a dog that looks a lot like this one that would love this treatment lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The negro that was Harvard educated and family man did that, go golf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lobeline PR at the #2019 #Grammy viewing party benefiting #StevenTyler's #JaniesFund!  #WeGetPR @LobelinePR… https://t.co/HMdt8TxqJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell me I'm not the only one thinking about this... @Jack_Septic_Eye  #jimhawkins #treasureplanet https://t.co/oUDPUpvIIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warmvibrations Honestly I figured they were trolling with that one but if they were serious idk 😭😭😭 nobody cares about her rapping career]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr President, please don't pander to the open border advocates at chamber if commerce. Many if you… https://t.co/gZq8jwpYxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an early morning stupor, I just realized that Lenny and Squiggy are mirror images of Laverne and Shirley, down to the L&amp;S names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward To GWTW this afternoon...❤️Rhett❤️ https://t.co/Ztt3vZyb3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[..when your Boy comes for your BDay 💜 @ Steam Pub https://t.co/HF91xqGUJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, but only to the runaway slave which Angelica and her husband paid Hamilton to return to their propert… https://t.co/pcr2nBrmQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official to Tulsa radio color analyst J.R. Rollo, who pointed out the clock issue: “Do it again and see what happens.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my friend she should sit on this guys face and the professor heard me https://t.co/ekVGQa8bGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenlucas7 This makes me so happy!!!  Sending you a hug, my friend! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need a refresher course on all the moving parts of the #MuellerInvestigation read this. Well done @AP !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooo this would be so pretty with my sunflower colored eyeballs! 💁🏻‍♀️☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition #TreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorIsFINISHED  # #TreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorIsFINISHED… https://t.co/QdlyBX84Ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[That pay raise is looking super nice! I’m eatin, everybody eatin!! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missed the last point! Maybe @Paul_Wischmeyer can remind me after. #CCC48]]></document><document><![CDATA[BGAPSA reception at 6 (@ Sweeten Alumni House in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/afPWQjxo0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherchannel why do y’all ignore Alabama like these tornados ain’t serious... we do not care about the snow up north or Oklahoma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesseleesoffer There should not be doubt ever. Nbc would be dumb to take ya off. My fav show ty]]></document></documents></author>