<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Cuando se pone dramático le digo que chilee, que se fume un cigarro y que no me joda. Que pereza amargarse la noche… https://t.co/gTR2oqNIt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new approach to fighting #climate change in Cambodia: empowering #women https://t.co/sR0l4Qp561]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never have anyone in my corner but im always placing myself there for others for support. Thank you, next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me Aunt Scrooge but I wish we could junk  #InternationalWomensDay in favor of Gender Equality Day. The former… https://t.co/CBL4o8a1XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why I was so obsessed with Applebee’s when I lived in Ohio. Like...there’s an Applebee’s here in my hometo… https://t.co/zctsJoZ8Ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a sad day when the barista messes up your birthday drink😩😢 @Starbucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTimmy7 If something seems too good to be true it probably is. I could desperately use the money with disabled… https://t.co/YWchM30Lm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I be the only one who really detests “Netflix and chill”? Like in all aspects? Like as a date, as a regular nig… https://t.co/scjffd8GxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad about this one! He was way too young. RIP 💔🖤 @LukePerryIII  #LukePerry #RIP #RIPLukePerry #strokessuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking over this thunder right now. It’s fucking terrifying! 👀✨  #LosAngeles]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like im so quick to smoke w everyone else when they don't have weed but shiiiiiitttt ...... it never happens to me lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elfcosmetics @NyxCosmetics @bhcosmetics @MorpheBrushes @KATVONDbeauty @COVERGIRL @LOrealParisUSA  these all the ma… https://t.co/Px3jKrMAc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as I hear these winds I’m staying in bed! #HighWindWarning https://t.co/ZDFcX6uubD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landokitty bitches who look like that and play wonderwall covers always are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get letters from USC addressed to: Dear Trojan Mom. I get a kick out of being a “Trojan Mom.” So much in so many… https://t.co/y95qZfVQBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sim_one27 @JosieLadawn @PPFA Did you find out about CVS? Even as a longtime supporter of Planned Parenthood, I am… https://t.co/iCNMHU3H7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[My face after three rounds or one hour of Shaun-a-Thon!. This mother of all workouts sure showed me how far I have… https://t.co/07DDYCD9r5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Lemon &amp;amp; Blueberry Cake Cookies. A fresh and fruity #veganrecipe - what better way to use up leftover… https://t.co/CGMnvxobQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lot_A Please add:  any Molson, LeBatt’s, Moosehead and (this one pains me) Unibroue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericmetaxas @JZmirak Thanks so much, John &amp; Eric, for promoting my banishment. I didn't know you shared it on… https://t.co/8vBiZ7PlPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singingfern23 Story of my life: “How did I get to an article about basket weaving from a Debussy page?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure @quinn_cent and I have been talking daily consistently for the last year 1/2 and it’s NEVER DRY. I thank God for her everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesTurnerYT The one my youngest son wrote me in 4th grade for mother's day, L too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was called bossy by two men at work for asking them to do a simple task. I can’t help but to think it’s bc I’m a woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OVERDOSE😵💔 Available Now Via. youtube @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/Lw4ChbdQ23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensively wonders if I’ll regain feeling in my frozen ass any time soon. Similarly wonders if the groundhog lied ab… https://t.co/8hS1E717kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCoachK15 @Savvy_Educator @jessxbo @KarlyMoura @SEANJFAHEY Andy, Y🤩U are ✨most excellent✨ Your genuine heart and… https://t.co/37QMr7WT4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Future Husband, . . Last year on this day I wrote you a letter in which I shared my desire to get to know more… https://t.co/yxKkA30yv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRaimondo My question: Did Raimondo Administration know any of this during  election-year 2018? When did it beco… https://t.co/HBk2XvlZze]]></document><document><![CDATA[True ❤️ || Is a man who will photobomb your #selfie instead of roll his eyes 🙄. #truelove #photobomb #couplesgoals… https://t.co/i2jIFR9Zbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few more March SF Crypto events!  3/7 - https://t.co/ohdTK1taku  3/15 - @sendwyre Poker Night! - https://t.co/OY9kBiwdnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanaRae15 @TamarBraxtonHer Girl ! I was watching Kandi do hers tryna learn some techniques 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to do THIS tho!!! #ineedarealityshow Sleep in glass pods suspended 1,200 ft. up the side of mountain in Peru… https://t.co/AK8oAns7fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexnewton53 @atiku @PeterObi @MBuhari @ProfOsinbajo @inecnigeria @PoliceNG @GuardianNigeria @OfficialAPCNg… https://t.co/6a8naeJvZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[some bitches just can’t keep one dick. always hoppin from one fool to the next]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Follett Corporation? We're hiring in #Lawton, OK! Click the link in our bio for details on this job… https://t.co/ZXWMcfuyBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii She is talking the truth from her evil sole, yes! There is a complite crisis in our Democrasy BECAUSE… https://t.co/WdFklsHcfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuddling with my girl after her soccer game while we watch Ty play lacrosse. @ Sicard Hollow Sports Complex https://t.co/DPU7CeAPOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[THATS the content I expect when I get on this site. THIS is how you do it ppl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this why white people need to stay out of certain conversations. don’t overstep you’re boundaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t officially meet her but she saw my potential and brought me to memphis! I will be forever grateful #RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamdeVry1 I had a mini stroke in my 30s due to a heart defect, very scary stuff! Luckily I got to hospital in… https://t.co/9GjFgPnhSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[AG shares about the excessive amounts of pills one receives after a medical procedure. What do you do with leftover… https://t.co/CK2Gwi4Pa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGkee It’s like a racist race between all the luxe brands to see who can be the fucking worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that even mild dehydration (1-3% of body weight) can impair multiple aspects of brain function? Be sur… https://t.co/IXzu38VOth]]></document><document><![CDATA[RE your Emergency Maintenance @Namecheap - there’s still something not quite right. I cannot complete a purchase of my domain names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanRabb @Soonerthon I stand for bringing the best doctors to the state so treatments/ operations/ recoveries/ etc… https://t.co/gwi4NHHMhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[so in order to go to copperdog I gotta get myself to the Beabers’ with my unregistered car on bald wheels. prayers… https://t.co/q6YzifObCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to Juan about the kids birthdays and about the shirts and he said “ let me know the color so I can get matc… https://t.co/XXrCJTJVpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gobluefan95 @MaizenBrew @WoodsFootball @CoachJim4UM @jamesearljones @MichaelPhelps @giseleofficial @OfficialTyLaw… https://t.co/uhf40zDlXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julianna_glass @CaththeWineLady @DemiCassiani @winewankers @wineworldnews @suziday123 @_drazzari @always5star… https://t.co/C6Qh16aMkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jensandler @TheFerrymanBway @briandarcyjames My daughter and I saw it over Christmas break and we are counting the… https://t.co/gGdYr9F4cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm exceedingly proud of this gif I just made: the #Billiken reimagined for Fallout 76. Will @SLU_Official love it,… https://t.co/TOD01aFfYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got out of the hospital for an asthma attack send me some prayers 🙏 thank you I love you guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[only i would watch “The 10 Most Heartbreaking Disney Channel Breakups” and bawl my eyes out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiroGomezL @lopezobrador_ Otro muerto más del actual gobierno https://t.co/cN4kEtcOiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last baby is WALKING 😭😭 and I’m not there bc they are in Russia until June 😭 he’s going to be running by that time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dancing all night with the one and only djjoshpeace Abbey ‍ https://t.co/2EQvaIyO70 https://t.co/xehcjs86RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so in love with me , I love my imperfections. 🌞 https://t.co/AShiQMeZbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday my girl @maggidieker got engaged and last night we celebrated with a dinner with a large group of her fav… https://t.co/mjNL9bGx3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think some of them need to be replaced and not have to add too so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD hey Salinas PD it's ignorant and wrong  to assume  a dog is vicious just because he's a pit bull. That dog… https://t.co/cbyr19ljCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Signs New Rule Stripping Abortion Clinics Of Federal Funding https://t.co/FvrJoIewBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naty_Krdnas Na que ver jajajajajaj 🤣🤣que tiene eso de clasista? De que forma lo estás viendo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanneInTexas It's someone else spamming it from my account. I'm so sorry. Trying to get rid of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiccoloFortuna Pat Flynn is a pretty solid dude. Can’t speak for everybody but they had a huge (positive) impact on me in high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up on something you really want. It’s difficult to wait, but worse to regret.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do politicians think the way to win Americans hearts and votes is to bad mouth our country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am beyond humbled to have seen Lisa Fischer sing last night. Truly one of the best voices I have ever heard in my… https://t.co/Xoq6vSMHos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rode some rides, ate a lot of good food, and laughed a whole lot 🍓 @ Florida Strawberry Festival https://t.co/iCvXi6PDNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sodmapef the truth is that I am not rich. I'm sorry I was ashamed to admit..]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are not going to silence me! This is about the lives of black children! When you walk around with a gun, it's t… https://t.co/oppu1HtGzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anonymously_all Interesting note! When I tried to RT this from my time line it said Deleted! Twitter censorship su… https://t.co/zQ289MookR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump OMG JUST STFU...DESPITE THE TOPIC, NOOOOBODY WANTS TO SEE YOU’RE FRIGGIN RAMBLING RHETORIC ANNNYMO… https://t.co/B4R7QkCq3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Funbungler @paulmac708 Nailed it in one! But I don’t get Ferrell either, so there’s that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLouieLouie Equal parts water and Apple Cider vinegar straight to the scalp for 30 minutes. You’re gonna need to… https://t.co/aTShOuBane]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bernie Sanders defends Ilhan Omar, says we must not 'equate anti-Semitism' with 'legitimate criticism' of Israel's… https://t.co/jxKaNPZN91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman Yes, a wonderful honor for black conservatives who don't listen to democrats whose actions  speak  louder than words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston 14 - Janitor - Warehouse worker - Cashier - Resident Assistant - Restaurant Dishwasher - Part Time… https://t.co/tf8phmPJKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, fellow resisters!!! My friend @PamUnderhill4 is new on Twitter and hates Trump as much as we do !! Please give her a follow 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here again at Leg Up Farmers Market! If you haven’t already, come down and try some samples of our refreshing craft… https://t.co/IjmIkZ1glF]]></document><document><![CDATA[After my car accident I’ve been to paranoid in cars 😂😂 i would’ve died in that seat 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOTVIKING I’m so tired I thought this asked if Funyuns deserve rights......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_vivalajulie @Evettexo Lmao me too makes me want to try for the girl 😂🤭 lmao omg Julie lol 😂  orrr have one 🤰🏻😍 I’m excited!!😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do we always talk about the importance of self care at work or in the movement space  but don’t talk or address… https://t.co/i8YHHjXFWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those that remain of him shall be buried in death: and his widows shall not weep. https://t.co/iTY0xiENo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storytelling in AR is Like Writing in 3D. #AR #storytelling #immersive #experiences]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is going to be a... crammed first campaign stop for @KamalaHarris in Myrtle Beach today.  There’s already a line… https://t.co/I82ca4dMqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m annoyed at how many of this year’s Oscar nominated animated shorts made me cry with overly sentimental music ov… https://t.co/xqqrvLdkHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyy, look! The balsamic loves OJ’s as much as we do! ❤️ @originaljoessj @ San Jose Original Joe's https://t.co/7Cv8mOtv5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken and waffles for the win! 🍗🥞 And my newest favorite coffee mug, of course. ☕ 🙌🙌 Thanks @morningrushatl for t… https://t.co/QNePYKmLHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amberwe85224886 My A-1‼️From @BigShotsNation to @HerdMBB https://t.co/aiBria2c8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrummondJeff @GracieLovesUSA @KeecoWang5 @Larryputt @Cindynine4 @Quin4Trump @TOMRJZSR @OutOfTheBlue201… https://t.co/rAverYufTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fansen @EdKrassen I’m 65 and we try to stay In touch. We do a family reunion every 4 years. I’m glad you all try,… https://t.co/xopwpOWC1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving forward doesn’t mean you HAVE to forget the past but if you’ve loved once you owe to your self to at least T… https://t.co/hGqMISRxj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoakley4 @BryanMa18455275 @Scavino45 @realDonaldTrump The legal way for a refugee to apply is to enter the coun… https://t.co/sfK4nERUca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ivan: let’s hot box danny’s car tio danny: let’s hot box michy’s car me: let’s go 🤷🏻‍♀️😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisToTheW @Barb81146 @MelissaFunGurl @ruthlesswench @MisleaderC @GrandmaVeteran @CunningSq16 @pleasure74… https://t.co/s4wARezTv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayoDotIE Aww peteeenn how are ya....I'm gone too long I live in New York now....Shure I love Mayo....Tis my HOME..when home..💚❤💚❤💚❤☘☘☘]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:41 in the morning and @Alexis_Santana8 is cooking me breakfast I think I may keep her🙃]]></document></documents></author>