<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of the great things about my new university? Near an awesome airport with lots of direct flights. #ASPA2019 her… https://t.co/pLDZS76zm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless Pope Francis, and all the #Jesuits around the world (including my brother...and my son) who help us see a… https://t.co/NsnZDwrmI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@18neverforget I don’t hate peoples Races, I just sometimes dislike people, no matter what color they are 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBuscaino Just watched your interview and noticed you are a Democrat. You do know the dems will not fix this, co… https://t.co/4BsGFCxZFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam and Dean Winchester meet NEGAN ☠️😂  @jarpad @JensenAckles @JDMorgan   #SupernaturaI #SPNfamily #DeanWinchester… https://t.co/fyeRo1h9jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Licensed Optician-Full-Time (Reynoldsburg #100) - https://t.co/8FeOGGYPnR… https://t.co/qLOu0xSq2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1947Farmall I don’t think there’s a policy only answer. This is a complex societal failure for which large corpora… https://t.co/Cu5Y5yaAzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willya02 - Thank for the toss at yesterday’s game! Meant the world to my 8 year old. https://t.co/b6xkl4mLPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakotaLeo @jjuston I don't remember that? Really? I need to rewatch that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you are a people holy to the LORD your God. The LORD your God has chosen you to be a people for his treasured p… https://t.co/oWkPIUCfcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forreal never drinking again 💔Last chance to get this exclusive baby: https://t.co/ehIvJvZxuR https://t.co/VeDkwGtnTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like I have this person inside of me that screams “stay out until the last possible minute you need to wake up… https://t.co/VVnrRlUXqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAillaud @pgreensoup Hey Jason!  Do you need to manually draw the grid, or are you overlaying an image that you have already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[X-Men Days of Future Past PSAs | The Mary Sue | Think happy thoughts!  Cerebro... #funniness #snicker #smirk… https://t.co/mPxAihfsZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skihouse2016 @MikeSeuffert @Sunlove23924632 @JacobAWohl It's all good, it's going to be wall to wall tomorrow anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIRLS 2nd DISTRICT BASKETBALL (15-13) McCracken County-41 (12-13) Caldwell County-47 End 3rd qtr.  Listen by: 📻 99.… https://t.co/qaHhoD91AD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a sure thing every time you grab a grease gun it’s empty, just a fact of life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some blood drawn at the doctor to check my vitamin D and a few other levels. I'm not afraid of needles, but t… https://t.co/2v0lJ2zIX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golfweek @K_m_Mitchell @PGATOUR @TheHondaClassic And he picked up about 6000 followers on twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly if Statesboro is bad for you it’s because you ran into some bad people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natureofdagame @MaddowBlog Exactly! He gets to inflate the valuation of one of his many properties by hundreds of… https://t.co/IGKMzBD8IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 I'm gonna have me a shot a scotch and get out the measuring tape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown meets with Art Rooney II, says 'both agreed that it is time to mov... https://t.co/ke4Q7TssrM via @pittsburghpg @seangentille]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to send them back please these illegals are effecting neighborhoods like mine, libs will not take them in, thi… https://t.co/Olyjfro4PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Aw shucks !  He should get in and muck things up more than they already are ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy preaching about telling the truth??!??  Omg 😲 @FoxNews @CNN @CNNPolitics @TuckerCarlson @seanhannity #tucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slumsof_stephee yay or nay bc i haven’t seen eye to eye with you in ANOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her strength is compelling and her confidence is an inspiration to all us. I am praying for her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Battle of the undefeated JV squads as @NGHSAthletics JV tennis teams travel to @brookwoodtnns. https://t.co/w1x13cn8Qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding kids right here that have brought tremendous #twppride to our school and community!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a Darrin's Dance Grooves *2*?! And I'm JUST learning about this?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masayang masaya akona #TheHalfSisters ang pumalit sa #IndayWillAlwaysLoveYou sa Sunday marathon ng @GMA_LifeTV. 😍… https://t.co/e1CJ31a2tK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Brazoria County Day. @ Hyatt Regency Austin https://t.co/TXtD04UyfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚢 Bon Voyage! I’m headed out today for a three day cruise! I won’t have reception while I’m on the ship so I won’t… https://t.co/gx046urky0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always5star @RitzCarlton @RoarLoudTravel @RoadtripC @TravelAtWill @MyVirtualVaca @MadHattersNYC @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/G6FrQKCHOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you tell them that if they’d have raked this wouldn’t have happened!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: 4 books I would recommend are Stormy Sea: Stories of Young Boat Refugees Picture Book by Mary Beth Leatherdale,… https://t.co/uLRJe5u685]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyMBB @lovellikc_ What happens when you’re the reigning POW?? We will find out Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarteenMorado Exactly. Striving for higher goals is something that is looked down upon especially in poor communit… https://t.co/6i3jbhoxz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se pierdan el Gran Jaripeo del And 2019 este proximo 24 de Marzo en Los 3 Potrillos antes "Nandos Wild Park" 413… https://t.co/5pPIep8p2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Punch Bowl Social - @punchbowldet in Detroit, MI https://t.co/wNnwGfKoeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What small crawling critter do the plump macrophages with chromatin that often condenses into slender wavy ribbons… https://t.co/Eqg8EJWOwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure miss Boone County Iowa is the spring time. https://t.co/XpJCrnffy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullitt5657 @MaraGay Yep. The next big opportunity that comes along will over look NYC as it has been shown to not be business friendly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this #CohenCongressionalTestimony like... https://t.co/IO58bXCK5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Kevin, I love the things you share! Great stories and I always question myself...would I do that...nope… https://t.co/55I6DbnBVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you much for prayers , head is a little better.. speaking tonight and 3 times tomorrow.. Gods good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teams weekly Friday Morning Study Group is exploring a new Futures Game. #design #futures #innovation… https://t.co/9Num8ppofm]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 80 gang members and associates indicted in joint LAPD-FBI takedown https://t.co/yon3Udcj2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess creating human minds is cool too, so the creative writing has its perks, but to be on the forefront of mapp… https://t.co/VVXIGJID2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@narahari24 @PiyushGoyal पीयूष जी खलीलाबाद बहराइच परियोजना से बहराइच के लोगों की परिवहन समस्याएं नहीं समाप्त हो न… https://t.co/A3Mjkqv2OB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy time change day! Spring ahead and get some daylight. A restful morning followed. Y several @premierleague gam… https://t.co/DuQY7JIVmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikacostell It must be like a weird week bc it’s been weird for everyoneb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a game between @PennMensLax and @NovaLacrosse both highly skilled. Sold out all over the field. Effort plays w… https://t.co/rQKKWOcEhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cook, I clean, I sing, and I dance for you @BuffaloSabres and this is how you do me? I think we need to take a br… https://t.co/MV3TFbfCdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanonUSAimaging  An Adult and juvenile Eagle today shot at a distance with the Canon 100-400 with a 1.4 extender b… https://t.co/zgRXKN3xLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighAnnPeter2 @larryzuares @Tabschools We have to look at the budget for next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandson Mason, hiding in the trunk of his uncle Joe’s car. He said he wants to go to California 😂✌🏼 @ Phoenix,… https://t.co/GoB88R9IlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vintage Wooden Arrowhead Necklace Native American Indian Head Headdress Profile https://t.co/xy9tzXPbjP via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[What has my life come to. I'm sitting outside my house debating if I should go in or not 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FergusFSU @CtCathCorner @noah_nonsense @PureSpew @Eschatologuy Was talking to @CtCathCorner. Curious if she shares… https://t.co/1G9kw7bh6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re on hold due to storm warnings. Stay tuned for updates on status of our 7 pm Mass for 2/24. https://t.co/QnsBu5KXvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachary_kramer My stress dreams usually involve an online course without a professor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SEPTA @SEPTA_SOCIAL standing at spring mill waiting for train to the city and a train just blows by us.  Was t… https://t.co/Z2ZeJK4jpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi gente ya puedes ver mi reacción al nuevo Trailer de #XMen #DarkPheonix en mi canal de YouTube #GeekyPopTrailers… https://t.co/h8O4lHR95U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LHHockey Unbelievable job on this today Dom! One thing I forgot about...I listened to Tavares media call after sig… https://t.co/aFbvSgjvNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 24:  Putting a little time aside for clean fun and good humor is very necessary to relieve the tensions of our… https://t.co/3n8mwG3361]]></document><document><![CDATA[PURO PINCHE EQUIPO AGROPECUARIO NOS GOLEA NO MAMEN HIJOS DE SU PUTA MADRE 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigga I GOT IT. Nigga swag hotter than a fuckin POCKET. She say she like me Girl you betta stop it. Up. Down. Aroun… https://t.co/tW5MD96Jly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to begin to think@primal vs advanced thought is a bad dichotomy (?) introduced by biologists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump TRUMP DOESN'T HOLD KIM RESPONSIBLE FOR OTTO'S DEATH!!! 😡😡😡😡 https://t.co/UPNI1OYW14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSowalla @JohnS877 @ACLU @carterforva The constitution protects a woman's right to get an abortion until roe vs Wade is overturned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going live with some @PlayOverwatch with my buddy @JeremyRWinter. Late night stream, Comp Maybe. SR sinking? Likely… https://t.co/epyvIUD0Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good shit here between Orin G Raver and @3MotherDuckers @GCWrestling_ #CodeOfTheStreets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberVeilsAZ Fantastic &amp; how is your weekend going &amp; hope your gaining strength &amp; feel a lot better 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and Bibi seem to be cut from the same cloth, but somehow I’m not surprised.  Their methods are similar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cabin in Big Bear for the weekend. ❄❄❄☃️🔥⛄❄❄❄ Capri's here too! @ Big Bear Lake, California https://t.co/AUn9yzeP0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntrider825 Yup everyone is still continuing to say we need to make defense a priority this summer🤦‍♂️ this forward group is atrocious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDJJames @KUTV2News Did I see it coming? Well...  ... There was a glowing article in the @sltrib this morning… https://t.co/3VydlJppwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I watch #baddayatblackrock I say how far have we as a society come from this kind of racist behaviour an… https://t.co/TBht85mP7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debera presentarse en la FAS  la Alcaldesa Rosario Quintero, de Navojoa, este prox viernes @MorenaenSonora… https://t.co/6QKuCPwGq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to The Bonniwell Music Machine by The Bonniwell Music Machine - Album Reviews, Credits, and Awards - AllMusi… https://t.co/Mywiuttqn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero que cuando vaya a RD pueda comer cangrejos y Chivo, tiempo sin comerlo, y si fuera en un patio, mejor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 I would of knocked that degenerate into never never land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional Pressure Washing and Soft Washing Services. Call or text 2818838470 @ Clean and Green Solutions https://t.co/peZaP0ET18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Papas and Beer 🍻 with the homie for memorial weekend, let’s get it 😎#DonOmar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone i can be with for rest of my life that will leave me alone most of the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been at the Palestra hundreds of times and tonight is definitely the first time I’ve seen someone smoking a cigar here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/ifnvYMfCwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I seen a ghost out Grandy lastnight and I don’t even believe in shit like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God for my preflight technician! My IFR could have went completely differently, just now.   Not wanting me to… https://t.co/Jhc1IXIH0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I think your staff is about as compotent as you are. You sounded like a" back bencher" in the hearings. Keep trying.#AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consuleduc Los eatadistas somos losi verdaderos patriotas queremos lo mejor para PR amamos nuestra patria cultura y nación]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yariii_25 I’ll move there with you so we can finally find our husbands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlysaAuriemma Very true, and that was why I jumped on board early in his campaign, but then I started looking clos… https://t.co/JmiwXKdLyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 3. Ultra rich, enriched by the Kremlin,  kremlin loyalists oligarchs.   Oligarchy is not very popu… https://t.co/YCduzpjCgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OtherSong #Is #Great #Song @ Walter's Walk - A Not for profit Counseling Agency https://t.co/AdoicHiGIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m working hard and having fun right now you guys and I absolutely love it.  And this isn’t where I am rn in my li… https://t.co/PR0CQov6Xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firefromthegods   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)… https://t.co/hsUFO3DB9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years  sho at (Frostburg)@Nigerianscamsss got me hip to drake first with take care and then so far gone , Change… https://t.co/mUfgbxiqTt]]></document></documents></author>