<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Look who came to work today!!! So excited 🥰😍 #lovingtouchanimalclinic #goats #happytuesday #happytuesdayeveryone… https://t.co/eox97tspJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: the cloud macchiatos taste disgusting and y’all should just drink black coffee instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneyschnoor @FactsOfSchool that’s what happens when you ignore me 🙄 smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSueHomes Thank you so much, Sue! ❤️ So excited and definitely thankful for you, the planning crew, IPA, et al fo… https://t.co/m09OBYhjVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HungryTrucker @bgirl0001 It does sound like a recipe for heartburn !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ironmagnolia I think our responsibility as white people is to broadly and unequivocally support reparations by 1.… https://t.co/q2UVmC6Cep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Maya Hamzy on being selected to the Spring Valley Viking Cup, presented by @SCUnited_FC  All Tournament Team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knitting an ear warmer from a pattern my friend created and sells, and watching daburntbisket stream. #streaming… https://t.co/pLto2RxgPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@iowastatepatrol tells me a fire truck was hit near the Huxley exit while responding to an accident. No word if th… https://t.co/9P9Aa3carg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I watch workaholics the more I realize @UncleBlazer is the funniest guy on the planet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fish Tacos and Margarita Pizza!!! Already enjoying the food of South Beach!!! #springbreak2019 @ South Seas Hotel,… https://t.co/rMBcqbWf7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: I have accepted @MrPetrotta’s challenge to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews, just… https://t.co/MgF6h9cGnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluezUSA Ooo, think he’d talk to us? That’s a great story! https://t.co/q4F7YJELhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s say it again...”All educators must share responsibility for teaching our ELs...” @ESOLMentor   🎤 drop! 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god I’m on PTO this week or I’d need atleast 4 days off to mourn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseHBeaumont @ICanBeOrg @messageheard @lamornaeliza @langfordprimary @ninamohanty @WomenintheCity… https://t.co/R9Ofgz8n8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hoping all progressive and liberal leaning thinkers consider at least twice what they see posted about candidat… https://t.co/16WUmbDW9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holcomb says maybe he didn’t stress enough that they need to call, write lawmakers. “We’ll Be hyperactive “ on this… https://t.co/qXuNHWpqzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was great! I got to learn no much more about makeup and the the beauty industry! glamourbyhosway… https://t.co/R0lvZvs5KH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night to meet the Third Committee negotiators. A big thank you to the Mountain group for organizing qu… https://t.co/iDktwTIigw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy day cuddle snuggles 🌧🥰🐻 #americanstaffordshireterrier #pittbullsofinstagram #staffygram #rainraingoaway… https://t.co/TSPstRBwwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_itzaes And I need to stop spending money like I’m an heiress and more like I have a 9-5.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danfreimark @OHSUDoernbecher I will still participate somehow some way, thanks for the connection :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to forgive yourself. You did the best you could at the time. #spiritualjourney @ Redeemer's A.M.E. Zion C… https://t.co/9Vx2o7vGBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird coincidence when I found out today that my friend @BiscuitsWorld is owned by @HalfOnionInABag ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished rewatching the first 6 seasons 2 days ago.  Today's 5AM viewing is back to S1E1. Yeah...❤❤ #TeamArrow… https://t.co/jywxkXpzwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful 💖. Gorgeous Sunrise sky this morning ! #delraybeach #grateful #beautifulsky #sunrise #peace #floridaliving… https://t.co/impDOCuf9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may be getting older and I may be carrying some extra weight in my short frame BUT I do not wear leggings in Wal-Mart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s beautiful out and I’m buried under a mountain of homework and reading. So over it! https://t.co/c6dbSWljOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Rings...Like? #whatdiddebbiedo #rings #jewelry#etsyseller #etsyshop #jewels #toptags #jewel #fashion #gems… https://t.co/IVQoXInHEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyHatch13 @Proud2BeAtPride Thank you for joining us! I ❤️ having peeps from Volusia with me! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JP_ComplianceJD @NicoleAuerbach @JeffZillgitt Agreed—will be better for all parties I imagine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Trump et al are guilty of everything he accuses others of - textbook grifter tactics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton River  is 3 years old, and his latest stay at Riley Children’s Hospital has now been since December 2… https://t.co/KZHs4GXrS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[VMin fam, how we doing?   #bts #vmin #vliv #VliveBTS https://t.co/hWnYn9lHqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t a frat party invite. This is embarrassing and disconcerting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have fallen into the category of people that only got 1/2 the tax refund we've gotten in previous years. We had… https://t.co/RJiwLo05Pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paging @ArtistCenter I notice why less exposure for Pauline Mendoza such as sps, studio 7,Eat Bulaga, Wowowin, othe… https://t.co/ruBJULaWQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the kinda people that are never around as long as everything in their life is good but come running when everything is going wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babies! As this day hold a special place for the both of us. He never forgets...2/18/98 bblaw @ Montgomery, Virginia https://t.co/HWYS4JKwvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do we want students to become global citizens?  Michelle has embedded social emotional learning INTO a global c… https://t.co/nWEECVCEas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowieCarrShow @SandraKayWard5 @BreitbartNews Omg!! Was waiting for the blame game. Funny but many have difficulty… https://t.co/1aOh7R48yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @yuhbabyarii are listening to @sammywilk rn and we’re going through a lot😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoycottUtah @realDonaldTrump I second that 🌏✌💜....I'm so excited...I know lots he's going to say..but I want to hear him confess...😁😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnGuillero @peta Just FYI it's '90s not 90's which is why written out it's "nineties" not "ninety's" . . . 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binanguyener @xoJordannicolee He said they asked him for his last for of his social and that’s how he knew instant… https://t.co/He172hrKK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti #60Minutes #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #MarALardass https://t.co/ZgI8rOWNzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving a vehicle from Spain-  I realize I need to brush up on my kilometer translation 😳 #landroversantana]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ended up going to my Primary Care doctor for OBJECTIVE family planning advice and she was able to include a hormo… https://t.co/IBtVyS9Sjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[lately i’ve been taking care of me... and this is the happiest i’ve been in a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how me and the uncle were talking about indica vs sativa at the dinner table like it was nbd 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever think “life is but a dream” is a weirdly existential lyric, for its context?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanberdan A friend of mine got into a fender bender with Kirstie Alley this week. There's a strangely large numbe… https://t.co/XHXw662O7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnySpice11 @yvngryvd @bayliekathleen Lol “footnote” my phone don’t even know what Fortnite is 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkelseeey_ @weirdradopinons @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley https://t.co/tkFMeRV97g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamlambert #TheOscars fabulous performance by Adam Lambert and Queen!  What an incredible voice and talent!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I’m always gonna stink at drafting. It’s one of my fave formats, too. #mtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw 3:13 at 33 seconds. Which I’ve been seeing 313 so much and what’s even crazier is I was born at 3:13 pm 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s all better now! Girl’s week in NYC.... ⁦@ThePierreNY⁩ https://t.co/EnqvwDAd2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Atrium Health in #Charlotte, NC. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs lik… https://t.co/UgpcJRroyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh, I feel personally victimized by every horoscope account I’ve ever followed and I’m pretty sure that’s on brand so carry on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeDoNotLearn73 Get real - the person complaining about an Islamic preacher would be arrested for racism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Is this what you call health care?  This Arizona abortion worker says there "may be movement" after t… https://t.co/gD9kZcuPD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops! @MichaelCohen212 suspects #Collusion as most of us sane people do...#RussianCollusion https://t.co/1PNmYLny5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇🏻👇🏻👇🏻 this is the first time I’m hearing news of Jennifer Lawrence in a long time which tells me I follow the corr… https://t.co/WsUZgp2c4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only question left to ask after the @RichmondDems meeting tonight...what @rbrexperience restaurant are we hitting u… https://t.co/3C9jYmIPhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen SHE DOESN'T GIVE A SH@$! About anyone but herself and her meal ticket!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[unvaccinated kids in the hospital for 57 days???? yeah sounds about right! VACCINATE YOUR KIDS SO THIS DOESNT HAPPEN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my back &amp; neck pains would go away. I think I might have abby beat me with a piece of sugar cane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir @BernieSanders @TheDemocrats @SenSanders If he joins the party then let him run]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJonAbramson @MattWalshBlog Yea, that's a perfectly reasonable response to this.  All these people blowing it up… https://t.co/eTJGeBf9EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @EricTrump Anyone supporting @realDonaldTrump has no business criticizing anyone on anti semitism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Bullying is not acceptable, not they need to pay the price.  Hopefully it will stop others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extrañando a los que no pueden tuitear porque están sin luz... Lanzando mil #madurocoñoetumadre por los que están en los hospitales...  💛💙💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onedaylight @krassenstein @AuthorJackieMc @realDonaldTrump Which actually proves they’re purposefully sowing disin… https://t.co/VIEFDVLjbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the awesome @JasonGrill for being our #SXSWKC emcee for the day! @GrillNationShow #SXSW⁠ ⁠ #SXSW19 https://t.co/fSY9mTBEF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @GeneralMills for finally bringing fruity shapes back to Trix! I had a legitimate moment in the grocery s… https://t.co/riV0OEvB7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[From #CoastToCoast, #LiberalismIsAMentalDisorder (Bonus slag on Swallwell included!) 😆  Ocasio-Cortez and Newsom: S… https://t.co/UJxhKtaWNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: Almost got ICE'd! 😡Not cool to park in the charging parking spot just because it's convenient to the door. I'm… https://t.co/OfLq2cGXQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend from school just got engaged to Brittany Snow Which is literally the coolest thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkznd4 Every damn day. I think they like to feel “woke” - at least in my area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be a guest at the annual #chinesenewyear banquet of Lin Sing Assoc. 119 years young! W. Senator Brian Ka… https://t.co/VoE8nfd3Yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard someone come out of an apartment near me yelling fuck you bitch and your trash fucking friends, I’m ne… https://t.co/omw05cZ1sU]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 more weeks of school and 15 more weeks until baby. Let’s go!!!! 🤱🏼👩🏼‍🏫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJCoastExp I was.  ^_^.  Yeah, hanging with a Bay Area driver right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is mommy supposed to sleep??? #momlife #atxmom #rescuecatsofinstagram #atx #rescue #atxlife #texas… https://t.co/P0CUnDAdO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing what I love to do, hoping it helps do my part for #betterenergybetterworld #ElectricVehicles #mncities… https://t.co/uw1l2rmlPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett I will never forget what you said about Mexican immigrants on June 15, 2015. I am… https://t.co/xizluVHSsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toftetech @jnepsund_VVelem @VistaViewElem @ISD191 @RahnArtsTech Sure! 😊📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[And You need to stop covering for a monster! Your actions will come back to bite you in the ass! @Jim_Jordan your p… https://t.co/cuwMzNWYq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marquisee_3 @shelovesrichhy @Joseph23_Thomas @tjohnson9565 @ItsssQuayyy @iatemykitten IMAGINE GETTING MAD WHEN SOM… https://t.co/bXYp1sfSAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton This country is now a horrifying place to live. It’s like the Handmaid’s Tale. Escape while you can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m just admiring how cute you are but not letting you forget you can be a bitch sometimes”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My battery is low and it’s getting dark.”   Thank you, wee robot. You did good. #OpportunityRover #RIPOpportunity… https://t.co/Ccl3xrDe24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the fantasy suit week is while I’m on spring break with my parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm plotzing over @ewarren's childcare plan. I've decided to postpone writing my own book so I can run for presiden… https://t.co/GBZf6yqkwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atvk55 I would buy this, except that he does it about 50% of the time, regardless of when I walk him and how recen… https://t.co/nEj8yGcDga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road trip on Valentine’s Day? Perfect opportunity for me to listen to sad music and stare out the window, pretending I’m in a movie 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abigale_hamlin Bish I already have my ticket! You know you’re next on my list tho 😝😘💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @JaybeeStewee And missing from Texas......@SenTedCruz  So, so sad.]]></document></documents></author>