<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Finally Wilson Chandler lol didn't we want him like in 2013 😂 #ClipperNation #Clippers]]></document><document><![CDATA[INT. BREAKROOM - DAY Student council sponsors a breakfast for faculty with array of breakfast items and a plethora… https://t.co/AP82UnjFjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Arvin Teachers Association invites you to come, mention us at checkout, and eat at the Pizza Rev on Gosford tod… https://t.co/gupHLtlgmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me tee-hee. #comedy #tee-hee #grin #comic https://t.co/4mzl5PSNPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLaurenRuby @MGriffith2015 @Andy literally losing brain cells while watching]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeministaCanada @womandefy @JeanHatchet #clusterfuck https://t.co/zHmJSXaQ5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veo mis fotos y por cierto... A mis amigas que les preste mi ropa #DevuelvanLoRobado 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I think she is extremely well qualified.  Wasn't it nice to hear someone actually answers the questio… https://t.co/ihySwS4vtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is hilarious. Talked Like Lovers And Laughed Like Best Friends Pictures, Photos, and Ima… https://t.co/4ZauX9R4Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mamaw1724 @thekathyjane @brennan_elliott No, Psula, Btennan said that incorrect info.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton 1. Its It's a shame how those  adults manipulated those children. 2.  I feel like the senator should ha… https://t.co/YBcQK4y1FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their first album together should be they top songs from like 10 years ago all redone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg Caught you last year on @crookedmedia. Each time I hear you speak I’m more impressed. You exude hope… https://t.co/yHMVhxeyWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trent_PhD Exactly!!!!!! If I start saying I’m from Atlanta ppl would side eye me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve needed my elbow tattooed for like a year.... it’s time to fuckin do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voices of LC will be at First Baptist Church Pine Prairie tonight at 5 PM! It is free and we would love for you to… https://t.co/vyKODiWHeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!!ATTN LADY BEARCAT FANS!!!  There has been a change in date and time on the second round of the Regional Tourname… https://t.co/jnEHkaWRq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone the most amazing commercially driven holiday ever!  😘❤️😘. I love you ! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/T3wWETislo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else’s Freeform @FreeformTV  app not working!!! Wtf I’m missing @ShadowhuntersTV #shadowhunters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably a bad sign that instead of getting out of bed I just turned on a collection of the most melancholy Radiohead songs huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalFamily @wabbey Beautiful hat, your Majesty.  Have a wonderful day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickgillespie @realDonaldTrump Yes they topped it! didn’t you see Warren awkwardly drink a beer 🍺 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WM0005 @McconneyMichael You know the definition of "antichrist" according to the bible right? The literal son of t… https://t.co/qIL9EKQAEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stills from opening the mold. Next step - making soap and pouring it in the mold. Mountain soaps on the way... nebr… https://t.co/KXANZyqzfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing an hour of sleep...#DaylightSavingsTime 👎🏼 https://t.co/3wCehW5AFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤘 @EmluvsSPNMarvel @coloradogal12 @Trucklady53 @fredsfam @kayb625 @Hiyaboopers @spacecowgyrl @AZGrammy5 @Nnja11… https://t.co/4TJ0Kypy57]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sleepover 👯‍♀️   dirtym0ss melsdrivein #melsdrivein #orangeshake #allthefriedthings #bffs #besties… https://t.co/vnRQlw20er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz you are a despicable and pathetic "man". You offer nothing but slime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Lindenbanks 😂 like , i be so uninterested &amp; not here for it at all !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the amazing volunteers at the #WOI2019 that make this event possible.  I look around the room and see… https://t.co/lAQAqA8P2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No you're not--crossings have never been higher and it's your fault President Putz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gunna start smacking Juuls and Ecigs out of people’s hands if they blow their nastiness on me https://t.co/fV24DvMXuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RioVistaMS Congratulations Rio Vista Condors! Keep continuing to reach for higher learning in science and math!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlatironDistrict #Manhattan #NYC 🥶 (@ Flatiron District - @flatironny in New York, NY) https://t.co/fWfIbxVNHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog started choking and out of nowhere my dad goes “teddy shut the fuck up”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait did you not just say two days ago that she WAS the reason your family broke up!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, I learned to play Halo in a arcade tonight, actually liked it once I got the hang of it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road conditions are improving in some parts of Wells this morning. But other spots are still pretty treacherous.… https://t.co/oWkYPfro7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato Trump needs to give it up, he is so paranoid. I don’t have enough room to list all the groups out… https://t.co/GSPSUKroE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a hilarious comic strip about natural hair. Enjoy! "Let’s get this straight" by Tall... https://t.co/qFUaoPyByg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone in China is using my debit card that I haven’t swiped in years 🙄 https://t.co/n4tPLGdjXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harleysulak It’s because you are awesome and amazing @harleysulak. So proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Lets just ignore her from now on...she is a fool. I just wish she would keep her mouth shut...not a g… https://t.co/sOXKlshPdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of town, Chicago is... 😍🥰😎🤩🙃🙂😊😄🤪 #chicago #june2017 #june #illinois #me #thebean #vacations #turisteando… https://t.co/sU0JIN9GMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New episode drops tomorrow morning! The Hollywood Actor Podcast speaks with @katelyn_gault and we learn how to refr… https://t.co/CoiawY5Kao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler Throw it away HARD with the lid  off so no child tries to save it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk: Elon your lawyer on retainer should read and approve any public statement you in your capacity as CEO of… https://t.co/Ol6iCE1aLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanfelicity @ValMackinnon @retail_recruit @CharlieAngusNDP @Puglaas @Sheila_Copps What is the basis for your com… https://t.co/rO8dmDa3Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representing my @LAKings while out and about on Waco today 🥰 https://t.co/dNDLvvlXuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teacher said American Samoa and now I can’t stop thinking about Girl Scout cookies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the baddest bitch alive @Rihanna 🎈 #RihannaAppreciationDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YOsinpokerface Donde es acá?  Yo la busqué aquí enEEUU y está en cervezas artesanales]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadddykat_ just wanna have love again &amp; grind an not have to worry about nothing but that &amp; God. the new me is ready ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[Job 1 of the two jobs I’m expected to do at the same time today. #TeacherLife #SpellingBee @ Tri-c Metro https://t.co/YHNXkel9fD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitching a ride up the mountain on one of the rope tows at this awesome tubing park in Quebec. #quebec quebecauthen… https://t.co/EPa2UgPBXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can hold our reading thoughts on sticky notes to share them later with our partners. Loved the “yuck” sticky not… https://t.co/iFSouN9g9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewportLost @riteaparty @DanJGuilmette “Anti Christian teachings of the Tea Party” WTH?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cutestcouples @aspca Rocky and Twinky 💕💕 @ Malden, Massachusetts https://t.co/bbMYyL7qn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on S Chase #Pulaski #WI  #realestate https://t.co/Xul5JgW42N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine actually thinking @Pouyalilpou is better than @TeamSESH LMAO https://t.co/LTiQk4sGfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gladly accepted a challenge from @Anj_Hendricks  to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no reviews… https://t.co/BzAsZJ6DVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaleyCox1571 @HensleyNascar24 @low_nascar @low_nascar2 @dega_boy_87 @NASCAR @KEMMOCupSeries @JJmachine24 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I get called Stephanie more often then I get called Stacie... it’s at the point where I just have to be cool with it 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XavierTheatre Thanks for doing this show! I love it and my brain has been needing a #NextToNormal fix for weeks. T… https://t.co/iTPMh40vPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[[VIDEO] Funnel Hacking LIVE 2019  https://t.co/nL1E4qvwtL  @clickfunnels @russellbrunson]]></document><document><![CDATA[they rearranged the tables in the break room at work today and I had an anxiety attack. what happened to my consist… https://t.co/uFjUn0EG1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Oh Lindsay! DO SHUT UP! You should listen to what Cohen said. It was far more imp… https://t.co/gRpLXM1hl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The evidence of multiple crimes is overwhelming @reslDonaldTrump just to name a few; #moneylaundering… https://t.co/yd2Fhzkctl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpeco1 @Lexa_Merica @marymauldin @maryllewis53 @HoggleJames @JedidahJXH @JanetCates2 @Gunpiper1 @Belizaleyva1… https://t.co/itTHUsIf0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Zoe in solid colors, choose the color of your preference and we make it for you 👙 #onepiece #trikini #twopiece… https://t.co/upiCKae7kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve worked at the same place for 6 years as a waitress , witch doesn’t make applying for jobs easy .  I don’t want… https://t.co/WF0EeVkZ5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsHour Great, start riots in the classroom; don’t study biology because it is a liberal plot.... it is about stupid and compliant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA It does pay much much better for very very few. IOW: art is extremely unequal. In #DarkMatter, criti… https://t.co/sZSi3K0W2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OES_smcps Thank you, Ms. Carlson, for your hard work with our students.  They looked like they had fun. https://t.co/Nq09F91a5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not quite done! #yumm #atx #bread #tx #goodness @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/72eaLTqbsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone come with me to six flags one day when I’m back home in two weeks pls and thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq @GOPLeader Yep. Done. Somebody write this down to show these fuckers when they conveniently forget the… https://t.co/GaNYCGJyoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE THE LORD!!❤ @ Pilot Mountain, North Carolina https://t.co/p475JbEoUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northernbruja wishing you prosperity to get the tats you want and be in more comfortable skin &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoppy and grapefruity. Love it - Drinking an Elvis Juice by @BrewDog @ Perkasie, PA  — https://t.co/vwbiuLU04u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even joking, the half-lashes from @xoBeautyShop are such a game changer for me! Not a regular lash wearer,… https://t.co/9DmgossWYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomHall It is so awesome...Just wish-others realized how vital WOLVES are to our ECOSYSTEM..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahParnellL1 A pitchers worth a thousand words. Idk why i felt the need to say that wow I’m sorry anyway ur beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao niggas always want you to be the one to fix them. I ain’t ya therapist boy lmaooo go on now]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best VDays are the single ones time and time again... 😘❤ @ The Shaskeen Pub and Restaurant https://t.co/7QBMeV5ylh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesEary @AncientAliens I believe in illegal aliens 😉😂 https://t.co/g0YlNc1NNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMTheHighway @brothersosborne John and TJ brought their A game to St. Aug. @RustonKelly did a great job as the op… https://t.co/gkT9RWPZV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @Cibouletteetcie !  A toast to #greatfriends #wonderfulfood #downtownmidland #frillydrinks and… https://t.co/YbppX7QiDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[re-forming the jonas brothers seems like a last ditch effort for the jonas brothers going broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would really go home this weekend.. but I promised myself that I wouldn’t 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve wanted to share this story about how much you can achieve when you work together.....and believe in the purpo… https://t.co/lsoV6nJO09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codywager15 I just started on Saturday and I'm on season 4 already. It's unhealthy but the binge is strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linda: This guy's been waiting. I'm running out of excuses so I told him our regular chef is away and you're his du… https://t.co/zKmOqfsmr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomHall @ShannonReports Waited way to long before hitting the throttle 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moconchobhair @devonzuegel Wow. That is a ton of money. I wonder where it was. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’d written three albums’ worth of incredible stuff. But I knew I couldn’t get up on stage night after night and p… https://t.co/qrLfhp1XTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In progress. Such a pleasure and blast with this piece. Warrior women. Thanks again for looking #tattoox… https://t.co/2MF2Sd4A3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrific choice. Teaching this book is a meaningful memory for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the Chinese food in Ireland. Yes, this is a very NICHE tweet. If you know you know, ya know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can do anything you put your mind to.” Come take a class with me this week! First one is always free. 🤗💪🏽… https://t.co/QHOzkwAQpi]]></document></documents></author>