<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LanaWWE Ok love you both. But please do not start the “better then Austin” stuff yet. I look forward to your futur… https://t.co/4W3Pn9EaE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBallgame1 @BradyJustBetter @glovesandhat @lebronisgod2 @tombrady_NFL IN ADDITION, THE NFL WILL BE DISCREET ABOUT… https://t.co/bmuJCPdO4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Trump is your President too. Please respect what he does for the country. He's not getting paid. But you can bet you are...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguin ISD has the best Child Nutrition Department. We are so thankful for the great team that is with us at camp t… https://t.co/xUHgWRMtTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Hoyt3 @NYIslanders They were 9-1 when both were in the lineup with the 1 loss being a 3rd road game in 4 nights. Let's find out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjcarjo1 @TheSublime @cnni And despite mankind's contribution to the already inevitable cycle, it's blown WAY out… https://t.co/433j9aCk6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BanorteEscucha sigue sin funcionar tuvservicio, después de hacer clic en el botón continuar, la aplicación se pone… https://t.co/4kIK7rnBE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xolotl @rschon I choose to interpret that based on this reference https://t.co/51gkVBUqOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pencils and inks on this awesome to draw commission request today. Colors tomorrow! #nickjustusart #sketch… https://t.co/9oDk7GFcwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids know THERE IS NO PLANET B and they deserve answers.   https://t.co/R9Nc4NqIOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Slowly but surely,financial Genius POTUS Trump ruining,bankrupting the USA Nation...!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New group of Bulldog tricksters. 7th graders 1st track meet ever. First day to actually see a track. https://t.co/P0P3HJMgo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed home this AM (at @TheRambleHotel in Denver, CO) https://t.co/Pf7Pnh1nMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myqueen #myrock #mywife @ Ms. Tootsie's Soul Food Cafe https://t.co/0dWpYG8MEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreeneTurtle_NB Ohhh nice! Can't wait to check it out! https://t.co/N1fMbrD7ap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLupica I was in contact with him on and off for several years thanks to my pieces on Tony C and the Win it For… https://t.co/UGciRHLXol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CKPolansky 26 members came. They are trying to do business quick before someone leaves and they lose their quorum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google’s Martin Splitt Explains How JavaScript Sites are Indexed by @MattGSouthern https://t.co/R7emklo8qJ https://t.co/DtbsGeujxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonPretty1 @DBloomberg Uh, Jon, your dealers in my house are going to have a hit put out on you when they find out… https://t.co/6RXvnsCL6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just backed Critical Role: The Legend of Vox Machina Animated Special on @Kickstarter https://t.co/1TvnRBSVbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nirvana How can someone with a family, so talented, smart and accomplished be so sad? Sometimes I think the world… https://t.co/CKm2FEDKYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stadium ready for biggest event at @soldier_hollow since 2002 #Olympics. @biathlonworld World Cup today.… https://t.co/YYh9r466n0]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I hate my birthday, I’m really happy so many people wished me a happy bday just minutes into it. I love y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGrigg1 @RonJeffries @Agile_Hulk Likewise for parameter groups. If they are common companions, that probably means something]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to drop my car off for service. Taking a few moments to keep up on @AndrewYNg’s AI for Everyone course on… https://t.co/o4emLBRJV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have a problem with what he said he can play for the 49ers this season let’s go Mr. Big Chest @AB84]]></document><document><![CDATA[The SNC Lavalin influence in Canada is far greater than Canadians may realize!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. This could help. (Henderson et al., 2007, p. 47). #ecumsa https://t.co/HGZskvp3Qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[LATE NIGHT BODEGA ACTION!!! #inspire #life #love #icandobetter #strongmind  #proud #wealth #active #strong… https://t.co/o9TEnSe25j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up earlier than normal on a Sunday.  So much I wanna do today but first it’s coffee, laundry and treadmill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jahh_Luciano word i feel like i’m in a shen yun play. one spin in already the production super drippy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njnativetongue @HistoryJumpman @AngDOOM he got banged on so bad he had to laugh about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways, Anything I’ve ever posted is a joke, most my pics from google. Ion do no type of drugs or even toutched a… https://t.co/YHe966yC7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossAMarchand @tpapres @VGKDefender @USPS terrible hockey team? hope you put more work into your job than your hoc… https://t.co/JB8v1R6Okn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now it’s gone! Oh my god so good!🤡 @ Broadmoor Bistro https://t.co/dxnUppLB6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saltystephs @javiertoo_ @jaccckkie_ Since my nigga giving trips away let me catch one too 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok who’s ready for the Instagram post about this right after they get smoked? 😂😂😂. Waiting on you @KingJames https://t.co/v4fB9XiC0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom What a coincidence! I just called Maddow’s office a couple nights ago to try to explain you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wiz Entertainment/Broad Streets Records Presents.. “The Lost Tapes” ALL Songs Produced And Mixed By N.O.Wiz At Fran… https://t.co/P2GPj6mJEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebjross @eSkilliam @jackblack it's a secret jack black retro gaming channel with other goofing off and I'm here for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woy Followed by a cool late ‘00s shower with the guy from #Chuck who is also #CaptainMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[...Not only was the interview a "professional" milestone as far as the PODCAST was concerned, but it has validated… https://t.co/XPZUt9ukcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with amazing people, create memories and enjoy life. Celebrating amazing person and our friend… https://t.co/5aexzMr1QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Portobello mushrooms are the official mushroom of the Trump presidency. Like his crowds, size matters (to him)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLBallinger Lol 😂 I think I got your intent, sir.  Just an opinion.  Just like yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheQuartering found a little somethin, for ya. Enjoy. https://t.co/2sUeDNOwxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @AOC Google "represent us" Get involved with locals to change election laws in your state. The only… https://t.co/4NPJU1BioI]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if to underscore her point, over 50 retired military leaders just released a letter urging US re-entry into the… https://t.co/JZI03d7Qbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lebanesesaywhaa So gross. And she’s gonna be a doctor. A racist doctor. Yikes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradenGall and @deemason85 please don’t take a morning off at the same time again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night that I was receiving hugs and congratulations from creators I look up to at a premiere for… https://t.co/8vOriwkaIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is some seriously good pizza. #valentine #date #jilly @ Rosati's Pizza https://t.co/WmoeutISpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day hunting with Blue Ridge and good Georgia friends rhettb22 and john.mcneill.9693 #mfha #hounds #hunting… https://t.co/viCzi3t4Yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roomway Never said anything of the sort. Cincinnati didn't even come up]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it is Not Spoken. Children are Furniture that Eats. Out the Styma they saw something. The Parents don't want sai… https://t.co/Amuh99FE2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siiiidb @serenawilliams Tough keyboard guy...come to Texas.  I can fix all your mommy issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hadji911_ @Gingersnap_ And the libs are saying we don't need a wall! Just more evidence, they could not care less… https://t.co/llF58npOpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork Humpty-Trumpty sat on a wall.   Humpty-tRumpty had a great fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krystalball @realDonaldTrump @PressSec  Donnie dumpo is a complete and utter failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for prayer warriors. I am physically and emotionally exhausted. Would you pray for me tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a time I got dumped on Valentine’s Day and it did not effect me in any way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like it’s license test season #operatorslicense #ontag https://t.co/vzIS4JSZJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realThrilliam 1. Dune 2. Cryptonomicon 3. All I Really Need to Know I Learned in Kindergarten]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥💥Just Listed💥💥📍 11138 Garden Grove Ave. Porter Ranch Gorgeous 3 bedroom single story ranch 🏊‍♂️pool home with an a… https://t.co/EtxudMVpEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders As a DC resident, I would like to encourage all presidential candidates to cut down on “all 50 state… https://t.co/1ULi9VJpUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InfyPathfinders #CSed #MakerEd #Elemaker #Makerspace #HourofCode #CS4all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHolmerr @josiahfitness It’s easy to defeat Joe 6pack. Just don’t drink and learn something over the weekend. Also lift heavy weights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brooklyn is having an amazing year this year...compared to last year 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[My college baseball rankings (top 10) after opening weekend:  1. LSU (3-0) 2. UCLA (3-0) 3. Florida (3-0) 4. Vander… https://t.co/8lRHRfEGqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya llegue a Miami en Pisco y Nazca Ceviche Gastrobar https://t.co/pq8V7ZtBzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing that I really love about the MTA is how as rush hour approaches they really force you to take a breath an… https://t.co/SXZVBFBhZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanMNarroA @CESARMTZ42 @OficialSarapero @LaNaveVerde @LigaMexBeis Y excelente persona y amigo, el tetracampeón con guacamayas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Swanson @RepAndyBiggsAZ @RepMattGaetz #TrumpStank doesn’t wash off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 28 #ValueChallenge February is #Value month. Please share and show how you value Time by completing the followi… https://t.co/yLEhsqbjy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Lipson @abesilbe @mkoplow @PopChassid @BurtonJM Very important point you (+@BurtonJM) made of how Kahane+his… https://t.co/P0R3sWqRWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OppoSuits @TeamRWB @GarySinise @Shinesty @OppoSuits I only know how to be 100% AMERICAN 🇺🇸🦅🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialchilli is here in Austin next Monday guest speaking during SXSW! With every fiber of my being I refuse to miss it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Competition The ZK No.2 Certified Swiss Made Automatic Diver and GMT Watch. Enter &amp; #RT for a chance to #win:… https://t.co/hBduOmeD3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was the ace of my all-time favorite team, #AmericasTeam, the 1955 Brooklyn @Dodgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Progressives are Already Sick of Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez https://t.co/t7rdMlKvXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i guarantee you every mf that drives after smokin does the exact opposite of this 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely night at @disneysprings. Sunset + hot air balloon + lovely location = a great night!  #wdwcastlife #castlife… https://t.co/j74XXav5Iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel the music  #missingpersons #missingpersonsband #dance #music #kidsdancing @ Berea, South Carolina https://t.co/GLOrsYw8Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every major religion predicts End Times, the final battle between Good and Evil. Does it start with a beautiful man… https://t.co/6DNU8o1jVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t have to switch djs every other 30 minutes, if a nigga is on fire,  let that muthafucka burn!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traumatic_one @natasha367b @AlanGresov @SenSanders Son's Experiment in grade school. Measured the heat generated b… https://t.co/YVwegZKP8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markschleff Looks like the game we’re going to May 20th vs. the Phillies was a good choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where you eat when it’s late, you’re hungry and haven’t had dinner because of #BizTravelProblems 🤷🏽‍♂️  @McDonalds https://t.co/nPPT96gGPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekMaberry @CowboysNation @akafreethought @my_e81 @Jeff_LJ_Lloyd @Marcus_Mosher Just like I take you and your 400 followers to heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan are you suffering from money lagg sir, are you paid in some form of foreign currency, you should do a… https://t.co/Xj26gC5sra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @politico Well this can only mean 1 thing thing: Mueller report is showing nothing happened and you… https://t.co/sklD4YLphJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobGrebe Totally agree, especially since it’s a fact that bacterial infections can piggyback on viruses. Gimme tha… https://t.co/sZhbq4sFqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for visiting me at school, Dad. #ucla #powell #losangeles #la @ UCLA https://t.co/gxpmNuYtA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 let’s all agree that @PGATOUR players should be allowed to clean the mudballs in the center of the fairway]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is one lawgiver and judge, he who is able to save and to destroy. But who are you that you judge your neighb… https://t.co/kiZJbKsMMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimByersTravel Other research. Toronto to Paris on Aeroplan. 60K points, $730 in taxes. I've paid less than that t… https://t.co/CdAhSpKPhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Your true colors are showing. The true party stays with Lincoln. The rest is history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peteholmes If it has to end, that was fitting. Thanks for the laughs. Come to Chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Fort Family......no school today so stay safe if you have to get out on the roads. Stand by for what does a Pr… https://t.co/Xoi88MyWPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannon_schulte I started watching it on Amazon Prime during our #SnowMageddon2019 days off. Shocked  by this today]]></document></documents></author>