<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s so weird seeing plastic bags in SA at H-E-B since Austin doesn’t use the plastic bags anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is this “tea” that everyone seems to be talking about? Did this become a thing the same time salty did?]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should not expect any privilege in return, no security, no type of promotion. Rather, in this life they will h… https://t.co/vXX07pc0jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen “After Life” on Netflix yet?  https://t.co/7Vmu7SVPaF Dark humor for sure but I loved it . Happy ending #cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Justine Skye said "as a woman i shouldn't have gotten involved" in her apology, I figured she meant being involved in defending him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how I made plans to see him after I left the bar with my coworkers but now I open tomorrow and he’s on his way and I’m not ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashU90 I have to tell you I out and out guffawed in reading this, how cute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely feeling this one as the dreaded 40th birthday is now less than two months away. 🖤👵🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_layton If only the rest of Canada clues in before the Federal Elections. The PC Party has stomped on The Charter… https://t.co/7ONFJYpwOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[From 2015 but I love this thread and perfectly aligns with my husband’s own scholarship and our convos ❤️ Sometimes… https://t.co/DAIQeeMoEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverboatRonHC Thanks Riverboat for continuing to Rally in our region for awareness and fundraising. I've never fo… https://t.co/daeXklCQKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOP 50 🔥 @mbax33315095 first bucket of the game moves him into No. 50 on Liberty’s all-time scoring list with 624 c… https://t.co/1k8mL75WsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I got to Austin’s he had Chick-fil-A and my favorite ice cream cake waiting for me. Itttts the little things 🍗 &amp; 🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you touch my laundry while the dryer’s still running and let me see your face...god speed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been terrified of cutting my dog's nails but today I decided to bite the bullet 💣 His front paws went great bu… https://t.co/r8SXgYCGtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probs never leave the house again. 🔥🔥🔥 A reboot of The Baby-Sitters Club is coming to Netflix  https://t.co/nYDA3fMHPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASMLibrary @sam_aye_ahm Love Denmark. Hope you get to all the incredible libraries across the country especially the Black Diamond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone , hope you had a blessed day. Beach was full today and it got me ex itex about my invention for you la… https://t.co/ggTRtk8BAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A police dog just growled and barked at me through a car window so idk what this says about my appearance today but okay DAMN KUJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamEdmund marten deleted facebook and instagram and spends time on linkedin 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @Lioness95834 Let him know he is not alone. It took me years to deal with my ptsd. It can get bett… https://t.co/HtR3oU4aii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhweingarten @clmcheesy23 Exactly.  No double standards.  Listen to the song and Retweet it. https://t.co/sU6OvyXLl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I be getting curved left and right by you ... I’m done done forreal now you just gonna be the girl I want to m… https://t.co/9XkPXWQLGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @hannahkaymusic! #TheVoice https://t.co/FFGNnOeDDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[WhooHooo. Beaming in from Belgium! #spsm #AAS365 #ImpactedFamilyFriends #IsThistheNight #AVoiceattheTable… https://t.co/MMcubhsIBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephMKavanag1 @madlymeditating @SparrowCove @MegSWritesBooks @EElleBea @MackenzieLitt13 @OwenGRichardsId… https://t.co/BqpnwIUSfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are problematic as hell. I posted a picture of something I felt confident in and y’all are in my snap message… https://t.co/lFuoxLOmQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#learnearnlivebetter loveyourhaircoltown 🎨🌈 Comment if you’d like your #hairstylist to #customize a #haircolor just… https://t.co/YAJHp7QIFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoured and excited to have @jheerND visit our @FACSFoundation #MeToWe groups this week! Can’t wait to hear his me… https://t.co/XAZtGz1niO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Valentine’s Day my mom would get me my fav Starbucks drink and box of chocolates and a stuffed animal 😭❣️ thi… https://t.co/QKH5C8lDEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helen Mirren and Jason Momoa are one and two on my celebration exception list]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here it is! "She's Out of Her Mind"​ The first of an 8-part series on true and funny stories about leadership. Enjo… https://t.co/ZjTYw3xocv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_In_CLT_NC @rnelson0 @MoorJebsen @cocokitty14 @PennyRed https://t.co/19dF6zmLTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you ever need a pick me up, just call damian and he’ll literally yell “BITCH WE’RE SUCCESSFUL” at you and then you’ll feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[The radio DJ mentioned why Don’t We being at the station last month and I fangirled on the inside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoJake44 @Brown70William @JackPosobiec @OANN Schiff not administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[FWIW, there’s no sociological/scientific evidence that I know of that shows kids raised by 2 dads or a single dad e… https://t.co/v3kivx30ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuyahoga County Executive Armond Budish shouldn’t be held criminally responsible for problems in the jail, where 8… https://t.co/jdKjD5fOVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scweeber @MurpheySean @girlscouts Me either!! I said “oh I need to go put the thin mints in the freezer” and Sean… https://t.co/cdvppbRNGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grey likes @treynkennedy! He never wags at johnbcrist. Maybe we should check his heart. @ Tennessee https://t.co/V4SPgHfLEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleMoody @ABC It's very painful!!! fever, high b p, nerv syst dysfunction, or sweating, muscle spasms, or sti… https://t.co/DOPMb5q2PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[But wait. Duke only dropped to second after they lost. KENTUCKY ALSO LOST A GAME LAST WEEK but they are ranked high… https://t.co/KMW2KCmkdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ The single biggest problem in communication is the illusion that it has been taken place” ~ George Bernard Shaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️⚾️⚾️ (@ JetBlue Park at Fenway South for Pittsburgh Pirates vs Boston Red Sox in Fort Myers, FL) https://t.co/V1uGgK9cf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickybobbybabyy Venn diagram Personality       Looks    /            /      \            \ (    Ugly  ( ugly)    U… https://t.co/3sKNCKAaFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If John Lasseter started his own company, then every employee would have been given the opportunity to choose whet… https://t.co/hVVkn6sGtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure if Ned didn’t decapitate one of the men from The Wall and listened to him about the White Walkers, half… https://t.co/z8hOFW8ZJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried going to sleep early... now my body woke me up and I can’t fall back asleep 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_reamswpa I'm loving @wakelet!  Will be presenting on this in the near future!  Catch the wave! 🌊🏄🏻‍♀️❤️🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraNiven @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott @hallmarkmovie Hope to see more of you in the Oct. movies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't go to work today. Roads were too treacherous this morning. (@ Winter Hill Solutions, L.L.C. - Wilmington in… https://t.co/MU2RZRgK1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Tell PETA my mink is dragging on the floor”  • • • #style #vscocam #latergram #photo #blessed #likeforlike… https://t.co/dU2oQLbz8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will always that bad ass kid playing around the corner way past the street lights and taking my lick when eye event… https://t.co/ytXsTjh0MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7covers7days 7 covers over 7 days of books I love. No explanation or reviews. 3/7. Today I challenge… https://t.co/ReRtzcrt6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small group Teambuilding to whole Group Teambuilding Time.  @GCHS_Softball #ramslife https://t.co/wVahR8RsSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pura y neta verdad 😡comprobado está que este par son unos corruptos,delincuentes igual o peor que Caracol… https://t.co/oZsrImYuqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[note to self: watch wendy wu homecoming warrior when you get back to columbia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSpadea @MattRooneyNJ   THIS SHOULD MAKE U THINK B4 U SUPPORT LESS GUN REGULATIONS!!!!! STAND UR GROUND ENDANGE… https://t.co/r2uk8tbmxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues ya rente una de estas bicis para aflojar el músculo https://t.co/BSgkE0gNM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell I'm an ultrasound tech. 2 kids in college. My daughter was switched to a new med priced at 497$ per month, impossible !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonzi and Fonzi back in action 😏 @Ashton5SOS  @Calum5SOS https://t.co/vam2tyO83k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coxchloeee @Maxdugan_ND i glo’d down lmfaoooo who’s the baddie in the pics :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[[PHOTOS] Un entrepôt flanche sous la neige à Wendake (@ArnaudKoenig) #JDQ https://t.co/kDB3U1jow4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinacruickshank I love this book and my students love its activities! https://t.co/IXfCjSNpF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrible terrible! This rose garden phot op for Angel Mother’s! Not the way to declare a national emergency! What a… https://t.co/JXHBCFVlH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is a #visitallthewards day. We started in @st3v3turn3r's, travelled through @ArielkeK 's (tea stop), had beau… https://t.co/FtJOmnF1X8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not turning hw in on its due date is the worst feeling ever. I’m a nerd, idc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That NEWT AND DUMBLEDORE DELETED SCENE THOUGH HOLY CRAP. It confirms everything I’ve always thought about why Dumbl… https://t.co/ZzYGsaxsut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some faerie girls just dropped off this community dinner flyer. Looks so sweet. ♡♡♡ @ Pescadero, California https://t.co/ygTm7U03zR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m a tad bit socially awkward but these dmv natives got me BEAAAATTTTTTTTTTTT !!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI this same person was nearly crying to its editor that he needed a puff piece from them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this idea! Can we pose similar problems on our math boards? @DunwichDuttonPS @MrsPriceDDPS @MrsLunnDDPS… https://t.co/6g0VpV0pFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to announce that We Design. You Sell won Best of Houzz for 2019! Woot! @houzz #bestofhouzz… https://t.co/O1roZxhDgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win a 93.9 LITE FM &amp; Wendy's Office Invasion https://t.co/nC9jSew5xZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGertz @TheDalyPlanet Good going Mr. PRESIDENT, showed him that you mean business and you weren't just going to… https://t.co/AyScGZk6kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ He has absolutely no one to blame but himself. I'll pray for real victims that now might be doubted due to this dumb ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelNogueras @KasoKim @JohnKaso @cruxwinery @_drazzari @thepinksociety_ @lawprofblawg @JoeJac31 @kimborhae005… https://t.co/64FzgRoIu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSug And as it turns out, voters *do* love conviction and honesty in politicians-- even when they disagree with the conclusions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stevec2370C Good morning.  After today I work the next 8 days😭😭 lol Today is more like a slide into hell for me 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time for Ivanka an Jared to be questioned about Trump. He insisted they be given top security clearances. It's… https://t.co/1bylMubTHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have some bad ass friends 🤷🏽‍♀️ my girlys really top notch n fck whomever think other wise 🤡🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my dearest movies to watch, it’s a must watch: Ruby Bridges  Short story - when I was in school way back whe… https://t.co/a0kPWSwXjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YtNmHEvwLd  Want to learn about #home #warranties cause this blog post is for you! Everyone else enjoy… https://t.co/H55x4F11wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ole Miss ASB Senate votes to relocate Confederate statue on campus https://t.co/n4sjM4yush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badler A perfect labyrinth of unreason. These houses are obviously so ugly. An objective fact that everyone agrees… https://t.co/LwikRz0byJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It genuinely makes me so excited to see how sunny it is when I leave work. Ready for summer 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenneth Branagh’s mustache is so mesmerizing in Murder on the Orient Express. It steals the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[never have i ever preordered an album so fast. is it may 3rd yet? #peptalks @judahandthelion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late post but .... Happy Mardi Gras!! Aubrey and Addison rocked their 💜💚💛 today at school!! #mardigras… https://t.co/zGNLMbiLxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueegg3r I forgot to tag you! Forgive my Flu filled brain. I missed many of my fellow TOYs....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9GAG lol! I couldnt believe this. Whoever made this is #funnyaf ... #9gag #memes https://t.co/6Tksv7BFH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Australian foreign minister claims Melania Trump assumed she was minister’s partner during encounter  https://t.co/X3jrYfbxaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2 @glammalg11… https://t.co/sBLub3YP0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXXBellaRose Of course... I need to go there it looks so majestic and magical]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveBasic2 The post was erased because permission to use this little lady’s picture hadn’t been obtained. It was… https://t.co/Svpu8oVs69]]></document><document><![CDATA[they didn’t cancel school even though it clearly raining outside? how rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Chicago police say Jussie Smollett staged his attack because he was 'dissatisfied with his salary'”/ I don't be… https://t.co/SRqJnzc7RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you aren’t sure what’s better...nails or new BOTM book. @bookofthemonth #sunday #reading #nails #almondnails… https://t.co/MJbFAZwRrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoniPhillips I didn’t say that. Only pointing out that reliving painful experiences that resonate with others does… https://t.co/SJHvpirJJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Caracas Venezuela 🇻🇪 Rio Guaire  Caraqueños hoy se dieron un baño de patria  Rt @partidopsuv… https://t.co/ZLwANMdG4g]]></document></documents></author>