<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@chicksonright Any claims if I did not know they were doing this if accepted, shiuld also be accepted on behalf of… https://t.co/12RYJs1OlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok how are Samoa’s 70 calories each? There’s literally a hole in the cookie #upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking him to the batting cages so he can break-in his $200 bat. #baseballlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf can sing this word for word &amp; i can’t stop listening to it https://t.co/Zq2BohzDkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AafLegends @TheAAF Man - I dont know...good drives ending in no points..just cant get into the endzone..Birmingham… https://t.co/OnZakYAzLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quit over thinking and just see where your hearts leads you. It may be dangerous but the heart wants what the heart wants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the media were honest most people in the world would concede that democrats are the most egregious and  Disgusti… https://t.co/sKKlKwJ5zP]]></document><document><![CDATA[saturday night.. @crisbruyere and I did a thing https://t.co/WHojUIYzeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This broke my heart! 😭 let us all think a little bit more before we post, complain, or jump to any conclusions. Let… https://t.co/Na6O0zE5A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antibiotic developers be like  #mondaythoughts #science https://t.co/toY2IogKmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a Sun d a z e ✨ https://t.co/dD2q3t04qh https://t.co/GtOv77CazC #liketkit @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/dzeFyq3Wse]]></document><document><![CDATA[from across the Golan Heights,” the bill’s sponsors said Wednesday.  Israeli officials have long pushed for US reco… https://t.co/LFI6Ssm621]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill The Freedom Causus. The Tea Party Is in the house quoting Jesus and Dictators.Confused. Family values should bring them home.😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARLadyBlazers Lady Tigers keep doing what you do best,  be aggressive , hit those free throws,  play that defense,… https://t.co/xhxNiBMgtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad today when I told him I have pneumonia: oh my gosh leesh that’s the illness that used to kill people left an… https://t.co/YALERquf8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok so like carisi is in season 14 of svu as a suspect but comes back in season 16 as a cop.... do they think we won… https://t.co/pYcqCGK6E7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr @ATX_fight_club @PlugInFUD If mispriced, why don’t you flip it Greg?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wind in Nashville is giving me growing up in Oklahoma memories https://t.co/YqDhtRr0r3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m in love with my nails 😍💛 i was nervous about doing yellow but i finally found the yellow shade i was looking for and i loveee it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number one thing I hate about living on campus is the fact that at all hours of the night I can here kids screa… https://t.co/yJmZrKUkSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofballgeorge @Sequencer16 @Serremmy @SGrannaP @shaniekay12 @Shelda21246445 @shellypage18 @Sheraleeable… https://t.co/qsg53mUWc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quer investir nos EUA?Abrir uma empresa? Mudar seus planos de vida e negócios? Em Abril, a Invest Plus convida você… https://t.co/iNPGT2IyIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi ho, hi ho, it's off to work I go, to train our interns in the misconduct canons and then make them dinner. Nothi… https://t.co/sRJAiG7duv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaMe_14 Girl it always has me in all kinds of emotions. But you know Cali is where it’s at 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who you are will carry you much further than what you do. @drjimbradford]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artistic Rock Hard sculptures using Clear, Gold Metal, and Swag Color Gloss #artisticcolourgloss #artisticrockhard… https://t.co/AwCbx3nIBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not have done this without your help and support beyond the ballot box. Thank you. 3/5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @donlemon needs to go to jail with his BFF. Your unfair and downright ignorant reporting is what enco… https://t.co/YH44yT1QXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[And tomorrow, Friday, feb whatever that is, at 10am in annex 154 is the  Public Comment Hearing for 200 KAR 3.020 /… https://t.co/cZSLYOH8Sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmi_williams I’m chill. Am I wrong that an athlete of Jamaican origin took second at the Euro champs? No. Did I… https://t.co/FIDcXR2hzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely amusing. #funniness #chuckle #grin #cute https://t.co/2spbeGbPXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassidayDeel I hate seeing kids like this these days. No respect. No morals. It’s truly heartbreaking. Teachers do… https://t.co/6cBbGOnYkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul He's just too STUPID to grasp the concept and importance of troop readiness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is so dumb that is Donald, that he hires one of his Goonies to cover up his trail of poor grades low IQ and stup… https://t.co/i9LAsDdFqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five things to watch for in the Canadian #business world in the coming week: Bank of Canada governor Stephen Poloz… https://t.co/hOwwgtPOq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristen_thorin @kahlams @underwood89 @virgil_maddox @cfisdmath Let me know when you plan on doing this type of mar… https://t.co/S4Ic1OP7Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[im starting the second case in aai1, and when i saw franziska's silhouette on the preview screen i just about lost… https://t.co/EAuYKsHtb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just booked the most beautiful Airbnb for our trip to Orlando next week. I can’t wait for the babies to experien… https://t.co/ezE6m0s6Zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deploralette @saynt614 @NBCNews Citizens who have already transitioned will not be permitted. This is basically an… https://t.co/1xJZ5QRsWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robyncnm @ACNM_DGH @GingerBreedlove @evitafernandez6 @k_semrau @Humanisingbirth Honored!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LIZJNY good morning Liz and Vonetta, help with my CVS (wrong gone earnings trade) now an Apr 65 straddle after rol… https://t.co/vK5geSVsKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl Examples of this all day long and it makes me sick. I’m so sick of people telling me the justice system i… https://t.co/0NBVbNKrNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me today as I chat with @chrisalthouse for #momtalk on Facebook live, as I share the lessons I learned as a mo… https://t.co/LpPTbCkNkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[HE'S IN LOVE (and we're all gonna die) - Randy Rainbow Song Parody https://t.co/twIEdZby1E via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIRED of McCabe talk!  Trumps FN CAMPAIGN mgr going to jail for working with the RUSSIANS! Flynn in jail for workin… https://t.co/sbSo4X3Y0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tragic he lost so many years in prison but what a wonderful talent has emerged. Thanks @CBSEveningNews for this sto… https://t.co/DsFU5grMy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen @mamakatie64 Wow Mr C soooooo well put  but the Rep who are backing this fool will make it really ha… https://t.co/z2tsVViu8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter is super talented‼️ I only wish I’d had a headsup on the questions to give more thoughtful answers but… https://t.co/RjtVLrbo0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse It’s very simple we want to stop the criminals in the White House]]></document><document><![CDATA[De todo el tiempo que llevo conociendo a @IvanGonRom nunca le atinó con su día de cumpleaños , siempre pienso que e… https://t.co/w3GRi1vT2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellenc53 @coleyworld My kindergarten teacher was named, Anita Johnson, I shit you not.  But she was wonderful.  Th… https://t.co/cYHFWbxO9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheFive.                                     Greg is right, it is a hate crime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treborjon Idk what you seeing in the mirror if this ain’t it 😂 https://t.co/Et6RdTZjGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand why I’ve been sleeping so much lately but it really sucks 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Florida_ACE When #FloridaACE19 is practically in your back yard... https://t.co/tAIVxzDeJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noramaryfranco @ethan_teicher wow I’ve never been more proud of this ship &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maden_marjorie Good afternoon Marjorie. Thank you my friend. Hope your Monday is a happy one and a safe one.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @kelseyann68!  #GPUG #GPUGCO #ChapterLeader https://t.co/75R34XMHSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krista91344061 @nathanvarni So you get GH and you don’t have to deal with Trump. I think I want to be Canadian]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just don’t get it.. how am i going out again @leenbabyyx3 why are we like this!!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminEnfield A mother one time called me about her son being bullied by my kid. Know what I did? Grounded his a… https://t.co/Y8GQcFJb6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do y’all remember when they made us learn how to square dance in elementary school????? I think that’s when i first… https://t.co/IDa0RC4EZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News8Daybreak #iamup i am a school crossing guard. Parents and kids are to come to the crosswalk. A lot of them don't. That is a pet peeve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macabeso Jajajaja hay te hablan @barbara_lopez21  Jajajajajaj https://t.co/Pd8FJnodT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@papicauseway My go to line when asking for money “it’s not that much, most of the number is zeroes”]]></document><document><![CDATA[tolerant and loving than the left can ever be.  The way some on the left act, you’d be hard pressed to find a compa… https://t.co/PpAsDwEZB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scottyplagues I assume people (if out of state) are charging this much to cover plane/hotel costs, as well as just… https://t.co/I6buNZgsGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a forced friendship @ Starkville, Mississippi https://t.co/iaPb73fCOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students in 3rd grade learning about fractions by doing a gallery walk with I wonder and I notice statements.… https://t.co/cbN6zbKkIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like how @hfdathletic’s hashtag is dangerously close to the @sixers #HereTheyCome]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have guest artist Mike Lucena mikelucena73 of flyrite_tattoo in the NYC here. He’s taking walk ins only on Wedne… https://t.co/XOI52NcTzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoCoHowie @MMRDisneyWorld i may be more attached to the being at epcot before illuminations and the preshow music… https://t.co/zg3SjIbXNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap. Yeah sex with a minor is always assault . Even when you’re a rock star.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:20 and I’m sharing a bed with Dance Dance Revolution David Leonard Nelson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@star_indie @networkindie @BamilMusic @_maddiemueller_ @DanielleVHaskel @jimenar31 @JenniferMlott @reisemusic… https://t.co/rsfJkxkA9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never witnessed a more honest and relatable email from HEB. No store does better. Hahahaha. https://t.co/NR7x8njwiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so basically people are insulting my looks just bc i said one of their team’s players was an asshole.. makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg @TheAtlantic No you are afraid of him, he doesn’t play by the rules, you underestimated the Americ… https://t.co/d5SAgh4SMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fxp123 The only reason they care od they arent getting a cut of the cash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xsunnystarsx Actual image of us giving all our money to Panic! tomorrow night https://t.co/ROQGM9E36w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris @DrLeanaWen First pregnancy I went to Birthright; minimally charged for service. 2nd+3rd went to f… https://t.co/IPgJ8MQJr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahHermann I will get these words tattooed if we raise $20,000 by midnight. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the focus on empathy when photographing by both our speakers today #WPOWReview2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox will be Running Cohen into the Ground while Cohen is testifying today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soulful Sips Salutes ✨Jacqueline Joyner-Kersee born on this day 1962 in East St. Louis, Illinois...She is an Americ… https://t.co/R8VlEpkPvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition to make galentines day the day after valentines day because then all the candy will be on sale? Just an idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Lizabeth #Syfybartow2019 @ Bartow, Florida https://t.co/ZUVYOEvM3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The difference 9 months can make...she has stole my heart. Tía’s big girl. ❤️#AdelinaMarieUrbina https://t.co/Jf3HpRaT3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Finally picked up my trophy that our team won last session. #poolhalljunkie #apaleagues #ilovepool @ Chicago,… https://t.co/3rJVeItwtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_prodigy I would like to express my deepest sympathy , I would also like to say that being part of the… https://t.co/1Tm8AT1pGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you guys stay at your job if you were making good money but not happy.. or get a job where your making less money but happier?]]></document><document><![CDATA[30% OFF!!!!!   Together with @wonderbra_canada and for International Women’s Day I am to share a promo code “MONIKA… https://t.co/nRUNmQskn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You opened Paradise to the thief who believed in you, — do not close the gates of heaven to the faithful departed.… https://t.co/T5ye5wsW4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubberNinja @peta I know right? I remember when he died, the world lost a great man. Now they are trying to vilify… https://t.co/ebGHkZBPxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salmon Burrata - Special appetizer at #LeSorelleRestaurant in Boca Raton and Delray Beach  Reserve a table and try… https://t.co/uE58TiSwmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry if me and my boyfriend scared you wen we ran up to you yesterday we were just so excited to run into you… https://t.co/9jWpWhLnA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We did it, #RESISTERS!! 😁😁👍👍👍  McConnell:   The Senate will #pass resolution  #blocking Trump's #FAKE 'emergency' d… https://t.co/qzM2CVqXMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam bought cranberry juice and I’ve had like 3/4 of it.   When I apologized for drinking most of it he said “No, I… https://t.co/OiRjURTque]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 @BamaBo17 When I got home I think I drank 3 more in about 15minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aniehinh Happy birthday beautiful good hearted soul🥺❤️ I love you so very much]]></document></documents></author>