<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#KindredSpirits tonight. #waverlyhills I really should drive the 3 hrs and visit. Whiskey Sour in hand. 🥃 Lets get spooky!! #spooky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball &amp; ribs with friends during Spring Training ⚾️🍷 https://t.co/zntBIdm1DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTOP10Sports @brudman_wtop10 @LukeTheKid3 @Mikemarrano44 You and your entire production team delivered the most pr… https://t.co/8lSzTBQcit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssaalori my heart hurts for you! God has a blessing for you! Stay strong!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter You've got a Great Wonderful smile which makes Me smile with You 😁😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m grateful to be leAving Dallas. To build the life I want. BYE BYE TEXAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over breakfast @englishfuturist brought up how after the creation of gutenberg press war in Europe seemed to excell… https://t.co/kegVfqrV1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 yesss but I can argue alll day why this makes sense and why this is FACTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are in line waiting for a show but you hear your  Fav is at the  casino 😩@ColtonWatkinson  #isitsundayyet https://t.co/eZF8xnMq9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The insta stories that I can barely make out have to be created by androids right?! Wtf is up with these videos???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Censorship is an insult. It screams" you are too stupid to discern for yourselves!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kirby Smith vs Stilwell Middle School Championship game in less than 7 minutes @DuvalSports https://t.co/9AKvKqKAh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi bebe y yo #proudmomma #motheranddaughter #mydaughter #mydaughterismyworld #bomdia #happygirls #youtuber… https://t.co/3EO0BIAxHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us this Thursday for an encore performance of Steve Reich’s iconic piece. Hear “Different Trains” again... and… https://t.co/jhdfxLvqZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[this would happen to me the day before i leave for SB but it was not the 2 step that caused this injury this time s… https://t.co/p4nQNrEBwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Nancy, we know your agenda.  No wall more votes for your gang.  You are DESPICABLE‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zimbabwe must sign into the ICC and ICJ covenants if they want money at the upcoming UN meeting because now their n… https://t.co/Y84FLf2GKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald learns there is ”NO” power in the White House. We are the People of this Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s some kids who watched hsm growing up, while the others grew up watching shows like Malcolm in the middle...… https://t.co/zKttNm3x9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@needyygrantt @jamescharles My friend @_peachygray  gave me the nickname 😂🤦‍♀️ and so many people have said it I just went with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGtonyhinelli38 @Sir_Daluz @DamarisDV @mjohnson201457 @IPoncho8 @josegaminho @angelocuaglioti @NazlyMejia… https://t.co/XtPA4ibfSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 Reminds me of the Kathy Gifford photo with Trumps decapitated head. Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frank_Frangie @jaxump1 @WalkOffJax A Special Thanks to @jaxump1 from @DuvalSchools for your support of @WalkOffJax… https://t.co/lJaclvFbOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimwilliamspais I’m forcing myself through your book, because I feel like it’s required reading for anyone who’s b… https://t.co/ZHJgQvkuqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnkazimirko @SIRRFS @SIRspecialists @traumadoctors Great job! 🥇Were you concerned there might be any thrombus in t… https://t.co/Szzgcv2Ava]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes u just gotta hold onto the conviction that God has better things in store for you 🤙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrokeHughe @MightyCuinn97 @dog_rates @GBeckTV THEY'RE ALL GOOD DOGS, BRENT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m letting my creative work go to waste. I need to do better. I was making a record label logo jacket for Sean 2 y… https://t.co/xAn8JZNtqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencercollins_ I agree, but...not when they don’t know what to say! 🤣 Some of the ones in the beginning were kinda cringeworthy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officiallaxgirl I know Cierra Porter’s parents and they are incredible people-they raised her extremely well!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iliriandisha I’ve been sober for two months and 3 days*  *Minus one day in London when I had like two drinks @ a club]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamelarwalker Thanks, Pam! But maybe they could give me a few days to recover?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @KIPPSI1 And gave permission to vile Howard stern to call ivanka piece of ass, and discussed size of Mel… https://t.co/EmZqgNpRSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveyourpetday # loveyourpetday2019 @ Brentwood, Tennessee https://t.co/ZlQk3DkJvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[totes stole this from nbcsphilly @ Philadelphia Flyers https://t.co/doHJA4TWH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milliken1997 Trail has put an adult team together to run in the 1/2 at Nationwide in October 2019.  Perhaps you co… https://t.co/85DpXEdM6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is more than a little unnerving. @ Skypod - CN Tower https://t.co/00OVT9K8sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend doesn’t give a shit about Game of Thrones, should I dump him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @LindseyGrahamSC @SenTedCruz @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @Jim_Jordan  @RepMarkMeadows stop this harassment of OU… https://t.co/FTGBaDj4w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulHoles #murderinos everywhere are vibrating with joy ❤ https://t.co/SxFOzPmeXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniStudios Are They Bringing The Ride Back....????  #BackToTheFutureTheRide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great overview of the science (or not-science) of Super Snow, Blood, and Wolf moons (and yes as a stereotypical Nor… https://t.co/Lj9vNSPuyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday brought to you by balloonsaloon 🎈🎂🎈 @ The Brooklyneer NYC https://t.co/WfG9uJ7D9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts on over-sleeping for work in a Mary Poppins Returns t shirt: Barely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be real only reason my fatass is tryna go back to pasco is to eat Andy’s 😂😂😂 sum bout that breakfast got me stuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is more American than the carousel room at House on the Rock. #AmericanGods]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOSTON BUTTS FOR SALE!!!  What: Boston Butts - average 7 lbs pre-cooked $30 When: Saturday, 3/16 PICK-UP BETWEEN 2… https://t.co/cxtdb4HXBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to LEAD us, you must first follow!  Start with Aiden, Turner, Rhiannon and Elizabeth. They’ll show you… https://t.co/eTIVWJz8Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKarmiDance @lionfirefocus @carlozaktion59 @Makedni @BillClinton @Interpol https://t.co/kQ6Qfeb4cT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re ever feeling frightened about what comes next, don’t be. Spin wildly into your next action. Challenges al… https://t.co/N79xKGuDqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last semester was not good for me at all and I just looked at my midterm grades and I have all A’s and man it’s ama… https://t.co/nM54eaOx2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come work with me! FIRST is looking for a Director of Education. https://t.co/CONt1QHbo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkolligris @LRobbTeacher @BiscottiNicole @aweninspiration @heARTISTatWORK @TanELLclassroom @ThirstyBeesNY… https://t.co/Jiwk6cEuVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments Did you really expect the truth from a bunch of lying paid off Clinton operatives democratic donors… https://t.co/YsmH6KfMB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp Are the printouts that Ken Had doctored transcripts where it made you look like you were the bad g… https://t.co/0lBkauEMqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone...like his attorney...should explain how the law works to Mr. Smollett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARSantos1946 Good morning Amelia. Thank you. Hope you have a very good day. Bundle up if going out.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @Deb10122 Ewww.   Look at that face.  The epitome of “slime ball.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oigan! Ya viene la Primavera! Ya se va el invierno! Ya podemos guardar la ropa de inv...”  Monterrey: “Hold on my… https://t.co/ZmI3i2tyRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiiMichelle That’s a huge blessing. I had to rebuild two houses after Katrina at 22/23 all alone and I do not wis… https://t.co/RF6XfTQts0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are working as teams today to build magnificent things! https://t.co/38QEeceRBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[*IF* the Jonas brothers are actually doing a reunion tour (which I am still skeptical of) I will make sure to go be… https://t.co/YNwHNNCVya]]></document><document><![CDATA[pole spining training before my workshops at lotusfitnessstudio in Orlando !! . #poledance #polespining #polecombo… https://t.co/4yMxcUNHGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently sitting here drinking barefoot pink moscato and eating nilla wafers... what is life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueWaveVsTrump @Xuspmurt Maybe @KellyannePolls doesn’t realize that @BetoORourke live in #ElPaso and represents t… https://t.co/ivQtUcv99R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makeouttyler My heart, and more importantly, my bank account can’t take another reunion too soon! Cause you knowww… https://t.co/gecaxXxgRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Dude, chill. We know you play well. Stop making yourself look like a jack$$$!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[however, saying the fire was still burning and it is feared there are dozens of fatalities. https://t.co/196n8QJLOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler I hate my younger self for ever thinking he was cute #pig #douche]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Colton and I’s relationship? Why? How? Who taught them English? #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[He loves gay people as much as he loves everyone else. Hateful Christians (not really Christians honestly) will tel… https://t.co/dOcQEbkmoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyZilka @Firehound55 More than odd that a high profile man is singled out so publicly while Adam Schiff 's liaiso… https://t.co/rfow7UlC37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happysadlion True. And many people don’t enter the social media sphere to further understanding so it can be futil… https://t.co/vqc2KDmZtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanjaSaily @TonyMcEnery Yes, Justin used to be popular among my students too but apparently there is now a shift t… https://t.co/5QGe87FXSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[In truths that she learned or in times that he cried, the bridges he burned or the way that she died....remember th… https://t.co/ci6SKcMX42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh thank God Sam is okay  it's too early so you know more action is to come. Who else is involved?#ncisla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar You don’t get to Have An Opinion On SHIT! You are a RACIST! @jordynwoods I’m tired of people Coming fo… https://t.co/OlQ087EGba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Never will subscribe to this awful rag sheet!  You have gotten more stories wrong than right!  When are yo… https://t.co/kqY936QGFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamJiles @CamaraDiputados @elfrente_amplio Inutiles .... les va a caer en la cara , pa esto si tienen tiempo .....… https://t.co/W9s9LxXFZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[what is y’alls obsession w comparing trav and rocky??? make it make sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @TheDemocrats should file charges for kidnapping and child endangerment. #LockHerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fran_wilde It needs the boob doilies. Honestly, I wouldn't have even noticed them if they hadn't been pointed out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anielovejoy @BT21_ @BT21_Japan @BTS_twt JAJA SIII y tmb me gusta mucho Luismi eh :P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @Daimler and @BMWGroup announced the future of the 50/50 JV that was previewed last year. 5 new verticles- ou… https://t.co/eh2HkuLXQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris Typical Dummycrat response.  You don't like the facts so you ignore them.  That is more than distu… https://t.co/0HlpYPdNGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making Memories @ Epcot International Festival of the Arts https://t.co/drSvVFFE1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying our last night🍹😁 #NYC #CityLife #Love #TheBigApple #Cocktails #HappyTimes #Views #TimesSquare… https://t.co/jKfuXXdXtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missingwords Dude. For real. I have a lot of thoughts about typography in the SWU 😆💦⚔️💖🔥🔥🔥🍵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockybalboahp Creating a new narrative.... good to hear from you as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought that was super sweet. Went to my kitchen cupboard to show him the last VD gift from my dad (and my dad's tr… https://t.co/XZlvKyoZhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djframeatx @BriannaMychell I’m saying tho!!! Then they get more mad cause I’m laughing 😂😂😂 oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREhseIN heart obstacle course to finish out heart month in PE class. ❤️ https://t.co/qxXSHGnpGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch Break Yoga is cancelled today 02/20...due to inclement weather... Stay tuned for evening class updates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a doña, if a guy doesn’t talk to me first I’ll never talk to him first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a fun update: didn’t get to eat breakfast and I’m absolutely starving. Go to the kitchen at work to get my s… https://t.co/3xqiLVy74i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaCantaloupeH @ZunigaConsuelo @Trinmarin2 @Cuemar @CarlosAJimnez4 @AkireLincho @heidi_belikov @PoetaCaminate… https://t.co/yTYQpvXpyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TElonians @JothamKitara @mayemusk @Tesla @teddyteshome @28delayslater #frunkpuppy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KojionGuitar I just  read this completely so it was like  Hebrew school!  I'd love to understand Japanese but ever… https://t.co/7O7Ndy8eNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @coldest_night (get_repost) ・・・ Thanks to the fundraising efforts of our amazing team, Walkin' for HOPE,  e… https://t.co/nOqrCBdem0]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why this meme is good👌🏼 because it says “friend” and not male or female https://t.co/D9Q2dVicZi]]></document></documents></author>