<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@bredrew2 @jillianbowe @GeneralHospital She should've been back since 2013 when Scott and Laura came back along wit… https://t.co/HD4QW45dO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The brand is strong!!! @desusnice and thekidmero coming through and keeping me entertained while I wait for my late… https://t.co/oJEPaFc5Sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the same @RAGECAGE16 school that quit when down by 40+ and barely came out of locker room at half and had w… https://t.co/q7LgkozvPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at the Jazz schedule and with 21 games left I pretty sure they will finish with 50+ wins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamboMoto Hiyo haiwes make it! Sisi watu wa “Kiu” itakua tricky. https://t.co/FVWxCqNBiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy - not happy - hoped it would be @Buddie52 who would be tapped Wellman’s successor #Bittersweet #DiamondDeacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfcassidy @TBLightning In any case, good discussion.  If you have a few minutes, here’s my take on this issue: https://t.co/kw7XI4EyHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love #Woodbridge #chipotle #noline !! Unlike Menlo. 😁🙌🙌 @ Hopelawn, New Jersey https://t.co/E8uPC8xkyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the People of New York City aren't engaged in opposition to NYC position as "sanctuary to illegal aliens", they… https://t.co/u3LLZ5imLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla Hmmm .....as an EA I’m not feeling all that good at the scale of these sudden and significant reductions @elonmusk]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a sunset! No filter @ Daytona International Speedway https://t.co/MmJHi3vTMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary I felt like I would never have followers!  But… https://t.co/HV3Rq0xbCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The country needs a “Howard Beale” to tell the truth. #Network #WeNeedTheTruth #TellUsTheTruth https://t.co/SfpdUSBG8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sferik Sure! While I’m working on my laptop and wearing headphones and want to have all my audio running through my laptop -&gt; 🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeskeets @MichaelRyanRuiz He was real good at basketball but poor dude isn’t very smart...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpectacularTs @lithium66 @blacktgirls @GroobyMike I LOVE LICK ON AND BETWEEN YOUR BIG JUICY DELICIOUS CHOCOLATE CAKE BOOTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @brfootball I ordered that jersey today and I’m about to cancel it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @SethAbramson This position trump is a criminal but no impeachment will collapse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for another big day of racing? Here’s some help. #saturdayspecial https://t.co/Q8BvaDATQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew_Tynan this do anything to you?   I’ve been watching this on loop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently rocking out to some @GojiraMusic while drinking a @budlight. Yeah it’s a good night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Let’s get 1 thing straight she couldn’t wait2have sex with isis so she can stay over their. If she wants2… https://t.co/ORH5kewWeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I don’t know if it has been announced but Bethany students come to the game tomorrow at Tabor, free admission… https://t.co/Ggbq1veKWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great times at the #Willard dance today! #sausdproud #sausd @ Willard Intermediate https://t.co/iYGEHTSVHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @cnsnews She must think that we Americans are stupid or something. https://t.co/z3H1Hh8JTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meteorologist @WesWeather is joining us on #UpLateATL tracking the potential for severe weather on Sunday. https://t.co/kTcLh93eHd #11Alive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Well someone should be asking trump are you using  American People's money- to give to your daughter for- a project?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Henry19F @EdKrassen Yeah, it’s got me all upset🙄 I don’t trust either side plays it 100% right. I still remember t… https://t.co/ejvLky1g1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bitch... When u come back to the States maybe you'll get ur gold handcuffs . Running to Vietnam ain't gonna help you. 😜😂☕💅🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed Saturday brunch + conversation with these fantastic friends! #NexstarNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Y_not_AZ @JasonScheer It’s really simple. Arizona wants to LOOK like they are taking compliance in the program rea… https://t.co/SleAci3KwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett Intelligence Committee, He’s an Oxy-Moron!  #termlimits will get rid of this MORON!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hump Day inspiration 🌸🙌 . . #flowermagic #humpday #fiorioakville #oakvilleflorist #downtownoakville https://t.co/ybWVRHwR5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback Friday! 2013 at Bethesda Blues &amp; Jazz. @ Bethesda Blues &amp; Jazz Supper Club https://t.co/Ox5ocq6eXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my Dad and Stepmother for opening Pizza Ed. for business!   Located in Hartselle, Alabama my fam… https://t.co/7N03NedM9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is getting played again, and it’s putting the world in danger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furthermore,Nigerians in diaspora must be allowed to vote.Nigerians should be able to vote from any location.The pr… https://t.co/5tDqnZi5NT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dyson #instabasset #bassethound #bassetsofinstagram #bestfriend @ Haddon Heights, New Jersey https://t.co/aeuikC7x0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocRutcosky @_ClassicJeff Spending a whole day with me on a golf course, you might regret saying that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristynwongtam And the city of Toronto doesn't care.... oops that is YOU and the rest of council.. go back to cove… https://t.co/x17yBsELLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurs aren’t even that great anymore, and it would be nice to win at San Antonio for a change. #OKCThunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKrisWatkins @MrsWatkinsLHS You guys have a great time!! Grams, TJ, and Casey have Harper and PopPop has your two… https://t.co/qnjyBXPdF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoundRight @carlatomsmd @realDonaldTrump Wow and I bet you order your wife around like a servant.  Does she stay i… https://t.co/TChok9A8i8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cristophmusic This edit and your remix of Real Life = pure vibes and on 🔂 #consequenceofsociety]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/EPT2Eqb5fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinlineaMx ESTA MARIHUANO Y ANGUSTIADO EL GUEY. QUIERE LLORAR, QUIERE LLORAR, QUIERE LLORAR...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is funny cuz we watched it together and I found it to be extremely inspiring and I cried like 3 times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two quick things this morning.  1. I remember thinking “Barnes and Noble is destroying book stores! Fight them!” No… https://t.co/5wL6VL5TuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure it’s been 32° outside my house for 15 hours in a row. Starting to think my thermometer is busted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Tristan O’Tierney, Square co-founder who created firm’s first mobile app, dies - San Francisco Chr… https://t.co/AGEssh3TLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Bury the corrupt democrats. We are so damn tired of them getting away with everything. Get a grand jury… https://t.co/5hAZqkXIXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @Jim_Jordan @Rockprincess818 CC, you should probably just stay quiet, so we have to wonder how stupid you… https://t.co/lc24dPhgNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeLanaHarvick Happy anniversary you 2! @KevinHarvick my wife always says that too I just tell her I loved her firs… https://t.co/eZMVwyaULN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned that a player is taxed whatever state they play in. Playing half of his games in Cali at 13% compared to Il… https://t.co/Gm6luZnkD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“... and some vaccine objectors have even created their own churches to opt out of vaccinating their kids. “  Pleas… https://t.co/pTdjGvaUEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great intimate conversation about @GoogleMyBiz with @JoyanneHawkins @localseoguide @gsterling @flohuebner… https://t.co/2Vp5g5noYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1212GrantrealtyLLC #AcaciaNetwork #AlessandraBiaggi #mayorBilldeBlasio #VanessaLGibson #LatoyaJoyner2020… https://t.co/Sj30Qb6eO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge cancer arrives to be cancer in new team! No World Series trophies in 13 years! Washington will go farther then… https://t.co/7IkHK1I4aH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Long1Ryder @JoItalia_PhD @TwistedOne96 @rogueranger23 @Randal68052371 @RickLRobbins @unctarheels5633 @wwoodward921… https://t.co/5WMHbFOsN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Obamacare was supposed to solve that problem and is 100% the reason it’s getting worse, but yes, let’s… https://t.co/zb5rWRPOtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[for those who have not yet seen my family’s Christmas card https://t.co/6ChqhhWCFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure what’s going on. I thought we were in the desert 🌵. I haven’t seen snow twice in a week since 2002.… https://t.co/HHteMVlisD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Before you go “nuking” half the country, you might want to take the… https://t.co/to9hqLqrPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve also learned that I have to put me first and always be good to myself. Even through the difficult decisions life forces me to make.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tido1421 @MurphysLaw74 @NYP_Brooksie @BruinsCLNS In a heartbeat if it comes with an extention]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielCollier2 @FOXSoccer @AlexiLalas @fccincinnati Too bad it’s not a legit league, can’t be taken seriously when… https://t.co/EqGm1F2rha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @RRRRMMMMM14 That's such a horrible image it's going to scare even senior citizens, oh wait that is Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr @Mc_Driver has always been a very underrated superspeedway racer. He can win this race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol exactly and it completely ignores the fact niggas was walking around with big ass camcorders the whole time]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know it’s cliche but 🌹 stores and 🍫 shops are buzzing for #ValentinesDay. @WNYT is @CKCandies in Guilderland. https://t.co/9tDrhXgcTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadMikeSports next time you do a video giv ya boy a shout out cause I said all off season vic wasn't going anywhere and ya'll didn't listen]]></document><document><![CDATA[My idiotic ass didn’t recognize this fine gentleman @jccomplex til I actually met him after the show. I blame my me… https://t.co/aCBoUO3tIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned off @ZachGelb because it was non-stop Kaepernick talk, just as there was in the Huge show before him. Turned… https://t.co/bWIp5ok9YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 3rd  Wheelersburg 48  Chillicothe Huntington 34  Lady Pirates get hot again toward the end of the quarter. Unof… https://t.co/nSmMqRrxNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraftCMS Funny, I don’t even see where I can do that. But I did complete the contact form on your website.  (Full… https://t.co/ug2YDU2pUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farmerhawg @Caleb19801 We aren’t gonna be able to spread ours until August the way it’s been going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoskinsventt Bout to spark then I’m slumped I  promise, big day tomorrow❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wce she’s my light in my darkness 😍😍 I love her 💕 https://t.co/eVsWurg7UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/xiO7xuP4ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a frightening number of hostile debates with myself, is what I'm trying to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for helping me reach 25 followers! Who else do you think should be following me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Only1_ModelHard You can but I don’t know where. Even I have a certificate and License to Sell Vehicles and that’s… https://t.co/8eet6eVLkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me again how this team is fine without a modicum of toughness? #LeafsForever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyMPatt @bflay @bobbysburgerpal Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music… https://t.co/eyXWGR3tNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clutched a 1 vs 4 last night in league play and man does that feel good #CWLPS4 #CallOfDuty #BlackOps4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pending Pending Pending !!!!! If your intrested in listing your home Please give us at McTygue Group Inc a chance t… https://t.co/bR49G37Go5]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine wanting to join a frat so bad you let yourself get peed on while laying naked on glass, kicked with steel-t… https://t.co/ClVFlyp42p]]></document><document><![CDATA[So.......someone is clearly bored this morning. 🙃 https://t.co/3Dn13mhE4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tucahernandes @luciaguimaraes Tava rolando algo sobre uma empresa com esquema de corrupção que ele estava passando… https://t.co/BXiv2up8DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must not define ourselves by our past, but use it to transform our future. We must believe that change is not on… https://t.co/UW5UIdAiwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[With so many things coming back in style, I can’t wait til morals and intelligence becomes a trend again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpYouWell Yes!! I'd love to see you both again! Unfortunately my next three weekends are booked but I will let you know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caihoops leads Lanesville 52-50, 4:53 remaining. This has been a very good ballgame. @newstribscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can, please take a moment to say a prayer for my sweet grandpa. After suffering from a heart attack and pulm… https://t.co/3jwdv1AE1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, lets finally check out Hereditary. Doesn't seem like my kind of horror, but I keep hearing rave reviews. Maybe… https://t.co/kLpmAVpBN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccahanlon19 You do realize you’ll run into 3 guys looking identical to them anyday in Windsor, Red Lion or Dover.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Give it the whole season trust me I did the same thing. Quit and came back a year later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkmatchmaker I, on the other, was asleep at the wheel, and missed that. So, props to Nam. (I am also probably too… https://t.co/0OtE8l0ZJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious why out-of-state dark money is flooding #Texas to kill #renewables? A secret someone doesn’t like the renew… https://t.co/iLglHwHlcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my latest column, I talk about how @MissouriState is underfunded by our state and how YOU can help solve this is… https://t.co/mWtJUPLoMU]]></document></documents></author>