<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@funnygirlescope @AbigailPrestri1 @GOPChairwoman But to your point about Helsinki, this is where DT was coming from… https://t.co/akpQwjUgGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAGovernor @LincKroeger talking about how we are. revitalizing rural Iowa thru IT like what Linc is creating in Je… https://t.co/OfQeeNHtSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moved to Nashville over a year and half ago and I still have not met/become friends with @kaitlynbristowe yet. But hey girl I have wine 🍷🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand that I’m in a casino... but I really hate that this chick is smoking cigarette so close to me. 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geez #MorningJoe and Mika , what don’t you get about @samstein comment that Rep. Omar “has opened up a very complicated  conversation?”’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on 53🏋🏽‍♀️  Let us design your next training 🏋🏽‍♀️ #greatness #trainer #athlete #muscles #fitness #fit… https://t.co/T3RTb4ryiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mystic Healthcare and Rehabilitation Center has been recognized by U.S. News and World Report as one of the top nu… https://t.co/GBvIgNLTP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You jump, I jump, Jack. ☂️   Forever my favorite show and one of my favorite episodes. Sometimes life is about taki… https://t.co/prwEmSibxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will seduce you with my words. #Books #writersofTwitter https://t.co/CPm0RMdRzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilandJoeOTG At least you won’t have to sit at the airport by yourself for as long! See you soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss @totally_camila telling me “you’re lucky you’re pretty” every time I was a dumb bitch 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to Panera &amp; they said they were out of bread? How can you be out of bread you are bread]]></document><document><![CDATA[The area is all clear. Thank you for your cooperation and patience! #GATechPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad that millennials see the science behind vaccines and aren’t buying into the antivaxx movement, but can you… https://t.co/SA0p83z39m]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy valentingle day. no boys give me tingles these days because they are all loserz. hopefully this offends them &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper Not me! I live in the high desert and the summers are like living in a blast furnace!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecutors want death penalty for man accused in killing over PlayStation - https://t.co/JsZYVaZAKg https://t.co/9rMGBANY8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcwaca February Membership Meeting! #ConciergeJoy (@ The Phillips Collection - @phillipsmuseum in Washington, DC w… https://t.co/N0bVdgGLo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGreenDenver hey Tom...a salad is defined as...  a cold dish of various mixtures of raw or cooked vegetables, usua… https://t.co/BILdSDlKzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themainsmith99 @shaunacoralee I love them tooo But I don’t agree with some of them , what Sin is Sin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmtrialbird1 🙋🏼‍♀️ I had all three in another decade, but raising my hand on this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kilonova_gold @funder And the c word. Does he cal his daughters C1, C2 etc.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rc_cooldad @sjcaruthers @alexcaruthers @MacCaruthers I love this!  Congrats Caruthers family!  A little bitterswee… https://t.co/UhKAIDeLFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Snowy ❄️ Owl 🦉 ... making his appearance in RI  📷 ~ burnett.joseph #outdoors #owl #winter #wildlife… https://t.co/1BbxpcH586]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chanel fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld dies aged 85 after cancer battle https://t.co/XAAdMutLKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trendchasernews Please follow me at Coffee4josie@coffee4josie it is for the latest HW tv show tweets. I am trying… https://t.co/AYA0zGdNgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle I don't know if he should sign it or not? There's not enough money there to build the entire wall bu… https://t.co/uYM64hWNDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleggss @ryanejenkins @sciteach212 @tinkerguy1 @wonderfulideaco Yes! Fun happens when @andreak3051 is around... ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu enquanto assisto a transmissão ao vivo do carnaval pela tv do outro lado do mundo https://t.co/vaRGHKAIi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump My, is this the same course immortalized by the documentary showing how you destroyed the lives of… https://t.co/RvtTLITpQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will wait for a Pope that thinks like Pipe John Paul &amp; Pope Benedict]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i need is one or two tickets to see @Daniel_Sloss at the @LargoLosAngeles on tuesday at 8, because i’m a dumb s… https://t.co/qCOrF5mkXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a human sexuality class and honestly, most of my notes are about genitals but like in detail.   But there's… https://t.co/KnFP90qJWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phoenix rising 🔥🔥 @ABHcosmetics dip brow in medium brown @MorpheBrushes X @jamescharles palette @ColouredRaine vivi… https://t.co/ICZ2h1HMBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s talk travel pants these soft camo sweats are perfect for a travel day #rewash #travelday #camo #soft #comfy… https://t.co/PT39sEoZlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[She AND AOC are killing the Democrats!!!! Death by a thousand bad words and their lack of TRUE insight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s one thing to hurt so much you can’t fall asleep at night. but once you start to feel numb and the things that… https://t.co/RN7qwAiPNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Teacher’s Day! Thank you to all teachers for your dedication to the most important profession in the world. —… https://t.co/NhvpEJMrmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recognition is different than appreciation. Recognition is fleeting, about what they did. Appreciation lasts in sel… https://t.co/dhm4lrQyZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieffisher  If she becomes my guardian angel (👼), I will (may?) live. Otherwise, I die hiding under the covers… https://t.co/btwRkxbT8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know @prof_mirya has tagged you in a tweet when you check your phone and have several new poli scientist follow… https://t.co/IKg9no3x3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreylabarrie ordered my sweatshirt tonight! See I listen; I ordered your merch too🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my @_acaastillo was here 10 times outta 10 I’d be up and about and not lonely]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at these 19 and 20-year-old babies! Still in school! On their first trip together! Falling in love!   F I V E… https://t.co/eKZln7wB6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDelonyKHOU @CCAlliance @LisaKHOU @RussKHOU @StephKHOU @KHOUBlake11 @ChineduOgu You all are AMAZING, thank you… https://t.co/fdtZTvTTc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two things.... 1. Why he always sound like he singing? 2. ...He did it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[dont know what hurts more... watching the lakers play like this... or game 7 of the 2017 World Series...   jk we al… https://t.co/QChsxp26nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of witch hunts. #cohentestimony clue GOP he's already been caught]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gym_picker @JaimeBoswell2 @cp_basketball @Tabchoops @hoopinsider Wahoo!  Go all the way Blake!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't you had enough special investigations that spend money and last forever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyRW86 Nah u so pretty! ✨ Every time I see you #Flawless #Ageless 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love coming to visit @matern_hannah because I’m on vacation yet I just get to hang out at a friends house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys please Follow and Share my Link as well @somizi @bonang_m New kid who wants to share his God given Talent with… https://t.co/TlFr6gKmm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SextonDickson I "loathe" him as well. Actually is there anything stronger than loathe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to earn money. I like to make money. I like to have money. I like to keep money.  My mom KTNMMM wants none o… https://t.co/cxiNyYQVw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4D454F57 @augustosnunes Ei, Augusto Nunes, você já conseguiu provar que Trump é tudo isso aí que você afirmou ser?… https://t.co/q6L0epmyUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chemosh933 @JoshuaAGibson @RashidaTlaib And what does carrying debts have to do with being a good worker, tenant,… https://t.co/9pFLCwZTcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbsmasher I had this same experience with a (male) cardiologist! It wasn't until he was doing the investigation/ab… https://t.co/DE9CJGvMzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I care about policy views, past accomplishments. She can eat with her toes, I don’t care. School yard, infantile at… https://t.co/SO71OslwLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m certain God is with you. Your hair looks amazing. Did He pay you a visit? Locks of gold]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing my girl on the big screen rly made the hell I went through this morning so beyond worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danydiae happy birthday boo! Hope today and last night treated you well🤪💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OptimistPanda Thank you, Shane!! It’s important to me, but I also know that I developed that skill as a defense me… https://t.co/QzMzWGaPdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gumpnatlien The New Testament shows the fulfillment of the prophecies from the Old Testament. It’s a testimony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also didn't fight back with him, because I wasn't going to get into an argument with a friend over politics, just… https://t.co/7yiPo48Gc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/69uCp4MF7N Omar isn't AMERICAN. She grew up thinking like a Muslim with a dislike for Jews. The no. 1… https://t.co/vgWWnt1sno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @shaunking Is Flint, MI going to be the 1st place that reaps the benefit of this proposed water deal!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aopete1 @airandspace @IamCPS @GEAviation You are the best Anna Petersen!! You have always your kids so well prepar… https://t.co/UTJ7gzU1hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConcernedEdS @RepCummings @HouseDemocrats I believe that anyone looking to flee horrible and dangerous conditions… https://t.co/yXzKUf51JV]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWFT Blockchain @SwftCoin is very honored to be one of Draper Venture Network portfolio companies, together with ma… https://t.co/NESEsk7va8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen He should step aside and let some new/young faces represent us. Nothing against Sanders but we need dive… https://t.co/yghaIeTOMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaybeACrook Ooo you grew your hair out.  How upset are people when they find out you're not DeAndre?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilDocCollins @KFILE @SenSanders @AOC @SenFeinstein @GOP They definitely do that — @SenFeinstein video edit was a… https://t.co/GkCmytCxgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch I agree! you know how many beautiful men &amp; women I see around this campus everyday??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry defense twitter you won’t see much about the FY 20 budget here because it’s #CERAWeek #oott]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyBecaya The sweetest 💚 I’m sorry for your loss. She looks like an angel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me standing outside Prada drinking a Dunkin’ Donuts latte just tells you where my life is at the moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian hi I’m raising money for the American Cancer Society today as part of a fundraising mission at my sc… https://t.co/ITp6Izdesq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_patriciann @clairermassey @ThaddeusArjuna @msdusa @Jamesb40595620 @PaulColby2 @Chihuahua1900 @kathrynresister… https://t.co/d8bhCeW0Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Hwang In-Beom is going to be a superstar #WhitecapsFC ... poise, technique and vision]]></document><document><![CDATA[Past insanity to have @NancyPelosi run ttps://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/emily-ward/pelosis-chief-staff-speaker-w… https://t.co/ruAnQ6QXs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning i already wanna go back to sleep because i hate my informatics class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think the only lie Cohen told was what he said about you and collision. I think he knows but doe… https://t.co/eNbINa0qE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@universalfurn @cryptonfabric sponsored for our seats on the stage! #finedesignsint #elisachristinellc @ Grand Hyat… https://t.co/nALdBVEQmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrTab3 #BakerSportLaw I think both have great potential but I’m going to go with Acuna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swampy 🐀🦎🕸🕷🐍🐊.  Is this what Ford calls being responsible with Ontarians tax dollars?!  Another great example of lo… https://t.co/fUxWCOYHQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @PepperBurruss Thanks for being an excellent #GSSI partner and great example for @Boilers_ATC students!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincedemello @ShellyRKirchoff @VaGyver So much agreement on that! And on you being amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only pull this one out when it's absolutely necessary but it works 😂 https://t.co/1acYLrvfL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @RonVan944 Dan, I’m so sorry😞 Jeopardy music played all night 🎶 I still ain’t got nothin for ya...I’m not… https://t.co/PGRth1Ciiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day!❤️  #ImpactFamily #makeadifference🥎 https://t.co/UgczRFYsoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of the day, it doesn't matter how many stories you wrote or how many events you oversaw. What matters is… https://t.co/G1ZSPH2Q21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr Fried rice is great! Though I would skip the hot dog. Maybe spam instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncusack I asked you about canvassing in Ohio in 2020.  Let’s see who the democratic candidate is and we can coo… https://t.co/BpRtunaoRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @jathomas551 Good way to honor your friend. So sorry for your loss]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want people to be so successful in what they do and to enjoy their lives. Easier said than done, yes. But I… https://t.co/YwbAnrYhnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas House speaker Bonnen's dyslexia gives him unique view of learning disability funding issue https://t.co/hhRmvpsyHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_queenofcool So awesome!!!! Some glitter &amp; cheese to celebrate!!!!! https://t.co/nqbxLHht85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I feel awful for Otto's parents as I lost my son when he was 38. I know that pain. And I appreciat… https://t.co/8boR7o8Zr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/TBdVye0eE5]]></document></documents></author>