<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp Hey Matty, pick ANY 5 minutes of POTUS’ flat out bonkers rambling diatribe at your hate convention today… https://t.co/681Biqf9mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @LesliMelendy to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challeng… https://t.co/OaezJ8ZpbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have hit NOLA for Zulu Ball. I go every other week for egregious, facetious shit. I can’t believe I’m watc… https://t.co/AISBveNwcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here it comes, the fight for the heart and soul of the denocratic party will unravel this presidential cycle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thirtyaG Kill for me, R.I.P Got a hoe all in my bed, she gon' freak for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tophergrace wins the Internet! (P.S. Don’t think I saw one clip of Jar Jar Binks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnysTaverns How the hell did you get that video of me from college?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gonglei89 @WaltFrench Value is a forward-looking exercise, so I suppose the way you capture the value of large inf… https://t.co/qXoKxoLsT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than a dozen such new class GNB drugs in the CARB-X preclinical pipeline by April]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomsegura you were very funny in #Instantfamily. How’d you land that gig? Keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @SBALinda speak about the importance of small businesses to the U.S. economy at the @ShopFloorNAM Spri… https://t.co/NUXKczhW97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phattsao @AltUSPressSec @DanCrenshawTX @IlhanMN https://t.co/uNSUqqIQ6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGGYAZALEA “Lil’ Sally Walker walking down the street! She didn’t know what to do so she jumped in front of me!”… https://t.co/XIRORKDC8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlieTaylor_ @Onthemoon54 She said “I have to cancel the test scores because I found out somebody had the answe… https://t.co/2Lwbg0l6xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if sports unions would do better with a PR strategy of “cut the fan costs by X or pay us a fair share.” Di… https://t.co/pWGmoBQajT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still trippin on the fact The Dream gave out both a quality and quantity project. Almost every song rockin. folks p… https://t.co/yYooEGfFA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happypeepsmusic @WhiteHouse I control my gun every day. Right on my right hip. Are you suggesting that everyone re… https://t.co/PXm357MODe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cubanlovesTrump @allidoisowen @Ellysa_Maye Right and you can see the indoctrination in schools nowadays too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SauberF1Team, can we have this as the paint scheme for the year? This is awesome! #F1 #WTF1 https://t.co/Xy1dlDeHL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yingyangsamurai Then add my birth on top of that lol Alright, not crazy for you, but crazy for my parents I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HungryTesla @NotRyanAdams @sheetz @plugshare Keep spreading the gospel bro. Hope notryan listens to you. @Tesla GR… https://t.co/k8E4NlrXx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress Delusions of grandeur seem likely. @AOC will take over the Democrat party if she survives the Democrat challenger in 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting the weight loss journey full on tomorrow. There's a reason I only do chest up pics. First goal lose 76… https://t.co/seJavkXArI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPawluk Know the plan from talking directly to Cash. Build from within and spend strategically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Days to my tag team partner @lahill122   I ❤️ You undisputedly https://t.co/eILjekztPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me Chillin' next to Madea's car!!!😊😂🚗#madeasfarewelltour https://t.co/6VsmWDfSnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommywheeldonjr @AlbertaSoccer @jgibson_john @CPLsoccer @CPLCavalryFC Hi Tommy would love to see/hear about what y… https://t.co/ZcvTvcS4fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[More McConnell douchery. He is having the vote to try to show dems are split. Only reason and for election propagan… https://t.co/EEPwaNBQEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵It's so demanding when  you're set on expanding A Boy supply And it's do taxing when the City keeps asking to conn… https://t.co/fgKWv4h5Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check me out talking Chicago sports with some old and new friends  https://t.co/UrZpC95MBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BY2PWpAGcx 🛑WE SEEN THIS SHOW BEFORE.*THEY'RE GOING TO THROW IT UNDER THE CARPET AND PROTECT THE PRESI… https://t.co/DThkPCu8q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business II sn't the problem; most Dems like a merit based system that existed when Reagan was prez, involved a me… https://t.co/mX8itZ0iFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas You have a wonderful wife Mr.President😁👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePornMistress @axajay @axajay  really love that you are wearing very sexy lingerie a very shiny sheer nude lace… https://t.co/cGVnqxlTP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence Dems are gonna go full blown socialism? Never go full blown socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras tanto una reta de futbolito!! 🎶con un cañonazo vuela el balón🎶  Gracias DIOS!! en Parador Turistico San Pe… https://t.co/xx5AIRybJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @DonLagreca describe every emotion I’ve had as an Islanders fan and why last night’s win meant so much… https://t.co/heWFerWsZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShewardBadd @davien_farr5 You think we can win the starting job over Ben Hicks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to stop @kopaceticbeer for a bit today. Tried a few New Beers and One of my Favorite Beers all time (Had a coup… https://t.co/BeiwKwa3hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headbanger practice for @lost_lands this fall with @Excision 🦖 https://t.co/CMI1Vb79Qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bullshit. @SenatorBurr @realDonaldTrump It's coming. You Republicans are scum bags. Vote them out!! #VoteBlue2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Underpants Skips Out on a Four-Figure Bar Tab ... Tra La LA! (@ Bernards Township Library in Basking Ridge,… https://t.co/zpg3M7lo0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow my cat has been a heat-seeking cuddle missile for the side of my face that had dental work yesterday. Today will be rough…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetWithBobby @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/gohIT3eHxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDNHL This is what hockey fans want from their players https://t.co/ODSEPg5fXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today should be Friday not Thursday. Being Friday Eve isn't good enough for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, enough heavy policy debates for tonight.  Time for a really stupid one.  Deluded temporary Californian… https://t.co/Hw0GFY29iY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need A Custom Dial Created ? Need Borderless Setting ? We Got Ya Covered SERIOUS INQUIRIES ONLY PLEASE Contact When… https://t.co/XOtsyp1S8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like ppl are arguing about the relationship between race and class again so I’ll submit Fred Moten’s take: “[… https://t.co/ANhKY3Lz85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMarkPBarry What crazy fool would believe that?  Look at what happened in Libya--Kim Jong-un sure knows what happ… https://t.co/eSgZWvyeFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grilled Tuna Steak 🐟🥩 Brussels ➕ bacon ➕ onion butter ➕ balsamic 😋 Zucchini and green beans Plate full of veggies w… https://t.co/P4gR2f84IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaFOX32 Good morning, Sylvia! Have a blessed weekend! Thanks for always being awesome! https://t.co/YoLFiZIPaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't even really watch baseball, but Bryce Harper signing that deal with the Phillies is HUGE! Not only for the… https://t.co/iBZyBy4CF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DAVILACOLON No exageres Luis! 😉 Yo solo veo como 55 en la foto, no los “cien gatos” que mencionas! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vuelosolo @betocastilla @ClouthierManuel ... que a la fecha no han podido comprobar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brit_lv I always laugh when I drive past this grocery nearby https://t.co/hHQDyMj1Yy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1st Player Signed from the @SAFCProAcademy to the @SanAntonioFC 1st team. A major milestone in our club history… https://t.co/5wCnLX7KTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waflanagan @DGRinMSP @RealMattyMcBoy @TheGeoffey LOL. Thanks. I do nothing but soap and water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DameGrundy @HoarseWisperer Tax cut is only one year in and has helped boost economic growth, tightened the labor m… https://t.co/IPark0dTf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not saying this to be hateful in the slightest BUT I swear you all put your significant others in the closest u… https://t.co/5AvaLLMjOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenifa_0_Jenny How u mad at sidney he been loyal and he got her a vegas residency and plenty of shows , that's good work to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[NHL trade deadline is tomorrow. #VGK should only have one target: @GrittyNHL .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKrisBarr well you should give she picks cause last 2 you gave me ASU half and Iowa half Gabe been garbage...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilmilch @ScottShap34 that would be my biggest drawback on going..... hard enough to get to the rink for a 4pm gam… https://t.co/boRc2TMTOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of comedy for you. This happens every time my dad looks something up. Lol https://t.co/sP4EaYSPGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why but this is what I pictured watching #leavingnetherland https://t.co/6eczm6IkbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdIsBackKAG2020 @BlueSea1964 @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Impeach all socialists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening, friends!  Robert, special education teacher from Cleveland. Bouncing in and out tonight. #multitasking #pln365]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kellzbewellz @dalocksmith S*** I could tell you all about me too, but just not as fast and fancy, and put down over bomb ass Beats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aggiesalltheway @marchmadness And minus Queta, playing with the same players.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Scripture #scripture #scriptureoftheday #bible #bibleverse #biblequotes #godisgood #godisgreat #roswell… https://t.co/fP8UHeMgiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana es San Valentín ¿Qué es el Amor? Escucha el programa de esta semana  Conoce, Ama y Vive Tu Fe Podcast Audio - https://t.co/klucXcPi2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Never Never Forever Forever by @TheVeilBrewing @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/ZwjQCv6PV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InvictosSomos @InvictosSomos ya vio lo a pasa con la @CONMEBOL y el torneo @Libertadores donde los equipos no son… https://t.co/TSHiP6VFna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill If @realDonaldTrump had any money, I’d say he was backing this lawsuit a la Peter Thiel. But @peterthiel i… https://t.co/XV79q3VJY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cruz22 @RiceBaseball I bet there is a Cruz in there! Good luck boys and to the Owls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aliasimme is going to win some grand slam tennis titles I'm thinking. What a talent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a pleasure being a part of such a diverse ecosystem. @partnerforce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webboxingleague @BlackTowerRadio I believe he has a much better shot than most. I was really impressed by what he… https://t.co/GjS6A6PZZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roommate: “Hey I have to get up early! Will you please be quiet!” Me: “Cool!! Will do. If ur up super early will u… https://t.co/zIXdpIpbzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stardust_1416 Another big anti POTUS troll is RyanHillMI. He pops up as fast as the Krassenstein bros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ragarci2 @MIRTHxCRISIS One of the most fascinating cases of copyright was around Girl Talk, have a watch: https://t.co/v9tKbfDuId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Bukowski Turn 89 targets into a helluva lot more than 55/636/2 with disinterested blocking and an inability… https://t.co/pdCiEvVJqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marty_mcfly43 owes me a 30 pack when i get home. Don’t forget it you weasel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Hollywood Wax Museum https://t.co/B1EvKzv99p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eggako2 @DebbieR52621893 @realDonaldTrump Then you have major crimes https://t.co/7shSNi7a39 Undocumented immigran… https://t.co/pDtnBH2Zko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aubrey Plaza is half Puerto Rican. Author Justin Torres is half Puerto Rican. Aubrey Plaza is hosting the Independe… https://t.co/Gn6DgXoACQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is fast, in all the time when you’re looking forward toward the future, Don’t forget to look up #LookUp @ Los… https://t.co/pM1BTnC6al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packing for a quick business trip, taking the dog out, and drinking coffee... helloooooo Wednesday morning. https://t.co/ZCwDdHQsIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There definitely are worse places to watch the #sunrise than #SpringTraining. ⚾️ ☀️ 🌵 https://t.co/7Q5jjbLmdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohndMeyer Start you own @BaconOps movement. OH Wait!!! There is already a @BaconOps movement. 🤣 My mother-in-law… https://t.co/YvzUOYXpoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel that the GOP acted so terrible that I feel maybe they are guilty as hell along with Trump. They were embarra… https://t.co/LDQnfwabaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[with Recharge you can book a home by the minute to shower, change, or rest after a redeye. free 30 minute nap to re… https://t.co/4h7M4LwQIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottwww @nealboudette Because if it’s several, they’re running 20,000 miles a year. Which would be hard to do in… https://t.co/7LBohzq0xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Chas......you’ve worked so hard and deserve all of the accolades!!!  It’s been a pleasure getting t… https://t.co/N69qn9zA8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @HillaryClinton I voted for her because I knew him to be crooked! I hadn't known just how much he is corrupted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name another brand that has customers with this level of commitment to its mission. Amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@500mbVorticity @NWSBirmingham For a TDS, the correlation coefficient generally needs to be below 0.90. Here, it is 0.97-0.98. Not a TDS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@930Summer We'll probably hunker home for a while. We'd like to explore a bit more of the US (Montana, Utah, Dakotas, etc)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really up on this tower jamming to country while enjoying this Kansas snowy view 🥶💆🏻‍♂️]]></document></documents></author>