<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I need to get some ideas for my birthday downpacked!! photo shoot first 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so embarrassing and stupid i honestly hate myself, ima just disappear for a bit. thxxxs ✌🏼 https://t.co/kGBxqAR9jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elreys doctor called me and told me he was to high on his vitamins and iron like how are you to high on vitamins lm… https://t.co/zUyr0AyGN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatalanKay @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @Sgt_LarkinsGang @Windagayle @nanafrey7 @Christina_Roof @tkeleiott… https://t.co/cMtVah6lzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing Agent Provocateur and smelling like Dior. I should probably go now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning the process of writing a letter using voice and deciding between whole truth and perception. #3.15… https://t.co/XX79tXIhJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[[ SUNDAY ] Join us Sunday, March 10th from 1-3 pm for an open house at this amazing private estate in Central Austi… https://t.co/RtWJbqaxq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasSadoski I’m quite sure there was a HIPAA VIOLATION (privacy rights) here.  The family should sue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristarenee7 Just got home from the worst night at work and this made me smile. Lucky to have a friend like you kris miss you already]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can’t keep characters who look similar straight in TV shows and movies. I need a filter that hovers the… https://t.co/LEl2KmCyO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you River-&amp; Chase,this looks like your dad,long blonde kid https://t.co/RYx7nIpJGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw shanehallofficial and his band for the first time last night at prohibitionsd BLEW MY MIND! He’s playing at t… https://t.co/iccogETStB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who needs to hear this today, but call your parents and tell them you love them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiChism @_taracook There’s seriously an request list right now. Who knew 🤷🏼‍♀️ lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m taking friend applications. Dms are open for that. FEMALES ONLY lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times dressing in character today to get ready for our Dr. Seuss Read-a-thon. #lpsAD #lpsleads #WonderWoman https://t.co/7M4Fh8IPzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gym sounds way different when you forget your headphones... 😳😕 https://t.co/LV3W70x1Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Elyse &amp; Jarretts Place in Seattle, WA https://t.co/h9p3ylQrZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaileyLund happy late birthday to my forever roomie/friend/mom! Can’t thank you enough for helping me start tech s… https://t.co/RjGlVkRurk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will notice my stomach has a white line under my bathing suit. It’s that bad. https://t.co/RdRM6F3eqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaSchuld @NewsNatalie @BarreCode_MKE @sarajohnsauce @StephBuffamonte Not bad at all 9:30am!!!! I wanna go again, come with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are these ppl creeping on my stories.... like either follow me like a normal person or get out of my page lol wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of patience, love, progress and sunshine this morning to start this Wednesday 💛💛 https://t.co/paAHSqdEFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt And which President prosecuted &amp; spied on reporters?  Let’s be real here. https://t.co/hqQfp8WX80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpoplover9911 @pavedtheworld P.S. I really like MinHo since watching him ShineE in Hwarang!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When internships overlap.  @ParkHillPS #intern with Park Hill Communications, Mary Garrett, interviews Professional… https://t.co/OtSeWccQ5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexChalekian @craigiskowitz @FinTechie @jaypalter @TheRudinGroup @psb_dc @kirsten_plonner @jlahita_IFP That’s the… https://t.co/6qDzhuri52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think Grey’s Anatomy can’t get any better...  here they are better than ever!! @GreysABC… https://t.co/98aYOF1ft1]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I mean obviously not at 100% because I just said currently and rn in the same sentence. But it’s fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrardVP @MariaLuisaLebar One of the smartest most passionate people I know #PeelProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heaviest snow arriving now then will taper off through evening. My forecast next at 630pm on kdka #KDKA #kdkawx @ K… https://t.co/7Xd4ejnsHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so smitten &amp; happiest when I’m with you. ❤️ https://t.co/1CxcCLx2Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA  Now that I’ve laughed my evil laugh, I have a question. Who is going to make sure the… https://t.co/ekLc7HSUwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading Mario Vargas Llosa this morning, on Venezuela in Nov. 2013: “[It] will spend many years recovering everythi… https://t.co/Qy1AWd4AzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[aww sister you’re not dumb and you don’t deserve that! i love you, stay up!  🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frankie thinks The Spot is better than Big Star.. Should I break up with him or...??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simarilian Because they don’t want mothers raising children. We may not do it the way the state approves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to practice emotional first aid | Guy Winch https://t.co/162pPoLnQy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else hates that when you pay at Panera it asks how much you’d like to tip? Seriously? I’m already paying waay t… https://t.co/Gcr1ebkunH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at @PLTWorg we want to inspire students , turns out it’s the students who inspire us!  Via  @vincebertram… https://t.co/5z0ZCjJ5HI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I second that emotion. Hate to ask for followers, but to take the steps that only We the People can take, the more… https://t.co/OC6pw8VVwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why Dems smell blood. GOP leadership and lawmakers are mostly flat footed here and have little clue how to… https://t.co/AUyCkXTx8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that gets aggressive when they excited the song for the fireworks came on and I’ll say “get your ears on mothafucka” lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSassyMama @NEWS9 You’ve got me curious about matzo ball soup. I’ve never tried it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CentralMATweets @ShiriSpear @boston25 That’s the “you’re screwed and you don’t want to know” area. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy that she kept the song with the acoustic vibe!  I remember first stanning Billie and hearing this and… https://t.co/s4DxwQaL2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 44% Off Blow-Dry at Studio B Salon and Style Bar https://t.co/U6mWVnkF8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CPAC is a cancer on the country. Can you imagine if liberals held a conference every year? I mean I think it would… https://t.co/trX1tqjZl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[at #NYC🗽 during #NYFW 📷 taken by @8and2  #YuFujiwara —————————————————————————— #FashionWeek #documentary… https://t.co/SayTwzeOzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephItUp123 @COOPaulsen @Vegas_Princess_ @XxCinthiaXx @Juliacardona55 @Tishka11 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t care if y’all come for me bc i know i’m right about this. no it doesn’t make ppl who go to bigger universit… https://t.co/BIgCW6AgXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj When you make a statement, then say "But" that means forget everything I just said...This is how I really… https://t.co/h663Mu9hxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/F1RJdVjkI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; this ain’t about me 😂I just peep everything that other people do around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanting more Truffle fries. Who makes your favorite fries? @ WINEBELLY https://t.co/R7g6lfWXA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought my hangovers where just becoming more violent because I was getting older but I went to the doctor cause… https://t.co/bT6x28LJfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[the same group of people who mockingly call liberals ‘snowflakes’ and ridicules the idea of safe spaces with troll… https://t.co/bgQgv1A7Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como me emperra, me caga, me frustra que me manden solicitudes de gente vendiendo esa madre que no se qué es y me v… https://t.co/GBKXtjKd82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarvinLarry @Kerry91756735 @minxy99 @StopBadDocs @headdock @Kelly @LelenaPeacock @HilaryKimMorden @Katamac1967… https://t.co/8shKPxi975]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne I'm so, so sorry for your loss. In 2010 I lost a son at 21 wks. The pain never goes away, but your daughter… https://t.co/iHdYquBVsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know she's his daughter,  she's a liar too!!! I'm still waiting to hear from Silk and Diamond 😂😂😂😂😂😂… https://t.co/Rb9NGsTAx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABOUT LAST NIGHT// 💙 We support the arts, so when @sonjatmorgan asked us to support this event we didn’t hesitate.… https://t.co/Y6LrhI2evY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night replays in my head n I can’t hold the tears back anymore it’s distorting me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @iregco It’s ridiculous that people accept this bull shit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to know when she's going to be set her  down and remind her she is a congress member her words matter and it… https://t.co/a5gAhyBFCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have  children in your life who love to read with you? This charming  little  train ride will thrill your hearts an… https://t.co/zlGze7cpvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[May you be surrounded with LOVE ❤️ on this Valentine’s Day by a certain someone.. family.. friends.. a pet or by yo… https://t.co/sYE5qYt4ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleychestrman May be good for him to get back down to the ground floor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisVolz So much time and money wasted on the border. When is our government going to focus on the real challenge… https://t.co/eqbNrNyWMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnonymousOtto Pat Robertson is non-religious and does not know it. Probably needs a beating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did @billmaher allow @johnlegend to get away with his "#HumanRights for #Palestinians" comment without stopping… https://t.co/9vhYVVu6pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm trying to free up some space on my phone lol.  #meme #dank #dankmeme #imgur #ifunny #twitter #tumblr #pinterest… https://t.co/VeYGVYHyp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_lefty5 Bruh think he a godly pg but no one knows him cuz he don't play comp i would like to see it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaptiv I hear you don’t answer emails so I’m trying here. I wasn’t able to use my app/contact anyone to cancel for… https://t.co/tBpttpm1X8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLilPoundcake @washingtonpost I think it's illegal to make someone stateless for any reason. But that was back w… https://t.co/8jvSiTnEVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVE ME ALL/ALL/ALL YOUR WORRIES AND CARES - JESUS https://t.co/Xo1hWTZ6FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can put ANYTHING to music! ⬆️ student engagement #PA #R10CIRCLE #R10ECservices #ECEchat @ICanReadDallas https://t.co/Z7IDiBn2iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Certainly can understand why.!  What a couple!  Please finish the rest of your time on the show loving, r… https://t.co/RanCeLhTap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever me and Raul drink together it’s the funniest shit. We talk maaaaaad shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finalbloodbath @VivaMarlon Dude yes like $582 but just for the rear brakes and rotors or whatever. Like everything… https://t.co/MLp3Gk204u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl at school said.... how you wear thongs, always having something ride up ya butt 😂😂😂 it’s comfy to me😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends and I watching the Christopher Robin Movie:  Ingrid: If Pooh got snatched by a freaking heffalump I will… https://t.co/BaxlKsKtvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosomar_tr @redshadowpr @deddieromeropr @millycangiano @EngellMarie Guapisimos estos tres caballeros que mas qu… https://t.co/h61jIgSezG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this crazy lil girl🤷🏾‍♀️🤦🏾‍♀️🥰 New install......minimal leaveout.  Flawless per usual💆🏾‍♀️ @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/F2RRx6koaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meal Prep Sunday 💙💚💛🧡❤️💜  Had a busy day but I still found time to get my Meal Prep in for the week. When you have… https://t.co/ckPNtuEgUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyMcGarrity @jeff_wire @RealJamesWoods Not at all, most of us aren’t brainwashed, America hating, no facts, no… https://t.co/UaYlHyj35d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boston25 your time/temp on air is off by about 25 minutes. Thought I was losing it 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is starting to fall again in Henderson ❄️ This was recorded from the Anthem area around 4:30 am #8NN #SnowVegas https://t.co/Nzu6S12aac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katie gets outta the goal and gets the ball back. Panthers transition and are on offense]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah, i’ve got boy problems. that’s the human in me. bling bling, then i solve em. that’s the goddess in me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly try and make everyone happy but there is just no way. It’s like I’m the only bottom in the room filled w… https://t.co/4SJXnQga3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishspy @JoeC1776 Kirsten I think you are good person but you have lost all logical reasoning ability. You need t… https://t.co/fn5lE9s7Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not freedom@of speech this is libel @SenAlexander @MarshaBlackburn @DrPhilRoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT: FIND YOUR VALENTINE AshWeHo The Legendary DJ cazwellofficial on deck sisipandaofficial performing LIVE Cel… https://t.co/at5fMDZsDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning can be messy, and we welcome that in our no-ssh @Shepard_LC with the 6th grade #cardboardchallenge today!… https://t.co/U7rIwlHBB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @BeachIlove •  •  •  •  •  The Splendor 🌴 From Mark Girardeau @mark_girardeau while aboard newportcoastalad… https://t.co/guds5X2DBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A calico angel in the morning light 🐱✨☀️ @ Bradenton, Florida https://t.co/thDJG7Wbqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredibleCulk Depends on the class, gender, likes and dislikes. But too much is never enough of a white chocolate… https://t.co/rbNJHPAIkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is National Athletic Training Month https://t.co/lFopZ7W1eI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman YES SHE SHOULD BE IMPEACHED CALLING THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES A MF. I REPORTED HER TO THE ET… https://t.co/KZsADg2D98]]></document></documents></author>