<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Buenas noches @RAEinforma ¿Cómo debo referirme a un actor que ha ganado varías veces un Oscar? 1- Tiene varios Osca… https://t.co/NDSieDlCXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carter's 1st day of skiing. Awesome day at Blue Mountain and Carter loved it. Until next time Kids at Blue.… https://t.co/9yU9lyXO8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubric94652453 @ShireenQudosi That...might work? I, at very least understand your points and agree with your reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ireland That and the notion of creating more dry land by levying or otherwise walking off a river from its natural… https://t.co/z724BnkaLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz Monsters would snatch my feet if I slept stretched out so I would always sleep curled up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a stripper wants money, give it to her. She’s entertaining you and she likely hates you and hates herself so the… https://t.co/y3PHc7rc1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaBluMamba Plus I never said oxtail was a prize cut i said it was a trash cut like chicking or how ever u spell that slave shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Veronic55917416 Don't you think I've taken enough. Seriously, like I'm asking for more shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast playing the 2nd Anniversary Party at the @BeardedFoxBrew last night. The beer, the crowd, and the food… https://t.co/hewl0sXUZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown after finding out he was traded to the Bills.... @ Heinz Field https://t.co/rB2Kc0u936]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenlemonWSOC9 @NABJ @NABJREG3 Great seeing you again, @kenlemonWSOC9! Your insights on that panel were invaluable,… https://t.co/HeTgUBcaAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the theme music from Hunt for Red October going through my head?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eatin 🤑🤑🤑💯💯💯💯🏋🏿‍♂️🏋🏿‍♂️🏋🏿‍♂️🏋🏿‍♂️ #HTers #HashTags #active #bodybuilding #cardio #cleaneating #determination #diet… https://t.co/1TvZ0MW20F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get a kick out of the announcers talking about Tiger as if it’s still 2002!]]></document><document><![CDATA[En ICATSON con el peruano, Ing. José Luis Barrientos Maraví, al finalizar la plática "Manejo de personal en Agro -… https://t.co/3rmf0hAj6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are my heart, my soul. You are my sunshine. What I’m trying to say is I love you and I’m so happy to be with yo… https://t.co/oEe6HMHdu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[In tonight’s EarlGaming news, I discovered you can give your Switch a nickname and I came exactly as close as you’d… https://t.co/WIK7hVxFRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a psa for my homies out there getting laid: ALWAYS PEE AFTER SEX !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dshow23 I was just thinking of some of the shenanigans that Don, Darrel, and Dad used to do when they were together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Girls1MicPod @adamconover If you get him on your show. Can you try to convince Adam to do a segment on the adult industry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKONOHIO We the people have a right to know which politicians were paid off &amp; they should charged!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a sad sad fact for our country. Would they allow there own children to be treated that way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrollinThunder I dunno, the Pittsburgh Puffins and the Washington Lower Case Letters look pretty solid this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsMrNeil Honestly, @taylorswift13 #TS1989 #DLX! Music iz 1derful soo many GREATEST HITS yeti this album is atta… https://t.co/b3BW2y6RBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrenIShiKiddo Who grants babykillers religious sacraments? Need to avoid that "church"]]></document><document><![CDATA[La inversión tiene que tener un ROI rápido, para comenzar a sacar estudiantes con buenas bases en matematicas, cien… https://t.co/xckF1EhHLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_potter114 You will rock this out! You will come back stronger and faster. You got this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m old enough to remember when the Raiders refused to pay one of the best defensive players in the league so they… https://t.co/dAZuBq4Vcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What you know about blood? Bitch you ain’t even my type” #bars -@sushitrash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlyReloaded @MarcelloNova @mbachelet Cualquiera persona con un mínimo de sentido común se percató de eso. En to… https://t.co/7oNEBmVRjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schug_Keith @LarryTankersley Lucks doing it too. So is Wilson. So is Ben.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Bella Runyan for her recognition.  All-SJ 1st team and All-SJ Non Public.  Well deserved!  #GoFoxes.… https://t.co/G4XIFuZHKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neoavatara Go on... ...Because I think ...not. (I mean, it's not incoherent, I just think it's wrong.) But I'm ope… https://t.co/IhXO1ECKjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bravesburner I know he had a sore shoulder, and that scares me a bit, however Gohara is my pick. The kid has so much upside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allygracee_ @LouisLA14 Have you seen our cornfield to cattle ratio, best in the country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before every meet. 🖤 Year of Being Slefish. 🙇🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/VGVy5gblew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wileyx @DavidRagan Joey L #22  is on fire. Brad K #2 will get up front fast, Hopefully he can capitalize and win i… https://t.co/86hdB07KRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CenterGroveHS @msichicago @PLTWorg @tveerkamp Another Exceptional Educactional Experience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetTee_77 I understand...lost my dad almost a year ago...... April 27th.... God bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganBattalion @ShaneSheehy @BernieSanders Really starting to like this Sanders guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Nolan is more curious than George. @ Universal Studios Orlando/Citywalk https://t.co/y3mHQiO3dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stuck on a @GOtransitLW train for what looks like the next two hours due to a fatality. Unfortunate situation to be… https://t.co/kjOljcpRvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Coach Mike Neal and Norman High girls getting that state championship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KneesPenguin @MadameAmerica Ain’t that truth I live here &amp; can escape 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NBC studio doing an utter u-turn after the knives came out right after the match? ODFO...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyehuntyou And as for a living our lives accordingly, I can live a life of goodness and charity, a life that any C… https://t.co/dR3KojfLlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fave YouTube comments from #MiddleChild 😂😂   The dislikes are from the fire department.  This shit is harder tha… https://t.co/Dtqe0Xcnlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andymtaylor @5NEWS The @arkansasonline piece makes it clear that the funding has nothing to do with lunch, somethi… https://t.co/3gusOSJcQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pravdy_net_ @pricklykaktus @RussianEmbassyC @mfa_russia @PMSimferopol @RusembUkraine @EmbassyofRussia @RussiaUN… https://t.co/zxxoFqHCqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait to have a family of my own of beautiful kids &amp; adorable puppies w/ the love of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/CFRqo4lCuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you assholes criticizing the WNBA, I bet that any single one of those women can make a better sandwich than you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to guarantee that in the next elections there will be a patriot in each electoral polling to guarantee the… https://t.co/p5bP9KZthq]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2003 we saw @RealKurtAngle @ZachGowen and @StephMcMahon all in respective matches slay the beast @BrockLesnar Fo… https://t.co/NttEgHBnvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you red E for me #shawnmoralesfanart by syrs wearing @gearworxxx photo by @jaredmechaber @ Precinct DTLA https://t.co/qBtaKpyz27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a good time with the fam @jayFredo . No picture but I felt like y’all should know lmao #PirateFam #ECU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertJohnDavi @POTUS You are an equally good patriot and actor/singer/showman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magistraJ I use my textbook (Ecce Romani) for vocabulary and grammar pacing only. Other than that we basically rea… https://t.co/ZNVIgTU3mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an honor! Thank you, KCS teachers, staff for making our school one of the #BestPlacesToWork in S. Florida. Thi… https://t.co/TY5gBJPwI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew flipping an image horizontally could make it so cursed? https://t.co/zsrZiE7mpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr I got @JEarnhardt1’s autograph Saturday! He’s a cool cat! Trying to find you is like trying to find a leprechaun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The inside of my spumoni dessert!! This is absolutely my favorite from caffe.capri #motivation #positivity… https://t.co/AxuGfW7aLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcuban Then you support free PUBLIC higher education for everyone and private higher education for those that choo… https://t.co/C1Ncs7Ddbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING RIGHT NOW: President Trump is meeting with North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un in Hanoi, Vietnam. Live feed… https://t.co/2BCm4Wnidq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salute to @irapbetterthanu for the reaction video to Stephen Allen Music- Do or Die off his new album African Ameri… https://t.co/HOBK71458O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3onyourside How can anyone hear that story and be against the death pemal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcoffey06 @blainebrown24 @j427floU @EastOKChiro @finebaum @KySportsRadio @CFBPlayoff https://t.co/nkcLNRA12y]]></document><document><![CDATA[KNEA's @desettiks says they don't have any problem with HB 2257 #ksleg #ksed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDHSAA State B Final is underway! @DeSmetBulldogs vs @EthanRustlers catch it on @SDPBSports #SDHoops19 #ArgusPreps https://t.co/jwODixufzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubinafillion @femrica @AOC @SenWarren @SenSanders AOC=socialism=genocide!]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Pool F - @NTBasketBall def. @CKaTTBasketbal 66-60 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one day I play to get my ass up n go to hump day the forecast says it’s will rain 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[That stench wafting through Washington DC today is Michael Cohen frying Trump's ass  at his congressional hearing!! https://t.co/n8QqEkDDL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara And allllll pundits should be asking people who say he’s a liar, “Tell me what he was caught lying ab… https://t.co/4lfAWNI8NH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump And everyone as mind numbingly stupid as u shouldn’t be allowed to drive a car, own… https://t.co/tfBSk4VtgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It doesn’t become important until WE get your attention” #TNM #WEwantALLthaSMOKE https://t.co/MDNNG3XDtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blondenorsky You'll know, I think. In prison, Jean Valjean was dogged by a guard, Javert. After some years Valjean… https://t.co/tVTkj3o1Z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning everyone ☕☕☕ When leading, one should teacher and show others if they are not understanding, don't make a f… https://t.co/1E5EfAUEyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four units left - 11Park - #newcondos - #closeout - priced from $995,000 to $1,225,000 - BEST PRICE PER SQFT FOR NE… https://t.co/4s3XyjFdvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuburnSoftball It’s all good 😁 just making sure my dementia wasn’t kicking in 😂 keep working! WDE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great event tonight. (Friends of Scouting Dinner). And a proud speech given by the Honorable Rex Tillerson; long ti… https://t.co/1JJMSFWcx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve never tasted the Dunkin’ Donuts coffee roll.. shit is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @realDonaldTrump @NASA THANKYOU ELON, Without you it wouldn't have HAPPENED! Check Out My ROTARYWING for… https://t.co/9rC8OwwSNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to springing forward, daylight savings time. March 10. I like the extra daylight]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our system was established so small states like Maine aren’t dominated by big states like New York,” Brakey said.… https://t.co/Nzn6eAGZw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[They Should have banned Hundreds Of Thousands !!!!!!Durbin You Are The One Who Should Have Been Banned Years Ago Yo… https://t.co/6fkOh42NAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWG_News Bacteria and Viruses have transfiguration we must keep ahead of them with that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing with my new camera😜. Please leave a comment below and subscribe .. jajaj.  #enjoylife… https://t.co/BWMmw1Kl3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenGutowski @CharlesFLehman Is the question why so many or why has it risen (if it has)? The federal constitut… https://t.co/O3elVtWt3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to the @Tylers_atTAcK ...recruiting friends and grabbing coffee. It’ll take all of us to end this madness. https://t.co/0CYbv1yl8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sunshine_1601 Whoever it is just just block they ass and keep it moving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Stop the lies little Eddy! Stop the hate!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMZebraCommish @ADs_NMAA Hey ... don’t give her an out. Let’s GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!! 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaleighHoffman I'm going to die 20 years before you. Just think of that whenever you need comforting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump Bugs cost $30 people. Retreaving it is harder than dropping them unless you use wireles… https://t.co/cWaJIZiAzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen of Hearts drawing tonight at 7, pot at $3530.00 right now @ Scalpers BAR &amp; Grille https://t.co/W6FfQ3UGOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me smile.  Any cheer with @DrPeteEdwards1 in at Nordecke will not sound like last year’s owner cheers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaCantanteDulce Jeje un bello CANTANTE porque ERES un lobo jeje me encantaron Besitos y Abrazotes para uatedes Her… https://t.co/bjibC7xb8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its funny and all to laugh at Loomer and Wohl because they’re ridiculous but what they did in Minnesota is also a s… https://t.co/AewBYrZvul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woLgnuH @missy_ryan First of all I mean I think they have received little better in Afghanistan and Iraq as well a… https://t.co/IGs6aC18MY]]></document></documents></author>