<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Why not have a consultation with Elchapo to how and where drugs etc.come through??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec It is sad that there is so much effort to hide the lies and corruption of the Trump administration.  I wi… https://t.co/7ZZnYOD5M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the Fallout 4 Soundtrack, again on Valentine’s Day . Also love the new Fo76 music. Wish I could buy it! ❤️ya’ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[wish me luck i just Know my crochet group is gonna drag me to for the Whole hour today rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahgirl @FallOutJerks Me too. Back then he wasn’t married and flirted w me—-oh. We’re not talking about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burchama @MikaelaHuntNews Oh man, I live even closer to Grant hospital now than I probably ever have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfanderson I don't think so, they sell it at Trader Joe's and next to the peanut butter in grocery stores. Seek it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @angela_bagan Pay for a HIGH POWER ATTORNEYS/team to fight this abuse if u mean it. It takes $$$ to… https://t.co/zjN5qqGaKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bron bout to work extra hard to get into the playoffs just to get swept by GS, 1st round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have y’all never stepped foot on Bathtub Reef Beach??? What about Honeymoon?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phervik @KTHopkins Yes Latin!!! If I had to do it all again, I would. You can get better understanding of grammar by learning Latin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollywood514 Him and Colin Jost go on tour together often. I'd love to see them both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Taylor Prophecy 3/4/19 Leadership will be punished by God.  https://t.co/WX6IXMr5li]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to all of our @EastonWrestling Jr. High and JV wrestlers this weekend in their individual @PIAADistrictXI… https://t.co/4l1BZnl0lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umami!! - Drinking a Bourbon Barrel Aged Wee Heavy (2018) by @ZaftigBeer @ Metro Area Transit #8  — https://t.co/3W7XQ17p0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to the work day - had a seminar on the mind/body connection, and got a heart healthy breakfast 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Wojcicki: Censor YouTube Kids - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/wPky9HZEId via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[God told me to STOP focusing on trying to make money on my own and He gave me a small sun dress. 🤗 ❤️ https://t.co/r56zSxj4xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I denied that ado, even tho it’s going to rain later 🥺  I’m so proud of myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[why woeful i get drunk on a thursday night knowing damn well i have a classes tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 If there was anything of substance Mueller would have acted on it already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beeeswanky @lildez100k Bitch don’t do too much 😂💯 we was at the apartment for HOURS bitches ran right past my car… https://t.co/JgQfyUK8m4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lolo_NoELA Of course they were women. A man would have say “boy grow some balls!” ⚽️ 🏀 🏈   😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews @sntpvenezuela 🤦‍♀️OSEA.... k ni siquiera para informarte tú mismo sirves??? Deja de las mentirás k… https://t.co/YAELygfr2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because they repeat it doesn’t make it true!  Do the research because lying is rampant thanks to Trump!… https://t.co/3fSFSjgvKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[To best AM news team ever @3esp @ireneoconnorch3 @ScotHaney3 @NicoleNalepaTV hope your day is filled with love ❤️ https://t.co/bpFpGX9ED0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @summerjpops for participating in #Mardi Gras to support @delawaretech students!  #CoolestDessertInTown… https://t.co/WFSoPTWSVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMKristenBell @daxshepard halfway through season 2 Veronica Mars...and I know this is sudden, but I’d like to be y… https://t.co/NxCCQPw95q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @QueensDABrown for your 28 years of service and commitment to #queens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaReginaa @veramagalhaes @jairbolsonaro A @veramagalhaes seria chamada aqui nos EUA de "Gold digger", é como mul… https://t.co/cIjcIwRHEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerwhat16 @OntarioPCParty @fordnation @OntLiberal @OntarioNDP @OntarioGreens @CBCNews @CBCQueensPark… https://t.co/jNbMPslMNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @BernieSanders It would be easier to believe this if he had done ONE single thing in the 40 years he's b… https://t.co/KqOMloyLyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, @EmpanadaDada has churros! #Winterfest #LowellWinterfest #likelowell https://t.co/7QER5IGjXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Statue of Liberty ✔️ Ellis island ✔️ then we headed on to the 9/11 memorial and museum #manhattan #America… https://t.co/LSiVNUMpfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all do know the fuck up is the husband right? This wouldn’t happen if he didn’t reciprocate Jordyn’s actions.....… https://t.co/uT0uK9CGXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dramaima @4literacylife @villani824 Thank you for inviting me! Being in 3rd grade is the highlight of my day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMANGO @DannyLeBlanc24 @spyderrider63 @CupCakeLady1313 @KCJO_LABMOM889 @Pixxydoodle @dega_boy_87 @mustag_girl71… https://t.co/RLjPWoeAnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @w_terrence TY Jack for that info. @w_terrence - I did a little dance myself.  btw, Jussie paid the guys with a check.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time I see a grapefruit I think about that one episode of drake and josh where they got fake arrested and the… https://t.co/YFbHL0nQ2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmchairExpPod should have @JohnMayer on. 🤯 armchair expert / current mood crossover would be 🔥🔥👏🏻 #armchairexpert… https://t.co/jOd3VcpRpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s so weird how so many parents these days have come to shutting their children up by leaving them unsupe… https://t.co/9d2bHy7zvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sifichick @AlmostShawn @imcorinnemec The news that the university of Sweden killed six dogs instead of giving them… https://t.co/CW9krMw9fC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Like Whaaat by Problem on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/N2HHpkaaKk Another one of @realDonaldTrump ‘s favorites. His… https://t.co/SxtwD4i54L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grandmommy tried to use the word “YEET” on words with friends and it wouldn’t let her. She’s thriving]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV Girls take the win 1-0 v. Lassiter! Way to go Eagles! @MiltonSoccer https://t.co/DtcdvCyqon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epallred @nypmetro Oh..@AOC is a cheating, dirty, lying, underhanded, deceiving, money hiding, fast favours, crazy… https://t.co/W0msEzBhdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think taking the lane is (should be!) legal but he had his hood on, was not looking around, had headphones on, an… https://t.co/XTnRtHVEat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorker @HollyMorris2 @MuseumModernArt One of my top favs. Would love to see this. Thanks for sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicrobioGen Ahhhhhh yesssssss let’s get a whole bunch of cool people together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for all of the support on my new single, “Hunter”💕 Over 1,000 streams in a week! Super grateful! Continue… https://t.co/2oFoYxebVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Henry. When the weather is nice I go a little crazy trying to do everything outside in a day like shooting bal… https://t.co/4JFQRTMTcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped my JUUL somewhere in my room. Y’all wish me luck that I can find it tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find you a partner who loves you as much as NASA loves robots #RelationshipGoals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maxine Waters calls for rallies across the country to oppose Trump https://t.co/SSPuA4iBBd via… https://t.co/mISCJUgjxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[February teaching kitchen recipe was mango salsa!  Stay tuned for our next teaching kitchen coming soon!… https://t.co/HgTKAmaiT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Antonio88404992 @amaliarebelde @bettysp3 @CouohLeticia @Chio90221187 @Gabriellags001 Buenas noches amiga linda https://t.co/SGirn7OGkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/db90RoeNKT  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 644-33  What happens in Vegas stays… https://t.co/2BYAWX5ENH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas Cody and Bellemare only two players that play 60 minutes every game... Deryk the only D that gives it his all... IMHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and Kurz: not best friends, after all https://t.co/UqYCKMWbDP @RonJBee @tony_ganzer @diplomacy_lab @liuglobal… https://t.co/1f69EcsRwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[still can’t get over how pretty the background is https://t.co/1NFR8fCgpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdMRound @atrupar @foxandfriends Independent of laws and accountability..... In his mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricedaddy7 More than one person has drowned trying to save an alcoholic. Self care isn’t something to feel guilty… https://t.co/z7dsNTYaE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm soft porn nude model married to bully in Chief 🤦‍♀️flipping great role model]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311Toronto @Ainslie_Ward24 They didn't do requests from 2 weeks ago.  So no. that's not a proper answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BECAUSE THEY DONT BELIEVE R CONSTITUTION  THEY SUPPOSE 2 TAKE OATH 4R COUNTRY WITH R BIBLE R CONSTITUTION  SWEARING… https://t.co/qh9VwFmx5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you can get THE SILENCE OF THE LAMBS for only $2.99 on #Kindle: https://t.co/DBFrILyDaC #thriller https://t.co/dMInAEbBTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can guarantee I will not get accepted by Penn or Temple. 😂 THAT TEST WAS HARD. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hollywood de pie y a la vez rendido frente a Queen. Presentación única en los #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is to say that not every person in our country is afforded the same opportunity as I have been privileged enou… https://t.co/8HiY69YTB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoked to see @TimJDillon headline tomorrow in #LA! He crushed it on @joerogan! https://t.co/gnpoypwqrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep telling everyone I live in New York’s version of Stars Hollow and if you still don’t believe me, please beho… https://t.co/BzNYpMIk87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBuckley @shnsf You look gorgeous Betty. Thanks for a look into your world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontStarr5 @NBAonTNT My son just turned 16 years old .... and he lives , breaths for basketball .... when he start… https://t.co/XYuBsCfKWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsareNazis @StephenKing @realDonaldTrump In all fairness do democrats ever tell the truth about votes or voting records?]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEAGUE OF WOMEN VOTERS ACTION ALERT: Please click here 👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 ERA Last Chance: https://t.co/0dNQeHxsTj @VAratifyERA @LWVVA @LWVLoudoun 🇺🇸💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you beautiful❤️❤️ I’m so glad we are friends because I don’t think I could survive college without you! I’m r… https://t.co/V8tcvJ9zzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confront? Pahleeze. Stop voting democrat to save America! They’re destroying our country right before our eyes. Sta… https://t.co/kMI56t0stT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discharge date!! March 9th, 2019 💜 Looking good here babe 😘 https://t.co/tibjuK5Np2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pwash25 really a joy to watch your kiddo play ball. I can’t even imagine how you feel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Errriee Hang in there sweetie. I thought the same thing when I lowered my Paxil. It was like night and day. Not a pretty decision..😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody Good morning. Same here! When my boys return to school tomorrow, that will show the full effects of… https://t.co/osYYe7oK7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 Hope you’re feeling better. I’ve had the crud for a week. I feel like I’ve complained too much, too… https://t.co/N1vWRTsL7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Krieger's first grade is loving this circle dance! #BowWowWow https://t.co/iGfxBS4kKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @CA_DivinityCats on giving everything you have on day 2 and brining home jackets. Thank you @GoCoastal for… https://t.co/5SCu0v7Sbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I might buy a dog  Puppy so I feel like I have a friend   If I move”  -my roommate who might relocate to a new cit… https://t.co/72c78CZV54]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news, @NDP clearly intends to fight for Quebec with the appointment of @alexboulerice to lead the charge. Bonn… https://t.co/aG9R8zyd7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's an empowered woman and I love her dearly. She inspired the girls to rise from their struggles and pursue thei… https://t.co/YRXjiKvqTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a preview of the #HanginTough30 festivities I attended in #NYC 🤩.  This was from the @buildseriesnyc @nkotb… https://t.co/DGoRHOMKbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT please. Here we go @DatelineNBC starts now!! #Dateline also your favorite is watching @MelanieScrofano… https://t.co/VjZnVXH3CA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #fattuesday so you know I had to go find a #vegan king cake! Mmmm I’m looking forward to a slice or two before… https://t.co/3KkgA78ZPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardEGrant @melissamccarthy @foxsearchlight WooHOO!!!! https://t.co/G5iLvsTL1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its like he knows I want to have a life and is doing everything he can to make me absolutely miserable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nataliew1020 You are a great mom. Sending love and prayers on your journey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOP the COLLECTION ● https://t.co/bI13JoDh6z  . . . . . #ShopDaddysGirl #DaddysGirl #rainbow #thick #urbanfashion… https://t.co/CxTs81E3Qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a beautiful 72° day!!  #GodsWondrousCreations 🙏💞 https://t.co/VNuYrtSnHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massive fire breaks out at DeKalb County office complex: https://t.co/dmIShSzSBU -- @DarrynMooreWSB is at the scene… https://t.co/qh3UcHAQJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw this on Facebook with the caption.                                              “Go to sleep or El Hee H… https://t.co/AwIzqOfvP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi cerramos semana  Gracias rturo024 por invitarme a ser el elenco de tu fiesta de cumpleaños   Gracias por confia… https://t.co/PKL0NERWzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crusader alumni Ryleigh Buck continues to achieve success on and off the softball field at WIchita State https://t.co/oyWgCdO5Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_e_nnedy Idk it was weird, I’ve never really heard someone say anything like that outside of the internet.]]></document></documents></author>