<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_morganadams_ people are stupid don’t listen to them i love you ♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This project brings a global issue into a sharp, local focus in #Savannah. Many practical applications on the horiz… https://t.co/rc5iEdnWys]]></document><document><![CDATA[There AIN’T no school like the the OLD school. pizzabyalex in Biddeford is the supreme pizza joint for Greek-style… https://t.co/NTxzC75nGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible work by our #abc13 team on this #CrisisOfFaith interactive page. @TomKochABC13 live from The Vatican thi… https://t.co/6Al8OZwklg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorjensen @WGRZ Yes please do... and tell him to speak to his doctor about blood clots and how to identify them in… https://t.co/pYOcvuMRiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Hate for our ways is raging inside of you, Who the hell do you think you are trying to force your BS on Am… https://t.co/Pxz3swCyi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be registered legally blind by the end of my stay at Vegas from all these bright lights in my face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babygirlnic wait bitch the fact that I posted this when I was illegal lmfaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walkin’ in a winter wonderland ... 69/365  #project365_2019  #project365 #day69 #stpaul #morningwalk #nofilter… https://t.co/ngsJmbcMZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️😁WE HAD TO SCREAM!😁⚠️  Virtual Self at @iiiPoints https://t.co/zRrzQQs58B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedBeretsM4All @RepBarbaraLee @NicholasPogson @KamalaHarris I am so confused. Congresswoman Lee has been a faithfu… https://t.co/II8sURl6f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesEDIT @Nikki29752620 @buckeyenut82 @Sebastian5706 It isn’t a rivalry so it’s not hard. Y’all try to make it on… https://t.co/tUFQvedq8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Night I fell asleep while facetiming my bf and before he hung up I was able to hear him say “babe I know you’r… https://t.co/h2TTOBq9UX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 Great thread discussion thank you @lynnv378 for asking the question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisonjaime He’s in @TGowdySC territory now. He’s taking note of Trump’s schedule, and using it at our expense.… https://t.co/181A5ajVkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Hang in there. Surely it's almost done. Seems like all the greatest hits are covered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aramark is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #FacilitiesMgmt job openings, including "Maintenance Mech… https://t.co/bp6XEjgFth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marizulca @AnicaVan @MichLdogs I could spend the entire day just watching her. Cuteness overload 🐱 🐈 😻😻😻😻😻😍❤️😍❤️🐈😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czthaday @HNTurtledove Not a cowboy. Boss Hogg. Look for him on YouTube.  It’s embarrassing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with a bunch of political nerds tonight #lovettorleaveit @ The Chicago Theatre https://t.co/5WPlKgcXh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin out. #showleg #tgirl #trans #transgender #MarysWeHo #sherilyns_hot https://t.co/dFfYWk0JWb https://t.co/6TqaT0MADr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@averyholton @LeeHumphreys @mariahlwellman @UUtah @UofUComm Exactly what we were talking about today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #fridayeve and we're getting ready to wrap it up for the weekend! What are you looking forward to the most?  F… https://t.co/Npz8jSdFMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[second college acceptanceee!!! @csunorthridge #kinesiologydance ❤️❤️❤️❤️ :))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouRaguse Love working with you Lou, you are among the best—often stand in awe of your gifts. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tachira Puente Simón Bolívar  Régimen de @nicolasmaduro Ordena a su lacayo criminal de guerra @FreddyBernal a ince… https://t.co/SgyKB2X2Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ur responsibilities to the land and its people don't end the moment u go South of any artificial borders. From Nort… https://t.co/hnYlBueO1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sommbeer_john @RJellyman @zappafaye @bodyfit67 @lhtetrick @cellmavin @bullpenbabe @Zippy_TMS @PadresGeekster… https://t.co/8jfWR0to4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNoahRing It’s called the scales of justice and it’s pretty simple really.  You break the law...you pay the cons… https://t.co/Fml7S6laLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson If i did that to the judge in a case of 1/2lb of pot.  Where would I be tomorrow?  He knows and so d… https://t.co/bXBceXWvk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy’s cooking or pizza? Love this time together. #anthonys s.axani #sas @ Anthony's Coal Fired Pizza https://t.co/hP375OrTMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got stood up on Valentine’s Day.   It was by the person I was suppose to interview for a story but STILL HURTS💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP Ooh...can we list the racist people who should be taken off GOP committees?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well...I was hoping that St. Louis would be closed today due to the weather, but it is not! All I wanted to do is s… https://t.co/6PvKraPzn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d I do t understand why the news media did not pick up on that statement THE DAY HE SAID IT! It is so dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can wet just make @BoRhapMovie the best picture of the night? #prettyplease #lovethismovie #AcademyAwards #Oscars #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everything hurt more on a Monday? I mean physically....  My hubs petedin206 turned 40 yesterday. We had a… https://t.co/M2bDZwCoAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JULEZ_91 @elonmusk @i_shtpst @MKBHD Would love to attend! But if it’s referral based invites, I doubt we’ll be invited. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we are so exceptional could we not find the best way to provide HC to all of citizens @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi But you are OK with babies being ripped from their mother's womb's as they can feel pain as their sp… https://t.co/8EuiZ2EMVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are contradicting narratives here from the Clinton camp: 1) Bernie didn’t do enough to support/campaign for h… https://t.co/VPmDMg6LCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PAHumanServices Pittsburgh corruption has made us suicidal. A true life story happening today in Pittsburgh, Penns… https://t.co/qbJWgbvERR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that we're going to build these cities, now that the world is urbanizing means that unless you have a 0 em… https://t.co/GrU9HNhu7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ari has no bread. Ari is Ari because of Herbo! He made that girl. Y’all tighten up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatGirlDixie @realDonaldTrump You wrote that filth on your page?  Ms Ignoramous I would go with being a bot if I… https://t.co/d6TUGN9Wl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KHouston4Mayor Thank you “CHIP” the BayBridge Chicken for caring about the children! 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatly looking forward to the private kick-off event next month and for being amongst the first wave of viewers an… https://t.co/QwOzy6s1gN]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOORAY! It's about time! #IndictKushner #IndictIndividual1  #IndictIndividual1Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROOF! FB is shadowbanning me! https://t.co/3aLLhbn8yS via @YouTube David Harris]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see my sister lead an entire school and community to spread kindness and inclusion by creating #TheBigGame was s… https://t.co/YRrzw9Qyto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barry_abides makes fun of me (lovingly) for turning into a pumpkin at 10PM. But I can still can close down a bar i… https://t.co/SyspY2g9Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸SUBMIT, SUBMERGE, SURRENDER🇺🇸 Scripture even says that the LORD is OUR ROCK.  This ROCK is coming with HIS judgme… https://t.co/t9yDF3AKza]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday I. AM. https://t.co/kXD0XIwfok @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/DvPuAWW2rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gl3nnji @G2esports @R6esports @G2Pengu @G2Kantoraketti @G2_Fabian @G2joonaszki @G2Goga Believe 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rut ruh....no longer in love or needing to regroup after Cohen testimony?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel as if my school administrators dislike me. All because of judgement and I am a way better person than that. If only they knew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that’s first class Staff Development service! Snacks brought to your seat during today’s staff meeting.  Thanks… https://t.co/s3uL9nSqNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Took Two Months and Nearly a Million Dollars to Save an Unvaccinated 6-Year-Old From Tetanus https://t.co/c8CJ0B3cmm via @gizmodo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 8:1-3 KJV When he was come down from the mountain, great multitudes followed him. [2] And, behold, there c...https://t.co/9OwOKVKFOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump @SenateFloor @WhiteHouse @HouseGOP @HouseFloor is it too much to ask that Republicans come ou… https://t.co/nLKpyragpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really gotten icier in the last 45 minutes. Glaze on vehicles, patches of ice forming in lots, side streets messy.… https://t.co/Dw4BtHpWBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans on this committee are being ridiculous about all of this but I REALLY don’t trust Michael Cohen. Not bu… https://t.co/JHWWO3kGvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with my girl tonight ❤ @ Hard Rock Rocksino Northfield Park https://t.co/GzUnK5X9D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unreported hate crimes, not hoaxes, are the real cause for concern - Southern Poverty Law Center https://t.co/hjbrJghHQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met Stevie Wonder at a fancy tea shop I used to work at in West Hollywood.  I played him my demo and he gave me a… https://t.co/tr38SgITDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled #OliviaColman won. Loved her work for years. She's just such a genuine and delightful actress. Hoping… https://t.co/7eXkaGmC8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally @paulvillanueva_ when we go out and I’m driving ... hint hint]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear swim meet people: DONT GET MAD AT ME FOR WHAT MY ATHLETIC DIRECTOR SAYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) Freddie was in a long-term relationship with Jim Hutton when he died. Yes he had relationships with women, but h… https://t.co/4bdhY7AqFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzzfeed quiz: Shop for a Korean skincare routine and we’ll tell you who your KPop boyfriend is. Me: This is it. My ideal quiz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesley7001 And it all happened like back to back like fever one day then the next day sore throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyman_brian @MGMAdvertiser This is some very fine journalism. Raw and honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying Sorry by a teenage girl with Aspergers LaughingWithAspergers 2 Teens. Aspergers. Awesome. https://t.co/w5nu3eaRAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2006_tiburon @emiliailq @fierecillla_ @ciralarcon @adeladessire @mircoferri @luisfcocabezas @Haterinna @ifornez… https://t.co/CEc2eny0OB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a Twitter ruling, please.  Is this appropriate to wear today?  I ask because it wasn’t a home game, so no do… https://t.co/jgQpDFk0Ux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResisterNo1 @AquaZizi @kylegriffin1 @MalcolmNance I find it ridiculous that people are speculating about the Conwa… https://t.co/7Zi2zosOlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop focusing on what you don’t have and start enjoying the things you do. —@joshua_becker https://t.co/9O1rTGCFlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theAmyMCR #TakeAPill4That #SpreadPositivity 🤩#Avoid #News #ReadComicBooks ❤️👍🏼👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up! These are the funds working to fund #femalefounders. Thanks @shellyporges for the work you do at… https://t.co/fN1JycXuIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump It would had even been in a uniform instead he gets a two week down time and he cou… https://t.co/TvSOzHznXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrscraindrop @apsitjen @beckyg314 Had a lot of fun sharing with you all this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday I’m doing 15 minutes at taocomedystudio I might just rant about how happy #Jussie must be since Findi… https://t.co/ezjA7CDdCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t even gone into work yet and I’m already excited to go home and take a hot shower 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in Connecticut, get on the damn train and come sip some Ice Cold Bev.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are cutting the grass on campus today and I’m preparing to die because I didn’t take extra allergy medicine 🤦🏻‍♀️🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[How long do baby showers last? Also, why no mimosas. I am slowly dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. What does your monthly income look like? Do you have any dependents? 2. It sounds like you might be eligible for… https://t.co/DoIUFFnuS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laur_carr I JUST RTED THIS WE ARE COSMICALLY LINKED https://t.co/Q6sDxqsIRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never leaving this place in my mind. #shishi #beach #oceanlife #pacificnorthwest #pacific #ocean #coast #coastal… https://t.co/8z7AGW80h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What moves you?? 🕯 This is my most favorite piece of #art + when i saw Psyche + Cupid firsthand i died + went to he… https://t.co/ANtBn501q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vegasseven Gorman has looked good in every game I have seen — they have their moments like every other team but wi… https://t.co/bVg9Mrxdf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHH!!  The Knights Of The Round Table!!!!!   YEAH! I didn't  expect THAT and it made me laugh! Are you a Holy Grail… https://t.co/B4OwKFpps2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t think I’ve ever enjoyed a book about creativity so much. Super inspiring, motivating and witty. Thank you for… https://t.co/igiemmiTcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 a success at my alma mater @KentState with the @dustyarmadillo 🙌🏻💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! I’ve been feeling very judged by them all morning long during my liveshots...as they hover above me 🤣… https://t.co/7FcH3nkWu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaineD27 @JesseKunzweiler @ajhoefling @Bunt23 @TyHoefling @BrockMoser1 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shavondasumter My daughter @bridgetanzano is in the audience! @GWtweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edcampOSjr @AimsCenter @IdeaPaint @Wipebook @Spotify Classroom Goals 😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no one better to dance for and serenade at the top of your lungs than a dog. No one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cowboy fans are losing their mind Rn seeing that Jason witten is coming out retirement]]></document></documents></author>