<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@farheezy11 @xCarlosMZ @BenStinar @TheTraeYoung Bruh 🤦🏽‍♂️ only thing trae got on luka is passing. Luka better in e… https://t.co/cjx632bXMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Old man, anyone that believes in your words doesn’t know how to read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @RaylinAnnx @MsLezleyZen @SamanthaRone1 @HillaryScott @brianabanksxxx1 @Club_Sandy @emberreigns… https://t.co/LuC7wSp1Zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuning the first @hailunpianos Hailun #piano I helped a client purchase. Still had a #beautiful #look and#sound @ D… https://t.co/pkR3oq8vUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraK9doc Thank you. Sometimes it’s difficult to feel caught in the middle, to be patient, but I think I’m moving… https://t.co/fNKkQx0Mdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationalLeagueH @Wentland828 @natemar3i0n If I show up 10 times in your news feed it's because you're following a… https://t.co/IPT9ssuoII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmeudy @Zak_Bagans @AaronGoodwin Our favorite show by far!!! We made a trip to the Old City Jail in Charleston bec… https://t.co/jddXOTD8NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacolbyCriswell Fabulous campus, fun college town in the Triangle, and an awesome educational opportunity. Have a great visit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DON’T FORGET ABOUT THE BITTER COLD TOO! 🥶🥶🥶  How many chocolate ice cream toppings do you think this ultra cold Mar… https://t.co/l4G9Uiz2zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s getting stronger every week!  #Repost @verayatsula with repostsaveapp   · · ·   Omg you never know when a ran… https://t.co/6EMYbeRsQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has some right wing dork made an Alito: Battle Angel image yet or will they and dear god what if I'm birthing it ou… https://t.co/JyzWFgOvO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful @jordangaylor_ should brighten up you evening. @kennywebster @westcottlighting @_fujilove_… https://t.co/zTd7v2f1qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChooseTotalNews @JackPosobiec No his own words will be enough. As with all the sum that has been fired from fox it… https://t.co/eH65V2Jjq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Client meeting South County Edition... #TheRhodeLawyer https://t.co/vVJd7Arfnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone ever had pet toad?? I wanna vet one but i need some info first]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining the D-I SQs are Firelands' Payton Burgdorf in D-II, and Lutheran West's Parker Watson, EC's Steven Ferguson… https://t.co/tfH4nLuxBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DacascosFan @txs75 He still right. His avi has literally nothing to do with anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yasarshah_SP @iramshabbirr @NareshUttamSP @amitabhk87 @MediaCellSP @PanditSingh7 मेरे प्रिय मंत्री जी ! यह आपकी जा… https://t.co/G3Zsp70Kg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I had over 280 characters to tell you why I voted for @kerenswan in the #ShortyAwards. They are so amazing and… https://t.co/AcN1hd1EOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is socialism? https://t.co/VRFek6Bt7E via @msnbc #Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents… https://t.co/apSIhrsotw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gnarley ice storm on I-66 today!   • • • #icestorm #i66 #commute #weather #extremeweather #standingrockfarm… https://t.co/3XlIfeBbUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as no hands touch me we good. #southernu_rys19 #fisk_rys19 #Tuskegee_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni @senatemajldr @RandPaul @realDonaldTrump it is disgusting that Trump and “We the people” don’t have Republica… https://t.co/zVM9WTCUC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Always Sunny In Feltonville in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/SVizRzSTUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My aunty now shout after my little cousin cause he watching the fish he just got 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 “ The fish don’t want you to watch them”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped watching years ago. No longer about true athletes. So many great athletes don't have the money for training… https://t.co/pDGgTRNMrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Good lord. One tweet? What are they so scared of? Debate? I was respectful. Talk about snowflakes.… https://t.co/7TaAW4ToL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Hurricanes squad is fun to watch.  Best we’ve seen since 2009!  #TakeWarning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DezMASTERKILLER Dany is a total 50-50 guess. Her Targaryen blood is too strong. I don’t think the writers will kil… https://t.co/fMyuxxpAvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valenti89277620 @wdunlap @Doc_0 They also are disproportionately in the majority and therefore enjoy safety in num… https://t.co/SwCpKzHVuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jah blessings and guidance this week mi Twitta ppl dem! Yow, we haffi dweet so mek we just guh hard and done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tio is telling me to celebrate, even tho I gotta wrk early tomorrow! Fuck it lmao https://t.co/PgJQlJHLjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Mike ever auction off appearances or dinners with himself? If so, I'm maxing out a credit card! #Wasu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soflofins_ Ay ay I'm drippin again, the way that I drip this shit should be a sin https://t.co/dCgL9BAh2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[They told me there wasn’t enough room for a swing-set. Huh?   Who’s laughing now!? https://t.co/3szAM5BkO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queen050780 @easttexasdem @sianoresist @JoeBiden *recant and repudiate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popped this after an 8 mile walk. Clean taste, dry, light. - Drinking a Citra Solo IPA by Lead Dog Brewing @ Three… https://t.co/K9xR7KQMOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched People Places Things on Netflix and absolutely recommend it. @AJemaineClement is phenomenal as always]]></document><document><![CDATA[HINT is a great resource for differential TF footprinting in ATAC-Seq data!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachPeteAyer @iaabo44 Well earned (despite a rowdy father in the crowd). Congratulations‼️Best of luck with the playoffs🌈⚡️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALT_uscis @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids Nothing wrong with always changing for the better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatsbyjs @johnpolacek @jxnblk @4lpine I don't know the exact stack, but https://t.co/aWPFI3hRpz is also a Gatsby app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curryja @ret_ward I think "alarmist" is a much more appropriate term than "denier" in the climate change debate. I… https://t.co/lOVzLE3UZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @AlecBaldwin @nbcsnl Still crazy after all these year.  Take your meds, Alec!]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL | (2) Virginia clinches their 4th regular season championship under Tony Bennett with a 73-68 win over Louisv… https://t.co/S433ohXzkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day: March 2’ 2012 Tornado Came Though, Eastern-Kentucky.  @JenCarfagno @SpencerWeather @amandabarren… https://t.co/tBFrENbof5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want my children to have all the things I couldn't afford. Then I want to move in with them.” ~Phyllis Diller]]></document><document><![CDATA[The neoconservative view on foreign policy today is sticking your head in a hornet nest and, when you ask to remove… https://t.co/uVGGYOGQi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slaxz Quiero que sepas que siempre te quise a pesar de que eres magallanera y madridista nunk kmbies nos vemos en la otra vida]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @HEB in Cleburne, TX https://t.co/aVJ1LzBZe0 https://t.co/UqUXDmuj1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda like it. Very Briney, nice dry finish. - Drinking an Aw Shucks by @PonoBrewing at @belmontstation  — https://t.co/LUAEGR3anV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So jealous of the weather from four years ago. We won't be seeing anything remotely that warm anytime soon! Maybe i… https://t.co/KnCpTfSyPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy stupid love day to all my twitter bitches. y'all the real mvps  forever yours, lamashtu xoxoxox https://t.co/6fvtPlxex2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dansblog1 @bungarsargon You most certainly know you could be purposely wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA20272639837 @ThePatriot006 @KamalaHarris @AOC The Democrats are the Party Of Racist, Resists, Obstruct, and Di… https://t.co/MEFuYnZ0UX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well looks like I double booked the kids and I this afternoon.  Birthday party straight into a #DaddyDaughter schoo… https://t.co/ilJz38svKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2beckysKMBZ Nickelodeon is planning a Spongebob spinoff.  #CelebrityRocket]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Blashill should be extended why? #LGRW #FIREHOLLAND #FIREBLASHILL #COMEHOMESTEVIE #LoseForHughes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have deets on @MichaelCohen212 book deal! It's actually @HillaryClinton who got the deal, since ahe told us all o… https://t.co/vZtkfPjJs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenThayer1 @KP24 @LeopardCreekCC Well we can at least agree on that. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeytonRoyceWWE 🤣🙌🏻 You’re the best @PeytonRoyceWWE https://t.co/h5q2SnSxVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Krejci's late goal helps Bruins extend points streak to 19 https://t.co/Azf6GzS5DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hotboymonn2xx Y’all Niggs know how I roll I got the first night it drop]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say dump his ass.    Kaley Cuoco's Husband Ruins Sexy Photo by Saying They Look Like Siblings: 'Moment Over' https://t.co/SDa7wtYLqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BewareOfMe13 @caruss18 @IslesTerritory @NYIslander27 And how do you explain trotz saying he needs to get better th… https://t.co/vx7ldMJvdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at University Club of Portland in Portland, OR https://t.co/wBwMFOCE7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A movie is a movie. Theatrical runs are only a criteria because Hollywood made that rule. I’d allow any movie, but… https://t.co/RkRWlzEWo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[El jueves previo al abordar un autobús, un guardia de seguridad pidió mi boleto e identificación (en las credencial… https://t.co/zE8sYPfnGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrankyNickles Same to you. From me and Sigfried. https://t.co/KniaQp6z2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of democrats in Congress are frauds. Take A O C. Ass Of Congress she want to destroy our country. We won’t le… https://t.co/mhgbDagsI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand we have an issue with homeless people in this city. There is a difference between those who stand on t… https://t.co/FtEB4YaSFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weinbergersa I once fashioned a soup spoon out of a used piece of tin foil and I'm both proud and ashamed to admit it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been waiting on this since it leaked on YouTube 2 months ago 🙏🏼  https://t.co/gyK96vAAYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erik_G_T @ehnprodigy @sdprevo33 @jareddiamond Keuchel in Petco would be a huge difference than pitching in that li… https://t.co/nGiVtxWrkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to Vegas and my buddy @MarkHokeShow introduced me to @PeppermillVegas on North end of the Strip. Waitress s… https://t.co/l9pUkwEoHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColanNielsen @JoyanneHawkins @DarrenShaw_ Lol you beat me to it!👊🏻 https://t.co/BtZAvGfhGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spanish artists put way more effort into performances than any rapper does🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyCameron @MizunoGolfNA  Cant wait for golf to begin here in Wisconsin so at least i have a reason to drink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globovision #DIAV #VDAY 🇻🇪⭐️🇻🇪  Lo que está por ocurrir; lo que certeramente está por ocurrirle al régimen narco d… https://t.co/phYcU94qjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Bradley Cooper would ask me if I was happy in this modern world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to complete the #MuellerInvestigation Join me in defending our democracy #ProtectTheInvestigation https://t.co/QSJeYWriCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia Thanks for the laughs tonight on the #followtheleadertour Shit was hilarious. Another sold out crowd 💰⛟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock @lucfrenette @gutekunstlaw @PatrickDoyle_35 @Peter_Grinspoon @arandamdphd @tal7291 @DanLairdMD… https://t.co/1LLcxmlBpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Friday, Tyler Mabry announced his transfer to Maryland. He’s the fourth player to do so since Mike Locksley took… https://t.co/rBnBuQ3h0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bed at 12:06am.....Boxing at 8:15. Going to be a rough morning https://t.co/FoTJkx4Wph]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t rock with ANYTHING voice controlled. You gotta fuck wit the lights haha turning off all the lights in… https://t.co/iVAgpOh5Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had their time and chance w me now they don’t we be to leave .. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moderatelylong That’s what I mean like that sounds terrible 😂 if I had someone to room with I would do it maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flirtyflipper I’d get angry at you for tweeting this if it wasn’t true! Lol! 😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The PastryArchy Pecan Pie by @DuClawBrewing at @duclawthemills — https://t.co/AnW8eHNy8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregorydmurray @marchmadness @PackMensBball It’s all good. There are no new ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDever At @SEBTS we read Nine Marks of a Healthy Church in the required Supervised Field Ministry course, and W… https://t.co/j4te7OQ2jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews 1) This is not what I was looking for But, Do you honestly think this was a surprise to anyone pushing… https://t.co/sLkUReN9s8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I’ll probably go somewhere in June too like why the hell not I have 180 hours of vacation time just sitting not… https://t.co/uqkCMixgEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngieNOLA @JelleK11 @TheLoveBel0w @rcbregman @TuckerCarlson Doubly obnoxious is that you bring up Hillary Clinton,… https://t.co/GvjsMVAyQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @Gorjess9119 for being the best girlfriend and making me a lunch during busy season. https://t.co/TE92LQI8NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[you could the finest mf I’ve ever met, if you carry yourself like a hoe...i’ll never take you serious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiponRedHawks @riponcollege @RCCoachLauren @MWCSports Congrats to @RCCoachLauren &amp; the whole squad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen She works for Putin.  Spying on trump until trump started working for Putin. She's still watching him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling the @TMobile  love! @MoOniica_14 @sarapalaciosdm https://t.co/HlejuYv9Zc]]></document></documents></author>