<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[unless it’s Hershey’s Cookies N’ Cream, whoever likes white chocolate is a serial killer]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, who out there is discussing this request? @MedNetOne and @MichiganDOs are ready to submit an opinion. Are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bobinette et Mémère Bouchard immortalisées au #Musée de la civilisation #mcqorg https://t.co/jMQESHnlwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that basket stands? Why wouldn’t it stand? Off well-before the buzzer. #pcbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just learned all about how to properly light a cigar. That seems like too much work 😂 things I learn at work 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber you have got to figure a better way @LAX ! A 22 minute wait is ridiculous #taxicab faster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yysxr @connorhannigan4 Pretty sure that’s the exact same one that’s in our hallway 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man is teaching me everything my maternal grandma has tried to teach me since I was a child]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJohnsonPGA @WGCMexico Glad you’re playing so well.  Wondering if you remember me?Good luck in final round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC keep up the good work. It was an attempt to bring down our president and we all know it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single year, I forget that Ash Wednesday is a thing and I spend several minutes of my morning being all "shou… https://t.co/trlQmtX3Z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvinp4001 @mviser @anete_newt Not even going to try...just my opinion. Race is obviously an issue, I just think… https://t.co/GimZSc21ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping #ThankYou to all… https://t.co/T7BZVtOJCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Saturday @ Courtyard by Marriott Atlanta Decatur Downtown/Emory https://t.co/bOiySs58E0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My interview on 'Anne Frank' In Hollywood Re-imagined Using #Hispanic Actors https://t.co/GNPV9fxf29… https://t.co/fKYyZSdfzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[WEED I HELP YOU TODAY? 🤫            I got edible arrangement deals too  1 cupcake 1 brownie 3🌲for 40 2 cupcakes 2 b… https://t.co/vO9gDwoTt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the Joint Bond Review Committee meeting this morning. Lawmakers are set to decide whether to approve the new… https://t.co/rlINMez9so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckyysara @CW_Arrow Way to go!! What a great accomplishment, congrats!💘🎯👓 https://t.co/GDRlK8A9go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft rules because through them I’ve ridden in a Tesla 3 times!!! https://t.co/hZ7l4S7yFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because people be saying am a hater Then shit....  am a do ME💖💖💖  🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺🌺 So nicely I say this "Don't… https://t.co/IJOeVlNkvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The title for this weeks brilliant idiots is “why you always Lyon” https://t.co/cLj1XR8P44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samboa @RedState I’m not afraid for me. I won’t be here when America fails. My grandchildren will be. Probably you… https://t.co/Xdx5yXHKq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ORUBaseball @antmartinez13 Been watching you when I can. Do your best and let God do the rest. He is faithful. 👍🏻🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crankymomofsix This dog does a better job than my BF. https://t.co/drWjAdh5bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndianaDunesNPS Visited this gorgeous place many times when we lived in Chicago. Very happy to hear this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMGynecology @serdarbulun @NorthwesternMed Too bad it's too late for many many women!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laker477 @ElkeHansen7 @barb71 @OldSmokeEater @TeriHentschel @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong @FMedic921… https://t.co/XU8SINhWTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers going out to Luke’s family and children way to young to have left!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madjforevs Relationships? ako din mag work muna siguro tayo! Pero tigilan mona yan! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know how tired I am??? I just used the flashlight on my phone to look for my phone. ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇵🇰 Can anyone provide feedback on this? Extremely Urgent, needs to be implemented! Zoos are LAWLESS #Pakistan, keep… https://t.co/5wzFUFtMYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s never gonna change he’s childish someone needs to put him in his place already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharleyHoke @DallasHarrelson it’s never been a joke, it’s only been my biggest “ongoing” insecurity i’ve had my whole]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kwfr2019  Inspirational Morning!  #itdoesntgetanybetter @ New Orleans Ernest N. Morial Convention Center https://t.co/Ji2bRW98iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you aquinas for turning my commute from 20 minutes to an hour and 20 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Older black men like young black men that they see who work hard or do they job correctly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if Kelpiens feel naked without their Ganglia. #StarTrekDiscovery #StarTrek https://t.co/0fyoT5x1e5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What? Guns &amp; beer drive thru? What about crack? They don’t sell that? #HolyShit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s technically Valentine’s Day, so if you need me ... I’ll be busy listening to Jagged Edge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect eyebrow finishing products. #makeup #stylish #fashionable #fashionblogger #cosmetics #looks #lookgreat #abh… https://t.co/J0XSna1SYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was rushing to pick up my phone I had the funniest thing to say on here oh my god it was so funny I can’t remember]]></document><document><![CDATA[District Semi-Final Boys Basketball: Nick Leibacher 3 ties it.   Timeout South Central.  49-49.  :11.1 to go.  South Central ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Goldberg Tax Services Satellite Office https://t.co/MwYTakc4x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt @KurtSchlichter @Radioblogger Kurt was GREAT!! We enjoyed him all week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey I know I wasn’t there for like your whole life, BUT I’m here now!” Lol k bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@quintewest 'goes pink,' raising about $10,000 for womens' #CancerResearch✨💖  Last night's #PinkIntheRink speaker,… https://t.co/Vh4CVM33dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Rudd walked out on stage and @MegIsATurtle said “It’s Mike Crap-Bag” 😂 #Oscars #Friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[1992 Leaf Ken Griffey Jr  $0.45  (Please check my pinned tweet for sale &amp; shipping details. Thank you!) https://t.co/30AIPadXD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMMnow Out now! @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has always been one of my favorite views #garnernc #northcarolina #farmlife #nofilter @ Garner, North Carolina https://t.co/7hgJJLpoJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍰 A wonderful Sunday afternoon with the lovely isabellaaa7 at the northbrowardlinks Red Dress Soiree in benefit of… https://t.co/RafwjChau0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemesSpaghetti1 @TweetOfSpirit_ https://t.co/3tFbaHN26x A Madea Halloween by Tyler Perry always is right. 🌟 #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did lil bow wow not win an academy award for his performance in Like Mike.  #calvincambridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justsumgirlhere tru i wanna know how to tell them they need a different undertone too 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jo642 @CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo Agreed, and we literally can’t bc it’s just one long stream of consciousness abo… https://t.co/zf7edkaPiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I just think about the time Alec Baldwin ate at Selva and it was the one night all week that I didn’t wor… https://t.co/j6fNSvzFsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgibby55 @tweettruth2me @ilenej @ktwinch @charliekirk11 Nope, you’re the uninformed idiot who can’t tell the diffe… https://t.co/25PXsl707O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low key plot twist, if you seen my tweet about hating on the person who stole my earphones at the gym, turns out my… https://t.co/pk5CDSfPb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzDyvon @yeshua_porvida @CockDestroyerz I just put what the Lord tells me if you can't take it it's not my fault]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this today, "when you realize how much you're worth you'll stop giving people discounts." 👏🏼 #preach !! #healthyboundaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer The majority of Americans voted for someone other than you! You might have forgot so just a reminder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vancouver44444 @minotauresse @GerdasEquineRes Yet the turtle would need 60 years of future care depending on age!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikesaa309 @srslymgc_ @WestJaden24 he's being paid for his press and television appearances, he's also pushing for… https://t.co/2oRczlKPuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the good vibrations! I know I sound like a broken record but I get as much and more than I am able to give when… https://t.co/wWobHKWHh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days you just have to show up when you’d rather bow out. Poor Friday night decisions are best used as reminder… https://t.co/xjyd2NiDLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t I drink half a bottle of water without having to use the restroom every 10 seconds..]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only been a month and half but I’m loving the small changes https://t.co/FmGxcrf1Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreshSpellbound @debbiegibbshalm When Obama drank Flint water the white man side of him came through Power and Money first WeThePpl 2nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day to all those who identify! #BalanceforBetter every day not just today. #IWD2019 https://t.co/aF9yibXXkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[having a car &amp; license has giving me soo much more freedom, i love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMurphyLaw Because they’re proponents of the #socialist movement. #ERA is not on the agenda of the social #democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new @Glen_Hansard song has me feeling things I didn't know I could feel in my cubicle. #FoolsGame #ThisWildWilling]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMO... Grassroots efforts from within almost always have more success than outsiders coming in with a “one size fit… https://t.co/cPCkOEjAWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vindicationn @imagine_enigami @CrabRangucci @terrycrews https://t.co/cQr9FIvPZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t even tell myself shit too real to be true anymore. i know i deserve it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Online Business Greeting Cards From Four Sisters Printing  Visit at https://t.co/NhO3To1jZI… https://t.co/tXjEX8TEJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @VictoriaD6363 @SUPERGOCHOo @malekalby @marinavibu609g @PatGrant7777 @AAvallones @EliLeonarda… https://t.co/9UTSTzE5OE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wondering... What is the best book to prep for the GRE? I plan to take it in the fall but might as well start studying now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me about it, Audrey... #Dreamboat #MySpecialAgent #AgentCooper #youareperfect #TwinPeaks @Kyle_MacLachlan… https://t.co/cJpJBsobc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am goddamn stoked that we declared this a “Vanishing Point”-watching weekend #vanishingpoint #kowalski https://t.co/qDV6JmO8e6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjanikis @lindacoolbaugh @wakelet You’ve been sleeping 😴 on the good stuff. #StayWoke In the meantime, we got your back! ✊🏽#NewselaChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Kali and @KStateWBB for letting me tell this story. Her journey may have been difficult, but by embrac… https://t.co/JX6B5LivHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJacieMaslyk @ECET2NextGen @SFecich Seriously cracking up that I am looking out one side of those very large glas… https://t.co/54rzwtU9pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey now!  I think I broke the @nytopinion.  The piece on 'Dark Star' is still at #3 after two days.   My editor sai… https://t.co/CiaYYN2anD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texasmario221 Im just trying to make everyone realize and know the truth about her]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found this awesome giveaway check it out here! https://t.co/jEzHkzRCGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao this guy decided to honk at me and tell me to go fuck myself for coming to a complete stop at STOP SIGN!!! I d… https://t.co/83LC4UzApX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! Can this BE any worse??? I’m still reeling from yesterday and the horrible stance taken by the MORON IN CHIEF… https://t.co/XBfgNnaFRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@szaafran maybe you can talk some sense to the White House about this opioid regulation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Who cares what this moronic excuse for a human being thinks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I hope that all the rich Hollywood entitled and all the over paid athletes do realize the line between democrat… https://t.co/LOWXOgU3gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[you guys i met a freemason are they still like a secretive cult should i get some intel or what]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tend to think those poll numbers have more to do with landlines than anything else. #MorningJoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[supporting each other since day 1 💯💙 @boncheech https://t.co/gRYanPE5L9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOSullivan36 @StraightTalkI @BernieSanders @HillaryClinton @DNC That was polite.! i like reading… https://t.co/fbEaojIOb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveBling6 @tammiesawakenow @Josiegirlz5 @Magz_62 @heidi_weigand @1wTheForce_FIWM @bkerb953 @Donald06106186 @930VM… https://t.co/5sE9xauqYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We look forward to meeting with all of our intern candidates!  Keep those applications rolling in—we can’t wait to… https://t.co/GKK3xRI0hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHS_Debate @RoseCoyne_ @realTylerUnrath Yay!! So proud! Congratulations!! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop telling people to come to section 109 https://t.co/pu5JKh1gPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whole thing is impressive but she threw and caught it 3 times with her fucking neck.... skip to 1:00]]></document></documents></author>