<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@john_fostrr Where is it and what makes it better than Community BBQ In Decatur?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to take old headphones when they broke, but still worked, and build little Lego speakers for my GI Joes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day in Shangri-la!! @ Marc Roseman, Coldwell Banker Bain https://t.co/HNW1B5GJcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKalenAllen Yuck! Though I remember eating raw hamburger as a kid, but just a tad, not a slider! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has been happening forever and will continue to happen cuz females be different]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomMinske @DynastySnarker @DFF_Dynasty Oh yeah, and mainly because it fills the empty void of the offseason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bama_katie It might’ve been me. I put on a hoodie earlier and took it off right before Bierman ended the top of the inning. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[A difficult thing about being my friend is that if your feelings contradict fact, I don’t care about your feelings. Truth trumps all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTurnerPTF That’s interesting because in Q3 2018 we imported 10.3 million barrels per day. Granted, we export… https://t.co/mTwCpEnuZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARYCECY32 Sabes que si, yo ensayando mis canciones y el se arrulla jajaja gracias!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetiredGoodBoy @IamBellaKush I’m happy but I still want him to start scoring more goals. Start contending for the… https://t.co/NO59MjmXRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also just two drives into the game and you can really see what @The_Coach_A means in his article by “positionless d… https://t.co/eURIVREu7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Tick tick, Individual 1. It’s my pleasure to support this Pledge To Impeach Donald Trump.”  Thank you… https://t.co/wY9e6cJPl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristysf Perfect! If you teach them common sense and world history as it happened they'll be far better for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for @RandyLambertMC . Last year coaching at Maryville College after 39 years. After a 1-4 start this year… https://t.co/K1GGEPPHqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was truly an honour and pleasure to meet the 📚 author, journalist Waubgeshig Rice @Waub today thanks to @IAESC1… https://t.co/DYXw8kHbJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone at work is really trynna convince me that the NBA is rigged cause there’s a magnet in the rim and the ball… https://t.co/E70ZGPywku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like hearing with your ears for the first time what you’ve been hearing in your mind. Demoing a song for me… https://t.co/XqDWkzzUYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Likely nothing will happen - but let’s hope she does get a good dose of pushback. One can jope for a ‘reality check… https://t.co/7pnLFu47NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the lack of scoring depth Rayados have, they need to drop the cash to buy him in the summer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganlesniewski I’m tryna take you out to get that Wendy”s 4 for 4 tommorow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonislawskiM @NatashaFatah I guess Katie Telford for now. Curious who the new principal secretary will be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dolphins fans 2019: Kyler is too small Dolphins fans 2020: tua is left handed]]></document><document><![CDATA[50-50. Avery/Mitchell heading to overtime in playoffs round 2. @acthshuddle @averyhighschool @PolkSports… https://t.co/PWxgMnDMxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sandler seems he’s probably tougher than he looks, but he *did get his ass kicked by Bob Barker...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this works.  I have been to sites that made it difficult to page back &amp; had to close the tab. https://t.co/RYsEWf2fQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 21 - Week's Top Stories:    Where Does the Road To WrestleMania Lead After Houston?;     Breaking… https://t.co/QXud0ED86l]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is disproportionately bent on reaching the lost. As the church, we should be too! ~ Pastor amandahodgesx… https://t.co/454k1QOgyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I felt like I was back In MKE found some fun bars like at home and a pizza place just like Ian’s pizza. But… https://t.co/bJcqT8k6yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell of a nice day to be out. #allwaysridingneverhiding #81 #81support #81supporter #81supportcrew… https://t.co/bTFxnx8qzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't GOUT known as the Disease of the Kings? Well 4 years in prison for Manafort should cure him, no steak, lobste… https://t.co/iEyW8qPl4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Oh, is this a game where you say just about anything, and then call it socialism? I want to play!  Gun… https://t.co/p47UDWCzhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTFOz Agree to disagree. Sincerely, "The Giants win the pennant!  The Giants win the pennant!!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Believed the Lie, It is not the Liar’s Fault  https://t.co/74A9nZvRC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlmomrn @TLeeLaxDad @PeasandCarrots3 @beersolo @itsallinwdw @CoolBlueStrat @Grumpy6767 @evanmethuen @Alabama863 Gr… https://t.co/ny4Xdbto5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @TomPerez You’re in for another surprise! Wait till you see the circus on the left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sergioulloa1 @patricioalv @jg_valdes Eso pasará en Chile con tanto apitutado pero afuera y en Princeton las cosas… https://t.co/1bvTtamOMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve finally ranked everything I ate and drank at the DCA Food and Wine Festival, which is the coolest Disney ev… https://t.co/e3vn6DyesF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of President Trump’s national emergency declaration, VP Pence says he’s thankful for support from Senator… https://t.co/LBtEN6leWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped my wife today by cooking all the pancakes for her class for Valentine’s breakfast. Polite young man named Jo… https://t.co/aMRPFbMdZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockey_ohio @SIHSPREPHOCKEY C’mon. Give high school sports a shot in the arm and let the boys play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paacreek @HeyAwstin @Zacuum @Vipey_ Awww thanks Paacreek! https://t.co/SoPHZqw2tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTLSaiyan 1. Zelda BotW 2. Super Mario Odyssey  3. Super Smash Bros. Ultimate   Favorite moments have to be seeing… https://t.co/15mYEsYLTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roastchili @FilmCritHULK @CinamonPancakes I was simply asking how we can be sure what the filmmakers intentions we… https://t.co/eafjBevpT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3 amigos out for a ride on a nice day in the winter. red_dodge_shaker  707_fjs  👍👍🍀🍀💚💚🔥🔥 °°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°°… https://t.co/GaG6eKSH8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cant live by the rules of the country you want to move to stay out]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Middleton outside of Bryce Harper’s house. https://t.co/38qr8XYkHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattbaileylns @BridgetMahalek @1000ydguy @MikeSautterOWH Ball game ‼️🤣🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Betterduck @Canes228 @naturalrights23 @HurricaneStiz @CanesEDIT Ponytail! 😂 @CutlerRidgeLAZ https://t.co/aE68uFGSbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[. Listen to the interview with Christine Lagarde on @MPRnews @NPR this morning.   Still, US women are paid only 82%… https://t.co/YzZV1t1MyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GRATITUDE! #begrateful #expression #heartfelt #emotion https://t.co/5zsL31bk26]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLACKVIPERICE, LLC - Product Information Sheet - VIP "ORIGINALS" - Official Release April 2019 @ Center Line, Michi… https://t.co/5kV4cAKyBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoHolyScripture Are you really sure that there are gradations of morality? Perhaps I am misunderstanding you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJDEMARAY @purplebuckeye @JacobNosbush @JoshMenschNFL @b_heintzz I can't see us being too bidder for Saffold... He's going to get PAID]]></document><document><![CDATA[A que hora entrarán los marines a #Venezuela ? Ya ese pueblo no aguanta más sufrimiento.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont fear u id rather fight w you .i cant win.stop it.i dont fear u id r a ther fight w u i cant win stop it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the whole team gets frost tips@astros @ABREG_1 @JSMarisnick @el_yuly10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bell_debbie @Neuro_Skeptic Wait wait a minute, so men have three items to add to their hysterical  egos. Thats been the problem all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjane87 I was a young film buff when I watched it. It scarred me, and I can’t even recall exactly why. Only that I… https://t.co/UE1ipRTIbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atticascott4ky Like in the record for real? I thought todays news couldn't get any more bizarre. 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[After not qualifying for the meet last year I am blessed to have been able to make it to the national championship… https://t.co/HkR62ujHc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLNewshound whole damn office when the Friday snack email is sent out at 4 o’clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS... the Oak- Seguin, TX.. . @Friend2theRabbi... let’s do it...   🎧 Southside Of Heaven by @RyanBingham on… https://t.co/v949vrfPSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leamosuncuento Gracias amiga. Hermoso que disfrutes con tus niños de la creación de Dios. Bendiciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥⚡️⭐️🌟💥I Present The Photo Of The Day!!!💥🌟⭐️⚡️🔥🔥 . . Photo by @mygolfinggirls . . . This right here is a mammoth c… https://t.co/mDmUyDKAEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagzillaGorilla @ac_cibock FACT CHECK:  There's over 7 billion people in the world.  When the Democrats open the b… https://t.co/wDiEWNQZRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk about a #dive #bar I dig the #sassy #pittsburgh #pennsylvania #walmart #folks @ Jacks Bar Pittsburgh https://t.co/CpHUDlivDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the support of our lead pastor @jchowardspeaks, today about 4 weeks of hard work comes to life @hohmacon.… https://t.co/5JY0rLAdzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game Day at Chozen Martial Arts Academy La Verne @ Chozen Martial Arts Academy https://t.co/Ol5AJJTQYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexaBliss_WWE @WWE @YaOnlyLivvOnce Both of you ladies are so fire 🔥 ❤️🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflections: Monday Mirror. Hope you had a great weekend and week ahead. #selfie📷 #mensfashiontrends #motoe5plus… https://t.co/boSolTGLM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VernBuchanan filed a bill to make #DaylightSavingTime permanent. #Sarasota #Florida @VisitSarasota https://t.co/loU6xCs6KW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fucking Lightroom crashed and cleared all my imported pictures/presets...everything..welp guess I get to start a… https://t.co/ZiaXIslB6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet me at the mall We could blow a bag I’m about to ball on my Ex Poppin tags 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes “There’s nothing like going to a big dark theater with people you’ve never met before and having the exper… https://t.co/Xc5UHXCnM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teleflora DO NOT ORDER FLOWERS FROM THIS COMPANY!!!  I ordered roses for Valentine’s Day and they sent a spring bo… https://t.co/dth346ImNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewzViewz @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump How AMERICA began wasn't on the news, just in school. Was fake news. Most v… https://t.co/c7Gfsl8zL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to a new survey by Edelman Intelligence, 53% of Californians are considering moving out of state due to t… https://t.co/ZeXbd7cbY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant trust someone who considers Olive Garden a good italian restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is way too complex for us to try to break it down. You won’t find meaning on a bottle of whiskey, a country so… https://t.co/5icVhYbrfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleRockBSB What in the world has this world come to. My boy josh going deep]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 I will love thee, O Lord, my strength. 2 The Lord is my rock, and my fortress, and my deliverer; my God, my stren… https://t.co/YuVOtDPaA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to use a foam roller to relieve neck, back and knee pain  https://t.co/5dsIp71VJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude! This is legendary! @clairesignshere and @Autumn30452565 are super talented! 👇🏼🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartmindy @KamalaHarris Ummm says the one with a profile picture that looks like it’s from a porno https://t.co/UbUzPgzWq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If there is no collusion, you have nothing to worry about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @AdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump Yes, open a Grand Jury and let We The People Decide for once!!  This money… https://t.co/GpHPxZZzfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMDeDominicis He’d be my first choice to replace housley if he is in fact fired]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say a sentencing of 19-24 years is excessive for Paul Manafort. .. yet y'all lock up POC for longer than that for weed .. FOH!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Korra has been driving the #Korea talks 4 the last two years. Better more  step-by-step talks than false peac… https://t.co/9EY9D3ci85]]></document><document><![CDATA[chill being jealous of people in their winning season , you don’t know what they lost in their losing season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing Toscona waterfront condos from the $215k to $260k price range 2 bed 2 bath with one car garage nestled in t… https://t.co/rjq1RSB0Os]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JIsbackintown I've become a sleep test evangelist. I have a CPAP machine and it's changed my life! And I didn't th… https://t.co/AEjbRpPfSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmartiPants83 U can take your spelling &amp; grammar test over to trumps website he needs it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@novia_online @TheSantaBot You done a latest animation of someting or other..LoL  come here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfr0716 @SykesCharlie @EWErickson Well, if tax is out there as a matter of choice, they really can’t complain too… https://t.co/wVm9VYQv9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ORlGlNALUSERNAM I can't save for shit, I have no good reason to so I just have $1.27 rn lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevClown ah. I do live in public housing - a fairly unusual case of recent, city-developed and -owned, middle inco… https://t.co/4zGU6dyhER]]></document><document><![CDATA[FWIW, I need a solid 2 hours or so of #TwitterAndTreadmill tomorrow to catch up on all your comments about yesterda… https://t.co/1DhpnV9E9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[If straight and gay black men could find a unity we'd all be so stronger]]></document></documents></author>