<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Picked up my new to me SUV!! 🚙💨 God is so funny and good 🙌🏼😆  He surprised me when I found my original Black Beauty… https://t.co/lATSHiZM8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my godddd. First someone brings into work a 10 week old baby girl, then seeing Kody with Mar tonight and then TH… https://t.co/CnCvtzviAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends in #Colorado -- you don't want to miss this screening of @KevinHinesStory "Suicide: The Ripple Effect" comi… https://t.co/qQH7CiZ2xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Really??? You who disrespected former presidents and our intelligence agencies while overseas? ❄️❄️❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faaderera @inecnigeria Yeah but I still want a better Nigeria. Home will always be home 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[so many things i wanna say to u, but above all know i miss u more than anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many used to say It’s CRAZY for girls to play football. More say it’s CRAZY for a team to win more then one state t… https://t.co/yYEsgmUIsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hangtenstories 825 A  #slight  nod  was  all  that  showed  he       knew      her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChloePolitiCat @AriMelber @5thGenCaliNativ But then how will we know if a 109 year old woman gives birth to triple… https://t.co/EDHwCbpTIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarterLHorne Carter you blew them away! God Bless  you in your awesome future !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a lot of fun doodin’ it up at @sketchpartyLA! https://t.co/H4zvs8P91O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande Thank you 😊 @Kimberl38218406  is amazing 😉 @ArianaGrande I love ❤️ you]]></document><document><![CDATA[We @GMES_Hawks have an awesome principal! Today, @jrhymes2002 stopped by the Music Room to dance and sing with kind… https://t.co/jZPGqbqiAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Summer 2019 Management Trainee Intern - https://t.co/jMChboYtpb #CampHill, PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kizomba class after practice! #Kizomba #fayettevillelatindance #hayatyogashala #dance #practice #demo #kizombalove… https://t.co/4Dt3QneI1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really about to end these neighborhood kids existence. SHUT THE FUCK UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[On May 21, I'm volunteering for democracy by joining @fairdistrictspa to talk to voters at the polls. It's a unique… https://t.co/0bLP0PhcSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 in Alabama... salon day... byeeeeeeeee brown roots!!! #makemeblonde #byyyeeeebrown #rootsgoaway… https://t.co/cq0mqp5KsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nestorfabian74 @luiscostabonino @OrsiYamandu Las caravanas huyen hacia Venezuela?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jared Leto looking very emo and very skinny in line at Poquito Más on Cahuenga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joji лайвом замечательный. Очень круто поёт и минимум плейбека, два синта и клавишник. Надеюсь, его привезут в Моск… https://t.co/WfziE5lLek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Millions know they are ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE! WE STAND WITH YOU! GOD BLESS YOU @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/siC5NSf2i0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiffany Distel started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/5jWcBpdPrQ #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbrianne_ that’s all you sis 😂😂😂 mike already know what i will and won’t do in a workout]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trysting with a footman during a costume ball? Someone’s been reading their romance novels @masterpiecepbs #VictoriaPBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusicalAbuse @realjoeyfatone @PodcastOne The second I seen him the teenager inside of me came out I instantly knew… https://t.co/D8irKgK9gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mytalkcolleen @bradleytraynor @mytalk1071 Huge thank you to you guys for introducing the term “pushing a baby out… https://t.co/JOtt74ZXSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnvalle20 Perfect tan!  What a beautiful skin color, Kathryn Bernardo everyone 💙💙😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC If you substitute “knee-jerk loyalty” for “dual loyalty,” there is absolutely no issue here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalJustin We had to have the civil rights laws passed to stop mob injustice we don’t need to bring it back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te dolerá mirar donde hubo sinceridad, porque ya en mi alma no gobiernas, lo digo yo 🎶 🎶.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker has the flu. Another coworker's husband has the flu. All of my patients have the flu. I've never felt l… https://t.co/XP16ci9RB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caleb said let’s go do a little bit of shopping and get dinner tomorrow &amp; I couldn’t be happier 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kiarah Nope but it’ll make me feel better since I can’t whoop his ass 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeManeDavis Loving every minute. Watching on the west coast always puts us behind ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This farce hearing Michael Cohen's lawyer is Hillary Clinton's lawyer and Michael admitted today that he colluded a… https://t.co/ZdgYuywxWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bambam9_9 Luckily I bought a lot of tickets, I have a feeling they’re going to be hard to come by now. I should pr… https://t.co/yQpxkNptQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creckling @CharlesPPierce That's the 64-dollar question. It's obviously not about making Anderson Cooper sound better than he already does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaftanWoman Heartbreaking! Three hilarious and talented individuals sitting on that couch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost No surprise. trump has never admitted to anything in his entire life. A regular choir boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JelasHeart @WhiteHouse He made jokes in NC after Florence after some one else’s boat wound up in another person’s… https://t.co/U0vLO3AtJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's time for everything... Great day for me https://t.co/3ggjoLHCT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe 2/ He said, “wait here,” disappeared for a minute, and returned with a bouquet of flowers. I thanked… https://t.co/SPelRN6ZWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unrooolie SUCK MAH DICK. Greatest fucking game ever as a child in arcade. Fuck the PS1 version though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A moment I’ll never forget ✨ @WTEN (📸: Chris Boehlke) https://t.co/rrU4iTnP6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss America forgot the words to the National Anthem and then Princess Aurora came on the stage to send us off...it… https://t.co/VG8zMqoXuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day to #showlove to those around you and to be #thankful. Thinking of #MarjoryStonemanDouglas and healing thr… https://t.co/cC8PiP0wmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy that it’s only 21 cars on the lead lap @DISupdates #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElettraSantana @danibacedo Brasileiro nao aprende. O MYNDO NAO TA NEM AI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @GOP MIKE you are to  F-In Stupid to ask, why would he not show his taxes? What i… https://t.co/rxgghl2KWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is gentrification right? They tore down my neighborhood Little Caesar’s and put up a Dominos]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 7:25 pm, I’m in Manhattan, and I’m wondering if it’s too early to go to sleep yet. But tonight is spring forwa… https://t.co/2xnTwB0ouI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work so fucking much that sometimes it’s irritating because I don’t even have time to see my boyfriend anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in a long term relationship and was cheated on multiple times. I have suffered trust issues. I’ve changed mys… https://t.co/eYgKeHjqAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning, storm! air heavy with rain’s perfume juncos trill, ready #haiku #dawn #birdsong #highdesert #NewMexico https://t.co/XXkCHnnxeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a year since i first saw the waitress tour, so i thought i’d share a bit why this show, especially the fi… https://t.co/TylesxyCLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineInMD @ryanjreilly I live near Mission Beach. I grew up here, but moved to L.A. when was 22. I lived there fo… https://t.co/lIM4VFu7U5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t know how good it feels to be free from the trash ass toxic men that I’ve dealt with over the last 2 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te espero hoy en Radio click , una obra de @luciarmiranda  que integra el grupo de siete del proyecto I AM MÍAMI en… https://t.co/2skhEvFodc]]></document><document><![CDATA[-Y porque te gusta que mc davo canta ella es una amenaza? -Pues 🤤🤤🤤 @mcdavoo https://t.co/3jS9eI8QM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherschwitz5 @richardmarx He was born in 1907, how many from that era do you think are still alive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning more and knowing God has my back! I can prosper through everything believing and knowing God. Never just post scriptures; live it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been listening to too much Beyoncé Instead of Trina growing up and it shows 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been drinking due to summer/4eva body in progress so one martini really knocks my socks off 🥴😬🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 @HillaryClinton @BernieSanders No! Not now! Never! Mr Sanders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vintagetextiles #antiquelace #vintagesewing #art #fiberart #femmage #collage #mixedmedia #design #patterns https://t.co/hLEwz3NS6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my future man doesn’t binge watch The Office with me then wtf is the point?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm no one's second choice 🖤 ... especially my own   #sexyisastateofmind #lifted  #plantsnotpills #pharmafree… https://t.co/UUdRFIuzMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moritherapy @nolaready @CityOfNOLA @NOLACityCouncil @nolahealthdept @NewOrleansEMS @NOPDNews @NWSNewOrleans… https://t.co/ikWIQXJddZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead This will be great. You and Melissa together is the best. Love you both.❤🍻🏍😎❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Enclave At Coral Ridge Country Club in Fort Lauderdale, FL https://t.co/4kgmsVfz98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalakala778 Finally A Star is Born is on in 20 minutes. I'm snuggled under the covers with my baby Gracie dog. A c… https://t.co/a7QrCB38gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When G.O.A.T.s pave the way in.... therealruthecarter  #Congratulations #OscarWinner #Oscars #Fashion… https://t.co/qq6uIWQNwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most boys won’t understand but ik I’m not the only girl that closes her hair in her car door\window]]></document><document><![CDATA[No joke compared to last year all I do is work work work🤦🏽‍♀️ last year I was out and about every weekend en los ba… https://t.co/mHm0djS8oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEADLINE Y’all want a black Batman one week but a light skin can’t play someone who was dark in reality 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A si es Doctor Ledezma el dictador narco terrorista genocida ladron no sale con dialogo ni con votos ya no es presi… https://t.co/8NhpCoPw78]]></document><document><![CDATA[School is cancelled for the day @ Rio Rancho, New Mexico https://t.co/g2X45tSiaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked Maya to marry me. And she said yes. So... I'm engaged. #Heartland]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Bible verse about speaking in tongues ... I never done it I always thought it was weird af lol https://t.co/AQv1Hba1RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@ManMadeMoon⁩ ⁦⁦@amandapalmer⁩ ⁦@trent_reznor⁩ ⁦@neilhimself⁩ Trent had the cutest refrigerator magnet in Studio C… https://t.co/yo2iiDsyyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 💯 Matthews!!!! #GoLeafsGo #AustinMatthews #LeafsNation https://t.co/potCgTF1iM]]></document><document><![CDATA[BANE Qualifier and bid winner   https://t.co/8s6oYSoodo.  #NCAAMVB #EIVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Eltrain @occupied_stall @AnnKing28 @seraphicpetal @creaturelives33 @ZandEDad @acakes421 @DandMe_MomOf5… https://t.co/l83DCbW8WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone come out to the game!!!! i promise you won’t regret it, our ladycats are something special!!🤩 #wearewalker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reality Check: 36 Politicians With Staggering Bank Account Balances https://t.co/FJx0mvMmMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[GLORY TRAIN CHANT OF THE DAY&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;SUBMIT, SUBMERGE, SURRENDER! https://t.co/8xOzgF3PuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I should shove my heel down your throat” -@demi_burnett  Needless to say I’m VERY excited for the #WomenTellAll @BachelorABC #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankie_leanne @ColourPopCo Beautiful!! @Vahalia241 @arcadiarose_ @Naddez @PanRose30]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a psychic and a ghost used their one phone call from the grave to tell me that my dad is an asshole... yesss girl haunt his ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hago un llamado eb este momento de alarma nacio al a las empresas #Movistar y #Digitel para que den megas y minutos… https://t.co/gOkfXZH62t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eileenleftnotri @TedNesi @RISpeaker The killing of a ‘quickened’ child - ie one that can live outside her mother -… https://t.co/axXosJjwqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanAndShay 8/10/19 is my wedding day, first dance is to Speechless. Feel free to surprise. 😂😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[^ Just a note to say that Counterpart is EASILY in my top 5 best series of all time.   Unreal good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spotify @MarenMorris Omg I’m so excited! #GIRL is going to be amazing 🙌🏻💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PT_bostonCrondo @Emjay_43 @BluSimba_ Always tagging me in anything related to the office, I appreciate you Paul😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 9th Fact: The average dwell time from colorectal adenoma (precancerous polyp) to cancer in the general popula… https://t.co/RKZKMkszFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Awesome!! After every criminal getting off we are finally starting to see people pay for crimes!!! ❤️🇺🇸🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House TODAY! 7 Charlesfort Place in Hilton Head Plantation from 3-5 pm. Contact Tammy Moody 843.384.9126 for g… https://t.co/RTsHcc2lFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[obstruction. Everyone involved in cheating these victims out of their rights to a trial  should be charged too. No… https://t.co/O7lLXpO46i]]></document></documents></author>