<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wondering which Flint-area teams will win girls basketball district championships? You're in luck. I have the answe… https://t.co/SFHSWOd45o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my big bro! Live a life of many adventures and are a cool dude! #ManofLeisure #TreatYoSelf 🎉🎉🎉 (o… https://t.co/uvF8Mnb1GP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, @MrJerryOC, if you’re not used to seeing snow, in your neck of the woods, there’s the propensity to freak a bo… https://t.co/oyOsXhALQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbroken Minute: We go through a critical basic concept that distinguishes why a fat adapted ketogenic or fasted st… https://t.co/jl5mLwE0mG]]></document><document><![CDATA[TeamMate tomorrow in LA at Teragram Ballroom! Who’s comin’? https://t.co/dQa01ATEEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever believes in the Son has eternal life, but whoever rejects the Son will not see life, for God's wrath remains on them. John 3:36😇🙌🏾✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse How many more Americans has  have to die just because of drugs and violence on the sou… https://t.co/0vBmGL5IQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely merry. Free Funny ecards - Create and send your own funny Rotten ecards https://t.co/MYv2GXWdDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daviesinator Nice! We have a couple of those floating around. I couldn’t tell you what type they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eyebrows are literally always changing I’ll see a picture of me from 4 months ago and judge myself HARD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realpaulincoln We need to remain to keep #ISIS from getting that ground back and help our #Kurdish #Allies.... The… https://t.co/we05kRrRDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauleyMo67 @bishopjdave @SarahTaras @lordsilktorn @MarciPreheim @joythruChrist @BamaTrolley @Shayes1983 @JeffTheGK… https://t.co/LKxLkseOR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronDawgsFan @2kCompGames @Big_Brudda_PURP @ayo_RANKem And he's got a mill MT PS4 for sale 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GillianHTurner @RichardHaass @realDonaldTrump It's part of being a salesman, part of the negotiating process.  Whe… https://t.co/sN0I6nFsfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bad Decisions left unsupervised runs this town. Great day out at the @LangBullseye 50K Ultra and Relay. Relay?… https://t.co/5OZ5tichBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for our @Avalanche fundraiser game next Tuesday! $5 from each ticket gets donated back to the rescue. Come… https://t.co/gd5IdRhz2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner WELL NOW THAT YOU SAT IT IN ALL CAPS IT MUST BE TRUE! good lord, meathead, calm down and have a snickers...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homeboy gonna get a slick Right Hook on the Night-Night button with that technique]]></document><document><![CDATA[#877877 Just Text Brady to #877877 VERY URGENT: Vote to close Charleston Loophole on gun sales today. But oppositio… https://t.co/VULiBN84LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @jaketapper Exactly..... how can we take trump serious...exactly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Server that makes more than everybody in the restaurant but receives 1 bad tip:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should you get a 2018 Mazda 3 or wait for the 2019? Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides!… https://t.co/qD8SgFy7ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpdateFamouss @TheEllenShow @lizakoshy @RyanSeacrest @KevinHart4real @NickCannon @itsjojosiwa @tyrabanks… https://t.co/nCqDCYI4NS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me right now at work after turning up all weekend https://t.co/hL2D2WuHXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down in our area, we hope that we can get a Ranney vs. Wildwood Catholic sectional final. White and Thweat vs. Lewi… https://t.co/JZvdYLIDYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @PasadenaMag for naming me one of the 2019 attorneys of distinction #familylaw #divorce #lawyerlife https://t.co/n6xJGrM4Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanNehman It captures awesome sunrises then when turned to the West sunsets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reganroberts7 No one trying to make you jealous if you don’t follow me why you seeing it 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gathered to watch #andrachansen in Houston - no @edinjusuframic or live action @ericsaademusic 😪 but plenty of… https://t.co/D4LUzIqD6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbrahamBelilty @gretchentovar @edgarzambranoad Por supuesto, pero vamos a La Castañuela, aunque yo soy abstemio. La comida es buena, dicen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enjoievan Supposedly they took out the line about Erica not being allowed into a wrestling league, so I deeply app… https://t.co/A5eUcyKIHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abuchean tres veces a gobernadora Pavlovich con AMLO, él la defiende y pide reconciliación  https://t.co/mq9ylZ1mR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you think you will do when she wants you to convert? C- to what? Z- anything else C- God is universal, s… https://t.co/aak1C7BL6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥When you remove carbs, you remove 30+% of your food options and you're removing the yummy things people tend to mi… https://t.co/izSFO4MvBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the only appropriate response to Falwells ridiculous statements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuebecSolidaire Commencez donc par exiger que  Vidéotron diffuse 100% Québécois!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IU could literally punch Wisconsin in the face and they wouldn’t call it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoonerGirl1969 @EJAfc You don’t follow people you disagree with? I do. Because I’m not always right, and it is goo… https://t.co/19QbyM6cF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickwhannon @AaronKlein Are you suggesting that this could be an outlandish and public violation of the #fbc. C… https://t.co/tk5JzKeAQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty bad when the Coach doesn't seem to know what is wrong with the team. Another disappointing season. @TDA3397… https://t.co/vyDws7tAlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little snippet from last nights photo shoot.  Clearly it was extremely professional 😂.  #pizza #ilovepizza… https://t.co/xWw2iZECGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this @KTXS_News feature on our plans to bring eSports to @mcmuniv. Thanks again @courtneybrowntv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my life had a theme song. My life could be summed up by this song https://t.co/uQejRquIMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the 37th in the @Mock_Kings #FantasyCaresCharityMock Draft, the #bucs select Jachai Polite, EDGE, Florida.… https://t.co/7tbdFCgFDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop by the Myersville Farmers Market this morning and sample some #wine. https://t.co/0Udk8uK6TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday @jillianknipp miss seeing you everyday. Have a great one🎂🎁💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rosé Amour - R &amp; D Series by @texasaleproject @ 3 Flights Up Taps &amp; Tacos — https://t.co/GaycPEZzhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAPCenter is definitely a better arena for hockey then @TMobileArena #sjsharks #visiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raaytweets Somebody told me that week that up north niggas can take a hint if you aren't interested, and move on t… https://t.co/T558tXlRG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like she’s genuinely crying over her nails? This world is messed up in many ways lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it garagistemeadery The Pits, BA Vanilla Reboog, Purple Waffles 😋 @ Garagiste Meadery https://t.co/8Uvpq6EvtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to last Spring Break when we pretended to be undercover NYPD cops......it’s a long story https://t.co/6SqGfl0C6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wow…  Now this is a Beautiful Strong Black Woman  that’s a TRUE Representative of  Black Woman’s Day!!!  Senator F… https://t.co/6SjPCAnqrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Min @JYakabuskiMPP and Min @VictorFedeli for hosting an excellent forest strategy consultation session to… https://t.co/A2HOO3oU1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlaveToTheRhyt6 @tajjackson3 @tjjackson 3 videos Of Latoya Jackson on details of  #MichaelJackson (1993) #RARE… https://t.co/9d6jAny9t9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“With 3D printers #Dominos can print a pizza” @rwang0 #datadriven19. 🤔 Pepperoni toner???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unprecedented Group of International Lawmakers investigating “FAKE NEWS” demand public meeting w/extraordinary coll… https://t.co/INOl9eqV4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pappy used to pat me on the head and say, "you a pretty good boy, I reckon I'll keep you".. lol  I loved that..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T__Neil @JODYHiGHROLLER @nyknicks Give the man a shot, we can’t get any worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[My co-pilot at work The Notorious B.I.G.  Spread love it’s the Brooklyn way! #biggiesmalls @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/smQNhukwan]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Korean propagandists are sending an envoy to @NHSEnglandLDN in the hopes of learning how to up their game whe… https://t.co/jfJzYe5ihJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley Yes and in other countries they would be lined up in front of the firing squad!! Hre they go on a book tour and lie some more!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ever evolving safety threat, a challenge for LE. #specialeventsafety    https://t.co/Jh4yJxy6oX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little range time with Zack to keep the skills sharp. #2ndamendment #freedom #liberty 🇺🇸 @ Point Blank Range - Ma… https://t.co/OknQhnquyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyJonesMcCoy I mean we could just jump straight to this day started because some dude got his head chopped off for marrying people...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: the children have been found!  Thank you to all those who helped share this important message!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We often only show the success on IG so I thought it was appropriate to share an EPIC FAILURE STORY. One of the MAN… https://t.co/o8DkYIeSjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders I would make myself a cheeseburger for breakfast at least twice a week and eat a bowl of Cheerios for dinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RpmacPaul 😂😳☕️☕️👍🏼 Good morning Paul! Happy Wednesday. https://t.co/fAFRho8go7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dying over here. Can’t stop watching (listen with the sound in) @RealKevKeenan @ShaneHelmsCom @LukeHawx504… https://t.co/fm3BnKq68v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris More Satan work is been carried out by these leftists students]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alpena! I got another #DuragDrive for ya! Stay tuned for my weekend adventure. https://t.co/W6bOy2YVXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanchBeef1 I wouldn’t sell anything to him unless I tripled the price!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaCarrillo Hi Jessi exitos en todo desde New York Colega Muchas Bendiciones 🙏🏻❤️🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fernandez has skills but he's gonna have to muscle up a bit. Columbus is manhandling him. :-( #RBNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[These clams with celery and spices was amazing. Wish I had more at Charcoal Kebab in San Gabriel. @ San Gabriel, Ca… https://t.co/KKb1DmSeOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is discovering that God loves me that gives me my greatest sense of worth. For to be loved means that someone fi… https://t.co/8Ts8dl7Ciw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either scenario is a pathetic reflection upon the Body Politic which authored &amp; enabled this escalating insanity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why people can’t just be straight up. Like what is the point in lying who tf cares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slutever Hey Karley, I absolutely LOVE your show @NowApocSTARZ. I’ve NEVER seen anything like it! I’m a longtime f… https://t.co/Ls1wTZ6vaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBoyVol @247_vols @ZehDuck @fishinvol365 @glpresley @Clint_Stutts @Diakonda For sleeping with the preachers son usually]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airwolf is one show i like to see remade...wouldn’t have the same cheesy greatness...but i would give it a gander..… https://t.co/7cO6JQ0Vir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmwired @ChrisG_NSF “Plutonium not Available at O'Reilly Auto Parts. Please contact your local supplier.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the RBNY groove // #SCCL2019 #CCL #CCLFever #RBNY #newyorkredbulls #COYBIR #REDtogether #redbullarena… https://t.co/82GhJgQVG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an extra 16 card #NHCD Canadian set that I’m looking to trade for an American set. Lmk if u want to swap. @UpperDeckHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trailblazers taking on @hornets ...Sorry in advance to @ScottBSports for getting this ‘W’ on your squad #ripcity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke with @CamEdwards on the @tonykatz show about why this criminal who emptied his gun at rival gang members with… https://t.co/aflirJGtht]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Walt Disney Studios 500 S Buena Vista St, Burbank, CA 91521 https://t.co/fSnawRDGua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contentment is not the fulfillment of what you want, but the realization of how much you already have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burrrr btch!!!!🥶🥶🥶 🔹 Snapchat📲 "kingfrost30" 🔹 #ChillyThoughts 🤔❄️💭 #chilly #ChillyVybz ❄️🌀 #king 👑 #frost #quotes… https://t.co/ZmY50NpL6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[New SONGS and BEATS is on the way! Before you hear what's new, check out whats already out from Goose Pärk. We Here… https://t.co/ENVnGyNE1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marykayconsult3 Our government and far too many Doctors have caught a contagious disease which renders them blind… https://t.co/DbuVkzt9Q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bike Warm Up   #NyC #Brooklyn #BrooklynHeights #NySc #Gym #GymLife #Fit #Fitness #GetFit #StayFit #FitOverForty… https://t.co/lf5AnIkH8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaNeher What I am suggesting is that they stop doing calls for scores and spend time looking for music. But I un… https://t.co/PKQDC2jN3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still deleting old email from my mailbox at this time of the morning @ Boerum Hill https://t.co/m35lW7IGHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tom_Bricker @hintofspy I’m not originally from Florida. However when we moved from the North 12 years ago I forced… https://t.co/bDnIUWpyzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/jlRwM8poHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen Inicio de semana! @HitsFm1061  Me puedes complacer y programar "Deberías Estar Aquí " de @RioRomamx poorfavor!… https://t.co/Nis33od1Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmsfcx @logmeoffplease why is there a straight up 11 year old in this video]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissGinaDarling Lol look at their comparison of likes and retweets to followers 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️🧐🧐 HAVE THEY BEEN BOUGHT??]]></document></documents></author>