<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Someone buy me a JMBLYA ticket I HAVE to see Kevin Gates and Lil Wayne. I HAVE too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CajunChick25 Seriously, we need current, photographic proof of life, or even consciousness. Every media report of… https://t.co/zYUImaGFsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved having @HaptX guys @joemich and @AndrewMitrak on my podcast this week!  #vr #haptics #technology #tech… https://t.co/mExtxBdsIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it masculine energy or my yawning that causes men not to approach me at bars?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with beautiful and positive people, who love you and believe in you. — @BryantMcGill 💕… https://t.co/pU4iHiOZXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Date Night @yardhouse #yardhouse #pasadena #valentinesday #craftbeer #liquidcompass #mochamachine… https://t.co/ebUCdQepue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@durantmainst @AllisonMary1994 @blakeshelton @gwenstefani @azarraga_feli @russko28 @willowfrantn @Friel_Dee… https://t.co/glcxGIpLQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtraLrgPopcorn @M_Hutsell @AlexPorter82 I never find much difference in the prices. Or not enough to justify the… https://t.co/T3i4k8qmN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass  #MarALardass #MarALardass… https://t.co/80LSruBHxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junerivera2016 @pnp_pr @ricardorossello @RosarioCortes51 @TATACHARBONIER @maver23 @QuiquitoMelende @ManoloMartin51… https://t.co/k4qBNzyLVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was supposed to be productive and study for my Conditions and Neuro exams...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well then. I'm going to guess there's a whole lot of law breakers in OK. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCHOENAMYYY the volume on my twitter doesn't work but I can see you're in the hospital. Please take care of yourse… https://t.co/AJEKTIA93U]]></document><document><![CDATA[York Police arrested Lester Varnadore for criminal sexual conduct with a minor. Criminal records show he was convic… https://t.co/AaZvXaxsrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougducey are you checking out AIA's comment in making schools travel in this weather for state tournament #safetyforourkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤯❤️ | a petty bitch ! I didn’t think you were gonna really go to the army but you up and left me 😩 I cried like a p… https://t.co/f8Il8ZseM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I told ya all about Neil Gorsuch's Books. https://t.co/7SWIdzaz1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve never been to a @GoldenKnights game, you’re really missing out. It’s amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending Slavery &amp; Human Trafficking Hearing - Opening Statement https://t.co/QroHAVlc6F via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for helping me reach 25 followers! Who else do you think should be following me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckGrassley @Rachelbomb Senator, get it done! You can be trusted to be honest.    Also, I want legislation that… https://t.co/Tn0DOmrsFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhadleyconrad @chucktodd Really Chuck Todd, unfortunately I do not agree with you. In fact I rarely do.  I am some… https://t.co/66n8XMcPNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When James Taylor who is suspect af notices how trash the Bach fandom is when it comes to WoC you have well and tru… https://t.co/JrC2yVpjHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[They ain’t picture me like this so I sent all of em selfies 🤑🤳🏾 - Rylo Rodriguez https://t.co/TZEozIBFMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part about doing a mud mask is getting up 60 minutes later to chisel—I mean take—it off your face]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday Rachel and I passed Kristen Stewart on the street and I was like Rach that was Kristen Stewart and she wa… https://t.co/Na94WR6kUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Benny3339 @RidleyHockey @Ridley_College Congrats Amanda you and these ladies work so hard. Well deserved!@RidleyAthletics @Ridley_College]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @amfam, we protect your possibilities and dreams.  Here’s to the movers, shakers, and dreamers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaimbey naman pakinggan magsalita nitong si @GaryAlejano. Masyadong pasiklab halatang nagdadrama lang. #Harapan2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! 🌞 Let’s go! #workoutflow #lift #Saturday https://t.co/nhIQTDbAUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinks about you When I learned he blocked you After he he didn't come and refused to talk to you Do you have no se… https://t.co/yasqwaU2iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish me luck that I don’t murder this prick mid-flight. ✈️ #Keshacruise bound!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skywalkerbeth @sarahkendzior Rivals Vanilla Ice in whitest hip hop name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg what a sweet 🍭🍿🍫 little shop!! Right next to the diner on Neil. I tried the jalapeño popcorn and it is fabulous! https://t.co/KFmPcG0HCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major props and sincere thanks to ER docs and staff @DukeRegional Their kind consideration, talents and efficiency… https://t.co/s8y1CgExIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AryaResists We are catching our shower warm-up water in buckets and we are using it for hand laundry and to flush the toilet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers VOTE!! In your spare time! 💗 NoChill 👊 #FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing a #giveaway? Use https://t.co/n1Bo2xjbDf for fairness. @dvdInteriorDsn #designinfluencersCon #InfluencerMarketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandysternshein At the moment I’m in Valencia. So wherever the fuck that is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain And I am an actor  look on line I went to two school not only that   I know what America  like just like bl… https://t.co/ACLlmsSQUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamTheMan180 We need to be at this game.   Sounds like a very late birthday party for somebody!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why ISN’T TEXAS IN THAT LAWSUIT OPPOSING THE NATIONAL DISASTER PROCLAMATION????????????? @TexasGovernor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claudipoppp @JaIenSkutt Yessss plus their actually beneficial to your whole mood/well being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my sweets cole 26th birthday! honoring your birthday today with Grateful Dead music around the house💜💜 i love you bub!]]></document><document><![CDATA[THESE FISHES IN THE SEA, THEYRE STARING AT ME • • • • #youngthegiant #cainsballroom #tulsa #oklahoma #way2ill… https://t.co/mVVn314Xra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bran_ONeill16 @MsBoland42 @mrscrawfordfhs @MsHenryFHS Well deserved honor for each of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t see it but I’m eye rolling myself into another plane of existence over this. Good to know anxiety is on t… https://t.co/8wK8tQIueu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jadeinnm @michaelschweitz Yes. I mean, how do you get something like this going? Do you say, “Hey, look, everybody… https://t.co/6RkWOK9uK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[when @CarlsonKeeli says she “only” has $4,000 saved up and i’m sitting here with a hefty amount of $0 in my savings account 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[oof i'm literally seeing bts and ariana grande both in may let's get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovin_shelby Thank you for the shout-out!! Looking forward to seeing you again😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPS_GamerDad I don’t know what to say. You make my heart hurt 😢. I wish I could hold you and make it better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to put my hair in some big box braids with triangle parts.. hopefully it dont take all day.. im tryna go out later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so easy for ppl on the outside, to sit behind their phone screen and shame moms for going out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[being apart from someone you truly love to better yourself is a whole different type of emotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[because of astronomical prices that result from the supply/demand of higher education.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to I Have Nothing by Whitney Houston on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/7mub1QhmmV https://t.co/JOUlZmZ4Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the days that my job allows me to spend time in my second home - a classroom ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean is there anything more relaxing than the sound of complete silence and snow falling from trees #bliss… https://t.co/pkVJsoCSt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmdouglas23 Ok but high key I’m trying to figure out when I can bring my typewriter here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Yes and this young man is a teenager. He is a child! How dare the liberal media destroy a young lif… https://t.co/dFrieVGcmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong, confident and radiating with courage! @ Spraytopia Airbrush Tanning- Waco https://t.co/ICe08Bhbew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei We’re on our way to the Escondido Art Museum where they have an exhibit of Photographs of this monstro… https://t.co/EXb8a8h4gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonJCLeBON Haha, no, but I thought you might like this 😁. https://t.co/htxWsc9WDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patience is not the ability to wait, but how you act while you're waiting.🙏🏽💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge From a fellow RN almost 77.  You're right.  Must end reign of Old White Men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s something to start your week: RSVP to @crestview_strat event this Thursday! It’s going to be a party! 💜👸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being skinny. wow my fried catfish from birth fed ass cannot relate  :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Wells Fargo VP says there’s evidence of trouble in iconic stagecoach program. @JStricklandWSB investigates c… https://t.co/4MhxKnzDaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from work and already watching @Daredevil again. I really think I have a problem. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go camping to a far away place where I can hear the stream running n drink cold water from it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book your glow up today with @GlowSyGlow #DallasClient #gorgeousglowbysy  #ShreveportMUA #TexasMUA #makeup… https://t.co/TnVapRY4ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's Emergency Declaration an 'Unfortunate Decision' https://t.co/jWedlI8Mec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esp_media @TLHTempleIsrael @KatzsDeli @abc27 @LeadTLH @COTNews @accesstally @LeonSheriff @WCTV @SeanPittman… https://t.co/lagdXIeJtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferMktg I think there's old people dancing at respectable hours on Sundays at Stony Island Bank, but I can't yet confirm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puede ser lo que sea pero para e una exposición de tipos de tampones 🤷🏽‍♀️ #Glacia https://t.co/Jw5MorNamk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes me smile when people hit me up looking forward to the next @6dnetworktainmt’s “Live! From the Living Room” 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suffer The Little Children, Pennhurst State Home: Eugenics + Social Serv... https://t.co/SSpnCA3Gti via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MValvarez64 @lopezdoriga Me acuerdo y me vuelvo a enojar, en lo personal fueron -$15,533 😠 y todo por un capricho… https://t.co/m8a66s0EGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up today and remembered that Green Book won best picture...talk about a gross Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaiderrr Say that to me when my heart rate goes up to the 180’s even when I’m just sitting down. Actually, I’ll ju… https://t.co/V7qlhqSMyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoabbaabba Finally this sick pos will pay for what he has done. For his victims my heart breaks. Also wtf is wrong with people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bincerli @rakiwane @lizkelley @kayvz Good but not Kayvz hoodie good https://t.co/BJ84Agt47R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @LuluLemew @kpolantz omg..nothing like a good old fashioned curmudgeon for a judge..most excellent]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOLO, vehicle stolen in Papillion... Dark Grey Dodge Ram with a topper Neb plate VUD 216 @omaha_scanner @SarpyBlotter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changes need to be made at the Industry level, not so much the consumer level. If companies are forced to use alter… https://t.co/I04ZdmHZ2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillCorbett I'd rather look at dogs on Twitter than the 5 million cats that show up on my Facebook feed every day.… https://t.co/V1kDwVbmK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don Sweeney talking to his team during crunch time of the trade deadline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @TheView Let’s hope Congress has the courage to debunk ‘national emergency’!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrulySocialMel @SproutSocial The Sent Report is your best friend. Set up great keywords in your inbox, read ALL yo… https://t.co/2LjhRXBcJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[At gym working out,    Me: i have to pee can you watch my hydro flask  Sehrish: I will literally cut anyone who looks at your hydro]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love leading the #Arkansas chapter of @AAEteachers! @astapro serves thousands of #EDUAR #ARED educators.… https://t.co/jAnClpxhPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oshanada I know they met their goal, but I just contributed. I encourage others to do so. The school can use all t… https://t.co/lOcpieFOZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arts &amp; Culture SHSM Day! @piratespocock1 @DpcdsbShsm https://t.co/wRsHebF87g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylordavis1020 I completely agree. That’s why I said that there are some people with specific situations that can… https://t.co/FxE9A8egDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @Almagro_OEA2015 @IvanDuque Atentos estamos!!! #VamosVenezuela #VamosBien]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my coach adds another sweet potato meal to my plan, i had to e-mail and ask if she was for real 😂😂😂😂 sweet pot… https://t.co/UBv246E0EH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoo chile God Bless the child who takes up most of my bed and not enough covers @ Montgomery Village, Maryland https://t.co/ErxEEBQCsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatPlainsInst @CityMinneapolis @MNCERTs It’s been our pleasure to work w @MPLSGreenBiz and his team! @IsaacEvans22 #savingBizEnergy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAPGAPDAY @KipHenley @JFrickeGolf @jpatonpga @dhansenAGG Ok dude I might have to come kick it ass now or maybe tal… https://t.co/J31ESlijiC]]></document></documents></author>