<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If this happens, @DaveFoster17 and I will take that day off and become superfans in the stands for both sides.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No TV or Internet and the only help I can get is a technician on Tuesday. Major Fail @Xfinity @comcastcares]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suggest she move to Venezuela. They need genius like that to load guns for the establishment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kzelyck My first question concerns risks if a patient takes an opioid after they have the implant. Some will likel… https://t.co/QqAcNoyLUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so ready for the weekend. I promise I’m gonna catch up on some sleep Saturday morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TO WHY WE A 4 th WORLD COUNTRY=VP PRENCE IN EUROPE SAW AMERICA HAD NO PLACE ANY MORE\\SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connor Visnic 9:18.17 - 2nd place CT State Open. New Amity indoor record 3200m. @amityathletics https://t.co/lqvuTCHyqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I start at Edison High School 🏫 tomorrow, Wednesday, March 6, 2019. 💃🏽🕺🏾🍾🥂🎈🎉🎊🏋🏾‍♂️💪🏾🏅🏆🤑💰💸👼🏽🙏🏾🇺🇸 @ Minneapolis  Publ… https://t.co/GSGq1XPoEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber Question: Does a House vote for impeachment mean yes remove from office? Thu 21 Jordan 8… https://t.co/vMBGKwJA6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow morning I will be preaching at Oak Ridges Church, pastored by my good friend Keith Montgomery. Thanks for… https://t.co/UEul6OxC1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Houstanity -gun buybacks don’t get the guns off the streets that are going to be used in crime imo. You’re getting… https://t.co/A89FtxcpOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darts !!!! LETS GO!!!!!! (@ MT's On 8th - @stcloudminn in Saint Cloud, MN) https://t.co/U6CvLijapI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peggynoonannyc What makes his testimony "credible"?  Is it the same level of "credible" as Blasey Ford?  Or did it… https://t.co/Rka7nfVnaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 days, 7 non fiction books I love from @hdighn. Day 1: https://t.co/Ib5QHnyaYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGAmbrose Same lol the man is incredible. True captain. Mkhi has been huge for us. A lot of positive things to bui… https://t.co/If39WVHpIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thugmajesty I don’t know of anything but housing is much more affordable out here! Living in Denver isn’t too bad… https://t.co/YffB4xOobu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despicable Me Character Design by Carter Goodrich #mirth #snicker #smile #funny https://t.co/NhkXzY3I2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash He thought America will eat that fallacious investigation. I am glad he was fired and hope he will be… https://t.co/8kw0768bCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I yelled that there was a fire multiple times and nobody wanna leave? Now they in the hospital, fucking idiots. I l… https://t.co/F76bz94BpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up at 5:45 am thinking it was 5:45 pm and ive never had a bigger heart attack]]></document><document><![CDATA[They got Trina and city girls on repeat at the club right now 😩 the dude I’m with is so confused lol but I’m throwing it back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah! One of those #challenging repairs! #piano #broken #music #love #fix @ Narberth, Pennsylvania https://t.co/EzPtB7V20M]]></document><document><![CDATA[#untpreview #frankwandsuemaybornschoolofjournalism loving the atmosphere and feel very welcomed here feel very hype… https://t.co/qBKmp5iYHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Tucker goes on that spontaneous vacation that was actually planned for months in advance, looks like Hannity is… https://t.co/E5ZGAezwSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fincherism Agency is empowerment what part of that dont they understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Kozora A Buffalo radio guy said BUF gets 20 and AB, PIT gets 9 and a 4th next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked like the guy having way too much fun shoveling the snow listening to this!  @AdamSandler https://t.co/0yp80T7fTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GREATBLACKOTAKU The judges will deduct points for not sticking your landing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week wasn’t the best week and I still have a lingering #cough that won’t go away.  Hopefully, I will be better… https://t.co/eKNCIiDpfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[can't wait for summer mornings in the Smokies 🌲 . (can wait for flies and humidity) . . . #greatsmokymountains… https://t.co/24BLBxrblZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkjemisin OK tweeple, Marge says this is the two of us dancing. Guess which one is me! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @catscovemedia • • • • • ❌ SATURDAY FEB 16 ❌  You don't want to miss @joebassband, The Do-Gooders, and… https://t.co/F3HbctAv2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical Trump Cult Followers Changing The Real Truth. You Pinheads NEVER had that Plan in Place. Pathetic, Still Ca… https://t.co/jcG39sUQtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did @JoeNBC just wake up this morning, realize he knows nothing, and then decide to make shit up for the day? He's… https://t.co/0FlTIQQPH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madonna Yeah baby! MTV’s most groundbreaking music video of all time!🌟🌟🌟🌟🌟 https://t.co/0laufRG5bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Berry Good idea - Bank of Jackson supporting American Heart Association with Valentine's Day fundraiserhttps://wn… https://t.co/M3wcp2hyVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaprockHigh_TX for a boys showdown between Shallowater and Canadian @Lee_Passmore @AmandaMAtwell @806SPORTS… https://t.co/4tOelJTa61]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LMULions getting ready for PCH Cup part 3: WCC Tournament edition. Win or go home with the winner advancing to pla… https://t.co/vJ6VpoPQEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it really has felt like this the past couple weeks. https://t.co/pFcRmIyJ4g via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[BHS Athletics- Boys SWIM States at Bowdoin College 11, TRK States at USM 12, NSKI States at Stark's in Fryeburg 2,… https://t.co/JxXtdJWCDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escuchando a Julissa Ortiz hablar de los dones para servir, en la reunión de jóvenes de ruta.61 en IESP Central https://t.co/2NpSqmguJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[She thought she was so tough closing out her statement with periodt just to spell it wrong 😭😭🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tricky_dick_tx @chadfelixg The killer even asked a patron of the bar where all the females were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really not a photogenic type of person 😂 I’m more of a video nigga lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went in for a double cheese $2 and got upsold to a healthier choice $6. I’m not JOSHing you! @ Burger King https://t.co/AvzANyXi00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers and love for Coach Curtis Holt. Teammate and friend! You got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have an old laptop or one you’re not using anymore? I’m in desperate need of one. If anyone would be so… https://t.co/HM7rYB6xcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s look is done by the lovely @EmilyAnne1821. I think she will be the next @jamescharles https://t.co/xCSdWocHRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @SebGorka Meh. Let’s focus on her proposals as they are childish enough. We’ve all whiffed one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennmhumphreys @cvpayne @FoxBusiness I feel slighted now, 😂, my 85 average in high school, C student, would be an… https://t.co/CIYJyVdJvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Scripture is inspired by God and is profitable for teaching, for rebuking, for correcting, for training in righ… https://t.co/hYMh7AnRED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northernpapa @DSAArchaeology There is a 3 story outhouse in Trapper Creek, Alaska very similar design.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cockiest guy in the word! Sad! Cant wait to seenyou turn up in the CFL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch the ball, Dolphina! This awesome girl is hanging out in the shelter office waiting for a friend to play with.… https://t.co/sfmqjxUWNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all your ways be mindful of him, and he will make straight your paths. Do not be wise… https://t.co/9tF3DvfdQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissMoore24 Shut the fuck up...i want you to be successful and have children. Lol I not being creepy. Good luck yo… https://t.co/myeYwbcZrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y'all. You may want to keep this #pycascades2019 talk handy for PyCon US. I hear you may be acquiring a new toy… https://t.co/mHhdXbE8mH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanebacon The 18” putt I made at Hazeltine on the 72nd hole went in the side door, if that counts.😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a bum ass bitch gonna act like they don’t have manners and respect to speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨If you are not following my friend and expert instructor @bobgrissett you are missing out on a TON of knowledge! .… https://t.co/y4LNrdGc0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fruit roll up. Better than expected. New Glarus Wisconsin Red. - Drinking a Blushing Monk (2019) by… https://t.co/h6nAQPpiVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamamann1995 @CFB_Bets How about you tell me who you bet on, so I can double down on the opponent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think one of the first songs I slapped belly buttons to was J. Holiday’s “bed”, from then on....it was over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedNolesFan @TheRealEazy32 Lmao I always think about Eazy when I hear stummy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lelulovexo Lelu...you deserve all the awards as you are a good person....good listener...❤❤❤❤❤🌷🌷🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryjanesosexy Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rangers go on the road to South Pike and pound out 28 hits over two games....winning 13-0 and 16-0. @rscummings19 w… https://t.co/izkAyNog7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to head home, looks like lite snow everywhere but nothing that should slow me down today! (@ Continen… https://t.co/hP3ryxVxcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachergirl00 He is who he is, not who he plays. Either way, he's perfect as far as I'm concerned! 🌹💙🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me on Ellen   Ellen: So I hear you’re a fan of Grey’s Anatomy   Me: Yeah!  *Ellen plays How to Save a Life*  Me: Oh my god Ellen you didn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So hypocritical coming from a coward who’s daddy got him out of serving]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY FUCKING 21  !!!!!!!   When I first started my gym journey , I read somewhere “it takes 21 days to build a habit… https://t.co/bai9jZtR16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @xoskylarann went out in our fits tonight ❤️🥰😍 https://t.co/jK2suv3RUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just look at Cassius Winston and wonder how he is good at basketball?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSlatt @jareddiamond It’s been a minute buddy!  Hope you have a nice warm day, a hot dog and some popcorn!  (Oh… https://t.co/gWuxZF3xNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Britney really is that bitch 🔥@britneyspears https://t.co/Ts5HcuOhpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consequence This is what happens when you are broke and haven't been funny in 25 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nos vemos mañana en la @BMA_NL para conversar sobre justicia constitucional y democracia en la 4T https://t.co/BWSpk52eSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lástima que siendo peloteros, jovenes, super estrellas, se liguen a contratos multi anuales en equipos muy limitado… https://t.co/r2Aae1IsK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennyYoungZLX @wzlx @NationalGolfXpo @iHeartRadio The #NightRocker brings the #Sunrise.... https://t.co/zgDwCOIOwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump: Sometimes you have to run along side Kim's car to make a deal.. - Trump says "sometimes you have to w… https://t.co/dvqW0Mkcqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesnt China limit the kids u can legally have? #communism, #Socialist, #LeftismIsAMentalDisorder ... I wonder who… https://t.co/gHwVCp0XJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes but all you journalists should know that if @JussieSmollett was really guilty of what’s being spread THE CHICAG… https://t.co/0ZkOvtP1hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenrogers6abc @6abc I felt like I was in an episode of “Dark Shadows”! 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miiidnight_ @magee333 Have a great time in Mexico, Laura! Have a nice, relaxing weekend, Ash!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Artist Mind. Mixed media on canvas 16" x 20". #mixedmedia  #artistsoul  #artcollectors  #artconsultant… https://t.co/69cObgfxJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJGIV79 @RingsideC IDK man ..maybe something I missed you know how bad it is out here]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL IM CRYING!!! MY BEST FRIEND JUST WON NCA!!!!!! EVERY TEAM NEEDS SOMEONE AS HARD WORKING AND AS DEDICATED AS TH… https://t.co/B9klyU5lJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art #artistsoninstagram #artist #arte #boy #girl @ Oro Valley, Arizona https://t.co/59kiBIUf8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floridajjh @BusyElves Kings and fake news.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/177… https://t.co/IwvRJxr0Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Bears were overmatched tonight against a highly ranked Marian team. With the loss, the season comes to a close.… https://t.co/55ER07i1Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life for the first half-hour after I get home from work. #catlife #Eratosthenes #Enheduanna #nonturbulentcats https://t.co/YxCAiXvJp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for .@lelepons to perform .@premiolonuestro can’t wait !!! #lelepons who are you excited to see perform ton… https://t.co/uAi2QroehX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickJVT @sweatscience When the time factor is added in, though, it’s more than just chest and arm strength. It… https://t.co/lZz51ZMUJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the @NHL @Capitals vs @NYRangers shootouts on tv. How bad the @nhl referees are? Just clueless 🙈🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary (I don’t actually remember) https://t.co/C7xkJMQQY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSpeier Polar bears are driving taxicabs and Uber cars in Miami...No Global Warming?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After listening to the new Jonas Brothers I can fully say they are back. 2019, what a wild year. #JonasBrothersAreBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KU_Womens_Hoops is headed to the #PSACwbb semis, dropping Lock Haven 81-64. They’ll face Cal on Saturday.… https://t.co/3PNUqNCmEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can’t say you care about helping your people succeed in their professional and personal lives and then suppres… https://t.co/GOtDvDKVMp]]></document></documents></author>