<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[By and large, we HAVE put an end to the misguided horror of “conversion therapy.” I’d like to see it illegal on a f… https://t.co/NtIuhsFhIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#model titaniaartmodel #rich auburn art group #oil paints #canvas @ San Anselmo Recreation Department https://t.co/x3FjQDhokY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never had Buffalo chicken fries like that, but they look KICKIN !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that pit stop practice over the winter being put to good use 💪🏻 https://t.co/nWKA5JVhya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinnotjust1n @TeamGaryVee @garyvee Sweeet!!! Oh I will. I watched he 6 hour and the 4 hour super bowl!! Appreciate u!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you can build it now without the money you asked for, why the 35 day shutdown? You either are l… https://t.co/3auf8eaTTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValorCollege @aaroncrabb79 @amandascrabb @elevation_wrshp @HISHEIRESSANDCO All natural!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/Rk37e6uxIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNEE Lo que deve de aser Donal trump que mande viveres a esa pobre jente que lo nesesita los soldados para que madre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day Four: I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @mmorrisBHS. I’ll post covers of 7 books I love—no expl… https://t.co/hxov2qcoZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes i notice that 9 years ago bored at work I created a sports group on Facebook which in turn gave some dude… https://t.co/1GtFmmGsmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other words they meant to fucken do all this shit and embezzlement from our state and load there country's up wi… https://t.co/rExfnaxU6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very Happy Birthday to the most wonderful wife and amazing mummy in the world! Love you so much Mamma Stooks! You… https://t.co/fxaFkzW87t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before we got married we decided that Valentine’s was a little silly, definitely a greeting card holiday.   BUT, it… https://t.co/amwla1HDf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucymcbath I’m right there with you congresswoman. Thank you for your tireless work on this important issue. This is a national emergency!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not being used for the auditions, but here’s the work vehicle for the Nats Bullpen Cart Driver. https://t.co/qssx6ueYTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your 2019 Suffering Knicks Fan face makes @kevinlove’s Instagram post #DoItForZion https://t.co/bduWURdNed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillgray He's Like A Helium Balloon Recycling His Intake  https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanTheMan1118 @stamfordpaul3 We were in the driving seat going into penalties until that moment. It completely fuc… https://t.co/YQE9yWkari]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdw1973 It’s so amazing. Glad u are enjoying. It’s one of our 4 favorite places in town!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at stacks kitchen in Waxhaw, NC w/ @aheart4god316 https://t.co/9ku3OBinzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworkers trying to set me up with this fine ass model chick, I love my job lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUtdDub I saw Ashely Young make an inaccurate ground pass in the corner 3 yards from his targeted man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 1st United Methodist of Callahan https://t.co/Z71gH4blxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. 351. Doesn’t really sound as cool.   If y’all don’t come support this team next Monday versus UConn after what… https://t.co/lHvEw9rAGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beauty  #lingerie  #stockings #fashioneditorial  #personalityportraits #lifestylephotography #editorialphotography… https://t.co/Y8YtA2RUh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andoenpando Sin embargo,cada uno elige su vida. Descansa en paz Kukin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/fmWbhTIRb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[These ball fields get more and more out of control by the year. . . Wouldn’t trade these field nights for anything else tho!🙃🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a pretty good representation of how Mardi Gras weekend went https://t.co/MXTHeD08B6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all learned a sense of curiousity, wonder, and general kindness from watching @pbs and it shows.   Keep i… https://t.co/3Rcj1eUafZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para broncas nomas yo y mis huevos. La neta no soy de esos que ocupa gente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katyperry i hate you!. i will never forgive you for what you have done!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCU_Gooner @gooner_toni We haven’t seen Mbappe’s best yet while the law of averages will see Lukaku being the old… https://t.co/oclKU9dftw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello March! #jrs #jessesroofing #jessesroofingservices #GreenRoofing #hellomarch #Friday #fridayvibes #memories… https://t.co/fgwX94CMyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Durango's Riley Amos, Christopher Blevins and Howard Grotts were all named to the @usacycling mountain bike… https://t.co/JLAaMGyjxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatclouthier Felicidades mientas estemos seguros los mexicanos ! Y sea para salvaguardar nuestra integridad EXCELENTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the new logo for @BUAthletics @MatthewMcCord4 https://t.co/vPUxqFuOxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingRicochet I support you everyday. But after living in Owensboro KY for 10 years; Paducah is a Crap hole and smells like it too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AVPhenom @tastefullykate @NSCA_systems Uh Me too Mark you are missing me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWECorino @JeffreyBJones @Phillies Ummmmmm what the he’ll are you doing, @WWECorino!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling creatively drained all this week. I want to take time off but at the same time I need to upload something t… https://t.co/engw0Lwoeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvme2274 @FlandersTeam1 @RyanCole1623 @bevaj2002 @ORLANDOSHINES Awesome work! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the big fella @2ReidTravis2 is eating in the post!! #BBN #CATS #GrownMan #LoadInThePaint 🔵⚪️😼🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will have a #EbonyAndIvory line up on MARCH 3rd #StandUp #Comedy #EchoOnPico #Laughs #takeyourLimethere lls that… https://t.co/BmewM6wNBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HariSeldon2100 @HHM3Lifeisgood @CoryBooker And you are beyond an idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon by The #TownsendTeam  Recently renovated semi detached home in an incredible area.  Spacious eat-in kit… https://t.co/9nbVkUruhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can just tell this dude wants to be a Dodger so bad. Hopefully in due time. 🤞🏽💙⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My offer to @elonmusk (lmao Elon Tusk good one bro) my initial offer that is valid until the sun sets here in Ann A… https://t.co/G8nbf8VzdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet he wouldn’t be upset if the Isles signed Austin Matthews away from the Leafs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewUbil @pivettahype Everything I've read suggests he's still in Vegas. And that a deal will be completed Monday, Tuesday at the latest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it's so groovy now that people are finally getting together...Oh wait, Wrong Again! Nancy Pelosi continues… https://t.co/B93KoLbHxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-show glow later gram! 😍😍😍 #mattdamonimprov #glowedup #bhm  #blackhistorymonth #intersectionalAF… https://t.co/ztjfdYDbVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spillygoat19 Very happy for all the Rockies fans. Nolan seems like a 100% class act.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a very busy week, nothing like a toasty snow-run. https://t.co/l6Qg1MLVpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsiren @SPCEliteInvite Wow what a schedule. BTW @sportsiren you have beautiful handwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to create the ultimate theatre room in your home? Come see us this weekend! Don’t miss out on our awesome deal… https://t.co/lMyz21kWaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMirror @CliffShep When does the next Hale-Bopp pass?  #NeverForgetBenghazi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last last shopping (@ The Woodlands Mall in The Woodlands, TX) https://t.co/ZjoGMS9JgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the behind the lyrics on spotify and wishing I had the natural verbal poeticism these artists have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/06EsyUqgB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coated them in corn meal spiced with cumin, coriander, chilly powder and curry leaves, crispy heaven. @Jacksonville… https://t.co/GH0iDdn1dB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skelechiwatson u were amazing in last night’s episode! Every scene u were in brought so much joy and emotions. Tha… https://t.co/lnR6J3AgYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPeaksNValleys @chriscampanioni @GPhoto2 @ModelViews @ChrisChasePnV @81TakTsukada18 @Todd_1014 @SpectacularBody Arm game is strong.💪🏻💪🏻💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Google Not my entire google account, just the gmail account was deleted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanpholman @camachocigars My absolute pleasure buddy!!  Hope you enjoy them and see you soon my friend!!!… https://t.co/NWzX95xxla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Molloy has 10 points, 1 steal. Louis Perona adds 7 points and 4 rebounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GertieJefferso4 Blessings to you Sister Gertie, thanks for the encouragement sweetheart♥️ goodnight 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear as soon as I pass the exit for Mechanicsville my country accent comes in thicker than molasses. Bless my heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m soooo bloody close to loving @anthemgame with ALL my heart, but tonight saw me dropped to Home no less than 8 t… https://t.co/UPKuPpbVHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You ever been so drunk you can’t find your dick”.... nope not there yet I always find my dick 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewclaussen @gopherstate @cjzero @ChrisDilks @Ben_Jones88 I assume it was an offsides. No announcement here in th… https://t.co/ouSNzUAw3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Queens Boulevard Bridge over Sunnyside Yards in Queens, NY https://t.co/QKxAMUpW1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEAD THE FIFTH: like this &amp; Imma dm a question and quote this tweet with an honest answer or say I plead the fifth. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmmJaay1 והלא הערבון היא כל ישראל ערבין זל״ז ואכתי אינן נקיין בענ׳ זו]]></document><document><![CDATA[technology isn't all that great, thank you iphone for accidentally calling 911 WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I love cutting red hair. This guys hair always turns out nice. Styled with sea salt spray and a blow dryer👍… https://t.co/3QzkLtAubU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other mfs be hot asf sometimes, Like damn foo thats crazy facial symmetry you got going there, who your barber as w… https://t.co/pFYgx9kNA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom But this is a direct result of SYG laws.  The resident should not be prosecuted in this case.  I don’… https://t.co/f9d2fYCFmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No church official, no matter where he comes from, should return thinking this isn’t a problem back home     Via… https://t.co/wLm2gQhm8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Sunday's Welcome Team pointing out the Easter Season @ GCCC. https://t.co/c6zlxmBPCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHeggie Supposedly it's all the rain, making the track unsafe for the horses when they run]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Julia, Please stop with your radical tweets to get your daily approval from your fake friends. You… https://t.co/DbkRzXwZWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indy Hoops 3rd grade B Runner-Up. Nice work New Pal Heat 2nd grade. #Strive2bGreat #YoungDragons https://t.co/1V8AsYhtJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank YOU @DoriKing2! Getting to work with the kids always makes my heart and soul overflow 😭🤡💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you, Mr. President, for dealing with the extreme Democrats who obviously care not for the sa… https://t.co/7qfwE6y4k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst thing about high pressure and cold air masses(happening now)? Treadmills become motorized shock machines https://t.co/KZ57dbzL6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn to thrive in your personal and professional life through the gift of true connection. Join us next Saturday!… https://t.co/ZuZ75aIRTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@col1015 That first pic is legit! Also makes me realize how poor I am 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbuckshelp How does one get to terminal B from terminal D when there’s no signs 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinAstrosFan @colbyklaus @BillSomhigh36 @cmsense18 @CypressEd I’m far more proud of this exchange, though: https://t.co/bHztMdPWDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harrisburg | REAL IDs now available to Pennsylvania residents https://t.co/VCArEuo5Xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racefancentral @NASCAR @LVMotorSpeedway @ISMRaceway @ACSupdates @jjpb_nscrgirl @TariBKfan @4KevinHarvick @kross700… https://t.co/eP8qzngVGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @TheRickyDavila @FoxNews @GM @Buick @chevrolet @GMC @OnStar @Disney @ZipRecruiter @Starbucks… https://t.co/w9aUqyi9H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[News 25 now showing bad weather north and east so why dont they close the roads...    You wont catch me out in that crap too dangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Foles is NOT coming back to the Eagles next year as the backup. #StopIt https://t.co/0dQBVeq4Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSerweKETV I’ll be on S4E3 by the time the snow stops #GoT #WinterIsComing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday funday! Go Miners 🤙🏼 #matchday #epmad @UTEPWTennis @utepathletics utep_miners @ Fort Collins, Colorado https://t.co/HsSxMByCc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: Non-emergency emergency: US politics  https://t.co/DlvuZgUS78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UA1831 @joshclackler No!! Uncle Phillip was a good Christian man. He was talking about deer.]]></document></documents></author>