<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@vickis @CartierAwards @AllieB @erikashimizu @LorettaMcCarthy @MandelaSH @Portfolia1 @rorrovillar @sarahkunst… https://t.co/t9894YQrgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. HOW am I supposed to leave the animal care center without this puppy?!?!?! Valentine’s Day is over, but Brow… https://t.co/7H7PWC8X27]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why @realDonaldTrump doesn’t finance his wall the same way he’s financed everything else for years—Rus… https://t.co/AfAtRn4BPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[O no siento nada o te amo tanto que no me da el alma, no hay punto medio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnowledgeLegacy   I`m Professional crystal cup manufacturer、if you need pls contact me .all of my products are han… https://t.co/hCIrRC9phQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btweenlovenlike @tonyposnanski Spit on him, anyway.  Feel free to say it's from me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generation Z Surpasses Millennials In P2P Payment Usage via @forbes https://t.co/nx5sGM7nGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss What is she talking about? Did her oath of loyalty mean lie, lie, lie, no matter the cost?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay admittedly, I am at the biggest weight I’ve ever been, BUT, I’ve also never been as confident as I am now. I w… https://t.co/xFZt55LUtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheYAGuy @Jamie_Beth_S @TomIsbell @SJSchmitt @ErinRhewBooks Josh, I've been like the guy who said, "What? Homework… https://t.co/01oiCxJRmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that can't eat, can't sleep, reach for the stars over the fence, world series kind of love. #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention all Knights, were 48 followers away from reaching 1,000. Follow us and retweet one of our latest tweets f… https://t.co/StPGOjCwxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a documentary, there are drug enforcement officers cutting down marijuana and just let it go up in flames… https://t.co/BmJLiDgMzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This my go to right here 💗 Izick will always be a real ass friend since day 1 love you and appreciate more than alw… https://t.co/NnlRK0izTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clarknt67 @DeirinDC @XCleXo @SenKamalaHarris @JimObergefell @ACLU Here, at least we can agree. It was Edie Windsor and the ACLU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattEdw12312749 @Irma46977582 @DontBuyMurder @Cynwel73 @JanuaryBabies01 @Dave06031956 @jadeo09 @sailorfawnie… https://t.co/f9QSoMxkhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @_CARTERDANE @alex_mecum @BruceBeckhamXXX @adamramzi_xo @corykanexxx @Beaux_Banks @TeganZayne @TheWesleyWoods… https://t.co/wvUwrkUder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already trying to plan for internships and summer classes.... and trying to juggle traveling holyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama close the door. It's too cold ❄️ @capitalweather Falls Church https://t.co/LyR1G30QbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir @reply New York! It gets me one step closer to visit my sister!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlitterCheese I actually think it does pass bechdel because of that woman at the reading who tells her not to writ… https://t.co/tUEim0Ci1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men have been doing this since high school house parties, you aren’t unwrapping a hidden secret]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kniggej fr! but at our house it was all on the girls! the only thing my brother had to do was take out the garbage… https://t.co/qabw9Gr4dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaRoisman I WON!!! Can my son get a shout out tomorrow!! His name is Aiden from Evanston IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I catch myself wondering how different my life would be if my mom was still here - how different it would… https://t.co/ozHdVi2NFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want you to know @codyjohnson I break all the rules of radio!! This Texas girl LOVES #COJO and proud of it.… https://t.co/Nr6nu6CNoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgtv Not sure where to post this, so I'll put it here.  I would appreciate your comment on this, #HGTV.  I asked m… https://t.co/YiXrkovEYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiroad77 @Easy_Chowder @nypost Except that’s not the platform so try again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabrinaMcD I love these! I usually have mine redesign the book cover, but these “one pagers” have a lot more detai… https://t.co/mAoGZNmQqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So arrogant that he can’t not watch a show that he knows is going to parody him yet he’s only upset because it’s no… https://t.co/kN5CjBYw0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m, apparently, hear-the-new-Bruno-CardiB-duo-vis-a-vis-@nprmusic-years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen This is beyond criminal. These children need to be reunited with their parents. #FamiliesBelongTogether]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missouttamyway I fell asleep around 11 like normal and now...not sleeping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spirittribevibe @Sinixstar Sounds like a predator. Plus I have a cougar around here and I’m always scared it’s goi… https://t.co/QzQC2DVJED]]></document><document><![CDATA[u ever take a picture of urself and u feel like it doesn’t even look like u and u have an internal crisis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @warrenwarmachi1 @AOC I invite her to live just one week without ac, in DC summer as I have in FL.… https://t.co/P1lh9fik7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's a rainy night in Georgia... #YouEatOreos #FanlmilySizeForOne @Nabisco https://t.co/OnC68jJzzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illest_Leen Damn that hella sucks. I’d be pissed if I couldn’t have mashed potatoes anymore lol. They gave me the… https://t.co/cISgoQwFuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for a buyer on 1072 Brayden #Hebron #KY  #realestate https://t.co/7cS6LREbV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Road_Guy I can’t even comprehend the situation. 11 years old. Completely innocent child. Senseless, brutal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Do You Feel All Right by KC &amp; the Sunshine Band, from #SoundHound https://t.co/hwkpRQNwbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leafalcus Thank you! Happy Friday and Happy March🍒🌷🌸🌷🌸🌷 https://t.co/XtSMDZVss9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally haven’t even clocked in yet and my boss already annoyed me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True except he almost beat me to death. THANK Goodness some senses came to my head before I ended up actually dead… https://t.co/X7WeJON6j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: Fantasy Island sort of gave people an immersive empathy experience. #mrrourke #dtk12chat #sxswedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobileSA All I care about is the camera!  Want the best camera on my phone that I can get!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @chrislhayes would you post the clip with Sean Malloney telling you about Republicans not showing up t… https://t.co/v7rJkk0PiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElCigalaOficial I live in the Bay Area, saw you in Sydney, AU and flew to LA to see you again! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful #hikingwithdogs in the marsh yesterday #dartmouthma #winterwandering #vizsla https://t.co/BiTlpAH2im]]></document><document><![CDATA[I posted flowers twice, and someone like “Ohhh your new boyfriend treating you good good” if you don’t shut the fuck upppp🤣😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElvisPresley @GIPHY Too bad this wasn’t in #68ComebackSpecial GIPHY 😢 It’s my favorite! https://t.co/Fi59zZAlis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigredwavenow Santa, never heard of that one. St. Nicholas is being rewarded for rescuing &amp; providing for the children]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early to grade students’ essays, and I swear Franklin is silently advocating for each one of them. https://t.co/y9JkRAOj1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hobichuu The fact that he was smiling as he talked about drowning his children. He SMILED. That’s extremely fucking disturbing]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t tell me we have money for technology, but not for books” @pernilleripp #MRA2019 #MiSchoolLibrary… https://t.co/GD6ExrDRLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cricket6 @madShana @Fridaygirl1969 @enelra5 @mia_nj @hannadjh @nm9139 @pm3900 @ThePhightins33 @davisis1… https://t.co/FuXwuRN5Mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoundsTFS @FreddithWapith @Cookie_SMIF @TeamFusionOG So Freddie what pounds is saying is that until he could chang… https://t.co/BMy3ldTMxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank u for ruining my party and my emotions &lt;3 now..when’s the next tour https://t.co/7gUPfiEKpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chère municipalités/villes du #Quebec et chère #MTQ...  Commencez à remplir vos trous, ça commence à être sérieusem… https://t.co/uqinlsPZde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoeywrites I would start contact a staging company...and a company which builds staging ...and ACAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when women have different men every few months, and have their kids call them daddy.. like wtf. You’re hurti… https://t.co/OhYMLSNuRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[So can you do me a favor make if i pull it together make it sooner than later]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just turned the brightness up on my phone...I meant to turn on my light on my room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianne_gray @SideHustleWino @RoarLoudTravel @always5star @MadHattersNYC @monstervoyage @_sundaysunsets_… https://t.co/BAzCJ6r2AE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take Me In To The Holy of Holies - Serious Worship https://t.co/tLKfRpyePT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just reminded of the long ago existence of the Caribbean Zone bar in SF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is my last night pouring resin for a bit so I can finish all the stuff in my work in progress bag. #resin… https://t.co/zFPOhyDspH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature People may no like them. But remember the a a necessity to the ECO SYSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow In 2003 at age 90 my great aunt died on the plantation where my mother was born and my great grand mo… https://t.co/rpVwIekOg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealpeterm @DanRather @ZerlinaMaxwell What was it called when Obama did the same at the border. He used tear ga… https://t.co/04J6xesrOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[How a Raw Vegan Diet Helped My Mother Beat Leukaemia and Stay Cancer Free For 16 Years https://t.co/UbNWcaAhQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered a Pretzel Pizza 🥨 🍕 on the 7th and still pissed about it. Lmaoooo I was looking forward to it sooooo much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner This is without a doubt so true!! Dems need to unite and speak the truth about the most important things to all of America!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m rewatching Game of Thrones and everything with Catelyn and Robb is so hard to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game2 - must win #hockeyvalley (@ Pegula Ice Arena - @gopsusports1 in University Park, PA) https://t.co/KvbU4mChyp https://t.co/eCY9IghKyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmortensen But it was just an old woman with big sunglasses! What have you done! Oh god what have you done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made Steak &amp; Broccoli with Bacon Sushi rolls on the side for dinner tonight. HOLY YUM is it tasty!… https://t.co/1gIPnYsLXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @JoeNBC @IlhanMN The truth is a hard pill to swallow. https://t.co/62mVfzqWjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Best Song From Every Fleetwood Mac Album https://t.co/GvmPq5cg7Y @UltClassicRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejonas @billboard @RepublicRecords @RyanTedder @FrankDukes @Philymack https://t.co/WI9h1EuuCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week ago, I was in Fort Collins visiting Colorado State University. I visited it last Friday for the Theatre Visi… https://t.co/RZaEIHuuu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started singing and dancing in a restaurant in my dream but it’s totally something I’d do😂🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musingsofmegan Can’t believe he paid with a check. What was he thinking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker said Kim listened to Cohen's testimony and was like "nah, nevermind" and that's why him and Trump couldn't reach a deal 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated Australia Day a little late and a little too far east(?) today in World Geography!! Fairy Toast, collabo… https://t.co/dtrzZBj8Ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiCkYGoN07 you are the beautiful @ Fox Riverside Theater Foundation https://t.co/T9sY6XfjRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one gives a shit that Lebron passed MJ on the scoring list. Continue the game please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t you taken enough from me? Won’t you torture someone else’s sleep?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinLawson_ @nick_jimenez06 Right ? I don't understand. Like if I acted like this my ass would of been red from the ass beat I'll get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can’t wear my Stoney sweatshirt in public then sorry idk if I can do this whole teacher thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg sometimes in my dreams, i run away from harm and i always end up running down stairs just like this 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingersSnapps Very his son sent a pic in he has that look and they called him he’s in background but in one scene… https://t.co/d4LvsLAU3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else wonder if Lt. Kennedy and Williamson are being pranked by LivePD fans?? #LivePD #LivePDNation #chaps… https://t.co/yYEucDo4u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will eat fast food all the time, drink soda like it’s water, get drunk every night, and then talk down on marijuana]]></document><document><![CDATA[i forgot how much it sticks to be a server during tax season.. IF YOU CANT TIP DONT EAT OUT YOU SHITTY ASS PPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop Calling Them Soft Skills; They're Essential Skills https://t.co/BMhFpZeX9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up extremely sick today but somehow I managed to get out of bed and to work. Knocking this bill out with 2 ear infections 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hobbies include: regularly sitting in my car eating Dunkin’ Donuts in a @tjmaxx parking lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come over and enjoy the happiest #HappyHour in Philadelphia. $5 sips and bites, Sun-Fri from 5-7 pm. ¡Salud! 🍹 @ Ti… https://t.co/8Swgy5gM8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[He might know more about his faith but his personal faith in Christ could be shallower than that of a person who ha… https://t.co/tvKkJwDOAX]]></document></documents></author>