<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChipReiderson EL CHAPPO IS GOING TO FUCK UP THAT MAN IN THE WHITE HOUSE IF HE DON'T LEAVE HIM ALONE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelelacroix Yeah I respect him for having that mindset, but it is something that should be asked of both parent… https://t.co/nC2GERUO5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's unfortunate about this is that "MAGA" itself IS tens of millions of people making dangerous racist comments… https://t.co/u2vrb6WCd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t agree more. Braves won’t truly be relevant again until we have an owner who prioritizes winning over linin… https://t.co/ZCqzqnUHTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[halftime in Iowa City @CityHighSports lead @bettathletic 25-15 Aubrey Joens 14 pts. Allie Brownson 5 pts for the Bu… https://t.co/X1BiWkeoqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule I don’t really know what that means, but I’m pretty certain it involves his anus and not Uranus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite falling behind early in the second half Battle Mountain rallied to tie the game with Incline HS at the half… https://t.co/kkWVMgM3p0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My interview on Pet Fashion for World News Now on the ABC network with @WillGanss. I'm with model laurennycity  and… https://t.co/eb587PMB7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you spend 12 hours a day doing work you hate, at some point it doesn’t matter what your paycheck says”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosvives @traslaperla @FUCAIcolombia Antes de hacer una pregunta con sarcasmos!!! Hay q informarse del tema par… https://t.co/TELVxI9Thb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t spell Bourbon without #BBN @ Woodford Reserve https://t.co/86nzVLQgDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn more about phragmites including tips on what to do if you find them on your property (and just as important,… https://t.co/vgdzC0V8eO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely a mask type of night. Been getting oily again which is nice but I'm not digging the pores that come with… https://t.co/nT7Lmfopc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anntensity I’m on the same schedule my wife’s not and she is being brutal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días... Salmos  18:3 Invocaré á Jehová, digno de ser alabado, Y seré salvo de mis enemigos... DIOS los bendi… https://t.co/Q970AOz4kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the HOTTEST MIXTAPES FEATURING SOME OF THE HOTTEST INDIE ARTISTS IS AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW ON SPINRILLA!! Go su… https://t.co/vcGYC3PgMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly proud of my wife and the work she does for the disabled and elderly. Thank you for the incredibly kind w… https://t.co/6VwZvhXW9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derSchepp @rachelandrew I expect exclusions to come before regions and appreciate that feedback]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadbaddy What day was the Holy Spirit poured out/ or come down? The Day or fulfillment of Pentecost?  It was a Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majornelson @geekmadedesigns NICE. Great idea. Does it come with some kind of clear cover? I leave my control out… https://t.co/HKpkbqOQOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Scottsdale Motorsports Gathering https://t.co/auLg6jHBsH. Going to stretch the CLS550’s legs and go out there… https://t.co/8nGjxeuL10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty excited to work with elevenspeedcoffee. Roasted locally in Victoria BC, these are the beans that fuel many o… https://t.co/iUcdkpuNaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluedevilslive Congrats!!!!  We are guaranteed to have an M7 girls Richmond finalist.  Best of luck vs Radford in… https://t.co/sRsdBQMblA]]></document><document><![CDATA[missing this a little extra this year. love and miss my sweet momma, happy valentine’s day❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re getting our first Cole feature of 2019 tonight ladies and gentlemen]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @LVMPD is releasing a "cold case" plan today. Why do i expect wide spread "totally constitutional" DNA gathering?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is an update on @Nike stock price since the blow-out, @darrenrovell ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And finally R. Kelly charged in Cook County with aggravated criminal sexual abuse https://t.co/vY3YpiPCEN via @suntimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarcinogenG @matthewschmitz @PatriotGeorgia @EllenPage https://t.co/9Df9BZbC1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattkoonmusic it’s great to hear you talk about road trips with your son! That’s probably what is miss the most from my dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me know when you see it 😉  Tim Apple Jeff Amazon Elon Tesla Mark Facebook Jack Twitter 🤔 Jack Square CRAIG GIGW… https://t.co/SdBU3tzrmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica So being a serial lying heartless wench must age you fast]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just called to suggest that instead of WaPo counting every time Trump tells a lie that USA Today should take… https://t.co/2EiX1JBvtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it is time to harvest, do not wait until the crops go bad to realize what you could have had because you wanted… https://t.co/6LgYLeTa9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_YaHWeH_ @Yongyuan0162 @HMinistries8 @DulleyTopBooks @elliesangelwing @GodsGrace57 @gwen1173 @radioshowccc @kristia101 Amen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reflog_18 Gosh I hope John still has that twinkle in his eye/mouth after week 6. https://t.co/63FFoVWGnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wrote about Lent, check it out. If you like it please like/RT/share   https://t.co/yCWRMVI1SM]]></document><document><![CDATA[16,069 is a new attendance  record for the Cubs today . This is also a Cactus League record attendance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyknicks vs @spurs in the famous @TheGarden 🏀 😊 https://t.co/8qV4f79kUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear ad targeting systems: I have made decisions and purchased both new pants and shoes so please stop targeting me… https://t.co/2Qb2ya6uQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem is these fans think players are their pets . Players don't have to take this bullshit. I have gone to m… https://t.co/lHJqg3EHgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCarlanGay 😂  Tell your boy Rowan to teach his son how to shoot free throws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Denver, CO, check out this job: https://t.co/mAacJpoDCV #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanieBrian @gmcclain61 @MDeFranks I meant I would scratch Ritchie to make room for Cogs, I used "bump" in a different context]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is half right. 🤣@fuzemaster @amy_mcclure08 @GoldenKnights @TBLightning https://t.co/W1ZlvKwfJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish there was a actual restart mission choose in life just like video games. #wishfulthinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallascpa @Harrisoncole08 @DiscountTire It’s hard to stay connected to the family, keep up healthy grades, compete… https://t.co/3CifYWI1gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PioneerBoston You are advocating for better history education while once again sidestepping nuanced history discus… https://t.co/q25kca3r8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tidal breathing is a better answer #CSD1080go   Is speech breathing another term for quiet breathing? #csd1080go (via @KDelatore)]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick 13-0 run gives Nokomis a 54-53 lead with 332 to play. #sjrpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has a funny way to put you on the right path. Pay attention to the signs #motivation #dreams #goals… https://t.co/z2bQUsbujW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @RepDebDingell @kasie We grew up with guns in our home. NONE of us were scared of an inanimate object! @NRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesJordan24 That was my second choice, something about the pickaxe though is 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has no chance of a Nobel Prize. Scum bag traitor liar award sure bet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than 24 hours after Cohens testimony and Trumps disastrous kowtow to KJU, if you're a republican going to chec… https://t.co/SWRIK0FnMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you do, whether in word or deed, do it all in the name of the Lord Jesus, giving thanks to God. Colossians 3:17]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be live on the radio at 6pm eastern playing the band w @livefromhereapm on @npr ! Listen in or watch on YouTub… https://t.co/ZAwdSZ9glp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trent Open in Peterborough @TrentUDurham ; Classes Continuing as Scheduled. Always decide if travel is safe for you… https://t.co/5BR5qQcMEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @KFCBarstool this had to be one of the best fucking articles you’ve had in years. I hate poop gun girl so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncamitzi @SenMikeLee Dem’s Believe abortion is a form of birth control! https://t.co/Y4ho8BMRE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It will be available on demand @HBO through April 9 #AfterNeverland #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[but who do you know that stops that long,  to help another carry on.  The world moves fast and it would rather pass… https://t.co/t36TEcv167]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic is crawling in #WakeCounty on I-40 WB between Hwy 1 - Exit 293 and Cary Towne Blvd - Exit 291, wreck in t... https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNocco Wondered what happened to Murph from the old 76 Station commercials.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to experience Project Based Learning with an authentic audience at the @DowntownTucson Partnership.… https://t.co/NGFwRokPWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's crazy how God blinds a man for something so little when he opens the eyes tells you how dumb you really are,,,… https://t.co/FgS49xQdCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t seen anything this disrespectful since the Harden step back on Wesley Johnson 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/DoOMk5X7ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prior to 1913, most Americans owned clear, allodial title to property, free and clear of any liens or mortgages unt… https://t.co/tcGfoGK1IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AddANameToASongTitle  Uncle Albert.. let him in https://t.co/9YCAWkmKnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[this weekend w my fave people was greattttttt, miss y’all already 😭💕😘  @maxxboo26_cj 🥰  @villanuevalinds 👯‍♀️… https://t.co/PBlgevbElx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tacky_Nerd @thesillybuddha @G0nFreaks @Demthagod @Oh_Watup Twitter orgy part 2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I watch basketball to see what sets teams run and what defensive schemes the other uses to stop it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerRamsbottom @GobAbiertoBOL @AOC @RepAOC Worry about England you twat, you have enough problems]]></document><document><![CDATA[The casting for this season of #TheWalkingDead has not disappointed. Ryan Hurst (@RamboDonkeyKong) is absolutely pe… https://t.co/Zc7alzY28N]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry to hear of the passing of @sambassartist rest in peace my friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @KenMatthews Mitch, saying the IRS does not know how to do their job? Hell when I worked a day job and… https://t.co/mZZqmVDlSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdruva41 @charliekirk11 Because Charlie Kirk has a detachment from truth. He wants to follow in the footsteps of C… https://t.co/UKLgbiZPxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Purisusi @SenRubioPress @MarioDB @USAmbOAS No, Susana... nuestro contacto directo es de Bogotá... ¡Dios les ayude!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahDillingham @weatherchannel Yes you may use it.  I was downtown for a couple hours after the tornado hit. The… https://t.co/PEqd7vSIKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaraEOspinaG COMO EL MUNDO HA CAMBIADO ENTONCES QUE VAYAN CALATOS AL COLEGIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NDBlackKnightFB @Maddoxjohnson42 @NBS_XCIX Congrats @Maddoxjohnson42 @NBS_XCIX.... well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got asked earlier today why my attitude changed and I answered because I'm sick and tired on not being the best p… https://t.co/ZvKT3hxtZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you shouted You Blew it on ATH. I heard a great heckling booming voice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RP💯 🔂 #love #defy #nyc #westchester #rp #hustlers #friday #2019 #instaquote https://t.co/tfmzrVgnn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaF3mm3Nikita 1st clue this person is not a Democrat... the inability to know when to use a noun vs. an adjective!… https://t.co/pphOzBBJPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was these made in recorded in late 2013 to early 2014? I remember when Mac Miller told his fans about you that's ho… https://t.co/txu8GKeivB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a third question: how should social media platforms treat Russian bots and trolls with respect to… https://t.co/LvyLBZ5dN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANTIGOPMVMT Coming from the Carolinas, it's not surprising.  That's where Lindsey Bo Peep farts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoedeehoe As Kapernick will learn its generational, I'm sure he thought another team would pick him up, nope, civi… https://t.co/ZoQJf3xYOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snagbuddy @ceylon_ger Yeah🤔 I guess it does. Samus's parents getting killed by Ridley hence their rivalry, Krystal… https://t.co/FKyfWdjRLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmacfsu24 I want my money back if Lucha House Party shows up tonight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes please. Hate to ask for potential jinx reasons, but Tom Jones is thriving &amp; healthy, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeCalderon @BenitoGuerra @RallyMexico ...y le brindó a López Obrador su triunfo !]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @EagleParkBeer for just being nominated for one of the 10 best new breweries by USAToday, now we need t… https://t.co/NXaRswX5Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Occasionally - not often - my views overlap with those of David Brooks. He wrote this week: "Were Republican House… https://t.co/3v1IaCNpfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You #Biden #Obama #Clinton #McCabe #Rosenstein #Podesta #Mueller Scary Frighteningly Horrible @DFBHarvard]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d post a screenshot of @CoachTurn24 text reply to my question about their win tonight...but....children might be… https://t.co/BA0fkM5cQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Contino @_Salotti @JoeFortunatoBSB @BlueSeatBlogs Should've named him Gudas. So many cheap shots when I've wal… https://t.co/4fNk67oJ6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsuaristocrat @aobdrprof @profjenksaob tsudrumline tsufantastic4 aobnation @TnStateVB tsutigersmbb tsucheer @ Tenn… https://t.co/9OUfVi76ir]]></document></documents></author>