<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Love reconnecting with friends I haven’t seen in a while!! #fridaynightfun @ Texas https://t.co/LLPkdZCqLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Did you hear @MalcolmNance discuss how the whole antivax thing is 100% a Russian misinformation campai… https://t.co/1Xnug4aiVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is a blameless life?  Citizens get as much “justice” as they can afford.   Former Trump campaign chair Paul Ma… https://t.co/tV5Tmq4jd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend I'm "the public"? That's cold man. I'm a highly individualized person. I like my pancakes just so. Respect!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesssss! Miss Junior Queens link up 👏🏾! UAPB y’all better vote Jade West as your next Miss UAPB 💛 #Jade4MissUAPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[To WORSHIP YOU That’s What I Was Created To Do To Die To Self For YOU I Was Created To Do To BLESS Your HOLY NAME I… https://t.co/b8JrVVFECp]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Webeen #GalaViña19  #PartyChilensisFtGala2019 https://t.co/j8KHRbh0CP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How many did you pay for? Maybe @MichaelCohen212 will spill the beans Wednesday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl is FaceTiming her friend who couldn’t be at the @ASITISofficial show during this song that is clearly sup… https://t.co/1ZYmwKyoCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The parents say they want impartial engineers to find any sources of #mold.” https://t.co/AxE6LnDAsG #blackmold… https://t.co/6KlhkknZ7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino social media gets people in a uproar because if you ain't like them u ain't right!  Live and let live.  W… https://t.co/gRyJWCE3qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shirlenevibes #dailyinspiration #dailyquotes #quoteoftheday #quotestagram #life #duality #instagram #instamood… https://t.co/KZjkrJY4dG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah us UM people in the Lansing area often seek refuge amongst the more friendly Brighton crowd. #GoBlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to move out this awful state that doesn’t prioritize public education and wants to take away from our te… https://t.co/MCt7UmbVCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[India Love seems like the kind of girl who’s down for a threesome with you &amp; your man 😏😍🤤👅]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day I was thinking of white dick and I was just so high and I felt like I could see it in my face and I almost threw up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @myserenity69 @SpeakerPelosi Oh and Pence will definitely impeach him? Really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcpr what is with the overly large signature? Is he blind? brain damaged?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the lunchtime #BlackHistoryMonth celebration @Twitter, including an awesome menu and uplifting music/dancing… https://t.co/gMOCMoMBGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okey doke folks we’re getting started on Fifty Shades Darker. I won’t be changing the hashtag, because I’m lazy. #ElyssaWatchesFSOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait.. did @jamescharles delete the tweet he quoted from me..? Someone help me and tell me if you still see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing about chaos engineering from @SchillyVanilly &amp; @StudentOfAgile at #devopsmsp. https://t.co/xo85Tt5FtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol my camera roll in 7 months is gonna be filled with pictures of my baby and I'm excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lung cancer survivors are raising $$ for the research that has and WILL save their lives.  Thank you Emily, for bei… https://t.co/ZgE9A1rFm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP #JohnCandy, gone 25 years now! He was a funny funny man but I loved him in this sweet romantic comedy Only the… https://t.co/BEfCpwVNl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julesrprecious Will pray your insurance covers it.If not make arrangements to pay a little a… https://t.co/1uB2EqdZl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday, March 3, 2019 2:30 pm Communion Service  Spanish and English  - dual translations  @TheCOFChurch… https://t.co/auMCepvXeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took Denton on his first date !! 💛 @ Chuck E. Cheese’s https://t.co/sNcJFp9HKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAISnetwork How innovative and passionate teachers are paving the way for an exciting and inspiring future of our schools!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words can’t express how proud I am of @zachary922.  He works so hard keeping his grades up and to better himself of… https://t.co/upif2u4XPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished stitching some new pieces for Easter &amp; Spring Cards! What do you think? @ Niagara Falls, Ontario https://t.co/785kAwOk2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein They should be already. However there will still be those that will wear it proudly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkclove09 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It would be nice if you read something about our military procedures or other government items oth… https://t.co/aXEBZXJkYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your man doesn’t give you butterflies and orgasms, what is you doin baby?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalebJHill Chiiiiiile my biggest fear in life is getting pregnant when I’m not in a relationship. Like, OFFICIAL relationship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last, "Alleluia" before Lent begins! Happy 15 minutes til Ash Wednesday! https://t.co/td1cK2XmOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BestBuy Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/eqW8KW0dxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmeanswell Did you get one!?!? It’s amazing. I’ve never wanted a sweatshirt more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I choose precisionnutrition as my nutrition certification? It was the 1st platform that I found that resona… https://t.co/yMeozfme3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all think I’m kidding but the night in question I was legit crying over an Australian reality show that auto play… https://t.co/eU6c4UMRf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kick ass 3G class taught by the amazing jonnie_agresta!! 🏋️‍♀️🏃‍♀️🚣‍♀️  We loved your class, you and otfbayside!! M… https://t.co/2GiMCaXbR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recorriendo y recordando las vivencias desde un pueblecito lleno de artesanía y manualidades tan creativas como sin… https://t.co/WtgoE2wxMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanobles Non of the Democratic runners have a chance to beat Trump they are all wasting money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pablohidalgo if you want to head out and drink this for me I can save it. I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigvox @BillBubbaBussey Well, I just turned 50 last week, and I didn’t remember the jeopardy bit from last year.… https://t.co/849PHSfGmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know Minnie Mouse and friends come to visit every Sunday? 🍳 Join us Sundays at Letterpress for a… https://t.co/LT0VhGK04X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve heard the Harper will sign for 10 years, $310 million. That contract is too long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbrockenbrough Is this a thing? Like librarians search out "period" and "menstruation" and all things that allude,… https://t.co/R6J5mH97Ap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently taking a lush bath while pumping &amp; eating a 20 pack box of gushers. Livin my best life over here 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fundraising for the Decriminalize Psilocybin Initiative in #Denver. You can be part of the movement by donating… https://t.co/CW3adZJ7SQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one was actually injured in this learning experience..but everyone was highly engaged.#ACCLovesCTE https://t.co/PzuHsEiewE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP He was paid or threatened by the Deep State! He is a Rat &amp; Liar 🤥]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SOUP: the only good thing about this seemingly endless winter. Our current soup of the day is carrot-ginger with m… https://t.co/sy5K7PeArq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmhobsonschoice That meeting for tomorrow (Thursday) has been canceled.   The next meeting of Health and Family Se… https://t.co/zhv55VXUCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaLuizito @rosecooleredboy @MariaEd07812623 @GuilhermeBoulos A grana foi para aquele superávit primário,sistema fi… https://t.co/didpbXM6Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st baby!!! I am so proud of you &amp; all of your accomplishments! Live it up queen. Love you so much @imaleeexxxx 💕😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Goodyear #AZ  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/lU63WI6hWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s coming to Rumba Latina tomorrow night? 💞 Catch me in the drag show DC 💍 https://t.co/K6MbydHWmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hollyoaks I really miss Celine, Kim and now Tegan! They were all such amazayn, brilliam, extraordinharry, fabuloui… https://t.co/6LtKszjLlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas felicidades mi querido @tenorjcamarena !! Otro éxito más... y en mi estado natal! Abrazos y más éxitos.… https://t.co/vyjSb3OzMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re really stupid if you do 30 minutes of HIIT before leg day @MeganFalkey #subtweettomyself]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real...I feel we don't know her like that and I'd definitely love to! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep saying Alexa when I mean to say Siri and I just can’t believe we live in a time where I’m getting my servant robots names mixed up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 stay calm.  I wish I could pull up my comment to McSpockey.  even that didn't have as much informatio… https://t.co/9PQI1nohCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and Tea ☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/G1027BWEPk https://t.co/Tm2nLiCaKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna wish one last happy birthday to my absolute best friend @AntonettaNicaj!! Thank you for being my fourth sis… https://t.co/ngkhwytKEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnderSecArmy @ArmyHouston @USArmy Did I stop a heart attack? I’ve been very stressed, yesterday walking dogs I had… https://t.co/ZtmTTSkUoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BevFries @BreitbartNews Also learned his sister married to Geo Sorros son😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_cipressi You’re the best candidate. I’d like to see you in my office this week ;) let’s talk 😅😂🙃🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @NightShiftNews probably kidnapping American girls and sending there😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Savors’s Oscar Party. @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/aHSw0xiuJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnymuskoka Yup.. On top of 6" of ice. Its a stellar situation here in the "shitty"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes my heart fuller than knowing how much my friends missed me like damn I do matter somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got to cover the new york special olympics this weekend and it was an incredible experience that i’ll never forget. photos to come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertPicardo So I guess y'all in the States got Jared from Subway for a president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking love Kristina that bitch will forever be one of my best friends 💘 #highschoolbestie]]></document><document><![CDATA[They still ain't returned those wigs to the wig store on 54th and Crenshaw. And they need to buy clothes somewhere… https://t.co/rGlp0CdcLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccidentalCajun I told our project manager to let me know when he’s going home because I’m going home too. “It’ll… https://t.co/hIzMYzFjAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i guess i have “fuck kenzie’s feelings” tattooed on my forehead. i’m over these dumbass feelings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishSTFU9 Source: I binge read those threads alll the time. They're fascinating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the new @GhostAdventures I’m so pumped!!! #iaintafraidofnoghosts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to tell the people how nasty and unsettling this is the first 150 times you take it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GVartwork That would be great! Could we request an xxl and could pick it up late afternoon tomorrow- Saturday the 2nd at Kent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carbloading par excellence.   #50kmUltra #Belmonte50kmtrailrace #BlueRidgeMountains  #FatTuesday… https://t.co/uB9tQGzmmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarMKE1 @Darth_Farley @MilwaukeePolice @SURGontheWater @CarnevorMKE You can count on iHeartMedia. We will be there to support.  Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanted to take a 10 minute nap in my car in the parking lot at work this morning before going in, but i just HAD… https://t.co/PUxkMW8ZXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredibleCulk Hiding in plain sight. Expose them all. #pedophiles #satanic #pizzagate #pedogate #podestaemails #Hollywood #metoo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MShiningElk It does, but I am glad that he is being charged so maybe no one else tries this. Plenty of hate and abuse out there NOT MADE UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest workin woman in womens college basketball.   Bar none.  @JackieYoung3  #iwannabelikejackie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iamallwoman #iamallwomaninc  #iaaw #iaawinc  #iaawproject  #iamallwomanproject  #iamallwomanpreneur… https://t.co/JwUXBSJa9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babysitting and the kiddos need to lay down for naps soon. Honestly, EE needs a nap too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibleedeaglesgr1 @THEJeepMafia Good morning kind sir! Have a wonderful Sunday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be so surprised at how quickly the universe will move with you once you have decided. ✨💓 @ Los Angeles, Calif… https://t.co/xknKTLnQyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never been the hating type. It's room at the top for all of us to win. 🥊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a pair of haunted mansion ears on IG &amp; now I really want them 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lunch staff at my job gave me a beautiful baby gift...I appreciate them so much ❤️ @ Research Triangle Charter… https://t.co/wyIIo3KI7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at @Whataburger after work to smash some food before going to bed, and they gave me a #14 with no fries 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SquarespaceHelp - my website isn't loading. I was on it without issue 4 hrs ago though. Now images don't load, etc. https://t.co/LTsHIvCl4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandra Whitney posted a comment on #GoFundMe — Thank you all so much! Your financial and emotional support keep… https://t.co/JVwPGRo7em]]></document></documents></author>