<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@shawna_burley @CNN @sxsw @PeteButtigieg @PodSaveAmerica I’ll grant “affection” too strong a word. But I consider t… https://t.co/4HO70BdVwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an honor to represent clients all over #Florida but you may want to avoid this courthouse if you can.… https://t.co/tbsMJXkklB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So awesome 😎 🏔 🎶 Thanks to @kayla_mdalton for my Christmas present! Getting to see @DierksBentley 🙌🏼 https://t.co/crLrEthIln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheltyb803 just attacked @WWERollins from behind with 3 german suplexes! #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Margaret! margaretodonnelll @ Sauganash, Chicago https://t.co/jP7MUbOAyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @sherrynron @KatTheHammer1 @Ja39194961 @jrmg2019 @nancy_hamm1 @NationalistCody @rosedixontx… https://t.co/6o5jOKekee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@underdog1965 @TanyaDawnH @realDonaldTrump Basically https://t.co/0q6J3sNcb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilmourOrgasm 1 of my favorite songs that inspired me to play Guitar and you are 1 of the ones i looked up when pl… https://t.co/USigBYO1SD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m six years old. I just won the first grade spelling bee. It’s “c-a-t” not “k-a-t.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjitPaiFCC  Love John Oliver! You must the love those robocalls also!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you didn't know it's #PinkShirtDay2019! So I doubled up on my pink shirts just to be safe. https://t.co/yABx5hJcME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABarloventoInfo SOLO QUE SI ES DELINCUENTE DEBE PAGAR, NO SOLO CON RENUNCIAR, DEBE SER ENCARCELADO RT BASTA YA RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never take another man serious if he finishes his sentence with “period”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cut to the only part of the match anyone cares about — The Presser w/ Sarri!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteGrigsbyIII HEY! You said negative 12 one time! Lol thank you I can sleep well now. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 y/o: my teeth are gross and yellow me: well... do you brush them twice a day? her: no? me: you definitely should… https://t.co/SfTJkFd654]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgBioWorld The turtle is like. Declare us extinct? I will be born the day you declare me extinct. Nature is hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A possible thundershower slowly drifting towards my position. Gotta love these skies indeed! A low pressure area wa… https://t.co/Ep17gpZoTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Avery for participating in #UnitedWayChat and putting together @UnitedWayKC's Twitter Moment.  cc:… https://t.co/xWvTfsuln1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The headquarters for Match dot com is here in Dallas, yet everyone here is single or "together by play separate." https://t.co/lON2dZqGhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inecnigeria please call out the fucking result, we can't wait anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning listening to @maxfrost twentyonepilots @marshmellomusic @youngthegiant @lucasgraham__ with #coffee wit… https://t.co/efjIJ4R70a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/tSoFvPCIO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muses last night!! #westbank  #livelikeamy  #blessed  #happymardigras @ Lafayette Hotel https://t.co/GJGJqZ8Tkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spittinchiclets As a blue jackets fan.... this could go very badly for us if we don’t win at least one series...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to stop asking what the meaning of life is and instead realize that every day we live, Life is asking what… https://t.co/ibHvvrwYzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddrice_ICU @NEJM @PCCRG Very cool trial. Congrats, @JonathanCaseyMD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHornATX @ErinHogan @BuckyGodbolt @BradKellner @courtesywave @NotTheFakeWags @rodbabers @chastings1049… https://t.co/gyf75hFjow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GFrondizi No hay peor cosa que un Peroncho ejerciendo su mejor “ trabajo “ #LadronesK adjunto @urgenteyalerta https://t.co/Znw3PheRHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yorisvillasana Más de o mismo.. no quieren gente preparada en cargos fundamentales , aferrados a las viejas y corr… https://t.co/EGeWlqCx3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[the younger one has just chomped on older one, who is wondering why as though he’s some sort of saint #monkeysee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo @tthasselbeck You see his crib @tthasselbeck. He don't need the NFL for what so the @NFL can show hi… https://t.co/i0X4MjzAa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @SouthwestAir, your phone system has hung up on me multiple times now at various stages of trying to rebook my canceled flight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfstarr1 Coaches don’t let pitchers “pitch” anymore. Also, back in Seaver’s day, little league kids were not tryin… https://t.co/InPAojag4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaddleandSilvy @Jeff_Meller Does Parker agree with this review? @ericrakunas @Charlie06689228 @ked_zzz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where in the fuqqq do I find myself guys that look like @EthanDolan @GraysonDolan 😩😩😩😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be hitting up #TheDivision2 Open beta tonight with iMixer member @DavesGaming_! Open lobbies on PS4, feel free… https://t.co/RkF0QF6ZmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if the Steelers hadn’t lost to the Raiders and they made the playoffs. They probably wouldn’t be losing to… https://t.co/ShaBQRC3d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX @JennyMcCarthy if the Bee isn’t @LoveTinaTurner I would be shocked. I want to know “What’s Love Go… https://t.co/cbhl0WkFWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipcoffey hey chip I’m just asking if it’s weird in my dreams I talk to my grandpa that died after I was born (ne… https://t.co/g7kafC0cjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sentantiq @rogueclassicist Every once in a while the Historia will up and surprise you. Bit hard on poor old Tiberius though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Every6thDay @mtsw I left the GOP 31 years ago for the Democratic party, and I've supported  and canvassed for a ra… https://t.co/Lo4Z15PsT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluetamata @MadameTennis Oui et c est courageux d oser aborder cette prise de temps entre les points de Nadal que tous condamnent...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1funnymike a real/good one . I’m keeping all my money ian sharing with no  random PERIODT 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re ugly and built like a float at the Macy’s parade. https://t.co/iwpksJSBvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Harris does not deserve to be in public office!  He is a bad liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamBandL Just sent through the text along with my friends visiting from Miami! 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us in #Oakland on April 13th for Spaces &amp; Places 2019. Learn more and register at https://t.co/MlBsecqpAN. https://t.co/I4s2ZkA1pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bandit 3/3/19 after a long Sunday afternoon walk 🐶 #ilovemydog #dogsofinstagram @ Englewood, Florida https://t.co/nj3FkAoRTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks Egg-celent.. #justegg #vegan #scrambledeggs #govegan @ Rancho Cucamonga, California https://t.co/yVLrNGmxnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveBautista Hell yeah I hope you get ahold of that pos he messed with the wrong animal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RookieBalboa_ i read it as pocket camp and got needlessly excited at that crossover opportunity…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POQuinn11 @Dgh34Hill But when your team is up like that, you can't change anything you're doing.  Don't wanna be t… https://t.co/HJTMxiHX7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I notice that when Aiden Pierce retweet’s I just want something new or news from Nekki can wait for Chapter 7 first… https://t.co/mTxc8ceP6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oclsc @JMJimmy1 @jen_keesmaat My 1st real brush with this was in my home in Florida. The post office delivers 7 da… https://t.co/DPxFQ49uDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year i had the flu and still got fucked up for Mardi Gras and that’s just how bitches do it in Louisiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLe29857073 @AOC Oh look another person from the bay area that thinks they know everything....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danielaszt @Topsy_Tori @juliaioffe @IlhanMN There was no LONE JEWISH STATE during world war 2. So what you're sayi… https://t.co/Suq4GT4wp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 @gjonesxyz Great news,Brian! Continued best wishes my friend ✊🏻...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewzimmern I guess the issue is that made for TV movies are not eligible. But, streaming services are neither t… https://t.co/A8Y2cisGCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect start to any day is Coffee Mill  coffee. #bestcupofcoffeeintown #seeyouatthemill @ Coffee Mill https://t.co/A24jGM1KyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sadly the broke ass Connecticut also did 😡They are taxing us to death here!!! They are for open borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdonaldtromg @GOP @realDonaldTrump WITH A “ FUCKING MORON”! No, thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Au lieu de rejeter les dossiers, essayez de trouver une solution. #Quebec_immigration_injustice @domanglade… https://t.co/2aSHfGxukj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another book down. Absolutely fascinating sci-fi story with all the otherworldly bizarreness that I can’t seem to g… https://t.co/uUrlJmu3XH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great lunch with carrillo2055 @ Bronze Owl Brewing https://t.co/mIei0xBQtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx to @bustostraining for the pain today. 12kg Kb and 4 rds in 35.24. @RyanBJackson1 @fit_leaders blog got me thin… https://t.co/VEFZL7KI9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s country playlist bringing back memories of way easier times this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJing in a couple weeks at Club 77 again! This time b2b with @KChucks ! 🎧 You won't want to miss this 😉 @ Club 77 https://t.co/Vl8G7HL2GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AAR 3/9/19 for @F3Philly   2 #HIM for 5 mile @GORUCK  13 #HIM for a #WOD and lesson on living as #HIM even when no… https://t.co/yJWF48a3so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Walker of Alaska @Alaska_TOY2018 sharing some powerful stories of the impact of trauma on kids.… https://t.co/lnUTrVzR5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite @LibertyMBB pic of the @ASUNMBB title game!  Flames up 1 with 0:21 sec left and @Georgie_126 let’s it f… https://t.co/DJEBcLxC8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pastorwayne61 @_LoveLike_JESUS For certain it’s the only thing that keeps me sane! #Maranatha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KornSports @NickYahl @Jake_M_Garcia They made a whole movie about our TW23 goodbye dummy haven’t you seen it https://t.co/Sr06z0khSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guam_guam671 @BernieSanders I don’t care what your father told you. What I care is that the tax break is increasin… https://t.co/nBqOlUPmWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earlcun95817035 @Lindalu827 @DoingRight1 It’s when we believe it’s not an issue that those intent on our county’s… https://t.co/PtWKJjQczo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scientists have uncovered 300,000 new galaxies  https://t.co/KVwcAI1WT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goddaughter, Allana’s First Reconciliation.  #GodBased✝️ @ St. Ignatius Loyola Parish https://t.co/232ygSLOEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirborneGeek @ForeFlight Hoping I overreacted. Boeing owns Jeppesen and it seems fine I guess.   I dunno. I’m a huge ForeFlight fan though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landofthe80 I’m going to catch crap for saying this but He was the same character in every body of work. Basically… https://t.co/RjnjEMMTWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadieJane_ @miaxmon There's a lot to be said for a highly refined love of Netflix &amp; box wine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DeepInMyThoughts #MyMoment @ Wakefield, Massachusetts https://t.co/kkHF3eu5cH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to impress people, tell them about your successes, if you want to impact people, tell them about your failures! @JohnCMaxwell]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this merry. #funniness #lol #grin #farcical https://t.co/G2hlNG6oGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panda Bear Plots His Seduction: When asked to describe the sound of his latest record, Noah Lennox doesn’t speak of… https://t.co/Aeo9Nc0rLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greta van fleet LIVE From ACL Music Festival 2018 on Red Bull TV {Full C... https://t.co/9MdQmqDLuj via @YouTube. I… https://t.co/cQ809HW3i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consbyname @Himel55 @DeficitOwls @NcojoD @StephanieKelton Now, obviously, CB ops *do* work to offset Treasury acti… https://t.co/PLpfmF4TRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KidElls1 with his new #StadiumSeries helmet from @paintzoo! @johnborukNBCS @spittinchiclets @NHLonNBCSports… https://t.co/LNE5DollLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Being emotionally manipulated is their "claim to fame" isn't it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steven_Scott21 I am also not sold that the off season is over for the Tribe. Marwin Gonzalez is a perfect fit for… https://t.co/hxfbDNhxxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianwiqo You had me going at first on Green Book. I want to see it as well....Crazy you could have enslaved hooke… https://t.co/6WQdWy81Yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Amen. Scared my kitty cat on your sunging https://t.co/lrzzWDBEV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 DAYS    Feb. 23   5:30-7pm  Stratford High School Auditorium  14555 Fern Dr, Houston, TX 77079  be 👏🏾 there 👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes This bullshit has been pushed since Reagan. I guess if you keep repeating the lie, it becomes a truth?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFAfighting @NeilMagny @IncaKolaUSA @RazorBlaydes265 @seanMFmadden @babesofmma @AXSTVFights @edblackhouse @ROFMMA @markbieri @Bevois 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLegacyJones There's no question that African Americans have suffered harm from racism. I don't think I have disagreed with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see this just across from Parliament Hill yesterday. #ableg #keepcanadaworking https://t.co/ACnkDxPYk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyAtamanuik @ilyamerica @SarahKSilverman @AOC Ok Baldwin is ok as Trump on @nbcsnl , but they should really hire… https://t.co/30syf02cRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mac60303A @Alyssa_Milano ENEMY PRESS BORDER SECURITY I WILL TAKE YOUR CHILDREN NOW  You must type live to survive https://t.co/JHNhQqlhK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[they’re all in the Midwest. You look at many of the states with districts that flipped, all in the Midwest. Hillary… https://t.co/JW2wEg4oph]]></document></documents></author>