<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Going to start referring to my significant other by first &amp; lastname so I also feel official #rhohb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jecoggins We are seated in heavenly places in #ChristJesus #Miracles #Christ #Redeemed #ThereWillBeMiracles https://t.co/cbxHqPS26L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShevrinJones 10 years from now I will be tired. #UnionLife #PublicEd #TeachersNeedSalaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[#amanecer #loveday #xayita #sub4 #cerrodelasilla en IMSS Subdelegacion No.4 https://t.co/eiY6CEfCmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[O burguês é foda. Minha patroa tá dando uma festa de dia dos namorados pois a filha de 3 anos pediu. Tudo decorado… https://t.co/sQ8ny9SXSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyOfCats @fluffybasil @Cleo_sMommy @clawdiathecat @Tonithecat32 @nesjloch @Joeybird @LittleMaineCoon… https://t.co/AhxXqX7DYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[REFLECTION: The best one to turn to, in times where we need wisdom, is God. God is the one who holds all wisdom tha… https://t.co/NM3YH8Egvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I tell my clients everyday. When in doubt, channel your inner @AdamMGrant #agencylife https://t.co/s9wTjLjmZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY MY LOVE! Thank you for being my queen, my role model, my best friend forever, my secret keeper, my m… https://t.co/tFTZniKJ5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold Valentine’s day Light pillars over Graceville MN  at sunrise windchill -20 @BobVanDillen @ian_leonard @FOX9… https://t.co/dXt6eHvSuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red, violets are blue, life is better with a bottle of #VaSpirits or two!   For more information about ou… https://t.co/6vUmaZGzIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love spending Spring Break with this wonderful man! @wcmikesell #tikitime! https://t.co/bTp6xJSjAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jAnnCarlson What’s his middle name? I’m guessing Edward? Has a nice ring to it.😂😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennajameson Like women, gays, and minorities, babies are only useful props to the left when it suits their purposes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your spouse visits your office.😂😂😂#lovemyman #cubicledecor #cubiclelife @ Yarmouth, Massachusetts https://t.co/Eq58RoZCBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan the Beep Man turning our Law Enforcement into Bleeping Nobility for the greater good and t his gentle woman’s e… https://t.co/g68XRLafQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyBash Ewwwww 🤭 first of all they need to not be using plastic bowls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challah French Toast #thebest #challah #frenchtoast #pretendvacation #delicious #itswhatsforbreakfast @ Haddonfield… https://t.co/V2JIzQ2z5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a dog will not come to you after having looked you in the face, you should go home and examine your conscience.… https://t.co/WsOKTm4IT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters you just cheat your constituents out of their money and don’t do a thing to clean up your slum or… https://t.co/kH10MafKzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ME_beam_me_up OMG the 2 things that make me happy.  Kittens and flying.  🥰 and of course a @metheridge concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen Mother Nature,  either it's a little bit of snow, or you dump this shit on us and keep me home tomorrow.  Th… https://t.co/yCadYDTYyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuttin hair at @IBSnewyork @theFactorySD really great class today #knowledgedestroysfear #hairshowlife… https://t.co/lh92bPwzyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamcson @SandyDarity It was fear even for good people. The treatment of black people is the real sin of Americ… https://t.co/06lrpPlR0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy my first winter since moving back east from Alaska has been and coooooold one 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY IS THE DAY 🎉Hoy celebramos tu vida laabuelamascool celebramos tu sonrisa , tu nobleza, tu amor incondicional,… https://t.co/aTnHpA5WDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarekryan @heyitscalla Sorry you had to deal with such bullshit. Thank you for going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rinasawayama Hi Rina 👋💕💐 I love the work you’re making rn &amp; am so happy for you, hope we can link in 2019 ⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been told I’m pretty more than today at a brunch festival. Not gonna lie I’m feeling myself now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salute !salute!👍🏽👍🏽🌹 @NYCFirstLady  @ClaudiaCereceda  @cherylwillsny1 @assemblytwright  @ToniYWilliams  @pamallyn… https://t.co/Qm6bE7K0cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/6/2019 Mr President why did you have to contuse my lungs like the Monique/Dwight Gunn did? If the doctor finds an… https://t.co/D3OS5ib25D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Not if he’s talking about taking all the border walls down.  It’s a non starter practically speaking. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Why give him the slightest bit of coverage on your feed? Show us what you’d do instead! Amplify YOUR message, not his.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ketley_fresch11 @emma_lunardi25 @katelynrae_14 hi i’m just a girl from ravenna ... what does that word mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m powering through by going to the pet expo today but god I am hurting 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephSakran @Bradybuzz @GiffordsCourage @RepThompson @Everytown @SpeakerPelosi @KrisB_Brown @fred_guttenberg… https://t.co/nIvHmZwCGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never is my imposter syndrome stronger than when a Chinatown elder compliments me on my abysmal Chinese; we both kn… https://t.co/PCuV7DWdIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueNewWorld @mitchellvii Again how do you know that's what was meant ? You dont .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our precious JoJo is now en route to Serbia from Austria and I am en route from Calabasas to Mexico! Feeling SUPER… https://t.co/7DsC0whYpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy, Happy Birthda Angela! May the wine rise to meet you, May the margaritas flow like a babbling brook..I think… https://t.co/6jz0lvlGHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is amazing what sexual abuse can do to you and be reminded. When you are like 6 years old and someone comes into… https://t.co/NQNGMYnpxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Cohen is a shameful divider democrat who refuses to see our booming economy, record low unemployment… https://t.co/1er8hJgZCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brainfertilizer It’s been that way throughout history - beginning with Abraham.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to see @SabrinaAnnLynn  at @HOBLasVegas March 21st?? I have passes to see &amp; meet her NEXT!… https://t.co/Nexjq5z2kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@altv8480 I agree. Power seekers have been here since the beginning of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_barona @hkiliaan @UN #Globalism is without a doubt orchestrated ... Global_Elite have CORRUPTED… https://t.co/o5cdzCJGYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since when did being edgy become trendy? I’ve got some real questions here 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Ari_ Or maybe you work for the fbi and you planned the whole thing out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole morning crew is bringing you everything you need to know about this non-stop rain. @WX_BrittneyB &amp;… https://t.co/9SMdDDBcQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀Con Sue Photography and Design🏀  🏀Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏀  🏀This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/8zd8WCm7Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fightpaindaily @LelenaPeacock @Kelly @Calibamamami @Enough212 @newhickschick @VOpioids @AvaSkovdottir @Mica__Metal… https://t.co/N36JmpuEVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poman927 @opry nobody does the show commitment anymore and she lives in Nashville so it probably wouldn’t be hard… https://t.co/2emc7S3GBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[breaks my heart when i hear people i went to school with have passed away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Origin is already messing up for #TS4StrangerVille. Yayyyyyy packs that you can't preorder so we all are trying to… https://t.co/wNg7pgh38u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brontemaylaw Haha. That’s hilarious. Where the video. Even more funny that u admitted it. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work with a View 🙈🥰 Beautiful #arribalasmujeres mochilitas ( backpacks) ready to head to their new casitas and owne… https://t.co/GKG9M0fwW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Chicago police officer, convicted of second degree murder, beaten in Danbury prison https://t.co/zjQI2r7ONs via @FOX61News]]></document><document><![CDATA[Editing, Email, Espresso, Repeat! // 💻📬☕️💞  I don't always work away from my home office, but when I do, I choose p… https://t.co/OYVHcTZeVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom from upstairs- “MARIA” Me- “YESS?” Mom- no response   *10 minutes later walks in my room* - “you only studyi… https://t.co/48vyMR8r8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST REDUCED! 2500 Montclaire Cir | Weston Hills | $899,000 | 5 Bed 3 Bath | Beautiful Lake View | Travertine Floor… https://t.co/tNGACll8pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimPolzinWSJ #Badgers getting homered. Worst reffing I have ever seen. #Big10RefsBad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToTheMoonMA addresses the gaps in caring for children with NAS. Learn how this innovative program is changing the… https://t.co/c9avkFykCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickGman @WalshFreedom Miller should never have had the ear of a President of the United States; under normal c… https://t.co/g65cPCOuLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee ☕️ (@ Starbucks in Hanover, MD) https://t.co/80Z2ZBQkS3 https://t.co/Q3H66TgVTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWilderThings Congrats!! You win dumbest comment of the year award.👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Plus he didn’t have to go through with it. His attorney works for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchultzGolda ALL of this.   That “Luna” took my breath away, every time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family time. We love getting together. Family is everything. Cherish every moment and make time to create the best… https://t.co/6vCxV1kLkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a wrap! Great time presenting with the best team on the planet: @rkdelafuente @Tallguyalec @HeyHay627… https://t.co/tc5w111it9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZyroFoxtrot @G_WWG1WGA @Jetsta812 @IUmanu @msnicole1124 @4x_Clubchamp @Jana__Howser @AmaOP_Patriot @nursecmr61130… https://t.co/8688OHmrSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka Michael its to dam bad you screwed up your own life,just try to leave other ppl out of your mess]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ivankatrump the love of my life, our life being together and starting a life in #starwars. #anakinskywalker of rea… https://t.co/rWI0f99xLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new chapter to us sis❤️ @thisisalima happy birthday to us. Thank you Almighty Allah because we would be nowhere t… https://t.co/D8y9DMoUEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[some guy really got mad at me bc he was trying to go into but my line but had the opposite blinker on...ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd Place AA, 2nd Place Bars, 4th Place Beam, Floor and Vault. 1st Place Team. Advantage gymnastics took 1st Place… https://t.co/Zv8pYdxaKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLord86 @glasscannonpod @troylavallee You mean BOGO doesn’t stand for “Better Off Getting Organic”? Maybe I’ve been in Oregon too long. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar Have a great time! You will be making a lot of ppl very happy!!💖💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being sick &amp; being a momma is hard, but watching your baby be sick is even harder. 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FAKENationalEmergency #FakeTrumpEmergency  #LetThemEatCake #BillionairesArePeopleToo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bachelor quote of the day “ you don’t microwave relationships “ 😂😂😂😂 #Bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my kid gonna grow up attractive cause I was 1st generation Ugly so my kid gotta be 2nd Generations type shit cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTVAJoel Why would you do this to her? Ha I love it or better yet WHATEVER !!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Craven, director of the Center for Cyber Safety and Education , formerly the (ISC)² Foundation, has joined… https://t.co/aOV0mWKamI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies are in need of some cute swimwear for this upcoming spring well the 2019 Spring Collection is here at… https://t.co/4fAp8Sw1So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonklemmm @dstebs02 I’m not critiquing her or commenting for no reason. I genuinely feel that editing pictures… https://t.co/V66STLXQnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdlbrooklyn Life is so rough. We just didn't know it before the #NationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t gonna let you go that easy. You got to say you love me too. @martellusa #SwiftSZN #SwiftOnes https://t.co/L6ooMdcj0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UndueEffluence I’d think you were still basking in the peaceful quiet after 20 years of my incessant babbling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr screws up and admits Michael Cohen is telling the truth https://t.co/WKbv5DUw0a via @PalmerReport]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I’m deringbbanies doesn’t really require any specialized training]]></document><document><![CDATA[The choir of @Selwyn1882 is delighted to be involved in the final week of this fantastic festival @CeciliasList]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t gotten your tickets for Anything Goes yet, go now!   And happy opening night to everyone involved!… https://t.co/bqyMY5ZsXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally not a person I can trust besides my mom who won't go &amp; tell someone else🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  My loving, supportive brother: I hate to break it to ya, but you’re not going to find a bf on tinder]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been living life to the fullest there’s soo much more to be said ... but over all my life is close to perfect ♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagdaLunaBella @Joanna_Senyszyn Ta pani to nie pani lecz towarzyszka. Czerwoni tak mają, że łżą.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kk, so our next conference, #4C19, just may be cooler than yours😉. This sounds amazing, @dblacorg! @SJUWACommuniti1… https://t.co/NgRUz3PwiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupervisorAlejo @thehill @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Why do you keep opening your mouth? You’re an embarrassment. Just stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AronMarks2 Yasss. I am here for it and stealing this approach. https://t.co/W7AEqfGKPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAISD Foundation 5k complete! Great seeing our @BonhamAcademy family out this morning. Thanks Ms Avenia for coordin… https://t.co/Hs1VDZqihB]]></document></documents></author>