<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just watched part of that R Kelly interview... Whoever prepped him for it did an awful job...the way he acted made… https://t.co/BOC1U017d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of the roles I have played during my acting journey. Will start filming projects this month.… https://t.co/kIOvfIZrc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Selling Scooby snacks and hearing aides #CapitolismBeDangerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scumbagking__ I be checking it out when I’m up there. But I’m just a tourist. But I see the intrigue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody born w an expiration date. Dont make excuses, live your life as you please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yes. More yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Leading with solar in California. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #Solar START HER… https://t.co/0YNAfN82Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheabsullivan @longhorndave A good cigar is nice every once in a while. And then three days later I remember why i… https://t.co/tqp24xi4uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCranley @fccincinnati @datdudeBPM @jbenedict1 @FCCTheBailey Somebody needs to buy our mayor a shirt with the current FCC logo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein why the flip flop? You seemed to care for American citizens then...why not now? #BuildTheWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sasha_de_sade @MissAvaBlack This is why I follow you on Twitter. To find out when the hot new vids drop! Will grab… https://t.co/2AaPlAikEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin the Trump supporter thinks he is the best President because he has set the most records! 💁‍♂️😳😂 Most resi… https://t.co/8D2WWBbcAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks ago it was @Idyllcreek for some snow. This past weekend it was @MarriottVacClub #ShadowRidge #PalmDesert… https://t.co/FOf5vIjJ56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khaynes001 We had @JamesLewisGIEpi out at aspen/snowmass two years ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTucsonDad I sometimes have nightmares where I show up to class naked and can’t leave]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝🔥🍭😍😘@latina https://t.co/slOkK5U7Uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now would be a good time to mention how many immigrant German communists were generals in the Union Army]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terribletileLLC @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Implying feeling were hurt; somehow? *shrug*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKellyPxP @espn I'm hoping to see @FDU_MBB on @espn 2 later this week. #uKnighted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaymondOAnders2 @Trumptweets2020 Well according to his MD, Dr. Dolittle, trump is obese.  So, there’s that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends are all trying to hook me up with a girl who’s whole personality is running 5ks. If I hear about a carb… https://t.co/dr4t0yw7Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we do this? Work our asses off for nothing?  Or do we stand?  David Bowie - Heroes https://t.co/JVGM7XYaRd via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffGordonWeb Time blurs as we get older Jeff. I'm 32 and they already feel like one long ass day. I guess with a… https://t.co/IFHLKfaz22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wastubbs @skywookie_0ne @Sahairah @JordanUhl Step 1: Get a gigantic mixing bowl, a half gallon of milk and a box o… https://t.co/03DQ6jPLAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Than Stubborn : The people that keep staying with Donald Trump are oblivious to the truth. They don't care abo… https://t.co/s0b8fe87Yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_millsey First time I saw R.E.M. ('83, Irvine Auditorium, Philly) Let's Active opened.     Great memory of a great show.  R.I.P.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bihhs get butthurt over a RT of another beautiful woman. Like bihhs don’t be out here calling other niggas cute whe… https://t.co/QHZyeCRUW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#elwapo #healthylife https://t.co/ZcZEMlfvCK Dream bigger. Do bigger. https://t.co/8VvKLBjxmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AztecaDeportes @ClubAmerica Recuerden que ellos no saben escribir y si tienen celular es robado así que como les p… https://t.co/y1H2BX0HDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what others did in 16. Go ahead, re-elect he who shall remain nameless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxsw hey  can i get a pulled pork sandwich  ready to ride the bull  #GiddyUp  -&gt; @sxsw + #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fika by Beer Tree Brew Co at @beertreebrew — https://t.co/lplinEqcWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffmasters1 3.essential. So Promising the public results with a tool like that would make better mental health co… https://t.co/KDIE64tFl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley A power grab by racist socialist anti-Semite anti-American douche bags.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best hockey talk in Pittsburgh. @MarkMaddenX It’s not close. It hasn’t been for...ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[An essay...may lead to a ﬁrm, unambiguous conclusion but probably, in my experience, will not. Nancy Mairs.… https://t.co/vWLs1dyo8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @trailmaster2213 @southernwayjim @Tweets4MAGA @TrumpOrBust2020 @MARINE_99ZULU @DaRealGrizzle… https://t.co/FCVUMjVKPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost 5 am and I have 3 hours left until the dispensary open 🙄 fuck Detroit drug dealers 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattpryorsongs Did you guys realize at the time that “Something to Write Home About” is a goddamn perfect album? #longtimefan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just added another interview in mid March! Looking forward to talking to Adrian Ferrari in a few weeks.… https://t.co/V1qaXvKZW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice night scenery of Hollywood, can’t wait to go back there soon. #throwbackthursday #throwback #hollywood… https://t.co/903tAPRifH]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Congress said absolutely no, they want to try again, what is wrong with the @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedude404 I liked doing EVERYTHING,coke will make you feel like a new a new man, problem is the 1st thing that ne… https://t.co/WMkKpnu414]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t need a #meteorologist when my #dog Ella let’s me know she is stressed by bad #weather https://t.co/8vLEUCbyJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the investigation was targeting a sex trafficking operation as opposed to ordinary prostitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @AMC_TV why do you show that you are showing Angels and Demons and I go on there and it’s not?🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bubble butt, bubble bubble bubble butt! 🍑🐶 #MyBFF #RescueDog #ServiceDogsOfInstagram #BigDogs #dogsofinstagram… https://t.co/3r5JhRNkSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idiot count. RT If you think former FBI bigwig McCabe is a patriot in trying to remove a duly elected POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jgoss1971 @SethCPayne Prolly that little lizard that runs like he’s on hot coals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cave_Art_Films @LuanaGoriss @michaeldickson 1,6 million Jews were murdered in the former Soviet Union by the Einsa… https://t.co/roPssTcEyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBob53 @ssgkrisgaming @BunkiePerkins Hey Will Wade paid players ok can I get threatened with a lawsuit too this is fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahargrove1116 @dirknotthinski @BleacherReport @questlove It's probably his son]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow It's Fox. Let's face it, Fox is a huge part of the propagandist media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo letztes Mal hier aufgestanden hahaha Koffer gepackt und ab geht es in die sonne 🤭 Ocala,Florida hehe und dann… https://t.co/UZKfYwdAtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcoguadalupi @chipkidd And thank you for creating such beautiful work 🤩 and those absolutely fun brushes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only I could afford to do this job for free. #nonprofitwork. #Rewarding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkwdcitizen @LakewoodOhio I agree she should not be blocking anyone for PG criticism on a city page.  Her personal page all day long...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSPortland 925ft,  45.23.24 N 122.16.36 W That’s in degrees.minutes.seconds https://t.co/eQsAuGR9ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another senseless and avoidable tragedy. Overturned candle and none working smoke detectors. we can and must… https://t.co/175bYTxgir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkaine Well-stated Mr. Senator. It’s been painful to see my home state go through this. But it provides an oppor… https://t.co/1luCiGkr2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[No entiendo cómo continúan las actividades deportivas en semejante caos de país... @CONMEBOL @Libertadores a cancel… https://t.co/GOd1djWJGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YankeeSource Injuries are part of it, that’s why the Tanks have stock piled arms in the minors. Hoping someone steps forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divorceddad420 I’m 6 foot but I’ve stood next to people who are 6 foot and I’m a bit over  But i got basketball pl… https://t.co/aq5FRYzoDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg Seems like an interesting reason to not meet with someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this case, I don’t think many people fully appreciate how much the financial crisis of 2008 did to undermine the… https://t.co/AUzPuYihks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that this isn’t the end for me. And I know that I have a strong future ahead and it will be thanks to your support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While it's a valiant effort, this is a terrible ad campaign. "Hey, why not pay for a bunch of 25 year old shit, as… https://t.co/zy8gTjJBCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They have no respect for your advice since you don’t live up to treaties or promises]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medpagetoday @andrewmorrisuk @AnnalsofIM Who paid for the study?  Ask the parents with autistic kids. You can try… https://t.co/OEF56zhQUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go HOG!! Let's get this to a million so we get this new video.   https://t.co/9ijkEXbyMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bouche1 @uaallamerica @UAFootball @AllAmericaGame @RocklinFootball @_UnderTheRadar_ @CoachDSage @HermEdwards… https://t.co/FpKLjobTC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD Planning for the Boppers forthcoming shark phobia and decades of therapy, I hope..?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin Kaepernick and NFL reach a deal https://t.co/Iinvohh2Jl via @TODAYshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReformedBroker at the risk of sounding contrarian / hot take / millennial / techy... he’s lost his fast ball. Owni… https://t.co/hOUqSfoPFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GAstarwarsfan Come on drop the green flag already. I'm ready to eat some wings @BWWings and watch the race. Let's go @MartinTruex_Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those with significant others, happy Valentine's Day. To the rest of us, discounted candy and chocolate tomorrow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just made me cry. Look at his tail. He is so happy. Speaks volumes of the energy she radiates 😇💕✨ @AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤘🏽💜 hows 19 feeling? I’m mad I didn’t really get to see you this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is @graniteuwnh's #UnitedWayChat Twitter Moment.  cc: #TeamGraniteUWNH: @TuftsPatrick @karrieeaton… https://t.co/Bn1DSxntpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday at 7:00pm get there to support the dukes !! Games at Proviso West H.S @YorkAthletics @vincedoran… https://t.co/8ZdbdJjxV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dolly Mac, aka Ashley Macias: The Official Leopard Of Chavez High School! #chavezhighschool #classof2005 😍🐺🐆🎬🎥🎱🎯🃏🎭… https://t.co/jQFXXsqIkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad. I really wish I had taken the opportunity to see him perform @LaughFactory_LB  earlier this month 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @Top_Sergeant @AP @thejointstaff @DeptofDefense I will defend you chief. I hope this news penetrates into… https://t.co/xJx9J6D0CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make love to me ....... like I was your first . like you never touched anyone else’s body .]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “#AI industry is a collective against inefficient decision making,” says Sankar Narayanan 'SN' of @fractalites.… https://t.co/V6E4ulVXA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Known this senior class for three years and can’t say enough about them. Defying the odds amidst NCAA sanctions to… https://t.co/ql563ai7Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to admit, I am not very risk adverse. For example, I have never had a flu shot in my life. Yep, living on th… https://t.co/VcVeTHlwOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KieranLalor @JrzyJoePiscopo @am970TheAnswer @WSJ @ChrisGibsonNY Kieran, you would be great!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobventrillo9 @DanGrazianoESPN @RapSheet @Chiefs Would be a lot of money for a box safety.  Would think cutting… https://t.co/rCWdAkbUx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always think about what happens after i go. Is there a life for me in heaven? Do i keep getting reincarnated and… https://t.co/yrt4IlX612]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just stepped outside for an invigorating breath of fresh snowy air where I live now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIDN’T POST ALOT OF #tbt BUT THIS WHOLE ALBUM STILL BANG IT WAS THAT TYME AROUND 1998 ALOT WAS GOING ON BUT THIS WA… https://t.co/ZffYFVOtcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Kraft's categorical denial that he "engaged in any illegal activity" certainly is at odds with the detective's… https://t.co/iNucBNn59I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Neither does getting called out on fabricating a hate crime you scumbag https://t.co/PWYHhFlXf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory How is that even possible? A loan, my ass... those grifters have no intention of paying it back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...planet is justifiably offended by your antics for one reason or another. Nobody cares what you think. Just quiet… https://t.co/nPjJjr5HG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tombellin @RealPressSecBot His vocabulary is limited. Someone should give him a thesaurus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen the brush stokes of “The Starry Night” by Vincent van Gogh? #painting #artist #chadharp #Moma /2 https://t.co/QuKCWuJ6gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump The Democrats are a one agenda platform, American values nowhere to be seen...but… https://t.co/DmAY6o3yvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody going pick him up I just hope it’s not the aints! Coming from a falcon fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!! I get to work with absolute rockstar teachers everyday @NBPSEagles . Check out @vinnygreco_  and @DawnCard3… https://t.co/tXCvzIoPsJ]]></document></documents></author>