<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[if @JakeWebber9 ours this in his video i will crack an egg in my head goodnight sisters #traphousememes]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really counter intuitive to sit 2ft away from someone in a single cubicle with the barriers. I’m trying to stu… https://t.co/CumX3SnvJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamwisp Tbh I thought your staff made you look even more badass. You were one of the best parts of my night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art // . . #okcmuseumofart #sculpture #anseladams #davechihuly #exploreokc #visitOKC @ Oklahoma City Museum of Art https://t.co/WWxVLJPNzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all marnigos! Live na po ang #POPSSSS7 now sa youtube! Tune in na.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetymoon @AhmedBaba_ Watch the whole clip not the edited one. She says she may vote for it and even offers one o… https://t.co/cf7VhAui7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love ur smile😊😊😊😊😊 @ Jazzy 159 Lounge &amp; Bar https://t.co/UjgSJc34cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo is there like a lost and found at smc this girl left her purple jacket in the cafeteria :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm loyal to the guys who were there when the hellcat was on meds.... You can still catch me in traffic like his du… https://t.co/2AfRcDJcM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have checked how much was left before I started this oh god https://t.co/djCwWWeaia]]></document><document><![CDATA[so our monday minute is about childhood sexual abuse and it’s kinda eating me alive to have to talk about it bc of… https://t.co/MasLAnAKRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class List for Friday, March 1, 2019: 5:00 am Wildcard Workout: Turbo Kick Round 88 WALK THRU with Cheryl E. Wood… https://t.co/0u7wqpseZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE THE WINE YOU’RE WITH 🥂 // Happy National Drink Wine Day 💛🥰 @ Nantucket, Massachusetts https://t.co/IN7POSWsKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSSuzanne @GC_Talent Thanks for sharing! This is what we need to see more of when it comes to the #GoC tweeting openly about our work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noon game between ND and Pitt will decide who GT faces as the #15 seed in the ACCT. Loser plays the Jackets who loc… https://t.co/CgY8yhDZAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClauCanchola Hay amiga no se, hay veces que digo “ si ahuevo no me bajaría” pero creo que papá Dios no se equivoca… https://t.co/7Ij66TAUS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing the destination sign . Passengers constantly ask where the 111 platform is. #ttc  #DoBetter  #111EastMall… https://t.co/dy7Kait6Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a cat or someone praying? Me, in bed trynna sleep with loud ass neighbors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas2DC1 @Tuff_Jon @rachelheldevans Have you witnessed this happening? How are you qualified to determine who is… https://t.co/waSIu4BDFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know why I prefer to be friends with a man first? Because I want to see how fair we fight in our first argument… https://t.co/zBhwsAJhr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backtothefarm @THR Johnny judges everyone. "I really do not like to be around folks our age who have kids. They ar… https://t.co/ienjHUTw1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's coming from outside in the sky some of it make them stop shooting the stuff into this house nuclear weapons https://t.co/9uZIuB0WM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukewhitmire1 @CoachMMoeller @MACUathletics @CoachJGamblin @CoachBRollins @CoachANero 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lory_farmer @PoliticalBee That is hilarious! 🤣🤣 This #POTUS has been the most wild ride ever!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinaBeLyke i need to do standup about dating in LA, like every other girl in LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @dlg_donna Anyone who listens to Cortez is out of their minds I am happy to know our President Trump h… https://t.co/NzBYun00v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonanRhodes Looks like Owensboro/Daviess County just barely got edged out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#4 on the court #1 in my heart💜 @ Alaska Airlines Arena at Hec Ed https://t.co/ZhTrqPMtcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnsenate having trouble putting safegaurds on giving money to the HMOs today. Accountability is a good thing guys. #mnleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m exhausted 😪 I’ve been wanting to get Starbucks for the past 2 days, but haven’t gotten the chance to because of how busy I am at work 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍒Jonerytime🍒Shimmer Glitter Eye Shadow Powder Palette Matte Eyeshadow Cosmetic Makeup https://t.co/hnnr8fQusN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out I can stream #Dynasties on BBC America and now I'm sucked into angrily tweeting things like "don't… https://t.co/RKWuWAQrfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soldelis_sade i literally was looking at the one shirt for you O k A y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tampa’s central business district had the 𝘭𝘰𝘸𝘦𝘴𝘵 𝘰𝘧𝘧𝘪𝘤𝘦 𝘷𝘢𝘤𝘢𝘯𝘤𝘺 𝘳𝘢𝘵𝘦 of any office market in the bay area at the en… https://t.co/Tqqx7Nbpuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julie Goldstein started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/ibf6JUOOJF #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @GabrielCrossXXX @KaydenGrayXXX @ItsMickeyTaylor @GrantRyanxxx @LincolnTunnelXX @Pup_Amp @KristoferWeston… https://t.co/48UjMe5TWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have been shadowbanned. I've put out 20 or more tweets, with zero likes or retweets.  #vaccines]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m officially all done my new school/ comic style version of wolverine. When my client told me that he really rela… https://t.co/QaXPhE5nCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talent is where you look for it. Would love to get reccos from my tribe @lmigno @jkhoey @Mr_McFly @wes_kao… https://t.co/ytjJdS3BCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my married friends and I send furtive snapchats of us with our eyes closed for no reason so here’s me with s… https://t.co/vyqtkMsy7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sierra8News @marlonawalker @AnthonyABC11 @NABJ @NABJSTUDENTS You’re welcome sweetie!! 🥰💞😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out #JakeCurran’s new single and put ya dancing shoes on. https://t.co/gFJ7x81SlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need help towing or pulling our rv to gridley from chico... Like asap please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump #MarALadass #McCabe #25thAmendmentNow #TrumpResignNow #TrumpFakeEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrShikharMisra @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM @MyEngland2016 @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe… https://t.co/ADBasBYtKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Don't they have genuine issues to deal with? This is beyond idiotic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieStepan yea! i’m super excited &amp; i really like it so far :3 i’m a legit barista now haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing Brianne! Through @Covergalls we’re working to remove the “non” from “non-traditional roles”, the… https://t.co/bTTrCJP76i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KB_CountryRadio btw thx for playing and tweeting honey bee the other night.👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to try my best to fill out this survey thread on the request of @CrazyPierre! https://t.co/hQBemfSLRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on all your accomplishments keep working get your game on]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be hearing shit about myself &amp; I just be like when tf I did that😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albthatdope Lmao . I would get the cheapest thing or pay myself. I don’t wanna look greedy 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posture Day 28: Airplane! ✈️  • • A darling of physical therapists and Pilates practitioners alike, airplane (aka “… https://t.co/3fzwp35xyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Go Cedar Hill Lady Longhorns Girls Powerlifting Team! Regionals here they come! #TTHL  #CHLonghorns… https://t.co/lsdziiqKHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #instagood #photooftheday #happy #beautiful #cute #like4like #followme #me #follow #summer #picoftheday… https://t.co/EnrXYFVs5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have discovered the worst karaoke singer ever.   And he lives in Houston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures in dog sitting day  4...... 🐶❤🐶  #dogsofinstagram #wvdogs #dogs @ Mingo, West Virginia https://t.co/LQAjjab3J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously confused how a toughie from the Bronx suddenly sounds like a Valley Girl, what am I missing here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#STEM fun with the boys and @DurhamPublicSch tonight https://t.co/Sbv0NJ8ma9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“FOLLOWERS ON SOCIAL NETWORKS” is the topic of the day!!   https://t.co/XstRyoDD0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethlinas My joke when people asked me why I was having children in my 40s was that they were my pattern recogniti… https://t.co/QOVuz1hXwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Michael and I are out in public together, I constantly find myself looking at him and saying “WHY CANT YOU BE NORMAL”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msjennimiller What sticks out the most is that this guy is just unable to tolerate your assessment of his movie.… https://t.co/TWEJU218ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you in #Cottonwood #AZ at @MainStageAZ Saturday night! #concert #show #rocknroll #music  https://t.co/kjxF9qYNzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FonziBonzi5SOS i was able to stand my ground everytime except once and they shoved themselves so aggressively betw… https://t.co/bieOP7MqES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @marcbona30 Remembering Joe Crea, longtime food critic at The Plain Dealer and https://t.co/NCUjtPq272 https://t.co/fJnfpjFRW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very interesting thread!  Thanks @spencerideas for getting the discussion going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Download–Conservatives in the Crosshairs https://t.co/G6EVMXeo9d via @YouTube.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliverdarcy @glennbeck @seanhannity Beck recently called Trump the last male role model]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon touchdown! Feels good to be back. #oregoncaliforniaborder #backhome #roadtrip2019 #winter2019 @ Oregon https://t.co/oDzGrH6z2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a magical night! Congratulations to my beautiful friend and her new husband. ❤️ https://t.co/vNEucuYJGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Said this multiple times but @tmcleod3 is easily one of my favorite founders. So inspirational. I’ve also never met… https://t.co/iPNvQHGfdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabrinaNYC1 @ericwilson A lot of plantations are open for tours here in the South, but in the past 10 or so years… https://t.co/CeQMbOvStf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonjsm No creo que sea tan exacto así jakakajjJ la fecundación demora y vaina, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[how y’all feel about Wendy’s Cheese sauce with Wendy’s nuggets ? https://t.co/oeLgQgKEyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedCali2020 @JohnAyr12294351 @oliverdarcy @glennbeck @seanhannity Impeccable reporting? Joined in the last few mon… https://t.co/GKw5PJ4Nq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noey1243 @JoshuaplaysPKMN @_ZoeTwoDots @trnrtips @PkmnMasterHolly @MYSTIC7 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this now (almost over, not sure if they'll re-air it). Pretty cool! The winner goes on to the national com… https://t.co/KoMlDdib6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s Trump Talk US topics: “We are so screwed. Finding hope when you know we are screwed. Our 1% chance on how t… https://t.co/PAx2Mz80gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't see the part where Mexico pays for it? #LiarInChief #FakeTrumpEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[having @SIRIUSXM radio gives me FOMO and stresses me out while I’m driving bc I always feel like I’m missing out on… https://t.co/Xn5NxnpSQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the point of wanting to use cinema lenses for everything now 😩.. regular lenses don’t cut it for me anymore 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este viernes en #VivalaviEnEl6 celebramos a las mujeres en su día junto a nuestras queridas @gina_pastor… https://t.co/h3IAH1ixtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobroba @D_TaPla @matsu_bomaYe @kk_kiosk @yesterdaydances @punkrockbgmouth @kyobashi_ @yuge43271471 https://t.co/yVAXgHM6PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CryptoCurator @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump I mean, if the Gestapo came knocking at your door, would you expect… https://t.co/9sP7Guuu2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton It’d be a failure just like all your attempts at governing!  Go. Away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can handle a lot but body aches are going to be the death of me...Come on 5 o'clock. https://t.co/li3Xjb25ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[We try to make other people look picture perfect, but when it comes to us we love any photo we can get together. It… https://t.co/NBAfCkEA7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not eating dinner tonight, thanks #grubhub for another stellar f*ck up! Oh and PS, your hold recordings are only escalating the situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffromthe6 Dinner first. The hotel room if you deem him worthy.   Or just go to the hotel room and order all the… https://t.co/6GR3KDXtKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 13 will be the world premiere of the new single @EnriqueIglesias recorded with the participation of the singe… https://t.co/40EyWGdKcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you give up on someone because their situation is temporarily not ideal, you don’t deserve them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[//Who doing what for splatfest? I'm more of a wizard type but I also like knights as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youth are removed from the war and don’t see the world as left or right, which is part of the reason @nayibbukele w… https://t.co/JcQRyHRWXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small practices want more practical EMR software,  #ehr #phr #hcsm #emrsystems  https://t.co/hdQkD0dg6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you live in Mass and they snow is coming 😳🙄 https://t.co/cKdCfTxwd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly can’t wait to go to the bahamas. Thats literally the only thing getting me through this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The smart ones know YOU are lying https://t.co/K7nambk0F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You usually don’t know when life changing thing happen, until after it happens... but with this I knew instantly]]></document></documents></author>