<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Pam_Bond_ @TNHTalk Why anyone who can think would hate Trump is beyond me, Pam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad my weekend is over... It was a good one.... https://t.co/t31XcSQ4kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing queens like Shangela and Miss Vanjie and Monique Heart look so stunning in rooted blonde wigs really makes m… https://t.co/WXgHJfv7p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been feeling really down :( Geico's clearly phasing out their little cockney lizard mascot :( 🦎😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 awesome miles for my long run of @hotchocolate15k training. Even with a little bit of snow falling and wind, the… https://t.co/xu6Jz3HO6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dnd quote of the day, " The man has no morals. I trust him completely." 😂😂😂😶😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmallGuyPromo13 @MattSerweKETV @RustyLord Amen... I'm sore and tired from my job...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either no one is in the house or that pooch chilling on the rug is the worst guard dog. #LivePD #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ver very boring movie Is Netflix's $25 Million-Plus Oscar Campaign for 'Roma' a Game Changer?. https://t.co/YdHzAlEf5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PookieDigi4Ever @DCZooWalks @CharmCityPanda @FamousBabiesC @VandyViking @aleftie @OrangutanRedd Thank you! Don’t y… https://t.co/4OVUjZ5EuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow How about the Lady is a Tramp. JK. My daughter used the song from the Wedding Singer for her 1st dance. Loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kidsartclasses #artclassesforkids #afterschoolartclasses #earlyartsnj #sonjaearlyarts #elmwoodparknj #december #20… https://t.co/CF7JodHPLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAPackerFan @WhoOrWhom I’m a professional editor, and I also believe “whomst among us” is a colloquial phrase with… https://t.co/mRR7dLItyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Bosslogic I could picture @jaredkeeso of @LetterkennyProb as Bruce Wayne/ #Batman .. couldn't you? https://t.co/y7fNtbEDkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟My Little Sunshine makes me so happy and proud! May the Lord bless you and keep you always!♥️ https://t.co/w8lI2E7Pup]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of stress my manager put me through today has me going crazyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we know YOU couldn’t get a Security Clearance. Do you think people forget, you’re a felon? 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[When an app looks great but then basic functionality doesn't work. #whyyyyy https://t.co/8ILVzyKB4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Florida 2. Five years  3. Bachelors and masters in Elementary Education, working on masters in Educational Leade… https://t.co/gbihH71sGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We circled up during Writing Workshop to finish our opinion essays. Writing is much more enjoyable when we share id… https://t.co/zFFEeiDT9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep way too early now I can’t fall back asleep and there’s no one awake to entertain me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time in #MetroExodus living out my ultimate fantasy: having a smoking habit.   I’ve never smoked a… https://t.co/IxyLoGjL18]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to @DVBBS for bringing the fuckin bass last night 🔥🔥 still can’t hear anything rn 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @tedcruz BUT HOW CAN THEY FO THAT---Only citizens can vote WHY CANT THEY BE STOPPED ❓I think the Re… https://t.co/bJQoM4oyCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyParton Awe!!!! He’s too cute!!!!! Love this @DollyParton !!!! It’s PRICELESS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Censored by #TedTurner-#Murdoch-#Bloomberg-#WREK-#WGST #Radio  Internet Only #News  #LouieDevotieNewton Pastor of… https://t.co/bAw9f6D0VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I need to clarify. I am followed by Billions. Including students. Hey guys. I am unique. We all are. But I am es… https://t.co/lstPajrzF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prediction: this the first of many @aafAPOLLOS touchdowns in San Antonio. #TakeAim Listen to… https://t.co/vBz4Vqwmyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year, it emerged that China was working on an underwater base that would be run by artificial intelligence and… https://t.co/kg1hOAJR3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@people So sickening. Let’s hope he gets out in gen population in jail. What kind of monster does this?  No excuse… https://t.co/f665Fv5v01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xowestleyxo @ArianaGrande PLEASE GOOOOO!! I told Joey to go too! Just say YOLO 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerelynForMD Look forward to tuning in! @mymcmedia team ROCKS! #MyWorkFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennBinis More than a few by that def.  what happens to school-based educators is they get pressured to “cover” co… https://t.co/k64Vw6jW69]]></document><document><![CDATA[molecular biology ruined me I saw this and got mad lmao .. if you know you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[ECAC Championship! Looking forward to watching the 4x8 run today at 6:05 pm! Good luck to Sophia, Grace, Allie and… https://t.co/5Nl5aorhzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes a lot to unlearn internalized misogyny and the notion that Black women are “fast” or promiscuous. YES, Bla… https://t.co/JYb9IVZwkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoePalmerJr @JLee418 @laura24fan @chevychevelle48 @DaleJr88FanNate @JudyJ31830202 @ToddTPrice24 @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/77QK9AKVV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Farmers and ranchers work their butts off to feed the world.  That’s not just sustainable but honorable” @BenSasse… https://t.co/A4baZAWkpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Well we have howard and The Donald show back! It was disgusting then and it still is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScoutDaddy70 @ProudResister Cut tax rate making U.S. competitive for businesses, (jobs.)  Ended forced health ins.… https://t.co/zz2IORrAZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[if God want me to wait on some real for 20 plus years then that’s what I’ll do 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changing up our view from ocean and sand to mats and medals!!! Congrats on a great season TJ!!!… https://t.co/wtquVFCZqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida Y ese es el presidente de México?  No sabe ni hablar, y mucho menos pensar.  Esto ya raya en la locura… https://t.co/8YmN8WTjiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why didn’t we see AB to the .@Raiders a long time ago. Seems so clear now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anneguitar @geoffgarin @Peggy55755993 @Jim_Jordan yeah - what is with him not wearing a jacket? Is it metaphor for… https://t.co/SvWkcBcvKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my bed frame is wack and likes to drop from time to time. Tonight right as I’m leaning over to turn off my lamp… https://t.co/uP3HLDZ0mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WomensHistoryMonth I’m going to take some time to reflect on and thank my amazing #Sheroes this month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Great! @LindseyGrahamSC Please subpoena Dir Comey and let him tell US everything. You’re an effing cowa… https://t.co/0P8fC5P242]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only men i will allow in my life are those with short king energy. tall men don't fucking talk to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gorgeous beast came up to me this weekend looking for all the pets  croadvineyards  #catsofinstagram… https://t.co/GFbQfgTdY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una noche única: Camila Cabello en el Rodeo de Houston❤️. #rodeohouston #camilacabello @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/UjzGtQorHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hurrihottie Yes it sounds like a horrible situation there. Very kind of you to contribute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I freakin love Edgar!! Always putting a smile on my face ❤️ got to love my Cholos]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unfortunate that Lemony Snicket is another year older! Lemony Snicket is a pen name for Daniel Handler! Happy… https://t.co/lNEvh3x8y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a heart pounding moment at 3:45 this morning I realized that I made a big mistake inputting the @girlscouts cook… https://t.co/ML0g7Fmhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dear Mr. President: Glad you are back in America, and safe. Blessed are the peace makers for they… https://t.co/NbxoOeSQ1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of February 18th #dool #days NBC spoilers  Rafe gets Jordan to open up about her recent trau… https://t.co/hbaJ1qXzUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community is my purpose! (@ The Naughty Greek in Saint Paul, MN) https://t.co/CUL4vt38Pp https://t.co/di8JfEKX7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ana_safavi @choo_ek And by failing to care for the health, well-being and safety of trainees, #MedEd imparts an un… https://t.co/Iayty030Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see a post about climate change I always skip over it I don’t feel like getting my heart broken on a Tuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s a butler gc for the girls in class of ‘23 named lady dawgs... i love🐶💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited for this coming weekend! I gotta do laundry and fold zines!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diane_artist @CREWcrew Absolutely that is THE question. What is Congress going to do about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as we got each other, we ain’t ever gonna loose 🌟 @ Guelph, Ontario https://t.co/5SjMnYFB7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am as impatient as you are, I was one of the earliest signees of the petition, this is driving me crazy....and I… https://t.co/vvj9OUICl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @vabeachteach! Excited to be on this adventure with you at the Virginia Council of Teachers of Mathematic… https://t.co/jqEt2KK3w4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here it is!! The big #Reveal! Thank you to everyone who helped me raise nearly $770 for the @stbaldricks foundation… https://t.co/hobt9oC8tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the gin's I've love before, who've traveled in and our my door and may I say I've had the best... I'm glad t… https://t.co/hRGA5xBcJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The replies to this are amazing. Trying to snicker quietly so I don’t wake up my favorite cuddly daughter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Win!! #keepbelieving #yougotthis Congrats! @HarbormenNews @HarbormenHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraleeB4real @MelodyThomasSco @DougDavidsonYR @CBSDaytime @YRInsider @YandR_CBS What a beautiful show. So many memories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reginaldedward3 I want him out of WH. His lack of thoughtful analysis on any issues pertaining to job, lack of con… https://t.co/lWkkBo5Hpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottaGetToBrett Sucks that they left it but at least someone reported it. You can never be too careful these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regarding #NWHL signing deadline: Hearing although Cailey Hutchison has practiced w/ the @Riveters ahead of Monday… https://t.co/ixMRZCPFgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad sent me a corgi stuffed animal and it matches my other one and I’ve never been happier to now have two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeAirRa_ Sure that may happen. But it’s important for ppl to know they can refuse consent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I give way too much of myself to the most ungrateful people ever. I will run y’all over with my car, y’all better appreciate me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You didn't think we were so great when we rallied n voted for Sen.Doug Jones...hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before meeting North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, Pres. Trump oversees big Vietnamese plane deal worth billions of do… https://t.co/cR2J4HbQ07]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for my mom she literally filled my cupboards with food so we wont be without when I'm out of here. Hoping to go home tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please read this thread - @realsabijoy says beautifully what I’ve been trying — unsuccessfully, to convey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBGordon nice meeting you last night. Let me know your size and I will be sure to get you the hoodie I was wea… https://t.co/GhtO9FiFB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Registrar/Hospital CMC" at Atrium Health, then look for people you mig… https://t.co/cK4GK4Cq8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacob Wohl: Remove Rep. Ilhan Omar from the House Foreign Affairs Committee - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/i4wxgYYo1G via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriscoffeytalk @JuliaManhattan @CentralParkNYC Of course, at that point, nobody knew there was going to be any co… https://t.co/jpvEsQb25n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Do you wake up every morning just full of nasty? Or does it take a minute?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to NYC this year. What Broadway shows are a must see right now? @BroadwayWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByLucha Last Sunday, I was on my way home, at the train station, decided 2 stop by Subway 2 get a sandwich, becaus… https://t.co/QCNfHFA9Q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody's suggesting anything.  Flat out saying she's the enemy.  Never should have gotten this far.  Needs to go ba… https://t.co/KIZoDs5ozN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalibuJones_ Yeah there’s some quote that’s like “motherfucka will hit the gym every day just to get shot by a skinny nigga like me” lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[just to let everyone know. ripley took my comforter off my bed and into the living room along with a stuffed animal… https://t.co/PYMg7k0cSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leslie, I did not mention anything about you or your tweet specifically. I referred to the word downgrade being an… https://t.co/9HAxinQ6cB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#feelingblue #meloncholy #depressionsucks @ Napa, California https://t.co/3f9A32ke0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCarlosPena Hi, it’s been forever miss you hope you &amp; the fam are doing well 😍 Tweet spree soon!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritesTruths Having worked in SV I think most nat'l politicians are clueless about the tech sector. At All. I'm al… https://t.co/7WSKe4OKYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #2K19NotWorthIt on @tyltsports. It has jumped the shark https://t.co/45i5v8lSwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[OUT OF ALL FUCKING NIGHTS, TONIGHT YOU JUST HAD TO BRING YOUR RAGEDY ASS OUT. Fuck you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bobandsueproductions celebrates the lost art of handwriting.. @fox29philly @ FOX 29 https://t.co/rgwvm3dUwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weather really makes me think “should I take another absence...I still got like 2 more “ 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[JM Family Enterprises is hiring in VA! Click the link in our bio to apply: Field Risk Specialist/Floorplan Auditor… https://t.co/kMoCiJPMeg]]></document></documents></author>