<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yes, little Indian maiden, think his lite it would have been if he were a DemocRAT? Asked the misfit… https://t.co/aDwrMzzh4X]]></document><document><![CDATA['Moment of reckoning': US cities burn recyclables after China bans imports  https://t.co/uT8uLrrlpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, Dan knows what he is doing. But, I believe Dan can still recruit even better! i.e. Jahquez Robinson committing… https://t.co/sV3z7IEknr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth0505 @JaedenDoran @HandsomeLatania @jenny1027 Good morning. I am blessed and nothing else matters. Family is wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Heart Health Month.  @JamesWilcoxKETV takes us through the steps with First Responders to keep you safe. @ketv #FirstNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BidnessSquare @OotyMac @knicksamillion @Nykterryandtray @LooseJointny @IanChisolm @Woodshed_1914 @AJTheManChild… https://t.co/8CIqyAcLMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @MrsHallScholars to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews - just cov… https://t.co/JRYg4Zp6o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UraniumSir The reason I say positive is because the more Uranium in that location, the more use for milling operat… https://t.co/4cEyyZy0vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[NY with 35-34 lead over Oak Hill. NY with ball coming out of timeout, 35.5 seconds left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay Riddle from Trinity Byrnes Rocking the #99Strong @ Crestwood High School https://t.co/HrUDPbkND6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gvazquez2012 What‽ you don’t mix it? Like who wants a mouthful of plain rice?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @AOC I think she must have done varsity debate at some time. 2nd Affirmative 5 minute round?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve made it to Tulsa Oklahoma for the Texas Society of Architects Design Conference. #becomeanarchitect… https://t.co/io9Hp7BROR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse America is already a country with a President "elected" following Russian interference to swing 80,000… https://t.co/wsIYEX8rLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmofxray Lmao idk how well that would go over but I gotta find a woman who’s down for me first 😂 if she’s dope like that, I’d do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is in a downhill death spiral. It will crash and burn. As much as one would hope for peace, it will never… https://t.co/qedUUQxA0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailed it! #baltimorechefshop #thecouplethatbakestogether @ Baltimore Chef Shop https://t.co/wgvFMuwxnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taurojam_07 Te espero a las 8 en la mufa! 🤣   * no come en todo el día para ir con hambre *]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyjacqui_ Sleazy O’Hobag.     What’s Irish and sits outside? Patty O’Furniture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celebrityhottub Are there bars anywhere that have Rutgers football on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[These women think we should be “100% energy independent” at the expense of the cattle, the birds, the economy, and… https://t.co/82D8lx7gZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILoveKPAlot Your health and welfare come first. Sometimes you need to protect yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin43399824 That is possible only when the hurt and pain felt by “non-traditionalist” is recognized.  If blame m… https://t.co/wBozm5s1qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temperature in the 40's as @GSU_Softball hosts @KSUOwlsSB from Panthersville. Spring is in two weeks. Here is the l… https://t.co/RJBhruNLMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days being a parent feels amazing and fulfilling. And then other days are today 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinsheehanDC I freaking love Drew Lock! I’d take him and not even feel bad about missing out on Murray https://t.co/iUDL6OiT7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mar_a_Hell_No @donald_j_putin @Maddygram @mog7546 Welcome aboard together we can do it Right !! Independent Conservative Private]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in Concacaf can you get a yellow card for being elbowed in the face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicrosoftEdge I can’t wait to beta test the new Microsoft Edge that’s will be used on Windows 7 OS! I already sign… https://t.co/IdJOiDfu7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OvOMayhem I cursed your controller almost wanted to take the other one with me but I left it like a good human 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the exact attitude every single member of Congress, from both sides of the aisle, should have. A congressma… https://t.co/1HHLQyLZXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no they’re going to piss off the “old sb heads”, they hate Travis so much like it’s his fault that he has so muc… https://t.co/w0okcWkW5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdgreenblatt45 I’ll be speaking about my experiences with this incitement while in Washington DC, this weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenCalebT @eaner0919 Didn’t he give away a truckload of turkeys one thanksgiving?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giovanniferoce @TedNesi @GinaRaimondo Is it me or did this guy respond and then delete his responses?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a city that’s exciting, it’s a city that’s inviting. https://t.co/EJMkVn0mMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only 3 minutes and 21 seconds 2woukd love your feedback!  https://t.co/OhERxEtdJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have waited so long for another trailer. And it has been blessed upon us. Is this the best thing coming out in Ap… https://t.co/U9ufbp4WwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta get back to meal prep’n... this cooking after 10:30 is nonsense. 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgesStPierre you are an inspiration to all fighters and Canadians, you have avenged both of your losses and had… https://t.co/vGeFW1OyEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Mercedes. Just wanted to let you know that Ian and Sean turned my worst situation into my happiest situation.… https://t.co/U7w7klo68C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 listen to you give a lecture to the president and ethics you pathetic piece of s***]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nancy's Pizzeria in Raleigh, NC w/ @speedbrawler https://t.co/LOMXaulES1 https://t.co/8JgJP0w1dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying my hand at a central Texas classic tomorrow with a take on a hot sausage. Great back end heat from the black… https://t.co/BIUTe3JNE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a West Coast IPA by @WeatheredSouls_ at @WeatheredSouls_ — https://t.co/50EySGFNrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a kid is giving attitude while also wearing vans and I throw him across the room, will he land on his feet? Asking for all the parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Priestley We have to live everyday like it’s our last, because none of us knows when that day will come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standardpunched did someone in dorms steal @marscha3d houses of the holy cd? I can't remember. The Ocean is a grea… https://t.co/fT59ntwK0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cameron_Gray @SpeakerPelosi @Ilhan Pelosi speaks out of both sides of her mouth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModulocFence Thanks so much! Had a blast performing at your National Meeting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Life size poster of trump and kY Dobbs has a man crush, he’s probably trying to be press secretary]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Web developer" at Robert Half Technology, then look for people you mig… https://t.co/DJP7fO64on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @nathanielsmith5 I’m thinking Skippy will any day now also don’t you #WArmy. https://t.co/vdEG3Ppsac]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 years and counting the citizens of America in Flint, MI are still living without clean water. Don't forget the fo… https://t.co/l6DAmOUzzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAWRAWRAAAA @_PeteLaw @RyanChurch2 Think these are from @Maatspencer psi data. May be another Adrian Peterson tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders You have no clue about laws unless it suits you. Law says southern border will be secured with a wall f… https://t.co/uoXO4BIBaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Everything you say has nothing to do with reality. The Republican El Paso Mayor disagrees with you… https://t.co/XVdAEc4bm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two most important days in your life are the day you were born and the day you discover why.   Mark Twain]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what the fuck Lil Pump is, but I was at the Jimmy Kimmel taping tonight and he had to do his “song” tw… https://t.co/0aV4jhJlS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[After years of increasing importance and power the office of President of the United States is now poised to the br… https://t.co/GeYxBq1ojc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cerner CEO Shafer's "move to stay away from the limelight was not only smart, but intentional." https://t.co/OPkMUEnd47 via @KCBizjournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in Iowa City in two weeks, might want to grab a ticket to watch this @IowaWBB team in person in the NCAA… https://t.co/GLNLdxUrt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarsonS13 @LadyVol_Hoops @evinawestbrook @Legend_Hooper Terrible play. Levy's not who we want to take that shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to CNN Jake Tapper. Jussie Smallitt might like prison. O wait my bad that was Paul Manafort. Well if the shoe fits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeverOurPOTUS Well, shut down the propaganda network #FoxNews which incessantly repeats the same tropes and lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryMcCollum @TroyEricG Oh snap! @TroyEricG? Response? https://t.co/ZDARtvKVII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chunky_60 @MSchatz22 @PhilAnastasia @phillydotcom @NJSIAA It’s less tackling I think.   You can do a lot with bags… https://t.co/e92UO3qK7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wb_thorne @Derek4943 @kcdoubleok @robinhanson @John_Hempton 5/n. However, setting aside the social welfare/ ethica… https://t.co/zp3GfQwyXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @KT_So_It_Goes Is that like referring to yourself in the third person 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN I support you! Keep doing what you're doing! Your bravery and sacrifice gives me so much hope for something better 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[FCC to review TV ratings system that critics say mislabels violent, sexually explicit content via @washtimes… https://t.co/KjG12wQ9ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a good ass job but woo child I’m sick of this place.... basically misery pays the bills!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karol the GOP pundits are focused on Venezuela which means nothing to someone in CA collecting biggly from the ent… https://t.co/opIyD5xm27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFalness Any chance you have an underling that can put KFAN+ on the mighty 95.7 so we can enjoy your call of the game this afternoon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaHalverstadt @Kevin_Faulconer sold for $17.9 million,College area;Willow Glen Apartments, 3635 College Ave.,was… https://t.co/srSF1ToE3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like to say happy valentines day to James raylee hamby. You have hurt your mom so much by not as much as sayin… https://t.co/02zNSgR85c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UndeadAzura @GigzT1 Apologizes. That’s all on this end of the chirp machine. But seriously. Here if you need someo… https://t.co/40kCbX9ODU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACGonzales7 If he got more than it’s great business, why aren’t teams and large corporations setting examples for… https://t.co/gqt96lxhWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kettlebrand I will not buy your wonderful chips anymore because the bag is too hard to open! You are idiots! I als… https://t.co/ggwTxEp4Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightfulWrestle Richocet,  turn Rollins heel, I can see them having Great matches]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to #global_markets, my #international_business students @Nichols_College realize that the world's nee… https://t.co/TR9s7pq4G3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyMitchTSN I'm sure, and I wouldn't either. Reading Hayhurst's books and others, there is sure a pecking order… https://t.co/2mQguuHoB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonVegas22 I saw a similar tweet on my timeline earlier. Because that was the last time UCF made the tourney, an… https://t.co/jMOkvlG4P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao, Raiders giving AB a huge ass contract makes it even more funny that they didn’t pay Khalil Mack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexialex Being a human being, you should be able to punch him.  The line starts over there. ------------------------&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gayredneck #gaymechanic @MattMuck1 I’m home in Mississippi and New Orleans till the 21st who wants some dick https://t.co/jTaYkRGNZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't even sleep my neck is so stiff it's hard for me to sleep I think I slept on it wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerronEShort This has been something God let us know through King Solomon who had 300 concubines and 700 wives. Al… https://t.co/NtR36lpp58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnandWrites @JuddLegum ...and the “I’m the end all be all of proletariat advocacy” routine that replaced intellige… https://t.co/nG15JsoWPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever come to Tampa make sure you check out the restaurant - Columbia in Ybor City. Great food, atmosphere and history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 @JEDBPK She needs a Carmen Miranda fruit hat on her head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp How is it biased to call a liar a liar? Because it’s beyond debate that Trump lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philadper2014 Just imagine if Jessie Smollett were a conservative Republican. These same people who are defending… https://t.co/lYDBQFs0fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[gretchygretch1 blakejul13 Tonight 3/2 at gothnightatcityclub our guest DJ is Pinknoise (former Luna resident ) she… https://t.co/R8OKatypqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunter2baseball @sam_vinograd @realDonaldTrump I never bastardized anything. I gave you the science and you claim… https://t.co/m8mEt4dFGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[What takes greater negotiating skills? Achieving an international trade agreement or getting a four-year-old to eat… https://t.co/xcOx0P3x7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mid of 8th: Coastal Carolina takes a 5-2 lead over UW behind Kieton River's RBI double.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalEmergency #BuildTheWall @HouseGOP who voted for this bill are #RINOS who want illegals to vote for Democra… https://t.co/yDqArXH3Vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoMag I wasn't either #ElChapo was in Mexico or Colombia somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haddonfield 67, Camden 67 with 103 left in OT. Haddonfield ball after TO]]></document></documents></author>