<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Liberals are good at deceiving.  They have done it for longer than Cohen has been alive… https://t.co/mMfUEDzlIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[wrong: thank u next has no skips. DW has.... wait. no skips. oh shit, we have to discuss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanOtto 🤷🏻‍♀️ no idea. I read that he had one though and was secretly looking at it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last practice of the year for my @O_Sports_Acad 3rd and 5th Grade Platinum Teams! Very proud of the progress they’v… https://t.co/0vteD60cPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryStebbings @Forbes @fdestin @piadiri @arjsoysa @stride_vc Congrats Harry, you deserve this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien @AP AP has experience or training in property insurance adjustment? Since the insurance company tendered… https://t.co/GEEov2C3lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piece meal public policy is more expensive...especially a system that requires such a large public servant  overhea… https://t.co/wGH4Z1HpOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[An extraordinary week at the @NYCComedyCellar in Vegas, with mark_coco_cohen @harrisoncomedy @lennymarcusnyc… https://t.co/BfZ5GG47On]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardueSuzanne an attitude of gratitude more than a platitude more than an interlude more than a passing fancy will make you less antsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since 2015, an estimated 300 million people (rising each year by alarming rates) suffer from #depression (according… https://t.co/Qq8yrNGKnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevEricAtcheson I believe there are elections where we vote to determine where the money goes,We the people,yes it… https://t.co/GIR8wX80RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would have helped me tremendously. Though there is probably a 50% chance I wouldn’t have continued my schoolin… https://t.co/wukbrVAiLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uuugghh. This one really hurts. Rip #kingkongbundy the walking condominium with legs and arms. https://t.co/CDKMhfIa7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming from the Ass Clown and Thief. The Exact Opposite is the REAL TRUTH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacksonville has the most shitty  weather one day your good the next day you got upper respiratory infection for not wearing a jacket 🖕🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaJaegerTV When you can't get that favorite Dave Matthew's song out of your head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come saturday baseball is back and saturday @Yankees vs @RedSox at 1pm only on @NESN can't wait @Yankees will beat them let go @Yankees . ⚾]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 they changed the name from RFOC in like 2k10 how is still known as the foc? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery And Greenpeace founder described her as a 'pompous little twit'😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @stevetyrell with get_repost ・・・ Back at in the Bay Area this weekend at feinsteinssf to play in beautiful… https://t.co/IxYyqF6GRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisfloridalife I kicked in the twelve bucks. Still hope to win the freebie because I'm GREEEEEEEEDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I called Wells Fargo to close a couple of accounts as I’m moving to another bank. Here’s how it went:  Me: Hi, I… https://t.co/001p4QHLp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomTrixie @MarkAndrew12000 @JohnCornyn YES it does. I moved to TX with 1st. Husband (military), I flew my daughter… https://t.co/F6uHDnPkrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImADuckQuackk It would stabilize the market for one thing. It would be the decent thing to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC keep illuminating what is going on and how the status quo keeps us a prisoner of the past Next battle eliminat… https://t.co/LaqjYTYdXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming at you Friday, Feb 13th at the Airport Tavern in Tacoma @airporttav  @BroadwayCenter @kzmusicmedia… https://t.co/i8ZMpKPGWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 True in a sense, but he did hurt the lgbt community and victims of racial attacks. In that now people… https://t.co/A7cdIjJFp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It occurred to me, in defense of Judge Jackson, perhaps he was trying to appear overly “fair”, thus undermining Tru… https://t.co/rXkJDiG9WV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Occasionally I hear old music and wonder: Why didn’t I know about this before? Example: Milton Brown (1903-1936), t… https://t.co/AORFt9dZ6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreatureLives @ProSlayer @deximeruya @AFreakyDude @RealEnli @DeityOfGaming @nitara38 @CardoHq @TNACreative… https://t.co/jRPJ6YUsnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGASIEMPRE @LanceMcAlister @PFF Shouldn’t have said that. I’m assuming]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t be understanding why people be debating about how much money is required to spend on a date cause everybody… https://t.co/2GWMbIcRHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[KGB has apparently had quite a run in placing assets in the highest offices of power in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanbpeterson So when Louis CK says things people don't like it's "Thank god for Louis CK, .....  ...but when so… https://t.co/iqMwGOsH1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RoadSafety: Texas has a texting-while-driving ban, but many commuters still take out their phone while in traffic.… https://t.co/ufcdwNn52i]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #Oakland #Athletics team 1965-2017 pitchers.  https://t.co/7Dd12gxVxT … … https://t.co/3cFLyu0mzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macneilj57 @pat_carleton13 Looks like the makings of a little community sidewalk sub committee!  #thanksforyourservice]]></document><document><![CDATA[124 all 56 seconds left.  Easily best atmosphere of the season. Hold on to your butts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DielLedetDuhh Absolutely! Have a great evening evening...time to drop a beat! 😉 https://t.co/4K3Pxquo7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHoustonWade @Bearded_Cynic @strokjl @SykesCharlie @EWErickson You trust racist cops and President Trump with a… https://t.co/z2VC9G94Fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hella tries to separate a bar fight in HB, gets kicked in face.   @GuaveraMichael]]></document><document><![CDATA[the guitar intro in Wish You Were Here by Pink Floyd is so soothing omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amelyore lavi ou Koulye a:  1. Fè fas a perèz ou yo. 2. Manje pi byen. ( si w gen mwayen an 😔 ) 3. Admèt erè ou yo.… https://t.co/2l0fCtiuGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON Dave any idea on if @GenuineLexLuger ? @Sting ? Or @HulkHogan will be at #RAW for the big birthday… https://t.co/d4yWeFbApG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Mr. Pitt had a referral from his doctor but Kramer told Elaine he knew a guy that works wonders. The… https://t.co/V7TiWrI85T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listos para bailar toda la noche? Nos vemos en #DanceRoom 🐻🎧🎚🔊🥁🔥 #Dj #BestClubInTown #Monterrey #Ocampo433 #Djlife… https://t.co/Mdxjgukx3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[You remember those infomercials that sold the solution to teenage acne in the late 90’s - Well the Doctors have don… https://t.co/0t3B9oIWRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SEPTA BSL Tasker-Morris Station - @septaphilly in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/vwxUv9Xr46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing quite like riding the Red Line after the clock springs forward to 3 a.m. and you're across from one guy smo… https://t.co/4m87pAy9IO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalleyErickson @stoolpresidente Check out @MaxBookAir’s Tweet: https://t.co/MAVapByFWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EasierSaidTuesday checkout this #originalsong &amp; #follow these awesome friends. https://t.co/NoOoEWKolM… https://t.co/zsuBFmJDkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna have dinner w my dad n brother.. dont know where we going yet tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Spring Break was still a thing at age 27. Tired of this cold ass weather &amp; need a dang beach in my life. 🏖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELGazette @AidanElt @11thhourspecial That point has been made and is well taken. I would assume, though, that when… https://t.co/zGUjaBSeuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisguidedAirman @Gadawg1971 @RobDreg @atillathehun412 @tammyTrumpedYou @JC2MAGA @LujanJamie @rkline56 @BrianHanes4… https://t.co/5kETJlkSfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing this team is starting to show us every game is their ability to step up and fill in. Who’s next in line t… https://t.co/7MTYkLW5yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning SATurday for our fantasy league. Tailgating while last year's loser Derek retakes the SAT. thedinerna… https://t.co/nxfGvjPCQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teenwolf325 Oh it's all bullshit. When he dies his kids are just gonna sell the team. How about before you die, ma… https://t.co/K409TqWxE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garywhitta Did you ever play the Spider man ps4 DLC? Was playing through it today and was thinking of you while li… https://t.co/cU4SqRrTBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[well gee Mulder there's that shipment of drugs and guns coming into New Jersey tonight...."I hardly think the F.B… https://t.co/3p46jyV0p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go @JeffersonDemos! David and I are cheering you on to victory! Do it for the PIL, @PPSConnect and our commun… https://t.co/YCVhHPZ2zR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is scarier than a goofy girl mad. 🥵🥵 Run at all costs, they’re out food blood 🏃🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I just got the Deck of Many Things. My flaw is being an inveterate gambler. This can only go one way. #dnd #dnd5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last book @mistiedawn77 @MicheleWingate @andystilp. @MeghanUmphres you’re up. https://t.co/MFIooGkOJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drlynnchiu And pick up on who are a-holes quickly - sometimes they are harder to spot than we think....at least from my experiences]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longlivereigns Who do you think should induct them into the hall of fame???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayAspin @deejayndn @AndrewScheer I will NEVER "come together" with racists, nor with any person who supports them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarnoRealestate @Steve_Pippin @KoNFX @netteKnows @DrEtiquette @Lorrilala @Diaper777 @catlady2099 @MikeLehman6… https://t.co/Pxsqb4ywyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In conclusion, please elect this older straight white man as your 45th older straight white man president. Thank y… https://t.co/T2vayW4MUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJWhit2020 @ByronYork Ok, and since Obama and Clinton release their tax returns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure he only went to Duke because he couldn't just enter the NBA Draft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I beat myself up to gain credibility so when I say something positive peeps believe it. Which what I say is the tru… https://t.co/ucnzzOwoxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain but no snow at Desert Mountain Golf Course in Carefree. #FOX10Phoenix @ECFOX10 https://t.co/svs47wS7B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraZi_HD @LeVeonBell They don’t have a big name outside of philly like the other players I listed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmadaFANB @vladimirpadrino @CeballosIchaso @NicolasMaduro @ceofanb @PrensaFANB @PresidencialVen @VTVcanal8… https://t.co/TXmQ3bQlPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke/Syracuse is going to be an interesting game today. Zion is obviously a big loss, but in this matchup, not havi… https://t.co/g29ruA5sOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Per @NotJackKemp’s recommendation, finally about to try out Melis. https://t.co/QWTfzbARIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing do but a bus ride will help ... #ctrainist. @ East Hartford, Connecticut https://t.co/doztwkVtGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eldiariodedross  no notas algo raro en esa foto   Hazle zoom y fíjate en la luna y la estrella que está abajo de e… https://t.co/GrLi11pffJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Years ago I was dead broke, I went to a wedding in LA and convinced a stranger I had no relation with to invest $10… https://t.co/0CEcwskGJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking bs bro who uses this we playing a game my man https://t.co/f3nuXpvzds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fatality_89 @blessedandsave @Mitsuownes @HoneyBeeCMNDR @PerfectLegend Can submit these to twitter for all to use ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TellHerAStory Take breaks, stay hydrated, breathe &amp; stretch. Have a great weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Villefrench, Sur Mer, France, Mediterranean Sea. https://t.co/TGvbECzL1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidbix this is truly the wildest Whole Thing i’ve seen in my whole life... how is there no information out there… https://t.co/3e7kRIC0ZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffnationwide if the PNP loose, might as well Peter resign on the day of the result.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssam440 And maybe that is just Ohio for you guys in general but I know I would feel the same way as you do if I… https://t.co/yp1eWrUiuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aledenicola @catirafaella Poteva semplicemente rispondere con un: “si è vero, mi sta sulle palle”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hurricanenita Still hoping for @hurricanenita cover of "The Man comes around"  to be @BeckyLynchWWE theme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, this is Southern California. Mountain living is glorious. Lots is snowflakes. On the plus side, the drought is… https://t.co/uPENnTt0fD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/59TOZMpBbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all better get full before y’all go to any air port food be high asf 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownskinReggie I saw somebody’s picture with gravy on biscuit and found myself thinking about the picture 5 mins later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in a dominantly low-income middle school and being roasted for looking low-income by other low-income kids. G… https://t.co/kwYIfVtCZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @joshualyman’s secret plan to fight inflation press briefing and as bad as that “bwiefing” was it is not n… https://t.co/Co0L3TYO0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Someone that does things like this have another issue going on in their head.  I respect gay people… https://t.co/9BxB8T5cQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go @realDonaldTrump ! #MAGA #BuildTheWall #2020Election can’t come soon enough!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLuu17 You gotta go to sleep, that’s the only thing that ever works for me. You can also pop a few excedrins if you can’t leave work..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maw447 I’m still not sure I am ready. This is all still very confusing to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too good to not share! Real Estate is changing for sure, and those that stay lean and mobile will remain. Hat Tip:… https://t.co/1gmKoGeb6P]]></document></documents></author>