<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GamesBeat @GameWorkers @JeffGrubb I think it is important to let Executives and CEOs know that there will be socia… https://t.co/z8J5ho9Et0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at White River, Ontario in White River, Ontario https://t.co/kz4IW6XPSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I go with my gut with this guy and be patient or just, stop waiting around and get on the boat again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won the Judge's Prize at @nutanix Global Tech Summit '19 HACKATHON!!!! https://t.co/BtUwqICjFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-watching @thethankyoutour with my mother-in-law because she hasn’t seen the broadcast and we were at the Oshawa… https://t.co/8lNTH4gnQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Story time:    Yesterday I took my best friends son out for his birthday. Woke up today with 15 text messages sayin… https://t.co/oxDynloYb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build your gorgeous house on this 2-acre residential lot in an established subdivision off of HWY-78! It is a short… https://t.co/UzNvGGZCZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @TrentMosley7 @LarryM0805 @ChelseaClinton Don’t forget the attempted rape!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In between a memory and a dream. The best state of mind. #consciousness #PositiveVibes #LumixS1 #artist… https://t.co/68CKuPBTTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved bringing friends into GA with me last night that had either never been to a game or never been in GA. They bo… https://t.co/sI6kpc7I0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited for this! He was the first concert I ever went to, I remember I was so excited I even remember the… https://t.co/cgo6MGnkDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the attention aint from who i want it from, its not reciprocated at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole thing is just inhuman for some reason... these people cannabals of there own kind and dna 🧬#LivePD 🧐🤯 we… https://t.co/9D0F2TPOM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Caleb he was the cutest boy I ever loved and he said “not for long!” (referring to baby of course) and i bawled]]></document><document><![CDATA[To have a director want you so badly for a part that they wait....wow!! @ Goderich, Ontario https://t.co/zX6L9pG6FT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccas1434 Love you Becca. Life can be so magical. Your one❤️❤️ https://t.co/ujpJrG8RUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a cost effective choice right now. For sure. Grow Solar - California! #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #Solar$]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Robinson and I most definitely live HE IS THE ADMIRAL FOR PETE’S SAKE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GodsGotThis Philippians 4:13    I can do all things through him who strengthens me. #Bible https://t.co/czOwbdn6DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Direct support professionals- who provide services in the community to folks with disabilities like I/DD and autism… https://t.co/GA0Yxy3Pj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes women bleed;  sometimes we do not.   we cannot be  so easily  divided up  into boxes  wrapped in  pre-pac… https://t.co/Ti8V0N0QXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple weeks ago this really hot dude told me I was tan and I think about that everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is every day. @tonyrobbins | Love yourself, Love Your Family, Love Your Friends, Love Thy Neighbor, Love The L… https://t.co/mh8u8RBKh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with this guy. Having a pool is costly, unsafe and it lowers the value of the house. No pool for me #HouseHunters @hgtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aleigh802 @Layla0406 @GOP @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @POTUS Robert I absolutely agree with you.  Where are Marco Rubio,… https://t.co/3jZkujehJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally watch more male beauty gurus and I’m not sorry about it 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC   Slow down, Andrea. Initiating ideas is good. Let the cows fart. More than 12 years. Don’t kill babies for wo… https://t.co/KarbKAVehT]]></document><document><![CDATA[currently crying because I thought about what if the entire plot of frozen 2 is Elsa trying to swim]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s leg day, which means the snow needs to stop so I can get to the gym (as I secretly wish it would keep going)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill. It’s nice to see Donny Jr didn’t fall far from the tree. Jr thinks teachers teach socialism? What kind of… https://t.co/5TGFxEt8EB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlecBalwin what a crybaby!! Hahahahaha.   That’s a threat to my safety.  I’m scareddddddy!  😢  @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/voljP7dXYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WritingCommunity How is your writing going today? Fun, torture, or somewhere in between? https://t.co/lJ2xWAVsKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s hope today flys by like yesterday did! The sunshine brought me a new energy and I am excited for the crazy mo… https://t.co/of22dVqjQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alivia0988 @kkendalllieghh Ok pretentious bitch “capeesh” lmao. She never said she’s going to go out and kill more… https://t.co/EbvPtKAKio]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s ignoring two obvious facts:  1) Trump never thinks ANYTHING he does is a crime   2) Trump is a moron… https://t.co/eE39m7aA6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[💀Zarif's sudden offer to resign rattles Iran, Rouhani yet to reply https://t.co/ylAjeqWX97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayyy_itsfay Not trying to be a jerk but if they say your veins are to small it means you’re not hydrated enough an… https://t.co/wxxySJ5YRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to hang out with my coworkers at work and man, the money I spent here is completely different than what I would spend in Iowa 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing by (@ The Mad Hops At Bobby Mcgees! in Bridgeview, IL) https://t.co/K3BwfepApU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy sweet 16 Kels!! I hope it’s been all you could wish for and more! I love ya💕 @kelseycowden]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senrobportman Tell the governor to stop taking them back in raised taxes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SciATM wow Gery just used the word facts! Sure Walmart is there for the economics - more money to be made selling woo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s all fun and games until those automatic withdraws come out of your account and you overdraft your account THREE DAYS BEFORE PAYDAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning after years of no video game card I have three important words: Destiny 2 good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I give it 12 hours before Nickelodeon pulls the video for Squidward Nose down and sues for copyright infringement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for being my calm place and my shoulder to cry on. You are so so appreciated Rylund. I love you to the mo… https://t.co/xsfn9Y0uV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776KAG @IFBpaul So much has been said that speaks my heart too. Your heart speaks my heart. Please don’t allow th… https://t.co/94rjbqtR0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[like what would you do if the driver decided to turn their app off and just take your child wherever]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many parking stickers/permits on my car it ruins the aesthetic :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Colorado is so lit... 🔥🔥🔥🎿🎿🎿 @ Copper Mountain, Colorado https://t.co/OUdUNsrdnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[And science puts the icing on the cake! Can our solids roll, stack or do both? #brentwoodproud https://t.co/TaiT9iHF0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[When sunning yourself feels this good. #havanese #graciemae @ Gearhart, Oregon https://t.co/EjNd0Bgp6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police estimate Gardin and Huntley robbed about 40 stores, though they have currently just been charged with 5, sin… https://t.co/B2P1hpOxCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WireAmerican No.  More important things: vet suicide, too many gun deaths, children need to be reunited with parents, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at City of Augusta in #Augusta, GA. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs lik… https://t.co/sc12GlQdf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler Did aliens abduct Michael Steele? Wasn’t he once chairman of the RNC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robbin_Young @pixelpreaching I have to agree. I was in KCMO in 1985 and was shocked as the court ruled that the ci… https://t.co/PmsgDfCOkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to nerd the fuck out and see the Lord of the Rings exhibit tomorrowwwww! Y’all I’m so hype 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one knows what this means but we found an STE at this bar and we’re making him do a goddamn shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, you don't know what in the ’H’ you’re talking about! The only reason you’re here is to create destruction of A… https://t.co/CNXPDeBodh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I’d like to go back to that little girl in crooked pig tails wearing tap shoes who thought me and Hannah… https://t.co/iKlwS53bui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pence met with silence after mentioning Trump in Munich speech https://t.co/xZTPS4wfY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t even bring myself to look at old pictures/videos, all it does is remind me of how much i have changed and how happy i’m not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oddreyonna Exactly!!! And I may sound irresponsible but I’d rather live in my version of reality. I know what’s go… https://t.co/XNwlZpEuHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to think of it, i just had late night in the day. I guess you could call THAT “night day”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, this dude is 77. He's too damn old to be President. Go away and stop fucking us over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ag8N0N50R4 vean el programa de  @baylyjaime @MegaTVLive @JulioBorges  volvió a delatar otro Militar]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy I had an early appointment in #Lauraville and naturally had to get some @josiehinke #eatlocal #baltimore @… https://t.co/4zH9d63crL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broken computer.  WHY DOES EVERYTHING BAD HAPPEN AT ONCE IN MY LIFE. I'm cursed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBoard1200 @tj_mayes_ @UTHealthSA @SACADATexas @AlphaHomeSATX Thanks for coming! Thrilled to have @1200WOAI at… https://t.co/NSepBwX8HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you baby girl!! So glad we were able to share this night!! And thank you Kiera for helping me make it happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation This is "my" Deputy.  We live in Sullivan County - our hearts are broken.  Praying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the day, March 5, 2019, slowly comes to an end, I just wanted to stop to say Thank You To Everyone who sent a Fa… https://t.co/n3fp6mUGTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have an example of what bravery means to you? I'd love to hear it. #brave #bravery #courage #shareyourstory… https://t.co/TZS3Q2KZHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zehra_Tnca Now he sure not behaving as he is interested in Sanem mind, last week touching her face now holding her hand he is rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day, another airport...😛 I swear I’ll run into Tom Hanks soon enough...😆👏 #TheTerminal But first, a mirror!… https://t.co/nu4ccntWPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all of that 🍪🍪🍪 dough! Fundraiser delivery @MPSRockwell today from 3:30-6:00. Please make arrangements to p… https://t.co/cUPElAXgFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and now I see my grammar errors upthread, YES! 😂 REWIND: You can contract the flu after you received the shot if… https://t.co/7TckvVgiHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlinconstan @ACShilton P.S. happy pony is in my Facebook and Instagram stories rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoushoubella I was ignorant about what Trump was all about until after the election.  What I knew up to that poin… https://t.co/cmCbo7RZC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Accurate representation of me trying to get to my car. https://t.co/7YEYoxkVzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a problem with this ad, maybe try considering you’re actually part of the issue because this ad is amaz… https://t.co/6x6KWXhbL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh. I live in a red state with...a lot of great chefs? I know we’ve all thought Southern cuisine and Texas barbecu… https://t.co/pbKGPPYTEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuhh they broke into my car i has a fever all weekend let’s see what happens next]]></document><document><![CDATA[@priskila_rosy @KissickSheila ABSOLUTLY ,NEVER STOP BELIEVING,MICHAEL WAS SENT HER FOR A REASON,SO WAS JESUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoeshine @pamelacolloff @BetsBarnes OMG yes I could talk about this to no end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PantherResists @NBCNews Women/Victims and children have not many True Rights in this Society and POC also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter always turns to spring  #spring #spring2019 #citrusflower #winteralwaysturnstospring #春 ＃2019春　＃花… https://t.co/d8BVwV7q6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankrejci @JohnFPfaff Yes! I can remember using bulletin boards to communicate In chat rooms,  floppies and dBase to write c programs]]></document><document><![CDATA[do everything that scares you, it’s worth it @ Wichita Falls, Texas https://t.co/gINkcnN4Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Impeach them both. We were NOT stuck with Nixon's crooked VP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan Gotta put Super Hazmat gloves on anybody who tries to massage his mushroom. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @MattWalshBlog He’s now happily tweeting about abortion to distract himself from this dragging. Have… https://t.co/rawy6k3mK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetBenMax Why #WeThePeople , the real left, don’t believe in a quite obviously broken political system 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @jensenackles ’s weekend Party 👑 🎂 #kingjensenackles  #MardiGras2019⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠ #BacchusLI  and @DanneelHarris 💐❤️… https://t.co/7iD3BkJ35q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gateway Women's Retreat 2019 Real Estate is always going thank God for brokers who go above and beyond. Showing and… https://t.co/QGFcNOEEOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think im going to write this new complex a nice long letter and processes and procedures. I love the property but… https://t.co/bsrYE6CLAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally listening to the @maebirdwing  episode of @ArmchairExpPod and I KNEW it was going to be delightful, but man… https://t.co/EsDgo8fzMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hahahahaha that made my sides split. I love you President Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night 🌸 @ Melvyn's Ingleside Inn, Palm Springs https://t.co/7XvB0GsecA]]></document></documents></author>