<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Yeah all these old southern crack smoking whores might support you. That’s because there pimps make them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mcfcguvnors @andelawson @MsMollyRachael Every other tweet could be deleted but this one and it still wouldn't crack the top ten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakupnuhanovic You make a good point. I’m happy the team has the ability to play both ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It didn’t take long for Fox and The producers of Empire to cut Jussie Smollett, looks like they are going to kill off Jamal for good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update it also now includes people who brought Tupperware containers of food]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAC --&gt; ATL --&gt; DTW (@ Jackson Hole Airport - @jhairport in Jackson, WY) https://t.co/mUXhHHx4Ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BretStephensNYT is exceptionally good at licking the assholes of the rich and powerful. His skillful tongue misse… https://t.co/yI7G9TQRBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junesrealdad @Lauritsen4440 @jlauritsen1820 Who tricked him that the “something nice” was a Huskers shirt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇩🇴🇩🇴🇩🇴🇩🇴💪 #IndependenciaDominicana #dominicanindependenceday https://t.co/TbsoDPpAWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTMannJr By the way what about the checks Mr. Kennedy corroborating the allegations; not a single attempt to attac… https://t.co/c1heYMC5aB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody knows "Honest Abe" is the presidential nickname that most slaps historically. But they called Millard Fil… https://t.co/HnpN4MMLEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElDattio Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy          Kindl… https://t.co/JN4lGtiDJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEY EVIDENCE: Trail camera near where Mujey Dumbuya’s body was found in Kalamazoo shows vehicle on Jan. 24, the day… https://t.co/H0GeDRvW5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to cut my baby loose but she came right back https://t.co/sHAlck7zKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamMatt22 Please do. I am sure The Gospel Coalition is just waiting to tear this apart. They’d appreciate any… https://t.co/XqShuaA98d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LUNAMACC You always said 2 sides to every story, but clearly something isn’t true. I will say tho, that interview… https://t.co/w19MBfKq1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing in a Walgreens at 8:50 pm on Valentine’s night in the Valentine’s section has to be DEFCON level 5 right?… https://t.co/XVYsYgWgSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lack of a strong manager. He’s putting out the wrong team. You can’t be content with a team that is only going to g… https://t.co/sYISsd3uwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael76446692 22-27. I’m not actually using him or anything, it was just a joke haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe this is your time for you and your supposed to be enjoying it for exactly what it is - your time, for you. 💘… https://t.co/FexTXquLXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- what are you writing? C- all of my knowledge of magic, most of which is healing magic Sari- what is not ? C-… https://t.co/VEVQlEfhF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr That’s not at all what she meant. You and your dad seem to have the same level of “stable genius.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope everyone likes how pitch black it is at 7 am. #DaylightSavingTime https://t.co/ddkWJxF7PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will miss teaching at @WMSFAPTSA this morning I support the future of education in KY! Here is musical and educat… https://t.co/cPnZe52XKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Review for Galaxy S10 Plus Case, Androgate [Pearl Series] Hybrid Matte... - Mason clinger - Blog Booster https://t.co/HaD4Pcu2hJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally went to a day party for the last hour on some chill shit, nothing else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@p_fournier11 @Incatnito1 @GOP @realDonaldTrump Should have been: YOU CAN'T BE A RACIST IF THERE'S A BLACK PERSON S… https://t.co/9Rxp8qlRB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Anna by @HillFarmstead at @asisnyc — https://t.co/Ir9rgqTWsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteJMcD @KGJOR Casillas almost gifted them 3 goals coming out for balls that were not his but no shots to save. Awful game but 3 points]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger's wife accused him of cheating. He responded by playing all his concerts, saying their marriage wasn't… https://t.co/HXqtVNAZRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out latest @CapitalXRoads updates https://t.co/i37egTQYsF @cfdesmoines @dmampo @DSMpartnership… https://t.co/Jm2O1887xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0xSeldszar The Dam is definitely a banger. I wonder if you could make a darkwave album of all these tracks 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tastes like a coconut old fashioned. Wonderful. - Drinking a Mash &amp; Coconut (2017) by @thebruery @ The Dingo  — https://t.co/wNvyQnTekg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The United States lowered the flag on Monday at the Jerusalem consulate that had served as its diplomatic channel… https://t.co/4eU8fbEF14]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Reader Detail showing frame. @ Heartside-Downtown Grand Rapids, Grand Rapids city https://t.co/0RPWTsSNId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisOpfer Why do I think it’s because Bloatus was involved with those teens n that billionaires mansion down n Fl… https://t.co/KBaf2N9kV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[$20 GIVEAWAY. All you have to do to enter is reply with a screenshot that you pre ordered my song. And retweet this… https://t.co/pJr9gOSPww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put some respect on @TeamLou23 name! Professional bucket getter since the jump. Maybe end the career back in Philly??]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York beer exchange, where prices change on demand! @WaggonYork #citra through the roof! https://t.co/7rf8o2GYZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[So shall My word be that goes forth from My mouth; It shall not return to Me void, But it shall … https://t.co/yemFrsweyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enriquecamou @robertozar1 Ojalá nunca pase eso, y no estoy de acuerdo con la existencia de los carros pafas, solo… https://t.co/tkw8ISLrJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTT2020 @US_FDA 🚨Must see 🚨well done production you shouldn’t miss. For  MAGA!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkstateTakes @DevinWilber @EricWright6 Is he another Josh Cooper, David Glidden type]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the folks that are running for mayor keep trying to focus on things that just aren’t true. @MayorMemphis ha… https://t.co/u4uCmkm2h5]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Texas, whataburger is the answer to the ultimate question of Life, the Universe, and Everything . #life… https://t.co/HtKGCRJbDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday  #9 @dpeoplesjones !!! 💪🏿🏈〽️  Go Blue and Dominate from Troy https://t.co/cpFACt1FsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌😘🍀💭📖 (Um pouco sobre 8 de março, Dia internacional da mulher)  Desde meados da década de 1960, convencionou-se com… https://t.co/EGCPBntQTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4AnimalLife @PreetBharara @iamsambee @FullFrontalSamB Are they in Colonel Gadaffi’s tent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday morning in Miami is no different than any other place. Oh who am I kidding, it’s WAY different.… https://t.co/rJx7T72w03]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems that it’s not possible to effectively perform 10 task at the same time no matter how forceful a persons deman… https://t.co/r8DdVCAFMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarborTrauma @SCCM @EAST_TRAUMA @traumadoctors Great fun catching up Dennis! Congrats to you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired i just shut off all the lights and walked into my bedroom with my toothbrush still in my mouth because… https://t.co/zfttlKdo6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahVukmir Do myself and your self a favor.  Read David Cay Johnston's trilogy Fine Print, Perfectly Legal and Fre… https://t.co/QDBSd9Ovkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tarrantcountydays transitions to #FortWorthSXSW and the collaboration between @FTWChamber and @VisitFortWorth cont… https://t.co/iWxKTi7M5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned on the #Reds game and it's a pitchers duel. 6-3 Reds in the first😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassEden Just read about your experience with facial surgery and commend you for your bravery, as well as being op… https://t.co/eDaKynrs9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Gran cierre! Sinceramente me emociona que el diplomado de #periodismo organizado por la @uabjo y la @apooax40 de… https://t.co/3r4PVAKXeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bollemdb O que é relevante? Ironias infelizes? Ou Selva ainda é a definição de Brasil pra quem mora fora do país?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Obstacles cannot bend me.  Every  obstacle yields to effort." Leonardo da Vinci]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sketching night - #sketches #sketching #artwork #life #comic #art #comicbooks #comiccon #follow #artist #sandiego… https://t.co/xlgNeMCOT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorySurname If it is them I would hate to delete it since it got nearly 1000 views overnight which most artists (i… https://t.co/L1SURRGnve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadGameHOF I’ve certainly played worse. And much better, too, but this thing isn’t the worst game on earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moratorium on creepy kids and dolls in horror movies from this moment onward. Find something new]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNicoleArcy Hope you are doing better! Bet you’re sore, feel well soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joesephharry @StephTaitWrites @secupp But that is what is implied by many in this discussion. People have been bra… https://t.co/DE9YdPSPco]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got chips and salsa for tonight and now I’m regretting not also grabbing queso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIndian8 Johnny McCain's former BBF, turned into a bitch dog...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back is finally coming along #flex #flexfriday #fitfam #gymmotivation #postworkout #gaydaddy #hairychest… https://t.co/2bVOWggTVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Scheise by Lady Gaga on @SashaGrey, luv u cute thang!  https://t.co/DCaJeK6TBa https://t.co/AwzSeQK2Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damnit you first world idiots. Vaccinate your god damn kids. Seriously. What the holy hell is wrong with you pe… https://t.co/Lr4TwpRwqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know for sure which arrest this was ?? I’m not sure if it was his third or seventh, as the pics are qui… https://t.co/JffiBrMQxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm processing a bulk order on other products this week, shoot me a message if you would Love to try our New 💙💚Spot… https://t.co/UNq508Gprc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyOrtega 2006 vs Pistons in the Eastern Conference Finals. Behind the back flip shot off the glass with the And-1… https://t.co/S0nXH4Pu8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @KCBSRadio San Francisco for having me on this morning to talk about what a #MuellerReport could look lik… https://t.co/PuW1SR5wkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larry55872287 @kimguilfoyle @JoanneTarpon07 Open a book.  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Ea… https://t.co/rOjGA8vriW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookehazexoxo #BonerInspiring #Goddess #Perfection #DreamCumTrue #DreamWoman #WCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every thing seems like a city of dreams, I don’t know why but I still miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Titan Wrestling still has 6 wrestlers left in the state traditional championships. We currently sit in 6th place overall in the state!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Foundation For North American Wild Sheep in Cody, WY https://t.co/JTHAQ0CBUS https://t.co/5Vfv5bhjQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7 of the @AndersonU great book challenge.  History, life, faith.  Thanks @astumpf and @owen_handy for the chall… https://t.co/9fA01vyTEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[First show of the night in the books. Overboard Comedy in the Brick Room of the @MadHouseComedy was so much fun. Th… https://t.co/GdIvgJ5Yex]]></document><document><![CDATA[before i find a place to donate it, does anyone in NYC have a home for ~40 science fiction and fantasy books i foun… https://t.co/LLp2rRmLda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mabulle ça ce vendait chère ? j'ai trouvé un costume a 900$ que je mettrais sur un mannequin habillé en noir et me… https://t.co/ORKHKTRmiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tulipanesyflor Nah eso tiene mucha grasa tengo que cuidar mi colesterol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let The Games Begin... #Gameday🏀 #WIT @ Centre College https://t.co/5ZktrmGSAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinJReidy2 @NRA Hey, Shallow end of the gene pool, SAD! U hang'n they'll figure your Rx cocktail any time now! S… https://t.co/4XFwRKRgG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say something here but I totally believe somebody would say that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump We should run through the list. We will talk really slow so the 'silver spoon boy'… https://t.co/hyxtov9xpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to make something happen after I broke my back for the 3rd time sucks. Want so badly to get my 86 Monte done… https://t.co/bIQVRW29WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baylor earned that late alley oop when they went full court press while down by 24, 20 seconds left, against TTU walk ons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do what’s best for your mind 💯 @ New York, New York https://t.co/dR6ecHcwzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Sweets! We expect big things! Big, I tell you! #bigthings #showbiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want that 🐱ate from the back ??? Or yo nails did ?? 😂  🧐 CHOOSE WISELY...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get my middle child, 14, to read some Raymond Carver stories — last ones first — but I am also afraid for his heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLeeZeldin So you voted to have another govt shutdown , your own party negotiated this compromise bill. You’re j… https://t.co/Hb076SeLvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bathroom project is complete! I didn’t lose my patience and the boys are happy. Thanks to Central Pro Tile!!! https://t.co/URdT8FiUtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo  – at Panda Express https://t.co/NdDKUJ08fD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiet on the Coast (@ City of Half Moon Bay in CA) https://t.co/ekt7Ymxtmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie , time change got me shook lol it’s 4:10 and I feel like it’s 12]]></document><document><![CDATA[it either means RS missed/reached on the pick or their wasn’t $ for the player. waste of development time &amp; money.]]></document></documents></author>