<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien We all know that there was collusion. Lock Trump up, lock him up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conmemoramos el #DíaInternacionalDeLaMujer una fecha para recordar la lucha por la igualdad de derechos y oportunid… https://t.co/c238dldZge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please, someone, get to work on curing pancreatic cancer. God, feel free to chime in on this problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgia_france_ But on the real, does this help people sleep? If so I’ll take 40 gallons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louder, please, for the people in the back!!!!! Safe storage is 100% on the gun owner! Lock. Up. Your. Guns. People… https://t.co/tQjnZaqPbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop controlling your S/O’s every fucking move. all you’re doing is driving yourself crazy and pushing them away. i… https://t.co/rvoUTjltPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be teaching tonight for @fpu Introduction to Teaching. #letsdothis #universitylife @ Fresno Pacific U… https://t.co/qpP7esChIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because @SaraCarterDC  when the media reports it they use the Democrat line that fewer people are entering so how d… https://t.co/KUOpDdUEDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread about people being good to each other is well worth all the time you spend online today.  💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimstinnett @lilsun83 Maybe ms Fox should compare the cost of a education from the time when she went to school an… https://t.co/sBnlMziEP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @TenNamesLater Democrats from here on in will be known as baby killers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to start doing more things creative again. Reading more, writing again...  Technology is truly addictive and… https://t.co/b4pjwo3lbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CROI2019 powerful message from Dr. Carrie Foote @PreventionAC about the need for a #UEqualsU campaign. Check out C: https://t.co/mlaAAoCFus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseDemocrats @TheDC254 refuse to listen to the people, who have them a chance &amp; voted fir them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest concerns are dangerous behaviours like drivers cutting around the traffic on the shoulders of the road and road rage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the girl sitting behind me in class. Did you really have to bring Chick-fil-A to class while I'm trying to eat g… https://t.co/yyNjcDjw50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody The love they give us is beyond words and totally unconditional I'm watching them age knowing one day… https://t.co/rOYe3VRCA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con el dolor de mi alma le digo nos vemos cuando termine la maestría, alemán.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don't think that we are going to get any photos of Justin's birthday they probably all going to be kept private]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother, My Dad an My son all wished me a happy Valentine's! I'm good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashton5SOS hey i sent you a really personal email and i hope you get the chance to read it and respond to it. it would mean the world. 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Augustus709 I’m not fat-bashing him - I’ve been battling my weight too.  He lies about his weight and his height t… https://t.co/Z6P1iXjPEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all of you complaining about Wernick’s statement at committee...  Don’t be so quick to jump in and claim that h… https://t.co/dPtPD50dJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pretty obvious @browardschools will not implement “safe corners”.  @RobertwRuncie has an history of lying and… https://t.co/ZAdQ9Fxxrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swhaye88 @MrRonHastings @RepMarkMeadows You both seem to be on the same page,I’m confused 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SXSW2019 Hey @GameOfThrones fans, here’s a MUST WATCH WALKTHROUGH of the @HBO @AmericanRedCross #Bleedforthethrone… https://t.co/s3pIlfgTVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of all my @GCIndigenous friends and colleagues who have worked so hard and for so many years to make this… https://t.co/gNOs1LMIUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victorianclare @TrevBroughton1 @JofVictCulture How did it go in the classroom? I haven’t taught it yet, but am thi… https://t.co/oKUQB6L3Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[In SC: A billboard for canned peas reading “PEAS BE WITH YOU” #roadtripsights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterPreda You bug him by watching funny videos on your phone at a low volume but loud enough for it to wake him because of the laughing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrdsb Can you please confirm that MyWay highschool course selections deadline to submit guidance counsellors will… https://t.co/0c81L9b9GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all really wear y’all airpods any and everywhere 😂😂 i barley use my shits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe Lucas is sleeping in his own room &amp; without me tonight ☹️ he’s getting so big]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior women leaders from @StateStreet @caissedesdepots @eurazeo @blackrock on panel profiling importance of gender… https://t.co/18PgddQeVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever feel like holding the love of your life and never letting go? I know I do😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day of riding by the_king_steve_9917 aka Julie girl @CleverHorse @ Beyond Stable Farm, LLC https://t.co/WMiXVr97Tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineInMD @ryanjreilly The liberal media helps push that false narrative. Shame on them. They've been around long… https://t.co/V3QzFkcUsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes to language reclamation/revitalization!!! We must end the replication of colonialism and its genocidal warfare… https://t.co/lHQed6FcVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/6/19: Shortcut to Shred - Cycle 5 - Day 3 16,700 LBS. 260 REPS. So back at Shortcut to Shred. Doing it a little d… https://t.co/ceJHX1Pb5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's @shinetext made me feel all the feels.  ‘Silver linings’ aren’t just fluff—seeing the good i... #shinetext https://t.co/hbEy6F3BNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to go to Mexico for the weekend and my cousins have been asking my brother who was originally going alone… https://t.co/CWbD2rlLkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the better question is do cops get nervous when they see your mom in her Ford Explorer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LauraJWilliams @VincentCrypt46 Her Twitter is very anti Trump/Republicans sooo, there’s that! 😳 She is not going… https://t.co/erWmtKLpqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nonewjails_nyc @NYCMayor Why are Sociología economic conditions not part of discussion ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to our VB🏀🏀🏀 team! Great first round in sectionals for the Big Green! #NaplesCSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to read "Free to Focus: A Total Productivity System to Achieve More by Doing Less" a new book by… https://t.co/QrHhbLOku9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When faith is Operating You can’t hate on other People  ~Dr. Eric Johnson @blkpasz]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the thousand reasons I love her #millahhhhhh #OliviaColman #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday! This weekend I’ll be working on my spring line of chairs, racing towards the finish line of a sched… https://t.co/jzmpw981DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think you need to learn yoga to do that, but you do need young knees. I don't have those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Mitchell’sDiscountDrug for your 🐾 MHS Partnership in Education! Reece is loving ♥️his CTE Internship!… https://t.co/dwTu0oDXsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night tour of the Conservatory of Recording Arts and Sciences with my brother. https://t.co/Mz2XDP1EM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nicthehairchic#thecolourparlor#paulmitchellstylist#paulmitchell#paulmitchell#myhairology4U#balayag#thedemi#paulmit… https://t.co/Lmc0qW8ny6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosLoret El más corrupto e inmoral y que engaña a los tontos ingenuos se llama #AMLO la perversion y las falsas… https://t.co/fPp8z9BKUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh just hanging out with a FIFA video game designer...Guest speaker, Darren Laver, at tonight’s @menssoccerths dinn… https://t.co/EMOiaXKs8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankBossKev @YourFavoriteZoe Talk to me about your experiences with those airlines https://t.co/R9EJdWaiO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tying up loose ends with my toy guy xleeplattx  for @monstermaniacon @ Time to Eat Diner https://t.co/vApDhBOXyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Watch now has @LoveMySilk creamers and it makes me so happy. It’s the little things. #SundayBrunch https://t.co/R6qRb4PDXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CCC #HWC #StudentLife Get in and out as early as possible because pairing adult responsibilities with student life… https://t.co/bD3B667Lnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[tecnicamente eu devia demorar só meia hr pra chegar no trabalho mas o trânsito é tão ridículo q eu saio de casa 7:3… https://t.co/TvFbwNvFQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sayantani16 @Scholastic Not suprising at all! So deserved. Congratulations !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA There are two, types, of #Republicans, in #Congress, today? Those, who decide, to "retire early", to sp… https://t.co/KNE2hNxKPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵🎵Chicken pot, chicken pot, chicken pot, Pieeee!🎵🎵 @MaTaylorsKitch1 bringing delicious lunch to the people downtown… https://t.co/nEoI2nB7Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want an explanation between Christian and Christian religion? Christian means Christ like. When you add the word re… https://t.co/AHZhAYZpar]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Valentines Day, so here’s a Valentines pumpkin from this past Halloween to get the day started! . The history… https://t.co/RdhfX2KQ83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganDBoling Last years team is better honestly. Way more mentally tough than these guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[When levantas temprano a la niña que cuidas para que te tome una foto blogera. https://t.co/Pg6TR1hJUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Provocations of Chef Tunde Wey https://t.co/oHbSMmyT2N via @gqmagazine]]></document><document><![CDATA[The intensity of problem solving through debugging of their two-dimensional shape @Ozobot program!! Go @DASD_WB 3rd… https://t.co/yNot07saiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @BEERGUY201 @The_Fool_Monty @Nick23929445 @MelissaFincher @gr82btnvol @Shawn172510 @jamesonandbeers… https://t.co/MJqtp1WXLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is ready for the weekend? 🙋🏽‍♀️  Have a great Friday from @goldengoddessNC ✨✨✨✨✨✨✨ . . . #friday #friyay… https://t.co/lmuLc8YK0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[well niggas capping on my name now time to get my bowl of cereal and call it a night soon 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheckyX @annamccachren My Spidey-sense is that “deploy” might not be quite as plain as “take advantage of” or “app… https://t.co/smPqvZQ1ZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[True story: I once had to stop one of Michelle Obama’s interns from puking in a Brita pitcher. It’s not a scandal,… https://t.co/iRVQTgvycD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly not having fun as a #snowbunny ❄️❄️🐰🐰❄️❄️ #aspenchronicles VS💋❄️💋❄️💋❄️💋❄️💋❄️💋❄️ @ Residences at The Little… https://t.co/yFAN4zROwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderHQ They are the 💓 and soul of our visual love affair of all things Outlander]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop watching this. My team loves each other so much. https://t.co/mSMWVnYgZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two are having a Fortnite party at Skyzone 🎮🎮🎮🧩 #middleschool  #fortnite @ Sky Zone Tulsa https://t.co/qAwGrWYSVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from a gig at @CityWineryNSH for @RenewedSupport Heart is full x https://t.co/FT72Ci1ooS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tired after partying all day at Five Points Kennels! @ Five Points Kennels, Inc. https://t.co/Qla84bUpMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizgross144 @StephenApp I am so jealous but I was wide awake at 4-freakin-a.m. so 🤷🏼‍♀️!]]></document><document><![CDATA[mikethomas1567 #2019MABREAKING #usbawba #breaking #martialarts  #photography by @danielekserrano #withmytamron… https://t.co/87sV0zdLi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week I’m for reals about going hard af in the gym. I’m so ready for me to get over this plateau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my morning off by spilling my water bottle all over the gym &amp; all over my resistance band. 🙄 and it’s not even 5 am yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonRockets @Esther188rod  CONGRATS TO OUR JAMES HARDEN 🎗️YOU ARE TO MUCH FOR WORDS GOD BLESS 🎗️ YOU ALWAYS https://t.co/mY7McK412n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diaper777 @HeidiM_67 @tony_tonyt @akuscg @akvawe66 @AuthorLRiddle @abytw @Darb_Dude @TT197 @FoundOne14… https://t.co/LyDEYyFs7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines best bud deal thc edibles plus cannabutter brownies cupcakes cake bites cherry cheesecake cupcakes. HMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Bless his heart. I guess he and my Foxy are having a large time in heaven, waiting at the gate for us https://t.co/i6f0Xhtnwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm how was this not top news? How am I just hearing about this? #WorstPresidentinHistory #trump https://t.co/4nLcGLOBQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[OOOOMG START COMMUNICATIONS WITH OTHER GALAXIES. JUST GOSSIPING OK PUHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing hurts me more than knowing my friends are hurting and knowing there’s nothing I can do to fix it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sunday morning!  We accumulated a good amount of rain yesterday, but we’re not out of the clear yet. We have m… https://t.co/8hnd0HdeMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Same day as our rally.. If anyone has Anything Plz come out so we can better our campus for the Future]]></document><document><![CDATA[In celebration of #WomensHistoryMonth Vanguard will be sharing stories from #VanguardWomenThrive.  Today, there are… https://t.co/3pbuWek0dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkhammer From a lifetime North Carolinian, glad this is gone. What other sport kills so many while audiences watch… https://t.co/3u6DkbqN8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn't like @sza performance its because you're dry af.... Periiiioooddttt #ArethaTribute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbkd1973 @SassBaller Homeschooling then. My cousin had a couple in her class. She pressed charges for this behavio… https://t.co/5OlvcDKTiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivingmzstacey People will take it back for cars as soon as the snow and ice allow unfortunately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarebear SAME. I had a cookie dough birthday cake once and that’s about where my life peaked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't misunderstand any of this, I let it all happen for the sake of other peoples feelings and suffered for it.… https://t.co/In3RkafupC]]></document></documents></author>