<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Gotta love those strategically placed quotation marks. https://t.co/jjECDJ0Dwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanKnockout @VanityOps @stfuEx @swrvah @VanityAnxiety @JrdnBeSelling @VanityViyzr Vouch even tho i carry you when we play w toxic ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommsNinja @maryjeanschmitt @DahliaBakery There’s also really good pizza at @SeriousPieDT right around the corner from Dhalia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachStone5 @Nickelodeon @AnicaBustamante @Viacom So much fun! Haha the guests loved it 🙌🏻😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neiltyson Absolutely.  I think we should call them "Slightly more interesting moons"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denise Richards have not held up well over the years and to think she was a Bond girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For non-divisional teams, these two sure seem to have some real animosity.  Super chippy out here at The Booth (cc:… https://t.co/SQ7Fr8GKPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@28delayslater My states one 😥...  Can't wait untill we have a showroom and the ability to sell them 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbla807 @realDonaldTrump WHY DOESN'T PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLE DOWN ON HIS BIRTHER BS?? Obama's Kenyan Brother interv… https://t.co/d46wATf4EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the work @nguyen_amanda and @RiseNowUS are doing - using storytelling, gamification and #hopeanomics to chan… https://t.co/Y7ppVTJocu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMortemm @creepycgirl Awesome people like you are Signs from God @MMortemm 🌌✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giants’ Johnny Cueto, 20 pounds slimmer, ready for a huge step in comeback - San Francisco Chronicle: Giants’ Johnn… https://t.co/Ns3JgSRMrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's an "Old School New Kid?" @WDFosterGraham1 Tells Us! https://t.co/wNjXVauwtO @TonyaGJPrince @TancredoBuff… https://t.co/Jm4x9efarP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved this so much.  Congrats on being a part of the MCU now @ThatKevinSmith 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice and light, smooth - Drinking a Cherny Bock by @bohemianbrewery @ No Name Saloon  — https://t.co/A0o6ABxZTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KipHenley Have you gone to a pga/usga Rules class?    I got a 96 on the test   How did you do, plus I have caddies… https://t.co/WZqX46Bubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeldelafuente should play #Thrawn or maybe  Talon Kard. I think Thrawn would be best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this merry there's something wrong with you. https://t.co/2T1FTmgjx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBVABancomer  no sé porque me llegó unretiro de $99 a esta hora de la madrugada son unos rateros ya me lo han echo muchas veces rateros]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little louder for those in the back  THE WHITE HOUSE BLOCKED U.S. REPORTERS FROM THE TRUMP-KJU DINNER  NK REPORTE… https://t.co/PTSKZ5TaeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great moment tonight with legendary actor Sasson Gabay after he received the Pomegranate Award at the NY Sephardic… https://t.co/u0l2Ebyqe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning from MdR! :)  Make it a Great Day my Friends! &lt;3 https://t.co/9LS2YgFd6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your car detailed today! https://t.co/YzD8CMqqFl Dm for pricing and availability today! #Wash #Wax #Sealant… https://t.co/7Y7JtHjTet]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time tomorrow night I should be pulling up to the Bay Area... Boy oh boy.. Been too long!!! And much, much needed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mai Tai P.A. by @alvaradostbeer at @citybeerstore — https://t.co/4kpW3bgWLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes some finesse I’ve seen you finesse he can’t know finesse you stay on my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerfectBimbo @bimbodreamer @Plasticis4ever1 @JlspzSpitz @SmokinHot4Life @SccsMR @MarcoMax4 They’re beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got my first win in @PlayApex this morning, but I literally did nothing. ZERO damage done, died and resusci… https://t.co/vyFjVoEPnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[ENJOYING THE SPOILS OF THE INDUSTRY!! ROAD MANAGEMENT!!! #ATLANTA WE HERE!! NEW CHEDDA CHIXS THOTIANA REMIX BlueFac… https://t.co/mIx8uZP9bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @JussieSmollett @EmpireFOX They may as well let him finish. They'll definitely be Frank Underwooding him in the hiatus anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @wattswebedawgs @realDonaldTrump Collusion to lose election. You got a great case there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@generalzuo But that's my point. Most things are wishy washy. All roads leave up to heaven. We're saved by grace. A… https://t.co/6Xf2PwtyPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jess is mega pumped ab her new water hydro flask top. “It’s such a cute pairing”... her words, not mine @ REI https://t.co/4Xus5rXbTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog This is a clear picture of the justice system. If you are WEALTHY and powerful able to afford a team of… https://t.co/zgkyfoI6p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGodfatherMoody @TimCindric @MayoClinic @RafaSierra5 #indycar #ChiefMechanics and team presidents don’t stand on t… https://t.co/QyNSwymwtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMLibrary @lawfareblog When you are sarcasting on broadcast TV or radio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very grateful. Love being around the sport so much, along with the amazing people I’ve come to know to know through… https://t.co/KHWaSerBdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #landscape_lover #ig_landscape #longexposure_shots #landscapephotography #landscape_lovers… https://t.co/oE9TfKejtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabostern E guete Tag i Allne Für einisch - bedeckt ond schön's Wuchefinale guete Start is sunnige Wuchenendi us r… https://t.co/sy04zFl3y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders What’s sad is, there’s a small village in Afghanistan producing over 1500 guns per week...how many h… https://t.co/gktzUpQu8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geekylonglegs @king_corsaro Fuck you vinny. But that’s also really funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesAALongman @ABCWorldNews She ceased being an American when she WILLINGLY spread her legs to isis. She is an is… https://t.co/oPdBFvwyJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Don’t change the subject. Give us practical solutions. W/o the “how” you’re just blowing hot air.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/sqJV0vJdvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The majoe problem with Strict Liabilty is I know of no clubs support who would trust the SFA to run it in a fair an… https://t.co/AKVntu3sqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MkirbyE it’s above the norm, meteorological winter or not - in California.  ❄️#SierraNevadaSnowpack is   161% of n… https://t.co/WfDzgEhAMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lazy_Alchemist I don't mean Vic specifically.  I was talking much more generally.  I definitely believe everything… https://t.co/VCEToNvVn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard to imagine the abuse that happened before there were cell phones. At least today the harassed have a chan… https://t.co/cXmRA5uJz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera Has the black lives matter shirt become that same symbol ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 4.77 km in 1h:04m:27s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/dNi8YtTAn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanesHook @Haydenfilms @skipbolden @noir_or_never @DamianHempstead @DocJohn90 @baker_johnnie @TrashCanDanpt3… https://t.co/4kdSZHERzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fabrici17741808 @lopezobrador_ Se debe creer en el cambio, no en la impunidad. Recordemos que cambio tiene dos ver… https://t.co/0Bz94EPDDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you meet @lights vs. when you actually meet Lights. https://t.co/XNQucxhIVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettin lunch at soda city then headed to the mudbog hmu if you wanna tag along]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah!!! Another great step towards my #goal still got to head back to the dr tomorrow for some blood work hope… https://t.co/7tFkopUYIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mynameisjro Wait. If we’re condemning human rights violations, why is Islam not in the conversation? The shit they… https://t.co/hTwPzbpjrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he stands there and lies while he does it. If you voted for him, you are responsible for this travesty. If you… https://t.co/0hpybfctQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏾‍♂️ This is what happens when your child has been watching how to use your camera equipment..😂 Meet the brains be… https://t.co/M96gde2JQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump do unto others as you would have them do unto you… He’s more like do unto others then split!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time there one step from walking on water even though there knee deep in shit If Michelle was to be exposed m… https://t.co/KearPgDcfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[SSRIs are great, for the most part. Prozac and friends have saved millions of people's lives and improved the quali… https://t.co/sr7eWuj8MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw I'm with u. I'd really like to see a bill that ONLY TAXPAYERS with a W-2 as proof get to vote! Let… https://t.co/4vyrpoRLIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine never having to work while in school because all of your life expenses were covered, then you get a degree… https://t.co/xDVMNg97Vz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adv3ntuRoss Tell me why I’m just now seeing this 😂  shit craaaazzzzyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilpinkn1nja I was playing this game, than I was dying at this part... it was so random]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregame Warmup at Taco Surf!  Let’s go 🐸 @ TACO SURF on the Shore https://t.co/DiC7YFt75u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @HillaryClinton @realDonaldTrump The American people's had enough of your non sense please quit now… https://t.co/pK3gQDzjQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Yes keep comparing South Americans to the Vandals and the Goths, that's a great look for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course you'll never see the calculator app when it's running in managed kiosk mode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdavidalbizo @Padres @PadresCentral @SycuanCasino @PJHughes45 I don’t know the answer to that... but as @TC_00… https://t.co/ywbrF4JkV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could be flames, it could also be the sun reflecting through the steam coming of Hotel Dieu Hospital.… https://t.co/YSiXPqPqMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much road do cars need? Not as much as they have. #EriePA @ErieDDC @CityofEriePA @ERIDTN @Emerge2040 @BikeErie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worked out. Squats: 95x10; 135x10; 155x6; 175x4; 95x10. Bench: 95x10; 135x10; 185x6; 135x10. Did some light benchin… https://t.co/9EtsBcrewS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is that what you’re growing under your chin? https://t.co/Up8MiKTG6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curlysmalls @PacDaGoat I did that the first time then year later came back and said I’m going to end of season 1 n… https://t.co/A0lc2uNB8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mucho éxito en tus nuevos proyectos @Ernst33 hiciste un gran trabajo un abrazo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I say Brittany is playing with my god damn stomach. Hurry tf up. I haven’t had no jerk food since I moved 6 weeks ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @HouseGOP @SenateGOP Your argument is that POTUS is going around Congress to acquire funds to secure bord… https://t.co/mmK63TIAuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun week #LasVegas #Home #LifeWithMarkBennick https://t.co/TUz7xFQn7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWolfers Indiana University. 1985. H213. History of the Black Death. Amazing class I took as a blow off. Lear… https://t.co/F2AXtf4Kca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckyBreeder @elguapo64 @BarackObama @JussieSmollett Two colossal frauds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr8tlaker Actually should read “intent” but for my cursed predictive auto-correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triple Crossing Brewery Battle Creek Double IPA - Clean, a bit boozy and hazy with forward tropical notes and fairl… https://t.co/ZYEZw3OzWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pooltalk at #shoptalk with @rbonifacino talking #ellastein (@ Palazzo Pool in Las Vegas, NV)… https://t.co/cUModGL83q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWorsham If only Chris Jackson would come back and visit with the team as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow on The Chiasm 2–4 PM Pacific! My special guest is the amazing @LucasWarford of @ThreeForSilver! You won't… https://t.co/QhoZ1yhWQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[World News:      Former Nissan chairman Ghosn released after posting bail;      American woman, divorced from Saudi… https://t.co/Qnf7rApTfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Old Skook by @3magbrewing @ City of Fontana — https://t.co/qTh9WvPjxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damion Willis measured in at 6-3, 204 and ran a 4.48 40-yard dash..  How he wasn’t a combine invite I do not know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@images_by_g @ColleenHolt20 @rbdjelkins I agree with your point of view. But as a person whose life has been fucked… https://t.co/wvcEc2i4pG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwiiishG @Foward44 @KyleBusch @RonHornaday It’s an easy comparison. Both Hornaday and Sauter ran for very poor Cup… https://t.co/iA1SAojGZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMichaelGuest @msstate Michael, so glad to see you out and about bettering Mississippi!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to our friend Adam McQuaid! The former Bruin just traded from Rangers to the Columbus Blue Jackets.… https://t.co/oL6oijYATq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hadn’t gotten a chance to visit here in a while but the Rodeo got us close enough: cool art by @TheWomansHospTX, wh… https://t.co/4yUviTms7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eevee To make something really open sure does take an astounding amount of consideration. Been a while since I had… https://t.co/u4Jg8nKgGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Matt Duchene links.   Duchene &amp; #CBJ try to solve their own playoff riddles: https://t.co/WkwIIV84HL… https://t.co/2J1D6r1Jlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSmeed I will. I have just learned that the site is roped off, but I am not willing to believe that this presentat… https://t.co/0E9XkL0sQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump hasn’t had to use his brain in years, just coasting along watching tv and eating burgers.  The presidency is… https://t.co/74yuHiOcAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKinPlano @ATT @PerScholas @RepEBJ @TheTalentBroker @ATTimpact Just putting more points on the board Barry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad it's only a conceptual thing, begging for attention. If it became a plan would be a win-win-win: For investors… https://t.co/lJCSySJBqq]]></document></documents></author>