<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Stud holy tf wow. Holding your hand is a BIGGG mood! 🤧💕 https://t.co/fOedMzVYPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some #ACDC Friday morning #vibes! #treadmill #hitthegymharder #everyday #fitlife #GOALdigger @ HQ Fitness, LLC https://t.co/E6LunNGL68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveWantz2Know @YusufnotYufus @levi06589174 @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump Lol keep believing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Year 7 Cuzzo, 3 more to go!! 🔥🍫 @ Hot Chocolate 15K/5K https://t.co/0QvIlJFm8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitting them weights on Thursday morning! #weights #muscles working on it #dumbells #shoulders #chest  #abs and… https://t.co/yRr2eClKCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 More wasted $. Why did t they build them in areas needed to actually test.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 50th Birthday to you, awillingham42 !  I hope that today is as soecial@as you are to so many.  Cannot wait to… https://t.co/Uj4gVWVQq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMGRIZZLIES @amberlaiche @umontana Good yell me good need baby grow school please find gril know me I love me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walburgers it's what's for lunch #conventionlife #ALLIN2019 https://t.co/gH0axClwRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1009Dolphins @1009principal @AnnLPGA Go Dolphins that's my co worker Jonella Williams the kids love her]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve also been shooting shows/bands since I was 17, and prior to this last run with Sharptooth, I was paid once for… https://t.co/5YStLuVYK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo playstation took like $200 right outta my pocket and i didnt even kno abt it, im a broke bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[With your help, our amazing @columbia_biz team raised more than $3K for rare cancer research sloankettering through… https://t.co/il6YzFMY4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whereby, once again, the Trump administration has no plan and did no research before implementing destructive and c… https://t.co/Lt3vzfz1aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShalveyC @AllCharisma I haven’t yet, she’s my bae. Did you watch #Firefly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS you ought to take @realDonaldTrump phone away   He tweeted at lease 15 times yesterday. This week will be w… https://t.co/guETcsYBvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my sister talks to me she says “my brother” like hoe, he’s both of our brothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh What Racists say.... I have black friends.... justification does not work]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have friends but I don’t put myself out there to make friends I would rather just die than feel so lonely all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I was today years old when I found out that I don’t really know how to work my iPhone! I need my photos be look… https://t.co/mN4CdmRKxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna say thank you so much to Donny @Starbucks #Store9599 for jumping in to help me out this morning when the issu… https://t.co/rpeAvIJq6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[R u serious? Is this a joke? @MarshallRamsey @MSUBASE @HailStateBB @clarionledger #notajoke #newsportseditor https://t.co/gFv4lYdI8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gianna Jessen makes America look like cowards on abortion! https://t.co/RKqk1QuXIs via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Family Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/5FoWWyjSYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @NBCNews @ABC @FoxNews @CNN Anyone watching 60 Mins knows we have a Criminal in the White House.… https://t.co/wFzDCGVb6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those people who say they’re strong, are not. Giving up is for weak people. So if you give up, you’re weak🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @trumps_feed @POTUS well  they use the wrong term most of fox is trump state not USA state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ButterzSomebody @Amy_Siskind Well, I was pretty sure from the get go that he didn't make it himself. But from what… https://t.co/ouGOotF8UV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickie1023 Thank God. I mean I keep rolling this over in my mind and I can't get over how terrible this was for y… https://t.co/C8td0koNVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so angry and sad rn that I could literally scream until I couldn’t anymore buttttt I have an audition tomorrow 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahDeeth @CHEXNewswatch Thanks for thoroughly covering this.  Its appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[about to see the queen 👑 @ Bankers Life Fieldhouse https://t.co/KpzOUYK3jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonReedman Yes , I know , but it's the crazy fans that totally ruined it for everyone.  The mobbing , the pushi… https://t.co/VxpZoCOrDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The secret world of content moderators: The Trauma Floor (via @Pocket) #longreads https://t.co/7KwxMKhJLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerrylifeloves All. The. Time.   Remember this #bloggers: https://t.co/tGaHVuOR3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[never felt so much happier than finishing my chemistry homework, biology homework, and calculus homework :') #productivityatitsfinest]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Soup kind of day 🥣 God bless my grandma for making it and my couch, my couch is awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how my boyfriends sister tried to get us kicked out knowing that I’m pregnant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post #5k...Hot shower... Tylenol... snack... and watching bohemianrhapsodymovie for the 4th time! Never tire of my… https://t.co/RRL3PhxuyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @chastuff LOOK it up! It's in the BIBLE!!!  JESUS was a JEW!!! HE was of THE Tribe of Judah. HIS GREAT… https://t.co/jUt8GZIqza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flowhisto @EvilTwinBrewing @GoodBeerTweet @imdrinkingnow @UKBeerNetwork @Beersies @IanStew55902399 @beeryeti… https://t.co/pQk7BbUz5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn my boyfriend and I both have deep ass dimples and now I'm lowkey worried our children might not lol they're my… https://t.co/gfwU5iufAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorDScott @charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris She wanted him to remember a house party he never attended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I get pulled over my joyful self says “hi how are you doing?!” to the cop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shoutout to Popeyes for bringing back garlic pepper wicked chicken. I owe everything to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesMchlmcgnn Hopefully the wheels will come off the support for Israel’s Government. The acts of genocide, terror… https://t.co/IQcHpMlTK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am driving 3 Hours To Meet @BhadBhabie in Toronto today! Fuck these High winds it’s #bhabieseason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @hmgivingsoul @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @Starofthesea007 @ja2cook… https://t.co/QvMApiqCqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week my students worked on argumentative writing by becoming attorneys and defending their clients in "The Cas… https://t.co/Jh59O7NcZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bo knows.  #mlb #baseball #boknows #bojackson #topps #royals #kansascity https://t.co/a38bJQ7EAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old Coast Guard station in Jackson Harbor. Conflicting info about where and when a lifeboat station first went into… https://t.co/vND4A7zcRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amikos, si me ven en el celular durante la conferencia estoy sirviendo en redes sociales.  No me juzguen 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[He satisfies me with good things and makes me young again, like the eagle. Psalm 103:5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brujaaverde @johnnnarose It’s a foundation. As for setting spray I’ve always been one for Mac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnellturner1 Thank you for the laughs and coming to NY!! https://t.co/tfQOGOiL1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way was I going to miss seeing my mentor and friend receive an award. Love her to pieces. Congratulations Dr. Ma… https://t.co/V8PL4R3OwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modacitylife Given my jealousy levels, I may have to unfollow you guys...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedofroses2001 @Kaibutsu SMH!!! This teacher needs her certification pulled...no questions asked, no reinstatement!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #jacksonreyeswedding #paeznychair #badass #elegant at the same time @ Alessandra Paez at Manespace https://t.co/2kut2NX5uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonafideSlimm Ok nevermind lmao i just went back and looked at the track list for Confessions 😅 its better than 8701]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joliekerr While I think the USA needs to convert to metric with the rest of the world, doing it ad hoc in a dating… https://t.co/7wYPaudcMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isaac_Frisby @CoolCat_Carmen @This_Is_Aj Luv u queen💞🥰 https://t.co/gVQ529PYmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT IF... @WATERPARKS TOURED WITH @VICTORIAJUSTICE LIKE IMAGINE HOW LIT THAT WOULD BE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gokulr @onepeloton Wait, like a TV or just the peleton screen? Because if he can watch TV and keep up in peloton classes, I'm impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went on a big drive through some American countryside today. It was weird and cool to listen to country music radio… https://t.co/UBGv6sFj3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_First_Man_ @DrRJKavanagh @MassRoots @GreenCultureMMJ How can their ‘by the book’ actions make them look bad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FashionNova I'm not sure I agree with this. And not just because I detest Oprah. But failure may inspire, motivate… https://t.co/T6w6tw9ZIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work with this great man. Congratulations, Bryan Frost. Proud to be an Elk. #1HERD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinjonesin2016 Erin you are the best. So many worthy ideas! Can not wait to see where you go and what you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakekaihewalu Will he be reviewing anything Wednesday or is he just leaving us like that lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyMoms 1st visit for my 3 year old niece and 1 year old nephew starts today..... I just know they will fall in… https://t.co/nl6YvvMVDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sad I missed this - would have loved to see the Grey Cup in #ygk! I 💚 the @CFL 🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Congress should approve #Trump funds to build the wall to stop illegal immigration and to hire border patrol offic… https://t.co/hInbdErywY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber  I loved the way you asked Lewandowski if he was afraid of the Mueller report because he… https://t.co/i3dicOVJGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMuscutt @MuscuttRachel She is. Thank God. She had a tear in her atrium of her heart, hip fracture, multiple ri… https://t.co/35aNbU4A2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Nobody cares that you had a nice dinner with your murdering dictator boyfriend!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@litsafari @viet_t_nguyen Thank you for having me at your school. Meant so much!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GS_Trophy18 @rogerfederer @norinchi_df @camerlengo73_2 @theljubicic Both]]></document><document><![CDATA[DQ biscuits and gravy and a moo-latte are bringing back way too many high school breakfast memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Supkeke You always serving the best looks and living your best life! Love you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warwickripd good evening all y'all! One of my top two favorite groups. I just had to tell you for dinner tonight I… https://t.co/TV5XoaZhoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoThenIfNotMe @LadyRedWave @OrenIShiKiddo Exactly and we are in this war for our Nation it is not about Left vs r… https://t.co/8aU6PWRd3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary we need you please think long and hard about this, these are dire circumstances.  We need your expertise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since its named after @reymysterio I hooked myself up with the #619 quesadilla https://t.co/lwTFfGpnzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[a man was raving about how it isnt “right” for women to shave their heads and i told him he cant be upset w me if i… https://t.co/REzvDEt6Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would he be wrong? 110%  Would she be wrong? 110% It goes both ways, no one should be putting their hands on anyone… https://t.co/0dAZXwv99j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worked with this kid on Modern Family.  He is a little adult.  Like this pick is him in person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pregnant #pregnancy #almost17weekspregnant #taco #baby #almosthalfway @ Northeast Minneapolis https://t.co/oRKTZPkk1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganAronson I write in books if I own them. Mostly, I write in craft books, though - rarely in fiction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellejade198 @NursingTimes Proud + thankful we have nurses like you, Danielle. Are wesome #leader you are! As t… https://t.co/H1BIxQPVbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krqe BREAKING : Department of Corrections Cabinet Secretary designate Julie Jones declines position. Cites persona… https://t.co/nwzz9NgZ2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Shs4lt2Ig6 IVE BEEN WAITING TO HEAR THIS OMG GUYS EVERYONE LISTEN @BEAMILLER AND @6LACK KILLED THIS ON… https://t.co/d4IltKhK8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind on Thursday. View. * * * * * #views #wind #amosartphotos #amosart #amosartstudio #AngelaOrtiz #photographer… https://t.co/8suXh7bkm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[next day song is cut and playing in a club she gets signed immediately. next day she goes on a date with gr manager… https://t.co/k7YyM0pGFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[After cats, you now make the videos of cats to amuse others: | Life Before Cats... #mirth #chuckle #grin #funny https://t.co/gQGWz7kbzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkoturner Uh... same. Also feeling V. Roasted right now. https://t.co/RSLXnL0Jvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[California's death penalty &amp; proposition 66... https://t.co/nnWIjGEkyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should have been done 2 years ago ..but..Republicans are either compromised as well OR afraid of trump/Russia...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hammy_sam_ Noooo I wish that show was on a Friday so I didn’t have to get up for work. Are you going to that show?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help but dance around my apartment while cooking breakfast when Sinatra radio is on 💃]]></document></documents></author>