<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KashaDavis @RuPaulsDragRace @RuPaul @michellevisage @WorldOfWonder @VH1 @eufratees Agreed]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first trailer for Jordan Peele's Twilight Zone reboot is here  https://t.co/as97xbC9Xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/71XG2jO5ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of another cold and snowy shift in an Infiniti QX80 #trucksofinstagram #suv #qx80 #infinitiqx80 #winter… https://t.co/764o3EYWNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanDawsonUSA You are probably the stupidest person on the planet , it's no wonder the Democrapic party is the pa… https://t.co/qyBCZtl1nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @reneelflorida @M_Gossard @InsRecoveryLaw @KathleenSeide @smalltwngirl78 @c_poesy @BriWrites @brianhartz… https://t.co/D9ASVRiU29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooksACarter My first single Brandon Bing- “Sunday Funday” dropped this weekend and is available on iTunes, Spoti… https://t.co/og5EIzmNI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what’s up with this Jonas brothers reunion? I’m trying not to get too excited because I don’t want to get my hop… https://t.co/cFiMSpH8NZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonynorthrup @gwphotographe @SarahRamsingh You might hate it at first, but once you understand it, damnit is it a… https://t.co/99JNxPSmjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like everybody's celebrating this soon-to-be snowstorm by eating Mass amounts of carbs should Jeff jump on this bandwagon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really hesitant to do this 10 year challenge thing, but I’m all about opening up and showing vulnerability no… https://t.co/oNTNyIZ9Ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I see people down and people who I have love and respect for!! If there’s anyone that’s feeling down. D… https://t.co/ba8DAhbhCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t lie to you, I like it when I see big time TV personalities wearing an ashen cross on #AshWednesday. Amen. https://t.co/XrdXPuy8HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least the kids at UC Merced will be able to party in boppin’ Bakersfield. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/WofoZztBde https://t.co/XlCy6AE8JM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Letter To My Ex by Pleasure P https://t.co/CyJKDVdUIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do y’all moms give racist names to dumbass drivers? 🤔🤔   My moms go to’s include but aren’t limited to:  Becky  Lin… https://t.co/pnIvmB8n2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Scripture #scripture #scriptureoftheday #bible #bibleverse #biblequote #godisgood #godisgreat #roswell… https://t.co/uiGLLufn8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darlene33036869 @Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/bzCzjLPQ6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think they’re about to euthanize they’re tweets after this savage clapback]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BogusLWAW U nasz na Bródnie obok szkoły stał saturator automatyczny. Za zeta była sodowa z sokien a za 50 gr czyst… https://t.co/lwv3HtoLgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Donald trump, ‘God’ fearing man of the average American... https://t.co/foAIV3XdYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[U godda have tenacity and perfect execution when dealing with these spics and niggas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So there's this anti-fanduel post going around screaming "fanduel is rigged". Just bc u dont win, doesnt mean its r… https://t.co/2MQmwKSf0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Love you but Trump will have to decide what he wants to do in spite of the resistance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/SZTiWJ5kMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @kelly_clarkson tonight here in Chicago then @NBCTheVoice returns Monday night!!! #LifeIsGood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyteisLIVE I’m alright bro. Heard them words and just wanted share them with my peeps👍🏻 #LifeHappens]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met the LEGEND @mcleodbob this weekend at my local comic convention. He was so cool and nice! It should have been… https://t.co/1BrT220ikX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your sitting on your laurels, you're wearing them on the wrong part of your body. - #DavidLeeRoth 2019 - so fucking good. 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Los Angeles! :) #Sunrise 07:10, noon 13:03, sunset 18:57 PDT (UTC-7), March 10. Day length: 11h 47m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wayne Rooney gets us underway as @dcunited takes on the @TampaBayRowdies in preseason action at Al Lang. https://t.co/8XxLx86ldN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches who openly admit that they don’t like to drink water give me no choice to believe that their 🐱 ain’t right 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in the holy hell could this number be as high as 37% - I guess mental illness is a much bigger problem than we… https://t.co/Gpie4auXWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pixxydoodle @BlackLab79 @low_nascar @ISMRaceway @IronMountain @low_nascar2 @SharonKarkowsk2 @KEMMOCupSeries That w… https://t.co/nLhAt3stTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veraktla gorgeous view from Aliso and Wood Canyon in Aliso Viejo today! https://t.co/HYjrpk8zmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I don’t go a week without wishing someone a happy bday on my stories 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_chloe_gp @myparentsrdeaf @_Chloe_gp is 100% right I hope five for Yell wins the election 🗳🥇👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thatsright6581 @CBPSanDiego @WhiteHouse There were over 300 mass shootings in the US last year, almos all by Ameri… https://t.co/QTfY82lqik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving around (@ City of @BellevueWa in WA) https://t.co/qdi4iAsym1 https://t.co/3oDcLIDvvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamin2g The media wanted to ask him “why people are leaving the party” two days after a bunch of MPs left the Part… https://t.co/iGdRibxnMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my new video  https://t.co/qhY3Y0QTDV https://t.co/A8VbBCoffV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadMoneyOnCNBC @jimcramer Jim is that 2 day upside down head and shoulders pattern on the QQQ SIGNIFICANT .. I had… https://t.co/BOcUtSrzeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxSportsRadio ben have a which president said this contest . Throw out some quotes. And dont forget geico quotes lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Ponce de Leon said he changed his name from Poncedeleon on his jersey simply to restore it to the original s… https://t.co/Z4F4WSOlfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael2014abc @IlhanMN They could have saved a lot of ink and grief by just saying, "We condemn hating anyone except Trump supporters."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazNuttycombe @CNN The face he made when asked to part between Trump &amp; Pence needs to be a new reaction image https://t.co/KIYs8oYJUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#prenatalmassage #relaxing #facials #hotstonemassage #reflexology #physio #therapeutic #pain #healthy #recovery… https://t.co/D0ME1Fl2Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimmersNapa @JamesMartinSJ I read the Catechism. Who made me? God made me (God made EVERYBODY). In whose IMAGE did… https://t.co/j3QfGlhvvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day in #kitchenerwaterloo today! Get out and enjoy!  #kwawesome #Coffee #RealEstate #morning #meetings https://t.co/0mvCVOxJwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmcurran @JoeNBC @realDonaldTrump ...and you know this how? You have a Top Secret Crypto clearance and sat in on h… https://t.co/HQhfIDfe7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadpool dance party #marvel #deadpool #danceparty #sandeigo #california #sandeigocomiccon #comiccon #summer… https://t.co/2SwtlPse23]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go, my favorite rivalry in football!☕️📺⚽️ #MyPLMorning  #MUNLIV #PL #MUFC #LFC https://t.co/HqXg75UajL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9NEWS 82k per game. My wife and I barely made more than that last YEAR.  Question. Who need that much money? Answe… https://t.co/2YL1NcfQu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavePMN @anthonyhauck @HyparAEC Above. Definitely above. Super cold for Texas though. I moved here to STOP competing for low temps. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whitefish_Salad I agree. More government = bigger gap between rich and poor]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few things I love ... 1. Sleeping on freshly cleaned sheets 2. Showering in a freshly cleaned shower. Things I di… https://t.co/LElfzEuwZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Scott Disick Syndrome is back and I’m going to try my best not to drive home inebriated...   too late. Pray for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaPaz aye think you could beat Putin 1-1 in basketball? He's strong, and he's big. He is also athletic. But, I du… https://t.co/sk0Bcc8z6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My business is bombing again thanks to “I’ll pay you later”. &lt;-$180.00&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IL0VEthe80s Mine was a 65 fastback mustang that I drained my savings account to buy!!  Wish I still had it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirginiaSmall6 @OpenSecretsDC @AOC Who is mainstream? What is normal? Is it relative?]]></document><document><![CDATA[NWO-CGI recognise USA as the shining lihht on the hill attracting too many for their globalists plans.… https://t.co/rnVeBDpMz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend made a Children of the Corn reference. Proud boyfriend right now #proudboyfriend #horror… https://t.co/t9jL1Q0LsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redban @Tesla @elonmusk You leveled up. That’s what you’ve done. She’s a beaut Clarke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonRosen @dongattack Have you called Adam to thank him and congrate him on 10 years!!!🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Beaten in comparison to murdered? There’s no contest. Lucky to still have his life. Be blessed with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1.375B for 55 miles of barrier equals $4,734 per foot. That seems a bit expensive. #BorderWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #SanFrancisco #Giants team 1965-2016, pitchers.  https://t.co/RMCz2UfYtd … … https://t.co/eY25TWuD9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[No need to worry about getting there with traffic since you’ll have to travel by boat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FireMooneyMafia @Newf_Finl_Solns Hey now, lets not take my name in vain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmoxnews your story said the Republican from Ballwin would like to address inequities in justice system(as in CURR… https://t.co/lWL2Fjv8Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xan_desanctis Like shockingly horrendous. I hope you didn't read the article before you tweeted this, because if y… https://t.co/i7vg8vS3xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly Thank you for your stand. I am so tired of being called a deplorable when my heart is full of love for… https://t.co/LYpW2rXMfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LwmSr It might be a little mutherfucker but by god I can see mine at 50 haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand up for peace and refuse to allow President Trump to send military troops to Venezuela or to its border region… https://t.co/YBs0Vv1r2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taxpayer Advocate Reports On Top Challenges Facing IRS, Naming Outdated Tech Systems #1 https://t.co/ZFBoPjIwlK https://t.co/mR4vXdUNsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing show!!  If you haven’t seen Newsies get out tomorrow for the 2:00pm show. You won’t be sorry!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnsmntfuture All in thou reminds me more of kobe pe but purple jumpman vs his yellow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freefaln94 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Your politicians aren't in tune with your thoughts. Let's take renewable energy for example.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjferri32 It’s only because they stink and I like reminding rangers fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanRomberger @AOC I don't need nor want their help. You all live in this entitled world. The 1% does pay their fa… https://t.co/zf5VwXQIKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could NEVER date a girl with a lazy eye. Sounds bad but imagine having to ask her if she’s seeing other guys when… https://t.co/HVHinsqIfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexandrVans @naxyi_alexandra @KIRILL_aka_KID @Le1ardo @dilenser @moscow_sity @Deadinternet У меня пол седьмого ут… https://t.co/KPpKsxlKqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited Legacy Reserve at Fritz Farm to speak as a part of their #BlackHistoryMonth programming. Took the opportuni… https://t.co/IOjsZcmdEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire That’s a great idea! Nobody wants another AOC socialist wondering on the face of this earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCall is sick and tired and there’s a good chance he’s getting tossed today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone worried about the environment can now rest easy. Think I have it handled. I’m now using vegan shampoo. You are welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream is to have a shop to work on cars and a place to store me and my dads cars and sport bikes 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[man I’m so blessed to be in this position in life. I just wanna be able to take care of the ones I love 🤞🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing changes...🦋 If nothing changes‼️ #grow #improve #change . . . . . . . . . . #springpreserve #lasvegas… https://t.co/ZeJ1E0TEBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DnDGeologist Oh wow thanks! Fighting isn’t hai favorite, but I’m sure he’d love to take up arms alongside your PCs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real Teddy Roosevelt laid the cornerstone of the National Cathedral in 1907, and today the @Nationals Teddy Roo… https://t.co/KRxQ9eyZQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got tonight bobseger @fox5vegas mgmresortsintl @ MGM Grand Garden Arena https://t.co/4wHIQL64n0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Totally 80s Bar &amp; Grille https://t.co/vG0PQUEjsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Backstorymom1 Hillary started the birther BS! she and the MSM projected her lies onto trump.. which he researched… https://t.co/ZM85aXeozm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zmanbrianzane Never knew this was a thing but now I kinda really want it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishkat123 @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr None of those MSM orgs have an Oval Office bureau.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know we are desperate to buy a van that when a van was mentioned on forensic files I immediately went "ooooooo van"   Give us yer van.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you smell like shit, you know who won’t smell it? You! Everyone else will smell it but if everyone is locked in… https://t.co/Xn5ZC5Zjx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea we know! But w the support of #MSM it is hard to make the case over the long term. The SPLC believes the ends j… https://t.co/c8e2mhBJ4D]]></document></documents></author>