<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The kids ate at Logan's Roadhouse and started driving to a movie theater. The car crash happened just before 10 p.m… https://t.co/TtyxZyXGbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nominated for 11 Academy Awards, winning 8, including: - Best Picture - Best Director - Best Actor - Best Adapted S… https://t.co/fROlXqoU2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa.  What a memory.  Not seen on live TV.  Could you imagine that now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs Bell turns 21.  Maggoo and Mommy too said I better not post this?  #daddyknowsbest @ Cafe Amore https://t.co/GdjGyGqAlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squatcher @CliffBarackman Oh, and that is a Baby! Id' bet my left crusty Italian nut!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not crying about the opportunity mission, I just have some dust in my eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[To anyone wondering.... #FoodForThought #OneToGrowOn #Inspirational #Motivational #Positive #Powerful #Affirmations… https://t.co/NRgt9uBbag]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we just take a minute to talk about how this my baby! https://t.co/23JP8EgbmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m almost 100% convinced we’re going to see the end of the world happen during our lifetimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[USDA @SecretarySonny on stage with with his Canadian and Mexican counterparts during the opening session of the 95t… https://t.co/fDO37S7qi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby @BreitbartNews Sooooo? Send them back where they came from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@studentactivism @InsideEdition What is the principle here? Majority of MTA operating revenue comes from fares. How… https://t.co/453nXGckMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iske43 Summer means motorcycles!! Kinda ready to.. just have to get past the “s” word....... snow....]]></document><document><![CDATA[These pictures don't even do this park justice... 🤯 . . . #bigbend #bigbendnationalpark #chisosmountains… https://t.co/oz8P2sOru9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewKahn Everyone who has to possibly cover the 3 seed in the 9:30 pm slot https://t.co/x5mSiIoFWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because “conflict of interest” is not in this Administration’s vocabulary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance4gardener @JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @woodywood1999 @MichaelZaker1 @TaggartRehnn @someone_1958 @wolflayla420… https://t.co/fIykNdAGDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanderMobusVO @ErikaHarlacher How disappointing, which girl from persona 5?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePhang Ewww. Why would he grab that when he’s been wiping his ass with it for so long?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claytonramick I told the boys to throw the game in OT. You’re welcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum Idea:  congressman on the floor discussing something changing into chimps shouting Russia Russia Russ… https://t.co/NROQC9NWi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[1970: Despite hemp’s strong commercial record and decades of government-funded research proving industrial hemp to… https://t.co/VyaTP4pmuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Why would you have raw cotton in your house? Who would have this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dance10Nico why you so thick 🙄🍑. You should show your ass off more it’s a gift from the god of asses 😂👑🍑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 *thing.   (come on @Twitter add a freaking edit button!!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny but sweet memes | funny animal memes, animal pictures with captions, funny animals https://t.co/jKN2Fb5EIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darinbunch Your urgency is a lot higher than most people I talk to and I find this interesting. So you think they’… https://t.co/8rP6Ob9sIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the Dallas area this weekend.   @TupeloHoneyTX on Friday and sixspringslive on Saturday.  mcmusic82 on ba… https://t.co/nEpj5zvKyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann I agree it is way past time. I didn't think I would ever say this but,I am ashamed of our country. We are… https://t.co/GmpI2kPLlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @DaneLIoyd coming to the riding where we visited @LaCulturaSalumi @BAY_OF_QUINTE @BellevilleON Councillor… https://t.co/cgNdPNuYi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLarter Great plan.   Step 0: allocate sufficient resources for the fleet we have today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Good Morning sraff, crew, Joel, @SteveDoocy @ainsleyearhardt @kilmeade @jillianmele and @JaniceDean… https://t.co/Bjzih8pmjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy my family had the chance to visit me and watched me play my last game in the Dunkin donut center..  Also t… https://t.co/oKaWtmZtmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_riddle It’s against my personal rules to invest in merchandise for my team that isn’t in alignment with the br… https://t.co/f7SQA3ENDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcGhazvini @FLforBernie @KamalaHarris Like I said earlier Mark I think it’s going to be a grand system as I plan… https://t.co/HP6Pej64jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgrant I’ll do my best, I won’t be on the main carpet but I’ll be at a few]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Darcizzle_ @WassmannBill I bet by the looks of things ,,, it must be yours.  Happy Birthday 🍧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe y’all see Brie larsons acting as “dry” but isn’t she supposed to be a alien or something so she’s supposed to… https://t.co/mVFyDN92Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If reprogrammed funds were designated to be spent on a Michigan specific project or program, the the state has stan… https://t.co/1pmcSTMFk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women are my 🦸‍♀️ hero#happywomansday#felizdiadelamujer#godovereverything#blessed#happywifehappylife#jalisco#mexico… https://t.co/XPecOFPVaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC As a man raised by Southern parents, I know the place Mama holds in your heart and how she formed your soul… https://t.co/HyUeDRI9oP]]></document><document><![CDATA[lucas rly leaned up for a kiss and eliott rly just ran his hand through his hair and left,,,, and you could literal… https://t.co/wEgaDnNps7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, new guys @hbo how do we petition to get another season of @CrashingHBO ? The show has only gotten better, why… https://t.co/64l0frRmM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kraft is a billionaire yet we are to believe he went to an regular old Asian massage parlor for a $60 rub and tug? Idk man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clarkson, Love lead Cavaliers past Magic 107-93  https://t.co/0uPG13T4fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not mentally prepared for the UM vs MSU game tomorrow for the B1G Title]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 5:29pm EST - #529plans and #ABLEaccounts help all families to save and save efficiently. Cheers to a great da… https://t.co/ykni6YN5FT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElielColina @Tom_Russell16 You have 8 seconds to get a 2 for 1 possession and you shoot a 3 when “the goat” could… https://t.co/2oCuFkA79u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mauro, pasa q Natacha no se subió al colectivo de actrices verdes. Así q no interesa si la violaron 35 orangutanes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyraDeBiase @AugieD5 @MMcLaughlinsong @lancevantine @ToddTrotter3 @SmithRandyUSA @sgmski2 @hickoryhill8520… https://t.co/hpmuISO8v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Panthers hosting the Red Wings this afternoon in Sunrise, FL https://t.co/my7pNfhI4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why we post what we post on here 2 make people aware of what really is happening this ain't no joke hate gr… https://t.co/2x23L6mGmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatwestboxing @UnkhanciousAmir Why do you care tho? Stop changing the subject]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does a player get a technical for looking at another player? Absolutely ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International womens day to all the women I know from Twitter. May you have a day filled with nothing but awe… https://t.co/x3bWkoJSzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashida_Linda @WickedEdTech @RiggsRealWorld @davejwallace @bruggsb @JoyKirr Thanks for the RT, Linda! Your insights… https://t.co/l2fw595D5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love KO, but if they just yanked Kofi out of #Fastlane and won’t give us #KofiMania at #WrestleMania you gonna ha… https://t.co/7dnzedxcOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaFreshhPrince @cxltmatic @HotNewHipHop Dudes saying that this isn’t even news they are just taking every chance… https://t.co/vOFwwFZx5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jokotri Kalau sekadar air mentah, tiap hari di sini orang juga minum air mentah, langsung dari keran nggak pakai dimasak dulu 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 20 years through the Education System, I am super stoked to say that I am officially finished with school for… https://t.co/WAFEYTdpvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 RDX A SPEC! 272 HP 2.0L TURBO w all the safety technology you need. Come test drive this awesome vehicle! You… https://t.co/vvCE2IMSy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[God loves PEOPLE more than anything! So thankful to share the WORD and to utilize my gift to encourage PEOPLE today… https://t.co/1GpkaSuUoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with my old man is a huge  honor. I love every second I'm able to see him. Love this song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Bots do something #Sabres #NHLTradeDeadline #Tradedeadline2019 #TradeCentre https://t.co/1OzEuZPLIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@th0tttty @CaptainLexus We’ll schedule a meeting for a first class next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democratic National Committee has voted down a ban on corporate PAC donations https://t.co/hUoN1fDHA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSmith4680 Guys you do realize we're talking about the most CORRUPT city in America??🤫  The city that gave us B… https://t.co/zSZjQwB9q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Griffith park Observatory observed LA approaching dusk, cloudy March evening with light spots of rain. #losangeles… https://t.co/3aOwT5hsqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fb_LewGriswold @FresnoBee Thank you for all your work! Love the jacket 😊👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileyCountyPD Moronic operation of a motor vehicle in a traffic circle will most likely earn the operator a citati… https://t.co/VZPK7sWCkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DespinaBarton @PatrickWelter @OrlandoCitySC Swag=Tweet. #HT @OrlandoCitySC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OceansStorm ...and adding to expansive list of items to try when I make my way out to the left coast again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing the ol charger, 😤 I think it’s time it goes up for sale https://t.co/vOfcY2IVMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just touched down at @DENAirport. I saw the Rocky Mountains on my final approach and I damn-near started to tear up… https://t.co/7C4v6om3HB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s all live every moment as if you’re an ecstatic Olivia Colman accepting your Oscar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KP_4_lyfe We're at our friends in Elgin and they're white and watching it now. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog And Trump gets 1 step closer to fascism and absolute power. Jis goal all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubymay1993 Doesn't get any better than that.. unadulterated curl your toes kinda raw passion..  it's incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSchweigert Started with Louisville Cardinals. Just took the opportunity to give you a hard time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of great quotes this week   Little know fact but "tiny shoes" is now jakes new nickname]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrible,  it needs to be totally shut down, unless it can operate with 100% renewable energy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#perfectpoolday #happyvalentinesday @ Fairways Royale Association https://t.co/78Po7hY1J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTuckFrumper Thanks for posting this...good to know how profoundly wrong these trump toadies are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Gringo Loco by @Prohibitionbc @ Tina's Deli — https://t.co/DupV7bd4qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minute terrorism is my new favorite term for an annoying prank. https://t.co/TNKxJTmvkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyJusino hey what is your new Cell phone number and unblock me please]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss just thanked the coworker and said I need to be more thorough before calling a job complete. In not sure wh… https://t.co/JEbgP8EhUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at the 49th Annual Cal State University Long Beach Puvungna PowWow  shirt by brown_wear_apparel hat by… https://t.co/h2UXLKRmRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫You Love Me Anyway by @swprophets, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/eeHA5o3RKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson Why haven’t you fired Luke yet? What more do you need to see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#harleydavidson #dealership #canam #brp #bikes #bikesforsale #atv #offroad #toys #available #dealsdealsdeals… https://t.co/7xZCcYoq4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was I just changed almost $90 this month when I agreed to pay $34 a month?? @24hourfitness @24HourFitHelp https://t.co/mzrck29gJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal budgets are a reflection of our values. This budget proposal in it's current form does not exemplify a comm… https://t.co/GVwdP6lBu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just trying to get to Sullivan (400yds away) but there's bumper to bumper traffic and the bus can't get through #BanCars]]></document><document><![CDATA[The painting helps to get rid of the bad feelings.The painting helps me to go forward in the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VazquezK08 He’s been good bro since college. But he’s impressed in the NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsBoyTony I remember him! My twin brother and I were around 10 years old. He never let kids on the air.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another closet racist defending an indefensible video. It literally begins with the cop walking to the vehicle, com… https://t.co/5PXSBghe0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spontaneous round of applause breaks out here on board AA1410 as they manage to get us airborne from STL after 2 1/… https://t.co/Clt9ojbK6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to say Happy Valentine’s Day to my arms for always being by my side, my fingers because I could always… https://t.co/fuPrdRoWdG]]></document></documents></author>