<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Jim Jordan is truly despicable &amp; a huge hypocrite. #TrumpLoyalist #CohenCongressionalTestimony #GymJordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get out of having to scrub a case and can actually eat lunch.. https://t.co/WCf4sLdufq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I posted a video on my IG story of all these girls getting cat called and grabbed on the street and said “men ain’t… https://t.co/4cv8PDJX2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Remedy Intelligent Staffing? We're hiring in #PanamaCity, FL! Click the link in our bio for details… https://t.co/lWRv5W4WCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mothertime62 @StephenKing My brother did. It ate up most of his pay as a bartender. He had to drop it to survive.… https://t.co/0TqJv51UGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPersnickety @Steelerschic85 @L_a_w_a_n_n_a @TeahCartel @TanziaMill @TalkToMeForReal @Suzyqfit4u @CindyinMemphis2… https://t.co/od0Vy2cZkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZenobiaK @amandadeibert @CatStaggs @ashleyn1cole @cmclymer @docrocktex26 @carolineframke @AngryBlackLady @mckerrin… https://t.co/0HaUrVQpHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all: no one with anxiety would ever wear this!!  me: yeah unless it came in pink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tombx7M @leslieau7 And people who steal power instead of earning it are always afraid that people will find out that they are frauds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders 1/2 I’m curious to learn more about the proposals for restitutions. Do you have any resources? Also- I’… https://t.co/e1jkp5SMCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thergeorge Oh but before I go: I absolutely love love love booksellers and of course bookstores and if ever I can… https://t.co/sh7LycOkpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@247MXMB @MostRequestLive @jonasbrothers @KarianneRadio @OfficialMonstaX #Alligator #MONSTA_X #MONBEBEありがとう 😡… https://t.co/OtuRkrGlye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epoch_awakening @notch Can’t wait to see how this all plays out. If anything, people are talking/ sort of starting… https://t.co/xI4hIS1EYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was doing so good &amp; i was happy. i really hope God doesnt make this go away..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheryllyndunn Good Night Cheryle Direct Mesaage me ill give you my number i love calling all of my friends love ya… https://t.co/ZQFtLEFiGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EfcMikee @soph_thfc lollllllllol her nose isn’t big! but guarantee it’s bigger than your sad excuse for a dick you… https://t.co/RrhNjoZoFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This annoys me. I have a craving for something and it’s so cold I don’t want to go out!! Why can’t @UberEats and… https://t.co/o1pCMt2IKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas be begging for pussy pics, but soon as you ask for a dick pic ITS A PROBLEM 🤦🏻‍♀️ like wtf😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dual Language Learners: A National Demographic and Policy Profile. https://t.co/XVhOHrULmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got 2 shirts for free from Express yesterday because I had $20 in reward points. I didn’t even think I shopped there that much]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s always a fucking misogynist in the audience, and in this case that misogynist is accusing sexual assault su… https://t.co/4x6Tjozx8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[And “Christians” voted for (and still support!) the man who orchestrated this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop buying heather stuff, I just want to get her everything bc I know she’ll LOVE it. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAnnWest @CuffyMeh I got my AA from a comm college in LA (where I lived) and transferred to SDSU for my BA. ev… https://t.co/JAscNmZhem]]></document><document><![CDATA[me after I hit bombs (or ya know just a single) at alumni @peytonamiller @laurmariemeyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came out yesterday!! Watch to stay updated on school events and other activities!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Franklin Boulevard &amp; Cosumnes River Boulevard in Sacramento, CA https://t.co/ESHiJ93F9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMajere2 I was just in Baltimore not too long ago honey maybe I’ll do DC next time I’m in that vicinity have a great weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeRooCruise stays calling me and he knows I hate talking on the phone 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregVorse @__clutchins @parkschoolbflo @SPECNewsBuffalo @nysswa @MonsignorMartin @GregVorse ...thank you!  This is so nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidakin @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas Because he disagrees. As simple as that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Williams crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 02:44:28, pace 13:16 min/mile, est. finish 10:28 am https://t.co/OT3ECsfEik #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[38. В своей грязной ветхой одежде, местами заклеенной скотчем, с огромной белой бородой и невероятно светлым и добр… https://t.co/OKwAb1NrJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help @Americans4Arts develop their online Public Art Showcase series! Take this brief survey and share your thought… https://t.co/bEXaaqPtQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🥰Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/7LH9i8ilkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond We're lucky you appreciate your fans like you do. There are some entertainers who aren't as receptive… https://t.co/23NXL2mDy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are TWO DAYS left to submit Statesman Torch Resumes!! As always, feel free to reach out to me with any questi… https://t.co/IKMxJazkbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandachisholm5 @kay_hallsworth @KCLSecurity @DefenceResearch @warstudies @cheng_christine @claudia_aradau… https://t.co/TUn3O4cftT]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the night begins. #toastedravs #friedcheese #thehillstl #garthbrooks #nextstopplease @ Joey B's On the Hill https://t.co/wpZJXPtd36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuddyBowman4 @admiralelite15 Yes was God's good keep up the good work I love oranges God blessings lol Tennessee up yeayaya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Third) are you a dog, because they don’t see “color” either, but they have a heightened sense of smell and hearing to call BS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s Up Wednesday!   What’s your favorite Oreo flavor?   #Nationaloreoday https://t.co/v9F1c7Z0ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched the amazing, Oscar-winning short, "Period. End of Sentence." on @netflix. Highly recommend checking it… https://t.co/EJhvgXdWFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews What about the millions of American you have insulted every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your Valentine's Day started right! Feeling the ❤ from our amazing choir students. Thanks, Bears #WALC https://t.co/NpFWKMxds3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods needs to start a YouTube channel and her first video needs to be “Taking a Lie Detector Test”]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love @jrgoldberg because he ALWAYS knows the right thing to say. even on his own damn birthday. 💐🥀 https://t.co/nhLKDpAxnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally stfu . some people have a hard time communicating their feelings, especially those of us who suffer from… https://t.co/IumXA21Nru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine @VetApologist And I believe she's a DemocRAT with a racist agenda towards ANYONE Who disagrees with her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great session on hotel contract negotiations #connectchicago #tompasha @KalahariMeeting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeehanCarolAnne @StuntmanStu Just like the rest of the city has waited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #WCPHX folks, we’re at #lustrerooftopbar with @wpmodder @marktimemedia @royboy789 @RobertJacobi. Y’all know you wanna come...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artificial intelligent and algorithms and robotics are taking over jobs. In 5-10 years 44% of our economy will be o… https://t.co/IbsFwt6y7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up from my after-brunch nap on the igloo couch to the boys doing squats in a single-file line in the kitchen… https://t.co/nrvB1l9nao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamriel1776 @dexterwebn What about Teldryn Sero? I think he's a great companion too.😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevekaplowitz being raised in the South I still have never got anybodys fascination with monster trucks maybe it'… https://t.co/i6JOn0Hg2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX13News @FLStrawberryFst Heyyyyyy, I’m home sick....I could use one of those!🍓🍫🍓🍫]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have to convince someone of your worth, they already don’t deserve you. 🗣🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science projects galore #TheBestThingISawToday @NessacusRMS https://t.co/yANAGcxgXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have yet to hear @StevieNicks  do this song live. Didn’t know it was on current setlist.  @smartyshortie thanks for… https://t.co/0zleNwVW29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pressapressa come on press!! Stop playing with me! Let me get on a hook!! I’m from your city!!   https://t.co/gxD8SiGM2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LulaOficial Mais chatice europeias. Cade pressao de verdade contra putaria no Breezyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Fbaq9pbm6c FRANKY BABY, WHO?.. TONY,..WHO??.. CROSBY... WHO??... MY GREAT FRIEND THE BRONZE "SHY" ADON… https://t.co/EbDT8qBO0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[My list of expansion locations for @TheAAF   1. Virginia Beach  2. St. Louis  3. Portland  4. Albuquerque  5. Milwaukee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t post up when you don’t know who you’re talking to. Might just make yourself look stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I get on the Red line, I instantly get high. I honestly think the conductor is blowing smoke through the vents. #contacthigh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlierShME @Octossey_comic @Franklee255B @_SJPeace_ Yep! To kill with impunity...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 100% okay with not having free health care but what’s the point of paying every month for it if I still have t… https://t.co/obDRVOgNMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting to find out if we can take daisy if not me and Jay found a 4 year old Male chihuahua named rainy… https://t.co/pPM5BzHArw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dead ass have been pacing this bedroom contemplating calling the vet at 1am because I thought Nahla has been cryi… https://t.co/qUHooGZ0jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxycharm @CoverFX @wander_beauty @modabrush @AppealCosmetics @OFRACosmetics Very disappointed!Is the language Im… https://t.co/k7ENByf9em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nothingface @msnbc_rocks @nytimes Universal health care and free college could b scrapped too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hashtagmolly @rahblah @NOLA_Fredo I have taken to either standing on or putting my chair on tarps. I’m like “I’m o… https://t.co/JQkgHMQlaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely afternoon with the dynamic Montclair Drifters Organization!  Thank you claudiawoodard1124 for the  wonderful… https://t.co/omFQVwJbxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyJohnsonNews Hi I disagree...Bryce Howard doesn't want to come to philly... why reward with him 325 million dolla… https://t.co/HIjVLoyyq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dadd told me to wash my car but didn’t give me money to wash it ;/  &amp; i need an oil change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast is ready to be served @graceatthegreen by these wonderful young women. #servicelearning https://t.co/PJAAOnSCKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidKubat1 @ReichlinMelnick Its a good thing they are so bad at their jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@activist360 Could Bernie be a Russian Agent? Where does his $$ come from. He &amp; Jill Stein worked hard to defeat HRC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sergiogoyri No permitas que un embustero y ladron como lo es  RicardoR Dañe tu imagen.Lo único que está haciendo e… https://t.co/mFrlMPn9wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was everything.   “And to be a woman is to be in pain.”   Thanks @tomberlin // (and thanks to @pedrothelion fo… https://t.co/Um7KgueBls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uclagymblog @MathewJayCarter confused ? I said if Utah sticks their landings they would not be behind Utah only ha… https://t.co/USabH2JJv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@timcorrimal Another great show this week. You, @Marnus3, @SueinRockville, @SethP23 and @T4booboo did a fantastic… https://t.co/z1VOjO0Ybu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wjameswolf this is what I meant to say I love Yorkville on ;) Dang Twitter newby :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found my spirit animal / Patronus / dæmon. https://t.co/LJPJqHO02D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my parents get this lucky cause that travel ball life ain’t easy😪😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EmergenciaEnDialisis #SinLuz #SOSVenezuela #aidvenezuela #askavenezuelan #blackoutvenezuela #FueraMaduro… https://t.co/7h34svrpXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leerion Of course it is, but Judge Jackson will give him just one more chance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*watching a shark eating a whale carcass on blue planet 2*  my little sister: mukbang!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have my stats class tomorrow from 8am to 12pm...... https://t.co/qD2D8aYhmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seen this yesterday and RT’d and today got a $9.99 charge from a free trial I thought I cancelled on Friday 🤦🏾‍♀️… https://t.co/ZqLQfLTttD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read this review of The Second Wave by Jean Copeland https://t.co/alWhqbdGlk via @LesbianReviews]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite thing abt myself is the fact that i listen to fall out boy unironically]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlachtga Jesus. I am so sorry. I'm glad he's up and feeling better but fuck that is hard to go through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because, once again it’s going to snow/sleet/be-too-icy-to-drive around again tomorrow, so done with this winter.… https://t.co/p9vff0nyno]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have spent so much energy discrediting others, yet no one seems to like you. See how that played out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awkwafina(that Asian chick onstage you don’t know) could do voice over for Lindsay Lohan’s new album and no one would notice. #oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlaBa10578465 @barbaraderegil Por esta razón soy su fan!! No sólo es hermosa por fuera! Por dentro también lo es… https://t.co/tzFW2Y1r4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[As soon as he put the hat on I was like “huh he kinda looks like Johnny Manziel” then BOOM i was right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosannaphillip @cpw_Numenor @LA_Karma1 @Mandalorian_Ren @jhgurf @broadwatertmb @dolfanria13 @shirazme56… https://t.co/Nr0TLTGhG4]]></document></documents></author>