<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes Love You so much!!! It would mean the world to me and it would totally make my day if you followed me!… https://t.co/2EYtGynnNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upgraded our photography website and made a new ig account https://t.co/OnwhyjKp0p | ig: @jechellephotography]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great running into one of my mentors and fellow Women in Gov @maryannborgeson at Women of NACo! @Gov_Women… https://t.co/MTYZXFLjrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[fun first read thru of Li’l Abner tonight! I love old time musicals - and the costumes sure motivate me to stay on track regime-wise.. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myagvng 16 miles 😅😅 idk about that lol you might as well get some authentic Mexican food 💁🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochaXete @boosge1 @jctm1 @maurobremer @lucianorepp @ltbittar @emicosalum Só vocês para me tirar cedo da cama.😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[we LOVE a good hawaiian night @ Winchester, Virginia https://t.co/NGj3G6huoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My spelling word was “shower.” My sentence was “frilly, fluffy flower took a shower in a hour.” I stole the sentenc… https://t.co/Ar6avBdQXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live at 9pm. #HappyWomen’sDay @ 1 Hotel South Beach https://t.co/R8dGIqwBFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be here this morning! And missing my wingman @frangsi, who is soaring in Ohio around PBL. https://t.co/3sflF0YpHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Conrad’s newest members of @CSSRhoKappa and to our graduating seniors. #socialstudies #rhokappa… https://t.co/VENBkEzizW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The face you make when you debating in your head if you want to go to Vegas this summer... @janetjackson metamorpho… https://t.co/OnAiNX9Ixq]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two are like - we let the kids run with this and they hosed it up.  Everyone is grounded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Trump's sons and scores of others receive document requests from House committee https://t.co/82kyIMQojl]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got a fat $150 campus parking ticket on sunday, so hey if you wanna help a broke girl out u can venmo me @ ara… https://t.co/bWa9naN4Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 8 year old sister is on a movie date with her “boyfriend” and i can’t even get a guy to continue to talk to me lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo much respect for this man, thank you for the kind words and never-ending support!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @DwyaneWade hit a game winner over the Warriors is the feel good moment we all needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dress codes for black students AND Teachers, HAIR discrimination. Reality. https://t.co/SPR85NM9Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los principales índices en Estados Unidos cerraron en terreno positivo,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPSSnews @SHADnetwork @NPSSGuidance1 @NPSSArts @SCDSB_Schools That is awesome!  Congratulations 🎉 Sarah xo ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylortimbrookk Hell no they couldn't but they sure can talk shit all day ha ha ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the Cohen testimony was just a tug of war between dems &amp; repubs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tea, anyone?  Having a British high tea moment at Mr. Delicious Pâtisserie in Pickering,  Ontario, lakeside locatio… https://t.co/opx2ExFeoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people think they know me 🤷🏻‍♀️ Like Sis know ya self first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily @h0n3y_73 @realDonaldTrump  Plays THE ROLE in Everything!  (Me) that's what he does... He wants cre… https://t.co/naVGVOXGUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelLeishman I'm assuming you know about this but just in case...  Go Inside the Fake Rehearsal Studio in Exclus… https://t.co/5COVfbaKbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[traveling through time zones on the first day of daylight saving with layovers in some states that observe daylight… https://t.co/JEzOwIxHOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, I am calling bullshit rn on Kirpa and Tayshia calling everyone else unready for marriage. Is Colton really… https://t.co/5FcHd787YC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And also, Colton better not pick any of the other girls after pouring his heart out to Cassie. Definitely would be settling for second best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SF is beating #HIV Why not #Houston?  #HTX’s pop 44% Latino 23% Black  HIV rates among young people of color are ri… https://t.co/R4331taYR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackKopplin @HushamHamad Seriously? Do you think they would dare to do so?  Good luck 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Finished before you start..  save your money, save our country.  Get out of Dodge...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher How stupid can you be? He acted guilty from day 1. Shameful! 🎬🎭😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Editilla @NOLA_Fredo @liprap @JulieTCouret @shadesofoffside @nolanolegal @nolamaven @NOLAcomments @YesICandice… https://t.co/RHfNp8pyum]]></document><document><![CDATA[One possible way America can come to a end.  A person pretending to be Donald trump records a video saying he launc… https://t.co/GIQea7feQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, John!!! John Oliver Unleashes Robocall Hell On FCC Commissioners – Deadline https://t.co/YtBv8xFZFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANNOUNCEMENT: I'm the new author of the Good Taste food blog @visitwilmington! Follow along on my adventures as I t… https://t.co/CGlZ4Dw3dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to mention at 1:12am that I still love @RWitherspoon. Always have, always will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we’re spending time with Pillar Community Innovation Awards finalist, @RachelEttlinger raising awareness on… https://t.co/ovcWDgox1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sink into an amazing comfortable sofa! @Tiffabf johnrosselliassociates  . . . . #interiordesign… https://t.co/HRCCu56WPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone:  me: have u heard “are you bored yet” by @wallowsmusic ft clairo???????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paso Robles, California creates Sangiovese with an Italian accent and pairs perfectly with smoked beef tenderloin.… https://t.co/kZoQXjGhMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serbarica @charlie_shields @SSavich12 @eggsniffing @Lobefasa @mil182 It’s probably the worst I’ve felt ever. Usual… https://t.co/tf1oIVxiPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @AOC Speak for yourself some of us care about the environment. Idiots think, "Hey man I won't be her… https://t.co/cu1IMv8IkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bermanswife @babydollbritney In case you didn't know, his wife is from Louisiana and she knows all about mardi gra… https://t.co/5kgXJzILc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET YOURS NOW ⬇️⬇️ https://t.co/w0EoptepqP  RT this and I’ll pick a winner for a free set! 💲💎🖤 https://t.co/IERnx850mH]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 the time I have left, I will try 4 U the #wildhorses all equines @CyntWhite Thank you 4 your support 🐎 https://t.co/v28FF2MBaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @pattersonaubrey and @822Tribe for an awesome quick chat! #822chat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you want the unending medical bills that come with having such a disability?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AD // I’ve partnered with @mysmartblinds for my new home and to #giveaway a $100 gift card to one of my followers… https://t.co/L5NOlYhp5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew669691 @GaryEll85341441 @patrizesyra1 @Aaron_C5 @mjmgop @LBengtzen @BretMaverick777 @BRIANCCRUACHN… https://t.co/kle9dqdW1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[SERRAT, hoy puede ser un gran dia.. https://t.co/Qe3OsnxDk0 via @YouTube https://t.co/HZ3C3eMBAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you don’t get pumped up by listening to Body by Loud Luxury and it def shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night 🙌🏽 Got meet and had a little chat with THE LEGEND! @quincydjones 🙈😱 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/8QX9Gm15Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean I've just ordered it!  "Mostly Sunny: How I Learned to Keep Smiling Through the Rainiest Days will be a… https://t.co/nlVQZgt7Md]]></document><document><![CDATA[A funny card is a great way to ask your Bridesmaids! https://t.co/O21Sblssse #funniness #giggle #smile #playful https://t.co/oVCUoPkZMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThxThx2EzThxGG I told him that you gifted me the skin and he wanted to take advantage. (Another jealous boy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @TeaPartyNevada We haven’t heard the last of this gal.  Ppl like this are constantly challenging. Sh… https://t.co/5v8Nu2gtAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvolvedGuppy So sorry. I bet he never left your side.  Heartbreaking . He has the sweetest eyes .]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do when your child who very much isn’t a toddler regresses to toddler behavior whenever they have to do… https://t.co/EpQEGYSMw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very well expressed @thecoffeecop and @ladygaga is a wonderful supporter #MentalHealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your best friend is already dropping the “best friend rules” on the guy you are kind of seeing 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joenstanley Its a fandom... and is often sexual. Its creepy. https://t.co/YUd0AC35AP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just starting S8 of The Walking Dead... finally... thank u Netflix. ... "I hope you got your sh**in' pants on cuz y… https://t.co/x1VEaxOJ5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR Welcome back!!  Y&amp;R hasn’t been the same without our Paul Williams!!!  We love 💕 you Doug!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adamo - “I was first!”  Pearl - “No, I was first!”  #siblingproblems #siblings #pearl #adamo #dogs #dogstagram… https://t.co/jIHD5Yz5GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wow!  You still don’t understand tariffs. The consumer pays the additional expense. China just sel… https://t.co/ebz0pZI8ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arisacox @BigBrotherCA @GlobalTV So awesome!!!!!  In Upstate NY, USA  🇺🇸 we get @CTV and this year they are airing… https://t.co/QP1e3afI7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoniLove @CityofDetroit @realtommyhearns Omg that's dope!!! Mr. Tommy "hitman" Hearns 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 nice pic Loni ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think there has been a single month ever in the history of my life in which I have remembered to pay my car… https://t.co/h1CK0VHq97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey It just keeps getting worse as each day passes. I don’t think it is p… https://t.co/uLW7XALojU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ive been talking about getting the monday show of muse/walk the moon tickets for months and i was worried about goi… https://t.co/07DPB9nK7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chandersaur I told dylan we should look at prices for Ireland and he had ads on his phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ETA Creative Arts Foundation in Chicago, IL https://t.co/E2ERdFTG7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo Uncorked 2019 #wesociety #rodeouncorked2019 @ HLSR Rodeo Uncorked and Best Bites https://t.co/m8tJ7nRrgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My type is a guy who doesn’t “quite fit in” but is still attractive enough to be a douche]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand fast therefore in the liberty wherewith Christ hath made us free, and be not entangled again with the yoke of… https://t.co/kMvUjB60Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi baile sensual #lol no se que onda conmigo hahaha (ya, buenas noches ahora si) @ San Diego, California https://t.co/UZm9FU1in3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amomthatsleeps @Target @PEEPSBrand Chocolate covered 😋😋 https://t.co/v1iso4pCOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.8 employment and jobs added , as well as wages going up. I am glad for people but these numbers can get us trumpa… https://t.co/8ntCyQIIQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre canto Side boobie ...  #SussyOhEnConvoy https://t.co/0wLaZCSrSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Envision Physician Services team! See our latest #Pediatrics job openings, including "Pediatrics - Medical… https://t.co/kglz5XGLZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pot o’ gold has been found! Congrats Coach Bardusk! 🌈🏆@RCEMiddle https://t.co/yRMlExeCW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franklin County Coroner issues overdose death spike alert after 5 died in 9.5 hours https://t.co/HnPUrUvU53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN Once again you are wrong!! What a shocker!! You did get 1 right AOC! But @RoKhanna @AyannaPressley… https://t.co/bmsFqDEQV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwheels74 🙏🏽 1 Cor 13:12 - “For now we see through a glass, darkly; but then face to face: now I know in part; but… https://t.co/22IJTlU1y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wonderful. Young reps are already digging us out of this mess. Your son and his friends will make sure it n… https://t.co/126ywFK3qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is he even giving interviews right now? Issue a statement if needed but a whole interview? With all this talkin… https://t.co/wwR15KP0dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProperlySane @sabrina68 @realDonaldTrump You have no idea! https://t.co/JtGDnXmTwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha we knew it was too good to be true. #88off #sephora https://t.co/SOElAExRBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christy53102 @mikiebarb @Wesley_Morris I LOVE @Wesley_Morris's delivery. He's passionate and light-hearted. I star… https://t.co/DWD8GoQVes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren How about we not to stop Trump before it’s to late! Or is it already! Get him out first before anything el… https://t.co/WpQXSlLHZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Once again, that's the pot calling the kettle black.  Duh. https://t.co/WC19ozPmIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chase  so I leave one bad bank wellsfargo and find another one.. yay me!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t matter how many chances or time you’ve given them.. ppl just don’t change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4aPeoplesParty @Tim_Canova Nope.  Can't be doing WOE IS ME in the corner anymore.  We HAD that in 2016.  We aren't… https://t.co/co0WNRnAoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yass @TheTraeYoung #hawks #atlantahawks @ATLHawks https://t.co/yj97ZEL33U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ewgc this one is for EVERYONE. Every parent, every teacher, every librarian. The principles you know, the ones you… https://t.co/136WFwkrVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[my religion prof gave me like 25 points above the actual grade I got on my final paper so now I have to tell her I… https://t.co/cGTHSJLkGG]]></document></documents></author>