<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SudsBitches @usasmitty Some here.... I wish people wouldn't speak about what they know nothing. 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I own is just sitting around my house in boxes... I’m officially claustrophobic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CulinaryBroDown @m_garrett05 @rhettandlink But is it large enough to hold the giant man child, or will you have to… https://t.co/UumcETrX3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dogdadbod @AmerMedicalAssn AMA’s politics have become more important to them than being a voice for all doctors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellydking @SaraSchroader @LifeWay Praying for LifeWay leadership as you make these difficult decisions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before @BlackGryph0n, I went crazy over this guy LOL https://t.co/80l2DIgPAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiffany Tygart Tygart crossed 10K. Time 02:22:36, pace 28:07 min/mile, est. finish 10:44 am https://t.co/f11SrlQDa3 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayBlogs #ACoA #AA #PTSD Check out my blog for thoughts on moving forward https://t.co/VCqTr9jXGy https://t.co/frXiQg3i2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The video is blurry which makes it look unblended but I promise it was I literally spent at least an hour building… https://t.co/gt2oQNzsYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresCatania You’re my fav NJ Housewife, but Teresa has met her match with Jackie. You know Teresa is wrong be h… https://t.co/GCJlVxYsra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple on a tv that I've been waiting for seasons to get together: finally gets together  Me: oh thank god, now the… https://t.co/mmRnqm36F2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood: wanting to eat my lunch before lunch but then I won’t have a lunch for lunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[especially now that i got my l’s situated.. im bringing the wheels back out.. PERIOD! it’s really over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr PLEASE!!! These things happen EVERY SINGLE DAY IN THE BANE OF MAGA!! So give me a break and get off… https://t.co/bBSdl8MyFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para que sepan de donde me viene la pinta!!!!! #yositengomuchamadre #actress #lovemiami #motherdaughter 🙌🏽 esta súp… https://t.co/W2Y3l0Kxwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, @SenThatcher. Enhancements should be risk-based. We need whole system to work from evidence-based risk assessm… https://t.co/Lwt47GeUfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: we made it home because I’m a professional even in a goddamn diesel truck 😁💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll never understand why random people think it’s appropriate to come up and start touching/petting my coat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @PeteButtigieg Take time to read about and listen to Mayor Pete!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLD.... I CAN SELL YOURS TOO!! Represented Sellers 🥳🏠🎉Welcome to 2927 S. Norton St., Los Angeles, CA 90018, locate… https://t.co/4XYggG2kWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignOfApril You’re work paid off and God placed you in the room to see it! #BlackHistory]]></document><document><![CDATA[my legs were shaking hella yesterday and no not because i got good dick but because i worked out and if that isn’t… https://t.co/SOrhuImJeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Who is that Wilber Ross, that idea came from him, he is so proud. What is it, "pride g… https://t.co/kDeP3uHS2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just living that William life. Have a great weekend! We have the OG kids birthday party! 12 boys vs 2 parents! Wish… https://t.co/gxlzcs4TXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gotmel_1 please for the love of god don’t! I know exactly what you’re talking about 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spent two hours looking for my mom's car in the park mgm parking garage😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nsrcworld @stevesong Such great partners @nsrcworld Thank you for doing what you do to train pipl, build nets, and connect!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicusInvictus @takehissocks @sean_spicier Move on, son. Bye. Make it a great day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta do y'all allow therapy 🐕 😇🙏 @angiefilkins. @latimes @theweeknd @VP @GovMikeHuckabee. Thank you all for your… https://t.co/uY5Or9tK9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HAL_LE_LU_YAH @WashTimes @BillGates @HowardSchultz Although you have to add Santa Cruz, CA, they have a huge probl… https://t.co/iBD0tzdE9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when my feet are freezing when I’m trying to go to sleep but I don’t like socks on.  ☹️send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son enjoying a healthy snack 😁  #proudmother #doritos #chopsticks #healthysnack en Tijuana, Baja California https://t.co/Q9Leih33eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the #JACAC winners. It's an honour to be here at the Japanese Embassy - arigato @JapaninCanada T… https://t.co/jkHu2E7Emy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarDamnDarcie Must have a Hoover or Mtn Brook alum on their team. It's the only logical answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @FoxNews Those who criticize Obama would do well to remember how much Republicans obstructed him. Had we gi… https://t.co/nzKVzeaNNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What scares me is that some people literally only watch Fox for news. Christ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS SUNDAY ALL YOU CAN EAT $5! Just go to this link to donate or buy a ticket! (We are adding some awesome cinnamo… https://t.co/aV5v9tpBEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so, I’ll admit the face painting on the adorable kids and their fabulous smiles was my favorite part! #imasoftie]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a full weekend of Teacher Training! We spent time on practice teaching, class design, teacher boundaries/ethic… https://t.co/q6Gu3AQKl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW VIDEO ALERT! Wonder what I’m doing my Friday night? Editing!! Haha new video is up! Reviewing the new… https://t.co/suDblYQXXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders So why did you vote against the Brady Bill FIVE times?  Rings so hollow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umm that’s called the 4th of July in DC, it’s televised every year. You’ve lived in DC for the last two years, so I… https://t.co/pXdLrMWHKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @MarkHess98 Awwwww.... Lucy girl, you just take your time getting it together in the morning, any mornin… https://t.co/WAx5klwQdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister How can republicans and Trump supporters think this is ok. What has become of this country??]]></document><document><![CDATA[People like this are spreading false information! That’s not what’s happening and if they actually paid attention a… https://t.co/17wUopHOoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! ☀️ Here's the top stories we're working on:  1) A tragic story out of Liberty Co. where a husband and… https://t.co/0fzo1TDcQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all watching this live would suck because there’s so many unnecessary interviews and clips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me back to last weekend.... Good times with old friends and people I can call family... love y’all and thank y… https://t.co/RFUBkIfqVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le dio likeee.. gracias @christophervele  no dejé de temblar por la emoción 🙏🏻😭😘 https://t.co/WHW0XROQkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @ShirleySharona2 Yes he does have that certain something. Trump isn't even in the same building with Obama, and he knows it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Beautifuls 🌞💗☕ HAPPY FRIDAY!!! 🤩🎉 Do your Friday HAPPY DANCE 💃🕺 and have a GREAT day!!  ☀️💗🎧🎶 @ Michig… https://t.co/af8bw6GzTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[God just reading some of the comments on my IG. I’m beyond humbled by the love and support. I’m so lucky and gratef… https://t.co/eAkuNSLIkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartnersAmerica @exchangealumni @ECAatState @FulbrightPrgrm @peglegmeg @GoAbroad @tpeden @CUDenverAbroad… https://t.co/8ccuPdKluI]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY WHY WHYYYYYY did you have to end the way you did. I just don’t know what to think. #TGIT #AMillionLittleThings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryrysmith @gayla_powell @CillizzaCNN She's part of the largest most bizarre cult ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoishesMom He's a monster.  The horror this beautiful girl Gypsy endured from her person is disgusting.  She looke… https://t.co/NTxOQAxXrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are the beginning stages of the male Green Honeycreeper. He is a beauty and I can’t wait to get to his gloriou… https://t.co/iytanBFeDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bodhihodi I can’t focus with a messy house anyway (though 90% of the humans I know would scoff at my idea of messy...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veterans_i @abronxchick @birdieglad @jihettly @pannlewis44 @graceslick77 @MarilynT4 @mgrossi1 @DLTrunnell… https://t.co/nXRvYujwvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryhelenad Grateful to have raised such a strong independent woman #SoProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get to see joshie today &amp; i can’t wait to just lay there with him &amp; get my mind off of everything right now..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesliegcoy @JoeMerchandise @joemcelderry91 How's your weather down south Leslie? Are you 65 too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinncy @jonniker I refused to watch wire because i grew up in Blatimore County.   I was a maryland distinguished… https://t.co/KljWW7V4QI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We completed the Cupidons’ pre drywall inspection today and all is on track. They are so excited and will be moving… https://t.co/b2K5sel4Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy ❤️ day! #flower #valentine #montreal #leplateau #mtlblog @ Plateau Mont-Royal https://t.co/YDWRigHXrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[◾️Always◾️ ✖️Be you✖️ #alwaysprogress  #downtown #haircuts #barbers #visaliabarbers #ladybarber #visaliabarbershops… https://t.co/7rREIKDo72]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about President Obama declaring 12 declarations of emergency in his eight years don’t they get ?? 👿😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun evening with @DartmouthWBB at their own team ChoppeD event! These ladies wowed with their tasty and crea… https://t.co/qICvtZsjQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[54/365 Apparently the Quarter roads are being patched for Mardi Gras. I wouldn't say fixed. https://t.co/fK3oH0KEE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS 👇👇👇👇🏆 thy think they are going to run on this narrative, and all that has to happen is explaining to the play… https://t.co/agcwh2rujX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusQuijass amigo te falle, quiero empezar una vida fit pero mi gordura no me deja😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGTeamPI @YouTube Get Joe from ugue to go and check it out in daytime it was scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapineauCouture @RealMuckmaker Yea, for someone who's always yapping about 'respect the flag, respect the anthem,… https://t.co/bKeTIupN01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red to honor my Canada-versary today. 🇨🇦 Today marks 19 years since I moved to Canada.   #canada #landedimmigrant… https://t.co/dlDLC34gK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a dad and his girls. 💕💞💓 #Dad #joon #father #happpybirthday #triplets #lovehim #bestdad joon3alex @ Orange, Ca… https://t.co/F2lfZ4TZ1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take my hand,  Take my whole life too...   ♥️💍💒 #kweonshim #annyphotography @ Old Town, Alexandria https://t.co/Fn1GD2vLDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump What’s also outrageous is the absolute silence from the #FakeNews #treasonousActionsByFBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the Beans LUNDI GRAS parades today!!! Now off the play a LUNDI GRAS Concert 7-9pm in Arabi at Zeitgeist theat… https://t.co/BQ3xrjIIUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricVictoria6 @MarcusSequeira @undr8d_c @ItsDrew33 @danibryan_ @drewski090 @yourgirlsavi @thaboi_austo @arianaharriss wasn’t planning on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @lspookie! It stuck! This 2nd grader suggested painting a “mural” on the side of this business that is under co… https://t.co/Y94omuKL8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrantzRunnem @MotownDR @DJClaussen71 You've completely missed his point. Bernie is going to be the Jill Stein of 2… https://t.co/wHwIznoqzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mermaidxhes lmfao wtf this don’t make any sense but have a nice life!!!!!!! 🤪 I remember shit like this when I was… https://t.co/pd1bf4011J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImDatDudeJay The one in Theodore will bring it to you for a extra cost]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're a desert..we'll be one for a long long time..get comfortable with the fact we're gonna have to do something t… https://t.co/4Q05N0VTPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would they not want birds nesting in a tree?  Are they spraying it with bug spray?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you leilaniking 💙 #osprey #nest #birdsnest #predator #mama #nesting #bird #nest #waterbird #nature… https://t.co/jHcBLNyKm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the day starts like this...... you know it’s gonna be a good day! 🤗🌞🌊🌊SMILE! #agentsofcompass #sagharbor… https://t.co/XVxCKSAqED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstGentleman I believe this was the same interview https://t.co/vcBfedMr9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryr62323720 @SenatorCollins @SenatorTomUdall I work in a doctors office. Don’t even start with insurance. Most o… https://t.co/XzvX3Rhexj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try really hard to make my once a week gym quota. Happy to report I just got home from the gym! First time this week 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! They think I’m #Fabulous #LastDayOfTraining #ItsBeenAwesome @ Macon, Georgia https://t.co/KLgORoyzyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me entering and then promptly leaving Flavor Country https://t.co/ntq4YFmyGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will McClendon at the line — makes 2 — Gorman 27-Clark 23 @BG_Basketball @ClarkHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy came to see me at work and since I work overnights, I know he real deal like me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @GavinNewsom He's not addressing the thousands that are caught and released every week that the govt… https://t.co/441rMHs0lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being a pest and annoying other people instead of studying for tomorrow’s exam :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the challenge from @jjablonska5 to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no review-just the co… https://t.co/Pi9nFhJPqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #OklahomaCity, OK job and click to apply: Housekeeper 1 - FT - Evenings - Environmental Services - I… https://t.co/IKFm2qRmdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch @AuntFannysPants Watched a rerun of Colombo with Faye Dunaway and went to bed 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[i WON’T be a theatre kid and I will never like a musical ever but...maybe the dramatic arts made some points]]></document></documents></author>