<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn r your constituents all trump dummies? cuz facts don't matter to trump dummies.  trump dummies just bel… https://t.co/omctDXz51N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MYHBeach @MiamiHerald @wef @WPLGLocal10 @ProfStrachan @elonmusk @DonaldJTrumpJr  stop trashing the planet 🌏 GreenP… https://t.co/xigtYqw7TG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMLeo @peterbakernyt @BretBaier @FoxNewsSunday @jackshafer Bingo Alex. JFC. The Fox crowd just wants to hear 'e… https://t.co/v07M9XPTka]]></document><document><![CDATA[First stop: #BaronWxConference   Second stop: Crashing @brendanschaper’s party in Nashville]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes watching stand up can be uniquely satisfying... sometimes reading meeting minutes is also...weird?... “th… https://t.co/AywCHWn06k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrimmage vs Denbigh is postponed for today. We will try again tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two lessons here: 1. Don’t give up on your dreams. No one is ever loved by everyone and your haters aren’t the judg… https://t.co/Z67LGMWBV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wgriffin28 @oreomina1 @ElleRguez @pensfannc5 @panekbill @pcdebol @eo_chic @JenniPrickett @mnguy152 🤣😂🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I met one of my heroes tonight. he’s one of the many reasons why i am an artist, why I am an activist, and wh… https://t.co/BzvTLqZtEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two of @WataugaSchools finest teaching our state leaders canvas magic! #WeAreWatagua @GreenValley_828 https://t.co/k5FNZZ80zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LingerConf hey guys , I loved the conference! Can I buy more Linger coffee mugs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when two girls walk into a barber shop and they look at you like you’re lost. #wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFC @ChelseaFCinUSA Thank you for ruining my first trip to London. Changing the West Ham game to a Monday yo… https://t.co/P5t4XfXLZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with this assessment wholeheartedly, like it or not AB is under contract and he alone does not get to dicta… https://t.co/yfxQZgvfTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump Your Goose is Cooked....Michael Cohen is Spilling the Beans On You...#LiarInChief]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradyszuhaj @ASITISofficial @holdclose_mo @sharptoothmd come back soon ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 of 50  Pearson's Falls Saluda, NC .5 miles  1.26.19 . . . . @ Pearson's Falls https://t.co/k28uFBKFwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 major changes tonight. Jermaine with the confidence to attack on O. Defensive intensity at an 11. Pushing tempo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop wasting money on cable and switch today! 706-392-0532 @ Phenix City, Alabama https://t.co/jYjq5DfICN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I. FUCKING. HATE. TWITTER. RESTAURANTS. this shit is in orlando florida fuck i look like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our newest patrol vehicle #gks #greenknightsecurity #greenknight #security #patrol #securitypatrol #securityguard… https://t.co/QC4rf6fJh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never before Dems got so low! The hate from the Dems is unprecedented!  They will pay big in 2020 elections! Mr Tru… https://t.co/X8UwM4fvD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XXXChelseaMarie Me hopefully I would get that chance and take full advantage of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kent Tekulve, 16 year career, holds NL Record for career innings pitched in relief (1,436) appeared… https://t.co/JiwkrrKmcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Moments to @OfficialTAZ @MarcMalusis @AndrewBogusch and the rest of the @TazAndTheMoose family..... Listen if… https://t.co/e2cpRuhBF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasty. - Drinking a Resinlord by @SigmaBrewingCo at @haymerchant  — https://t.co/e1N87Zl4qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @MarkNagiTDOT ; with the inclement weather this weekend, are plans still a go to open the new WB loop… https://t.co/ktgBfetkBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Ricks crossed 15K. Time 01:51:48, pace 12:41 min/mile, est. finish 9:45 am https://t.co/dCA5JdzF3R #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJem24 your honest , they wont give you credit for being honest but you are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 The secularist elites need to keep the truth hidden as long as possible- the truth always shines thru after evil fails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a dream come true of a night at Rainbow Pop 🌈 @laughfactory_lb The audience was a dream! The comics were on fi… https://t.co/LR7KaQZ1bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has Pelosi Officially Lost Control Of The House? https://t.co/K4P8Hod33F via @Conservative Buzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyrva @acart30 @JonRothstein I'd argue that Mike Rhoades could be considered COY over the others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AOC’s Social Media game is 🔥 these muppets tryin to come at her... https://t.co/ed7ISwWglx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get the sushi roll with cream cheese in it...... please seek therapy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making History - @KHSLAXclub warms up for their first EVER game at the VB SportsPlex. We know you'll make all the… https://t.co/ReAFZRVZdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[W Washington Blvd W Washington Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90066 https://t.co/d4ajgA7xH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[please help me with snapin dentures  trump teeth snapin 4 me https://t.co/fLp0y9aDzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s when the world silences so there’s nothing to drown out your thoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Mebane, NC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/TRZ6FaExas #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know a person is extremely conceded when they say u are obsessed with them yet you haven’t contacted them first in a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, weirdly, they might have one player with 50 goals and no one else with 25.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kubakostecki @pt Has anything changed since 2010? Why are we using random Twitter accounts as truth? https://t.co/UmaVCk2z0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fighterguy2424 @DbossBoston @Reflog_18 @RageRhino1241 @CSTRodB Great Job Alex P, loved Boston during his Buckeye d… https://t.co/aN2LEXNDlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiestone @TCHRadio @MeowWolf Glad to be there - and glad to see what you’re doing this year with @TCHRadio - it’s amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp He’s a liar you dope. It’s 25.5% not 50%. Get your facts and data straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dollyfande @RealJamesWoods Vote Vote Vote tell your friends , relatives and neighbors to Vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all my love 😍 #shotoniphone #iphonex #clips #valentines #tennis #bicycle @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/L4WiGB2aPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:57.0°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pairs well with my pink hair ~ - Drinking a Spontané Syrah by @farmhouseales at @capsntapscamas  — https://t.co/Kd9fX2Z5Ei]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyPresidentsDay A big #tipofthehat to those who taken on the toughest elected job in our nation that comes with… https://t.co/xeeqUSMVwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sizzling 20 point first half from @ZipsMBB point guard #LorenChristianJackson has Akron up 44-37 on @BGSUMHoops at… https://t.co/y4HxOcQrxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValerieNeuharth I want people to be creative when making their slide. I have a layout selected but the color and h… https://t.co/vZGw1sGCBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatherineHolom And I haven't queried in over a decade... so I will need a refresher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Age 28 in 1983. I guess I was going for the Don Johnson/Miami Vice type look, but instead I just look… https://t.co/eelPuoTePF]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF! This weather sucks! Sunny and 45 degrees is not a typical wake up on Saturday morning temperature!! Is this gl… https://t.co/eJWk6dY92x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure zero of the Democratic presidential contenders will have the FBI contemplating invoking the 25th Amendment, if elected. #Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is making me go to a little kid’s birthday party with my sister. #trapped]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yelotree @IllusionOG Hi. A washed up athlete is chillin here 😂😀https://t.co/NyRlDwk7fd https://t.co/660rzAqzvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viss @TProphet @SparkleOps Nope, I needed a professional designation to prove myself worthy of being issued a work visa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djfamouslee I know. I just wish the media was more (or as) on this than (as) they are on the #JussieSmolett story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsringel @ida_skibenes @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Dude, you can’t explain anything. Because... well, Trump. 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hall of Fame. That’s it. End of discussion, thanks for playing, Blues in 4, hasta la vista. #stlblues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YESNetwork Love Didi, he always gives you 110% on the field, and one of the real leaders of this ballclub.  Get we… https://t.co/LTzljTJLoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiniLaddd @KittyGamin @MatPatGT I think @Terroriser and @DaithiDeNogla raised money for charity, but I could be wr… https://t.co/Hlor2fLPZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredFredSanders @DZRishmawy #ImReadingTillichOnTheOutsideButImOrthodoxOnTheInside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anblanx @nbcsandiego looks like the governments were as justified in investigating this as they were in investigat… https://t.co/cK2bFrBKC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answering some mail from the Digital Complaint Box in a brand new Snark Report at 7 on @WCCBCharlotte. #WCCB https://t.co/ujWTd5FXPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[$6 for $12 worth of USA Today's &amp; Best Pizza in Missouri!  https://t.co/37UeuvErfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This track!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ The lyrics is on 🔥🔥🔥🔥🤘🏻😭 https://t.co/5aYKjW3lVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmurphypei Yeah I don’t have my weight in the back now. I could almost slide the back end over by hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutouts @sodrewski mightyempireconcerts For Playing My Single "You Ain't Know"  Music Video Dropping This Week !… https://t.co/ABzZQybmbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennoku @BaileyLAKings @LAKings Awesome that Bailey shares his birthday a day after your dad’s! Have fun at the ga… https://t.co/tfjvFeyAks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedNews @VishaanNYC New York City leads the way in saying “no, not all money is good money.”  If any city nee… https://t.co/bn8Lnl6VFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #MilkyWay season! Can't wait to see what comes out of tonight's overnight shoot! I've never shot it before, so… https://t.co/tUJnihiUF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Sunday Mornin' by @docpowell, from #SoundHound https://t.co/7MwFYsSne1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was planning to drive like a maniac on the snow-lined streets of our neighborhood following last night’s big stor… https://t.co/PaFA5OoH4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knicks have 13 wins which you would think would make them unwatchable....but they also have Mitchell Robinson which… https://t.co/mn2aFP6GrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Houston somehow manages to beat the spark and nyxl this week we could actually turn this stage around. Biblethump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted the challenge from @jennekrajecki to post covers of 7 books I LOVE! ❤️No explanations, no reviews. Ea… https://t.co/XG9ilWOrcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream last night that I cast @MeganK_Kelly as Norma Desmond in a production of Sunset Boulevard. #moveoverglennclose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricEstepp17, I was doing an impresdion of your Kyle Larson voice in class Friday for acting, and I decided to loo… https://t.co/8E97axGkzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the stuff kids are gonna relate to other kids with when they get to middle school school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them: UVa played in a close one this week  Me: I tHiNk wE aLL pLaYeD cLoSe oNEs tHiS wEeK https://t.co/3lTQu72c1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringneckryan @loc8ingoil Awwwww Chase looks upset. Maybe social media isn't for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am exposed to truth I don't judge it because it must be allowed to present all of its information and that h… https://t.co/K8gZt8fYFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnePatton You are a poor representative for the black race. Why don’t you get down on your knees the next time y… https://t.co/vB2K6dK5ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I like small functions. The name describes what it’s doing and it serves as a “chapter” in the linear n… https://t.co/yqnzlzkIA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @SWCorridor is a continuation of the exact type of decisions that led to neighborhood destruction.  But… https://t.co/5ILj6DmuUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildDavidWild When every major news outlet is presenting the same evidence, and pushing similar opinions, I tend t… https://t.co/oMrwcDT7SA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efarinas99 Que lo compartan, así me vuelvo como parido nicaragua, famoso por publicar pajas xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look Alex “La Rata” Padilla @alexpadilla86 what you describe is called circumstantial evidence. I used the preexist… https://t.co/ZLMZtEZ5xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record, I wouldn’t wish listening to “Chelsea Dagger” eight times in a two-hour span on my worst enemy. Nex… https://t.co/E7Yuai1ycv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Styrofloof: The impossible to clean up bits of expanded polystyrene foam packing that get everywhere when you assem… https://t.co/5zlDvY5slc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prediction for River Cats Opening Day!!  #RCParty @ Raley Field https://t.co/5EuXL3WBBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I smoked weed for the 2nd time in my life the other night and this sentence came directly out of my mind:  The bigg… https://t.co/S6pGBilxod]]></document><document><![CDATA[If television has taught me anything, the Republicans on the #HouseOversightCommittee are going to come back smarte… https://t.co/5VqZHcj66M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGWilliamBarr @Ed08792346 Well said Mr Attorney General! Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phpdudeaz @clarkphp I hear Nagios runs on IBM i .  So maybe a monitor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder who else is gonna hurt/cheat/lie/leave me again, I hope he’s handsome. 😆]]></document></documents></author>