<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Watching @SideshowGaming 's reaction to our Nepal Sanctum win was a fantastic end to the night LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ron_Decline @nytimes Did you get China and India on board yet? Any plans of it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goaltend at KY. Against Tennessee they Have a ref that is a LSU fan. And The Latest a Goal Tend to knock off Florid… https://t.co/wYA6IKk3TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be interesting to see if/how DPRK frames their take, but entire story doesn't seem to be out yet. You don't ab… https://t.co/xYF1rPag9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliemwall What a surprise. Good for you.  My son and his friends are matching next week. Not much stress. He’s… https://t.co/sbsQZxwtik]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/yFrzDbH03Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChumpNicholson More than that I miss the old PVP with OHK grenades and more powerful melee.   I recently played a… https://t.co/V3XAj2HiQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to shake @SenSanders hand after an amazing speech tonight. Good times. https://t.co/HXfOar5gdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the winner of @genesisopen who trusted Epic Flash Sub Zero 10.5. With the win, Callaway is #1 in wins o… https://t.co/K4rrn5Hc6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bettercallyogi Likewise my dude!! I’m super down to finally do that this season let’s plan it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s AWESOME!! Glad I could help!! Another Team Pep talk to victory in the books 📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi b Tatiana go except  when she Rappin bout her pussy and shit like stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Priestley writes to his 'dear friend of 29 years,' Luke Perry #90210 https://t.co/vHtf9CIvfc 👥👍🏼😘… https://t.co/MlxzMKo0Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEE G NEWS: From all of us here at Lee G News.......congratulations to @OfficialHTM on being announced to be induct… https://t.co/GXElGksa1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously never fucking with @ChipotleTweets again. Love their food but they can NEVER get a mobile order out in time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissazimmerle Down to fresh bedsheets.. I just cant come home to a dirty house lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bodgei Oh, hon. I wish I could be there to give you all of the hugs and love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want to kiss you and cuddle with you and you know that so this sucks :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pzorthotics @WindyCityOUTLAW @innit2020 @BenjaminEnfield It’s amazing for a gun free city how many shootings there are in Chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LetsGoBucs (@ LECOM Park - @the_marauders for Miami Marlins at Pittsburgh Pirates in Bradenton, FL)… https://t.co/LjmxgxFlYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paleshimmering @catsu And right now, I'm feeling okay. Job market sucks and I hate it, but when does it not suck?… https://t.co/BBsU2C9wMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonEnsor3 I hate stupid people. A robbery with a weapon is armed robbery. Semantics. It doesn’t say it in your… https://t.co/PIZ1uLa8ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcm_ct Urban Carmel stayed that previous ongoing bear mkts hv never had a Vix under 15, here we are @ 14.39. Curio… https://t.co/O7fJfvXFDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @horusrage @Cern_lXXl @PCribbett @BlancoIndian @CingetoOfBelgae @zapher134 @selgowiros @PolyRhuagh… https://t.co/MNXFGJc1B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bucks I say conspiracy!  The Buckaroooos we're mounting a big game clinching rally...  Then a bat is released and… https://t.co/GOPC7ShLMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonffl @andyholloway @TheFFBallers @FFHitman @jasonmoorisms 30 min mark... Mike!  “Pause for concern?” Mike is the new Jason!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson is the real moron!  Overly sensitive, and using his apparently, very limited, foul mouthed vocabular… https://t.co/HJ86dPSssk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trfinch_65 Yes, @carmenlynnsmith has done an incredible job in year one with us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moana is on TV. I own this on DVD so could literally watch it whenever I want, but I literally cannot change the ch… https://t.co/TnK4u79qS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well,the first thing you should know is it's already been done: https://t.co/rWwc2ISS77  This☝️then this👇  https://t.co/2unYKdhNPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help my friends over at https://t.co/m3HVnddWRE win a small business grant. Aaron is a great guy and does excellent… https://t.co/MtxVM95sT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The so-called wrestling experts can say what they want about Raw and Smackdown fans being casual fans, but from wha… https://t.co/5NwgYLlfsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillRohland @JReidESPN George mason made the final 4 before so are they good ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lie to me fammm. Lmfaoooo like do you understand the power that I have ... 👊🏽👊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianSlimdog77 @Insectsarecool2 You just said insects are stupid... so they are stupid super Nazi’s... can you make them look any worse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The otherworldly ice cave behind Tamanawas Falls.   #oregon #oregonexplored #exploreeverything #icicle #waterfall… https://t.co/jyw92QWVPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing kills my vibe more then when you crunch on an eggshell in your taco 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpoolKaraoke @beachbummovie @SnoopDogg @McConaughey @WillieNelson @AppleTV Hoping this goes down @LuckReunion next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@battleofever @GenFlynn @BarbaraRedgate @Corp125Vet @Beg1Girl @awaken_to_maga @PatriotJenn @ReconRandy444… https://t.co/9vQ44kaOgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFetterman What the heck does a man's clothes say about what the man is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimicDonalds @ilysjeno @jessskangas That’s bc there’s allllllllllllllllot to be confused about. https://t.co/OSycQ4W9pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djspindatrack6 @Kai__Williams @Wilson17_Avery @StevosSouza https://t.co/Oy4Ra5R3lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@88SEATTLE61 Let me clarify, I didn't mean that you were wrong but for Jr. to continue panicking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ellen4Democracy I’m a proud trump voter, and supporter. Tired of being bullied by keyboard warriors like you. U are an idiot and a commie 🐍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyhawkerfinds @realDonaldTrump Sometimes it feels as if every Southern Republican official is sexually perverted… https://t.co/SEfHd3HdrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Don’t worry Jim 63 PLUS Million Of Us Are Getting Ready to visit every Member of Congress for Dinner! Let’s celebrate shall we]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nipple #ear #funfact #didyouknow #sleep #goodnight #aandp #anatomy #hmm #earlobes @ Lumpy's Laundromat, Motorcycle… https://t.co/4WEPaNs3dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bible is much more about who God IS than about who WE might become.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boywonder091109 @GreatBriTom @UnrankedPodcast This site/article idk, but the rumor has been around for the last we… https://t.co/NSV2nQmgTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bobsouth1 @BrianHedger Correct. But... His buddy Dzingel and him will sign. $50 straight up. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenweener Same here! I was invincible when I was young now I have to prepare my body a day before to bare it. We’re just old now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sickening man. I see only hate n greed with all the spoils that go with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueCrewAZ #Padres have the #1 farm system, and Lucchesi, Lauer, Paddock, Quantrill and Nix are a few of their arm… https://t.co/gzpeQgGLXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Wilson is lucky Grinaldi is quick on the draw.  #fthismoviefest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Al mejor estilo Abrams. Elliot Abrams. https://t.co/twDe1S2Yj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @xrey1 @AE911Truth @OhioBot5000 We used to have to reduce everything to simple unit squares In order to c… https://t.co/vA9At80RzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator anus king says 71297  Governor mills says 70000 They are the same people 3300 actual Medicaid expansion Democrats got hoodwinked]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all my fault and I don’t know if I can fix it 😔 #notagoodday #stressed #maybeiwillleave]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice read and a fitting end to our Republic of Texas unit! @HumbleISD_TMS @tms_stem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoSportsy steve powells music career is chalked full of BANGERS so much talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillGrayGC Dropping from knee height is very simple. Thank you for recognizing that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson Exactly. And it’s funny seeing Berniebros brag about how much Bernie made since his announcement, s… https://t.co/yezfSmc4Cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyknicks your owner is the absolute worst in any league. He should sell the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone doing any Marowak raids outside of Latias? @Jack00721221 @Shinytracker @cadester22 @BrandyShemal2… https://t.co/btYasbFNhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't even put into words how excited we are that the #GreatFoodTruckRace has landed in Wolfeboro! When we used to… https://t.co/B4jRxUKXpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirBarrighini @sahluwal @SakreligiousKay I know, I was questioning the that myself ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Image artist Anna Feil #hotelsmotels Group hotel room exhibit with Sarah Tell sarah_tell, Anna Feil @annafeil, and… https://t.co/3EcmZy2tQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wally by @wachusettbrew at @horseshoehudson — https://t.co/O7p04DNQ1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Night of Celebration as we paid Tribute to the Queen Of Soul. #arethafranklintribute #hubbsgroove #nighttown… https://t.co/5gS1PfAdvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donald_j_putin. Comrade : i went to Santa Anita race track to get my mail. Horse's are dieing 22 horse's i think b… https://t.co/rWHakZLEKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittJillFit You must have way more patience than I do...👍🏼 up to you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @Cruellaisdevine Thank you! Great focus to keep your emphasis on passing the legislation needed to m… https://t.co/FKsLb0Dzt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Apple Wellington Green in Wellington, FL https://t.co/zJzYwrHD7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: No. 4 #UVA 29, Notre Dame 25. Kyle Guy and De'Andre Hunter combined for 17 for the Cavaliers. TJ Gibbs an… https://t.co/ekyCZJIr04]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9HEnvjVBPf #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops @GoLHLions  @_dbohannon  @ELCORaiderHoops  @LCHS1022]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is no longer the beginning of the end for Trump.  This is how Mueller took down Gotti.  This is the end.  You… https://t.co/aRXSJnilPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaPatsGirl Multiple timelines and all that I’m down with. So naturally I started freaking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alita: Battle Angel is just...weird...and kind of perverse really; it has some serious body dysmorphia, body horr… https://t.co/btPE0hEjRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[sipo tayari kuukabidhi moyo wangu kwa mwingine zaidi yako,wewe ni wa pekee maishani mwangu mwenye kujua hisia moyon… https://t.co/pLDDMvLHSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICHEJournal A methodological comparison of risk scores versus decision trees for predicting drug-resistant infecti… https://t.co/hUEkbkVBmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NABJSTUDENTS @WBKB11 Here’s my email: elijah@wbkb11.com send resume and reel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bankroll Fresh "Trap" (WSHH Exclusive - Official Music Video) https://t.co/mSMoyxe0xC via @YouTubeカ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nataliew1020 My heart goes to you. I hope you find peace and joy during your family time and living life to the fullest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proper twelve and ginger pre Main event. @TheNotoriousMMA https://t.co/kQUbWGUcYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jere7my @Andres228_AC228 @rianjohnson @LucasTurnbloom @Massawyrm @BBW_BFF @starwars Andres - I'm really sorry that… https://t.co/9GBZO5M8Ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate having to buy guitars so motherfucking much but I DO want to be Tom morello so maybe it’s worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dolojohn7 @MKvidahl @EdGliwa @ThePlumLineGS The creation of DACA was an end around congress and needs to be resolved by congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pharmacological management of pain in patients with CKD ca. 2019 from @CJASN #Nephpearls  👉🏼 https://t.co/fRJz3BOD1e https://t.co/tTl4LnxfZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collin Sexton is coming along slowly. He’s playing the hardest position in the league with barely any coaching on o… https://t.co/Mjs7rJlLmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[BAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!! *loses breath, stops to catch it* BAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrchidShow I just laughed out loud (alone in my hotel room) at this lady saying “I’m an alien. I believed it co… https://t.co/tA5OiwYuOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyTesla4Life @TeslaJoy @marc_benton I’m showing $2k https://t.co/gjqQCsOvN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobVanDillen Some would suggest ...  Indoor practice may have been a smarter decision ...  Cancel the outdoor for… https://t.co/KPDZqXOkDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dart4605 @scented444 @StoneColdChik @2AFan @slickchick81 @KickinBrass1 @elapoides @silentrunning12 @cactusflower81… https://t.co/MfchedLmFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day for Big Blue Nation!  College Gameday from Memorial Coliseum. Big Blue takes down Tennessee. Hamid… https://t.co/VgH5HFBPpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomstakes Chris Long has been highly productive, in fact, more productive in Philly than NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[😻💘💖 #precious #kittykat #catsofinstagram #closeup #fuzzy @ Boiling Spring Lakes, North Carolina https://t.co/5zsHuVGzKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I show up to teach elementary school today and all the kids are wearing their hoodies backwards. Like I just walked… https://t.co/IA9AlxpD1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lemon-Pepper Saison by @sapwoodcellars at @sapwoodcellars — https://t.co/Y985mpmhCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Irwin was and still is the man. Growing up, he made nature and animals cool, interesting, and their conversat… https://t.co/JP9Twstdgl]]></document></documents></author>