<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @PressSec Or is it because you are a shameful, disgraced excuse for an American who should reexamin… https://t.co/IqMPfLXkUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que tipo tan intolerable, misogino y lo que le sigue.. no entiendo porque el presidente @lopezobrador_  no le pone… https://t.co/BrP55wZx6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel bad for de B because he is unfairly attacked from right on crime and from left on housing. Then I… https://t.co/VIdQfeQIHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomchekw @UNLVLadyRebels I’m going to talk to Russ. Maybe he can help you out. He is a real good dude!]]></document><document><![CDATA[mis pensamientos, pero pues cada quien!! Mejor para mí!!🤩  Por orita sere tía ya luego me verán con mis bebés Jajaj… https://t.co/B1LORYGYrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sociobservermex Pero dependiendo de la SEP? Apoyado sí, pero creo que la autonomía es indispensable. Coincido en q… https://t.co/rwDjgZERfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Alexa! She and I painted our hands and made this artwork together. She wrote her name - didn’t she do great… https://t.co/wbiswppUMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellTerrell @jkdncn I loved it!! :) can’t wait to see you, again. Safe travels back home. 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so fortunate to have a wonderful Client Servides Facilitator to organize this and so many activities for our… https://t.co/p4L9Jk6Wg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm off living my life and keep getting notifications of people defending me and standing up for me which is super… https://t.co/SbnGNpgIIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date day part 1 with the hubs @grendelwarwolf ❤️ #brunch #bfgbrunch #bfgb (@ Bonefish Grill in King of Prussia, PA)… https://t.co/nPXZs0by7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years....   I’ve played in a lot of gyms, in front of a lot of crowds, with and against a lot of great athletes… https://t.co/SQprH2cYKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hungry. I miss sternberg. I can’t sleep. I’m sad. I’ll probably be fine tomorrow. And I really want a dog. That’s all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beezybdMRXLSP All this time I thought it went “ trying to get my perfume to be so strong “ 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[here’s some cute throwback pictures with my sis💘 ft. our fav Mr. Earp😊 https://t.co/HcELSRRtWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.4 PK Yonge Blue wave hosting No.1 Jacksonville providence for the regional semifinals]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at #WhimsyCon, a fairly small steampunk and costuming convention in Denver. There’s only a very small crossover… https://t.co/Yrzqa0EG2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has got such bad separation anxiety.... it hurts my heart to leave him every day. 😭💔 https://t.co/fo8Fmlnqbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[big s/o to @EZMoneySniper21 for always dealing with me you’re a real one 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods OMG.  These girls should never have children but not for the reasons they espouse but because they… https://t.co/IWW2w6pM6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @SenJohnKennedy He watched every minute. He cannot explain it. Laim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamDS  I have not heard word one from Trump or the Republicans regarding the domestic, white terrorist a… https://t.co/h67wgBDXoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 It is important to show how stupid and unrealistic the arguments about Dem policy really are Your snark highlights that Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonMartinCTV @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas He asked her if she was open to revisiting it and she said yes, according to… https://t.co/g2zPSpyPeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnfollowTrump yet the Trump companies still make their merchandise outside the US @IvankaTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idek what I did to deserve this but the universe is really testing me rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetNisCupcake Yep. But it was my own stupidity. So today is a new day and I’m going to replace it and not dwell on my mistake. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone bitching on Instagram Valentine’s Day, maybe just delete that horse shit of an app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Erica Flister,  Please stop favoriting freaky tweets about kinky shit, like you don’t know it pops up on EVERY… https://t.co/XTfa1ggj24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family photo. They truly are like twins even though they are 2 of the 6 lol. #puppylove #familyphotography… https://t.co/BYVxEGG7Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sick for the past 4 days and my friend told me “you look awful..in the nicest way”]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Quién tuviera el talento de descubrir el talento de los demás?  Oscar Wilde #OscarWilde #Quote #FraseCita]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why being a night owl might be damaging your mental health  https://t.co/t3DBGbE7db]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF WAY THERE WOOAAHHHH i can’t stretch out in this car and i have a cramp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MizKit2 @RepJeffries Seriously? Do you know who would fight doing that here? The for profit prison system, the alc… https://t.co/4O2QufBtJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really only women who offer a blue seat on the bus to a (clearly) extremely pregnant woman. 🙄 #ttc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jameliamonett_ @Muvamw Goofy as fuck! That nigga will never be BREEZY! He really wish he was on his level! Lame as… https://t.co/YE7rquH0NV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here she is the beautiful @tartecosmetics face tape foundation. I did an all day wear test with this foundation and… https://t.co/bgGblh2w9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[the universe doesn’t owe you shit. karma doesn’t owe you shit. God doesn’t owe you shit. there’s no “meant to be” b… https://t.co/fziM52DQ4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m no expert lol but the comparison I’ve had from good pregnant eating habits to bad pregnant eating habits, that’… https://t.co/IbMwqpF6Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgracemarkham @Best_of_PT I just convinced clients to hop over to Bermuda in March for a quick getaway (they know… https://t.co/cMwg1RFbaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I lost someone whom I truly called my best friend because apparently I’m not loyal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PJ41Bu4D0y #columbiauniversity #ivyleague #schoolofgeneralstudies #StudentDebt #HigherEducation]]></document><document><![CDATA[We grown! Talk to me about something deep! Your morals, fears, family, future, etc. “wyd” is dead !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have literally waited 2 decades for a bill like this one to pass. And while it’s too late for me, I am thrilled f… https://t.co/vedgxqfF4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody can but Trump will continue to con his flock with lots of winning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[go work in customer service and then see if you still support your own tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sisters 👯‍♀️ &amp; niece &lt; 3💝💝💝 #NewProfilePic https://t.co/FBaPDO3ho9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend Joey made this for me. #love #friends #pictures #cute #adorable @ Chino Hills, California https://t.co/RVrRaDL8TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND my son in the background SWERVING my mom... Maa: Austin, bring me a yogurt. Austin: Noooo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I worked out arms yesterday and I’m sore and I love it.... lord please let me keep this energy and keep me going to the gym... amen! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna I’m rewatching the premiere. You’re butt is poppin! 🔥🔥🔥#thosepantsareayes #yasgirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You marketed over and over! Yet on the delivery date you added up inventory with execution. Oops our bad! Deal with… https://t.co/cSE0I3D1Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[vaccines have always given me a true sense of security #measlesfreesince83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning World! 4:43 AM and I’m heading to work https://t.co/RL4G7Avq1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching movies. On a date that started a week ago and hasn't ended. She's been fixing my house up and landscaping… https://t.co/IgGnRgx1BB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump, your deflecting your problems onto Hillary is just tired. Nothing you tweet will cover up y… https://t.co/uF9YLvu2K5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#poetry #prompt #stuff #oneLine  Read the full piece and come play along: “Stuff” by Kathy Jacobs… https://t.co/7x5mSq8ICd]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 4am. the club is PACKED. i’m supposed to hit the road in 4ish hours to go back home. i haven’t made my nightly goal yet. UGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the LONGEST training run I've been able to complete in over 10 months (not including #SBRC track nights) wh… https://t.co/c9jmVC5g8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Because she's not a mole like Manafort... she's actually a hero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking hate that I can hear my roommate chewing. Like I’m literally disgusted I left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 5:30 am and I can’t sleep so I fucked around and became an organ donor]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAOOO but tell me why as soon as i saw my dead grandma laying on my moms bed in my dream i instantly started havi… https://t.co/LEJVCvZfWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't watch or care about the Oscars anymore. Sick of there politics and trashing our President. Lucky they live in… https://t.co/esVTtTu8I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like my job, I really do, but I would rather be getting a root canal than be at the office today.  Related: I hav… https://t.co/CQCV7K7YRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome time at the @GLMakerFaire!  Illustrations by: @SketchSquad123! https://t.co/m0Knx9SOIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicheleyBellie Tech Processing Assistant! Mainly in the back doing receiving, cataloguing, processing, a lil bit o… https://t.co/KLkdOoQivW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJFcolormaster The race was not fixed against him. For Pete's sake. It was a normal, Democratic primary we've had… https://t.co/hZebBdQ3Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnbc We keep hoping on Sunday we will tune in to @MeetThePress and someone other than @chucktodd will be anchorin… https://t.co/jzYd3eNrfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhiannon42 There's a photo sequence of Events trying to catch them and he's just getting progressively more frustrated]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday evening when I reached the restaurant and started unbundling, I realized I had put on three scarves. This… https://t.co/XqDVGAb3py]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny when women think they know what being a “real man” is, and when men think they know what being a “real w… https://t.co/hrIEhCAMKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pint_pound_pate Affordable local travel is more amazing and adventurous than most people think. I hope they explore their area. #UnderRated]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had someone DM me asking if I could be their sugar baby and told me he’d give me 1g weekly 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheV_Quadrant Military is not a solution for IOK. :) IF YOU WILL KEEP SUPPRESSING KASHMIRIS - THESE KINDA THINGS WONT STOP. Take care!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weather_talk @HillaryClinton What the heck did I just read? Something calling itself Weather Stream is trolling… https://t.co/WyVDt1LANl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never had white toes and I never want them. It’s all about black toes ok thanks 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m friends with the right people when almost everyone’s Insta story is just Jonas Brothers everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still life at #Purple party at #PaulsBabyGrand club by #PaulSevigny . #NewYorkFashionWeek #NYfw #portrait #bw… https://t.co/ogik71n4SX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Can Do It! Fixed the Bariatric Wheelchair Tipper In Operatory 9  myself!   Roll em’ in! #XRAY #proudmoment… https://t.co/HRsV2pZ19K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom shares haunting drug overdose photo to warn about US epidemic: 'Stop walking around blindly':… https://t.co/3jj3276WAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanyejulian Lmao a whole block of text when it sounds like she didn’t even realize she was missing it ?? https://t.co/gevbmsK8pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[是日金句： 工欲善其事，必先利其器 #是日金句 #正能量語錄 #慢慢細嚼 @ Ontario, California https://t.co/uz3G0E5odw]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/TuQup6QrZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkarredGhost Thank you so much!! 🎉🙌🏽😎 Can’t wait to release our product into the wild so you can try it! https://t.co/n4GtQubegL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it, it's going to rain this weekend. It was just wishful thinking @ChuckBell4. ☔️ https://t.co/gd7JAlOBcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeldaxlove29 @ultabeauty @JeffreeStar Omg yasss I saw they were building one there and got so excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever looked in the mirror and said, "I believe in you?" How did it feel? Did it resonate with you or did i… https://t.co/SmWTTsikXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[37 weeks 🎊🎉 I’ve made some progress towards delivery. We are tying up details at home. Our bags are packed. 15 days… https://t.co/4GaC3qOg31]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1 Never been to Mardi Gras but been to Fat Tuesday's a few times #Foodiechats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillMcNeff @RealCandaceO @CNN @JussieSmollett That's not far from the truth. How ever, he knows the difference bet… https://t.co/pYuRNM4BNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I miss my animals that have passed so much and then I see a post where people are moving "and just can't… https://t.co/2pm3HdQAKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy Meets Gallery, Betrayal Is it purple or blue? we think it's both! @artistic_nail #artisticcolourgloss… https://t.co/ypCzFu1asb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3/7 of the book cover challenge, challenged by @cschachter Post 7 books you love no explanations, no reviews. T… https://t.co/jVAR939gFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benoriginal Yes you should that’s why i keep retweeting it because we all have to be reminded. 🤞🏾🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rode @CulverCityBus for 30 years. The 3 Crosstown to school at West LA College and work at Westwood and Pico. And… https://t.co/ZggFBFp8MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelDick If he’s staring at you he wants attention. If he’s just staring into space, look it up online. Something… https://t.co/UQjTpXs3rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[KAI loves crystals!!! #cat#crystals#energy#healings @ Alegria Bazaar by Paula Carlotto https://t.co/0C8iBBgvau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another real post over here. 14 months ago I was giving up tracking things for a baby. Joe and I got married i… https://t.co/JXiEI3BW5E]]></document></documents></author>