<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A very on-brand impromptu DC reunion of the kids ready to fight the whole 8th grade social studies class to prove O… https://t.co/zBul5ljVN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salexis19 That’s the point... stay in one place and group... no one will be MIA.... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ijustinj I don't have any where I specifically mix that up -- but in short, yes you can mix it with prodiamine and… https://t.co/LQllkBgI9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[A los exparroquianos del "Patas", que sé que están ahí y me leen; por si no supieron, les comento que el Shine está… https://t.co/Lq6Ujx3QkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar I went out today to look for the @elfcosmetics primer, but I came back empty handed!! 😞 Neither… https://t.co/X8Iih5Ydmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN HE PEAKS HIS LIL NOSE THROUGH AND DOES A BIG SNIFF he’s like yep got em omg I cried my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely example of men ignoring women’s pain is last week male physician telling me I’m not sick and I should stop c… https://t.co/Att5taPzCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shellfarmer @Cupcake021613 @Scott47201 @MsBroz_ @Em45O @JayJay71985738 @purpleroses53 @ArtMarKAS @kevin_lunt @cory830 @TheSicilianDude 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IMPERADOR VE A SI MESMO SENDO UM IMPERADOR, NAO O PRESIDENTE DOS ESTADOS DESUNIDOS DA AMERICA DA MORTE. PRA ELE BO… https://t.co/SU7vIx8p4G]]></document><document><![CDATA['compromise' of sensitive information, following a published report about the Kushner episode.  Her suspension lett… https://t.co/sKdjUGgvUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pernilleripp How often do we as leaders ask our staff the very same question?]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHA Paul Rudd has got jokes tonight when presenting visual effects at the #OSCARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Totalitarianism is a mode of #government that #prohibits #opposition parties, #restricts #individual opposition to… https://t.co/zWPEzXYNni]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to be the next bachelorette. If i don’t find love at least i’ll get to sell stuff on instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one point, me throwing up the peace sign ironically became unironic :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dogsarefeminist @JohnCornyn Should we be expecting them to quote Hitler soon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shedd_stanley @axios My concern is the boy’s behavior, whatever hat he’s wearing. The issue is mutual respect. He… https://t.co/vh5pX8MxR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[But more realistically, my handsome boyfriend of 8 years! Love you @JoshRolon 😘♥️ #iFlyAlaska  #OTRCSweepstakes… https://t.co/UsPWdJYU9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael5SOS This pic is like if @blakeshelton and @gwenstefani got together years ago 😂 love u both. Pls feel free… https://t.co/HragQDKanQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleWCarter What?!?!?! You’re coming to Austin? Which part of SXSW? (And to answer your question; it depends.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#chinesesayings with my #buddy #loveofmylife @ Imperial Garden https://t.co/Rv3NIdNEpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every so often I see a show for the first time that I would instantly see again if there was another show. I buy a… https://t.co/LtAHYJ1du0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sgt_Rambo_N577 shirts/hoodie sale will only be active through THIS Wednesday, March 13th- K9 Veterans Day- get the… https://t.co/1LpU2frbHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs Loved the remarks to the unenlightened article. 😂 We conservatives are accountable to God Who gives… https://t.co/JTQnZ5KgAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know where this is and it is hard to tell what they’ll do. Maybe we can sneak it past them while  crying in… https://t.co/2Qtdei9Jwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I told my seven-year-old how it was impossible for anyone to “earn” a billion dollars and she understood me perfectly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to watch The Lobster, repeat everything Colin Farrell says, and probably be traumatized]]></document><document><![CDATA[6/7 exams down and only one more to go! It’s 35% of my grade, but I already checked out days ago so wish me luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course Western puppet Guaido wants all options open. His preferred option is to have a US-led coup remove Presid… https://t.co/cRYDIUuY9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharylAttkisson Up talkers (valley girl I’m a liberal code talk) are annoying. Also, our Mothers’ taught us to spe… https://t.co/j0nrnbdTX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday cuz, hope u had a good one!! 🎉💙 @ant_sylvester1  (had to bring back this iconic pic) https://t.co/0YJYulTF1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRB watching the @nikewomen spot on repeat, then setting my ⏰ to wake up show everyone what crazy can do 💪 @ Los An… https://t.co/pKfEFZiZnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTChargerTom @DPDErwin @SWISD_PD @JISDPD_Chief @KCDCCCD @jeremy_scruggs @GGalvezDCCCDPD @realmarkharmon… https://t.co/8OGsiu018F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dearest @MPCelina Thank you for your advocacy and care in Black caucus, as a strong woman and showing your courage… https://t.co/74Xm5rocKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I read and hear indicates this is a very strong, thoughtful, well-read, hard working, intelligent, unsel… https://t.co/2SyzQP71lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still shocked that my literature class was half decent last night.....  Jk we didn’t read anything just watched Bra… https://t.co/fNfIbTgOik]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what I like to hear 👏🏽 i know you’re looking handsome like every other day! Love you 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM SO TIRED OF LIBERAL HOUSE AND SENATE MEMBERS WASTING THE PEOPLES TAX DOLLARS ON ENDLESS INVESTIGATIONS JUST BE… https://t.co/QitrKDhKxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kangolforever @wahinyo Sa kilig namula ang beret mo. Jk 😂 and thank youuu ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful medium spiny neurons from the basal ganglia drawn by Ramon y Cajal 😍 #brains #neuroscience #neurons… https://t.co/UFvBalEgN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBNNews @CBNGordon @Franklin_Graham @BGEA Why don’t I feel a sense of purpose? I’m an older woman alone trying to… https://t.co/j1f1jTSWQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein What is the russian word for bible? Asking for a friend.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I changed my whole life when I learned to ignore them https://t.co/nSL9Ibp94C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland  My JEWISH friends are: RBG.  Alan Dershowitz. Jamie Lee Curtis and Karen Seal.  You get any endangere… https://t.co/zvwGqmOP9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Take heed, to the white men in America who still believe because they're white they have special priv… https://t.co/G25u27aQ8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry but i absolutely do not have room in my mental rolodex of Actual No Shit Trump Goons for someone named “Matty Calamari” lmao get real]]></document><document><![CDATA[_taylormadebeauty_ knows me better than I know myself ✨💇🏼‍♀️ Thank you for everything ILYSM❤️❤️ @ The Beauty Bungal… https://t.co/Teqdcfzae1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our custodians, maintenance crew and Chappaqua Transportation worked so hard to get us ready to open today! Thank y… https://t.co/Ccqxe2oxSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHAQ @ShaquillesLA @JeanieBuss @SSJreef Congratulations on your new venture..I'll have a Kobe burger please lol??!… https://t.co/16bg54OqaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Woman by #langleav. Be you, don’t let anyone take your light. We are #fearless, #strong, #unwavering,… https://t.co/7mDyQJNVTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start Your Day Off Sweet Babe 😍 📸 @xxkushqueenxx kushypets • •  #foodblogger #foodblog #foodbeast #feedfeed… https://t.co/HCUDZQz1Zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwoopyTheMogul Bet, join the support group and share your feedback on this experience with others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixers I have to get this off my chest I feel this down in my gut. I’m thrilled Joel is back BUT I think Butler is… https://t.co/5IMcnSl4C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelicans flying away when I came near. I never knew their wings are black underneath. There were hundreds and I hav… https://t.co/KGGJybaePr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear fellow white people, Please stop. If you can’t deal with folks who don’t look like you, stay home.  Thx.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing weekend trip to Joshua Tree with good friends! Can’t wait to go back! So beautiful! @ Joshua Tree, C… https://t.co/H0qybxtgg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ReginaKing on your win! Total goddess status in your dress ♥️ #Oscars #2019Oscars #bestsupportingactress]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Gratitude is Riches, Compliant is Poverty.” -Doris Day. . . Grateful for the life I get to create everyday💖 . .💫It… https://t.co/DWChzMc3cY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This drunk lady came out of nowhere and sat down &amp; was like “you got some GREAT BOOBS”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pinté mi cabello gris y mis amis no me bajan de que estoy cerrando ciclos. Putos todos. Yo me siento con muchos… https://t.co/J0MlQIvFTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would give the fae my name just to drown myself in hozier’s bog man music, and that’s just the facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBlankenshipWSB @KarenMintonWSB Congratulations Karen. I wish you all the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello stop messaging me just to say na mataba ako, I want to be honest din “madami kasi akong pera” HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga From one fibro warrior to another, you looked stunning last night and showed your true grit. Your gratefu… https://t.co/772QG2S1X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabenfica51 @acotrozzi @DoriCreates @AnnamariaVendi2 @AleZ2016 @zale3151 @DebbieS00060220 @DebEdmonds60s… https://t.co/GML0WxJlx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallKingBand @garthbrooks I LOVE this opening and song!! Thank you so much for it. It sounds even better live. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 @TeamArianaMadix @TomSandoval1 You guys are #goals I can’t get enough!! Congratulations on your new home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe’s So blinded by Tristan’s lies so of course she will put all the blame on Jordyn. She really needs to wake the hell up 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[To mto feliz que agr é March break nmrl, fazia tempo q n tinha “férias”]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Mac Miller said “why you always at the mall when you broke” like i felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_NeedThtThrone I said this last year. I said “Y’all think Gruden ain’t got something up his sleeve with all those… https://t.co/S8CB8gf28k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piedmont’s first ever STUNT tournament was a success!! 2-1 go cats! @PiedmontSchools @PiedmontAth @Piedmont_cheer… https://t.co/Bsc215phKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really coming down in Tacoma. And traffic coming to a standstill by the Tacoma Mall. ❄️❄️❄️ @KSeattleWeather #wawx https://t.co/OQT6CxFLNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Look back at my tweets, I said this several days ago. His Lawyer is working on a case where he just… https://t.co/px7EN7Supl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I think it’s a great process because it’s about competition,” Kastama said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love traveling, but honestly, guys, it can really take a toll on me. And knowing that starting tomorrow, my March… https://t.co/xrL5OmdRHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a job in the medical field, The Hospitals of Providence is wanting to interview you at their… https://t.co/fsGhiOVbis]]></document><document><![CDATA[My burn itches so bad how bad is it second #SecondDegreeBurn hazard of my job #Chef #ChefsLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says @TravelAtWill @TheTravelCamel @Touchse @iamvagabond It was one of the best trips to date - very unique!! ☃️❄️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobile its disappointing that u have not responded to my previous tweet.  I DO NOT want to download your… https://t.co/mE7IlKmyVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most iconic signs in the world!!!  ● ● ● ● vegas #lasvegas #vegasstrip #lasvegasvacation #nevada… https://t.co/RKdWHqoRDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the story of two families in St. Louis dealing with heartbreaking loss. It could be the story of any one of… https://t.co/P4uFXeHWxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 He has no real friends or associates. They're all thugs con men thieves and traitors. Even his family are criminals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have assigned “digital essays” with hyperlinks. The language continues to transform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[how does one do their eyeliner with eyelash extensions bc my lashes are not even that long but they're naturally curly and i sTRUGGLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooh gorl it’s pretty out. @ Fremont East District https://t.co/qTQdAKkOeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zariabledsoe Yes mam. Next game is Tuesday at 7:00pm!! Its our prayer that we make it down your way! 🤞🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julie_kelly2 @MollyJongFast Her reporting sounds about right to me. I applaud her for her sacrifice of actually go… https://t.co/UaGIWEP1NF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellActuary @RantsByMegan I think in my head she's exactly my age but she's actually a little older. She's pretty… https://t.co/5WQcM9D4iI]]></document><document><![CDATA[That morning after a brake up be making you feel empty af tbh.. I’ll be okay tho just gotta thug that shit out 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I love him! but..why are you still in Freddie Mercury character? It's Over Bruhh you Won! Stop already its just… https://t.co/rhsxCdz7m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/SMQYdH5EBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can't believe they remade a show about our shitty little town and its actually popular lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartiVzla POR FAVOR NO MAS BURROS que aprendan primero a hablar y leer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still one of my most favorite wedding moments, when Rebecca walked down the aisle with her new husband Chuck, and b… https://t.co/r0R2jndp8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I SAY IF YOURE IN COLLEGE ENJOY TF OUT OF IT BECAUSE IT ONLY HAPPENS ONCE, AND MANY WOULD AGREE RELATIONSHIPS ARE N… https://t.co/Q7iCNz8iNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I want a relationship, sometimes I don’t wanna risk looking stupid again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2WinFlame True, they will protect your emotions and love you unconditionally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/Her PDMP profile reflects 4+ physicians because her prior clinic was CPS which shut down 54 clinics in 12 states… https://t.co/PBpO6LwtN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Him but he's not the one who's doing the interview she is]]></document></documents></author>