<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @NVEmergencyMgmt for hosting and inviting @NCBRT to the 2019 Preparedness Summit! https://t.co/HB4YwI8COd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs @jigsawdeal YES!!! WORKING HARD TO MAINTAIN ELECTED CON ARTISTS TO USE YOUR MONEY FOR THEIR CONS AND… https://t.co/XEINGy5tw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew_Tynan I don’t think they wanted to give a multi timed remake an award. Plus Thr Greem Book was a tremendous story,]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍10 BEST LOW CALORIE CONDIMENTS📍 — A lot of people don’t realize how many calories can sneak their way in through c… https://t.co/cmFvqcg5rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Liar.  She has never worked a day in her life, just like you.  Can’t wait to see your air… https://t.co/zeFFIqDiYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeez. Said it before, I’ll say it again. There is no one who loves the U.S. more than Albania and Kosovo. First cou… https://t.co/Vl8S76gwjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpbferr @xan_desanctis So ?  They may have personalities that are entirely disagreeable but true intellectual hone… https://t.co/wGtPtBZW1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhamfiremedic I agree but that’s a slippery slope especially in states who work the 3 platoon system. Any way you… https://t.co/w8vxZAgx2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say this game features the two most historic programs in college lacrosse history.   Unfortunately, I was neve… https://t.co/QpoLOUC1BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok guys @airfrance apologies for being high maintenance earlier. I just really need to get to London...… https://t.co/S4d3Nb04wM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama’s bomber jacket that just says “44” might be one of the most baller things I’ve ever seen #DukeUNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[7:15 AM Service  "Christianity Is Not About Image, Its About Grace" Ephesians 2: 1-10 Rev. Ben Lollie]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t, if you not giving the time of day to somebody you wanna be with somebody else will....]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/10/2019 - 22:19 Temp: 52.3F   Hum:  65% Wind: 2.0 mph Baro: 30.256in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miketarasow @Jensnh87 Don’t be going on those stupid little websites That the mainstream media want you to get to.… https://t.co/vm3aOYKb4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatAngererUSA @HawkeyeReport Wow. @MattRandazzo looks better like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ceci est la première chose que vous verrez en arrivant en enfer https://t.co/c3PRremVax]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Through It All by @jbutlerguitar, from #SoundHound https://t.co/LxoTNuiO1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakersfieldpd It's amazing how the patrol car have changed over the years !  to see the crown vic still in service… https://t.co/iEhTxJKd98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao @bunnyyybby ok I think I’m ready to forgive you cuz I need you right now stormi can’t hold the phone for shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Yes Jamele, first they turn on that soul like Barry White or Marvin Gaye. Real Dogs take it slow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun and RELAXING day in Boone. Nature, wine, nap, beer, food. #boone #nap #beerandwine @ Boone, North Carolina https://t.co/HQWHvdClF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Luke Combs said, “well it kinda scares me the way that she drives me wild” He should’ve said, “it kinda scares me the way she drives”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the dogs insist on staying outside 3x longer when the weather is like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfallik @kristyshines Make sure you come by the @AmplifyPhilly house if you weren’t already planning on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RowlandRIVALS Young man is VERY astute regarding how to make it big in the 🏀 world &amp; beyond!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crysdb @theroyreport @mothersell32 @MAADIE_ @madmoneymeg @jcrowtc @JasonFi09345466 @AustinTGCA @cele_estrada03 Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on down to honeywhytesrva tonight. Grab a #burger and a #beer and watch the #cats in @docvelo_mpj get busy pla… https://t.co/WzC85P12Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysonbuford You see the Athletic piece today? https://t.co/kUjVeTbbDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving away Fried Baloney recipes @OaklawnRacing as horses are loading in to the gate is just one example of why I… https://t.co/y6jcD3klkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet that he had bone spurs but kept on going.   https://t.co/iAP8v5ijn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years on Twitter! I still remember posting my first tweet from London: “Finally managed to download the new Waif… https://t.co/n6474oMZKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok did rand paul get brain damage when he was attack hey you are a republican stand by our president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abducted In Plain Sight.  What the hell was wrong with those people!   That’s your baby!  Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been following the challenge on mtv for years now &amp; this season is sooooo good 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why type of psycho decides that tax season is a good time to cut back on coffee?   It’s me... I’m that psycho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umbrella Academy on Netflix made me realize just how badly Fox has mismanaged the X-Men franchise over the years. M… https://t.co/qVMacQEQUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[$100 to any girl whos middle name isn’t:  -Angelica -Cynthia -Didi -Susie -Lillian -Tommy -Chuckie -Reptar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaOfTheImpact @packratt1 @NXOnNetflix @NumbZombieMom https://t.co/ycLEzie6r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbobwilliamson @mkraju Exactly. India and Pakistan haven't tested since 1998. The US last tested in 1992 and befor… https://t.co/IHJC3ZQ3zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigftdaddy @LionelMedia You can 7mi from my house in Quincy. City of Presidents.  I got fake news. Most valuable t… https://t.co/RrQXiVmgje]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cup collection grows #mardigras2019 #nolaproblems https://t.co/aHNTV4pIh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlc2558 @JimCarrey He's fine. What does he need to be investigated for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to a great friend, love you ev and hope your day is amazing. i miss all the memories and i can’t wai… https://t.co/7fPofeOU4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder how many times I’ll drive 20 minutes to campus this semester just to find out class is canceled before I sta… https://t.co/3LnW0n3iIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING Massive fire in #Hopewell we’re headed there now. Look for updates on @NBC12 https://t.co/SLAZZjkDap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving Las Vegas is on and I’ve never seen it, so I turned it on. 10 minutes in, this was already a very strange m… https://t.co/jQmGJlCLaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisOD65316390 Then, when you stop crying, could you list Obama’s accomplishments? There are 23 I believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoda The word placement here is pretty brilliant as it hints that social networks were somehow ever built “for pri… https://t.co/AuODDyXnf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris yes enough is enough.  resign, step down, quit. Make America great again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crislopezg Not true - it’s been discussed heavily throughout the week, this is what’s wrong with America, people s… https://t.co/qxGAxNUvIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday and cheers for my special day today yall are invited to come https://t.co/etUFWBVBru]]></document><document><![CDATA[At home, in the snow, drinking a margarita and watching #MNUFC. Can’t beat that!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was out running 2.25 km with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/7SKeDjiyL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firestorm616 @TransformersTCG Burn in hell. LOL. 3.5 Boxes deep to get the Bumblebee Super Rare.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Column: Post-Dispatch remains profitable. But its revenues continue declining, as they are across the industry. Lee… https://t.co/5ENbd7nnKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[She only been in this country 5-6 yrs is she a citizen? How is  this possible????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElliottStephenB @WuTangClan @theryman Ooh, an oversight on my part. Might get me into the weeds of deeming what is… https://t.co/ko5iEGOspC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraMariaMTV Doesn’t matter as long as you get to where you want to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of loads that NBA players are managing this year would rival most porn stars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @RuggedPatriot5 @RepDebDingell @kasie Her noise doesn’t even make sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is eye level. Way past Chihuahua measurement. @ Saint Cloud, Minnesota https://t.co/RJXxQ4PJQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notogsixer @askmeabouthelaw @mavus15 So when I have an opinion it’s speculation but when you do it’s gospel? GTFOO… https://t.co/ANtrKZHxhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linda_whyman @bigvaldrewski @Peston Corbyn doesn't seem too interested in Labour members' near universal desire fo… https://t.co/q7kacTr3GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenLisaBoscola Please support the new grand jury investigation into the truth of 9/11. I know it’s not your state,… https://t.co/nPwsdN8tAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Game @JamesNahikianBG strikes again! I love the dedication man! @BGSUMHoops #AyZiggy #FlyWithUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time back in here since surgery, and loving it. #MMA #muaythai @ The Academy: Pittsburgh MMA &amp; Fitness https://t.co/RXSZ7VzbD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for Lebron to miss the playoffs #ShouldOfCameToPhilly #SpaceJam2 doe, much more important than winning basketball games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading National Institute of Standards and Technology's material, yes, "Daylight saving time, or DST, is the perio… https://t.co/LGeoWxI0LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three years ago I was shredded, if I can do it once I can do it again. https://t.co/VbHJ978eyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[But in the meantime Chelsea need to shock the world and myself by winning this game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVic @DetroitRedWings His stories were the best. His memory was sharp as a tact!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khalitoris Not playing at all bruh. Type in Southwest in the search they have the link. https://t.co/FeKJRpQGyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmanuelMacron This probably won't come out right.. but I will try.  YOU have 70 million citizens depending on you… https://t.co/Nno5WtGMoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdmondsSpencer Nah he’s gonna say that whenever he sees a turbo kit come in the mail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gangs as like U.S. gang bangers, its cartail , it's not like some general nut case American criminal, walks int… https://t.co/0FzGYaB1c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher Something happened on that golf course with @POTUS over a year ago with Lady Graham @LindseyGrahamSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a beautiful golden sunrise🌞 from work🏢 this morning, over the Sandia Mountains🌄, here in #Albuquerque,… https://t.co/UTPWBeYyVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorOsty @ElvisKnows @AGrossNewsday @BComptonNHL Was from the Soundtigers beatwriter, I believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump You got the McDonald logo on your forehead bruh😂😂😂🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need @mrvincecarter15 to come out and show these fools one last time how a #nbaslamdunkcontest should look like b… https://t.co/9RIK00QS1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW PRS for @nlukens Snatch, CJ, and Clean. WILL IT? WILL IT.  Hit me up if you are interested in coaching. I can h… https://t.co/DU3q4Cc87O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aikengolfclub Was at awards dinner last night    and heard Jim’s acceptance speech. Some of the most humble and he… https://t.co/gfwyVAyCoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making rolled flank steak with bacon jam and smoked gouda for tomorrow's Chain of Lakes Eggfest in Winter Haven FL… https://t.co/0dKbcv4gA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, you've played Uno.... but have you played DOS?! ✌🏽✌🏼 @ Ali Cat Toys https://t.co/1Fr8wYUcoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of hope (1968) and the rise of the privately owned command economy in the U.S.    https://t.co/qehUC8ODPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked this song better when it was called “Revolution” by @kirkfranklin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read the menu in @JoeSantagato trump voice!! #basementyard https://t.co/VuuOGY5hwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inject all the Duke-UNC games being replayed on ESPNU for the next 24 hours into my veins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NHdiving If you can read my awesome (go along with it 😉) handwriting, here's how NH area stands through prelims https://t.co/5LmnpU2Y2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSchultz13 @SenCoryGardner Sounds like a fantastic idea! Now to get Washington to agree with this! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenían a Lady Gaga en la panadería de Soriana y ahora está todo Born this way a todo volumen en mi casa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out #tedcruz will vote against @realDonaldTrump border wall. Really really really disappointed☹  My fami… https://t.co/l7ruyjBRxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy galentine’s day from the pink room. 💕 @ Provisions on Perkins https://t.co/grvhEM6j5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/3lX5zYdtp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarstProduction @diegoarguello66 @playcritically No one thing in S.F. strikes me as divinely “gotta have it” delic… https://t.co/Am8Ympdynz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the HS show choir group and HS jazz band!   You guys are awesome!   So many kids that do so many thing… https://t.co/cwFq2tDop4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murallaverde Claro, ayer en fútbol picante Hugo Sánchez dijo que cuando el jugó en el america el árbitro de vendió… https://t.co/A5S96miWGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guerrillacrypto @Novo_Burgo @TeaBoots @JohnWagner2014 @BrianKolfage I have lost interest in you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swing by any of our stores and we’ll be happy to help you pick out a bottle of wine, beer or spirits for tonight’s… https://t.co/GMbFjqmYVz]]></document></documents></author>