<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s The Bitches, Leave these hoes alone.. the drugs bad   #DontDoDrugsKids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition  This is frightening. We are on the edge.  What happens next?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelbrownPR @JonnyFreds A friend in legal is a friend for life. #PRlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sebastien_Btte @fallusinant @Enfantsdelatele Ça ne sera JAMAIS aussi bon que le fabuleux « On tourne, on tourne, o… https://t.co/QXo6z1mxT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Go pound sand.  And while your at it, it's been over 2 years and our Sweet President still hasn't all his pe… https://t.co/FkBPv42M62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ThatsSumerlin @youlovevicc @topchef_cici @princess_mwoods @ashyaspade @Nanibearz @Amber_Janessa @cc_shaakira… https://t.co/Z5dMRTay96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen he would make a good vp  he is very progressive and he has alot of experience and he isnt old]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s weather is suppose to be 63 degrees and cloudy and 81 degrees tomorrow       😱😱😱😱😱😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bake sale for the #victoriahumanesociety ! #puppies #kittens #cookies #Cupcakes #doglovers #catlovers… https://t.co/d4tCavytRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Michelle 🐶 👻 🚔 💖 @CmreddingDoodle ,Luis Beltran @luisbeltran7771 ,SHIRISH JOSHI @SHIRISH65149661, Edit(h)… https://t.co/dIUusipKpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello homie i got this on the fourth but when i go to the link it still says its just confirmed and to check back w… https://t.co/aUK2Cvxqa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Jr. Mint: quoting The Federalist?  You love your right wing hate groups a lot. https://t.co/lWW4UJYwKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s a disgusting pig!  It seems most republicans desire to follow Satans ways.  At least the ones I’ve been privy… https://t.co/sRyjyhezuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to disturb some college kids and comfort some others. #nacafestival #noshame #triggerwarning @ Shippensburg U… https://t.co/ef3aOxvycw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddywrbcks @EricReidell @MsCamilleRaye Hahahahah gfe on point *** who want a girlfriend anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet She has to go.  Her votes and what she defends are unacceptable to me, I hope others feel that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done @gbtpa_aus - so proud of our sister colleagues in AU and love with the recognition!  #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisMcQuigge @loleen_berdahl @BeccaRAlice Sorry I misunderstood - I have definitely encounter that view from oth… https://t.co/oEuvFuo7zC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, to riff on @Kristen_Arnett, venmo a woman today so that she can buy alcohol and/or cake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[210 pounds gone and yet it still feels surreal. It's incredible what you can accomplish when you hit rock bottom.… https://t.co/JvdJNudtlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[هؤلاء لا عندهم إنسانية ولا دين #ما_خفي_أعظم_أين_الجثة  في الفرن وجبة لأبو منشار لعنة الله عليهم]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump, what about you paying back the Federal Government for the billions you withheld in taxes fo… https://t.co/1BbPJAwhF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AboutLastNight The “Kid Ink” Dinner 🍽 With Friends.....aka @Kid_Ink DINNER 🥘 WITH @1035TheBEAT DJ’s... Starring:… https://t.co/USyVZzLVT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 month today... #khaleesi2019 #galleguillosmiraclebaby #blessed🙏🏽 #1montholdtoday @ Keizer, Oregon https://t.co/S5EptxbS1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t be friends with nancy, you have to wake her up yourself EVERY TIME y’all have to be up early]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yo_Hernandezzz Girl I know I don’t have time for people nomore. I don’t mess with nobody like that anyway so it will be empty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianne727 @amandapalmer I have three daughters. It wasn’t unavoidable, but in comparison to most, we avoided it pr… https://t.co/M2M4KK5Q2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPCS_TN we have the most wonderful readers!!! Thank you, Mrs. Robin Brown, for sharing your expertise and for brin… https://t.co/7lrF3HPEjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day work to become a better you. Not the people you see on your feed or on TV, YOU!  Reposting @AnotherGear__… https://t.co/Zdsd7OH978]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our big day is here Day Of We!  Looking forward to the message our community leaders will share with our students today!  #FMSBoltpride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I didn't wear my boots since precipitation wasn't predicted https://t.co/glM3od9Gd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen The naivete is sweet, Ed.  But they don't feel the same as you do, about the country or the oath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to eat dinner today, but happy birthday to Dwayne R., the boy I had a crush on in 5th grade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio But you are fine with humanitarian crises of kidnapping babies here? You are fine with white nationalis… https://t.co/OvUu6UeOVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chouchoutv @wralbleslie @WRAL Look at you guys still@color coordinating! #retirementlooksgoodonyoubill]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I wear, what my hair looks like, how popular I am, who i know, NONE OF THT MATTERS TO YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I play a 67 point word in Words With Friends against my grandma knowing it’s going to ruin her whole day https://t.co/ykFpy7L44t]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad the Y&amp;R is doing this.  Kristoff can not be replaced.  Will miss having Neil on the show!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might have said this before, but I think this might be my favorite tablet stand. I truly believe that if you are… https://t.co/djkENDdvlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd time to shovel today and mickeytx04 came out to help :) @ Berlin, Connecticut https://t.co/9gptYQbclX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ontario regulator pays whistle-blowers $7.5-million, a first for Canada /via @globeandmail https://t.co/HuYefAeK5e… https://t.co/Rt3kfuyiDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halferrier Omg I must’ve only watched a clip of it then..... interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe this was one year ago, today! The first interdistrict virtual exchange! So thankful for @awgtis and M… https://t.co/9LN0cLwp8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[what usually happens when i commend ‘HAHAHA’ on someone’s story   me: HAHAGAHAGA them: HAHAHA SKSKS me: SKSJSJS  th… https://t.co/tc2F1vAYvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @ljohn44 "Why would he lie about that - it doesn't even matter" makes a pretty good motto for the Trump admin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Short &amp; Stout by @scmbrewing at @scmbrewing — https://t.co/EQpvQDkbLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealrkl @LeanRight3 @BlodGlipn @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Obstruction of justice? Please be more specific.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Give it fucking up. We know! https://t.co/o4rgY2ci5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker PLEAAAAASE... don’t hate me..... pleasaaase... WAHHHHHHH😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of birthday wishes to my son, Cam💙 This young man can drive me insane and within seconds have me wrapped a… https://t.co/ZLjDCBcXdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turhan3rd @Hey_Tierra @_iKadeeja Y’all are the best!! Thanks so much!! I’ll see where to go next! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just need motivation to be that girl that wakes up at 5am to go to the gym...🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made these collard green veggie rolls; absolutely reccomend. #nomnom #veggiesandfiberandallthegoods  https://t.co/Cle9x3HGuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolaescreva @CatiaAmorim5 PQP! ESTA IGREJA JA ESTA MORRENDO. VAI OERDER MAIS PARA AQUELAS OUTRAS DIABOLICAS TAMBEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExiledHeroine Don't do it unless you are prepared to drink Pabst blue ribbon and do heroin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ref with a shocking decision in Fergie Time to give United a late win… Ole’s really brought us back! #mufc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azcentral That will keep the crooks from moving here. DNA tests for everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You 👏 can’t 👏 put 👏 Google 👏 down 👏 as 👏 a 👏 photo 👏 sour e 👏 Why 👏 is 👏 this 👏 so 👏 hard 👏 to 👏 understand 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YahooSports @ATLUTD @TheChampions The stream keeps freezing when you open it to full screen 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda like puking everyday bc it pops blood vessels in my face and makes me look like I have freckles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly vagabond: excuse me miss, do you have 50¢  Me: *accidentally initiating Siri to listen for my command* I’m… https://t.co/UidV33UTxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #TillyTuesday  Answer WWTD (What Would Tilly Do) AND then do it... 🐰🐰🐰💜 https://t.co/E4oa1LDxzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three hour layover = finally finished this book. I'm mad that I didn't discover Kingsley Amis until I was in my 30'… https://t.co/WgmNTCawRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday’s are serious business ya know.   #levonthelover #levon #aussie #levonhelm #dogslife #instadog… https://t.co/p1J6argAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • @hey__sweetie__ Looking to buy or sell in Durham and the Kawarthas? @trishialtodd specializes i… https://t.co/GIaW9kE1Wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda want to get back into Destiny but Jesus this seems like a tall mountain to climb these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay @lyricspoetic I agree with Joe’s argument about the integrity side. My thing is...Monique is trying to play bo… https://t.co/3OB1VW9shl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when on cooking shows you can hear the fork scrape the judge’s teeth. Use your lips, please. 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[how did i drink a redbull and then nap for 2 hrs i’m tired as hell i have to get on a mf bus in like an hour and a half can i Die]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throughout history, reading and writing have been tools of protection @AlfredTatum Reading is so incredibly impor… https://t.co/RCX0pJprMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[About yesterday: : If I’m not teaching, I’m learning! Great monthly accountability luncheon @ philanddereks with my… https://t.co/XIgq0IivJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG. If I hear “There was no collusion” spewing from Trump’s mouth one more time, I swear I’m going to lose it in an epic way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGKennedyOU_1 @SauterRory @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Really??  Try coming up with something new and or… https://t.co/DFup1eitAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UmbrellaAcad  Westworld Harry Potter  Batman Spiderman Goodnight Moon Outlander  Fantastic Four Yet uniquely itself! Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @SpeakerPelosi threatens a National emergency in an attempt to take away conservatives guns, but she doesnt cons… https://t.co/s4XNvzcAaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyNPH Neil you may not be the Peacock on The Masked singer but my dog thinks he is Neil “PAW”trick Harris ❤️🐶 https://t.co/xuxUOO4g9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to our boys' and girls' 🏀 teams, and our #NAL team!   The basketball #AllisonBabyEagles play @WpsBrooks th… https://t.co/SGBf80hOTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety Did you see the cookie she pulled out of that pocket later during the night?  #epic #queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GermanyDiplo @HeikoMaas ¿Sabe usted quién es el Alto Comisionado de las Naciones Unidas para los derechos humanos?… https://t.co/LQj7ftKhRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s 2020 Campaign Kicks Off With A Carnival Of Lies In El Paso https://t.co/VLQUebsAhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anitakirkbride I forgot quiche was...and frittata is, too. Damn, I got too excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gulnar_Bubeeva @WDimash @ElinorDear @Lindsay07474358 @charlilovesyou1 @DearStan7 @DimashMX @DimashIfied @dzemiodek… https://t.co/9f1nsnjLEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shabbat shalom! A home cooked #vegetarian dinner to start a weekend of rest. @ Southeast, Washington, D.C. https://t.co/3nvAomHkoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the new @OfficialPLT office! I could take pics in here all day!  Dress: @OfficialPLT 🦄 @ PLT L.A Office https://t.co/IXmzXXRR1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milton_Margiela Lol I went. I went to every single game with the exception of one, ticket prices are not the same… https://t.co/Sn9ILfTzrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish as a native of our gorgeous state, w/no ms13 in it. Wish u would go back to WY. What if ur Immigrant grandpa… https://t.co/6WSda0NWV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @trinity_titans Family/Advisory had a few special guests at our all-school mass today. ❤️🙏🏼 #TitanPride #TCHS https://t.co/I9GHoIiW6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya I bet that’s how the guy feels when he goes down on you too so chill with the sexist tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight filet mignons on the menu, i can see my breath while grillin 🆒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad driving on the roads according to #OPP #Toronto #Ontario Careful driving don’t panic they say to take it easy i… https://t.co/TMEBcej6T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone gave me major ojo today because I went from feeling great to feeling like shit in a matter of 3 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn't be surprised if someone takes Maduro out.  People aren't going to sit by as the people of Venezuela starve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel and I have only been together for an hour and he already made me dinner someone wife him up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this guy at work offered to train me for free and he could come to my house or i could go to his house... seems legit right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBryanOnline @AmericanIdol This young man has amazing talent, is respectful and so humble! He’s going to do great things! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brooksie1Jenn @METUPorg According to the @mbcalliance a study reviewing @NCIResearchCtr breast cancer funding they… https://t.co/5DSvapDZHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Augmon Sister are back on the hunt to be Champs again! This time on separate teams. Leilani Augmon, Silver Cree… https://t.co/GJxn8ayMrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the last day of #BlackHistoryMonth, I'm sharing the work of one of my closest friends and the most amazing peop… https://t.co/Z4uJxk6Rx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chelsealinaeve @kpowell624 @QuinceMountain A cheese curd is a little ball of salty, creamy, squeaky heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEDUSAS_BROTHER @MadonnaNation @Retweet4Madonna @MDNAMafia @MadonnaCharts_ @radityaoka1 @HOLY_WATER_ @madrevo1… https://t.co/UrhhbhN0vv]]></document></documents></author>