<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AOC Omg get over yourself. You need to go live in a communist country. We dont want you here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher I think he'll axe the 22nd Amendment and declare himself king.]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank god my mental health is so trash because now i have so much more time to be funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zclark730 27 Lakeside JHS students will graduate from the English as a 2nd Language program on Wednesday-would you… https://t.co/LoxlCY7mvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacqualineL_ I know it deep down inside. But I’ve got a serious problem with patience. And then I think the fact I… https://t.co/X6OkYWt7xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy dance for my $20 #ootd I’m dressed head to toe in fashion finds from @thefamilyplaceresaleshop! Been? Designe… https://t.co/grWDnIJmeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MrsAdam1010 to post the covers of 7 books I love (pleasure or professional) with no… https://t.co/NUOhXJtTWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are not...in the middle of a new propaganda war. The old one just never went away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I'm capable of is avoiding life's unsettling confrontations. All I can do now is scream and go to bed forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyMuseJennifer Me too! The worst wrecks were on 70 around mile marker 30-50. I’m off mile 21. Another storm tonigh… https://t.co/JSLKoOs4Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of the problem is how these types of crashes are reported (not in this particular piece). If you read “a car h… https://t.co/s9Vg9vysne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chocolateE2858 @stuartbache @JaneyGodley Def an imposter. We all know Melanie won’t hold his hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngiTaylorKISS @PaulinaRoe I love her!!! Would just like to spend a day with her and watch and listen]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy just asked me why I went to commerce instead of TCU... BITCH IM POOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just a suggestion stay there and help them through their trouble times are drag them into the hole… https://t.co/Po4sBwelMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yahoo Entertainment: Will Smith's rumored new role is causing controversy — because of his skin color.… https://t.co/lGL7pyHtgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson I hope the judge throws the book at him so hard it flips him over in his wheelchair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and support our students @SSTSanAntonio at their STEM festival! https://t.co/WMXt7O89g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why didn't they ask Haley or Alex talk to Lily about Aunt Flo? #ModernFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnTory @cityoftoronto @TorontoPFR @MLSEFoundation @CTJumpstart Out New Children's Charity is starting to get cos… https://t.co/zS0QRnsSOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t believe me, look up the public record for yourself... https://t.co/XsMYotanGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi get the facts 1st sweetheart 🇺🇸👍🏻 innocent until proven guilty is no longer valid since journalists… https://t.co/qTHqJ6d48w]]></document><document><![CDATA[“𝓦𝓪𝓷𝓭𝓮𝓻𝓵𝓾𝓼𝓽 “ [photo of sandy asscheeks that will not leave the premises of an English-speaking Cancun resort durin… https://t.co/PofF1QRDbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenYulinCruz @BernieSanders @Latinos4Bernie Nope. A WHITE reggae band? Are you kidding, typical Bernie. He will… https://t.co/TGs1S0BQKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way I love the one I call That Little Crow.  I am lashing at you. You know what you did, and should have kno… https://t.co/pAY0QZ5GWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePettyMess_ I think after her coming home she became worse God forgive me for saying that I know she had to be t… https://t.co/hdC7n46b8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder: We knew that MoC were briefed by the FBI. We knew McConnell wouldn’t allow any of it to go public. We kne… https://t.co/uLI0PaR2iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dindycelic Still gets me whenever I realize I no longer have a second wardrobe to tear apart when I’m running late… https://t.co/VeWf3Fr04U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm loving all them Pepsi commercials with @iamcardib brrrrrrrRrr owwww 😛😜😝😂😂😂 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not believe my eyes! Not a popular breed and not a high residential area. I b-line to the dog, in tears, an… https://t.co/LYZT2lL1Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a blessed day everyone @ The Auditorium at The Douglass https://t.co/mERKakZA6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s high on the list...hope she’s ready once I get my move done and my wifi back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLCFertco @A_Dilettante_ I would not. Stop assuming clown lmao I'm not even offended. The point is you don't ask c… https://t.co/0GzKOZQSuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought my fiancé to his first hockey game tonight 🥰 #HappyValentines #LAKINGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day: another day to #treatyoself, eat all the chocolate, and own your growth in self-love. So, you are… https://t.co/LEEFhuxnFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s handing out drivers licenses in Baltimore. I have some questions https://t.co/iWL2dIWwZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the first movies I’ve ever seen were with @elijahwood therefore...my firstborn will be named Frodo and my m… https://t.co/dZGgPMOXTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell Net Neutrality is bad for the little guys, like me, and my neighbors.  It's good for the big guys,… https://t.co/9AoJ4JhKwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurespin @ladycaviar @cookingmama48 @ThatEricAlper I had one of those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In hospital w husband yesterday and going back today because he’s coughing a lot &amp; easily fatigued.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump No, we did not watch the Apprentice! I did however love the John Barron chronicles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i truly miss when my friends were single . i’m tired of being the second option https://t.co/4hBopKN5GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow Judging by your artwork, you and I could be best friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[def know what it feels like wanting to murder someone due to negligence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Independence Day to My beautiful country Dominican Republic!!!!!! #platanopower #imdominican #quisqueyabellla… https://t.co/sq74MsnLo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign to oppose David Bernhardt’s nomination for Secretary of the Interior Department. Sign here: https://t.co/Ch0fpSt1L4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a game is much more important than fixing your relationship...  Lmao what a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giles_fraser 2) From the USA to the UK, this non stop diabolization of immigration uninformed, moronic. What are w… https://t.co/w79WWCzeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why people think it’s funny ybn almighty jay getting robbed for his chain is funny. This shit happens in the hood is it funny then]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I worked an entire kitchen shift with fake lashes on and I truly believe I can do anything now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Member pics are the BEST and we can’t get enough!  If you’d like to be featured on our Social Media pages, send you… https://t.co/iGs3fWFklQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#options #hub #louisville #kentucky @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/pUH47V8pg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to burst out laughing. #humor #laugh #smirk #cute https://t.co/ccgGk5YfyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Wow amazing how many public figures feel empowered by Trumpism to spew their racist opinions. Is this o… https://t.co/4Zibq9RSHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CletoRodriguez @NikuKazori @AudreyKENS5 @ForganySarah @barrydavistv @MHurstKENS5 @HenryRamosTV @RoxieBTV @JoeKENS5… https://t.co/Uox50E60Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s Big Willie she’s sitting on. Sarah puts them in wheel together a lot. Sometimes she scolds Donut for being r… https://t.co/CIEu0lPaOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my piece from the #artomat in the Cosmopolitan! Made a great souvenir from our trip to #LasVegas 💖💫 Check out… https://t.co/hE3mnx3JGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitchickfriday Repost from iamashleyortiz_ Too much to ask for ? 🌹 @ New York, New York https://t.co/oomZ6j8Esk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's obvious that those jerks has done lots of damage for Michael, radio stations are dropping his music, the Simps… https://t.co/oIgk7X9Jtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markshemel @AdamTrahan @Alyssa_Milano The law is not about narrowing things down. It’s about general rules for eve… https://t.co/XsYrrXBB8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is pretty much common knowledge that he fbi and doj worked within their rights and outside of their rights to re… https://t.co/qo4UGOQRxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re following an officer shot this AM. He’s listed in stable at OSU Wexner Medical Center. 3 suspects in police custody @nbc4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francoislegault Remettre de l’argent dans le portefeuille des québécois... c’est çà qu’il disait !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk what i did to deserve the people i have in my life but i’m forever thankful 💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavenW49839532 @peterdaou @leeladaou Actually I’m thinking about the opposite. How can women vote for trump?  I just don’t get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And how much will this cost?  Excuse me but we have a spending problem.  Where do you get the fund… https://t.co/PQk5NABcLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all #District3SA artists! The deadline is March 15. click the link to apply ➡️ https://t.co/913fBhCGNU https://t.co/ntqnKcVZmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby Taking all his money is much better then to impeach him]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Bless America &amp; Go TARHEELS because I almost had a heart attack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@councilofdc I’m honored. Sound of music puns are some of my favorites.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been relentlessly switching between email, Boston 25, and kindercare website for the past half hour to see if they… https://t.co/cAFxwXrmTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennaJulien @Jenna_Marbles My lil miss never gets up there. You definitely need a kitty now. 😻😻😻😽😽😽 https://t.co/faL0BeuRIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to have @JewishWarVets’s Erwin Burtnick repping our MMC in support of @SenJohnnyRay’s SB 294! @eyeonannapolis… https://t.co/yEx4d3Xiyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay90745 Omg. Get outtttttta here. Betty is 🚮. Veronica could get ittttttt and she wouldn’t even have to ask twice. 😂 Eyebrows included.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am already planning what I am going to do after nursing school ! Thinking of going back for NP ?! 🤔 There are no… https://t.co/qZCs6RHFEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many people attribute "The Franklin Cover-Up" to the "Satanic Panic" however i don't believe it has anything to do… https://t.co/ZrIQbRDZun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpookyCy they hang out with brianna because her husband is at school til 7 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey qué pedo me da un chingo de crinje las morras que se la pasan diciendo que quieren un novio pero... YO TAMBIÉN QUIERO UN NOVIO, ok?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like a walking trash can today what’s up https://t.co/I2vlCyQtI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulBerglMD invites us to consider the NAM definition of diagnostic error. What are its challenges as applied to c… https://t.co/1u8xnf48md]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the day with a briefing on economic incentives for antibiotic drug development. #AntibioticStewardship… https://t.co/ZqDo73VywX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you’re up.... will you feed me now? . . , #wwhans #inyourfacecat #petting #catwod @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/gnKcQIlc25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeakGeekZeek @enews No Trump supporter goes around screaming "this is MAGA country." Trust me, we're not that cliche]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet Not sure he can understand words with more than 5 letters or two syllables. Can you show him pictures?]]></document><document><![CDATA[She will follow your lead.  She'll pick up on body language and if you are stressed.  My Missy went deaf from Cushi… https://t.co/otk5UvOlYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring Fullerton! #MadeCoffee #Latte #Fullerton #LatePost @ Made Coffee https://t.co/DxkdbUMCwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤🖤🖤🖤🖤 Russ - Missin You Crazy (Official Video) https://t.co/8J6EIzyqbT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there for real girls that don’t shave their legs in the winter?? Lol wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markknoller @KellyannePolls The judge didn't allow Russia, collusion, or even the Special Counsel to be mentioned… https://t.co/IQclgkHvJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations!!! You look great!!! I’m still waiting for mine. A lot of my friends here on Long Island have alrea… https://t.co/619IS9UR1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about Jesus.. is Jesus ❤️ #KingdomMinded #LiveOnMission #NewLevels #ServedPeopleServe… https://t.co/Qe4j900Gp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMiyayo305 soooo I FT my friend yesterday with the T-Rex Animoji. It made me happy. 🦖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGreenblattADL @Le_CRIF @EmmanuelMacron Well said. And thank you from a Christian. I can’t abide anti-semitism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stfu. Take my money if this is true. I will fly out to Cali. https://t.co/P1Buppky2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill always a vibe no matter where I’m at ! ❤️ just a snippet of my ratchet since y’all never get to see me he… https://t.co/KpmTYTmg29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders What makes you any better Mr. Sanders! Trump wants to be treated like a king and you want to change the… https://t.co/h3s0xyxtlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop saying I like old men because a 55 year old just asked me out 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last lunch with this crew, thankful for every partner and friend I have made at UPS. “One measure of your success w… https://t.co/L4KCuRSl7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squeeeee!!! @j_mar27 #loveatholfugard @ Signature Theatre Company https://t.co/60Bpk3nhlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[you're going to giggle. Funny text messages, Text messages fails, Text message meanings, Ex boyfriend, Ex boyfriend… https://t.co/pEIzwoLCCQ]]></document></documents></author>