<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Win 1 of 24 Truly Wireless headphones from @crutchfield #gggentry  https://t.co/0EChVHWxvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alita: Battle Angel”. Eiza González #alitabattleangel #austintexas #moviestills #ricotorresphoto… https://t.co/OXYAE7zLHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you smokeing on?🤷🏾‍♂️ #PakReligious🙏🏾👳🏾💨💨🍃🍃 @ V-12 Boyz Music Group LLC. https://t.co/dnfL9e804q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Newport on the Levee - @thenewportlevee in Newport, KY https://t.co/X0jRC60Tax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or just get them out of the way now and start steamrolling teams. I can't take too many more of these.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the studio, recording many different commercials for radio stations in Milwaukee! If you or your business want a… https://t.co/zZfNf1Vr6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDC_Opinion @DailyCaller @ymosko Democrat Jews are more concernedwith abortion and extra rights for gays than Israel or Judaism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RajHVashi @wiIIiamlack apologies should be out of genuine remorse, not about the response. Nobody owes you forgiveness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorieshelley @Samuel_Murai @Cakedaddy4ever @SenFeinstein @_waleedshahid @cushbomb She would be a Great President H… https://t.co/3J70LVzuo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverHawkHockey 's Christian Folin had an assist for Montreal #HockeyEast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delivering Tuesday and Wednesday this Week. Call (813)495-2130 to get put on the Route list!! TAMPA BAY!! JON'S GOU… https://t.co/67kgDjJ8OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Abiko Curry in New York, NY https://t.co/CzdNg6uusQ https://t.co/eMQfpZrWM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manager_spa @HarleyQuinnxox3 @MissMariahALO @Rrebecca112 @AnastasiaLuxx @BrassLayla @Miina_Ottawa @brookebabyXXX… https://t.co/dS6GwTAwo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGreatAndino Ah, such great memories of looking for those figures back in 1999. Bummer to  miss Celebration this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3 hours of non stop 3D rendering, adobe decided to crash. My masterpiece is gone. https://t.co/ANmk1WD49C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Today is World Book Day but no one seems to be aware of it. https://t.co/QRBtSJVjJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanHagey @joeskc Sean, why do you have to do this to me?  Looks delicious, I want some KC bbq. I miss Kansas City.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Erie county executive might mean getting roads repaired and even plowed during storms. Don’t just vote down par… https://t.co/tXJr3SaXl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ganobleberries @TurfSpartanLord @andrewmuntz @cookmurray @jeff_salmond @JodyGillTurf @JaviPRcami @marketingmolly_… https://t.co/VUX999OiiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks being stuck in classes all day and not getting to eat, I’m starving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dougs1978 @BreitbartNews What country are these Hollywood racists living in?  It certainly is not America, my coun… https://t.co/6DcoodzkDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sailerjvpiter I take it back I’m watching the first episode and I’m LOVING it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work in progress #3.  This is why I don’t work 9 to 5 any more.  I get to make stuff.  I would emancipate everyone… https://t.co/aKjiODNw5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally was so paranoid tonight while FTing Dillion bc my whole family and I are 98.9% positive that there’s a sp… https://t.co/7NCgaGo3E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bowzer35Burns You know what you don’t look good! Stay home I can vouch..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamZagoria Is that going to be like a Georgetown plays Cal and Duke plays TX deal where they're hoping Duke plays Georgetown on Fri?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 @LiveryTavern in @GbrValleyWV was a pretty romantic spot, you know, if I wasn’t with a friend! #FoodTravelChat… https://t.co/HPA3v2JioB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Energy Secretary Rick Perry Fires Back at Democratic Governor Over ‘Secret’ Shipment of Plutonium https://t.co/7QxfOsM87p]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 de Marzo de 2019  Inicio de Cuaresma  #FraseDelDía https://t.co/vtpQslZBrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love METAL UP YOUR PODCAST - All Things Metallica | Metal Tales From The Road (Minneapolis, MN), let's play it! https://t.co/WoS1kf6D7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @BillieStarkz for helping bring awareness to Cierra's cause #dancerbeatingcancer. Thanks to both promotio… https://t.co/AA0sUy7cmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my boots but they don’t go well with air travel and feet swelling 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollywoodImprov March 12, Pre St.Paddy's Day Show - packed with the Irish get Free Tickets @… https://t.co/9WwEzaagZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS would  like too see you, I'm  handicap. Cant stand in those line. Can you help ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannaeBanda Como cada fds desde los Cristales Mty Nl. Saludos y muy buenos días!]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a #marketing and #branding standpoint, I have been SO fascinated by this. I’m not even a #hockey fan (don’t di… https://t.co/qPzziQ85Sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fell in love with @BahaMarResorts in the Bahamas. Can’t say enough about the people, one of my favorite… https://t.co/G7Ubnp8uoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #IntervencionMilitarYA #Venezuela no puede con estos tiranos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA. And you fools thought he would look out for you:  https://t.co/xAKpCGDUFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always appreciate the little things that have made a positive change in your life! #Grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFreeman83 I wouldn’t even put Lance since he was only here for a year. Honestly I’d probably go Parker and Bishop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonCowie_MUFC @SWFLive @JimmyControvrsy @johnmarzano3 @GrimsToyShow #HaveJimmyArrested]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @SenatorTimScott More lies, propaganda and distorted truth from the the Racist Republican Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianjpapineau The Venn diagram of people who still have cable and those who still watch 20/20 has a significant o… https://t.co/PBgsdkzgJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blasting biggie and big pun on one of my Spotify playlists feeling real hard and then naughty girl by Beyoncé comes… https://t.co/CFJd3Vmm0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @DoingRight1 @Ja39194961 @WI4Palin @Briteeye777 @OHIW14 @garway95 @EinsteinMaga @LaunaSallai… https://t.co/7ZxLs9hWal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC All of US Northeasterners. Can have A we experience in early March. Its. sNOWing!! thiSNOte is legal tender an… https://t.co/3tdZyLCQHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[As per The American Athletic Conference: @GoBearcatsMBB will be looking to make its ninth consecutive NCAA tourname… https://t.co/LfvN4DIVGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geneva Wilderness Area  #greatoutdoors #lovefl #optoutside #optoutsidefl #hike #hikeflorida #realfl… https://t.co/lamBvjs7bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug Parker: Demand American Airlines care about passenger and crew safety and security #PowerofCaring - Sign the P… https://t.co/INAwWtuHol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benedictevans In fairness, Apple has been very quiet about the fact that the light is controlled in hardware and c… https://t.co/hXuwv8aHrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeatManBam You know...... it don’t sound too bad https://t.co/iDO0qkRV4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rev Mike Stone sharing from Daniel 3. Take a look today. @GABaptist churches represented well on Capitol Hill by… https://t.co/2kkJs4sFQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Day of the Pig!! WHES 3rd graders LOVE Freckle! Happy Friday y'all! #FreckleFanatics #FreckleFriday… https://t.co/94UPssAHdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sambyhere @DaleSul88119090 @THEDonnaPiranha In reality she was investigated repeatedly by majority-Republican comm… https://t.co/gXFuKtbPgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewStilez how about… Carp Yadi Goldy Ozuna DeJong Café Bader  Wong Pitcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoDumbQs @Skittles Listening to it now, I keep thinking of this map. How different would history be if this was wh… https://t.co/WWIXMI5b5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mel_Mob95 @MjonesNick  no one on the tour thought that story was funny 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freedom, liberty, etc are all apparently lip service from #Trump and his GOP enablers at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring forward to an earlier sunrise. If it's Daylight Saving time, why is it darker this morning? #whydotheydothat… https://t.co/kXrIWf4y5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @realDonaldTrump This goes beyond trump and u should be alarmed https://t.co/UpEmJi6uvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clgaming why the fuck are you guys playing moon?!? He’s the worst jungler in lcs by far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zmanji @athuras The Thermistor Prize will be awarded to the first person to implement a fully functional Aurora cl… https://t.co/MEqR2cZPlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zone gets the ball to their half and calls a quick timeout to set up a play. 21.1 left on the clock, with the game all tied at 72 #GoBeavs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FootballJOE @lollujo let’s get a Mick Powell and lerrick fernandes mix of this you as Mourinho]]></document><document><![CDATA[No doubt! And the press is finally reporting Trudeau is unlikely to regain power in Oct because females are likely… https://t.co/KjMTzRGHLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @ROMACuaron at @SeattleCinerama was one of the better decisions I made last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[This do doesn’t, at all, surprise me thst trump is bargaining w/the USifA but to actually see it sickens me even mo… https://t.co/VH57IgXHDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwpreston @tsmith_co @arielsanchezmor @importcarguy It was turning into a sticky situation, but it’s nice to be at home sweet home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow ❄️ on the Catalina’s Mountains and the Tucson Mountains #tucson #snow #winter #santacatalinamountains… https://t.co/ybVUPdlCUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you gettin the results youre after doin the same thing? 🤔🤐 👨🏽‍🍳 @Chef_CB1978 👨🏽‍🍳 #askingforafriend #eat… https://t.co/NdpwALJmJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect. Thanks miles_koh for the reminder! @ Middle of "Know Where" https://t.co/2VwVnQhsu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cook is rocking the breakfast this morning.  #milliondollarlisting  #newhomeconstruction  #wafflehouse… https://t.co/ZkIBb1qzEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal Watchdog Issues Scathing Report On Ed Department's Handling Of Student Loans     Via @npr_ed @NPRCoryTurner… https://t.co/MBRJxuhLb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Most of the Democrats voted against the Born Alive act and of course, Alyssa is outraged about the s… https://t.co/vWyZgLzhLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it this simple to calculate how much the proposed Ohio gas ⛽️ tax hike would cost you. Thank @Enquirer… https://t.co/Qv5ucSbBLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a pretty nice person, but I also know if there. were an Asshole Championship I would place respectfully well in my weight class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Airlines is hiring in #FortWorth, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply: Programmer-Analyst/Senior Programmer-Analyst, IT #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d stop shooting my shot given my success rates but one of these will land someday and i will never give up that hope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyCKs1 At last I understand. Somehow, I'd never seen any of these videos the first time you objected! Or for a… https://t.co/8c6jgx3wxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccormicksworld @BobbyEberle13 @RyanAFournier @realDonaldTrump One click away forever. Age of media.  I got fake n… https://t.co/F0Ne3gqznG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VikingKing888 @TMBScouting You are not a great football mind. You're acting like a Packers fan with that tweet. Learn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I endorse this endorsement. Also @chetfaliszek will be there and that makes for a great pannel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redskinstoday_ I don't see Teddy fitting in with tht skins offense scheme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents’ Day! 🇺🇸  . . . Looking to #buy or #sell? Let’s chat! 📱: 919.236.9989 💻: joshmeyersray@outlook.com… https://t.co/3AhsL5Iugc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathmckenna @liberal_party @OCFLA Giving up Saturday time with their families to lie for a political party scam tr… https://t.co/j7b0KX9aKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warm_woobie @k8ai1 @the_ca_podcast @AiG To top it offPaul included himself amongst those who saw the Lord from the… https://t.co/vbCVpgOOvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indulge in the flavors of #PuertoRico at @HIWashingtonDC on 3/16 with a special charity dinner hosted by… https://t.co/GJr1Sgolrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busco ,hombre pasiva (Kissimmee): Soy activo 100%, busco pasivo , discrecion, 40 años bien caliente,8 pulgadas .lim… https://t.co/dp1dA2OpCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[am I a good cook or am I just good at reheating things from Trader Joe’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcoop25012501 I would say I woke up to more money in my account but I haven’t woken up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Gosh, Adam, how about Israel’s IDF violently beating, bombing, shooting and killing unarmed, unresis… https://t.co/RAIZlx5VA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas do yall use regular shampoo and conditioner for your beard or use special one just for facial hair?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow ! Super excited about our 19-20 Freshman Class.  Most ever.  #Wingsup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinnerminner I dreamt it man I can’t help it. That shit was probably like a 4g purple rock. I split it with my cow… https://t.co/KT4deNskhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my @AzCCL Flinn-Brown Family! What an incredible class to be part of. To this day, my fellow Fellows inspire… https://t.co/Ns0a5gd7Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy seguro que me vas a olvidar… Todos los días, hasta el resto de tu vida. Perdón... recordar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you get down the fiddle and you get down the bow I put on extra clothes because it’s too damn cold, Walking to… https://t.co/1s3VQLBTJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olympia beer played a large part in my high school weekend nights. Richard Farnsworth did commercials for it on TV. #FridayThrillerClub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to play my first    vibewithme210  event for sambanks210   I'll be opening the night with some very n… https://t.co/Y9s2ZWKjLw]]></document></documents></author>