<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#psychat @MtnHousePsych @Psych_Review @APpsych4life @ycpsych @taylorpsych]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I’m 33 today!  Can’t wait to celebrate with @kittybrucknell at @BeverlyWilshire tonight! (Aka the Pre… https://t.co/dN7b6SaE7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arruda_j @jimbooss @meteorpete @melissawenzelMN Maybe we should discuss this idea with a few local municipalities… https://t.co/fs6sqFOZmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradfo Lester and myself diagnosis with Non Hodgkin's Lymphoma in January of 2005  Mine was stage 4. Lester came b… https://t.co/NxSKKsYrcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZRishmawy @TheAlanNoble Oddly enough, 2 tweets earlier on my timeline Alan was reassuring everyone,… https://t.co/ZF3DnSQ91K]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what last night was February 17th so basically y'all would've been happy with @RubyRiottWWE having a two week title reign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingdavidotw Just picked up two $15 Xbox card to get the Spiderman in UHD...thanks bud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cyber Saturday for 3/2: Why 'cryptojacking' beats ransomware, Russian election meddling thwarted, rethinking 'data… https://t.co/MlYSiFAqZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a solid Midi Keyboard. We about to finally start working on some tracks.  Taking steps towards finally… https://t.co/W6qD7106my]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong… https://t.co/wHs7K5FlCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailyuxwriting Looking for UX Writer in San Francisco, CA. Check full JD: https://t.co/GzHDlqiytq, if interested.… https://t.co/9JcypkSjpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[negative. I been too enthralled w/Solange &amp; 2 Chainz if I’m being completely honest. how’s it sounding?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't give a shit about the color of a main character's skin, gender, sexual orientation, religion, and so on. Se… https://t.co/NOskpiKrDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches can keep my name out they mouth. Straight up like stop spreading rumors about me that are not true. I’m not… https://t.co/8DzDtPGklB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@james_dispanet I guess I can’t be a metrosexual anymore. GQ offends me]]></document><document><![CDATA[It will not pass Senate will kill it if not TRUMP WILL VETO THE SHIT OUT OF IT .DEMS DONT CARE ABOUT US CITIZENS TH… https://t.co/9CNsjfM9QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[forgot to tweet these ... ... felt delete, might cute later #GRAMMYs https://t.co/8LAN8v2FxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/61XUf0rKcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Trump family money bought Donald  a pass to stay home during the Vietnam war. He has twice been there… https://t.co/Kk7eqtKR6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valley Electric Association’s Chief Financial Officer Steve Morrison was named acting chief executive of Valley. An… https://t.co/J3GG7r3tMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Soundgarden, STP, Pearl Jam, Alice In Chains, Pixies Or Foo? #getaclue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm more just venting to myself but I feel like we are spinning our tires while putting very little effort to getting out of the hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profcarroll Why isn’t Mexico paying for the wall as promised?  And promised. And promised. And promised. And promi… https://t.co/owJJ8bbuQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnchilliard Xbox is the lowest priority for nicalis currently due to sales. I have no other updates :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natlpkbob I think I will be.  I have two other Trek bikes, mountain bikes, but this is my first gravel bike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sapie5 Шапочки, тапочки, звездочки в ряд-трамвай переехал отряд Октябрят. Сиська налево, сиска направо-трамвай переехал вожатую Клаву...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another thing to consider:  The Broncos reportedly had a deal in place with Buffalo to trade out of #5 prior to the… https://t.co/hsDr3VeQhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extreme closeup of some raw unpolished Lapis lazuli from under a microscope. #Mineral #rock #stone #photo https://t.co/Omf8SPVVaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_lindseyy21 #needs #VoteBlue #vote #Amazon #America #kubball #grownwiththeclique #Venezuela #nigeriavotes2019… https://t.co/yovW3D8EeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 down and it's time for football practice.  . . . . . . . . . . #superdads #dad #love #family #mom #father #kids… https://t.co/gknAquHOco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Having never heard of FISA until the Carter Page case, do they typically hold hearings on each case,… https://t.co/RJMB6FipMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bulls are playing a home-and-home with the Hawks? That’s rare. Plus, this game has to go to 8OT. #BullsNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlerFm @WBIRWeather @10weather @TNHouseReps @tnsenate @ltgovmcnally @GlenCasada @BillLeeTN Please no. Unless we… https://t.co/3jBTFwUMVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 Florida Offensive Lineman with Michigan offer. https://t.co/bigOgL6ELF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetYourPhil @JudahWorldChamp @JimCarrey I doubt very seriously Jim Carrey will do that. Form a cult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True. Foreign ISIS fighters can be brought back to Canada, UK, France, etc. to be prosecuted as nationals. But thos… https://t.co/Zk2reRrTY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Nebraska win tonight and Illini win tomorrow could yield a 6th place standing in the conference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iroelsanchez @marti160patria No jodas? Entonces estaban especulando con la propiedad ajena y ahora no quieren paga… https://t.co/aiLMAaLwNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delaneyca DITTO and everyone tbh I get rly sad sometimes thinkin about Solomon homies :’(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loislane79 @hijean @marisaroffman @SydneyBucksbaum Who’s finished their box of Nos4a2 cookies yet? I still have a few.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Sharpton really is a NOTHING. He is racist not our ELECTED PRESIDENT. There are millions of us that will stand with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules What you think about the War in Afghanistan then? Toppling the Taliban government?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rebrand Design: Puffy Paint Value Packs. Always awesome to see my work come together for a cohesive look, also humb… https://t.co/lY1OjxyWsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use of the 25th amendment by a select few to deposed a sitting president is a subversion of our democracy.  It is i… https://t.co/0xVAy260F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetJDUB2017 @kimhightower7 @TrvlPrst @maziehirono Nailed it. https://t.co/xMoJCvEtKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j66anderson @Lucas_Oil @LucasRacingTV @bobaru @JohnBommarito @BommaritoAuto @FVPparts @RustysOffRoad… https://t.co/MkLSRahEqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Business Analyst/Senior Business Analyst, IT - https://t.co/l1sWoGQDoF #IT #FortWorth, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is finally out, but this wind has got me like... #imoverwinter https://t.co/owGFSWSlZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a #friday night for #theroadto40 #vacation #laundry night with no where to go. @ At Home https://t.co/FGDobGYCeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isnickwright @tom_tml Yes when I watched I thought of how much it was like Rocky 3. Very good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t expect the current corporate media to share my thoughts as I recall that Bernard Shaw ended Dukakis in 1988… https://t.co/nSuPzSHDo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgatopoulos @lenaargiri @pierremoscovici I’m sure the average taxi driver who gets taxed at usurious rates would beg to differ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t cross me then get mad when I don’t give you the same effort as I did before 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished an f'n fantastic salad from Nations in Jackson Square. The container could barely hold all of it an… https://t.co/jq9cm7wnEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhgfssg @AwareFrequency @WalshFreedom And @Potus is the one cutting regulations that help keep them in check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_quincynichols_ @MidlandU @MidlandU_FB @NEPrepZone @NEBHSRecruits @BlairFootball Congratulations!  Great opportuni… https://t.co/xlI7rvNBDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must have coffee!! #CoffeeLover See this Instagram photo by @deathwishcoffee https://t.co/EPxjb2yTdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I don’t need to breathe to be alive That’s when I’ll stop thinking bout you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterRollins Trying to remember where the parable about the three brothers was. Orthodox Heretic? Can’t find it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been in love with the same girl for over 13 years, to this day she doesn't know. #justtellher]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any piece of shit who thinks it’s okay to set back two different minority groups for their own gain is dead to me.… https://t.co/EZEn7curOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaddleandSilvy I'm a Cub fan, but I like Rick Hahn. He's very Theo-and-Jed-like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is something so beautiful about loving your spouse for a lifetime.  Make this your worthy goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just seen your lil brother @InfiniteVillain he told@me@he gnna help me pack your ass cuz your a mark]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the judge in Manfort doesn’t give him light sentences especially he on the wheelchair! This is a put up job… https://t.co/b8QrMBOisY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran 3.30 miles with Nike⁠ Run Club#over64runner -Success does not consist in never making mistakes but in never mak… https://t.co/mS18LustkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[NY Times: Unfortunate Rep. Omar ‘Stung Again’ by Anti-Semitic Remark (That She Made) https://t.co/ewHLtJv5EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid and this is what I saw yesterday... https://t.co/8zhuftWZQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers followers! Hope your Saturday night is a good one. Roll with it or get rolled over!  #beer #cheers #coldbeer… https://t.co/hjrJdSGgw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solar__winds 15 years Oppy searched for water. On far planet Mars known well to be hotter.   Aqua signs found anci… https://t.co/APe4kxuG59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juice_Spur @FBI @realDonaldTrump @bibinetanyaho and COPS who beat up, rape, and high-fived need to be called out t… https://t.co/VL4HGRTutN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#norton.com/setup  Antivirus helps you to protect your computer, spam, laptop from virus, Trojan horse, malware, Th… https://t.co/Z1scrBEYtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @NBA @Patriots @Lakers  @AuburnFootball Every last one of you guys inspire me!! Everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[A church that truly truly truly puts people first is a church that is actually thriving. A church that truly serves… https://t.co/h01H9x6dZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @elonmusk is sending people to Mars, but how much would it cost to shoot me into the Sun?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fruich @pdamelio1 @realDonaldTrump POTUS has not give me any reason to think he's lying about anything. 2ndly, I'm… https://t.co/iIS7gblRSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell Bernie Sanders on Gillum, Abrams: Many white voters 'uncomfortable' voting for black candidates https://t.co/boissDyDja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaganWilson @LiveLikeGhee No doubt at 12 o’clock when FA begins Steve Kerr is knocking on his door with a big check for a max deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods McCabe looks like a Nerd....I bet that guy suffered so many wedgies In High School]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmc_nyc You weren’t the only one wearing your t-shirt backward today! Daylight savings always leaves me a little d… https://t.co/Nzufg15lTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimchaFisher Eat right, portion control and work out. That usually suffices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Cassius Winston for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/XBoiBqGJQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have @MedBillGurus ranking #1 in the map pack for the keyword “medical billing” #seo #digitalmarketing… https://t.co/9pLbZrc6Rq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah... cause libel laws aren’t a thing.  It takes true effort to be this dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmitch215 @jpklepesky @mattnevins @Adamlees81 @JoeGiglioSports He only had OVER 100 RBIs once, Richard. https://t.co/ETNUFDKxjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaPe30177955 @flyaway_k TERRORTORY TERRATORY TERRiTORY TERRYCLOTH TERRYKNIGHT THiS.    .NoTE i           YK zippers ANNUit TENDer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiekeEoyang @dcpoll @seanhannity From what has been said he never represented Sean. 1 conversation about real esta… https://t.co/JaOX33FYtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willmoriarty86 @shodrewshirley @TheresaRockFace Not worth the time. Just like it wasn’t worth it for me to respond… https://t.co/QrroxXqQcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA for all black women. Please, please, please stop going anywhere with that damn silky bag on your damn head. You… https://t.co/FKCb5U5Nmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoshanazuboff Listening to:@NPR @WLRN @MarcoWerman. Feeling #Enlightened. #stuckintraffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossignol Very true... will not forget when one @MetOpera got me two returned tickets in a sold house for Trebs To… https://t.co/QakltH3FSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're at #SCALE17x and are interested in containers, don't miss this security talk that includes an introductio… https://t.co/1t9zZ3mPzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdineenaco @AOC Nyet, Komrade. Some of your statements are laughably wrong, but thinking that for-profit companies… https://t.co/Xf3AyDS0M5]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I need help being convinced trying to talk to my ex is a horrible idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dedication Crews are working hard all morning getting planes at @Reagan_Airport @wusa9 #WUSA9Weather https://t.co/1uicG9T81U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total Calories, 2,586! Net Calories, 727! Total!         Goal!           Left!! Carbohydrates, 270, 453, 183g! Fibe… https://t.co/O8KPmTogL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@windell_11 I also finally watched the Andre the giant doc Simmons did and boy was that fucking great]]></document><document><![CDATA[DHS needs to be broken up.  It's a threat to us all.  It's accountable only to Trump.  No oversight from Defense or… https://t.co/fiWiZTR1QW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahnaaaaaa I’m not gonna lie to you g..... your Mob Psycho header so cold..I stole that shit. I clean stole it and I can’t give it back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialism is not the benevolent sugar daddy it purports to by but rather a wicked means to an end like the child ab… https://t.co/lpIbIZky9n]]></document></documents></author>