<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[He may end up in jail, briefly but a rich, white man with a good lawyer won't stay there for long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdomenech Pretty sure she was taking issue with the "massive amounts" part, which betrays the fact that Trump has… https://t.co/K6AWlTvyVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Justin @KPRC2 @Esther188rod  ME WAIT FOR JESSE TO GET OFF WORK AND BRING OUR DINNER AS USUAL AS LONG IF I OR… https://t.co/Rgx6n2cM2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call Congress and tell them to give children and families the valentine of #GunSafety! Pass… https://t.co/IHvAX9Wvlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @nypost - why has your app been so awful lately? Takes forever for anything to load.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You right but just because I am showing you a family pic or pic of my child... still do not scroll to the left or r… https://t.co/bHrIjrrh2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scopedbylarry I will say the traffic is lighter, people are kinder here even only 30 mins NW of Orlando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@animalpolitik79 @artorremobile Mándame tu nombre real por DM y tus datos de contacto, y quizás empieces a cobrar vida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think food delivery guys and gals should get to rate our pajamas through the app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m confident there is new music by my queen @taylorswift13 coming soon!!! New IG photos. New colors. New vibes. I’m ready for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yfnlucci check ur DMS I'm a female artist from Dallas tx..I Kno u looking for good talent HMU 👽🔌🔋🎤I write my own m… https://t.co/qmkZ27FIAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miles recovering well. Alive and kickin’ .. napping 😹 #boop #therealgarf @ Sunset Park, Brooklyn https://t.co/ahM25WPDTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenbrier Preschool of the The Bradley Schools in Columbia County is working to create calm down areas within thei… https://t.co/uDjdbIRDfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you entered? We are giving TWO FOLLOWERS each a ONE MONTH SUPPLY of DYPER all natural biodegradable diapers an… https://t.co/2Yv6ct7E6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shelby and I are on I-75 on the way up to the panhandle today to see one of our Montana friends at the beach.   I'm… https://t.co/iJkgQucZBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco No one is afraid of Trump lol! Everyone has his number. Trump is one of… https://t.co/lCzkOHwaOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[You try to surround yourself with as much positivity as you can, but when you are in bed.. alone..your own thoughts… https://t.co/XrWowD4Z0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up cedardalehealthfitness !!! Morning classes are canceled for Monday! Enjoy the snow, stay safe and I will s… https://t.co/yLcr0FTwf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMScholes @alyherr11 @RepMcClintock @MMScholes  @TomMcClintock also voted to allow mentally incapacitated people t… https://t.co/JkAjIdWkDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt BIRDIE saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea Jess Rescue in #Yangju #DogMeat… https://t.co/6WPjmEzhqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realitytea I wore my hair like that a few times back in the 80’s.  It was expensive for a poor college student to pay for curly hair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissAmeliaCat @IngrahamAngle @CPAC @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump Not when I can find it out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dateline_keith responded to my tweet. This is not a drill. #ipromiseimnotastalker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. Pequod’s spelled my entire first and last name right without me having to repeat it or spell it out. That’s a… https://t.co/C2B5fjfbJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like two exams and anatomy lab to get you in the mood for Valentine’s Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be so tempted to run his hair with a balloon Gianluca’s hair is so poofy😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariofraioli Boom. Nailed it. Also just listening after helps said person figure out their own problems. Allowing… https://t.co/ILchzDOku6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @RevengeBody #motivation #fitlife  #Gymlife https://t.co/5Nw90zQBM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[tfw someone says they're on the headliner's guest list, but they can't remember the headliner's name]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand Too bad your "moral fabric" didn't include giving @alfranken the ethics investigation he personally… https://t.co/u2SmIvPYj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom's testing out her new camera!   #thegoldenrupp #ruppthepup #dogsofig #dogsofinstagram #dog #goldenretriever… https://t.co/cpeTGcIQrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepClayHiggins And neither do you! What a fool you are! Shut up and listen if you can bear the shame of watching y… https://t.co/R2SgrhqdJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenMWoodford @nlightsvball @SLPPantherAth @SLPVolleyball Omg congrats woody❤️❤️ proud of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSpencerScott I just edited a wonderful book on an Alz caregiver. Just read yr article in WD. Great that you volunteered]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can barely hear anything because my head is so congested... this should be a fun day 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The consciousness that says ‘I am’ is not the consciousness that thinks”. -Jean Paul Descartes. When you are aware… https://t.co/IxsVZOSaUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DevanK @The_Matt_Piazza @FadetheDave @Marshall_Hansen count the rings baby we’re already winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas @QueenWillRock @adamlambert He's been incredible since  American Idol. Beautiful voice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents Day to all former presidents, alive and dead!  I got nothing for you Individual #1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been thinking about perchance methinks mayhaps uploading voice memo versions of songs i’ll probably never get… https://t.co/dvaezKL26p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news: I CAN officially breathe again.  Bad news: I think the steroid shot they gave me is gonna keep me up for the next three days. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamstephbeatz You did an amazing job, love the episode @iamstephbeatz 🤙🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @JussieSmollett If he did, then he should go to jail. And pay for the officers time for the fake  attack!🚓🚔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle @SOMissouri @oakley 🤣🤣 yeah.... I’m a @Nike girl. I only wear Nike shoes &amp; flip flops lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danettedandouni @danettedandouni الغربة مرة يا دانا نشلا تكون قهوتك حلوة 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenhayes     HI Darren,      You said about getting a tattoo I you are i got mine last week it's a Bhutanese dr… https://t.co/hQBjz00T3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread @AOC this should make you ashamed to have lied, but you lack integrity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTUKnews @RT_com It is of course the Carbon count of less than 1% on the entire planets surface]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers - Sucker https://t.co/BWuvDUxbvN via @YouTube.                                                    Om… https://t.co/MWE5aoeza1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday &amp; Felicidades Hugs to Wilfredo @SweetLizzyProj  xoxoxoxxoxoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #MTBoS Please welcome @hammermeister74 !  She’s a 7th and 8th grade teacher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m playing @MarvelPuzzle and I FINALLY got the BEST version of Black Widow in my opinion. She looks so BADASS!!! https://t.co/fukLoTfNzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FameThaDon @swiftxgreys @Nonstop_Pompeo @merxpompeo Lol who the hell is that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You say it is corrupt because they tell us the TRUTH about you.  Like you have said, if you say so… https://t.co/WlVNpfNqr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dulyssesfox @DianeRavitch Mr David Fox, you're my man! I'm interested in the data you've compiled researching thos… https://t.co/vEMwOqvOqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanHipp @RyanAFournier As the wife of a Vietnam vet, this brought tears to my eyes.  Thank you to all who serve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jason_a_brehm @ginger_coleman @Tenney1R @ChrisBergHD @ThdKelly @JosueJf01wq Congrats! He has a twin in this world.… https://t.co/XLbK7pbbHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ someone I once considered ok of my closest friends. Thanks for showing me your true colors. Needed to see that 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍💯 #heartmelted She looked at @chhadams and asked ‘will you dance with me daddy?’ And he (obviously) couldn’t no. A… https://t.co/Q0OdHffam1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You babes Have a great weekend ❤️💯🙏🔥🤤😘   #OTownLove   #OTown   #OTownisHereTostay  #OFamily  #Lovemyboys… https://t.co/UJ5AWRlrlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen Now: Behind the Scenes With the PETA Podcast https://t.co/hl22LnbAko]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch i got 1,630 days left in the army and you better believe i’m counting down the days 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Critical questions facing educators. We need lots of input from real teachers to move and evolve this work.… https://t.co/cuWlQDQbW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think the roads are bad, try walking. The sidewalk situation is exhausting and some people have no choice bu… https://t.co/N34Wpz7MVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back again 🛬 #businesswoman #businesstravel #airportlife #needcoffee @ Seattle-Tacoma International Airport (Sea-Ta… https://t.co/vLaMwixlux]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hotwire biggest rip off ever.  Don’t use this website to book anything!  Rental cars, airfare!  All misleading!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We found the secret recipes for Frazioni’s Pizza! #OSD135 https://t.co/eRo5ZLBxdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teresa_rose3 I woukd highly recommend 'Not Marked' as well as some of her other books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at President Street Train Crossing in Wheaton, IL https://t.co/ay0AzlJ2gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true! We try to make ourselves look better in others’ eyes rather than getting better for ourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the Wake of #NunsToo, It’s Time for Repentance and Conversion   #care2 https://t.co/4pil8FIdcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pakistan says it shot down Indian jets, carried out airstrikes in Kashmir https://t.co/etRWYJVYpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[[...] C’est ce besoin que les femmes ressentent de toujours plaire à l’homme et de céder à son désir. Adèle a peur… https://t.co/3ogUxyVC1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelRosas27 Bitch? You mad lmaooo what’s ur point I got fam all out here watch your mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCWSupergirl  #CW I have read where the ratings are down for #Supergirl. Why was it moved to Sunday? Did you wan… https://t.co/f9keFpHenV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar did not "criticize some supporters of Israel." She used anti-Jewish stereotypes. If Omar can't criticize… https://t.co/50aVYBbvCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stomach looks sooooo much better after this last minor surgery so happy to be in the way to healing !! Maybe I’l… https://t.co/eirosqWLPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1klinesofcode @heyriddleriddle @JPsoFLY @adalrifai @ErinKeif2 Oh hell yeah, even better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TS7 IS A MIX OF POP AND COUNTRY?!?! IDK WHATS YALLS THOUGHTS AND CONSPIRACIES???? #TS7 #TS7iscoming @taylorswift13 https://t.co/mvhLiLMpxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Ally Rep. Matt Gaetz Insists He’s Not Threatening Michael Cohen by Suggesting He’ll Expose ‘Girlfriends’… https://t.co/BqYG4QlFEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude this is fing awesome @MirelesPhoto #loganheights #sandiego #sandiegogram #publicart @ San Diego, California https://t.co/bBm28XEdGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Piccadillyxo Made this at the beach after watching the first season. https://t.co/HYdwG07UmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerie_shaw Ok. If you’re a language nerd, then I suppose “triple rhyme time” isn’t so bad for you. If you’re an ex… https://t.co/uZOnsBnQmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class List for Friday, March 8, 2019: 5:00 am Wildcard Workout - Strong by Zumba with Cheryl E. Wood @senseicheryl… https://t.co/QupPBumT41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xfl2020 @XFLTampaBay You guys just got the best coach. Marc Trestman true class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mcaron255 @Rosa6416 @msnicole1124 @wwwillstand @w_terrence @KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett @vj44 @lyft… https://t.co/QnvC28Y5Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all still have your friends follow me to see what I'm up to? That's cute 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 32 I am Strong I am Brave .... I Can still get AIR!! I Had a Blast with Jas, Lily and Michael at Sky Zone!! Th… https://t.co/o8LGdB5jb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump Because of his comments...  which I felt were totally appropriate considering who he was running against.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGodOfDeathA1 LMAO Lord Anubis, I swear to God that in high school I was teased by my friends and called "the pr… https://t.co/OOlg1Fay3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please explain to me why it was necessary to send a Code Red Weather Warning text at 3:20 a.m. about a… https://t.co/2V2OVhayg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNFLIGHTSELECT @torijrutherford @RBishop41 @ladygrizzhoops @tlownsdale @5StarPreps @Elite80Tn @neb_media… https://t.co/OKmhwnZKYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weird_Dana That is so cool! Unless of course you were really tired and needed to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3:23 am and I have tears streaming from my eyes watching this. People choose to tune this out because it’s too… https://t.co/8iDFcD6u25]]></document><document><![CDATA[What #DeepLearning are you doing to grow as a leader? Love these leaders deepening their knowledge in #LPICoach Tra… https://t.co/u1LI2eBP6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_S_H_K_I_N_G I'd be happy with just one and an R2D2 together. They can be like the veteran and the rookie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drawinglover98 I don't want to say this in public but ....   The reason my day was bad yesterday, is because anoth… https://t.co/vwubANdifw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneeky sneaky! U got any idea where I am right now?! In a warehouse... In Central, Ohio... Full of *all* KEEP jewel… https://t.co/1WBeuM7ym1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This high school girl told me and another castmate that our show reignited her passion for theatre cause she was go… https://t.co/iFIRd1sjgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to all the women I have grown to know and love, the woman who have shaped who I am today, and the future you… https://t.co/rcNsohrlB4]]></document></documents></author>