<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My aunt: “Your whole family is full of aggies, I think your soul mate goes to A&amp;T too, you’re bound to like them”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeomaJardon @Tesla Thanks for coming out and also welcoming Tesla to the neighborhood!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotAlexis That’s like one of those assey “and 1” that MJ or LeBron throws up as a freebie, Mane only tries that since they’re up 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LedoPizza Ledo Pizza People, I have finished my complex calculations and have concluded it is my turn to win .  🧮… https://t.co/PKdDTe1duo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillieKayWWE and @PeytonRoyceWWE just attacked @notsam with popcorn and chips (wassat?) on the Watch Along. Hilarious. #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Another national emergency retribution against Saturday night live you clueless effing buffoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys, I’m going to @Chilis if anyone wants to go with me. If you’re out of town you can go to your local Chili’… https://t.co/yhaonGNK3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I’m sitting in my office, watching dirtbike video😂 I really want to go ride my dirtbike😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have enough money to move out of my shitty home situation if I hadn't wasted it going to meet them lmao that's fucking awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty funny how all the beat writers and talk radio hosts are pretty quiet on possible #browns moves after falling… https://t.co/N5W4T3IrBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All the baddest girls got the biggest foreheads. -Jeffery”  - @DanNC11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I never watch the news anymore. If I want to be lied to I’ll talk to my ex girlfriend, but since I… https://t.co/JTQKBeDGlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maison Kitsuné Forms Joint Venture With China’s JoeOne https://t.co/l7CsphSFbe via @wwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for Glenn Close being a shoe in. If you haven’t seen The Favourite, it’s a great movie and Olivia Copland i… https://t.co/g2OwizfnnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vmochama Jack that last bit up to 'ballista' and you maybe got a backer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got two extra tickets for ISU vs Mizzou dual tomorrow.  DM me if interested]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanDavidReece @lukasheinrich_ @KyleCranmer Thanks for giving it a spin. As always, we welcome feedback! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcowgill50 - how do you feel about getting D. Jacks back?  #FlyEaglesFly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone asking this question should be required to explain why anyone should give a shit about the national debt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t over-produce it, guys.  Big personalities will translate through the lens on their own and the numbers will follow. ✍🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tannerschmidt42 @FB_CoachFitz @CalebTate52 @KrisPetroski1 Yeah keep moving that weight Schmidt!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how it looks when somebody got next for everyone who ever talked bad about me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would love to see the coaching staffs of North Carolina and Duke play a pickup game. #UNCvsDUKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got damn I gotta stop tweeting at folks who don’t know shit about basketball except Wins and Losses and box scores]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nowplaying🎧 Spectral Mornings - STEVE HACKETT #StevenWilsonStereoRemix @ Chateau De Cavazzi https://t.co/yvQIcQxPoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reporting live this morning in Uptown Dallas.  Police are searching the gunman who opened fire on  another driver,… https://t.co/6GiMe4F6Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ECR2019 begins tomorrow in Vienna!  Looking forward to present keynote on “Safe and Effective #AI” in #radiology—… https://t.co/8H3ILoHqgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steezytweets I mean is it really stealing if it’s an idea? He didn’t do anything wrong legally. He just beat them… https://t.co/rih664Xhcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nascarcasm @jeff_gluck I thought that was Bristol before Bruton covered it up with Concrete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  Parents at a high school game:  “AND 1! AND 1! Call it both ways!!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KennedyMiller_ @TheSSPodcast_ I could make an argument for my boy Melo on that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plantlady293 I don’t know about ya’ll but that shit is getting old as hell, give me some examples]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @TheDemocrats It says there is alot of queues up phoney outrage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Esome1980 @brookeolzendam @Dame_Lillard This is true we don’t have the room for everyone...:-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caso confirmado de Sarampión en NL. Vacunar es una obligación colectiva.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little 80’s music starring Phil Collins! @ Thunder's House https://t.co/jXtKq2t9zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqt__ @Tridon1955 @SheilaPierce51 @Berthagoodlovin @happygolfwidow @JamesHo03148924 @pjl1015 @Jimi_Jammin… https://t.co/qfkn1t2Gsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Crawford you need to fight better opposition and stop fighting in your own backyard,please fight the winner of t… https://t.co/Ui8dnlFr3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Jack Henry &amp; Associates, Inc team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/agJGUeBSyF #IT #Birmingham, AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somebadideas @kohquette has everyone here also seen Man Of Tai Chi, directed by keanu reeves starring tiger chen w… https://t.co/V6ldAUpSnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved watching Gaga and Bradley fuck on stage. What a performance! ♥️ #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpeal8 It took me a year to land my first job and then I did Everything I could to make it work. For me, if a recr… https://t.co/YtJBpXwd0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Deon Horn (@itsdeon__) for scoring the most points by a freshman since Robbie Eggers in 1989 https://t.co/AVFpecs1Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhh that’s great   You are there visiting !!  I’m his number one fan tooo  😄😄😄is love to work for Pres Trump !… https://t.co/AYeuhDV6Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_Kno_Betta @NBAonTNT @TheTraeYoung He ain’t from Norman.  He was raised there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiiii, me again! When is @Allbirds opening at @UVillage? https://t.co/8dciabBvtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 5 minutes in between classes and pulling into the parking lot blasting music in the morning and after lunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Umbrella Academy...get after it. Google it if you don't know what I'm talking about. Straight gas 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you expect of a Gov whose entire Ministry of Education is composed of DFERs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect timing w me getting home snd trying to pull up fortnite. UPDATE DAYYY WELCOME SEASON 8 MY BATTLEPASS IS FRE… https://t.co/y7BKbzbA5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[last year i got whooping cough and i really fucking hope this measles virus keeps to itself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RulesBenitez @europe3330 @KavalonThatsMe @Efrain99620830 @sweetsexy_39 @hortkoff3 @Hiqutipie @Marg1010… https://t.co/SzgZU1mtEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donkilmer @NewDay @MSNBC @maddow @AOC She participated in A/C violations? I have elsewhere expressed my concern ab… https://t.co/XoHcaUgFAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pim22j903s Verizon Customer Service Phone Number can help resolve the Verizon issues 1-855-431-6111… https://t.co/mJzWumSDas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroline_szwed @THS_tweet Your positive, happy and giving spirit makes me 😁 back! The world needs more people like… https://t.co/Z8HiO3Rp4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad meal on #UnitedAirlinea today plus all the Coke Zero you could drink! 😂😂😂😂 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/OaynZsu7o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JElvisWeinstein You convulsed me! (paraphrased from the Preston Sturges film “The Palm Beach Story”) https://t.co/mqQCHCaVy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjquinney @YaleLawSch I do have a beef with Republicans- say they are pro-life but don't want to help the poor- wi… https://t.co/H5XobHI7z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think Cheese on “Foster’s Home For Imaginary Friends” is absolutely hilarious https://t.co/xkN958PhAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hswift I mean, in two weeks, she could see a real boost in her accuracy. 🎯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drake dropped bars on the shop for real. I still wish he would’ve dropped that diss track]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You really should just shut that big orange yap of yours - especially when it comes to this fawnin… https://t.co/Kux5mLWhPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was as depressed as anyone when the Chargers left but I’m 💯 percent over it. Canepa is still thirsty for a team t… https://t.co/UFu35OVtON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia EMT who made racist remarks on podcast loses his job - CNN https://t.co/FF0MfkEhkT Trump supporter getting bold.😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the greatest start for Eula which finds itself down 8-2 just 2:09 into the game. #BigCountryPreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacerfox We're also due for a Disney trip if y'all ever go. We've been here almost 4 years and never gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathormot @VFL2013 I just read from CNN at this point she is not saying no. She just trying to get assurances that… https://t.co/OLdCJBZFKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kidd Kidd was so slept on, on this track. @Pace93til @__Marti93 https://t.co/wjUpcdchVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrangerSmith I’m not able to make this show because of health reasons but just wanted to give a heads up to stay d… https://t.co/9qeMeGm88E]]></document><document><![CDATA[EPH4:11-16 My part in the body of Christ is to study the scriptures God has given me, Be sensitive to The Spirit wi… https://t.co/SNCkP5NlVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theradiantcollectionaph  #radiantcollectiononwallslv  #alexanderphuertalv @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/Wyd5ppTffP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjwheelerali @tina_zita @PeelSchools Kahoot, google classroom, seesaw...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nctbasketball gets revenge against @CRHSPirates in the Sweet 16, defeating the Pirates 67-35 and advancing to the… https://t.co/Mh3wHC6zvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree 100%, subscribe to them by clicking this link everyone! https://t.co/kviPamCwgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyGreenley Why not? I think that was a tactic they used in The Hurt Locker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a outrageous crime and hypocrisy Trump supporters need to demand he is fired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chief321 @HeathVrbka If you wear a speedo, our wives will find a way to get you invited back. They have more pull then we do anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenny2Hugs @ConstanceM2015 @arek_janula @TPSOToole @GunOfBavaria @lisa_kirkby @BakicJelena @TenaciousPita… https://t.co/jQY9kLhvhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[you wanna cry? you wanna jerk that big fat fucking cock until you can’t feel it anymore? you wanna fucking blow you… https://t.co/Ovb4hOTQpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Delegate McNamara on final passage of his first bill through the General Assembly and on to the… https://t.co/feKgYGWMwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xbudz @DarshDavis I just picked up a 500 gb ssd for the price of my 2tb a few years ago. It could and should happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MidWEEEKKK!!! #HtownRush  @RussKHOU ⚓ @LisaKHOU 👠 @BrandiKHOU 🍷 @chitakhou 🌤☀️ @KHOUStephanie 🚓🚗🚕 @DougDelonyKHOU… https://t.co/4fBOPXy6eE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is for when I get my FIRST tattoo on spring break, so help ya boy out :(  1. On my thigh with the Aries stars… https://t.co/ZH1Zq2JC7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walsingham (Wisconsin branch) Anglican  pilgrimage: check! @ Grace Episcopal Church, Sheboygan WI https://t.co/jdcjxq7SXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrafficAlert: Shooting investigation has closed off several blocks along Collins Ave, from 13th Street north to 14… https://t.co/mDjIoJWawa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the day off downtown drinking some kumbucha! @ Good Life Cafe https://t.co/fjS27rW66w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Queen Latifah needs proof Jesus Christ open your eyes what an ass she's becoming. When there is so m… https://t.co/pZtykyXdmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Chris! - Drinking a Cafe Lit by @windmillbrewing @ Zoltar  — https://t.co/CRsXBJeTZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith got it right on Casserly’s diss of #QB @TheKylerMurray. #FootballNEXT #NFLCombine2019 #NFLDraft2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abducted in Plain Sight is the whitest documentary I’ve ever seen in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Except the majority of “hate crimes” are overwhelming directed at Jews. Look at the actual FBI facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever notice that if Respect by Aretha Franklin comes on in a public setting every starts to sing and dance to it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Sebastian, guitar  Cathryn Manning, singer  Sugar Rush Rocks are Bleachers 322 Tavern  sugar_rush_rocks… https://t.co/We2P9ZlDyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el proceso de dejarla de mi vida arrancarla... vuelve a pedir perdón...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougHenwood @HBoushey The Bobbsey twins are two sets of fraternal twins - 2 boys, 2 girls, dressed in bright color… https://t.co/Ivy0LcPsV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[En vivo Gallo De Sinaloa #lumarperez #CompaCanelo @ Compton, California https://t.co/kCp3zIOvgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former POTUS has great taste.  Case and point Michelle. ...I think Maria Taylor is awesome at her job and really re… https://t.co/nD6FMqBvc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kids had to dress like they were 100 years old for a class project...shout out to wifey for the costume designs… https://t.co/OlmqIy4B8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redbreast_US Decisions, decisions... I know... I'll just try them ALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta be a crackhead in Marvel to handle the heat from the lighter.... https://t.co/TGDVcqIfNq]]></document></documents></author>