<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly released from jail after child support payment  https://t.co/YHtBjmSQtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kittens knocked over my water TWICE AND ketchup threw up on me. Done with cats for the night goodbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missmiafaith I am now ded from absolute perfection. It was a good deth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHancock613 @phatcabb @CFL @Ticats Us too!! It’s gonna be great but it’s always sad to watch a great player go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anonymous__Paul I wanted to marry him when I grew up, thirteen year old me through he was the cutest teenager ever… https://t.co/Bj0lDqX3C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I worked on this #kettlebell complex. Check my story for my bloopers when trying the reverse lunge and snatch… https://t.co/kXbiHS1x0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I  support Daniel Valenzuela for Mayor . I know Daniel shares the same values as I do, he  has shown he… https://t.co/3qkaMr2732]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5:I accepted a challenge from @karamieszanek and @Edtechnically to post covers of 7 books I love: no reviews, j… https://t.co/6Zd3SyFyVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juandelcerro @Gazi2a @saif305 “GG” - that’s a Miami already closed. But G &amp; G, power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you picked the bad guy. the guy who hurts you or hurts other people and you deserve better. maybe you can’t see that but i do.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venezolanazo @jcsosazpurua Beeelllaaa!!!  no joda tenemos que hacer que vea su salida. Cuídenla y celebramos con otro video]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelhonoret Brandon when u told him to switch spots with Edwin https://t.co/soTLqcct3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[YESSSSS @doncheadle 💜💜💜 way to show some support for our most vulnerable youth on @nbcsnl last night!!! @ 19th Ward… https://t.co/KI3npFI7AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heidiklum @AGT I’m going to miss you Heidi. I don’t think I want to watch @AGT anymore. It’s not going to be the s… https://t.co/L5JPCHAZ4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this sound Familar? Blaming the Press? Blaming the Investigator? Refusing any talk of Resignation??? Isreal La… https://t.co/V4ieXqdMPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the afternoon with my sister and family. My niece goes to Fairhaven in Niles. It is fabulous the opportunitie… https://t.co/BIJ8HV9aN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Q6eUufK9dC @DAVDEE__ ON FUCKING REPEAT mirarmar vibezzzzzzzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[True friendship right there, flipping the bird as a goodbye #hannivania]]></document><document><![CDATA[FBI Officials Wanted To Charge HRC — Turns Out, They Should Have https://t.co/EiPd3fH5Ph @HomeOfUncleSam @ScotsFyre… https://t.co/bIfpteUOEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlphaDeltaPi @Lily_Dohogne @SemoADPi Livin’ for these girls each &amp; everyday💎 https://t.co/Zs4fyLi5BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The federal government is about to hit its credit limit  https://t.co/kIbRiWgdgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyAnchorsAway Then they had the nerve to tell me the Quiet Zone was a suggestion... Definitely not commuters. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Life moves pretty fast. If you don't stop and look around once in a while, you could miss it.” + These were true w… https://t.co/dadtBDFUg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[No llorar porque acabó...sonreir porque ocurrió. Linda Noche, mi gente. https://t.co/UvopGCy4VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lldipity @Lee_in_Iowa She'll be voicing her *opinion* just like all the other pundits you see on #MSM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soul food for Valentine’s dinner 🥘🌹❤️ @ Southern Flavors https://t.co/C4X5PBQajv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something else to think about...if they do this to infants, what's next for 65+ who are no longer working and "cont… https://t.co/FKsqbJJmGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uscnownforever @Deann4656 @bmiuc66 @nypost You're not, you're an ill informed idiot who has hate oozing out of you… https://t.co/XCX7doV41N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scored this @madewell1937 top secondhand and needed to get it dry cleaned so when I walked to pick it up I asked, “… https://t.co/wMRjEnUna1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iloverobots. Great @VEXRobotics competition underway. Over 80 elem and middle school teams driving and programming… https://t.co/hiTvmdc5f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my 3 y/o students just told me “I know the bust down dance, my dad taught me. You wanna see?” And he starts… https://t.co/wR7HZ5FRNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Henryhahadavis @IngrahamAngle @charliekirk11 You guys Rock🇺🇸 #MAGA #Respect #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelJFell @TuckerCarlson @realDonaldTrump Tucker is a TITAN...a GENIOUS A Torero, I lived in Spain 4 years, in… https://t.co/4MbHnNcfXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says @GeorginaGrogan_ This right here. I often get people asking when I am on a trip how much of that particul… https://t.co/uXly4w0nVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimmy Kimmel’s Baby Bachelor is literally the best thing I have ever seen on tv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lm1975 He’s gonna day he’s the greatest actor that ever lived, and the #Oscars2019 goes to...haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[That hearing yesterday was an early birthday present for me. The Dems made me proud!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! I think you'll love this deal at Clean Eatz - Shalimar:  $2 off a purchase of $10 or more  Tap the link to acc… https://t.co/2uCesecW6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep this thought in your heart today as you go out into the world.  Little things can be big things. 🌊  . Via… https://t.co/B4gY5B9Rls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since nickle is such a common allergy, why tf are all pants made with it?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bff’s dog gives me affection for the sheer purpose of making my dog jealous so he plays with her. What a sloot]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are starting a war in Venezuela to change the conversation from Russia? This is insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Magical GIF-Making Gods,  @TheLizLincoln and I need a GIF about “this is the hill I will die on.”  Surely this… https://t.co/FpksjjRV1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rahisilver @ecstacynights I guess he dont think Can will used that bat on his ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robbing Peter to pay paul🤡this is the guy who says he is a great deal maker! What a clown🤡🤡🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[last time I hiked my favorite spot in LA ⛰  and, it feels like, the last time I saw ☀️ almost 5 years ago 😳 . . . .… https://t.co/jGgDbNkeyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call your senators, too! Revoke Trump's tantrum "national emergency." https://t.co/VzKsAOndnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soft_white13 Hahahaha this is what you call self centered? I call it self love and it ain't nothing wrong with it😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[My child just read this book by @DrewDaywalt and started snapping his fingers and chanting “They quit! They quit!”… https://t.co/UFK04hLW8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate When will his 15 minutes be over? Why do they allow him any airtime?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d take a workout selfie but it’s awful 😂😂 so just believe me when I say I didn’t forget my headphones this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The only thing we have in common with Venezuela is a Dictator ,The names are different but they are the Same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud mama alert! 🗣 One of my @AVID4College babies won the school wide spelling bee 🐝! Couldn’t be more proud of hi… https://t.co/4o8bqT6ykR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent five hours doing my taxes and still not done. Send help. https://t.co/8HCrtUmfTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 @Bornabrit1 well certainly trump should be friends with him right? TRUMP IS A TRAITOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirFreebie75061 Oh I’m going you see, I have something better to do with my life but, sit behind a screen being a… https://t.co/jdmLvlxF6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the realization that I am not close with anyone anymore. Like I don’t think not one person knows me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleymkingx You should go and become a neurologist just so you can beat the shit out of your current one]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the worst friends I've ever had told me one of the deepest truths about myself. They said I don't love mysel… https://t.co/H2mqEpISWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckbarrett ugh, i regretted not grabbing food but then our creative director brought a bag of chicken biscuits in 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm vending at an event for the first time ever this month. Super excited and nervous at the same time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willoughby58 Don't  play  north Korea  like, obama,  Clinton,  Bush's.  Try a new approach . YES NK, has human rig… https://t.co/mXh90HkNZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great minds...dress alike? It's a purple day on the anchor desk. @claudine_TV #amnewser https://t.co/sVp4g2HD1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcwalsh23 Right?? Or maybe throw something low in the zone or offspeed?? Let’s adjust.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My college is celebrating black history month with fried chicken and mac and cheese for lunch and this for dinner👍🏼 https://t.co/HhmfP8w6DG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police officer pulled a gun on a black man picking up trash on his own property. Now, the department is investigati… https://t.co/t6XQwvsyH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hometown taught me to cringe, but not be surprised, when people say "Wolfs" rather than "Wolves" 😬🐺😬 #PetPeeves]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 4240 WOODMONT LN #Waldorf #MD  #realestate https://t.co/TyqAJ5Mw7O  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punkrockmattel @netflix Over and Over. We stan @nicolebyer in our house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great conversation! Thanks to Colleen Jamieson for giving us an update on all things IAUG 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the way you put it. I believe it is especially important to note “no allegiance to the US”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Who in the bleep gave Omar permission to go to Africa? She has work to do here that she isn't doing cu… https://t.co/y1u3iUh1X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make fun of girls who have a picture of just themselves as their background but I just saw a whole new level of b… https://t.co/i4mPUuIFNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I so fuckin uncoordinated lol I just wanna be able to snowboard 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @senmajldr @Jim_Jordan @MarkMeadows this is the man you traitors are defending!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackmjenkins This document is from 2017, from TEC website. The Episcopal-UMC dialogue has been going on for a whil… https://t.co/RNQ6mjfcel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @dibmustang2015 Still pretending. He cried on cue today‼️😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisahloveslife @ChristyLavalle3 @TeddiMellencamp @LisaVanderpump That would be the first thing you do call Lisa an… https://t.co/39n5EgjfCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dramatic decrease in #sentence levels would automatically diminish inequities. That should be the first step (not t… https://t.co/OCdfNR3eeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy FRIDAY!!  We hope you can join us for @FOX10News this morning! @michaelwhitewx https://t.co/D6rXDOZ4G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsStrattonTX @SBoiarsky I agree, Lisa. Sharing was always the hardest to get in each day! I like the idea of usin… https://t.co/ilOIpAwoBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsHour @KrisKobach1787 THIS IS NOT AN EXAMPLE OF IN DEPTH ANALYSIS.  Back to the drawing board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imjeremytho @blkumathurman @funny_layde This will be forgot about in no time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angela Merkel Mocks Trump Administration, But Ivanka Is Not Having It https://t.co/R9INJeC6PU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lovelies, enjoying the sun. @ Koitzsch Quick Residence https://t.co/MsnatJowYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skordle @Deercreekbball @SFWolvesAthl Let’s GO @Deercreekbball @mslate2121 🙌🏾☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to socialize right after watching serial killer documentaries, but that’s part of the appeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @watercutter11 They did THIS while DONALD TRUMP/HITLER danced on his grave! HOW much more EVIL can yo… https://t.co/udE7VKO9Sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotional status update: after being gone for 3 nights I was most excited to get back to my bed... DUNCAN must have… https://t.co/4k9hW642Rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rommelromero6 @Polificcion Con respecto a Paez, tengo mis dudas, pero no por él voy a ensuciar la reputación de… https://t.co/uaJpYb3Q0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part about winter storms is I don’t feel right ordering food because then someone who is just tryna make… https://t.co/m5voVxF5cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New vlog! This week, some of @100Thieves got to go to @UCLA to do fun stuff with their esports team @BruinGG and I… https://t.co/OGcY1xxdK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up singing in my head Year 300 by the Jonas Bros. It’s going to be a good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil don’t have horns and red eyes that motherfucker got on a pair of balmains , some butters &amp; a kenzo sweater]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can be a better politician then the republicans who are afraid to confront the corrupt president in office! It’s… https://t.co/qIQvo00G0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferAnWorld @Laurenrobz EXCUSE ME?? why doesn’t this hot ass bitch have a blue check but @RayBoudreaux does??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I just feel really sad and lonely rn. This wave of darkness just fell over me is what it feels like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marymclaughli10 @GameOfThrones @Xfinity Good idea! I need to get caught up on cocktail party commentary! Need to c… https://t.co/JCjWzMWKDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to be at work by 6:30am but it will be snowing all night till 6am 😭 tell me how will I drive to work… https://t.co/tW9BYquLAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingofSteel @KamalaHarris I saw her dad was pretty pissed about that. He is a professor at Stanford I guess. The n… https://t.co/pg92fbcSl2]]></document></documents></author>