<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KFILE If she rode an ox they'd be complaining she was a hypocrite about cattle farts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Confused_Canuck @FFRF If competition was plentiful and we didn't have a huge problem with bigotry, that would make… https://t.co/hVtqg4MoXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph N. Barometer 30.352 in, Steady. Temperature 9.5 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 72%]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I think about women in comedy I think about the funniest people I've ever met and how they've never touched a stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewinuk1 @ALfromSanDiego I love that video, it’s so hard to believe that’s our last time playing slots together with @ALfromSanDiego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroGilF Que inmoral eres pendejo , el corrupto sistema que impera en cuba no ha sido capaz de resolverles lo… https://t.co/p0IAOJkZtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are New Consoles Coming This Year? (Nintendo Switch, Xbox, PlayStation) https://t.co/3qPjNtyoh6 gamers have had it… https://t.co/3HrRvviYCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CetranoSusan @CKLions @Tom_Winter True, however, NY State is about to bring the heat on DIFFERENT CRIMES avoiding… https://t.co/1Y4MIB7EMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nose Piercing inkinri ray_ce #holdsteadytattoo #holdsteadytattoos #tattoo #tattoos #piercing #piercings #ri… https://t.co/fCOo8IoMLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobyMotyka @sarhilde @nyusaw @USAWrestling @nywomenwrestle Thank you! She won the PSAL state title today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[90 Day Challenge - Day 1 (Attempt 2) (@ Disney's Guest Services Call Center in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/h3mLHc2EoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, weather people. Time to earn your paycheck. #okwx https://t.co/tIU3KaxJyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyM84 @TehMartini @_Jeg_ @moxieplays @_Leoba_ @TheMikicus Totally, sounds great]]></document><document><![CDATA[New tint on Landy. Bracing for a summer as hot as this February was cold. (@ Agave Auto Glass in Chandler, AZ) https://t.co/muveZ9JweM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseBauz En el caso d Vinicius en inferiores tiene demasiado gol, en la mayor es otra cosa pero aunque no sea gole… https://t.co/zoZXwZTVx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaOrejuela @Janfilofobia Viernes? Sabado? Que importa que dia sea mientras se vea asi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFT_Podcast @chuckwoolery Roe v. Wade reversed because of those democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of our sleeper episodes #shellpod #uwfi   Listen to Gary Albright in UWFi - Shellpod - Episode 65 by Shellshock… https://t.co/epyNfYZq7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hkerkhofs @AtlantaAgCurt @FarmChicJodi @IHboog @HaesenAnita @mandrews64 @BootscootinGMaw @HedrickJessica… https://t.co/yuT4FBl5FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best wishes Doug! Thank you for everything you have done building social enterprise and community in Ottawa. I know… https://t.co/sWiAbg4NQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amber02731321 @Br0ckMcCullough Thanks Amber!!! Tell Tyler congratulations!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t pay fuck nigga fees we don’t take fronts and we don’t kick nothing upstairs on dis side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training girl puppies is the worst.. can’t tell if she’s squating or sitting]]></document><document><![CDATA[#casaamigoswednesdays &lt;Full photo downloads&gt;  Are found on my Facebook Fanpage • (LIKE) (@ByrdsPhotos) •… https://t.co/BQFRstSW1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSAL___ I was reading something about how stretching isn't as useful as we think. And idk I might agree I stretch… https://t.co/im5r72Q8TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow just started coming down hard in LIC, Queens ❄️ ⛄️ https://t.co/etTFqF5wXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamXMen on @TyltEnt—can't wait for the X-Men to join the MCU https://t.co/SqXWhg1JRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin with Chip Foose, Chris Jacobs,Wayne Carini, Mike Mason and Ant Anstead here at @Mac_Tools tool fair https://t.co/UsqH46Wzbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜𝐻𝒶𝓅𝓅𝓎 𝒲𝑜𝓂𝒶𝓃’𝓈 𝒟𝒶𝓎💜 To all my beautiful friends and family. To those who recognize themselves as a woman, female wh… https://t.co/wOEqJClerT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bballbreakdown Is it fundamentally different than any of his other games? No? Then NO!  I’m just giving you a hard… https://t.co/qWh9vGjIdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A positive attitude is definitely one of the keys to success. My definition of a positive attitude is a simple one… https://t.co/jw5jdIuLFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNoeShow @kfigg1 @ryanburschinger I just didn’t want Old Iron Innards Bursch to end up like this poor fellow at… https://t.co/d28dDZFA03]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York Islanders Play in Third Period Is A Weakness https://t.co/IoiaAXfp98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feast On is certification programme for chefs in Ontario who use at least 52 %  food grown in Ontario on their menu… https://t.co/bcY6XONX8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know where the door handles are on the 2020 @Tesla Roadster 🤯🤯🤯🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone, other myself, learned that Publishers Clearing House promotions and games are a "scam"? I have been pla… https://t.co/nhVbPI6cTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardiacDrop I’m not doing Anthem. I can’t do EA anymore. They’re just terrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg. You Never know what you’ll run into at Mardi Gras St. Louis. 😂 https://t.co/lDCnzsRvQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danorlovsky7 Thoughts on if the Lions should offer something up for Rosen just so they have a decent backup? I’m f… https://t.co/8X6gPrxbEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelmanDC @TayStern Doesn’t say it in the description... https://t.co/0dZBvEcLTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night out w/ the boo @VeronicaVega #LHHMIA #VeronicaVega #ChasingAtlanta https://t.co/8LEkECrGzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety You use our beautiful city to make money and make a tv show..  Words of advice get rid of him... ain't no pity in Chi city]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaynesMar @IndyCarNation @GPSTPETE I loved having the chance to do it last year at Long Beach it was an amazing experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoIntoTheStory Well ... what do I need to do to get the right ones together..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dailyinspo #blessedbeyondmeasure🙏😇 @ Huntington Beach, California https://t.co/4bA2iVSp7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45 #TrumpPence2020… https://t.co/MM1Ef3nSL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposed to be here on Thursday and it came early 😍😍😍 @dylansprouse @allwisemeadery #DylanSprouse #allwisemeadery https://t.co/Jf19XOocI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seve pitching it as only Seve could @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/oE5p6QhVao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't stand this honey, you know how soft my heart is..  https://t.co/gdn6KHWgRy I don't want to be mean.. but we… https://t.co/4Vpk0V9L5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshHikenGuitar @angelalynn37 Thank you you deserve some glory  to @JoshHikenGuitar , I dont mind sharing the atte… https://t.co/f91pkYG9wM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PirryOficial También de pedir disculpa por aquellos Animales que se creen que los Parió Un Robot 🤖 La Mujer La más… https://t.co/TJ3J05Hc1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras not just celebrated in NOLA, but.... this shit goes DOWN like no other!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnwhitehead81 At a minimum, it makes for a good discussion. And we will be having on in LA this coming Friday. s… https://t.co/uBybXX03MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just can’t get excited for Dark Phoenix. X Men: Apocalypse just kinda ruined that franchise for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, and the democrats are the ones advocating for tearing down the Confederates Statues while Republicans want to… https://t.co/IZXFZQNhfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke Energy was the top funder of a secretive group of coal-heavy utilities that paid a lobbying firm millions of d… https://t.co/cKsdmwlTPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson The president of the United States to McConnell instead of telling the American people. Why wouldn’t obama inform the country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klf113 @DanielAshley13 I wonder how many #FakeMelania there are. The one I seen though didn't look like her at all… https://t.co/v5kJykr5TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye said let’s have a 3 some with u and da blunt and It’s honestly very inspiring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hera Gfuel energy... make sure to use code monstcr at checkout for 10% off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow blaming Jody and throwing her under the bus. So much for @liberal_party @JustinTrudeau women’s empowerment agen… https://t.co/hgCgf3h3cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our energy industry is in crisis, but Trudeau is too busy doing damage control over SNC-Lavalin to act… https://t.co/SGh75Zz4d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alinn29 @shyelaine9 “GiRLs PlAy HaRd” ........ “GET YOUR HANDS OFF OF HER!” LEEDLE LEEDEL LEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reaching for “sloppy joes” to get a rhyme for “hos” shows you where modern rap is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWilliams_SN hey Matt are you covering the Peabody high school girls varsity hockey state tournament hockey game tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielleradford Omg the scene where they are in the lab high on edibles.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome capture of the clouds near kitchener,Ont late this evening @Lyndsay_CTV @MurphTWN #ShareYourWeather… https://t.co/sRFlQjuC4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberBobamber @ademilcf @RealSaavedra Illegal votes but hey don't let facts get in the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelondaxi Thanks, just tryna do my oartvsnd spread love 🙏🏽 , happy Valentine’s Day to you btw 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiShite @JoyAnnReid @SpeakerPelosi No One is saying take away guns Stop deflecting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP @AmyKremer @realDonaldTrump We've all had enough as Americans listening about Russia and how ungrate… https://t.co/5kFRFmxtNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu parei de me culpar quando alguem se afasta, eu sei que no fundo nao foi culpa minha e que o meu coração é bom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zer0724 @ATLSoccerClub @andrewbresee No relation to NISA. ASC used to be the Silverbacks and now has a new name be… https://t.co/A0XJEN2UII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viewsfordays @HoarseWisperer @tonyposnanski Exactly!!!! They are famous because one made a Fuck tape....C'mon.......really?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADuralde @RichardEGrant What I want to know is when are he and Essie Davis gonna throw us an HBO spinoff about the… https://t.co/Z7irlk6M3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice story about abook n spaceflight that I contributed to. https://t.co/sM9Z6mmsSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What God has called and anointed you to do will begin to emerge in your life. As you yield to it, it grows in stren… https://t.co/fC0JGN09ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[لما انقولوا ايران اخطر من اي شي اخر عالاسلام والعرب  ينطوا في رقابينا الجهله والغوغاء وانصاف المثقفين]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAtkinss @MyInfoIngridZ1 @EileenDiana @Shelley2021 @JewelsJones1 @elle_rube @ksandiego52 @mkel2010 @Anxie_TEA… https://t.co/BbXJtYUpa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday mornings @Todd_Norman.   Youth training in full swing.  #balance #stability #injuryprevention @ Laguna Beach… https://t.co/d2EgtQbsjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaseyKauff @johnny_sheridan @CSkronsk273 @MitchChalkley Just 18? I guess that’s one per hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei I don't know why people get so upset about this and like it how it is. In autumn you get an extra hour… https://t.co/UqqaHU6fTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidnaAsh Alright after Shoalin Monks being th last MK game I played I'm definitely gonna get this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mma_kings O’Malley is a bozo. Manny will have that boy snoozin’ within 3 mins. 🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ziegenkind094 DONT HOLD BACK LET THE GATES OPEN LET YOURE THOUFGTS BE FREE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SixoTF @Guido_Guidi Can’t we just get a Black Gold repaint first? https://t.co/mZ2YCDy4Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettRichey Yeah that should be the focus but I bet if Kraft not involved that story gets a lot less coverage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanpthurman @ScotPollard31 @KU_Football @CoachLesMiles Ron Prince was so bad, he won 17 games in 3 seasons. Which… https://t.co/yK9SYocfix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guxtg @DIAPOLA @jciragorri @JSantrich_FARC @ArielAnaliza @VocesRCN Basura.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent sushi. Lots of wood! (@ Hakashi in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/mJmrO15loI https://t.co/2o6NSkOCvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foone Never noticed. Just enjoyed the music &amp; Picard's tender intimacy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPM The sooner, the better.  Let's end this fucking Dotard charade.  #hobomessiah  Enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Motley Crue biopic probably won't include this quote I once heard one member of the band say to another in a me… https://t.co/UrWNAkf674]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1JWOZ4 They’ll still make the playoffs it’s whatever. Would love to see them end the season as the 5 seed and swee… https://t.co/g3ln7M9PxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[11/ you, Hal Brands, and Francis Gavin may lament that historians are not doing enough do the history that *you* th… https://t.co/5aXrgKr7Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a personal note, I'm 5'11 and I've always felt short because I wasnt 6'. But,I've never felt the need to lie abo… https://t.co/mPlFphqPk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel #StanLeeTribute #Marvel #Avengers @ AMC 7 Santa Monica https://t.co/VrlSdPYPYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is a movie that hopefully will have a good ending where ever my road takes me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonslagle Like I don’t like everything I see—but I’ll still high-five you for making it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😏Brothers.. If you wake up in the middle of the night to pee, brush your teeth while you're in there. Your bride wi… https://t.co/RCbuSYdOiI]]></document></documents></author>