<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_Hayyden @in_pubs @realDonaldTrump Obama inherited a disaster. Tiy@Ed it around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonLCarter I agree! My journalism degree is from @UofNorthFlorida and I write for a Fortune 150 company. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin's Trump returns to declare a national emergency on 'SNL' - CNN https://t.co/iWBFiwmsaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamdevinnsmart Get rid of them eye boogers and get on board.  Happy to have you ~]]></document><document><![CDATA[80’s @hdsa Re-Prom happening now!!!  Donate at https://t.co/6aHbr9UpGb    👗 is a legit 80s prom dress, make up by C… https://t.co/XX1wQ0tmrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChapoyPati  Nuestra protesta energica a televisa por faltarle respeto  a Institucion matrimonial mexicana y patroc… https://t.co/xJHfxigvQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purge the old mail before imposing the new guidelines.  This would make more sense.  Leaving those nasty comments u… https://t.co/4rEJsJZ3AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok if I started making cute earrings would anyone actually buy them because I’m not tryna waste my time n money lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what it’s like to be able to have more than 3 beers or drinks and not puke. I’ll probably never know becau… https://t.co/VOqK9mvlby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thevirdas Something we don't need. Carry on. If it makes us wha dafuk, we don't need it 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Valentines Day Cards #humor #giggle #grin #clever https://t.co/zqNNfwWHTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 @stassi Awe you have a fear of dying? And that’s so funny that you clean b4 the maids come, cuz we do t… https://t.co/CsPsfI2Iix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empowering, encouraging, and equipping difference makers (students and staff) mission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to spend the day than with friends? HALO’s therapy dogs came to campus for the students. I had to g… https://t.co/anlzgwEllC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilsonBasktball @curlybeviie @renahenry @Prototypemia https://t.co/M2Vr2qpkyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump so sad this is what has become of America]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because who doesn’t love a mint dress?!? 👗 👑 Kate and Meghan are both looking lovely today at the 50th Anniversary… https://t.co/DzFl72ZJVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Recuerdas cuando te uniste a Twitter? ¡Yo sí! #MiAniversarioDeTwitter https://t.co/o2HWnUtuGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I wanna be a poet!! @ Murfreesboro, Tennessee https://t.co/RdTlSqeCfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful &amp; powerful film ✨  @TheAnimalsFilm   #WeTheAnimals https://t.co/gjpwlpSSUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Just stop being sad,” - said the Worst. Cunty. Redhead. Therapist. EVER!!!!! #afterlife #AfterLife #RickyGervais]]></document><document><![CDATA[eating an entire package of shockers and burning the roof of my mouth https://t.co/QMZxImaBvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Because he's so deeply concerned and realizes his responsiblity to put America's  well being above all… https://t.co/EX6t20tq7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[One issue sleepy Jay.   It's the issue he has time for.  Lining his own pockets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras 2019 #theWilliamsturnup #baecation #noworries #blacklove @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/joVd2936cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of you clowns look like you learned how to dress from Instagram paid sponsored ads lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wtf this ghibli jazz cover of country home fukin SLAPS https://t.co/PwanK477AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the hell would ever write that about someone’s child, someone that already risks there life everyday for the pe… https://t.co/tDnK4zcpvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prairie_Bayou @trevormmccarthy Glorious! Wow! How beautiful. Im thrilled to have the photos to ah over!! It is lov… https://t.co/SFxw0zEiCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna redecorate the whole house in a Old West/Horse Ranch 🐎type of theme. So my jerrywaynegray bought me a sad… https://t.co/g9KA8ZO6yW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought Captain America was supposed to punch Nazis so I wouldn’t have to...yet here we are. 👊🏻#punchnazis… https://t.co/oXGtiPB6eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So basically I’m in a manic and depressive state at the same time. This has caused me to BLOSSOM at work, but when… https://t.co/tQGNt2TTAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home Ownership, it's about the simple things....... https://t.co/0N7Kc6DZpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump Is Committed to Achieving Transformational Peace for the United States, the Korean Peninsula, and t… https://t.co/5WgnrBjaZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie Katy Tur begs to differ. Recorded and on the record. Add it to Trump's lies....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challenge accepted! @kelly_hipp challenged me to post the covers of 7 books I love. No explanations. No reviews. Ea… https://t.co/79VdVgYl0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me la paso encontrándote entre mis sueños y voy buscando el momento para quererte con tiempo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bumped my credit load to 25 today.   In other news, did you know a wheat thin, some cream cheese, and a doll… https://t.co/ND3aoE7ZGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @auridgold @AOC @RashidaTlaib @steph93065 you are “Becky with good hair” lol LOVE IT!!! Feel free to si… https://t.co/VdwX3iQd2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ebb and Flow Bracelet in solid 14 karat gold, and my signature Sand Drop Earrings! 🔥 🤗 Molten gold in poured direct… https://t.co/AeqLPRc3tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I know folks aren’t super thrilled with the 24 hour library topic, and I get the whole how would it get funded… https://t.co/T3YbPhagjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Can we hold him and his I'll accountable? Will anything happen to them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone had better be working on a super thotty remix of the new jobros song]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/lM2HKWBB2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[So last Tuesday was wayyy better than this Tuesday. #22 https://t.co/kZ0JMoM5Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder when the rest of duke's 1992 team will be by to announce a #UK game? 🙄 #WeAreUK #StillHateDuke #BBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drove through what I will call an 'outlying' ruralesque area and let me tell you if you don't have differently si… https://t.co/OY20OjLNyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow She’s a problem.Too many questions are coming up about her actions past and present]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grace_crockett @EGA_ECNL @OmahaWSOC so happy for to grace! love you and your work ethic so much! can’t wait for the next 2 seasons!! 💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heart of the discerning acquires knowledge, for the ears of the wise seek it out. Proverbs 18… https://t.co/O0TI4nncvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staciemontero Yes let’s do it! I’m always up for a getaway! I got my new carry on and everything ready to go! Haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing about me is I’ll do whatever it takes to help someone out. I can never just turn my shoulder on anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 🎁@tperez3826 #GIVEAWAY AT 1,000 FOLLOWERS, WHICH WILL BE REVEALED AT A LATER TIME.🎁 . Now available-… https://t.co/YLDqifvHOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopeyesChicken  Store #3194 This was the absolute worse experience at popeyes I have ever had. The service was abs… https://t.co/m5EnaazkwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoffordTerriers @WoffordBaseball Congratulations @matthewbrown_13   Incredibly proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of the time I was so fucked up at a party and I smoked a cig down to the butt thinking it was a joi… https://t.co/ljlTp9zj9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bellport peeps who have moved away- you ever try explaining how special bellport is to someone and get so lost in l… https://t.co/lS4BLZ7jW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ Twitter!!! I can’t believe it’s been 9 years!!! Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do!… https://t.co/h47qyqv9XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anarchojet @carterforva Nothing in life is free. Handouts shouldn’t exist. People need to Work for what they want… https://t.co/zoSQEBbNQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I asked @maddie_morella to hangout and forgot to tell her I was still in slip, she texts me “here” and I looked… https://t.co/dvHQbEjjU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere I've had T-Mobile since 2003? I've already pre-ordered my Samsung galaxy 10. Hook a girl up with early delivery or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMuskin @jmksd @realDonaldTrump Or, do the american patriotic thing and let the courts deal with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thank Rep. Raychel Proudie for withdraw this Bill as of this AM. However, I saw her responses to other emails fro… https://t.co/z5zh7MKHhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a very classy lady.@BlogChurchWork @2Texasbears @McFaul @amvetsupport @BlueGhost40_ @LightfootInHwd… https://t.co/Nmut76WgbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Nothing would surprise me, but I doubt it. She'll probably pick the worst Democratic candidate and put… https://t.co/VF99JxgrRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hello President Trump!  I have been an avid supporter of you from day 1!  Watched every debate bet… https://t.co/aR2n1Bqk6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[ironically, according to the cleaning professionals cited here, one component of this hotel's green initiative is a… https://t.co/n1OnhoYk2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely beautiful. One day I’ll listen to this live with my person 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Micharty @katelynnugent I feel like @CJEytel is gonna jump in this any minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Korean and native American is the most attractive combination I have ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieunderwood baby is going to come out singing like an angel after hearing all these Elvis songs performed like… https://t.co/OaZxavgDLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup. This is about how speaking at council always feels: https://t.co/PyEHeGsVfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I have lied, but I am not a liar.” - Cohen. That’s beautiful. #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/24/19. Can't take it anymore‼️want it to STOP‼️Losing my mind‼️Can't find peace or relief or escape or distractio… https://t.co/zPeIk9BjXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola, estoy viendo Los Oscars desde un restaurante de Los Angeles, a menos de un km de donde están siendo, mientras… https://t.co/Dnhd5mpN3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @tammywalt61 @IlhanMN @Ilhan @SpeakerPelosi @LeaderHoyer @GOPLeader https://t.co/O0nFjiqnfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__thewrapguy__ So true!  Gonna watch your pretty car win tomorrow!  We are here now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/P5NwwPdhPe  Get a quick valuable overcome to your issues through Amazon phone number 1-855-431-5111  amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[baby girl said she’s going to catch me on sight lmao 😂 pero when I see you, you can’t even look at me 😂 she’s just… https://t.co/1AGkJtZhgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#c89robandmegan #niagaralandmark #redanguns #touringwithrobandmegan @ Queenston, Ontario https://t.co/kE8T98ct6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviFlyGirl @LauraHausch @harrisonjaime @LindseyGrahamSC Oh Man, that arrogant bastard is a real piece of work....with his  $31K dining set.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break the HABIT of PROCRASTINATION! | Mel Robbins (@melrobbins) | Top ... https://t.co/mV2KiWadia via @YoutubeDCTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever find that pair of jeans that fit perfectly and you never want to take them off? That is currently me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks To see this man sit in a hearing under oath is the right thing to do even if he wins again. Pull the curtain down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a PAID left media propagandist with 833,000 followers.   Are people stupid? BLOCK HIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite bike trail looks so different today than it usually does when I’m on it #BugLineTrail #LoveWhereYouLive… https://t.co/FYqFM6v2CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougJones @nycsouthpaw If the rule of law ever applies to lock him up, his son is out of a job. Naive to think the two can be unrelated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-Marjory Stoneman Douglas Student's Quest To End Gun Violence https://t.co/oofGPPEHri]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so fuckin giving and then turn around and feel used and lowkey will resent them for a minute because i feel lik… https://t.co/QSwXs9xzWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[guy from high school  *sees me at the gym *DOESN’T SAY A WORD  *texts me 20 minutes later  “i saw you at the gym”… https://t.co/xlAjUWcfbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway here’s a pic of my dogs begging for my chicken bites. https://t.co/n2mTU8C6pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to see this again in my feed. Welcome back to the road! @joekwon80 and @theavettbros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TemekaEaster Well. It is a fact that it isn’t a good look right now.   The media with all these different “sources. “🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPSTauro @OPSDAoust @NCC_CCN @PoliceGatineau Should have some kind of joint winter training with Gatineau "emergen… https://t.co/3OeVNvXxAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Part of forensic profiling when investigating the murder of a woman, is to immediately question all male family me… https://t.co/KADFyWj12O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building Resilience in Youth with Learning Disabilities https://t.co/FEX2AcOj8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Girl you live tweet yourself in the kitchen every damn night. What do you expect?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please donate to Vacaville Softball for our 2019 season!  https://t.co/bydDedtiAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning friends.  Let's have a great day! I'm probably going to run out if this hydramatte in Cher because I k… https://t.co/vzKYaBohQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry to everyone for spamming the tl with parx i just hella want to make this thread for memories and so ppl who c… https://t.co/cVtbvBzXfo]]></document></documents></author>