<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If someone could draw me dressed like Yusuke I’d be sooo grateful I’ll pay you too no cap]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a Trace Salton hoop from Grant Fuson, Lake Oswego leads West Linn 58-57 with 19 seconds left. #opreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @jeff_haden and @inc. I personally think waking up before 7am is for the birds. :-) I also believe going… https://t.co/FPw8egWg4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMayaAhmad Maya. My wife was born and raised in #KSA. We now live in the USA. Can you please help to spread her… https://t.co/IKiP6GWfRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @HillBeverlyhill HE THINKS THERE IS A PARDON WAITING FOR HIM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chronic_Tired Yeah, definitely not overly excited about any particular candidate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Lambo_Mercy_ @SethDavisHoops Last I saw them, they were getting blown out by Rutgers at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a project going on and need some inspiration. What are some essential westerns I should study? Or, what’s your favorite western films?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was the greatest @adamlevine country song I have ever heard! #VoiceBlinds #TheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to my #hgrbusministry #hgrkids they are growing up to fast! #hgrfamily #FAITHMTN #faiithmtnrevival @ The Rock C… https://t.co/78vVdS5PK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[in honor of @TheCW announcement today that @CW_Arrow will end with its #Season8 some #Arrow inspired art from the s… https://t.co/kxO2eGy5PX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news!! https://t.co/wCyxV7l7MT will be carrying live play-by-play of the Chester @ Lower Merion boys high sch… https://t.co/SDdVB25OT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1upmovement @PCisnotmything @tariqnasheed Bro those people were not peaceful ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ LA HORA, JUNTOS PARA HACER HISTORIA!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/YUmi8hjHVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckReising This ordeal not ending with a run of the mill, ho hum trade shouldn’t be surprising.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rcor13 @NorCalBaseball @baseballgabe17 Gabe is going to have a huge year this year. Going to be fun to follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everanever @Zendaya @TommyHilfiger @LUXURYLAW https://t.co/ZQtzMUXDim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@locknesss456 @GothCharlotte @lancehartfetish @sgt_doe @JimPowersXXX @SirTomMoore @jj69oo @ErectionAddict1 @pman43… https://t.co/Bi4M1afBp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnWDean I kept twitting when this all started two weeks ago...NO ONE KNOWS...but Mueller and his team! 😉👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bag of tortilla chips was reduced to crumbs so I put them in a bowl, used salsa as milk, and am currently watchi… https://t.co/kDvAzE8Gns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just brought up Ponderosa steakhouse to me from the old woodbridge center days.  Damn that buffet ruled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames these episodes too short bro! Need more content! Tell hbo y’all need an hour. Loving this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Praydrian Being the first or second baby daddy is cool, but the third !!! 😂😂 fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You Lord Jesus for LOVING me, even before I knew anything about You.  Thank You for teaching me about Your LO… https://t.co/xHmmQ2TH0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[First cannabis equity permit moves toward approval, faces pushback from rejected applicants - San Francisco Examine… https://t.co/OgIQerWqJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great morning speaking to new OTA students about amputations, prosthetics and life... @ Los Angeles, Califor… https://t.co/V6SvbR2dvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck man. I’m used to living in southern NM. Sick of this cold and wind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New project by Aummaah titled 'Quick Work Vol.1'  Listen now:  https://t.co/8gF60umrTG https://t.co/WIAKgvcLeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Employee Spotlight: Lauren Burton  https://t.co/wfxHdHfiS7 #automarketing #WeAreJandL #moretrafficmoreselling #digital #digitalmarketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[S. 548: A bill to reauthorize the Money Follows the Person Demon... https://t.co/DUTqKTvCM0 via @GovTrack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanmdav @LatAmFr Democrats would be exactly like Stalinists if the American people were disarmed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1) Instructional Coaching is ☑️personalized ☑️ ever evolving  ☑️measurable (progressively) ☑️mistake prone (good thing)   #EduGladiators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed a great night with friends and family at the devotionchampionshipwrestling #matchmadness the show was epic.… https://t.co/XjXToDMMOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[You finally get mom and dad to fork over 100 bucks so you can see your favorite band, but you learn that the concer… https://t.co/NyMMB7J6Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[[playing Monopoly]  Fights for 45 minutes over who gets to be the dog then quits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acmills237 @bkben3 God isn’t the only thing simple and impassible. Ben’s love life is 60% the way to classical theism divinity status.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Bennett:  "When you see that arm drop, it's not worth it for us or the fighter." #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you absolutely HAVE to take a pic of you in the hospital bed w a oxygen mask to post on Ig, is it COMPLETELY necessary at that point?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lilzizi___ I promise it slaps 😂😂 only if you one of the people that hate water in there noodles like me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bien dicen que las noches son productivas para los músicos #LoQuePiensoDeTi 🎺🎼   Tú, el paisaje más hermoso que he… https://t.co/RvMfgj7IVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come for the Blazers stuck on an elevator, but stay for the look on Evan Turners face]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not one girl on her that I follow doesn’t have “ people that you know follow her” I hate AZ bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TmarTn @ChelseaKreiner @OrlandoCitySC Will you be around for a couple minutes after the match? My little brother d… https://t.co/nCPxDT1lou]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damn seeing Rollins tear up during Romans announcement hit me in the fucking feels]]></document><document><![CDATA[On KSU winning the league: Great for them. Truly. An incredible accomplishment. That their home crowd then chanted… https://t.co/4aOl8aF115]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Penn is a Republican plant. I worked for him for one week in 2006 and my only project was to be part of a team… https://t.co/BdYsLAYE23]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am fairly certain that a large portion of the high net worth of rappers rests in their necklaces. 😳😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordannilson Lmao I know for sure @denali_epub isn’t going to murder me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatharineVogel @derekbauman @pat_laFleur @BusinessCourier @DaumeyerCinBiz Rob’s comments are pretty much comment s… https://t.co/SlrOzBMl3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were going to compete for pink slips, but Kappa Sig doesn’t have a house and ATO’s is too small...🤷🏼‍♂️ https://t.co/RAMMegcU2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ox Film Productions is a real estate photography and video production company serving Hamilton, Burlington, Oakvill… https://t.co/pkNPrukulv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReporterFaith @NatishaLance If they are free to walk around then, speaking to their families should be very easy t… https://t.co/sJNF8NiAm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 fouls in the first half.  6 fouls in less than 3 minutes to start the second half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saturnial False dichotomy - both are important. The two are related: non-scalable systems provide a bad user experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Butch_No_Way Saw somebody else said they’re playing Madden with the salary cap off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFGGGG. This is amazing news, I’ve been waiting for this for a year. Omg. Yes. M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDVMWeather Thundersnow in Flintstone, Maryland! So cool!! #thundersnow https://t.co/rLYMETu49Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncommitted @BlackSox_Ohio infielder @mattritch22 (@HBBaseball18, 2020) — #BoScoutDay https://t.co/gWsYQbKzOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinaGreco @GamerTex @Gardyone @BiloxiBomber @JamieKerstetter @Ray_Henson @RGPokerSeries @Horseshoe_BC I would like… https://t.co/Zv5DKT78hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KildayMorgan @TheDemCoalition @BernieSanders Mine are 1 K. Harris 2 E. Warren 3 anyone who can beat them and make… https://t.co/vfswMKvZyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_3C_3 @thebradfordfile Definitely he has turned political Failure to a BOOMING successful AMERICA by running AMER… https://t.co/a6JRA1gNCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got 2 tickets to see Kiss (final tour) in Memphis Tennessee Saturday February 23rd. Section 115 row T. Because… https://t.co/JYS5W3q7kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukas_sweigart You gotta check it out. If you listen you’ll understand why there’s no answer to that lol. It’s...something else]]></document><document><![CDATA[We may not be smart, but we're also not good at what we do.  Chris Harrison describing my life. #TheBachelor #WomenTellAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pats fans hoping they don’t get asked about Bob Kraft https://t.co/SzxmTIpP9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindSpazms @izzjarq Legumes are a no go with Keto. But that's what my wife said too ...😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbrogan For years they’ve asked. But do they need? No. Now it’s time to ask for a stretchable screen just to s… https://t.co/fD8pvaUt1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisoniMatthew @DavidVonderhaar @Treyarch Just like your mother is at making children...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radiofreihegel That's troubling. Thinking back, all the broadening experiences I've had were specifically because… https://t.co/B1SiZfidUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight... #lemonfire @gpen oleumlabs_  #gpengio #vape #cannabisoil #cannabisterpenes #5secondraw #79%totalthc… https://t.co/R4pT03xx2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @NDMikeBrey for these kind words. I’m not here without you, coach Morgan Wootten, and my first coaches - my… https://t.co/vidtbc174r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBarchard McCutchen, Segura, Harper due up. Let's hope they actually pitch to Bryce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/9E8DfyxGkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaquillaaaaaa Lol that’s exactly what I told em too! Cause he started feeling bad like dam I done messed up the surprise!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA That's what the voters wanted, ... and they got it.  Now they can deal with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthemgame @BenIrvo FYI: It’s possible for Commander Vule to show up twice in Fort Tarsis at the same time (In his… https://t.co/v4618avnP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I brought backup. . . . #mensfashion #weddingfashion #mensvows #husbands #arizona #arizonawedding #realwedding @ Tu… https://t.co/YEFVt9lLmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dw3099 @JermaineDH6903 @BWickkiser14 @GinoTemporal @AmirkahnAmir @FESAmanda @dainfamousmodel @oteroAlucy92… https://t.co/OBY3kqiiea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp y'all... your boy just signed up for his first half marathon.... 😵😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Advanced sense of humor”  Like what does that even mean?? Either you think its funny or you dont]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏽‍♂️The guy in my UberPool is googling "clever comebacks". Looks like he's getting roasted in the group chat with… https://t.co/Fm3YzRgBBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rpsp Presente su causa ante el Señor, y como líder Viva y acepte siempre la voluntad De Dios ! Núm 27.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Kenosha, WI? https://t.co/x1aINe2eWt #Manufacturing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing the Burger Revolution in Omaha on March 9th @theslowdown!#BurgerRevolution7 https://t.co/2bePFRF8ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afneil I was honoured to meet Sir Winston not long before he died. I was a child yet he made time for me even thou… https://t.co/YPHF5CovwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING INSTAFACEBOOGERS @ Farmington, New Mexico https://t.co/6AOGURPZxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the gutsiest wins in recent memory for Michigan. On the road. Short-handed. Foul trouble. Beilein’s wizardry on full display.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: he is intensely unlikable.  Lindsey Graham shares details of his personal life https://t.co/0JlwsU2b9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look it up, it's true ! #Obama was working on making #America turn out like #Venezuela just like @AOC is doing. Tha… https://t.co/TsBJFA4Qsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer pase casi la mitad del día pensando: “Puta madre que a la gente le ha dado por subir fotos con sus parejas en… https://t.co/JIirThKCN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murdochgurl26 @Helene_Joy Me too.  (It’s what I do when my morning conference calls switch to Spanish LOL). https://t.co/MNmEbNJwk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡HOLA TELEMUNDO! No se pierdan el MAÑANA viernes a las 4:00 de la tarde #mardigras #mardigras2019 #happymardigras… https://t.co/etP7UHqZTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God that we chose Trump. Imagine if it were Hillary the president. We would be like French, paying abusive ta… https://t.co/qYELZGSOyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Luxuryhotels used to be a family affair. @rogervincent’s insight explores a revival of the personal touch by… https://t.co/KqV4z6cky1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks This is what my venti iced caramel macchiato looked like after 5 minutes, without taking a sip 😂😂😂😂😂😂 wo… https://t.co/nyuGdPBrZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We judge ourselves from our intentions. Others judge us from our behaviors. We don’t see our behaviors. And others… https://t.co/UE8vhzqBWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish him luck, I don’t have much faith he will move the deniars, grifters, and abusers that have covered up the e… https://t.co/jw0OyQ4uAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filming on location at Union Church in Seattle with @itsrobynwithay for the Presbyterian Foundation. Great communit… https://t.co/eraXEuyKUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Ohh wow, you don’t say - let’s read the constitution   Yep, here’s where he can fire… https://t.co/lm8BCa4xqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday morning ✔in❗50min speed intervals #WMSFITFAM #ForcedObedience #FuriousFive @MsNardosG @austin_carla… https://t.co/OCd9CLOrWF]]></document></documents></author>