<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[so apparently 6 shots of whiskey, a bowl of Alfredo and a pint of ice cream don’t mix very well. I don’t care if I… https://t.co/mOf6pvEXbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo quería, pero no puedo! #venezuelalibre @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/aNXeAR5iJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cannonmw Yrs from now, will not be a big deal, you’re right...But he will always remember it. ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @amyewalter @TheTakeaway remembering time you interviewed me 8 years ago in NYC when I was running for #POTUS f… https://t.co/LQDCMz1v3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kysleee Grabe chills. Iba sha pag Live ano? Nakakapanginig ng laman haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner I keep saying this and also say that Trump and his campaign are watching our own divide and will use t… https://t.co/NIX2KQyTLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying to London tonight and I’ll make it time for the weigh-in. Big fight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally saw the #tardigrade scene in the latest Ant-Man movie on the way to California today. Pretty great microbia… https://t.co/khE3uej4HN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Addition of docetaxel to ADT does not improve PFS in biochemical recurrence after local therapy for prostate cancer… https://t.co/RlnnkFDyvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayes_melisa @Flipgrid @annkozma723 @Savvy_Educator @HollyClarkEdu @trev_mackenzie Such a great story! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece on texting for legal pros. For the 78% already doing so, check out @timeminerapp and bill for your text… https://t.co/aldrX7vHvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[To put this into perspective, this is almost as heavy as a Yamaha Grizzly 700 ATV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneViolence @GentlemanJackG I loved him as Hershel on The Walking Dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleswindell playing @SeaWorld . @diamondresorts  guests and owners are in attendance for an #EventOfLifetime #Stay https://t.co/x0fPJT0ZnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wonderful. I might not own the action figures but I know stuff about Star Wars. Come on nerds. You can't ev… https://t.co/qHOBbWU2hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quinnipiac seniors accept the MAAC Championship trophy. #MAACHoops19 https://t.co/0ekQEsGLI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl is the most beautiful and amazing person I have ever met. She’s the only one that can calm me down. I lov… https://t.co/bW78nsg3xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are literally my last three brain cells whenever I do something I was suppose to do. https://t.co/IP7ahGbmSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XP6CzhfDhL   #DrumSolo #ChucksDrumSolo #ChuckSmotherson #StLouisMusic #Blessed #TiredButHired… https://t.co/3Kb6ALT1Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aperly U need to start looking on the light not the dark and see the half full cup think positive will be good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her Lungs out and Intestins up Towards her Throat Which will Eventually Kill Her, So she has to have Surgery but th… https://t.co/XstmlJ4zOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachami @nealobermeyer Spider verse should have been nominated in every category.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @MTA,  Is it too much trouble for your employees to clean the train cars of the F train before it departs from… https://t.co/Am24YDQD9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Great perserverence,control and excellent training. Good shoot. Good cop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanO711 @harpersbazaarus Far and away predominantly black people were lynched. A few white but not many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too all of the girls taking 90% naked pictures on insta and thinking they are models. Same with Twit. Put you’re cl… https://t.co/O3D0LEiUxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KirkPWatson “We all believe in the power of decision making at the local level” #TXlege #TxEd @tasanet @tasbnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Winston uses his off arm any more, Zavier Simpson will be arrested for indecent exposure]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you want to #help people that don't want 2B helped you have 2B careful not to #fall into a #fleshy response mo… https://t.co/wbZ2AvdyiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKaergard @HOIABC_News @ParkRidgeIL @StCharlesIL @PeoriaIllinois @ChrisKaergard ZERO ppl “choose” to live in… https://t.co/pqWt7lX6yT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Says Upgrade To Windows 10 After Critical Flaws Found In Chrome And Windows 7 via @forbes https://t.co/DiBH4FYhX5 @1E_Global]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislongview @RobinJoyous Actually, the include white...all the damn time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest long term threat China poses to US industry :. In 15 years Chinas grid is powered by robust reliable th… https://t.co/eZNz7NxNzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCTheNational @eamorris_ @RosieBarton @ChantalHbert @acoyne @ShachiKurl The “why wouldn’t she resign if she was f… https://t.co/IIhLHDMVgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few of my amazing family members ❤️😍 @ Wood River, Illinois https://t.co/sBYwoTvLO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyaMoore bi·o·log·i·cal·lyDictionary result for biologically /ˌbīəˈläjiklē/Submit  Learn to pronounce adverb 1.… https://t.co/7YT1AWp84N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithLeo888 @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Nice touch....very nice touch. 😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t feel like I’m asking for people who are perfect, but just … I dunno, I guess I don’t want to have to deal /… https://t.co/Hz2prUoXaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetTxBlessed @HLAurora63 I agree but liberals get butt hurt if you are polite]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Ha9H36u0MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my @Bengals starter jacket from @HOMAGE today so I’m officially all packed &amp; ready for London this fall.… https://t.co/X8gwH3VQcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[9/ investment mistakes and you might find now that it is easy to see what went wrong. That’s because your emotions… https://t.co/ybgkJLppYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[MON WFR PICKS R1-3 1 2 R2-8 4 5 R3-1 8 4 R4-2 5 7 R5-4 3 7 R6-4 3 6 1 7 R7-4 1 6 R8-3 6 1 R9-6 5 1 R10-4 1 2 3 9… https://t.co/RaLoxoMCsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariaahhxo_ girl bikinis came in at target literally a week after new years, come on in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of 30 day fast.  Down 15 pounds #keto #ketolife #ketoweightloss #ketocommunity #ketojourney #ketodietlife… https://t.co/L5ZR6k0Hb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we will get two solid years and a so so third. I just pray for no injuries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NokiaMobile @nokia yeah so I've been supporting the phone but the charger magical stops working and for no reason… https://t.co/A6aQxbk51w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kersplunk #sunrise #surfing #ogunquit #maine @SarahLongWMTW @JoeGlauberWMTW @KJordan_WMTW @StormHour https://t.co/gimsKYVdVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelhsweet I get chills just thinking about it!  Whatever it is, it surely would rock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New life goal: be able to casually drop ken burns in my panel comments and refer to him on a first name basis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our little angel fell asleep between us during a movie. Sigh .... I need a minute .... ❤️… https://t.co/CHsi7KNZCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski What’s your opinion about Washington state governor, Jay Inslee?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Humanities201 @IlhanMN Wv is full of combat veterans they decide for themselves were they stand on issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_Andrade50 One day he is gonna see your tweet Ben and America will say thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you brother! Happy birthday.. I’m comin to celebrate 🎉🎊🍺 https://t.co/CAogoyQI8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @zacknichols5 and his @BaseballNav team. Wrapping up play today in the Franklin tournament]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlckTem Jarrett Jack. Smart player. Got the most out of his career from knowing things. Decent assist guy (retweets)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a Dave Bartoo like story about college hoops from my friend Andy @Stadium @JohnBishop71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelitapermata_a @ProudofbeinARMY @BTS_twt @lookatmin1013 Very nice 💜 #TwitterBestFandom⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠ #TeamBTS #SoompiAwards⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠@BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBrookhiser That made him greater than Napoleon.  Cicero is more respected and beloved today than Caesar or Mark Anthony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icehockeyjunkie @RobCameron642 @MikeMcMahonCHN dude, wasn’t gonna go there haha but man oh man did it need to be said. Thank you lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonBeattie @JenniferLoveUBC @Lummis83 @Chemjobber It's that subtle difference between something being paramagne… https://t.co/T3vJNv3QoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHL #DFS My @FlaPanthers stack was clutch putting up over 50 points and saving an otherwise bad night #WIN https://t.co/ISvFI2nLJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeGoldbergABC7 Wet icy snow in Deer Park NY, streets are covered with icy slush, black ice all over!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gonzalez___Benz @adrianxcollazo @SydLkAustralia Syd said no shoes in the sauna, gotta follow the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackannctable #TTMN Who are your favorite wrestlers to follow on social media? I dig what @itsLioRush does on his… https://t.co/ng9HiNsbLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmineSabia THEY SHOULD BE MAD AT PEOPLES TOO, WHO'S MAKING FALSE POLICE REPORTS THEY SEE A BLACK PERSON WALKING… https://t.co/o8e7mIgAop]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 12:15 am. Im@sitting in my living room, watching the Las Vegas Golden Knights, and listening to this gem of an… https://t.co/oZ2puXsPPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett could face up to three years in prison for allegedly falsely reporting a hate crime |  https://t.co/QWbEbRTOAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me la paso tomando chingos de fotos que ya ni se donde publicarlas   #pinche #chilango #disperso https://t.co/RZ66olcAvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Humanities201 @DonaldJTrumpJr So, are you snowflakes literally going to respond to every tweet by anyone with the… https://t.co/MpDxE2LjpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @kimcherrysings owned that rap, I had to push my button! #VoicePremiere @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scalzi That's your book? I thought it was the desk the books were sitting on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camphenn @SteveEmily2016 Oh my god that is so fucking cool. I’ve loved them all. Golden Exits was one of my favori… https://t.co/ktrV1nGgbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby-lights. Yes please, messy or straight, they look great !  Styled by myhairleidy  . . . #babylights #highlights… https://t.co/wDd0TdYjhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raul Flores black gown | worn by one of my favorite models misslaqueta 🙌🏽✨⭐  #blackgirlmagic #model #fashion… https://t.co/ffhzT0Ktve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAlliLux @AdahliaCole I understand your POV, but I sure do love my Loubies!!!! 👠😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal This is stupid, I had the best time not doing any school work being outside with my friends learning the… https://t.co/oht034fV7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fisty @MaurMaur82 @Phil_Noir_ @billyrunaway @hollye_h @1anomaly @IanFHood @Djloriee @Redhotknickers @vixticator… https://t.co/Hz45trPiXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[An #eclipse Monday night? If you’re in #Chile or #Argentina, Sirius — the brightest star in the sky — will disappea… https://t.co/HGBDVr7lgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alyssa Alhadeff, 14; Scott Beigel, 35; Martin Duque Anguiano, 14; Nicholas Dworet, 17; Aaron Feis, 37; Jaime Gutten… https://t.co/Qju2XPSWds]]></document><document><![CDATA[A broad can marry a man for his money, but a pert near 80 year old man can’t pay for a rub n’ tug. Shameful… https://t.co/5e7NcdoaOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cali Wavy Baby ☀️🌊 . . . #Sunset #SF #SanFrancisco #BayArea #California #WestCoast #Views #Waves @ Golden Gate Over… https://t.co/59K1NorLDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SR 436 &amp; Hunt Club Blvd in Apopka, FL https://t.co/FQkFtSFPH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daisy49103 @realDonaldTrump @GOPLeader @senatemajldr 😢🙏🏾🇺🇸😢 https://t.co/mbWsi0lKt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fight4Goodness @kennwhite @TheRickWilson That was covered in one of Robert Heinlein's early books, I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like, this time has been absolutely crucial for bonding with baby, as well as settling into a semblance of a routin… https://t.co/7DdbqMoVYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1pissedPolack I didn’t personally know your mom, but, we followed each other.. I enjoyed her political view point… https://t.co/IXrIYSf8Wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moileomota55 NO, la soberanía se pierde cuando un ejército extranjero bajo su propia bandera toma tus ciudades, ll… https://t.co/EHyoRk7kYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[💔silence-The Holy Martyrs of Japan pray for us. ❤️⛪️🇻🇦😇❤️🕯️ https://t.co/GqtAmcPjtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best mentor a girl can ask for, Thank you tanya_king_official for all you do #ottawadrag #dragqueen #lgbtq🌈… https://t.co/I6rvdfFUhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinStodd Same. Just don’t think he would have the budget for all of it. It would be good points to get him a ter… https://t.co/Y3PsNucQZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAILMANTAZ @PlymouthDawg He’s not in Florida anymore. Now he’s just being a https://t.co/8pTqNwYafr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyokaMuse also interesting to include dyslexics in the game.  nobody wins. https://t.co/dA5LLSSAPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like sorry none of the other managers ever wanna give me a chance to do other shit than work the drive thru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gametime.  Time to ball. @RutgersMBB   #GardenStatement #GoRU https://t.co/J1kKG1qkcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachingChanges Hinson is as good as gone, SIU fans were done with him well before this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[obsolet Technology missing change to the new Technology as Following https://t.co/pa8fTOj7Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HSHistTeach @RepBrodeur @jmpap1 @jillrt @GSteachermom @PapillonAnne So I had heard about it already and it was mad… https://t.co/6eEw976rga]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PjbYW90BRB How Quickbooks Payroll Support Phone Number +1-855-2367529 helps you In Downloading The w-2… https://t.co/FTIOpGxlS4]]></document></documents></author>