<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey Jeff, how about you cheat on the weekend and come do a little work. 😉  Nice try, @WeWork.  #SundayMotivation https://t.co/OHO8sS7Yy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/dWBZDPykke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC From past remarks, I think Rep. Steve King should be lumped in with Rep. Omar..........]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is coming down in Colorado. #Rapids96 #PORvCOL @ProSoccerUSAcom https://t.co/8pNsoancZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vigs072 @andreduvoisin @annarosenberg00 And in this moment, KXML (Kevin XML) was born]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 19 - Today In Politics:     In N.C., investigators find absentee ballot ‘scheme’ in House race;… https://t.co/bDTEVioSrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like YOU are the one rushing to judgement. The FACTS have not ALL come out about Smollet nor have they all c… https://t.co/lyscqpgMKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshabbottband @aricanastas This landed on my roof https://t.co/vI8oKxJu74]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to be more careful.  I jokingly told 3 told to go step on his 7 yr old brothers head.  Without hesitation he… https://t.co/M9V7Kos9S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chynableu I did, thank you. When you have children life takes on a totally different meaning!  I love my life. I’l… https://t.co/BNN8mDDqlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drink a little drink, why yes, we will! #EricChurch #SprintCenter https://t.co/B4aDNSMHK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The three most important things to have are faith, hope and love. But the greatest of them is lo… https://t.co/qGOzfURJKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[1916: A U.S. Department of Agriculture report finds hemp is capable of producing four times more pulp for paper man… https://t.co/7GrWVDMz0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My youngest son slept all through the night during the weekend. Week nights he wakes up right around the time I get home from work. 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigleaguechew @BleacherReport @Lakers @joshhart If they don’t slide in to the DM I’ll take some gum off your hands… https://t.co/dpvB353bG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrettMcPher10 @VanGorder35 No no, you don’t get to play that card. Harbough became a douche when he pushed Jim S… https://t.co/40LIybw5de]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heliaebrahimi REVERERI&gt;FIDES&gt; DEVOIRS&gt;unbreakable allegiance of LOIALTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Westbrook Why Not BHM tallas 9.5-10-11 precio por Whatsapp +584127395384 en Alta en Bergenfield, New Jersey https://t.co/rlBBdtHXUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a Simmonds jersey and t-shirt too... Way to ruin my whole day. The only thing that can salvage this day is i… https://t.co/Usb4QABi1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[First, @RuPaul, you sold a false history about Judy Garland’s death motivating the Stonewall Riots. Now, you tweet… https://t.co/4ZkZh18alC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cafecnn Ninguno. Siempre buscarán por donde entrar. Las necesidades llevan a la gente a lograr llegar a lugares do… https://t.co/zPl48B5mXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4) #GRIT is not a sometime but an #AllTimeThing model it, teach it, practice it And make sure everyone feels a par… https://t.co/H1eGGzRVg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Run_ You’ve changed. Im glad you finally caught up to my style.  You used to be all about possession.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wet light sour.   Not expecting - Drinking a Sippin' Pretty by @OdellBrewing at @WildwoodBar  — https://t.co/VRQxcqOcIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evoespueblo @Larissacostas Tranquilo que luego vamos por ti! #dictador #Articulo187YA #MaduroAsesino]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been hearing good things about #TheUmbrellaAcademy and I just saw a preview. I think I'm gonna binge on my nex… https://t.co/c23UaDr0us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady, three white leopards sat under a juniper-tree In the cool of the day, having fed to satiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[KILLER WORKOUT TODAY shout out to the team at @9round_maple  today #workout #hiit #intensity #Kickboxing #9round… https://t.co/1vTbFhLyUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently hiding in the bathroom at work until my coworker that I hate leaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaBrenner212 Wish I could be there @LisaBrenner212 &amp; @Dean_Devlin! 🇬🇧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sir Mix A Lot surveys the jar thinking of Carlin 7 Word Mobiles and the Pink Pony Express. Yes his paint had that M… https://t.co/NtpQmDQKme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLovesTaft Check VA and then cross check with service records, VFW and Legion honor guards can help too]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AGTG blessed to say I’ve received an offer from the University Of North Texas #MeanGreen💚🖤 https://t.co/zZyhjOVmII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stadium// #everydaybronx @ 161 St - Yankee Stadium https://t.co/cUm4iGvClY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean that’s what the book is all about and she makes that point about approaching dogs, esp strangers, not so hea… https://t.co/ayyUf85PFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Homeless man looking for a fresh start. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/UohUbwxVK1 via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KB805 Being a NY transplant for the last 11 years I totally agree. Having worked in rural area for 10 years at a F… https://t.co/2MUeczQAHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATW pre season top 10 SATX Member!  Congrats @JayJonez17 !!! Like i said “Y’all validate my list with your play! No… https://t.co/52YWd7iFTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Sharon Except it is WAAAAAY BETTER.  Besides there really 1 song that is the song of the Tournament which UCF… https://t.co/41mgUm9bEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tarheel_Sports_ Is it? Cause you can wear a mask and play with a bad nose... Zion likely to miss more games beyond… https://t.co/MU5chHMg1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[180 N. Morgan  @4cbars @SPACEARCHPLAN @ChicagoDOB @sterlingbay @FederalesChi #permit #architects #construction… https://t.co/4GTVgnAcb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is barely true; you could build in trenches, by extant highways, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of @kylacarlson2020 for a1st and 2nd place finish in the 400 and high jump at @cunebulldogs 3-meet series. https://t.co/KkNaDIqD8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year I ended up second place , this year I’m coming for it all!!! ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawrence97431 @RealSaavedra So kids without high school education can vote...OMG just kill me now &amp; get it over with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont want anyone in Cali to tell me "wE pAy FoR tHe WeAtHeR" anymore. It's 33 degrees and had to use an old credi… https://t.co/uChk43chZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillinSac Jill, I really don't care! It's Stanton all over again, we don't need him! Go Giants!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE having @AnneMarieWTHR guest anchor #WTHRSunrise . She laughs at ALL my material!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why a US city is searching for mass graves https://t.co/7wAv8cfaWm via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying some more macro shots with some irises. Used some focus stacking, which leads me to think I need to make a f… https://t.co/PLBohroZt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameByteHQ Yuuuup... #GameByte #gimmedatpack #ApexLegends https://t.co/zl1nNtN4fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyndy_jacobsen I’m not sure what that means? Communication has changed? Form of communication? To who ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhweingarten Yeah get rid of those pesky jobs. I don’t need no stinkin job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bicycletourusa8 @WGME Has NOTHING to do with politics. I’m trying to access data/statistics that are in the public… https://t.co/jsrVPMm9ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Great flight, but my bag apparently didn’t get to make it with me.  Hard to golf with out golf clubs. An… https://t.co/uwS8Pa6y39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcpr If anyone of these bibles either starts spewing blood or spontaneously burst into flames, I promise I wil… https://t.co/VpxtAd5YEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMovieMan Nope. More Superbad, a raunchy setting to a real emotional story about friendship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a picture of Andrew Jackson glued to the wall of my Hampton Inn hotel room @HiltonHotels. There should be a… https://t.co/xxkBXNHbbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[How should we measure success or failure at the Trump-Kim Summt in Hanoi? Some thoughts.  https://t.co/Fzmbm1s0id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @USPS They get mail 2-3 X per week! Luxury! Mail is spotty or irregular at best where I live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTrisano Si iba al gol, el taquitos la pone mucho más al centro del arco...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas be out here trying to stunt on they own partners 🗣 who raised y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being mad at losing an hour of sleep when the reward is the end of depressing ass shitty dark cold days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boston25 @ChristineMNews Christine, please inbox me her information. I will pay her ticket on Monday. In a Communi… https://t.co/JpYxzYMZqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter need to add a you sure you want to see this  button on videos cause the shit on my tl is fucking disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffGroves can I fight with you my brother in blue anytime? Your my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet It's the educational system they don't teach world geography. I've asked recent graduates of high s… https://t.co/ivXXPwljrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra I love a good cup of coffee. What was that address again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @USATODAY Whacked  never got his fat hands dirty in his life! Slug Get a real job jowls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Colin. Your better than this. Blood-clot is no joke. https://t.co/cAwteweigQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Carolina -4  Clemson 1-8 this season against top 40 kenpom opponents. They just haven’t shown much. They’ll b… https://t.co/uxRzP8Rff7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Unless you were around during the revolution, this is a complete lie. You’re an idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We came, they laughed, and we conquered! Great time with great people!!! Thank you Evan, Bourbon, Patti, Alex, Bris… https://t.co/HV5TOBTtfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMidLifeCrysis @Kmega4 That is exactly what I thought too. The combos really shine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sweet_LaLaLand Lmao no but I feel as if I need to be. How I’m sposed to survive like this? https://t.co/TR9JCtJEfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandryLocker I got a few years on ya young fella .. gotta live it .. now let me get one em Hustle tops in an XL be… https://t.co/kJ0nR2cur7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up with my newest fave @BravoTV show #backyardenvy. I desperately need the Manscapers at our place.… https://t.co/OQE0hgQCzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOUCH DOWN at Blue Grass Airport after report of landing gear failure. @LEX18News @united https://t.co/TzcFEm8LUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichiganOnBTN That kid is showing potential. I suspect he will be gaining much weight and muscle in the off season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlrantAl @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Would you like smooth talking Obama to look into the camera and .... assure… https://t.co/ho9EZUSxf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s okay @ladygaga I’m sorry for the transition but that just means there’s more time for us to meet one another :… https://t.co/frTqcbrNmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can find meaning and appreciation of life through first-hand experiences and/or with the desire to want to know… https://t.co/b7K37UtjmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMcKew With Stone anything’s possible. But more likely the judge will slap Roger around a little and maybe put… https://t.co/UcToRUl1yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volkswagen’s dune buggy is an electric shot of nostalgia https://t.co/jp0rq4fDvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonafexFA @Enro_the_Mutt But... you’re doing it. We’ve never talked before and you’re projecting all sorts of crud onto me. So... okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#redtailedhawk doing a #flyby as I was trying to #photograph a #sly #redfox #hawk #raptor #elite_raptors… https://t.co/C8BgJ86ZyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary is spot on about @realDonaldTrump back in 2016! #WakeUpAmerica #truthmatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[So heres a thought. Lets pretend that trump gets his way, get 25 billion for the wall, who gets the contracts to bu… https://t.co/zysXaXm7ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tested @MLS superstars on their knowledge of Montreal. One of the question was simple :  - What is the name of th… https://t.co/y3pBTsof63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_drew_jacobs_ @NorwayneStuSec You did a heckuva job! Someone has big shoes to fill!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far the coolest way to do the Sign of Peace during Mass. I’m open for other suggestions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stone09110 @Iyrytish @mitchellvii It isn’t satire, or it isn’t hard to tell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabyRhode @TomBilyeu There's absolutely nothing wrong with being content with where you are in life. But I believe… https://t.co/IbQQPXm1Uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdrose0718 @GaylynnJohnson @nzgrant17 @LoveBling6 @Josiegirlz5 @jkkc40 @WhitestoneArt @RhinoluvsUSA @fglaus… https://t.co/6jBRyLpsp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC : Let’s talk some more about your new apartment or condo. We hear it’s very high end, with a pool and a indoor… https://t.co/Z3xxCcGsMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think this snow will stick. #vegassnow @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/jzxuCnWHXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBigAndSexy70 besides maybe “pigs rank #4 in intelligence” because what on earth does that mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendysShakes @CadizOranges @RobDuboice @ChazOdalaigh @NBCNews I salute you Wendys.  I decided not to engage becaus… https://t.co/jK8Nva1cTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake fox is not a news channel. It is simply state run TV.  There is very little if any objectivity. The only repor… https://t.co/Ri3KgWjSfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to live in a world where LeAnn Rimes and Busta Rhymes are somehow related.]]></document></documents></author>