<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The bathroom at Julian’s 😊😎 #julians #juliansprovidence #juliansprovidenceri #coolbathrooms #providence… https://t.co/ctKw5iq6af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SentientApe @corvidresearch Yes.  I say Hello and they say Hello back.  No kidding! In English. I have several rec… https://t.co/tWHmUstXiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my autistic students can explain or understand anything in the context of the “Shimmer and Shine” tv show.… https://t.co/eRsnJXFSuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard @brielarson wanted to know what women of color thought about #CaptainMarvel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellamooreauthor I write video games. What I’m working on now, professionally, is under NDA but I promise it’s cool… https://t.co/hb4dkMK1Sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGrizzlyRose @Morgan_Evans One day I will make it to Denver and The Grizzly Rose!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caiscalifornia @calireading more literacy workshops coming to Southern California next month! Registration details… https://t.co/noOEO36B8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Pokémon Day!   Risa | Pokémon: The Power of Us  #pokemon #PokemonDay #pokemonday2019 #cosplay #anime… https://t.co/8wdKQwvygH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayceconatser11 @elizabeth_goble yep, same 🤣🤣 “I’m so sorry baby. My sweet innocent smelling baby” 🤣💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just need to give a shout out to my Bay Area family: the women of the Peet’s Coffee at the SFO Southwest terminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xzyliac Come over, you can borrow mine if you let me work for free as a soundtrack consultant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d pay it ... if I had it!  And, because the money went to a good cause.  One day I will meet @DollyParton and I w… https://t.co/Lklq0lwT59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realKWill @m_millsey I think they/we say “no problem” because it’s their/our job.... so it’s really not a problem… https://t.co/u9M7nuuwO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I rate it 8/10 Volkswagen Beetles—true crime doesn’t scare me as much, so watching with 🌿 helped with immersion✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[This game is gonna be 🔥 Spurs VS Wizards aaaaand @LiggieSmallz is starting 👏👏🏀 #HomeCourtAdvantage]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite things to do with Kylie has always been arts and crafts. It's our special time These days we're… https://t.co/fkIcUEUSYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy cause as many people hit me up say I’m handsome etc etc that shit don’t move me...niggas want to see my… https://t.co/E9JmeRmUCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my to-go wine and my scooter. Let’s ring in 29! #birthday 🎈 https://t.co/rSsweD2Yxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelBugsWorld @LiveaMemory @OrganicRoadMap @Adventuringgal @LeonandTash1 @suzytheexplorer @RoadtripC… https://t.co/db0FNYx0ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beccaleann_21 we wil🤩 we need to all come back up here before JMBLYA!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving again but this time I am moving home. Look out country here we come. https://t.co/8Sc1yIMdNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I must thank two people, God and President Trump 🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸🙏🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[He really wants that 1up 🎮😂#futuregamer #proudDad #love @ North Richland Hills, Texas https://t.co/O1jmdpyfjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank about this everyone🤔would you allow your children to go kids they don’t like names?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What getting sleep in two hour increments looks like #newmomlife https://t.co/oAED1B8cqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to course direct a Completely full DMEP disaster preparedness course @UMCSN in @LasVegasCity @ACSTrauma… https://t.co/GBjcS1Wg2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, thank you all for the kind words and support on yesterday’s post. I’m taking it day by day and am hop… https://t.co/cJXtGtmjBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treacherous music Its rhyme louder than its rhythm Go ahead fling ur hair tease him His hands craving ur sultry hip… https://t.co/XU9ZOqzYzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you: #editorialmodel #beautymodel #commercialmodel #printmodel #commercialprint #commercialphotographer… https://t.co/xWJIMfGdJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this humorous. #humor #lol #smile #clever https://t.co/4XAOYVoEco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein They aired the summit??? LOL Cohen was more interesting!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I woke up this morning, I was not feeling this day! I was grumpy, tired, non-motivated and just plain meh! I w… https://t.co/PGkp4TkRSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stormy Winter - Click image to find more Illustrations &amp; Posters Pinterest pins https://t.co/kKpDnHAGbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up gusty winds up to 40 MPH and snow flurries possible. Be safe out there! #8NN https://t.co/GDWgKYzCC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something, something about this place  Something, something about lonely nights  And my lipstick on your face  Some… https://t.co/Eg9EBr46eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lets see how crooked you really are and stupid since you refused to release your grades or SAT scores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeenaGaga Make it a point to do some serious self care. Taking care of yourself physically and pampering your exte… https://t.co/z1MGaaawDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2kidsnosleep 😂 It’s not like you’re an original KS driver, so it’s okay. Right?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamflongdichoso @VhieCaval Except Diana Ross’ coming out message is positive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallySeafarer I’ll keep a watch for now. I can’t spend a ton for something that they won’t do anything for. It’s d… https://t.co/VS2GuwiC6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM SORRY FOR NOT TELLING YOU I LOVED YOU WHEN I KNEW I DID. I FUCKING LOVE THEM. MY HEART UGH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at the University of Pgh celebrating my Writer’s Society students who won silver and gold keys in the Scholast… https://t.co/JcJMrwoqwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MrEarpLA @Telemundo @NBCNews @FoxNews @TheDemocrats Seriously!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you think I told you these things because I want you to pity me, but no. I tell you these things because it’… https://t.co/zx9x1NtXB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I look out the window out my living room window and say  “those fucking assholes” (because the neighbors have pa… https://t.co/j0lwi8dE2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[My intensely autistic kids (in regular school, in regular class, w support) absolutely love their inclusive school… https://t.co/Jn09ILhKM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh you know. Sporting some Princess Leia buns and some Chucks... 😜 https://t.co/cmdMIju4E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 1935 Ocean Avenue #OrtleyBeach #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/kYxZovl1la]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your calls- apparently there are still sidewalks that need cleaning! DPW is working on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ill be in Jamaica so soon that’s what is getting me through this rough shift]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Kathy, the impact that you have on your students is amazing! What an awesome life learning experience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union Elementary student helps us  count  the ways ⁦@62UnionESD⁩  Principal Welsh changes lives! #LCOY… https://t.co/Uzjt5jtj8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stayed up late to finish "A Short History of the Girl Next Door" by @reckj. Worth it! This book will stay with me.… https://t.co/bReuDArWPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corigamm Oh no.. it makes me sad that that happened! 😢 Hoping this year is great for you! For me, I think it’s the… https://t.co/xD8TPG6J2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence 🙏🏻’s and hugs for you. So enjoy your tweets. Speedy recovery❣️Please keep us posted. You can do this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scuse me, isn’t a wall made of slats just a fence? And how is a fence going to keep Americans who want to commit ma… https://t.co/gHckJeyYgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[now i gotta go see a therapist. i found myself routing for a serial killer &amp; that’s not ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see it Mrs smarty pants always wanna act like somebody professor smh 🙄🤣🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you the 1 yard line? Because I'm intercepting some feelings. https://t.co/dc2ZtMB8Vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM A HORNY SHALLOW BASTARD FUCK ME OR FUCK ME IDC WHO HURT U JUST FUCK ME PS YUNG BOOGIE LAURENT]]></document><document><![CDATA[working two jobs, trying to find myself and do what makes me happy all while being completely stressed out super th… https://t.co/3bAj3fV9yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megtownsendd Why do you hate little sweet children, Megan?! https://t.co/gkIamqTXk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time someone tweets or retweets an ARC of a book I want to read I feel like I turn green like a jealous person in a cartoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain load of Army vehicles rolling through BG. Oh, the stories they could tell. https://t.co/14JNSmXzX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuleChicago @CajunBlueAZ1 @TezHug @TappsReady @HiSpeedWobbles @wyer222 @Eathbound420 @P4boxers @FixesItself… https://t.co/UQEJDb44ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackstopSports Yes, yes sir Gavin Taylor 2023 catcher take note #GavinTaylor2023  instagram @gtbaseball https://t.co/fd6A2zFeqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[they played the i”ll name the dogs video yesterday. and i think it was in reverse ( this the day before intd) a few… https://t.co/uVZBQxYJNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend  wedding in the north country #NewHampshire #whitemountains #winterwedding https://t.co/xZQh7LTxxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesslynnrose @ChaosControlTM is my new jam. I can easily set tasks to go off when it's the right time to do them.… https://t.co/epU9QJ3Wae]]></document><document><![CDATA[In history class I'm furiously studying for my midterm for foreign policy and look up to see a freshman in front of… https://t.co/mBICOjS2tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t look up to someone more than my mama. She is simply something special! #gotitfrommymama https://t.co/EvrakYUIoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ MY HEART BREAKS A LITTLE MORE EACH TIME I LOOK INTO HIS EYES 💔 Thi… https://t.co/FZhrpCSHtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self control is waiting to eat your popcorn and candy until the movie starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst thing about my car being at the shop is not being able to go to the gym whenever I want 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bury a friend song and album artwork screams the exorcist vibes yikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @ImmaBlueDot Please go away to some church camp with mother. Leave the rest of us alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieM97077160 @Zak_Bagans LMAO @BillyTolley is a hotass too so I’m good with that 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just got lost in a hospital for an hour, finally made it to my appointment tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TaikaWaititi and @AJemaineClement have done it again! Their FX series #WhatWeDoInTheShadows premieres March 27. R… https://t.co/lTQLpcg1oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby doggy. 9 month old beagle mix. Mom was rescued preggers and we were lucky enough to get her!!! My Molly Dol… https://t.co/JwVdsbeFIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazycatguy7 @Patrici06147519 @erin_richnow @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews He will always… https://t.co/sxSOYYqIZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bankruptcy not an option in our case . #elderabuse.  First Complaint  There wasn't a Court Order for bk to prevent]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just warning everyone the new ears I made are the cutest ears ever stay tuned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misslillynola @TonySkratchere You def could, but ive smothered at least 9 men with my left breast alone. So.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twins of my coworkers got kicked out of the bar. I might be more drunk. How did I get them to the uber?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterpanBANNING hi David, I want to get in touch Re FITC retrospective at Walker, plz call me or text me contact info 612.518.8007]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise run - great way to start the day in Chicago. Looking forward to meeting some new faces this afternoon at… https://t.co/JgXfR2EG0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMillerShow the intelligence committee wants to see ivanka and don jr and his fathers income taxes according to msnbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCITLFrAphorism Instead dedicate yourself to only tweets filled with compassion]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those driving by while I was climbing all over piles of roadside snow this evening ~ this was my purpose. I saw… https://t.co/iLkKhTDsSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re going to sell your products for all, then you should listen to people , even if they’re not people of col… https://t.co/gsabPurAAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@future_majority They are not yet use to the fact that they are no longer in power  Thank God for the blue wave]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone PLS tell me why there’s weber’s fraction, and then weber’s law,,, which was discovered by fechner... bu… https://t.co/HkMe5kZjW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day of the Week: Sunday  Deity: Sun god Surya Mantra 🌞 OM Bhur Bhuvah Svaha Tat Savitur Varenyam Bhargo Devasya Dhi… https://t.co/10WlO3NjuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @MartinPengelly @WeWork Still? What hellish speakers are planned today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #InternationalWomensDay in Pawtucket with some remarkable women! @SANDRISCANO @Karen_Alzate26… https://t.co/CvHjH0A6yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger I was in the room at a Johnson/Weld ticket event in #2016. CLEARLY Weld was the much better informed… https://t.co/lagNnkWRvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry about what might have been — focus on what can become 💕 https://t.co/djshBALhdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I call this look #GoingBad !! Definitely took my time with this look and I can’t wait for you all to see how I did… https://t.co/iZSdIryscl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Day05291970 @PaulCalafiore_ Lol😂😁meant to say no need to brag your better than that !]]></document></documents></author>