<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mieeeeeeentras siga viendo tu cara en la cara de la luna, mientras siga escuchando tu voz, entre las olas entre la espumaaaaa🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is everyone ready to see why Biden has got his ass handed to him every time he's tried to run for president?]]></document><document><![CDATA[An absolutely huge shift - with major implications for marketing.  Brands are hesitant to appear near unsafe conten… https://t.co/M8QHaXLe7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business AOC doing her best to turn out more Trump voters BEYOND the foamy-believe-anything-base.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is a POLLUTER and ethanol destroys older cars especially small motors Mowers, power washers and OLD VWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSocialistDr @ProgBlacksmith1 Yeah, I'm not denying it. She blocked me when I posted Sirota's O-Rourke article,… https://t.co/QxD1FxQPF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @nflcommish and @nflnetwork @CBSSports the @TheAAF is bad. The refs are the only refs worse than the ones bumbling actual football games]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta bem estabelecida Equipment Rental Empresa tem mais de 35 anos no negócio e com o reconhecimento do nome na áre… https://t.co/vYOwmiyklD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillianSed Every sketch has been either a commercial or a fake show. Do they do anything original anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandyWi11354642 You truly sad beefin with a celebrity when u ain’t even got a profile pic.😭🦹‍♂️🤷‍♂️🚫🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EveryoneCanCreate and be inspired by our worldwide friend Ted Geisel a.k.a. Dr. Seuss AND... @ColtonScience along… https://t.co/2H9LeGLgph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigSBPA @AOC "There is no evidence." You follow her around her whole life? Call back when you get a brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycSassenach @BlackbyrdGyrl1 @newenglandgrl @SamfromSpain @SaraMD15 @KarramKaren @CharliesWhiskey @Vanilla627… https://t.co/RP8gWvuHTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think LD owns the whole campus of Duquesne after that one, those are just the types]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Single Hop Series: Simcoe by @hermitagebrews @ Santa Clara County Fairgrounds — https://t.co/ckgbWqaLmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_martin_fx That would create so much uncertainty, scare off the business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi's family were dedicated Democrats, and her parents were strict Roman Catholics as well. For a son or daughte… https://t.co/XjMQPrPv5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bruisertheadventuredog was loving the #mrbuddyheater at Feb Camp.  To be honest so we’re the rest of us. It was co… https://t.co/fiJlJ269Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter McCaffrey’s @VastBiome pitch is like listening to a beat poetry jam: “the cryptic delays of response outcomes… https://t.co/Qdlnbvkm0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveFie21332722 @MarkWarner Dave, these are some pathetic people that can’t get over the fact that Trump beat them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cortez is a Traitor and a Shrill! If Socialism is so good why then for over 80 years have tried to migrate to our c… https://t.co/Glo5PGvTHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orteguistasALV @counterchekist Why are you so wedded to Sanders running as a Democrat as he only becomes a Dem whe… https://t.co/d2AyE4Wwzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samanthaglaserr The road when you have a broken wiper. https://t.co/6BQl7xrFSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnThune Sort of like the GOP Tax Cut that has cost 2 TRILLION DOLLARS and has NOT PAID FOR ITSELF! #GOPTaxScaml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support public education!  Donate $1 to my #DonorsChoose project!   Help me get a Microsoft Surface Go for my stude… https://t.co/KeTL9tZiE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sweet doggo saw me crying &amp; hopped right onto my bed &amp; is spooning with my leg :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s corny when people who drink say “ it’s five o clock somewhere 🤪🤪” and I think it’s corny when smokers use “420” .]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more thing that wild to me I’ll never ever hope that UNC wins but over the past few years the fan bases of Kent… https://t.co/rRmRA2jQ8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CondieKristine @AOC STUPIDITY IS AOC The MRA for each Rep is calculated including personnel, which is the same for… https://t.co/wAWfOj1Wua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to @SXSWEDU to talk about virtual reality. Making friends along the way https://t.co/qHm7nEWWuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undeniable truth. This is the reason I look at #Trump supporters and just ask...why? Like, seriously WHY do you thi… https://t.co/tpMkLnJb1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anticleric The comments below are 25 years in the repeat making.;) They repeat the 1996 vrml and the 2006-9 virtua… https://t.co/UH30DI86cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @talter, the lyft surge is at 500% in clt right now. I’ll pick you up for $0, don’t even need to bring hasan or kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and the president and a Republican-led Congress proceeded to do absolutely NOTHING to prevent the same thing fro… https://t.co/xtgDwiludn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraScyrkels @sdeebocane @ilovemusic_76 @TomKochABC13 @TJParkerABC13 @abc13houston @ChelseyABC13 @ABC13Elita… https://t.co/DWzMTq9zu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ma527681 @dobermanmamma @BunkerGear_Gal @PokerDame i'm cute cuddly and adorable. Just ask .... me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wubanga10154 @HuffPost That's very mature of you.  Really enhances your credibility!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls with a human trafficking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCBerkeley Well, the Journal where I am Editor-in-Chief, Environmental Research Letters @IOPenvironment is open ac… https://t.co/KPWCjyWbYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbarawilk52 @NickKyrgios You didn’t see Stan SCREAM C’mon louder than Lleyton when serving at love 15 and NK mis… https://t.co/2EPJ97Aabd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady Tell me which conservatives exactly..  because non of us give a damn tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weareider brooklynsteel 2/20/19 Really enjoyed their Outkast cover!! #ider #outkast #roses #latergram @ Brooklyn S… https://t.co/Hw3tMEaaHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sold in #georgetown - 1626 29th St NW - #realestatemarket #update - #sothebysrealty #ttrsir #washingtondc . . . .… https://t.co/Iig7WJDCtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[perfect day to work 🙏and at night to toyota center rockets vs atlanta hawks😜 en William P. Hobby Airport https://t.co/1nVLJlMwPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseOyuma @FatherBlazek @sistervpaul_ @EdIsBackKAG2020 @1207go @PrayHard972 @Matthew82060400 @Lampasvlad… https://t.co/N1q26RUMx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday!  From today's reading:  Jeremiah 17:7-8 https://t.co/fssjdlcDqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bikemamadelphia Almost every intersection with Lancaster Ave is like this. Or with any of our diagonal streets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frfrankpavone @realDonaldTrump Oi. What a living piece of shit you are. Are you degreed in Theology? Because clear… https://t.co/nwSfL3SzL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone: posts adorable pics of their pets for #LoveYourPetDay   Me: https://t.co/LRaZXStxrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 dozen Paczkis and 20 gallons of Potato 🥔 vodka went into this years batch. https://t.co/ZZmhxxl77m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill It's pretty straight forward. Characters do evolve and grow. It will be interesting to see who is left in the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking Alexandria, Papa Roach...and of course our main band Shinedown tonight. AA was pretty good. And P-Roach is n… https://t.co/gbvhO2PxlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this great deal I found on Beat the Dealer. https://t.co/dg4wwAkVsV https://t.co/UK9ylLqJXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Csvich @TlalocRivas would you say 19th century theatre was not as insulated?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLPrntSolutions @GOLD_TOGETHER @CreativeClay A happy #InternationalWomenDay to all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t slapped the bag in a minute and my energy is off because of it 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schreckphd Another republican and another old, white, male. He has a very slim chance of winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use this soap everytime when i give dog a bath for the past 2 years and my dog is perfectly normal]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @FairPlayEsports   I've been all day today  Got any highlights from the hearing that are must see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivia12456521 It's actually plastic surgery and vanity that have not been kind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanda @TEDchris @TEDTalks Ooo can it be me? I’m deserving and a POC and a woman to boot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pickuphoop @UnwrittenRul3s @bansky Again. You guarantee me Lonzo stays healthy I'm picking Zo.  But I think it's a question at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a new Hot Wheel for the boys! @ Stagecoach Park https://t.co/rt1Ni2pLYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump getting a pass on the right from stuff that would have made them go crazy with Obama is the essence of the ra… https://t.co/pVSnkpEiNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nuraidilah Lol! And people still use them today? The only stuff I know about those kinda things are “kangkang”. Hahaha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @RepAndyBiggsAZ @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Lou, I watched your show last night.  I appreciate your passion.… https://t.co/0R8OYbrzEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Migos @DjDurel @1YoungTakeoff @OffsetYRN @QuavoStuntin @QCTheLabelMusic #FatherOf4 Yo This album is dropping after… https://t.co/Pp1Z35MxAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Milwaukee Delicatessen Co. - @mdcokcmo in Kansas City, MO https://t.co/xZ7KeBTV0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not that I need to expect less of people, but that in some cases it's better not to expect anything, and just… https://t.co/8F37rikCcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Childs is (or at least was) a MAJOR funder of Massachusetts Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardDawkins Or world is well beyond Orwell’s vision in many regards, but as far as complete control of daily li… https://t.co/oSt0zKN0Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[@islesdave Just having Kuhnhackl on the second line is why #Isles need a top six forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes MOST Americans would have preferred that they invoked the 25th Amendment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader You are a liar! You wouldnt even interview Garland. BTW, you are a racist! Otherwise why would you campa… https://t.co/GIiq4VfF7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arsenal Fans are deluded ..they actually think their fairy dust club is gonna be oles Manchester United by 3-1 today lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get if they are really all that stupid or they just play stupid for a paycheck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum I've only watched a few clips... my question was.... was the audience inhaling the same laughing gas that he was...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a moment to follow and check out all of our incredible female Resident Artists who have been doing such challe… https://t.co/oTCU0rSQZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing...@ReaganBattalion   Makes me ❤️ @BernieSanders even more...will be making my 3rd donation since… https://t.co/vwgJZU6wAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes our society sucks.  Good thing we have #LoserTeachers to protect our kids on a daily basis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobVanDillen I do not see Linda's point his from Trumpland he deserves more does he not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting a tone of bipartisan cooperation: @lisamurkowski and @JoeManchinWV leading Senate Energy and Natural Resour… https://t.co/uLy5CdcSBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Large puddles of water or reflected in the beautiful late afternoon sky caused by freezing and thawing, on the edge… https://t.co/TZC1pcoe4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video from @HeelsUpdates gets me everytime. Nothing quite like Carolina Basketball. https://t.co/8QfD3yu4fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #Then take care of the ones who were Poisoned at Zcamp Lejeune from 1953 to 1987 ! Stop the lying… https://t.co/rqBQonmwp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some laughter. The Army Takes Their Pens Very Seriously - BuzzFeed Mobile...,so do teachers! #mirth #snicker… https://t.co/GEcsEIdZ8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needed some purp n black for this upcoming fall and had to run it #TheDawgInMe 🔥🔥🔥🥶🥶🧕🏽🐶🐶 https://t.co/8atBCbFYex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ackenpucky @heartofhannah1 @mgwhammy @jake_zuckerman https://t.co/B2TyTsc0mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my 6000 closest friends enjoying food and wine https://t.co/pZOmwd7J92]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don't.  What makes baseball the way it is because it's a fun family sport.... and y'all look foolish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chill they’re gonna start teaching kids to turn a simple concept into a whole project 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcohol is for the weak @ Country Music Hall of Fame and Museum https://t.co/2nzBcvDtW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[New workout swag! Trying to change a culture one small step at a time! When you’re committed to getting to the top… https://t.co/v9VxvE78mW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never let them know your next move. ― Biggie Smalls (died this day, March 9, 1997) #LegendsNeverDie]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's International Women's Day! Who are some of your favorite female writers? #douglasville #douglascounty… https://t.co/lFRhSPYsju]]></document><document><![CDATA[i still respect ugly god to this day for releasing a diss track on himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for comedy . . .  #humor #tee-hee #smirk #amusing https://t.co/Se4qH1PSt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leachfortexas @RepDennisBonnen @I35travel when will you pass an transportation bill that would allow @TxDOT to bui… https://t.co/x8jdFtOkM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walmart has a recycling program for plastic bags if your store doesn’t in Walmart would]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t see any of these designs being very useful yet, but one thing for certain is that the Samsung version… https://t.co/46kmxSkqWW]]></document></documents></author>