<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@zebulation @IlliniDan2 @JeffreyGoldberg I think you’re a Russian bot, since that’s the only explanation that makes… https://t.co/uQnMMQamda]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy asked me if I sign my own returns. It's honestly so surprising how many tax preparers there are who will t… https://t.co/GsBWCKgE6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Snow brings a special quality with it—the power to stop life as you know it dead in its tracks.”  Nancy Hatch Wood… https://t.co/F9GlKPQOlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a LOT of snow in Breckenridge last night. 🌨 @ Breckenridge, Colorado https://t.co/w3foYdYzkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: estoy mega feliz de que esté cayendo un tormenton en Tijuana porque mañana no tengo que ver a to… https://t.co/kB1G4tylgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not afraid of love  I’m t e r r i f i e d   [it never feels like how they advertise]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ListMccarthy Also, it’s interesting that you criticize the social sciences then present the results of an applied… https://t.co/RBUqpmlTmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeHillyer yeah i’m not a huge fan of big corporations but i think that there are certain cases where their effic… https://t.co/6z2ggdwWqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cats have British accents and I don’t know why #4amthoughts #catmom #grumpywicche]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undograce I think it’s probably because dirty hit is a smaller label. I could see him getting more attention in th… https://t.co/UJ2EZGR2SK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryPornima @Harry_Styles #iHeartAwards #BestFanArmy #Stylers @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con todo esto del tema del aborto te das cuenta de que la peor enemiga de una mujer es otra mujer y que tristemente… https://t.co/FI6VWXofMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are the boss of nothing,  Ms. Bug Eyes. We are your boss. Taxpayers voted you in and we are paying your pa… https://t.co/s8YcdFls42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xonecole @khloekardashian @jadapsmith @jordynwoods Well said 👏🏼🙌🏼 I’m team jordyn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretService  @USSupremeCourt @DCPoliceDept @ZellnerLaw So Pres Trump is back home and he decides to touch my ass… https://t.co/T9awKAveZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demario__davis I’m gonna miss seeing you dominate on the field in New Orleans]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just WON a vacation!!! I get a 4 day/3 night stay at a Beaches resort all-expenses paid. Did I mention it's for T… https://t.co/1xhWdDIsyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sings* LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT MY BEST FRIEND  #NationalLoveYourPetDay https://t.co/amMxijUNAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I am officially latent tuberculosis free (we hope). 9 months of antibiotics, down the hatch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what hinders us from cooperating and collaborating with each other? It is due to human weakness, namely, fear, i… https://t.co/M9repJkbDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's totally SICKENING, THE CONTINUING BIAS STATION/WSB IN ATLANTA GA!EVERY SINGLE CHANCE TGEY GET TO SHOW  IT(TGEY… https://t.co/0Loahq3MRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week, I forgot to post these #Bear #Peanut #Sunny #NewOutfit @ Arlington, Washington https://t.co/fuUoNAhOI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we hear the wailing  of a tender hearted mother whose son was waiting to plunge into life but  has now been sile… https://t.co/GPhDgoqSRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Rezz ever goes on a music hiatus and then comes back she should name her tour The Rezzurrection]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I ❤ @ColumbiaColg! 🐾 #WeAreCC #ValentinesDay #Party https://t.co/NYNWqkxIxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This international concert will bring global attention to this unacceptable and preventable crisis and raise funds… https://t.co/MTni0zBQIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@Qualtrics completes us [@SAP]” - @BillRMcDermott  #QualtricsX4 https://t.co/O1in9xFRnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor, Senator Stewart announce Solar Tax Credit legislation https://t.co/W3o6hlJRAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielWBIR @wbir The best part about this is now when @NancySechtin visits you, I'm within driving distance 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally can’t sleep because i’m in so much pain from everything she’s done to me. i know i never talk about my… https://t.co/rPPeYPqiOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun weekend with the best people. Now back to work. #train73 @ Union Station https://t.co/sZmUzdhPbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ i like when he’s late for school and has to skate really fast “ toe describing back to the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S FINALLY HERE!!! PATRICE JÉGOU and TAKE 6 @Take6official “WRAP YOUR TROUBLES IN DREAMS” 🧡Watch on YouTube👉… https://t.co/5VR0m5cDR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1011WNOE @MarySSteele thanks for playing ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ What Makes You Country by @LukeBryanOnline for me ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️… https://t.co/khn5nuqlaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work is chill af today and I’m so fucking grateful. Like being an hour late and no one noticed type of chill... 🙌🏾😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital  Scotty Baldwin never disappoints! @kinshriner I had to create this gif. I'm confident it will com… https://t.co/qHmlYqzFhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary-do tell us about separation of a child from their family... Where are all the children Hillary? If Al Gore… https://t.co/3GNkT5OlDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started loving shotgun houses nearly 20 years ago, while in grad school studying mixed-income neighborhoods in do… https://t.co/DT8prYX6Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing a little customer experience comparison this week with my hotels. So far, marriottbonvoy Elite at fairfield_i… https://t.co/2QfvoqBgOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!!! ☀️ Thank you for the sweet message! Be careful out there and stay dry today 🌧]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Willow Grove Park Mall in Willow Grove, PA https://t.co/MAkvncMrvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all honesty I have a real bad headache but I'm super stoked rn. Like just take me away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically, and something @realDonaldTrump never understands, what sets #US apart is willingness to criticize itsel… https://t.co/59RJjlML6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is way easier to get caught up in mindless scrolling than intentional connnecting on the internet and that bums me out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunPolls33 @ForeverBSer @NBCTheVoice @blakeshelton @kelly_clarkson @adamlevine @IAMJHUD @johnlegend @CeeLoGreen… https://t.co/tl7d61W5f3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kandi I know what you mean the weathers bad here in Chatsworth Georgia to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@novpurpose Tbh 😂 right after that we just watched him the whole time. He didn’t even buy them 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special ‘Thank You’ to Joe Birch! You’ve been in my corner since my journey began 11 years ago at 1960 Union Aven… https://t.co/D0ITkuJx0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pancakes with the littles. (@ Original Pancake House in Madison, WI) https://t.co/xEoXCPKQy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[District EVM and CEBSI 50th Anniv Celebration at SGV Locale #proudtobeinc #cebsi50 #weareonewithevm… https://t.co/OC9q4iiStU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #MedalMonday for our girls. Varsity finished 2nd overall in last Thursday's meet, coming in just 3 points behi… https://t.co/mhGwUblKNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pass it on-  One generation will commend your works to  another; they will tell of your mighty acts. Psalm 145:4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegAndy76 @neuroticjomomma @lifewithshar @LBuckeye77 @tenacious_tiph @leelee1873 @mjs03093641 @leahisdarkness Than… https://t.co/ULk4Rv8ZWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pups fly to London without us tomorrow and I’m trying not to freak out😭😭😭 they hate flying so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[No climate change, rotten California Democrats cause the pollution, No immediate action is needed, the wall is #one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been feeling under the weather all day....ughhh   Maybe sinusitis issues this is that time of year....this weather… https://t.co/OlU1msveDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he drop you off &amp; he don’t wait for you to enter your house all the way inside before he leaves you is the side girl 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the rain. Have a good day everyone! #wednesday #smile #car #selfie @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/hPYkRGoPbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[8. Uno que me dieron tarde en la vida, y que me tardé en aplicar. Cuando lo hice todo mejoró. Es medio raro, pero e… https://t.co/MFKzighMCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Good for these kids. My husband has dialysis three times each week. He can’t risk missing a day. I’m sure the… https://t.co/qYFblu50Qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revolve has got to stop showing me $500 clothing on Facebook ads it’s honestly just rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain  THIS IS WHO U SHOULD B WEEPING 4 ON T.V.! THIS SENATOR W/ REAL FEAR OF HER SON OR HERSELF BEING MURD… https://t.co/foFuhtPA13]]></document><document><![CDATA[My relationship with my grandparents is honestly more than I could ever ask for. I would do anything for them and t… https://t.co/801m7cjtNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HawkeyeWNC @CNN I think he's hinting what everyone already kinda knew: there's not gonna be anything really in the… https://t.co/l2vp8Y7YNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all in the details 👌🌿. . . . #homestaging #homestager #staging #interiordesign #interiordesigner #forsale… https://t.co/tMEyIOAN6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than twenty four hours until #Oscars2019 and my predictions are coming your way tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFeenixx Lol I think maybe you need to eat our word. 6-3 @MapleLeafs #LeafsNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your #PapaGame is strong.. yall I love what I so and so should you. #Paparazzi #Preordained #PapaSmile… https://t.co/njRlBK7fLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t expect a Rosen or Borgman call-up here. Both are out with injuries right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iansomerhalder You are such a loving dad and hubby! Hope you all had a fabulous Valentines Day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday princess, our little munchkin celebrated her first birthday at the weekend and had a blast... look at that… https://t.co/Dv7orFn29T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Hey Fake Doctor! You come back and continue harassing and against our President Twitter’… https://t.co/WIhvJzz37S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever forget to breathe? I mean, of course our body is breathing on its own, but sometimes I stop and take in… https://t.co/fBHcozNs9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Dewitt, MI? View our latest opening: https://t.co/XVWKJKQVMo #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this idea to kick up research projects an engaging tool utilizing  #studentvoice @hcpslib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn i wanna wear one I've always wanted to wear a tux and a ball gown. why not both at the same time!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinH2222 @mommamia1217 @TeaPainUSA @realDonaldTrump The ankle length ties  that the cartoonists never forget really crack me up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for over 300 of our @FCSchoolsGA Middle School Honor Chorus students to perform! #forsythfinearts https://t.co/lMGdCairDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came home from work and took a two hour nap..... woke up, ate supper, back in bed. This weather has my body all kinds of tired. 💤🥶😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougJones you don’t represent most Alabamians. Why don’t you speak for your democrat buddies instead the people of… https://t.co/6ne8dDZCgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I see it, all of these disrespectful, childish beings all have an interest in hearing and seeing their faces on… https://t.co/4XoIjUFK0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever just walk on the beach while talking to god? You try it sometime it really clears up a lot of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Arizona for Chicago Cubs Spring Training. So excited that baseball is back! I have missed you my friend!… https://t.co/8t7HZEsktM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like do I like mulaney’s interviews with Meyers or mulaney’s interviews with Colbert? Or his bits with Davidson? Why not all of them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[And without faith it is impossible to please God, because anyone who comes to him must believe tha…… https://t.co/sv3rZ4J3MQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @onedirection more than anything else but the @jonasbrothers introduced to the world of boy bands. They will… https://t.co/sPopBJdg6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easter Basket - my easy Easter-related piano pieces for children/piano beginners on @SheetMusicPlus at… https://t.co/1htS2yybVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT: it’s your last chance to honky-tonk on a Monday night (10pm) with me and band at the @WhiteHorseATX before… https://t.co/y001KXJk7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive @DanaPerino @HillaryClinton @realDonaldTrump Some Co-hosts have similar traits of Pelosi's. Act like Juan,… https://t.co/muzQKPmiA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the love we take is equal to the love we make, I know with certainty, #PeterTork will be surrounded in love for… https://t.co/EPqGvEjhnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🏽🕯🇺🇸🌹 #11september2001🇺🇸 #worldtradecenter #twinstowers #memorial #groundzero #usa #nyc #newyorkcity à Ground Zero… https://t.co/IuOa2jJ0HO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Waiting For a Space Launch &amp; Watching a Car Chase. Merica.  🇺🇸  #carchase #spacex #Dragon  #NASA https://t.co/jmEM3lmQXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 5.0 mph W. Barometer 30.097 in, Steady. Temperature 34.9 °F. Rain today 0.14 in. Humidity 58%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Corrupt lawyer working for a corrupt man....how long was their working relationship? 10… https://t.co/53QPQSteWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @DuluthTradingCo for the laugh! Best laugh I’ve had caused by a commercial in a long time. #humorsells… https://t.co/yWttv7Wqf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our members phonebanking last night! #MakeLibertyWin https://t.co/I0mTN2d9AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 4 weeks left! I can't wait to meet you baby girl! 💜 https://t.co/u7hSGqhvuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im not sure if a guy fucking/making love to other women is something this single girl couldnt handle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt terrible for making Kenny wear his muzzle while having his cast..... I left it off and I came home from work… https://t.co/4PTevhUcXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimdogg @DigitalTrends I want one that cleans inside and outside the toilet ... seams like a lot of money and spac… https://t.co/dSO0mwfyRv]]></document></documents></author>