<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Delta staff in sky club NOT helpful at helping me figure out when flight is leaving. Waste of $ to go there for so… https://t.co/96gw6MpgqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Bring it all on for debates &amp; hopefully 2020 will be a teaching moment for all Americans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ate jack in the boxes mini churros too fast now dying on my couch and I have to force myself to the gym in an hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lightskinhxc I thought that was weird and then I realized hidden valley has a whole line of ranch pasta salads so… https://t.co/J0YyzeUCM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What an insensitive, clueless piece of poop. I knew you would start bragging about how you got him… https://t.co/4zC40IcJOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @NMHU_Athletics on their first #RMACmbb tournament title! #ChampionshipsElevated… https://t.co/nduRsrD5oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceyram The woman involved in this story has refused to talk to any other media about it, which itself is bizarr… https://t.co/h257cbuEhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll have halloween on christmas, and in the night we’ll wish this never ends..... we’ll wish this never ends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemphoNewsLady Andy just bought me Girl Scout cookies and I’ve never loved him more 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Festival with my good friend Eriberto at The Dominos Park #dancingtango #withmyfriend #calle8miami… https://t.co/EnU1fqC3OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron said this and Lakers fans wanted to lynch him. where’s the same energy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i remember the time my cousin called my phone just to ask my mom how to cook enchiladas (hers slapppppp) and she to… https://t.co/TGnh7mSkyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so stoked to see the Super Mario FX in person tonight! #NCAAgym https://t.co/6f9RAuppPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can never understand .. y’all swear y’all so naturally pretty but take your lashes off and weave out and be looki… https://t.co/7UOiAPICqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like so many ppl have birthdays today, May must be a busy month😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[for valentine’s day me and kourtlyn got pedicures well i usually don’t keep my toes painted and with it being winte… https://t.co/xxDkaZPKCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brbird @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV @SCHeartHome You might need a bigger spoon. He's sure stirring the pot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Please don't sign it the Democrats don't care nothing about the American people keep us safe Build That Wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sundrop76Marie thank you for retweeting my fundraiser. I really appreciate it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've eaten a ridiculous amount of bagels in the past week. I need to stop...right after I made pizza bagels for my family tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still wake up around 5:30 most mornings. The time #myson left for work. Stomping down stairs and slamming front d… https://t.co/PCzj8XHsmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @EmbassySuites Not an isolated incident, unfortunately.  https://t.co/hISOWRSt8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MennaElnaka Hey Menna! My name is Liz and I'm a Media student at Ryerson putting together a short documentary rega… https://t.co/5A3zZ8MmXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You stay on that grind” well it’s better than staying stagnant in the same place in life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capnbutthurt @nytimes NoVA has been diversifying at a rapid clip. Where else can you get some of the best Vietname… https://t.co/gn4KfZiLvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of you guys’ nail techs don’t care about how you end up looking and it shows, and I’m so sorry it had to be you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawBeautyKristi Do things that make you feel good! surround yourself with positive people. Listen to upbeat music. Eat the masseuse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duncombe_cher @realDonaldTrump I downloaded a Kindle copy of your  novel. Sound superb, Cher 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fodderfigure My kids are "clingy" still but I like to think it's because they enjoy my company?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I was a huge fan of the Jonas Brothers growing up so y’all have no Idea how excited I am for their comeback 😍😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[1983 Topps Rickey Henderson  $0.75 each  (Please check my pinned tweet for sale &amp; shipping details. Thank you!) https://t.co/muJXaguyIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disneyhero323 @JulieReichwein1 @POTUS I love this picture! #KAG2020 https://t.co/p4JCeuIbEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Anthem Karaoke @ Maryvale Baseball Park https://t.co/xZiXQDqtKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissLizz Let's do this.. we can ride all night. 🇺🇲🇺🇲 hoorah! https://t.co/Su6tsNX4Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twelve youth learned about #blockchain this weekend with  @apprent_io at @EthereumDenver.   They pitched… https://t.co/xJmirNjU11]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's an indication that we are nearing the end of the witness testimony on #ERPO red flag bill. #coleg… https://t.co/YGLvA85jAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkindonuts your Dunn Ave location in Jacksonville FL is the Worst EVER. Management this morning was unprofessional and rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is easy for me to say because it wasn’t my team,although let’s face it,cowboys have made plenty of poor choice… https://t.co/yN5kLndGAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I watched too many episodes of Criminal Minds and listened to too many true crime podcasts? Perhaps. #SSDGM https://t.co/TCzU5Mi8tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Unfair question. So many to love. Billy Jean. PYT. The way you make me feel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton The crises that we avoided was your become our POTUS. When are you ever going to stop with the race baiting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My professor grading the essay I had 3 weeks to do but did in 2 hours instead   https://t.co/6LtPRmUbfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Well she spreads trumps lies so...... Sounds like they're getting nervous!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barb71 @thelastmilehome @FMedic921 @iAmBoomerStrong @bluefamilyprays @ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @laker477… https://t.co/RMgD3Sa1gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOLA_Fredo @AttyJasonAnders Totally. I would make a purchase at the parade route.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched @RaiderReCap for the first time, and they have solid shooters. As a team, Baylor made 8 3s against Christ… https://t.co/SVU3WUTCL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On to beer tasting #wakewomen @ Footnote Coffee &amp; Cocktails https://t.co/Vc1bkovmyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inclusion is our choice and we are a community who believes we can empower women to make a better world for pets! J… https://t.co/bYy5ofRANT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepping for CoderDpjo this afternoon.  See you at 2? (@ SHAK MAKERSPACE in Kokomo, IN) https://t.co/YeVjyW9mGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[broo this is literally my besties and I until I have an asthma attack lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Claire_Bear @BritniB714 Al Dillard forever and always as a Hogs fav.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gettin ready for u to come out cheetahshollywood 😜💦 @ Cheetahs Club Hollywood https://t.co/VuRlYhNH2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[if timmy hated vicky so much then why didn’t he just tell his fairy god parents he wished for vicky to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[But @FoxNews been saying communism been in forever https://t.co/MxI7BBB6nY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my parents genetics would have mixed better. At least given me a chance! https://t.co/ESzjhI1sOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to testify! #showup #SB166 #nvleg #equalpay #InternationalWomensDay2019 https://t.co/JlFmYDmiek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise a Glass 2019 @ Marinwood Community Services District https://t.co/MefKkihXZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have any questions for Episode 2 of the #ClipCity podcast, ask them here and I’ll answer them on the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRA @ChrisCoxNRA NRA has taken money from Russia. Doesn't anyone wonder why Russia would help fund an American lobbying corp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoIsLife @Andy Margaret told all of us, Danielle has No friends No girlfriends. Reason why the cast where her b… https://t.co/vHQRcNKpXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaCAAlves17 Thank you so much Anna. You are a very special friend and I totally support you and love all that yo… https://t.co/t7cTgDViAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[those winged shining and world-shaking horses which perhaps even now expect us with impatience, pawing and snorting… https://t.co/fveXqyU1BE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The checks Michael Cohen was given by President Trump, which Cohen says were reimbursements from his payment to Sto… https://t.co/tju2jMQySz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is humorous. #hilarity #laugh #smile #jolly https://t.co/1lNOVbgpZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just remembered that a girl I went to high school with and hardly knew’s mom wrote a book where I was the main an… https://t.co/AcNbiD0jQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavisStrmndrng @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Obama may have been respectfully  bowing; but we all know what Tr… https://t.co/AZTZqS9NRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ovwrestling @TheRealAlSnow @IMPACTWRESTLING @GWNapp I signed up for the @GWNapp subscription and I can’t find the… https://t.co/cO4XHb35YW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjjackson I'm just glad we finally have a voice, thanks to social media. Before, we had to try and get the attn of… https://t.co/R6DbzxE4M4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy muy feliz porque me prometieron que cuando llegue a Colombia vamos a ir pizzería por pizzería buscando la mejor… https://t.co/ZpQxr9eqt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to be appart of this magical process. All in the name of ART @earthfest15 2019 #artarmymtdora #artjunkie… https://t.co/NpVmukCULr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @Seboaty1 @realDonaldTrump Prosecute them all on the coup to overthrow a President who was elected to… https://t.co/RLDEcM4Hwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so anxious about the time period between tonight when we go forward an hour in 🇺🇸 and when most European countr… https://t.co/KyRYfkysz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gonna be fun! #waterwaytrivia #ourwaterways  #natureconservancy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jax_persists Yep what is this, three Snapchat filters on ur pic and ur hand covering ur face ? Lol if ur gonna rag… https://t.co/n8BZldNqhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[call your grandparents.  hug your mom.  set up your dad for a joke that’ll make him laugh to himself for the next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have been disappointed if Shallow didn’t win Best Song. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[FBI to all business owners with electronic data systems: 𝙃𝙖𝙫𝙚 𝙖𝙣 𝙚𝙢𝙚𝙧𝙜𝙚𝙣𝙘𝙮 𝙧𝙚𝙨𝙥𝙤𝙣𝙨𝙚 𝙥𝙡𝙖𝙣 𝙛𝙤𝙧 𝙘𝙮𝙗𝙚𝙧 𝙖𝙩𝙩𝙖𝙘𝙠𝙨.   Aka,… https://t.co/vzAkgMasc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad would love to see this solar thing catching fire. Making California a leader in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia… https://t.co/j6ccH9efuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this look like a picture straight out of Clue or what?  @laurennovik @codyblackout your wedding was fantastic!… https://t.co/JWBeiXY1N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejansen98 @lauronmoron Of course not but member jackets will only have Lauren on it as the name]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united: One of your customer service agents assured me I could select a seat on a Basic Economy international tick… https://t.co/txRhBYzwAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kendall Jenner and Ben Simmons were at the restaurant next to the one we were dining at this weekend. Very pointles… https://t.co/bs4o4JPJZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d New York Times. And just about anyone else is more honest than trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call the office today to get your child’s name on the list for VPK 2019-2020 school year! #KnightsHonor https://t.co/PGIRzYnas6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't finished listening to this yet but what I've heard so far is excellent!! also the art is very very very g… https://t.co/GExJT6R2Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Results Have Been Amazing! Text or Call Me to Schedule Your  Appointment 805-559-6286 @ Camarillo, California https://t.co/yCUpZVBhQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still out and about... 🍸🍸🍸🤷🏻‍♀️ @ Saint Felix Hollywood https://t.co/w5dEmTWve9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are unfit and will be voted OUT in 2020.....stoke up the hate on a new reality show instead of in America]]></document><document><![CDATA[$15K on the eBay auction. Seems legit. Why do people have to troll like that? That’s just wrong! 👎🏻😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[#365diasdegratitud #Dia54 hoy agradezco las palabras amables de desconocidos, el 📺 del que  disfruté los Oscars y l… https://t.co/oyovJhPCu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sir_squiggles_ @jamesxingleton Consider how sexual sadists like inflicting pain, torture, and humiliation to get t… https://t.co/7qvl4SWrYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Texas, one files complaints and gets licensure as a  Child care provider via Texas Health and Human Services.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TranslateRealDT @DVanDyke2 No, too many people do not get it. We need to educate rather than insult. Difficult whe… https://t.co/UVaGNcCO3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smhadimousavi حق با اقای توکلی هست. شما درست نفهمیدی, دور زدن تحریم خودش پولشویی است و بعد شما می فرمایید در زمان… https://t.co/3fkjXBDbz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the feels, lots of changes coming on the home front. We will be better as a result, but it’s temporarily quite painful &amp; scary. 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone really said R Kelly and Jussie are in there having a sing off good fucking bye 💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming home on 42 and there’s like 30 cops, armored trucks, and riot gear?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimdonovancbs3 @JanCarabeoCBS3 that is dense, and I don’t mean rich!! 😣😣. That’s about the dumbest and most TRIFLI… https://t.co/oNglLSOSre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIBO_SoCal My Sibbo issues and IBS-C  has caused my life to be changed so drastically. With those problems along w… https://t.co/J9SlVGyj4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I agree. I just wish we could have a big eraser to make everything go away]]></document></documents></author>