<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We averaged $135 per day (for 2 people) for our 3 weeks in Portugal. Here's the complete breakdown -… https://t.co/8oNTN6rEJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeBrusk!!! Kid is on 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 #NHLBruins! @Toucherandrich is the slump buster! More Cheesecake!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran 3 miles in 25:21...90 minutes of tennis with my AMAZING eldest son...30 minute ab workout.  It's been a product… https://t.co/RQ4dEPdp1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more sensitive you are to God’s Spirit in you, leading and guiding, the more your are empowered to overcome and… https://t.co/q8sfKkrGGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CoCoSheriff says 18 y/o was shot and killed Friday night in Lancaster Circle, Bay Point. https://t.co/NKcEpyqdXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitewinery haven't seen a tweet from u in forever https://t.co/XzlaUDzFgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gstzombie @85Graeme @Simpsons_tweets Don’t do what Donny don’t does...they could have made this more clearer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible daughters, and I'm glad to be friends with one of them, Courtney, @LivvyLevyLover. Momma SC, never chang… https://t.co/l5HcTkv0Xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottcarnold @RadioFreeTom @USATODAY I've seen no compromise coming from Dems, not on their hot-button social issues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Jill Nathanson is a profoundly intuitive (albeit widely read and thoughtful) painter. Her radiant, lyrical paintin… https://t.co/L0IRUBXyrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizLanders @joanwalsh @SpeakerPelosi @VP Trump told Jewish Republicans “I don’t want your money.” He told Jewish… https://t.co/P1vqSFsBT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 Use it to bookmark and also to let you know I like or agree with the tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new fan experience seems to have hit some early hiccups. Will Sky Blue have some competition as sketchiest tea… https://t.co/I0ldLILBdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[next time i go to Atlanta I’m fading Cascade on a Sunday 😭😭this my type of environment lmao i loveeeee to skate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Operation "National Sword" could be a wake up call... But only if everyone can hear it. #recycling @RecologySF  A m… https://t.co/ovBAbvILdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stanford Deputy Director of Admissions is accused of attempted murder. Sources tell @nbcbayarea that 26 year old Ja… https://t.co/pSL4szY59q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseEs22585133 @AOC 3. claim that hasn't even been made. I can only assume people are either not reading it, not… https://t.co/oodDpDDqjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing your own yardwork is the equivalent of an actor doing their own stunts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neonbabel I’ll listen to select tracks. It just felt not great to me, but I really hated Pacific Daydream when it… https://t.co/Sz30vnEaAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c__laura @puregiana That’s why sometimes I like waiting to the last minute cus I be like https://t.co/duyD8DIFD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Only a piece of trash like you Brit trivializes this story as a ratings issue, rather than the fact that… https://t.co/3RqN8znqEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiddy2nap @KaitMarieox @thecjpearson @KFCBarstool Why would anyone with a wife want to work that creep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slimchilly @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Nope just playing the swamp game]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB when he found out he was going to the Raiders. https://t.co/VMcze91juT]]></document><document><![CDATA[03/04/2019: Fascinating talk by Angjoo Kanazawa (@akanazawa) at @UCBerkeley on work done in reconstructing 3D non-r… https://t.co/gmzL3vGwuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celticsblog Tatum disappears way too often, Rozier sucks ass, and Stevens is soft as Charmin...]]></document><document><![CDATA[How morons like this call themselves Habs fans off a deflection &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BestFriends #MargoAndPennyLu @ Ditmas Park, Brooklyn https://t.co/J7PsgRDNjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I walk into palenque grill and my waiter recognizes me right away, sits me down and says,  sir I’ve got you’re beer… https://t.co/1qO1vxuB1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly preferred the old vide game set up where you didnt have to download the game to be able to play it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know if that translates to an All-Star, all-offense exhibition. He might be fun for the players, but with h… https://t.co/woUOLNnX30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I just wanna see @iamcardib in concert.. that’s all I’m asking for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taaaaylrb might snap a flick or so, not trying to be that person that films the whole concert lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, of course not. That wouldn’t be fair to gangsters all across America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiskey color and Belgian aroma and finish. Fruity like a Triple, ends slightly dry. Excellent. @IronHillWilm… https://t.co/btPN9QFx7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oh_tooly3 I agree respect the game. My daughter doesn’t pimp walk and celebrate K’s. Respect the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much to a caring leadership that not only provides lunch and birthday celebrations for us @tn_vca but com… https://t.co/oNKl0ERhWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total mismatch in D1 North first round — Andover leads Lynn English 36-9 at halftime, Bramanti with 16 points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to leave college is less about being silly, and more about watching how you and your friends respond to trauma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandkelts an excellent way to do that is to not contact the attorney for Vic so he could make a statement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSearcaigh @giddy81370604 Evangelicals: I've seen your lifestyle. You would be blessed to have ours forced on you.… https://t.co/P188lfSv2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thing walking into an airplane and seeing people eating croquetas is the most Miami shit ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin truly amazing how my fight on Instagram has the world seeing what a piece of crap you are @mercedesamgf1… https://t.co/gY9KRY4LhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exhausted. But I’ll be damned if I don’t write this late night / early morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The random things I see. #CedarRapids #Iowa #IowaRocks #iloveiowa @ Cedar Rapids, Iowa https://t.co/ljnMqirafn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunsetswfl To this day no one is asking was the FISA court duped or were they in on it.  Either way they have questions to answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day in Atlanta for some Georgia Tech baseball. @EmorySportsMed #sportsmedicine #emorysportsmedicine… https://t.co/HCTwpiD9BI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @AOC Anyone who underestimates her does so at their peril  #NotoriousAOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sttepodcast @LASTEXITshirts #Westworld @LASTEXITshirts for the win!! #puzzles and #robots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@igot_mojoback Man, you should come watch it with all of us.Everybody bringing a dish. Smashing and watching lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Locked Junior up who got things he stupid I think you stupid to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EM6211 It’s been awhile since I’ve watched it, but I *really* liked it when I did. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @espnW @Torrie11 How the hell does she get in before chyna or @REALLiSAMARiE smh and respect to torri but like really]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebrook24 @ErieOtters I’ve just heard 3-6 inches today thru tomorrow. Will figure out tomorrow morning if coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the morning 🙏🏿😜😛 @ East New York, Brooklyn https://t.co/nMAUQ0gpDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/rXhP5x73qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My two cats were extremely curious about that attuned cat , came across the room and were looking around the room t… https://t.co/kW8SvA3IDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to my online home. I invite you to come in, learn more about me and my work, and stop to embrace the slow p… https://t.co/8kWAJco23O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelAnneRose @cpw_Numenor @D_resists @Mayo4Mz @ninampls @GOVTWINE @phyllisj1003 @maryh92 @PollyPapaya… https://t.co/T4KPt03nFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to Chicago for the Chocolate, Wine and Spirits Expo today. My brother backed out at the last minute and frien… https://t.co/BOztx0aEe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why @Spartytweets needs a bigger gym. For nights like this. See you Wednesday Night at Auditorium]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge s/o to my guy @wooding_charlie on getting everyone and their mothers aboard for some late night hoops. Simply… https://t.co/YHw4MyxDfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glass, metal, wood and brick. A Sunday morning walk through the Cotton Factory in Hamilton. (2/2) #hamont… https://t.co/XSsmge5WNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias I am all for new NYC housing, but the idea that it will fix the long term housing shortage is like be… https://t.co/bqzK0uGCZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djfandango @Jesusleviatan @RosaCarmen85 @IleanaPareds @rub_n23 @chemoazul07 @HijasDeLaMx @PoliciaFedMx… https://t.co/qtOIddEgR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Iditarod2019 starts tomorrow I dont know who the odds on favorite is but the field is wide open with Dallas racing… https://t.co/IbkkghfOUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to look up.....  - - - - - - - - - - #love #Supertags https://t.co/3Y1hHtVjfX https://t.co/3Y1hHtVjfX… https://t.co/jujCB4nWNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodoragoss I use Twitterrific. It just shows tweets in order. No “X person liked Y tweet.”  Not as fast as Twitt… https://t.co/pvi9dZx8So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith Making fun of someone with mental illness. You’re a fucking joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Imagine being a Democrat: You historically lost the 2016 election Every prediction about Trump failin… https://t.co/lQsyoKPKgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquaman - Official Trailer 1 - Now Playing In Theaters https://t.co/56MJeAV011 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[DANIEL LEWIS JUST SHUSHED THE OK ST BENCH AS HE’S RIDING OUT THE #6 WRESTLER IN THE NATION 😳😤🤫 #TigerStyle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance4gardener @JonAnthony7 @Beantowndougish @TaggartRehnn @FrankBenXXXOOO @MynameisMok @KingPeachDP @JoeMomma833… https://t.co/34IxuOEBFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDEMUSA @WhiteHouse That’s a huge journey to try to say that the military isn’t a socialist program just because y… https://t.co/t9nNuPCdJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianVorce That’s not his fault. I still think the Cardinals would be a better team with a true ace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know things are indefensible when Trump trots Steven Miller out. He is the political equivalent of the Mouth of… https://t.co/HUkgqzYgs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/wYvGbY096S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Managers sue Aramark over 2018 bonuses; seeking class-action status https://t.co/W8WS2wZHJZ via @phillydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sen. McSally revelation really puts the GOP message of “If it really happened why are they just now coming out… https://t.co/aWqSMwGjJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsbrenner @Cernovich "Everyone who still engaged in unquestioning support of Trump on Twitter" is a good start to answering your question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AOC Her voice is one of those that can penetrate laminated steel]]></document><document><![CDATA[TNT Players only broadcast is less than desirable. Especially during a matchup such as this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compass Zone by a dirty head over my top pick and bet, 10-1 Tigers Rule, as Carrick a wide-trip third making 4yo de… https://t.co/dd4yHGKl4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krm1285A @HiCaliberLilGal @ImabitcSumtimes @Thatconservati6 @OrenIShiKiddo @watch2c_H214 @Briteeye777… https://t.co/gcFCteLkn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter really a porn site lowkey. Can’t scroll down this bitch nowhere without some shit popping up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karinardz247 @ab1ul @WWE @WWERomanReigns @USA_Network I hope he’s announcing that he’s healthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKinzinger @RepKinzinger We were there last night, I assume you were monitoring the procession from the a spa no… https://t.co/e4RTsMev0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw both parts of the Harry Potter play today. It was disconcerting how many adults were wearing Gryffindor scarv… https://t.co/nTfXsYQocS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna watch @SpiderVerse again while I #workout BECAUSE I’M AN ADULT AND CAN WATCH CARTOONS WHENEVER I WANT! https://t.co/L5JfpGtbCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDavidEPrice Keep fighting David. Please focus on gun violence as a treatable condition. Work to get funding to… https://t.co/qpFNn8aD3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanLittle Trend Following with Michael Covel...very broad topics about trending following and human psycholog… https://t.co/nn7mAMp62d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about just giving up on sleeping tonight. My alarm goes off in three hours anyways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle Georgia State (NAIA): Victor Hall, who had been serving as interim head coach of the program since February… https://t.co/oqTH2y3IRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVelvetDays @JamesFrye @QuinceMountain @archivalistic @Way2gosassy @GMTminus7 Consumer electronics aren’t good a… https://t.co/hyNBGdaZru]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nowspinning #amerikkkant by weareministry from #exclusivecompanyoshkosh #vinyl #records #vinycollector… https://t.co/lQjD5gXXrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overture Awards - Visual Art https://t.co/DCy3wVeMdy via @YouTube. @MyBrothersKeepa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amgvs29 This is awesome! Thank you kindly for the suggestions. I’ll add them to the list :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“However, because you have the freedom, people end up getting lost, or just spend a lot of time travelling between… https://t.co/S5E9LCJq9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bketelsen My pup learned 'walk' and 'W A L K' pretty quickly, so we had to break out the thesaurus. My family stil… https://t.co/7oZV43RHUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[accidentally took two birth control pills in one day https://t.co/sNWmBTUhyR]]></document></documents></author>