<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[National, local, large, and small Charity Jar has them all! Choose from +1.5 million 501 (c)(3) charitable organiza… https://t.co/1S3ZxbCgOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lake Champlain at sunset. It’s one giant block of ice. #vermont https://t.co/9zKxhjPdra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tina_Brun Always look forward to seeing what you’ve done for your team! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day... from my valentine and I. ❤️😁 @ United Club, Concourse C, Near C17 https://t.co/d9qziJxcrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my seventh graders go home tonight and tell their parents they made babies in Science class....   It’s not as… https://t.co/cRVbkXTb3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[White people be getting mad at me bc I say I don’t date outside my race 😳😳😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most definitely! TY Emily Gibbons @TheLiteracyNest #teardownthewalls #openoureyes #kidsderveit #thinkingup https://t.co/63xSiID46o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Da Birthday boy! #ejm90 @ Casa Fina - Restaurant &amp; Cantina https://t.co/UWby3qkHel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like our photos 📷 Follow our IG....  These photos were taken by me! Photography by: Connie Wheeler @WheelerConnie… https://t.co/xJuPvyWOts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabe lahat nalang pinaglalaban ko, konti nalang sundalo na ko. Pati America papaglaban ko na.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These ppl paying extra money just to get on the plane first....umm those seats are WAY more cramped than the lobby… https://t.co/ZbY0AglyFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeyhoose15 @MSNBC @CNN @IlhanMN @GOP Just like their comments on how Elizabeth Warren can’t shake the Native Am… https://t.co/pr6ReYU8JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public defenders are the key to our whole justice system. San Francisco lost a very important citizen. RIP. https://t.co/JyL26oc8cS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to these two Ladybirds today! They are competing in the State Hoop Shoot Contest! 💚🏀💚🏀💚🏀 https://t.co/ZAfF1GFraA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Antho421901 Merci tu me diras ce que tu en penses, et oui je suis d’accord avec toi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayfordema Brendon Urie smells like to be able to make it to the meeting tonight  SJDJDKDKSJSJ 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Half a truth is often a great lie.” Benjamin Franklin partial truths are often seeded with lies. #Adamantbook]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm excited to see @TheChainsmokers perform live this upcoming Fall on the #WorldWarJoyTour. Are you? I'll be using… https://t.co/iQnYNWZnaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Grad and Paczki Day. Best late winter day of the year, BY FAR. I’m wearing my NOLA beads to work today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJITFacilities Yes I know. I’ll be watching and still cheering. Let’s go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't get out to my computer and vinyl because little love bug decided to fall asleep on my lap so it's a good thin… https://t.co/yyh4UHjlTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty picture perfect sunny winter day downtown #WTC #Oculus #sunreflection #freedomtower #amatuerphotography… https://t.co/Nl8es3Zawo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edbenson98 @Michael_Hudak @23_jhawk @JillLog91645576 @MG62967 @scott_canda @MarilynLavala @mailman576… https://t.co/FsFJ1vSfQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know more about CBD oil??? There’s a info seminar today out at the Paramont Estates clubhouse in Prospect 3… https://t.co/hHhaXquJN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NO1GifQueen @faxtors I commented. Disrespectful for a so called man to speak like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMdazlinjew4les @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert @HallmarkMovies @hallmarkchannel They are best paired couple I have seen in many years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advertisers promoted posts of large companies are free game to critique. #Wokaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemp Mansion is such fun!  The food is outstanding, service wonderful.  A great leap to a time long gone.  Don't un… https://t.co/9HgnVoIfjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: I need all of my friends to be available @ 5pm EST/2pm PST tomorrow (Sunday). I’m gonna need you all. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorisZelaya5 @Stewart7Donna @SudeJohn @alvin_manova @Bijomjohn1 @emmanuelobi476 @beverlyfelix3 @RevLDReed… https://t.co/jGSgnjU66F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeltingBonnie @AlanHenry @HOHmusical I walked into a donut shop and they were playing "Mad About You." Not gonna l… https://t.co/GLWngryDRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[the girls left me in Econ by myself but I don’t blame them bc I wasn’t gonna come either lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn  You voted for Obama care....yet against the wall and national emergency? If this is true, who do you r… https://t.co/Kb4CObyth2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see some true fashion risks, spend Saturday in a valley laundromat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll forever appreciate jorge for telling me what i need to hear instead of what i wanna hear 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Munezero_Divin @chelsarakaza Lol umwana akeneye help ariko she is seeking the wrong kind of help. First she needs… https://t.co/mnjkyoT18w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at the politics of my home and native land 🇨🇦 https://t.co/ntWsWpus7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLZ @KentuckyWBB @UKCoachMitchell @howard_rhyne @greenblair32 @Maci4Mo Congratulations to ALL!!!🎉💙🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge thank you to Dr. Hecht for hosting a neighboring district to showcase their awesome Launch program. We alway… https://t.co/y8UJw0wI7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Wonderful tweet. I am a veteran and will never forget that he said that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[***Swipe*** Our relaunch is here for BLUE ONYX TAMA FACIAL 💆🏼‍♀️ We have upgraded our machine with 11 new protocols… https://t.co/KB9pPOvNX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarllonOVNova Quem é o bosta do Felipe Neto pra falar de fake news se ele já cansou de fazer isso aqui no Twitter? Boa noite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoradoSparky @NBCChicagoFire Not hard to believe! Its a Great show! I Love Chicago🔥Fire! Chicago Med! Chicago PD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've just entered for a chance to win an XPS 13 9380 laptop from @WindowsCentral! https://t.co/7QCaJV2G30]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Parque Industrial Lagunero in Gómez Palacio, Durango https://t.co/7kWYCI0nw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @KevinGFox “What are you in for?”  “Felonious Instagraming.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfarero30 Primera impresión fue q se están mudando y que emoción!! 😅😅 pero Noooo solo están posando pa la foto!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can see hate through the smoke if my mind is at peace” 🙏🏽 @whoisclever]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Downtown San Francisco in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/WPLjhBAYu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Lordt knew my heart, knowing I never really wanted to go, and makes a way for me to not have to go 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Jim Jordan is trying to get Micheal Cohen’s old job as the “fixer” after he is NOT re-elected. This is a… https://t.co/CXTGgfmItJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalKarapetian I find it interesting his wife and Lady Gaga are sitting next to each other 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twilight19521 @RobertFauss @freethinker322 @lbc360 @Desiree54984868 @TheDemocrats demorats have destroyed themselv… https://t.co/q7ZDyDVmsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you never listened to “gold on the ceiling” by the black keys on a Sunday morning while your mom made pancakes and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KUSH_ Lmao yep. Packing up, cleaning up....house full of unnecessary shit...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mealeyman @thedailybeast Exactly what she said, again along with "that's classified," and "conversations between t… https://t.co/SELi7jLBIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSU_CHSS @WritingisLIT @ksuNCTE @ncte @GCTEnglish @DrBarton_EHS Sure! BTW, I teach English 1102 at KSU in addition… https://t.co/VV2uTTlrIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 6 inches of snow so far and it’s still coming down 😳❄️ #californiasnow #frazierpark #lakeofthewoods @ Lake of… https://t.co/21OLMYtwTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can I never sleep?! Holy shit. It’s annoying. I JUST WANT TO SLEEP 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly like fr fr.. the gym literally helps me flush away all my problems, if the gym isn’t your second home, wydddd????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with a friend tonight at my house. Asked him what he was doing for his new GF for VD. He said he was mo… https://t.co/Y8rGiSV3na]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClientBrittneyP @brittneybad_azz is getting in some personal training live with #GloryFitness #gotthatgodjuice pra… https://t.co/3ZYtNGUKnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hayley_Landry I thought about getting a shamrock shake this week in honor of that memory haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really don’t understand how funny this thread is unless you know how true it is😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich @Porouje1 I forgot about the hole in the Ozone layer!!!!! 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Winstonwrites @agnesfilms If you’re ever in NYC, I’d love to hear more about Agnes film.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can read my tweets all you want but that's not an apology for the lies you told about me or sending my picture to other pastors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like mine alittle aggressive, assertive,and clingy. Slightly Sensitive but to me only. What am I? 😅 ion really ca… https://t.co/tZBoin0qJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I knew somewhere that sells T.bacon, egg, &amp; cheese was open this early..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjeong I'm watching your Netflix Special You Complete Me, Ho" Here. Love It!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaguars @NFL @KStateFB @Alex_Barnes34 @TommyBo40 https://t.co/1TwpEYNTtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[All us TRUMPERS need to speak out and support r president. And why are the jewish ppl still supporting the democrat… https://t.co/N88xgmm4GM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this on my IG timeline and I had to tweet this... https://t.co/jvgmd8m3OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’m real life a correctional officer.... working in a prison.... I’m still in shock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seattle showing its true colors 😍   There really isn’t a more beautiful city in the world! True story. #seattle https://t.co/ENYy6j0Q7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OU_Softball made the trip north for the weekend and I already see 2 of my favs @leawodach @kelsarnold12 ❤️❤️ #playball #girlpower]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindazukowski @PrimeVideo Most of us start at the bottom. If you work extra hard you’ll get a head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomStark913 @ErikMCarson @_DumptyTrumpty_ @mori99saki @XDHALFDEMON @RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Bitter much, Tom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hookinhall It’s chilly here for sure!  Looking forward to Orlando weather SOON!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So not the place @JrJayBasketball wanted this journey to end, but I was sure proud to be there cheering for such an… https://t.co/tK0xMkFxN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day cheering on our Cardinals at spring training game in Jupiter! I’ve always wanted to go. Besides the humidit… https://t.co/bxLztVmNqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idu how people can jump from relationship to relationship just like that 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Willow Grove Mall Water Fountain in Abington, PA https://t.co/VuX3FOxIsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__afitz I have a hair appointment tomorrow then after that I’m not doing shit if you aren’t busy ! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of favorite things to do when I wake up: decide what time I fell asleep and count how many hours sleep I got. T… https://t.co/BneNf7J14B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s gooo @ramiroruiz 💪🏽 . . . . . . #VamosConTodo #FuryFightingChampionship30 #SanAntonio #LetsDoThis… https://t.co/veX8YgnImk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khoganpe Hi Kerry, No, anyone who would like a copy just send me a message with your email and I’ll send you the p… https://t.co/gbOc1J6g1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speechless 💔RIP sweet angel 👼 may your soul rest in peace 🙏 absolutely dreadful outcome not the one we were all pra… https://t.co/nfwNhlv36n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what  Democrats are putting in our government! Keep putting Democrats and you’re going to have a Jihad coun… https://t.co/w7TArp2h3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lazlovely @jeffdahkillah @Notasquirrel @Zozie_zo @BarbaraBpiwetz @LBisaillon @lynda3035 @chalkymacalpi… https://t.co/KQyJ03inYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i get sad i want ice cream but i get more sad because i’m lactose intolerant 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDunseth thoughts on the officiating? Did it play a part? #SanchezOut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ @TLC Looking forward to it Jazz one hour to go waiting to see what his mom has to say about you. I'… https://t.co/2Hoosn5KsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else’s twitter notifications doing this? It’s giving me anxiety @TwitterSupport https://t.co/L2Ll7Hsjul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely read this. Even if you have great insurance, you are not immune to the cruel and wasteful whims of our i… https://t.co/3rpNqlM3vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefjoseandres Please be safe. Thank you for the hard work and courage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[made frozen pizza at 230 to eat in bed and I don’t know if this more of an influence from vacation Mandy or sick Mandy]]></document><document><![CDATA[But in the fourth year all the fruit thereof shall be holy to praise the LORD withal. https://t.co/runHBEhA8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jax_persists @realDonaldTrump Read what his black girlfriend said about him . https://t.co/vgnZxyiJ3F]]></document></documents></author>