<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mochamewz @bunnyarchive @12superrabbit *hugs hiccuping bunny*  THAT'S SO CUTE!  TY!!!!!!  ^^]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very good. Had in Grand Rapids last weekend and really enjoyed it. Had to get a 6er of it. - Drinking an Official b… https://t.co/ZzijSzix6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Entérate La Bella Vidente Estará En Hoy #MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni #MhonienHoy No Te Pierdas De Las Nuevas Revela… https://t.co/jwEPmfgaG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBenediktM @PlugInFUD @elonmusk Live footage of me reading this tweet https://t.co/sa2BeNYiBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my latest Beats, Hustle, and Politics interview with @NPSvoices's Asia Norton on #njplus #nowplaying https://t.co/8e500Ic4CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebguts10 @TheCDJohnson @TheTrueVanguard from everything I here the end game and content is a major problem in Ant… https://t.co/Y3ZjZJ71Fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[People from LA make me hate them so much while also making me want to be from there so badly that I have a personal… https://t.co/WJDUEQqfTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I beat Thrill of the Fight in 13 minutes on normal with no pausing in-between. Knocked out everyone in the first ro… https://t.co/I5hcvfC4K1]]></document><document><![CDATA[They never teach you real Democratic History in school. If they did there would be no blacks that would be a Democr… https://t.co/G1jE5wWXcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB205, a bill I sponsored, creates the office of the Child Family Advocate.  This office will streamline the curren… https://t.co/HE3C2c86Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who trying to put they income tax checks together and buy this indoor facility?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this mean it would be possible for say, new england, to get julio AND AJ Green?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjx @CWNP That's how I met @jsnyder81 2 years ago but we didn't realize it was each other until 10 days ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMoreno1015 @LakersNation Thanks Luke for standing tall.  We are lucky you are the Lakers coach.  Class act!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMaxwellStory We can’t kill them here... but you want a cool challenge? Try and get a picture of Canadian Goose eg… https://t.co/M3coRRlBwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAME RECAP: Kings 115, Knicks 108 | https://t.co/Wh8eFuTIEZ #knicks #newyorkforever  https://t.co/p0aFroPfBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pnjaban @ReginaPotts20 I think it’s time for a 2nd special counsel to investigate all things done by the investiga… https://t.co/sDrP5jOGWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to today's webinar on teacher pension costs. ALL public school teachers should tune in especially u… https://t.co/T7PgIvSsN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlubbyThePone @MisterAntiBully I'm sure I'm infected now. Why didn't anyone warn me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's 12 inches long and makes Bills fans giddy every time one is thrown on the field?  A pass from Josh Allen to Antonio Brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my visiting friends' houses and garages. There are always so many interesting ideas and stories... 🤔♥️⛽… https://t.co/MIzxZMm6ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyersWasHere They can recover from losing this game. The Wade injury could be a killer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFBMemes_ @FloridaNatic @UFNewsUpdates @iLuke_M @Noah_bird04 @franksbetter @uflajeff @UCFanatic @UCFStool… https://t.co/0hlNpa8T6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vena_dot_com Pizza bread with potatoes tho? That’s made up AF.   I get what you’re saying but that’s not what this “list” has.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_queencobras is legit crying because #Opportunity died. https://t.co/EpL5etE6gp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump I’m glad he’s not a politician but he has done more for this country than a… https://t.co/XX4xLv9ppi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think Mike White was the most underrated Quarterback to come out of the 2018 NFL Draft and think if the… https://t.co/UWJ9pAqh5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucille2482 @Sue564 @gatewaypundit David Duke has always been a democrat but I bet Omar isn't liking him endorsing her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amarie1043 @CassandraRules They need lots of stimulation. A good long walk everyday and regular visits to the dog… https://t.co/UWpkG1zy7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZehDuck @JBCVOL It would be quite the conundrum. Want to get mad for hiring a man but can’t because it’s Pat’s son]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to get home early enough for some #tabogganing #gtsnowracer #batman #expos #bluejays perfect weather… https://t.co/nEzvDn1NL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a difference one year makes. I knew I had it in me all along, just didn’t know how to believe in myself and le… https://t.co/MYh8vPC0vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two fantastic young men that can cover both ends of the floor ... academic and athletics, that is! #capfam #capmbb… https://t.co/XDoGZ0Omja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobAbramowitz Well, he knew enough to vote no on the Iraq War resolution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl You might call her a coward.  After all, she runs around sniping at people, then hides her tweets… https://t.co/jVAZ2e9WyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s wild that millennials delivered Obama the presidency and would’ve delivered an Independent the dem nomination… https://t.co/3ydjulNdEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kuzma has an 11-point first quarter and Lakers lead turnover-plagued Clippers 34-26.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tupac is the GOAT. Anybody who listens to his music and thinks differently doesn't know hip-hop. This dude was REAL… https://t.co/5EwTO6gSYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué es más cagante que una lesbiana "Todas mias"?...  Una lesbiana "todas volteo", esas como pinches hartan. O sea… https://t.co/Cdg8o2UwJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan When Meadowed marched Trump's token black into the room yesterday, my mind instantly went to... https://t.co/XovKfJhgLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity How about all the media, celebrities and political people also?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stru_Alexa @ovierablanco Tenemos 20 años de dictadura y ¿no podemos darle unos días mas .@jguaido?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demi is such a horrid piece of trash. I’m sure she’ll soon follow in her mother’s footsteps - YEAH I SAID IT! (Can’… https://t.co/YRs3LJXduY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shots from the Sumerian event at the AWS Loft today. https://t.co/byxjQG9m6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien So basically hope the shooter is a complete moron because what was described will not save anyone from rifle fire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sues3jewels God's will WILL be done no matter what. We can accept it or not. I'm convinced that those who fight Go… https://t.co/g02VOiQwGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BundleUp #Brrr #ThisMorning  A new #WinterStorm targeting #NewMexico Get an hour by hour look at the #snow right n… https://t.co/VBIq4759Fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8Wdp7tD4EE  Era Mayo de 1958... cuando el Gran "Javier Solis" se presento 2 noches seguidas en "Carneg… https://t.co/gzcepFRidl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park and Ride Exit 11 in Clarksville, TN https://t.co/XrBe4Xsh5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold brew coffee for alcoholics. Well done. - Drinking a Full Grown Man-Child by @tuppsbrewery at @drunkendonkey_1… https://t.co/PexmVjijrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone’s still angry over her bath and hair cut 😂 @ La Salle, Michigan https://t.co/sITuPop73u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Stetson, Like Stretches dogs are co-hosts all their own. The sumptuous eat-outs are another flourish. The cast… https://t.co/8Mej96N1Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @Filippo60 @Wills_Place @DallasBrownin16 @Toddscrypto @PeterMPicoulas @RonaldLorenzen1 @marburell… https://t.co/l1PEBqueL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love because He first loved us. -1 John 4:19 God is love and He wants to love others through you! I pray you wil… https://t.co/IDgkbNWevm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a load of crap. Explain how an already born infant has anything to do with the health of the mother.  Voting n… https://t.co/fLfbD07a0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlphaBESTEdu @WTNTitleIAssn Cheering everyone on - you are all#GoingPlaces! @peterhreynolds]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OliviaColman wins the night! #Oscar2019 ❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/MvjCTgzN4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRaulJenkins @Leo_G___ @potus4madison @AOC Which people? And why should there be a healthcare issue, Obamcare pro… https://t.co/O56ua1Rm0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big mouth Berni 😻😻😻😻 #catsofinstagram @ Parkesburg, Pennsylvania https://t.co/vKKxjCi3sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four Seasons em Austin. #sxsw vai se espalhando em Four Seasons Hotel Austin https://t.co/xKIVx3UKDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ticket Fly @ticketfly is so easy and quick and low on service charge. Ticketmaster @Ticketmaster is the absolute wo… https://t.co/rccUhiMX0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching John Wick 2 for the first time. Fight scene pre bar drinking was incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhelicksLowpess Now why would you show the world your bathroom like that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Stern @Josh_Macri @lil_mils24 @Buster_ESPN @dschoenfield @esotericeric0 I want to see him hit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulman156  from @SeattleSportsU  had a great baseball article for @SeattleUBase  check it out folks https://t.co/mawpO89CXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all antivaxxers, alternative (fake) medicine proponents, notice it is the financial sector (not the medical esta… https://t.co/TxsAp7tXfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthew_peirson I think I’m spoiled off this season I just want to win them all lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXACTLY. As a NYer that lived in the Bronx, if you try to erase Latinos from hip-hop culture, you’re a whole jackas… https://t.co/OCwPeh1mIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[like bruh wtf i just checked my account yesterday &amp; i was big chillin', now i got 86 cents and a dream 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry to hear of @peterframpton’s diagnosis of #myositis.  Peter, the disease affects children differently than… https://t.co/dQpvN7s1rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody outside of you and the fine denizens of Beantown give a rats ass about your beloved Celtics...give it a rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually that isn't fair, maybe I'd better compare it to that one movie Scarlett Johansson was in that was also based off a manga/anime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You people are all idiots, your lame party will be out in the open soon, build the WALL DUMMY!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_R_Berna @MeltingInMarana @jonz970 @ImabitcSumtimes @Serremmy @Trump_Girl_USA @Dannybr18031504 @rkline56… https://t.co/CaqNAZrntT]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s got to be the best weekend I’ve had in a long time and it’s all thanks to you. 🤷🏽‍♂️ but don’t forget I’m not that great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavLucia @albertopetro2 @AlessandraCicc6 @matibo11 @SalaLettura @cmont4560 @alberto080461 @marialves53… https://t.co/noEad8FEBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[La salle est encore vide. Les demi-finales se préparent. Plus que quelques minutes avant la 1ere confrontation de l… https://t.co/u4wua65bIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine anyone?  I jus got done shoveling snow off the deck and needed to have a glass! A bottle of Mini Reed's Red Bl… https://t.co/6JXvVLDOt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Pacific (7-1) beat @SacStBaseball (3-4) by a score of 6-2.  Tigers take the four game home-and-home series 3… https://t.co/5ZLmOila2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pgapro1 Patience. There are more important things to worry about. Like you getting one year closer to retirement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished this exterior today #lakemurray in #Timberlake today. #chapin #carolinapainting #changemypaint… https://t.co/AtReadkoSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great trip full of memories🇨🇱❤️ @ Katy, Texas https://t.co/qmVRX5CoLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UAALLAMERICA 📍Blessed To Have The Opportunity To Compete With the Best of the Best‼️ https://t.co/wSXIQ0THyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ll remember you guys forever,” Coach Angela Moore told the Taylorsville seniors before tonight’s game. “But if y… https://t.co/5GEgABHPcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's game time for the Warriors! @Waukee_Hoops @WaukeeHS @NoahHartx1 https://t.co/HtsrAPIQWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[4/ Join the Rare Disease Congressional Caucus. This is a bipartisan, bicameral caucus that works to raise awareness of rare diseases.]]></document><document><![CDATA[100%! This is one of my major aggregations about working for the federal government. If your job performance is of… https://t.co/h84tzxaIkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burning the midnight oil with bulleit..... @ New Rochelle, New York https://t.co/sqqxIstn2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BanjoPope A fashion trend setter there. She showed Minnie Pearl how to be styling with that hat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyiballs There were people who threw rubber snakes, along with the jersey tosser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowie and the goblins are better babysitters than anyone else in this movie.  #FThisMovieFest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianaLima @angelcandice They are not able to handle this threat matrix from the Miami Beach Police.… https://t.co/EgT52GB9tM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prashan17544781 @rashmiprasan @down2earthindia I read it. I guess I misunderstood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nightly telescope show at Cinemark Tinseltown theater. Year:  Spring 2010. . . . #photooftheday #magicufo #elpasotx… https://t.co/6boOXJ0KZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the TRUTH is apparent &amp; yet still manipulating those words!  GAWD🤷🏿‍♂️🤦🏻‍♀️🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoucheTimothy @_Drew_McCoy_ @JamesGeschke @evil_mara @NickRiccardi Let me ask you this question  In the gun scenar… https://t.co/seoK3pSnI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one got A LOT of you talking and engaged.   Good.   Learn something from it:  Don’t fuck over your friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdcity DAMN YOU  GOD DAMN YOU ALL TO HELL  For making me laugh so hard. https://t.co/19I1kJzKWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thevulnerable @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump There is a lifetime of evidence that he does not read. Drooling, obseq… https://t.co/BodgxJ5Nzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key Question from the text today: Does your heart see the lost?   Statistics are helpful, visual aids for a picture… https://t.co/anloS05zGP]]></document></documents></author>