<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Trump claims he found ‘free’ fireworks for his July 4th event -- but he’s just hijacking the annual Park... #Topbuzz https://t.co/ZGdxW8SM29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NguyenLuce Depend how big you go with “apocalypse”? On the typical studio model, net emissions seem pretty minimal… https://t.co/JvNcT0gsmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are blessed to have the sports media people we do in the Peoria area. @KurtPegler is one of the best! Well deser… https://t.co/A2ohrsaLbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@710Express @cannaworldsite @Bklynbby @Raymosaki @Smokette_ @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @james_bong13 @_jena4n… https://t.co/LteTktr8SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason Skills, Money, Charity.  Power is temporary but charity can survive the grave and make lasting impact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyright3 Just went to freeones n rated u 5 stars baby ur a true big star⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaasssmyn When I had FB I used to delete them everyday when I looked at “on this day”😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Club Deportivo Campestre Del Lago Matamoros https://t.co/tcrhiJsOh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[...statement leaving me feeling like i haven’t said anything that makes sense at all or that i’ve not defined my fe… https://t.co/fw7ICQNILQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rondarvin @UBC_LLED Oh no! I’m not flying in until 11 tomorrow. I’m sure this will be great though - break a leg!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_Lynch24 @24TaylorMade Triple threat matches are always no dq, man. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have Warriors moneyline and you’re entire soul shuts down after watching this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching The Happening for the first time and this scene just happened and I am inconsolable.   https://t.co/LtMr08FH35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlyPashlee @suziday123 @marshawright @TlrWorldWidellc @TheTwinPowers @TomHall @TheGood90551276 @JuliaGrantham2… https://t.co/aAradhOdRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met a girl who spoke Portuguese, it sounded dope. All fluent n shit lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Your country. Your church. You are the one to blame. No one else. Girl, 11, gives birth to child of rapis… https://t.co/TZLlCxOnOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeandersonsr   They have no idea what they’d get into lol https://t.co/D624FGREl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bighugh53 Had me wanting to watch Boomerang!!  Unfortunately it's not photoshopped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScreamBTCH @dani3palaciosdj Ps yo le tendría más fe al tarot  que a las iglesias o los santos de ahora !]]></document><document><![CDATA[43 days ago I was on an island right off the coast of Mexico.. I need to get out of Illinois for good 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m down and sad I buy shoes ... thanking God for online shopping 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[we still partying but tf playlist just started today and it’s already 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerErnt @TimBurtIrvine @OCSportsZone @FVBaronBaseball @Warriors_WHS @PortolaBaseball @CIFSS @FoothillBasebal I b… https://t.co/BcPvZAlnG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m celebrating @ele05944’s birthday by proctoring an #SAT, which is what I believe she’d want. And if I’m wrong ab… https://t.co/ujik2bIuhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petting zoo @ Tucson Petting Zoo &amp; Funny Foot Farm https://t.co/OHlNcvlZHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me enlighten you ❤️❤️❤️... . . .  . #chris_sells_az #love #lovequotes #valentines #valentines2019 #lovewins… https://t.co/pqgk1DmIaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Nature: Starting that new gig tomorrow?? Here, try this https://t.co/emOx6ccjTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the President of the United States attacks more press, remember that his words aren't spoken in a vacuum. They h… https://t.co/wy1zXsKVl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenatorLankford @JimInhofe @repkevinhern @RepFrankLucas @RepMullin @TomColeOK04 There is no other way to say it:… https://t.co/QgdqfePQyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordylancaster My deceased father in law had one. It crawled up his pants leg. He opened his fly to get it out, ju… https://t.co/5smJkGlmbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started early with some #grooming no school for the girls so they get to spend the day as JR Patrollers and help me… https://t.co/SJbn85k6N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow If Mark Levin says you're pathetic. Then you are egregiously pathetic. Drain the swamp and MAGA🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Ferrin Don’t do it unless you get a guaranteed caffeine kick and extra incentives for not burning your tongue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't go to the East Hill Publix often, but I did see Moose a few times. I'm more sad than I thought I would be s… https://t.co/rTqTh7Z6e8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I doubt this will cut it in the primaries. When you’ve been promised cotton candy and unicorn rides, you don’t want… https://t.co/ymGaJhm8tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorrainepascale So glad you're back on in Spring.  I'm on a mission to learn how to bake sweets and substitute for… https://t.co/lzPZy6A37h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santiago4kd @rayelizalder @TigresOficial no seas niña Santiago,  encaralo ahí en la conferencia,  en twitter ? com… https://t.co/A0cqeatwqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @HouseDemocrats We are #Americans and we can speak any language we want, without prosecution, because w… https://t.co/4EAV1NBuIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenoblebri @KofieYeboah @TrainIsland @BigShotMill @LilBill95 The fight against child molestation never sleeps Bri]]></document><document><![CDATA[me when i thought i was going to marin county jail https://t.co/ezUaCuKUgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t like it. F1 has made a few changes this season that I’m not a fan of so far 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevistaSemana @DELAESPRIELLAE @HOLLMANMORRIS Feliz día a ElPerardo. https://t.co/6XFsccDQOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChildrensHD @BeckyJohnson222 Then it will be mandatory to take end-of-life protocols if you become burdensome on t… https://t.co/7W4uygendv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerFernando Trudeau will be paying the price if he boots her. Anyone with a brain believes her outright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_ruckart @gumby61184 @MattWeaverAW Not a good attitude to have when you claim to have the best drivers in stock car racing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VloneMario I’m against spending bread on expensive socks 😂😂😂😂And since the pants are cropped I would prolly wear t… https://t.co/JnH63x5kkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam Did the Fox producer get a phone call from Prince Alwaleed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I would say this, but I wish my lunchables didn’t come with Oreos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer Shootouts 19: Teams are securing spots, it’s going to be another great summer of hoops! May 31-June 1, June… https://t.co/8vHMBBZUUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a La Péninsule by Les Insulaires Microbrasseurs @ Les Insulaires Microbrasserie — https://t.co/UuAJVNNebq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylie_oneil75 @migrantsaid @gatewaypundit Iike most anker babys and welfare recipient's, are white, though white A… https://t.co/hsde8gEoGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This How I Feel, If you Not Rocking With The Movement #YARDGANG 🖕 U #ThatWay  . . Prince kojo aka Troublez  . . . Y… https://t.co/kAjbtuYRrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here reminiscing I miss watching my bro @Flex_Asap ball out on Friday night 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and I forgot, AB is getting $30 million guaranteed and he doesn't have to deal with Ben Fucking Roethlisberger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrov_svilen @SuperMugatu @JeffreyALoyd @77cyko @PHKhedge @JeffMacke Hang on, grabbing my backup. https://t.co/DjSUY1sRjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyVanBramer @SenWarren @CoreyinNYC @ewarren #jimmyvanbramer .@ewarren I like her, but you Jimmy are a sham, you… https://t.co/br1gcH4cjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rally in support of Oakland Teachers @OaklandEA @ish_the_dish #WeAreOea #Unite4OaklandKids @CaliforniaLabor #1u… https://t.co/9ydmzqQtSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_fameONE "Please......don't sue our frat bro..." https://t.co/jTENSGiZtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Nitwit American people keep electing her.  Assholes.#dumbassAmericans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please Preach!! ♐♐♐🙌🙌🙌 Don't Lie To Me Baby, Keep It G At All Times! 😩😫👌💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should think about what happened to Mussolini and what his own people will do if they get their hands on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gustafson’s first points of the quarter put Iowa up 49-45, 1 and change to go in the third. @CRGazetteSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially involved in two businesses now so if you start hearing less and less from me there’s the reason 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s annoying when I plan a conversation in my head and the other person doesn’t follow the damn script]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another snow, another 12 miles in the bank. @ Centre County Courthouse https://t.co/CYp7FU1EZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Eres comunista? O sea que obligas a la gente a pensar como tú y les enseñas a odiar a los que piensan diferente. (Sigue)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NCHSAA wrestling finals begin at 4:30 p.m. in the Greensboro Coliseum. Five @CCSAthletics1 wrestlers are in the… https://t.co/PMD0HuXYeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioNovelli @Heberlizeth @mbachelet será q esto aún para usted no es violación de los derechos humanos o es q su… https://t.co/ZSnqFDLspC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gypsyglutton @LakeMomLPB @DocSupafly @BullshitMike90 @HerrMorgenholz I missed you so much. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Wallace or  RUSH LIMBAUGH RELEA... https://t.co/qKn3cs2GFp via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attn: Sacred Heart Parents: Please pass on that walkers will be dismissed to the church parking lot.  Buses will be… https://t.co/yakUTM7Rbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsKris10 @MickeyKnox_xxx @amyrx1220 I didn't know how to use and uninstalled it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikeGeorgetown will you all have the infrared 6s in GS &amp; PS size??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayApex why are the shotguns so trash? See lot more people running two smgs or two assaults. No one ain't using t… https://t.co/5QolJTAhpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see this sticker, you know you're getting quality stuff! Finally my slabbed #cgc graded #OldManLogan #50 c… https://t.co/KK08jgwCBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wallgrinnoize / @corinnarmusic / Lonely Boa divingbellsocialclub @ The Diving Bell Social Club / Club Social Le Sc… https://t.co/vGo2qaQcIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[****Traffic Alert****  This morning EPD was notified of all RR crossings crossings down BNSF advised that there was… https://t.co/vaFBFmvAqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glen Burnie MD Sun Feb 24th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Clear Lo 31 MONDAY Sunny Hi 45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VarialsPA needs to be on the lineup for the Atlantic City @VansWarpedTour date 🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just getting caught up on #TheBachelor. I’m guessing there is going to be a co-Bachelorette of Caelynn vs Hannah B… https://t.co/aCfkd0g8dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d love to see how people would think of MJ if there was as much media coverage and social media during his NBA da… https://t.co/LRrax7jjFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody knows that @jimmyfallon is way into fitness and exercises all of the time. 😉👏🏽 #FallonTonight https://t.co/rcIK9M4Ao3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnharrington Love it man! Just booked a @BMW X5 on @turo for $300 less than what it would have been to rent a Co… https://t.co/cETmp2HkaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[TY Cub Scout Pack 285 - we're so glad you came to see us - we see in you the next generation of law enforcement, so… https://t.co/XIAEVVG51w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meggerino @DogginTrump Who's gonna break the news to this kid where his cocoa comes from? #Irony #parentingfail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpchowdog Kelly Johnson and the Skunk Works developed some amazing aircraft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already picturing Rafa sliding his bifocals into that top pocket of his. #rafa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesWStork @beccas1434 @BetoORourke Still don’t know when to fold them! Perfect song for a Democrat! 😂😂😂. #WalkAway #KAG2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to watch @candice_on_cam videos 💚🌹💙💙 she’s got some of the sexiest moans you’d ever hear put you earp… https://t.co/AOTYtGBnJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/gxml48zwax! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/QdKMsdnkQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new look grizzlies team plays well - and plays together.  3 guys rushed over to help up Delon Wright up after he took a charge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is incapable of class and civility. Shouldn’t expect such from him.  Just put it all into the “To remember in… https://t.co/Tsl5hruFbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need to sit on the potty for THREE minutes! "I don't hafta go potty!"  "Too bad, sit there anyway." *Three mi… https://t.co/z3il5JVieL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@txommy @stoneroxxbitch @_4everunknown_ @Fuck_Twelve_ @_4everunknown_ &gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's 3 a.m. and the only song in the world that understands how you feel is this: https://t.co/7of5ufV2it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... maybe I’ll be stuck in Florida longer than I thought: https://t.co/RDmgKdbpMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to jump out of a plane yesterday. Sadly no pictures of me falling but here’s my buddy Mike. #iloveautopilot… https://t.co/xHHxa6cduG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hemp Crown - YouTube https://t.co/xZ6KeP0mrA @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/oSj5CYQEj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe millions vote illegally. This Democrat fraud is endemic in all 50 states. This is why they fight hammer a… https://t.co/vLpIg6aNDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper If I started a fight I was in trouble, if I lost a fight I was in trouble.]]></document></documents></author>