<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Reposted from healthyaging  -  Another benefit of being fit? Avoiding injury.  #Repost @participaction with get_rep… https://t.co/a4chA9CTx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A non-binary transgender author is nominated for the first time in its 27-year history. Nigerian author Akwaeke Eme… https://t.co/XkPLyUxb3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonkeysVentures @Dreams_Abroad @KaraDiDomizio @LeesaTruesdell @tblack729 @PackYourBagsOrg @Sostraveluk… https://t.co/CNNjCbAQA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning view of St. Lou! It’s a balmy 18 degrees outside and it looks great from the warmth of the apartment. I hav… https://t.co/cQxksOyoK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlinmarie71 Can we have a full class dedicated to it bc I feel like we only skimmed the surface last time :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Palmer Report got it all wrong. Trump is Projector in chief and Kim was the one who walked away after seeing Cohen… https://t.co/UMjyv4Ba3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great month to welcome in every year. Happy international women’s day! 💞  How will you celebrate this month?… https://t.co/Hni8V7yP2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[More friends and finally posting product! #smallworld #kbis2019 @ Las Vegas Convention Center https://t.co/slmOvcuCzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-PESS Day 2...continuing to refine their practice of supporting principals. @R4Leaders https://t.co/szyZI6wwjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Silver Ranch, Katy, Texas https://t.co/U1kD4PyLz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC So ABC is of course under a lot of fire mainly because of the GMA interview with RR.  Let’s not forget that th… https://t.co/T4IM9Zbs2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCampeggio @JoannaLeeSimon @katydrinkwater If you make these, please invite us over]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve fallen in love with birds since being suddenly widowed. They seem to show up in odd places and are often rare… https://t.co/l22gdcgyCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car in front of me is smoking.. a cigarette.. in California!! Wtf is going on..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand people who can’t talk to some one with a sense of empathy and compassion. Grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leontynesjr @NatGeoEducation @NatGeo @LindbladExp @JustinKaput We should totally organize a CT GTF meetup!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a direct result of the trump regime's bigotry and hate. They incite people to violence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of sleeping before my opening shift like a responsible, mature adult I’m thinking about how funny it was to… https://t.co/5WbWAnVqbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you need is LOVE❤  #HappyValentinesDay @ UNLV Student Union https://t.co/z6nOe48qgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[still can’t get over this wonderful night at a Pre Grammy party courtesy of @hoochapp tapcoinofficial &amp;… https://t.co/xR3opY6vvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@autumnjohnay Best mission in my opinion. That one and burning the weed and getting hella high]]></document><document><![CDATA[@argumento_ Nunca se me va a olvidar una carta escrita por un soldado ruso que narraba como los mandaban a tirarse… https://t.co/4aFxq0nqAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BUFootball @solo_turner We see you Solo! Fishing? I never knew that! God bless you and never forget #oncealion #GoBears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanOLearySMG @FostersDailyDem @seacoastonline block party @abbelaurence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherinePaiz Why not, you can always get extensions if regret sets in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay now watching #Roma ... so good. Poignant, beautifully shot... already in love with dear #Cleo @tenaciouslibbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@factsimile1 @siano2020 What hobbies?  I have absolutely nothing in common with this guy.  It seems like a nightmare blind date.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if no lines were drawn If every race and tribe belonged Imagine if we stood as one To see each other as dau… https://t.co/qeQY06RVbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@704heather @TheValuesVoter I agree. I’m always afraid to voice it on Twitter though - because of the passionate di… https://t.co/5cbnnjPqGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineMonge @KatieJMcNamara @profe_c @rswanklibrary @hamilton_bunch @TimDewar1 @wilebookwizard On my way]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #Agenda for today. The #Love ❤️ of God. The #Grace of God. The #Help from God True #Blessings fromGod. Peace ✌️… https://t.co/O0S6lPclE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femwriter Wow! Gorgeous! Too bad it’s so friggin’ cold!! Too cold for a glass of wine on the balcony anyway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioDorian @BrooksAndDunn @RODEOHOUSTON This is the song that turned me country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the world sweetheart! #itsbabyseason #osv #lambsofinstagram #marchbaby2019 @ Old Sturbridge Village, Mas… https://t.co/3KsBcsJlCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Agape_Lover Arts was but gpb had those big women in there and I trusted there baking lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard Maybe because he has pointed out all the BAD dems have created and intend on creating and people are af… https://t.co/ql3o6Ayna7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerDroppings We finally have a winning basketball team so the feds can’t stand anything positive to happen in Lo… https://t.co/IidzN5z40T]]></document><document><![CDATA[wish everyone posting shit for international women’s day would vote for women, purchase from women-owned/run busine… https://t.co/gLnjMIYOXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class B: Crete leads Skutt 48-29 with 1:29 left. The SkyHawks have been held to nine second half points. #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mais um ❤️❤️😭 @nickjonas ai gente eu chorei de emoção depois https://t.co/LuhQ4D00d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jone_loyd Happy, happy birthday! 🎂🎁🎈🎊🎉 🍨🍦🍫 ☕️ 🍾🍷🥃🥧🍩🍺🗺   I had to translate that tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCoachK 🙋🏻‍♀️https://t.co/IEMCuGn8vH 561-495-7272 ext. 207 ask to speak to me directly Coach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meray34902584 @sh8tfeel @kingwarrior152 Warrios daw? At king? King kong leche hehe.. duwag talga..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Little Adam 💩 why don't help people and 💩  build affordable housing for people living in their cars… https://t.co/3fVoKjtRRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collagen induction therapy, also known as microneedling RF or skin needling, is a cosmetic procedure that involves… https://t.co/KxPuCVlbqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Is the GOP compromised thru dirty money funneled thru the NRA? ...pics in the “vault” at AMI? I soun… https://t.co/fkZV7QBvhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mouth pain from braces is the worst 😭 going to take my pain meds now.. gnight. 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRoofFiddler @SinclaireU @thedailybeast @TheRickWilson It’s a cage. That was kind of the ploy she was playing. I… https://t.co/iHcSMIwhpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEAST FOR BACHELORETTE 🌹  #beastforbachelorette #thebachelor #womentellall https://t.co/pZsWLkZti0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally thought i was gonna cry w this workout. We finished 10 min ago and im still shaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vxbTEzglCg  #karatbars #gold #cryptocurrency #payyourselffirst #savingingold #tokens #freedom #win… https://t.co/jsQ4euNzCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantstern He will not be jailed but I am certain that he will Manafort and end up in jail before trial!  #MarkMyWords]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @maggieNYT @MichaelCohen212 Too little too late. Did you apologize in person or on Twitter. https://t.co/Mn942w0lYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at Steve!!! Representing for Team Blue Face! Steve said he not scared, he got this! @FlandersTeam1 @411MikeP… https://t.co/HNZtFcslO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So clutch from Keith Mitchell. How amazing; I wanted his debut win to come soon @TheHondaClassic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin @Hectoesme35 Tell me Russia isn’t behind the anti vaccine rhetoric. Please. 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come intern with us! We will actually pay you! You will actually do things that will actually be on the radio! You’… https://t.co/s1temSBIJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like they some slam shit when the spotlight actually on them but they'll whoop someone's ass on league pass games lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelby_young Yeah but we get more light! It’s so depressing driving home at 5 and it’s black out!! More sunnnn! Ye… https://t.co/WZKTlkltT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I just found out my manager drinks arrowhead water...I knew something was wrong with this place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benandkellyshow you know ppl complain about hearing Ariana a lot but at least it’s different songs where as with t… https://t.co/7dSlRnyNcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeGarvin @HeyLeauxla @snipy Love you and your ability to find the perfect make up solution that’s not too severe… https://t.co/6yL21YbvYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabresbills18 @FrankJannuzi @RepAdamSchiff @Susan_Hennessey @POTUS https://t.co/xMFoGe6Tqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brief stop at Elway’s for some steak and wine. #sundayfunday #cabernetandsteak #denverairport #nextstopla #denver… https://t.co/Ci8pJIeoyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[INBOX: As @MarkMorganWI leaves for @NRSC, @wisgop announces Mark Jefferson will become the Executive Director of th… https://t.co/ENnkJbbc14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Alana_96 @carkeys33 or i sleep on my comforter with another blanket lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little fun at Peterborough's newest play place. Opening soon! @ Peterborough, Ontario https://t.co/MizsBHMSkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The womb forgets them, the worm feasts on them; the wicked are no longer remembered but are broken like a tree. https://t.co/5pm5TpZDZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the #SLAMDUNK Sweepstakes daily during March basketball madness for your chance to WIN $250 + a variety of… https://t.co/rBzLF2XTja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genetics are wild. We watched fat, sick and nearly dead and this one white dude was like 400+ lbs and the dr told h… https://t.co/5G15eu7ttJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finishing up #supergymnasticssaturday 👍🏾😊👊🏾 #whgfharlem @ Harlem Armory https://t.co/7K0CbspAMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbsings @BNBuzz Just listened to your new album ✨💖💕 my treat to myself for Valentine’s Day  MB, you are one powerf… https://t.co/HSbNFpqUg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I guess she is telling us she can't be trusted with a gun even though she has armed security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You are an idiot clinging to power AOC already usurped. Do you know why? She is 29… https://t.co/yuXpuWB3i5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/a3o2k5zc7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellouelle @dianelyssa @ECMcLaughlin Girl read my tweets. See what I fucking said before you come at me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About that time.. I think everyone is curious to see how this Louisville Basketball team responds after dropping ba… https://t.co/8BwoLPlrkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Joe Day, Joe Brown! PORTSIDE ADVERTISING       https://t.co/hqzO2ZA0bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rand Paul should be voted out next election if he votes against this, he doesn’t care about American citizens!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every evening the Arizona horizon puts on a sunset show. @ArizonaTourism @VisitTucsonAZ https://t.co/wzYqAw7ndh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying get ideas to make my first YouTube video! What should I do I need help!!! #YouTube #YouTubers #firstyoutubevideo #sneakerhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spin It However You'd Like Say You Didn't Know When Asked Deny Deny Deny Just Understand That I Know And Just One P… https://t.co/1mUNGvPzMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahFinley01 @gwGSEHD @BethBianchi @TechTeachVB I have one! Thanks so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[and she yelled “too bad I am the one whose doing it so get over it.” The customer service was absolutely AWFUL! I w… https://t.co/TR3ZvFc3Rz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please speak to me in English BEFORE coming to give a word. Facts facts facts be friendly 🦄🦄🦄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Kim I hope you have the absolute best day ever!!!**british accent** love you so much, can’t wait to… https://t.co/wyBSvRLcXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trade Wars are easy to win. @realDonaldTrump  Trade deficit highest in decades.  #RecordSetter   https://t.co/P9b7aa8sdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[First stop! @bythebeachbear @bythebeachbear #blackbeardiner @ Black Bear Diner https://t.co/CiCPSnYNYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lastpatriotsusa Would appreciate a follow back. Thanks! #PatriotsUnite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossdroy @Ginohard_ Why?  It’s at the end of the game it’s not hurting anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain was like “livestream in the shower” and my other smarter brain was like “haha no that would be disastrous”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely one lucky girl to have you in my life!! Makes me feel special on every day of the year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[well i want that money n to count up my bandzz i need math, that’s the only time ill fw math]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valac666 @JanetBarstow @thing32010 @ashionegallery @SharonG40210896 @jeanine_new @Mary60053440 @deborah05293636… https://t.co/iT4oOoAuwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryOConnor @SebGorka @WashTimes Time to ARREST Members of CONGRESS for the Next Illegals that MURDER are Another… https://t.co/ZqdQ3feu5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep at 6pm yesterday and just now woke up sad and confused on my couch at 6am. 😓  Welp, so much for having a Friday evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[openly discussed the issue with both US President Donald Trump and Vice President Mike Pence during his visit to th… https://t.co/fuIZbohUpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ @khloekardashian You are way too beautiful and sexy to put up with a man that won’t stop cheating on you.  Val… https://t.co/H397Y50iIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Dr. Phil's Chris Watts episode part 1... New information and new confession... Not the best quality but it's be… https://t.co/3MpIh0quro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowboy6pak @gle327 @laurie988 @rpx53 @BradSollberger @LarryZak4 @lilmscass @Dori30036555 @ChicagosFines19… https://t.co/UfZiJDX2w8]]></document></documents></author>