<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat Watch out! Sometimes when you rub his back, he lifts his hind leg and pees on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times #chocolatecity fun nights @ The Payback Oakland https://t.co/rxPjYYeWRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST MAKING FOOLS OF YOU GAME. REMEMBER WHEN THE STATES HOLD HOSTAGE AMERICAN PEOPLES LEGAL RIGHTS TO LAND TRUTH AN… https://t.co/q0LVNXfUfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I hate to be a party pooper, but I was in a horrible auto accident in 1985.Wait there’s more. Horrible back an… https://t.co/UvvdsbrsdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonHodgson @ThomasJTobin1 @AttyTMD It’s not a good look. Shame in the doctrinal sense can exist in an earthly s… https://t.co/rcDd5kz7Lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aqui vamos nós! #UFCWichita 9demarço  Here we go!  #UFC #march9th #coachDaruStrong #AmericanTopTeam  #GymKing… https://t.co/cQwbtNrqkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my birthday is to ride for @aidslifecycle and to finish! Your donation today would help me get there! I’m… https://t.co/6m6x9zr1FN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill the only ones that look up to AOC are the ones that have the same IQ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This St. Patrick’s Day, I’m giving back by supporting @GuinnessUS and #StacheForCharity. Are you in? Learn more her… https://t.co/63kKHrguJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asteristico @Vakeroporno Nomas pregunto, ¿Como hubiera sido tu vida en la escuela desde la primaria a la prepa si… https://t.co/rBjwmAtGvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[BNP Paribas Open with wifey @christiehuynh #novakdjokovic #djokovic #1 #naomiosaka #osaka #1 #atp #wta #indianwells… https://t.co/hHmPbYRsnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like my event tomorrow is cancelled due to "threat of snow" so far nosnow tho @ Embassy Suites Alexandria VA… https://t.co/Qvf5oRgIh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up, Doc? 🐰 I’m back stateside 🇺🇸 and in a few days, I will be checking-off a huge item on my bucket list. CA… https://t.co/EIEp5QyXUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small gets a swinging strike 3 to retire the side, we go to B1.  MSU has Mangum, Jordan, and Westburg due up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteinmetzNBA On the radio you sound like Howard Eskin @SportsRadioWIP @howardeskin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Bullshit! Sometimes we don’t have a choice but to take out loans to further our education. Sometimes… https://t.co/wRESDpGC72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans this new Ghost Adventures is so unsettling! @GhostAdventures]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 State Championship Broadcasts in 24 hours on the @nfhsnetwork to wrap up another week #NHIAA @ Manchester, New Ha… https://t.co/lr0beW6TLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The look I got when I asked for a pint at breakfast, true Englishman in New York ay x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMikeD42 @moodyredhead @drzack87 @TRHLofficial So bimetallic systems are unlimited in supply?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Excuse, but the climate has been changing since the planet formed.  The climate will continue to chan… https://t.co/haGoc9uUdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytpolitics Depends a lot on which ox is gored, and how extensive are the injuries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougPolkPoker when you answered did you say"whats up guys? doug polk here!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnerKay But there is a fair amount of evidence that just giving poor people money does in fact improve many area… https://t.co/G9iGrnuWXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MosesJJames @BobsBurgersFOX @anthemgame She was on The Office (US) as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance No! We want to take away your hamberders. You can have as many hamburgers as your pudgy little self wants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s spot on. Robbing future generations of unprecedented opportunities]]></document><document><![CDATA[So out of curiosity I looked up my rising sun and rising moon sign or whatever, and they’re the exact opposite of e… https://t.co/8kaSwqoGc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @KamalaHarris Even she knows it’s make believe time in never, neverland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 @AOC @BernieSanders @CoryBooker @TheDemocrats In the current system it is highly likely that every p… https://t.co/bJO4L3uh3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCToronto MISSING WOMAN - Gabriella Antoine - Missing since Jan 23rd. She has a medical condition that affects co… https://t.co/UjWmF4M6qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews The idea of racism is obsolete. You need to look past the color of someone's skin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bren123Luke Bushi and Kinny (the second one is because of his accent but still hilarious)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog’s really going through the same trauma we went through as kids when we first saw this scene]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Red Rams and Red Hawks will tip momentarily here at OCC! Catch @SachChristopher and I on the call at… https://t.co/2JbxTElfDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALGANCTNwx My Honda Generator carb looks like it has Shellac inside. During our selling old home, shopping for new… https://t.co/ViEMstxr07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa Give anyone who wants such a payment one Confederate dollar in token compensation and then move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex63222302 @JohnKircher4 @deadstock_9 @AdamSchefter Wentz was a MVP candidate two years ago... https://t.co/aHlHUyMXwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Day! Week 2 of February. Today is the perfect day for self love. Because practicing love to others is th… https://t.co/GcZTX5wtBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesilberman Can you imagine being a member of the Secret Service, on presidential detail?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shripadde Happy customers stay, they tell others, they can be case studies. Sales and acquisition is expensive, ma… https://t.co/e5XLwtXISx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonJLangley @amybuss @EAbanatha @heatherwarrell @MrsDoolin @Msbrandynew @mrsgregory03 @w_york @MrsWyattsClass… https://t.co/VEd9ZWSEdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @JohnDelaney Who's the biggest Communist you have interviewed so far.  Such a plethora to pick from.  Any Patchouli wearers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both Matt and I are already in bed sick as a dog. Gnight ppl. Lml #iactuallydontlml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Listen to Ken Dulin, and vote #Trump2020 Bio Non Degradable #Indie #Country #Rock #Blues #Singer… https://t.co/71UWIAVAJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoudBluePeg @BPPPpiranhapig Don't forget to make your first tweet when you get there, 'Hey, Utah! I'm in you!" You… https://t.co/CdSdHG1BRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillestadCara @girlsreallyrule @FunkyGallina Sorry, I haven't seen that, but if I do, I will be as quick to lectur… https://t.co/Cou0otzwru]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t even know what i would do with 52 pink flamingos, but you better believe i entered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IESTroutman @CCC_GR AND apparently YOU have a hard time dealing with that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday! #project996 #wassergekühlt #porsche #911 @ Caledon, Ontario https://t.co/oA3jatGZjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[These freshman are beginning their first lesson in the COJUSD Google Certified Student Program. Lesson 1: How to Sc… https://t.co/qnqSkVx69P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting tatted tonight and get to see trin Eli And Kenzie so that’s lit]]></document><document><![CDATA[action bronson : we're all about elegance and nothing but fine dining.....body, what's ur favorite food of all time… https://t.co/qu06DbQEgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdracing I couldn't stop cheering for you yesterday Matt. So happy to see such a talented wheelman get the oppo… https://t.co/7JugELebPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpporter @charliekirk11 @thomastrout21 @GOP Tax cuts do not 'give' people money, they allow people to keep more of… https://t.co/qHJUzi5oqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1percent Art Claus puts them in the Same too Clauses they Just got out of. " The People think you will Remodel… https://t.co/uvvzmRpsLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a great #TaxTimeTunes morning jam...  🎧 The General by @dispatchmusic on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Ei1nriFR0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris #JussieSmollett America can't have people running for president that make snap judgments about a case… https://t.co/ExihBi5ijM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rocc590 @bschaeffer12 I’ll tell you what, this would make a great private text chain between the two of you!  🤣  I keed, I keed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cadbury hiring chocolate taste-taster to work for $14 per hour https://t.co/ZQvrZnpRGy #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jl-  how many would you teach? C- less than 20 and I would teach them art Jl- why art? C- you want more art like mi… https://t.co/M0QBX21AQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind sophomore standout Cameron Binder’s (@cambinder2) postseason heroics, including the game winner in their 30-… https://t.co/Ua0RtGhPij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being dead is like being stupid: it’s only painful for others. @rickygervais 😳😂🤣 #FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Willie u r a legend n a icon to ur fan no need for apologies. U r a master n artist god bless u .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion and LeGroin lead Sportscenter every night and neither have done anything in 2 weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to personal reasons, I will continue to like these “due to personal reasons” tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sip. Hará falta una operación Ira de Dios. Auque no creo que haya una Golda Meier en la política venezolana. Salvo,… https://t.co/LQoXsZfagv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why The Keto Diet Will Change Your Life | Mark Sisson on Health Theory https://t.co/XKjUq8aHjB via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 @Grudecks AB ? Dude what’s going on Bills just backed out ? Anyone want you ? Your so great ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveMyHusband8 @pattistarz Suffice to say I wasnt happy with it. If they wanted us to fight, we would have...just ask. #90DayFiance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Ramsey!!! 1-nil, Arsenal. #COYG #AFC #FOYS #TOTARS #NLD #NorthLondonDerby #NorthLondonIsRed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1AndOnlyChicken Nothing is a given at this point.  There may not be a new site. I’m working on a few things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ievamikalauskas Helps me be more productive at work, i get my hustle on to try and block out whatever negativity is dragging me down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tempura Brie and Shishito Peppers | Thai chili Mago dipping sauce #myfab5 #food52grams #philly #insta #foodporn… https://t.co/PpcaXY11nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bye bye👋👋, underarm #sweat!💦  Hello, confidence with @miraDry!   #ArmGoals #DrGrantStevens #MarinaPlasticSurgery… https://t.co/MNxlUsKnCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephsAmusic can't wait for tonight to see the show, not only see the show to see the most beautiful woman stephan… https://t.co/u6IBAnSSu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; Mrs. Jones......   We got a thang going on!!!! @ STIXX https://t.co/KOMBSegorq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@20committee @TheRickWilson Conservatives have embraced as their voice the most vile grifting kooks every assembled… https://t.co/CnptZfLIrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GracePeekHarris @NoMoreMrNiceGa1 Not OPD, Sheriff's Department.  Still confused with who is who in this city.  Lol… https://t.co/eD1K7n2px3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to join @MezcalElSilencio tonight for An Evening of Black Magic. See you tonight @maxnosleeves &amp; Pat! #MESBlackMagic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PatrickPryor @XoneWhite Pat got me running #TheAnthonyWhiteProject back again…]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro i need some new music. i’m waiting for Salice Rose &amp; Jeslyn to drop their music 😤😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years ago was a night and a game I’ll never forget!! Let it fly Seniors!! #ThankYouSeniors #gozags @ZagMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought maybe he had a stellar prof from a Harvard or LSE up his sleeve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ballislife @SwaptySports Bro shut you have enough relationships with officials 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to sound cruel but Jim Boeheim killing a pedestrian on a highway isn’t all that surprising to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penguins fans, If you encounter a @NHLFlyers fan on @facebook/@Twitter  today during the #StadiumSeries game. Just… https://t.co/Uw1tCE0U0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Madison, WI? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/CVpIoUM4Pp #SkilledTrade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davesportsgod @JasonLawhead @davesportsgod knows I’ve been asked a lot how I became one of boxing’s top announcers… https://t.co/d4nUTP77vO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socialistcity Who are the people in this branch. Do you have your own emoji?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me : I should get Skyrim again! Me after playing Skyrim for 6 hours: FUUUUUUUUUUUUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanHirabayashi @MaryKelliPalka @emdrums @markfromjax @Wayfair Omg. The girls need one, no two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateJake25 Mostly it doesn't matter because he'd be foolish to pass up baseball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Sad and TRUE STATEMENT SIR!!! How long till we have a MUSLIM Congress and Senate? #nofakenewshere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackpocketBrew Luke gave me outstanding service and I am very pleased with the beers you had available. I’ll be back soon..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried shooting it from half court earlier today and it looked just like this...maybe you can do better and yours… https://t.co/sVJk6NoGSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my this girl stopped hanging out when I got with my ex. Turns out she was jealous. She ended up killing my pot p… https://t.co/dMwlu6P09A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bridging #shoalcreek #dailywalk #urbantrail #atx #atxphotographer  #getolympus #omdem1 #olympusem1 #texas #street… https://t.co/xyeF7Z7FL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisTravale I feel that all Twitter accounts should use their real name. Example @alanstrang2 @AmyFor6  .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frigginhiramguy @tuesdiwoodworth Beats the pants off almond. Almond? Are you fucking kidding me? Almond?]]></document></documents></author>