<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 13 - 5 Things for New Day:   Border security deal;   Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzmán;     North Korea;… https://t.co/VxwVyZJjwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venuslilith1 @Stephane196301 @tvanouvelles @MarieRose42 Villaneuva, ça cest le p'tit incompris qui a essayé de dés… https://t.co/OhP2kATl74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @drawandstrike @nytimes @adamgoldmanNYT @matthewhaag Attempting a coup that’s treason hang em all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Child neglect is failing to protect your children from a known danger.  The anti-science anti-vaxxers will put a he… https://t.co/O5vGPtWk4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣Titan of industry, and seminal Black storyteller, @SpikeLee has won his FIRST #Oscar for Best Adapted Screenplay.… https://t.co/i0MCVivzmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @NBCLA @AdrianNBCLA @DaniellaNBCLA @ShannaNBCLA @alyshadelvalle @latrafficgal @ToniNBCLA @AnnetteNBCLA… https://t.co/wdCNuf6Mcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SailorSlob I honestly feel the same way. I wanted more from this game after a 14 year wait. I wanted the story to… https://t.co/xrDeR4XP2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jchandlerteach @aaron_hogan @TeacherMyth @BarbaraGruener @froehlichm Appreciate that shoutout for #ThePepperEffect, my Bandmate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deplorableHills @hjhoosier @Oh_Lovelacee @JimEvans24 @AOC Do you enjoy carrying the water for billionaires with ne… https://t.co/CvaCwB9sv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are selling snake oil. Tax returns are no measure. A tax return  is an excess amount of money an employer had w… https://t.co/WYJZADox0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indeed, teachers in the classroom should aspire to- and be required to- possess and TEACH those qualities...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhinosOutsider @League1Fun @HomeSweetSoccer @USLLeagueOne @RochesterRhinos @oak_brigade @Daniel_Volkovas Definitely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homesweethome #canada🇨🇦 #saturday #ilovethiscountry❤️🇨🇦 en Sainte-Foy–Sillery–Cap-Rouge https://t.co/jUT8XDh5A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canbewhoischris @macyv_ @wheredatwifi Bro we’re grown, we all have skeletons in our closest. No ones perfect. Im n… https://t.co/Vb85nncEFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the “Changes That Heal” seminar with Dr. Henry Cloud! Join us for this free CITY-WIDE seminar as Dr. Clou… https://t.co/qtLVfSB8Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joejuba @elisefavis Joe what was your alter ego where you had a handlebar moustache and wore a trucker hat for a week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my nanas bacon and eggs and I miss my grandpa cooking shit I had seen him kill myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devils add one run in 3rd on Lunt RBI single, scoring Norman. 18-3 Red Devils.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I finally did it!!! ••• Happy Birthday to me, as Vicki said yes to spending the rest of her life with me! I c… https://t.co/ut41pH9hNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch When Obama could not swear on the Bible at both inaugurations after saying that he was Christian. Th… https://t.co/shQGMOgJJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatVazquez91 Awe... that’s so sweet of youuuu.... https://t.co/0iefdvI6Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real question is:  Principals: Will you push yourself to adjust your policies and behaviors based on the result… https://t.co/VtJNbccKbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 20 years since James’s twin, James Leonard (JL) arrived here and immediately went to heaven. We know he’s… https://t.co/SC1XwGhPgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilfSherriff @Manateejay @jizzlich Hahahaha  That made me think of Ivan Ooze from the power rangers movie https://t.co/MbbpS0NDut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMPACTWRESTLING   Ok not body shaming but it really looks like Allie got some work done, in that skit with RoseMar… https://t.co/1VoHu0mNCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @AaronGoodwin @jaywasley @GhostAdventures I’m watching the Phoenix Gold Mine episode and I went to thei… https://t.co/EKLdLqYdpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frpaul1 @ArchitectsDCA @ladybugspicnic Wait wait wait.....  There's a half plowed bike lane down there?  Up here..… https://t.co/d93BBTxCpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fernandeznorona Todo el PT voto a favor.. primero hable con su partido.. Saludos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sniff009 @Keith2TheCity I'm stunned on this trade as that's a solid 2nd 3rd line pick up]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love having a rant twitter account because who the fuck else is gonna listen to me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack5heridan @ThPattyMatthews @OldTakesExposed @JDebrusk @ChrisEvans Seems like your bad at a #TwitterWar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow @chucktodd Ask Joe "how many Americans must die before he would declare National Emergency???]]></document><document><![CDATA[AT LEAST AMERIKA'S ATHEISTS HAVE THE "DECENCY" TO LEAVE GOD OUT, BUT ITS "CHRISTIANS" ADD "GOD," AND THUS NO "MORAL… https://t.co/tlD8No4ET0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be really surprised if the #NHL doesn’t announce Houston in the next year. Gotta even out the league.]]></document><document><![CDATA[where is my wife? i’m more than willing to step out of the being horny on the tl game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump: The Long Road to the White House (1980 - 2017) https://t.co/dirTEcV8FG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidebrady @MailOnline Well the hair on the affected skin turns white as well. I got a little of it going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@temcmillan @ReginaClewlow @tpap_ @CaltransHQ Yes but no one is talking about the longest mile, which is why people… https://t.co/V6QXLqq4ZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiansTrump @TrumpOSU @NBADonaldTrump @Indians @TheRealSlamtana You don't know that. Nobody has the pitching we h… https://t.co/2gybGGW1zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdUtica1 @TheAthleticNHL Hi Ed. I do hope you’ll reconsider. Here is a link to a free trial, so you can read the s… https://t.co/XNUwHJpnZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole09322402 @AristemoFans @NeonBreaker @Pukerainbows7 @SCorcega18 @GIOVANICORSA @JessYaoi @MomentosDAmorHD… https://t.co/zLDoqUJ8nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunshine moved from Austin, Texas to join PHA in August, 2017. While in Austin, Sunshine spent a decade directing d… https://t.co/1nttR1dart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruins win! Breaking Chicagos 7 game winning streak. Have a safe night everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Two To The Dome by @3starsbrewing at @MrBeerysSRQ — https://t.co/yRbQtMOEfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradydonnelly You can't beat the old fashioned warmth of a good ole heat stove. ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Aquariano @atleastRESPEKit It’s always ugly broke people who actually look like rats trying to call someone trash😂😂😂🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chupiband @MariaCorinaYA @PoleoRafael Yo no insulto a MCM, ni remotamente. Me parece que es la madre de la abstenc… https://t.co/j6Fd7CIALP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really go on morning walks to watch the sunrise like I’m 80 years old?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Though the cue ball stands alone and out of focus it is the one who moves everything along.  Never be afraid to sta… https://t.co/Cp2BlG3xq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've made plenty of dumb purchases from advertisements that pop-up on my Twitter timeline.   This is by far my favo… https://t.co/E0TKf9PADx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESUGARDAD1 my 7th yr Wedding Anniversary is in 2 weeks. What a gift! 💴 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epicciuto This has all been really helpful to some of us not definitely diagnosed, but for whom this all has been… https://t.co/Gs4eHMATvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is complaining that the NCAA owes Zion $. Zion could have been playing in the G league and getting paid. T… https://t.co/GeQpuFawNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wellllllll I’m here for this, dammit let’s go KUUUUUUI!💪💪💪💪#kubball https://t.co/XHGIIXq1wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brinich1 @StevESPNKim @DAZN_USA these guys look out of shape and way past their prime]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a body on a sidewalk tonight around 2am. I asked a nearby business about him, and was told he's a bad dude, a… https://t.co/OTV0v2gXQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look closely. Is it just me or does it look like R Kelly really can fly? 😂😂😂 #idontsmoke @ Quickmode Studio https://t.co/ck1D0LqxWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonydombrowski @anzalone_cam @UnloadedM @RapSheet I'm sorry?!?! we sell out an  70000   seat Stadium weekly. To sa… https://t.co/ZfEmaeLmZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBallgame1 HOW DID MCNALLY GET A COPY OF THAT KEY TO GO INTO THE OFFICIAL'S LOCKER ROOM? WHY DID BRADY SMASH HIS P… https://t.co/2PycbZcVUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredssolomon @SaraLove4MD Your bill today (HB 1091) is also common sense. #MDGA19]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Patient Care Technician, Clinic PCT job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and… https://t.co/WnPCKJlyY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coralsncaves @AlongsideWild Should be more of a gap (undercut) between neck/flippers and shell if a real turtle? I… https://t.co/kfzFWymiDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the @Jeopardy #JeopardyAllStars? Neither can my arrogance, classlessness, and non-display of sportsm… https://t.co/jWMNmZCpMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also recall how they tried to fuck contractors out of pay when they closed for, like...ice or w/e. DC is trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Larrys Place by @nickelbeerco at @nickelbeerco — https://t.co/jPWg60Ot8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 18 years of free clinics (I grew up poor), 20 years of military dentists, and 8 years of bouncing around, I c… https://t.co/l8uLGCwLN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ISTA_1501 Неее, это из интернетов. Мой старший пожелал маме сильно любить папу ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gateway #NYC . . . #washingtonheights #manhattan #160th #nyc #nycphotographer  #streetphotography #street… https://t.co/Q1qC2p3bCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to talk with executive directors about #nptech for @nonprofnetwork soon!  https://t.co/9eKeOxcdSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zylogram @AdamMaloon Wow this blew up, everyone check out @zylogram's SoundCloud here https://t.co/Y1FQBtydNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[quotable Wyc Grousbeck: “Danny [Ainge] would throw his mother in for the right trade.” #truth @celtics  🏀🍀💥 #SSAC19… https://t.co/lpTuxwuJKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again (in complete opposition to Maduro):   A few things not mentioned:  1. "Black-Gold" (Oil) = $$$$ 2. Elliott Ab… https://t.co/3eOkqvNpLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y cuál es la preocupación de usted ?será que ya no le tocará su mochada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dick_nixon Big Venezuelan expat community in Puerto Rico, and lots of Puerto Ricans have moved to the I-4 Corridor… https://t.co/av1ILYO3p3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In interview, Roseanne Barr calls #MeToo founders ‘hos,’ says @KamalaHarris 'slept her way to the bottom' “Look at… https://t.co/GrFfmMdutv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Hemsworth Reportedly to Play WWE Legend Hulk Hogan in Netflix Biopic https://t.co/65znPwyBq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNC is just flat out making a statement. Zion or no Zion still 4 McDonald’s all Americans for Duke on the court]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xestern_ @IGN Lol nobody said that. Also that's not about the movie. That's you literally being mad about what som… https://t.co/VeRdlNtTjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION BALERS!! Happy Monday, In your homeroom today remember to vote Sofia Lemos as your ASB Vice President! 🐻🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clintellis Twitter on my phone crops the photo where only the Cardinals cap is displayed. I’m not bothering to ope… https://t.co/2bsKBOoQJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[# just see it   @luchsasaras @Fernand31004793 @austinmalestonr @AustinLuchasar2 @Valerie_Perez @ImDanaDeLorenzo… https://t.co/PqVweBmyle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paparazzi in Italian means fly on the wall. These little insect bites will end up spying on everyone. It’s not scie… https://t.co/sLoqTQp1GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guardian: Rumours of rift between Saudi King Salman and MBS https://t.co/4uTq5A2CYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying family time and all the rodeo riding before Panic! at the Disco. #rodeohouston #familytime @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/ExQQTaKZIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imogenrose Question everything...where were these kids parents? Who is comfortable letting their children sleep in… https://t.co/Y9xmu1DiWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot sauce goes on and in greens. I’m scared of what our workd@has become without this truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @alaannual (Or, better yet, come on my podcast @circideas  and let librarians know how much you love us.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr  Let’s understand this: donnie tRump does not, not has he ever cared about America… https://t.co/HXpFiYlCB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbiemiller @SwissLehman @freeboulder A witness yesterday addressed how false reporting does not get punished with… https://t.co/GfXC7JSIkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDCgov has reported that gun violence in America was 40K deaths in 2018 the highest level in 40 years.  The next P… https://t.co/zOZe4KV5Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaylaniTatz @AnaliseYoel Would you like to use my PIN to let your dirty text dear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Every day 342 people are shot with a gun. Why is @realDonaldTrump ignoring that? Instead, he spends his tim… https://t.co/GAnVyDfmVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just talked to @wheelerallen2 and I can confirm he’s coming out of retirement to train me for the famous heater flip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunshine &amp; Peace of Mind💋 . . . #vibes #selflove #sunshine #issavibe #foodandwine #selfcare #chef #privatechef… https://t.co/0BxPGNEToF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you fucked up at work when the there’s a wide school email about what not to do after you messed up on simple procedures 🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job by the Keynote speaker, Mayor March @ the Latin Chamber of Commerce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@settlemlCFB @MannyM83 @sneakerseminole @DMFrank_ @ahaf21 This could be the first test in branching out the storyli… https://t.co/iGmvdCv6sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I had a pit-Lab mix named Penny Lane, who passed away, four years ago, from lymphoma. She was the swee… https://t.co/VlITntIxdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first few @onepeloton #Tread workouts have been doable but exhausting. I love it. #sweat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Las Vegas Nevada. I just want to remind you that it’s not supposed to snow in the city! That’s why Mt Charlest… https://t.co/LDeM3BAAxA]]></document></documents></author>