<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@darkangelx1 @People4Bernie @BernieSanders Well it was in DC (wish I’d have been able to go to it) but you’re right… https://t.co/Ijy5SvBw4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you invite me over for some ass and I show up and you got no sheets on your bed just know I’m gonna turn right a… https://t.co/7HrbuZiR8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanPayton please contact Commander John Callahan of the local VFW POST 7286 - 985-264-6767 He’s been leaving mess… https://t.co/0VacjprnJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one last try on for you this week and it is from @aerie! This adorable romper comes in three different color… https://t.co/P5IeV8FaBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amonymoush @boglethemind @AydeleB @4everleather1 @Sarah_Q_Smithy @sleeper_awoke @patrici61580698 @MasterDuke1… https://t.co/wP2AXBnvg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Cassie broke up with Colton and then said are you mad at me was the funniest moment in bachelor history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz If writing for a newspaper doesn't make you a journalist, I'm not sure what your litmus test would be. I… https://t.co/XqNzCdhxOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omar_spring @vexingpython340 @OMGSTF @bradchad4eva @orlando_smart @HoneyGuwop @King_llamaa Who tf said I was a “li… https://t.co/XF8oJnyBHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice going Altitude Sports.   Is there such a thing as a freelance editor, where I make sure everything is spelled… https://t.co/Il0i925RQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I simply do not have room for my cowboy boots in my suitcase. I’m so sorry people of the United Kingdom. I’ve failed you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDebateHitman @StephenAtHome @SenSanders @SenWarren @AOC Compare his accomplishments to @SenWarren]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayfreddy4 Exactly. Always wanna pay less for education and expect more 👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast 🔥 I ate all the chorizo and eggs already 🤣✌😋 @ Stockton, California https://t.co/002P7pdNKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Leach crossed 23M. Time 06:13:58, pace 15:40 min/mile, est. finish 1:04 pm https://t.co/pvg8ZsgFgJ #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @JIDsv still working on that R&amp;B only album he was talking about🤔🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amazon @Google #Facebook @TheJusticeDept #antitrust :@ewarren on ur case. Retweet. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is you Tag # Instagram is all about using the right set of popular and brand specific hashtags to get your pos… https://t.co/FXqb6O7Xfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[But we just radio edited it to “Let’s Get It Started” so it’s fiiiiiine 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMTheHighway Does he have a website or something to share the story? I’d love to share the whole sound byte you played in the radio 📻]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s Some shit I’ve been through that I haven’t told NOBODY about. Not my mom, dad, siblings or even close friends...]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Student tweets 🐥 #whyiread #PositivelyPWCS #pwcs #ReadAcrossAmerica #readacrossamerica2019 #reading #fun… https://t.co/AlCsTskG94]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm cold!! My side of our heated Mattress pad is wonky and only works for 5 minutes and to reset it..well, it's a p… https://t.co/YpoKHPwXrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in Toronto and going through all my footage from New York. Four days, 20 gigs of footage, and at least two new… https://t.co/DAgXxOKzXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Telephone Sales" in #Muskegon, MI. Go on informational interviews. The best way t… https://t.co/sMK2LbA5jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan u r boring on the five and your opinions r taken with a grain of salt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabbbbygloriaa @_mumbunz I am a nurse. And if you read the comments all of that is covered. The whole point is for… https://t.co/JZYZK4gay6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni @CNN @FoxNews @MSNBC @realDonaldTrump @EmpireFOX @TherealTaraji @terrencehoward @JussieSmollett @CNN @FoxNews… https://t.co/UerlYQTKAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud mom...my daughter and her team competed in Northern California Volleyball Assocation's President Day Tourname… https://t.co/aaK6cgxPeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malave_nancy @DrodriguezVen @VTVcanal8 @tattianac5 @Yudithh99 @cainecagua @MagdaNueva @mcolozzal2021 @Deci3003… https://t.co/Ovy58ljr6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @TokyoBorn1234 Of course he did, it's payback for Saudi's forgiving Ivanka's 100 mil diamond scam… https://t.co/HY6Ilxz9X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 Exactly, I agree  This whole Feinstein fiasco was propaganda and disinformation from within the Dem party… https://t.co/p8k3TiaXLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone surprised that @anthonykernaz is a piece of garbage? The former cop was fired for dishonesty and lying. N… https://t.co/DRqyTDKi9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please take the time to read this thread on ADHD. Whether you’re struggling with it, know someone who is, or just w… https://t.co/KqEMRnu9ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw an ad for la Croix on a Crystal springs truck. This is America]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 35 minutes into #TheBachelor and I've yelled at the TV 163 times. https://t.co/gLlCrOUp3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann is right. This is like the preacher's kids who don't get the attention they need because the parent is too busy… https://t.co/k0mtp9eZS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Hit me hard when #traitortrump shoo'd American journalists away then entertained russian security in the… https://t.co/RGrHJoX250]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliasmakos @mitchgarber All together 🤝👌😉⚾️❤️💪👍 https://t.co/OBA9ZRaJji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh they didn't tow you?! Uh no but if you are removed you will not be coming back ever !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenmadigan I always thought they were movies starring the DeVitos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdyBarkan Thank you for all the work you're done on these issues.  And I wish you and your family all the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beatles had 3 hits on the billboard that were GOOD.  AND they were a revolutionary group.   Ariana has talent b… https://t.co/aYmqvVZsym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habitchuallyhay I feel kinda bad about it, but then I just go about my day singing “I want it, I got it” and forget how embarrassing I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve noticed that EVERY time UVA turns off the ball, an announcer says “a rare turnover for UVA”.  This has been a thing for a few weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiKettering @Cooper_DebraR Congrats! Nolan all of your hard work is paying off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbyMook @TeamPelosi Also, Michael Cohen if you’re listening Can you do us a solid and incriminate pence tomorrow… https://t.co/p9gRK8dbNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[To anyone who sees this rn.. I posted a new nail set video on YouTube. If you wanna check it out that'd be dope!! H… https://t.co/hS0ySKvydS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiigggerrr @RealJamesWoods @SpeakerPelosi No. This is part of our Washington’s Birthday Celebration. It is called… https://t.co/lNHdiWRRy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Haley!!! Thanks for being such a great friend, i hope you have the best day!! I love you girly 💛💛🎉🎉🌼 https://t.co/35wfovqgue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChauncyOnTV @abc13houston I just did without my WiFi for 12 hours. I DIDN’T LIKE IT!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabsNGripes @Dax_x98 THANK YOU! I NEEDED A LITTLE  VIRTUAL LOVE! I DON'T KNOW WHY I GET UPSET OVER STUPID PEOPLE! LOL ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portugal has found an antidote to right wing populism https://t.co/L0MZ3EzYQy via @Kontrast_at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahDrake628 Yes Hannah!!!! I've always been a fan of you &amp; your passion. Love u CHICA😙😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kk_rae_ab I do not defend it, in fact I have been put in Twitter Jail for my criticism of the horrible, barbaric p… https://t.co/XC2AijVtYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rizmc Look!!! PD named a K9 officer after you!! (Why he’s pumping gas, I don’t know.) #bodhi #RogueOne #StarWars https://t.co/gQ7ep5gm0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsraelUSAforevr You’re going to make him scream? Uh, ok, TMI. I guess...make sure to use protection?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when ex's trash your name after you break up with them. Nah, I didn't feed you for 6 months or try to wait f… https://t.co/iN3X3vu3wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; they can’t steal the love you’re born to find🖤 https://t.co/qGtHR5klv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our mom and dad in ministry @bishophilliard @PastorBHilliard  Thank you for your importation ❤️❤️❤️ @ New Light Chr… https://t.co/Hrjjh3SzzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moore_pabst @wada_woo This has gone on for years near the downtown bars. I used to see some of this during gigs.… https://t.co/SDJsTlRgw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started out cool and cloudy but much better this afternoon in Paradise Island, Bahamas. @ Paradise Island Bahamas https://t.co/40lvUybSdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a cereal date while we sit and look at city lights while we discuss some existential crisis. Until we both g… https://t.co/WnpYkiOC83]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘SPEECHLESS’: Top 5 moments from ‘S-P–SPECIAL B-O–BOY T-I–TIME’ https://t.co/hLvGgoEwZU  @masoncook @BrotiGupta… https://t.co/6x4gI8t5At]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_staal @LRPow79 https://t.co/JY5bpRIv75, and @SaxMike71 is my friend there. We will find you! Don't give up… https://t.co/NFWQSrwzAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Khloé you should also bring showing True not to admonish other women....what you’re doing she True… https://t.co/hRg1plKwM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a “fan art curation” account, use a repost application. Don’t poach art/photos and repost them. Don’t cr… https://t.co/kofd3bsVO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaneWalker2 @DavidBrothers1 Of course you can join! I agree, the last part I read discussed using the mode average… https://t.co/6kLl092bea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to come and delete Door Dash off my phone because it’s almost 2am and ya girl over here be like.... https://t.co/mH3KmEr5XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarceloMitnik Love this movie! Seen it six times! Happy Valentines Day to everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[fr I’m such a stubborn ass bitch I swear when people tell me not to do something/off limits, makes me wanna do it a million times more]]></document><document><![CDATA[im sorry u guys have to see my face all the time but i just look so good all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get off at 6 but the oil change place doesn’t open until 7 🙃 #ijustwantmybed]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 days away #NYC! Faton Macula is a beast on that there #guitar. ✊ #NEWYORKCITY WHO 🤓: Singer/Songwriter/Actor krod… https://t.co/vxea5BZAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been following @jarvisguidedog as long as I have followed You, Dave. You both have taught me a great deal ab… https://t.co/vnbeuYpcwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever be on someone’s page just scrolling and you forget you ain’t on the TL and just keep retweeting their shit, yeah same... gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[moves for saturday 👀👀👀 make it happen for @TonyRomo4409 https://t.co/0PHeyWdEsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYP_Brooksie @nypostsports Henrik is sad about more than the loss of Zuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m offering intuitive readings at thebagladyintuitivegifts this Wednesday from 10-2 (link in bio to book) let’s ex… https://t.co/CZVKQFmVpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafiyahNoor1 @MTrued @KenDilanianNBC This reminds me of George Michael when he went to a public restroom in west h… https://t.co/QBfde7BV36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @NYCREMilton @pkamla1 @m_ainihi @AmandaRay02 @CarlosD27801704 @YuHelenYu @HelpBefore @Sky13861654… https://t.co/xjjpDlUDxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dietitian told me i should see a therapist like umm excuse me do I reek of sad bitch!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain U got to wait till u own ur own stuff   it's kind of like u using other people  just be honest  it pissed… https://t.co/2H7FL1Aq37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a2dradio_com @Phillies @Bharper3407 315M FOR 10 YEARS  WITH  OPTIONS  RELEASED  AFTER  4,OR 5 YEARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we saw Zuckerberg the same way we see a chemical executive or anyone that runs a big comp, he may not have been… https://t.co/6ZoZYEY2jN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrZelensky @Mammals_Suck @NYCuratrix @bat_biomes @ashleyshammond @elcwt @KellySpeer @acaragiulo417 @Drew_Lab For m… https://t.co/EKHe7WyIxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raffa2006 @K9Loveofficial Okay I checked again, it was there!!  Yay!! I voted!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estamos en @LPQUSA aquí al lado de Central Park y entraron a cantar. Están cantando cielito lindo 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. We cannot truly change this unless we have diverse groups at the table together. Full stop. Who makes the polici… https://t.co/cKoU5Fb4i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndiSutton1 @GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Narcissistic And Borderline personality disorder: exagge… https://t.co/0obO1gC0Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @RepAdamSchiff Seriously?! 😂🤣😂🤣 He’s been saying that for 2 years and has yet to show us anything. Put up or shut up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_White Igot ask you to ask forgiveness for me I want to know what ido them satan did that please help me prayfreedom there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson @digital_crates why household and not individual? Would a single, childfree adult get the same as a… https://t.co/HSNwIaxKN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to stop becoming emotionally attached to fictional tv characters it’s ruining my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KodakBlack1k when you’re in Des Moines for the concert can you PLEEEEASE sing baby girl or down south bc I would die to hear that live 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most frustrating part of winter as a reporter is having to reschedule stories for a third time because of the w… https://t.co/FnXseTG8t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redbox how is it that I get a promo code but when I tried to use it it didn’t work...then I tried again and it sai… https://t.co/HsrDI4qfp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poor child... his country won’t treat his cancer because he is an orphan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richmondcat5 @rryjackson Oh nooo I was worried about this! I was just saying, i can’t believe there’s anything to… https://t.co/P19YpJrYE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last five years, since dmarshiii have been living in California it’s been such a crazy ride filled with ups and… https://t.co/qCQ3p9q7dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi i hate reading and i have read 2 whole books in 2 days. College makes you do crazy things man]]></document></documents></author>