<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JTJ24 Could not agree more.  The real challenge is to have these men play out the season without worry about their… https://t.co/v19k1yDTc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimAmosWV @WillieAtFLO @wvssac This is the time of year where I find out if I’m still blocked by the @wvssac and t… https://t.co/kjHJinMX9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromBenC @DEANintheYAY @CALmatters Don’t listen to the haters. The cartogram has consistently been the most popula… https://t.co/nPbZxxrg3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[But seriously, a guy who won’t do something they teach in Little League just signed the largest contract in America… https://t.co/oJHyWrw5EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super2ndsMrsJ OMGOSH all your games make me feel like a dinosaur! lol I had to grow up with only Atari PONG!! https://t.co/GZKLK7C7aA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My accounting professor might go to hell after this https://t.co/lSPEz3nCOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotcouponmama @ORobHarris @MayorHodson @JKaseOR @dirquez @OregonGovBrown It is quite honorable that she chooses pe… https://t.co/92dyr6rlm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaf fans who have tickets &amp; can’t make tonight’s game due to weather: https://t.co/1nPeySJBxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT  LORD, WE ARE… https://t.co/J3PqEsESqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMUrbanView @karenhunter @marcusglo Please help this guy w/your interview. He’s really struggling on air🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m wondering if y’all think the #Sixers can bounce back against the #Rockets. So please give me your votes. Who wins tomorrow’s matchup?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhymestyle  feeling the @Nanogenix  luck after downloading jp and summoning just once for the heck of it https://t.co/WYdnav5Vzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoyWire @WeekendExp DYK @penguins Phil Kessel is the 17 American born @NHL player to score 800 points in his career]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_c243 @ThePoniExpress It’s cool bud as bad as you wanted to call me daddy it’s never going to happen.  Just get over it and move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eflow_egiap Sometimes you don’t really know that you’re in the good ol days until you leave them. Safe travels Winston.  😞😞🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @gmbutts Okay, so if there's nothing to see and everyone should move along  why did Mr Butts resign?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to switch the tags on hockey sticks at Dicks Sporting Goods to get $100 sticks for like $10]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the back of Luke’s head. @ Walnut Park, California https://t.co/99nG2rt4Xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandy Gutierrez Is Head Over Heels At The Blue Banana In Havana #chavezhighschool #classof2005 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/9Y8jDW2Mk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@samfinnerty3 caps a scoreless inning with his 6th strike out. Sam has faced only 1 over the minimum through 7 sco… https://t.co/CrMMZQpN8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venmo  your customer support is awful I have been trying to reach you to unfreeze the account which was wrongly frozen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse You’re a fucking moronic, insane, delusional liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Dekalb County Sheriff's Office just held a very brief press conference that did not reveal any new informat… https://t.co/ZiM3AZdj6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[RSA Cybersecurity Conference starts today. $PANW $CYBR PaloAlto and CyberArk in focus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @Merri__Magic a documentary after he has been indicted, convicted and imprisoned should be made to teach… https://t.co/AmVEbjNJGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I'm not mistaken start your engines car with just made by @LeahPritchettTF and @MattHagan_FC @OfficialMOPAR… https://t.co/6IRTVS2pnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aimeeterese Yeah. "Sincere" means "meets my specific standard. Ironically, "I'm sorry if you were offended" apolog… https://t.co/C80nogMHBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me, or is everyone really bitchy this morning??!! So annoying!!!🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foundinblank @naomicaselli @AdamCSchembri in the hashtag for the original video there are two interesting phrases:… https://t.co/0SULI00Hr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyNascar @chaseelliott @RonCapps28 @NAPARacing @NAPAAutoCare @eddiecolvin7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCun11960413 @NYPD @MinaMalikForDA @GregLasak @MelindaKatz @BettyLugoForQDA @CabanForQueens @JoseNievesForDA… https://t.co/CFqMk5AzFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is making our personal dozen donuts (@ Duck Donuts in Huntington Beach, CA) https://t.co/BtvTJzRqyk https://t.co/FbAxIEMHMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got so much work to do today and I’m not feeling well. But I want my weekend to be with my lady and my family so I gotta rock out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR @NASCARONFOX these cars are slow and this is not enjoyable to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you redbeth04 for giving us the low down on whiskey @drinkwellaustin today! #Sunday #Whiskey #History #Powers… https://t.co/tGkOF7IYbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you get this, the game changes for ever. Deuteronomy 8:18 #integrity #real #money #truth #selfgrowth… https://t.co/AGh1xxNf3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @TuckerCarlson @maddow @NicolleDWallace @SRuhle @Lawrence @chrislhayes @HardballChris But then how could… https://t.co/ho0fMD30Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabían que en los #Oscars hace un tiempo cambiaron la frase "And the winner is..." por "The Oscar goes to... " https://t.co/nTQYViQmi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It literally says on the card that I'm over age. Why does it fucking matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗞IN TODAY’S PAPER🗞  🏀Seniors from Genesee Region, Niagara-Orleans strap it up for exceptional senior game… https://t.co/ZI6p4n8PEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @PattyMurray @SenatorCantwell @TeamPelosi @SenSchumer "When the speech condemns a free… https://t.co/SyG3bqRr1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[So musical.... is going to be a puppet show this year? Okay😂I thought we had actors for a reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mama_O_G @wardsfowler @BretBaier True. All wing conspiracy is bad for us. 👍🏻👍🏽👍🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artie Lange February 16, 2008 Borgata Casino Hotel Event Center Atlantic City NJ  #artielange #comedyshow… https://t.co/gKxDXhh3sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabionPicheco @edgar224u We had one that would never ride in the trailer. Drop the tailgate he would climb in]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if you have a restroom exclusively for your group at your workplace but tell me, which guy has the bad… https://t.co/5XIYH9atR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyCarmelo2 @neileatson Couple of things. Why was the old guy the only person who stepped up to help. Lastly, pol… https://t.co/bZ5TYDAc6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ThunderNation Someone tell Russ to shut the fuk up you guys didn't battle you got the living s*** beat out of you… https://t.co/ETxNj10RUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mind Day light savings. #UnpopularOpinion https://t.co/uVlk95QHLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Political correctness is American liberalism’s biggest malady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that said, @joebudden smoked Crack so I’m not putting much stick into anything he has to say but I’m definitel… https://t.co/IELeO2xRCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the eve of livestreaming my 4th #spellingbee, I look back to 1996 when I represented my school in the regional b… https://t.co/QyT2AjJWWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Margaritas for Victors birthday! @ Ponce's Mexican Restaurant https://t.co/2VSaQxKoD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday at work, Maryland Democrats voted AGAINST an amendment that would require scholarships be given to Maryla… https://t.co/Jg11eNJRMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ruined #BlackHistoryMonth for me.   I had plans to honor the ancestors.  I was gonna put these White men in c… https://t.co/Tv8PDK3Io0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elex_Michaelson @BillFOXLA @FOXLA Finally Ed Buck is getting his glare in the media spotlight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump The orange suit should have been for bill &amp; Hillary Clinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the truth hurts! #DavidQuinones #DavidQuiñones #HolyGroundMusicGroupLLC #ShiloMedia #JohnArrington… https://t.co/eQgZLQNWzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnActualWizard @AuschwitzMuseum Kids will be kids until they chain a PoC behind their vehicle and drag him to his… https://t.co/BODufWgA76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sue51684 @gadiadelman @MamaMiaNOSharia @Tommythesider @PubliusNV @whiteshot I know why President Trump Wins , God… https://t.co/rf8dJs1SOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#64 #pictureoftheday #nofilter #labreatarpits chriss_petiteaux labreatarpits_museumstore @ La Brea Tar Pits https://t.co/6R6YAXjtT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abeardedshooter It's insane. A charter member of the American League and they are treated like shit. Bet your ass… https://t.co/uThIRYtE4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memphis ended up being an UV because his parents couldn't make it. But they're still planning on taking OV to WSU a… https://t.co/Lke2hLSn6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hiphop #rap #beats #music #SteadyGrindENT #duukie #silver @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/IEWJvRiJg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlintSkelly I was surprised myself to see all of these posted. Good 📰 nonetheless. 👍 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allbymyfandom @kaitcoaching I am with that!!!!!! 2nd Chances season!!! 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just beat my first Pokémon game! Let’s Go Pikachu was a really fun game (minus the throwing mechanic). Definitely… https://t.co/xiEFkTua3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Audio Dynamite - C'mon Every Beatbox https://t.co/7QRKluScTn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kausmickey Sounds good. Didn't expect you to go that previous round, took it as signal to continue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@averageman97 @think_again_7 @admill79 @altobelli_mark So mankind was not born in sin?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradA53472906 @theedwardrose @tetrickracing No incentive to try harder to improve product if they feel it’s a majo… https://t.co/C2uAEntilB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed this time and am excited that @abbyhamblin and @RunGomez are joining this important conversation!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love of god do not let Lin shoot the ball. It’s not working out]]></document><document><![CDATA[This from a CFR think tanker who was still touting Peña Nieto’s “ambitious reform package” in 2018. 2018!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDevilHistory That seems to be the thrust here. It wasn't Obama that opened up possibilities. It was Trump. If a… https://t.co/1ZN2v4T8oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennifoggteach Often important to any sort of accreditation process in for-profit schools. In non-profits, orgs mi… https://t.co/8CUzUpw4VS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicoleeasalazar oh idk i haven’t even attempted to listen to any of it. i don’t even like the regular song]]></document><document><![CDATA[captainmarvelofficial is here and it is stunning‼️💥One of my favorite MCU origin stories to date‼️ @brielarson kill… https://t.co/QU6vcwHsvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #InterceptorJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HereLiesMoon watched the ride this afternoon. Laughed at @KingScottRules concertina rejection. Honestly surprised… https://t.co/DV3zj60dRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If people know your too busy for them they stop asking you for things…they stop coming to you with life problems.”… https://t.co/Wuc3TvrAWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love God enough to trust Him and gain access to protection, compassion, refreshment, and wisdom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farm Boy just outside of Toronto is a brilliant supermarket and a great place to look at retailing ideas @ Whitby,… https://t.co/3mKuWPpNSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed for Ciampa. Interested to see which way the NXT Title goes with this next set of taping and the Mania Takeov… https://t.co/4qdLIJkU6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardDarsigny @CanadiensMTL @919sports J était le premier à dire qu’il a connu son meilleur match de l année la semaine dernière 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast The best outcome is for @realDonaldTrump to leave the presidency a distroyed man an a lost family fo… https://t.co/mcPHfyLTLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll track it down and update our site where all links are:  https://t.co/5aOw0tH5Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pateast @citybloomington I realize now that I may not have understood your question. If you’re asking why they wai… https://t.co/0d48KiWAga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Przemysław Tytoń was my go-to GK signing on career mode when he was at @rodajckerkrade. Neat to see him in @MLS! #CareerModeStar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexhardin56 @cooper_ray @TheOakdale My man Mike Singletary may not have scratched a point yet but look out for the Memphis Express]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here at Fuzzy’s picking up a to go order,it’s crazy busy for valentines. Girl is very dressed up ,little to… https://t.co/m3sPd0M5LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneNFL I hope the rumors about his weight gain are true. He might never get signed again]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I find amazing is the democrats seem to know what’s in it HOW is that]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #nationalloveyourpetday - Here’s our crew of 5 rescue pups. All spoiled rotten. 😁 #rescuedogs #dogsofinstagram… https://t.co/IC7bHmgfgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen immediately following the Helena-Flathead Girls game on the AM KCAP at 950 AM and online at… https://t.co/HnQyVJo1L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConstanceM2015 @Jenny2Hugs Just have to open mine first and lick the tops lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[aight see y’all in a bit I’m bout to warp speed my meat into sumn nice 😤💪 https://t.co/HICiIYpBTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’ve done what I’ve done sometimes. Everything, bad and good. Everybody has a past bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0RMoYEXUv2 @GeneralFusion @ORNLEnergy_Env @DukeEngineering @AeroMechND @CornellEng @PantexPlant… https://t.co/5Wbzbg4rgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great game @UAHChargers and @TFinley15. 🌧 3s 🏀 #ChargeOn https://t.co/6RGo5mravE]]></document></documents></author>