<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Badass save last night by @rayalfalla. It almost got ugly with the 24 not realizing what lane to stay on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle There’s a lot to unpack there. Feeling the need to boycott an actor supporting children. Anyway, love y… https://t.co/qEthDYMeFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gio_mcmurtha Bud, they're like 9. Of course they're gonna interupt. Its typically difficuly to teach kids that stu… https://t.co/vhDdkYgday]]></document><document><![CDATA[An offer to help, and a refusal, and Harris, Ft Bend and Montgomery county residents in Texas should be a bit disap… https://t.co/5RNySrKug9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got pulled over 2 times not even 2 hours apart with 2 tickets nigga can’t even get a warning god damn boy they trying to break a nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch I used to believe that - my guess - Not with Bill Barr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was born to have adventure so I just followed her up the steps https://t.co/fR0BCKGEYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pirates #letsgobucs #buccos #springtraining @ McKechnie Field https://t.co/hWLFE59JG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Días de muchas emociones ❤️❤️❤️🇻🇪🇻🇪🇻🇪🇻🇪🇻🇪🇻🇪 Te Amo #Venezuela  _ Les confieso que he llorado mucho desde ayer con l… https://t.co/1n3tfBYlT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally in a shuttle. An hour and ten minutes out. @sheratonhotels was a huge mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Tristian once he got away with it again https://t.co/ybVR1lrXnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks my bro! Same goes for you. Gotta get you up here soon so you can coach up our kids! 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the March for the Murdered and Missing Indigenous People today. Standing in solidarity with community and family… https://t.co/9AOG8agSGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with SG1 10x15 “Bounty” I do find it kind of hilarious that they designed a space tra… https://t.co/4Q1PmfU7R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[important announcement: i have the best mom ever https://t.co/nnn96wT9In]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @sherrynron I saw the first film taken from the death camps at the end of WWII by the British. At first… https://t.co/rDs21DXBRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has markings of a terrorist. Not our values. Recall her, deport her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day at the Under Armour @AllAmericaGame Camp! 🙌🏾🏈 #UAAllAmerica https://t.co/owzXuc1nYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dare for somebody to try and defend this embarrassment of a president......does anybody even realize what Trump i… https://t.co/57LnPHxjhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowyLoli Yeah, send those.   Weird that for me it's under "Puffin"; maybe they make it different for a developer'… https://t.co/tI9ajofeyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly don’t understand how someone can be this dumb I truly truly do not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adrian_Wenner @NoahGarfinkel I see your mattress jingle and raise you a “melodies are for losers”  https://t.co/bcaHK7upUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump454545 @gaye_gallops We are screwed! This is our future,cry cry and when all else fails in life,beg for a bailout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it countless times but I should be fucking medicated and put into a mental hospital. Somethings wrong wit… https://t.co/2il8cnu1Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erossin48 @ReasonableYid @skjask Being against the actions of the country of Israel—and questioning why the U.S. s… https://t.co/ZYM0VzK4KA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like the Bills talking all offseason about their cap space, and how they are ready to make moves in FA, and… https://t.co/GOQDMIrevw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__arlicious I feel you,  jus ask yourself do you really need it when you wanna spend that 💰lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @LuvEvelynClaire @APOLONIAPORN  @XandraSixx @AshleyFires @KalinaRyu @HaleyReedX @sarahjessiexxx @rosexmonroex… https://t.co/WIV3d3kzYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0220Masters @CoachMattPugh I want my player to finish the shot. Up on two land on two. If you are worried about sp… https://t.co/gzc0UEM8RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pollorecargado1 @sol651 @jaarreaza Can you help me out by signing this petition? https://t.co/qWMiY1JRJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump No virtually everyone I know oppose the corrupt sellout of a bill that you politicians ar… https://t.co/EYEkWP34EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @HillTVLive Didn’t the English try that around 1776. Bit more completion these days. A few states I avoid for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Jessica for placing 2nd  in your class today @katyisd Show! #FFA  @NationalFFA https://t.co/PbmcHyDn6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashy_erin23 and for your information, I don't drink everyday https://t.co/IIBW5RyS4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Fireshine בשנה הראשונה של התואר הראשון הייתה לי שלישיית לימוד נהדרת. בילינו המון ביחד וגם אנחנו נקשרנו מאוד. ובסו… https://t.co/T3VEqSpHH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now it’s to the point where my love is up for debate or maybe it’s too late to shake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I remember how disappointed I was in several @TheDemocrats I respect on the knee-jerk reaction that I… https://t.co/b6HnLu8CeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Build an Exceptional Newsletter, According to People Who Did @MarketingProfs https://t.co/ypvs1KCy6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[This rabbit-hole stuff is all about power. Privileged people don’t get to create busywork for oppressed people. We’… https://t.co/9KwpKQ18hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanaa5 @JovanaVucetic1 @LoganFraley2 congrats on the Senior Day celebration and win. You girls are vital to this p… https://t.co/oaiQXcJ1oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipReiderson More sad than outraged but still https://t.co/C4uywmn5oD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjturcios @Valenzueia I have the $5 student deal with Spotify where you get Spotify, Hulu and Sho time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esperanza HS JV 11-3 over La Habra - Ryan Kirk EHS’22 5IP 1R 2H 1BB 9SO Good Job Dealing In Relief Today! https://t.co/jxcerG4T9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo el capítulo final de de la última temporada de la serie Club de Cuervos https://t.co/V7riDiArN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upgrading my phone again for the simple fact that it can’t get GarageBand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving the station (at @CTA - Fullerton in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/txz5EYSrMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me this Friday March 8th on @CBSTweet in macgyvercbs   This Saturday morning March 9th on @CBSTweet in cbsins… https://t.co/YbfmKniqPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key to being significantly wealthy is always starting/running a business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do SXSW like a local! Stay far, far away from downtown and make Ranch 616’s Fire in the Hole shots at home @ Austin… https://t.co/1r8wdfbzCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity She revoked her citizenship to align w/ the terrorists &amp; she still is one!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @PhxGOP @AIpatriotIZ @BernardFarquart I almost feel sad for this people. They see Arizona slipping thr… https://t.co/id0tk5RC6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday March 5 - The Rachel Maddow Show:     Democrats launch wave of inquiries after GOP oversight abdication;… https://t.co/v6nK2gGqKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, they have @krispykreme donuts! #YeagerDonutSaturday #SOW2019 #NVLeg https://t.co/fLY2n4XSjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t spend the day together but it doesn’t make it any less special. I’m happy to see another Valentine’s Day w… https://t.co/h6k4EnjMPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guatemala Intel Head Says Caravans 'Well-Planned,' Not Spontaneous https://t.co/WdwGVoAwAj via @BreitbartNews The D… https://t.co/SkLpNestx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landed at the Santa Fe, NM airport super late (2 or 3 am) b/c of delays. Was planning to take Lyft/Uber to hotel, b… https://t.co/FmzJL0C4KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiedupree I don't like this line of tweeting. I still think he has diarrhea of the thumb and hurts his causes.… https://t.co/rW77HCBDXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought I had cultivated a perfect timeline but I haven't seen a damn thing about the #UmbrellaAcademy dan… https://t.co/bJobjAQHVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C2BLHotTakes @higdon29 @ChronAVT Thanks for taking the worry out of answering..but I’ll answer anyway.  It’s moot.… https://t.co/SmnDK2gbFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialism is incompatible with the US Constitution, which is why Socialists hate it so much. It’s straightforward b… https://t.co/FxJhtE7KtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are all the Black QB's from D-1 n HBCU's programs. That played in the last 3yrs? JT Barrett? Types, Dude from… https://t.co/VUt9bS8JEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rub1xcub1x @Angels Might?  No way we make the playoffs with that bullpen and not having a legit Ace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like that the @SD_Fleet are shouting out my San Diego buddy @JonathanJones_ with the #AllHandsOnDeck hashtag. Classy move. #WakingAshland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coordinadora1DM @luci_esperanza1 @nytimes EL GOBIERNO COLOMBIANO DERECHA  TRAIDORA-agrede con mentiras   a VENZUEL… https://t.co/CRhe7nebbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling sipping cucumber sour @ The HandleBar Cafe https://t.co/cwpsbhW5Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lenka talked to me when she had nobody else now whenshendont need me she dont wanna talk in too good for her anyway fake loser shes pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonfavs Jon, the Green New Deal talked about the elimination of many things in ten years. Things that can’t be eli… https://t.co/j8rcIgQM6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The TP Drill!! #seaislandgpc #golf #golfinstruction #golfswing #golfcoach #golfcoaching #titleist #teamtitleist… https://t.co/wT8obQRkbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charofernandezr Siiiii!!!lo hizo otra vez!!! #VivaMexicoCuarones !!!🇲🇽📽🎥📺 https://t.co/buKPGI3ro5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my official super hero costume!  #FridayThoughts #FridayFeeling https://t.co/flSSv0a9Am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the alma mater back in the spotlight! Plus a top 25 victory for the softball team. Back in the spotlight..N… https://t.co/XbDeyrdd5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me gustan las facetas que estoy dispuesto a navegar y a sortear, el miedo no existe. @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/G0RMxAstR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“JET LI” Coming soon! Produced by prod.slxwclxp  Featuring @Bentlyman16  Enjoy the Sample!! - - #jetli #newrap… https://t.co/U9ghKP1obJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaePhoenix I would scoop my latent racism out of my skull if I could, but the best I can do is know that it exists… https://t.co/tfTR5p9EVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt Siblings Nell and Jonesy (Ms. Nelson &amp; Mr. Jones), about to turn 3. https://t.co/vORsTspZrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL Forest Hills Central - 21 Lowell - 28 #JVLadyHoops  Jillian Weston and Faith Stepek each scored six points to… https://t.co/wY6y7FZIpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[May have got the car stuck but still able to take some 🔥 pics @ Winter Park, Colorado https://t.co/x9UYo1wBOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its ironic all the people who were against recreational cannabis legalization have disappeared like ghosts..theyre… https://t.co/N91mIWmLdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib thank you for tonight!!#RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/nnvW2q1eqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gc2109 #iagc2019 Does the daily Christian Advocate come out each day? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driver arrested more than 2 months after veteran loses legs in crash @WFLAVictoria https://t.co/Ht0e0k5EMI @WFLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackson_ilena  Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianBreakerODR It’s all the figure FUHtography I keep seeing that makes me want to buy these sets! Btw see what I… https://t.co/Hgj6QPAMy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes I completed from Community Police Academy in Menlo Park.  This incident will result in mandatory arrest, o… https://t.co/qUverT3bzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #50FORLIFE Mental Health, Depression Awareness, and Suicide Prevention Race Project is still underway with the… https://t.co/uSOBHbqByt]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time Ruth Law flew an open-air biplane Chicago &gt; @Gov_Island #NYC in 1917. Broke records in #WWI @WW1CC… https://t.co/9XCHceZKpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This interview appears to have happened at the Trump Tower in Chicago, where Kelly lives. I was told he was plannin… https://t.co/LeX5VNEKZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Formula 1 Drive to Survive on @netflix.  Can’t wait for the season to start!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final in Class A South GBB 1/4 finals Brunswick 56 MTA 30 Semifinals v Marshwood Wednesday at 10am at Cross Center  #GODRAGONS]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were playing it defensively long term nba landscape. Ship him out east]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I don't know about the Green New Deal. But, I have been exposed to the original member of the Idiocracy Larry… https://t.co/dWyluyCQso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP But if the GOP keeps up its ways... it won’t matter you will certainly outspend it with the outlandish “tradit… https://t.co/5pS4QqMPc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Side Story - 10. I Feel Pretty https://t.co/loF9A6195o via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeZee13 @dspadam @jimmyjohns Big Z I had to go back for one at dinner and get the peppers. My life is changed forever. #GameOver]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need cartoons  🗣HULU PLAY RUGRATS!   I am drained!!! I need to reset! https://t.co/nbWt0VWMyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Chuckanut Oat Lager by @ChuckanutBeer @ State Street Beer — https://t.co/1VL57pUfE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump Ha dummy. If your innocent you would not have a problem in submitting what the house is asking for. I gu… https://t.co/QtnuVpPPzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ This is heroic. I certainly applaud the fair use in violence in defense of a citizen under ruthless attack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least there’s art… #flightdelayed @westjet @ Toronto Pearson International Airport https://t.co/t0WDYNglMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phenomenal morning and lunch learning from Richard Weylman founder of The Weylman Center for Excellence in Practice… https://t.co/8Nab0MxqsC]]></document></documents></author>