<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @Twitter @mattgaetz Dang dude. You seem obsessed with @mattgaetz. Matt it might be a good idea to get… https://t.co/AH5QiZkInB]]></document><document><![CDATA[White House Panel Will Study Whether Climate Change Is a National Security Threat. It Includes a Climate Denialist.… https://t.co/irNgz5roHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsMBrewer @mikebrewer @MotorTrend @discovery_uk Looks like getting rotors turned. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The episode was among the first of multiple ham-handed efforts by the president to carry out a dua… https://t.co/Ba4eUf030x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYforSanders @BernieSanders @dailykos @markos Well centrists would know all about cheating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes things don’t work out the way you planned—thanks weirdo candles! But it didn’t matter, my birthday was a… https://t.co/I5WZ5kduqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerGirlCA When I was a kid we used to do this all the time. We have a very large cemetery (on a corner) back home… https://t.co/5y6Xxeb1WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 22nd birthday to this crazy man of mine! I’m so glad we’ve stuck together through the hard shit, and than you… https://t.co/qGHffaFWFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Forward: when you set your alarm but hit snooze for two hours anyway. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Results from @JennyGuadamuz's analysis in #SOL show that there is significant variation in hypertension control by… https://t.co/Nbu3dLyRDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought because I'm at a fisheries conference in 2019 I'd be treated better than an object. But because I'… https://t.co/AEgwSlvlNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing I hate more than word counts. It’s either minimum of 250 words and I’m at 50 or maximum of 500 word… https://t.co/LTeDf3fcId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterwo44376851 @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump From your mouth to Gods ear]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 3 legislators stood with the majority of parents. Thank you to @reprebeccadow, @votealonzo and @gallegos4nm fo… https://t.co/bwzAoNe1nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[More pics from the @spurs game! @ AT&amp;T Center https://t.co/jm5LbLAtBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You keep running your mouth as if you and the state are one. That you are being investigated is no… https://t.co/IBrc3MtFuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i’ve never had a nightstand before and now i finally have one and i’m so obsessed with it, it’s so perfect and cute and makes me so happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlynbristowe after publishing my story last October, it’s been my mission to help other girls and women with th… https://t.co/w6TuVth9Xn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Maybe rock hard is a better descriptor. https://t.co/xXjBYZzrFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ONLY place to be TONIGHT!!! U already know how me and @Dj_G33k do. 🤙🏽😎 @ Pub Webb https://t.co/kojk0TCvUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriminalAOC @J_TrumpIN Lady, u r insane! If u think the people of the US r stupid enuf to listen to u, ur in for a… https://t.co/zEhUHI4Qml]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve let lots of things y’all have said and posted slide. But one thing you’re not gonna do is insult the memory of… https://t.co/knPnkeuFQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larry walking through the racetrack promoting commercial credit! Great job Larry!! @rockholds5 @BrendaH36992250… https://t.co/fdCwoWD49P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XenaGoldspink i am so god awful at shooting games like.... i would be a detriment to any squad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tooth ache.  I have one.  It’s miserable!  Would not wish this pain on anyone other than child or senior abusers, a… https://t.co/dROIulqj1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better than trump tho and he has many dem followers so we dont want them to feel alienated either...we need whoever… https://t.co/8YtrpEZANB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Atlanta #AtlantaAirport #MAC #macmakeupartist #IWantToBeABride #SillyMegan @ Fulton County, Georgia https://t.co/pplrKjw1Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my powerful Seester and the rest of the freshman class performing in The Lore Projects! (Also looks lik… https://t.co/ojYS5vX0ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@14RickMorrow @Mountai77286701 Too bad we didn’t have an impeachment mechanism in Canada. But then again their majority is strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPRKelly @DavidKris Not just awful, but dangerous.  And a huge slap in the face to those of us who repeatedly jump… https://t.co/F2AKgjLlzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people refer to Jp as my husband, I don’t correct them. Like we’re basically married so why should I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nealtmorton @MariahCarey I'm grateful to @MariahCarey for all she's given to @educationlab and @seattletimes overall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadChangeTrish No. Processed. Especially in the evening. So that means no wine and no dessert. Really helps and w… https://t.co/hsonZZyBbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[K pedo con el niño de mi salón que siempre me ve y cuando sonrió para que no sea incómodo el momento me ve con cara de tu que? Oseaaaa mande]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends @FoxNews Why doesn’t anything get done?  The American People have had enough!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are not required to listen to people's problems. Do not feel guilty for setting boundaries and/or distancing yo… https://t.co/yOIpYwnkoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: We should go to the...uh...lighthouse! I wanted to say nightlight but that’s not right  @ChefSeis: it could be… https://t.co/lNm6QtZQiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of this student on my team. She welcomed guests to our Black History program with confidence, grace, and styl… https://t.co/i3KDHCQ5MW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msisodia @timesofindia @TOIIndiaNews  Panders to @narendramodi @PMOIndia]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FayettevillePD Officer Percy Evans  responded to a structure fire and pulled an unresponsive woman laying in the… https://t.co/RU5s3DFGqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling wimpy about being cold in Oregon, w/ ice tsunamis! #Weatherwords #orwx #scicomm https://t.co/n0fwtwibBb via @SmithsonianMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@readnallthetime @Csziber @HillaryClinton Border security doesn’t stop them !!!!   Look what’s happening now they f… https://t.co/f8qYpeclUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how i feel, i’ll never allow myself to be with somebody who doesn’t look at me like he knows and cherishes how fucking rare i am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couples thatjuul together stay together... until one of them takes both chargers 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shopping with @Shellz_nchz! Look at her new car! So proud of her. 😊 https://t.co/Vk7UM4qpD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorful, colorful, shiny corpses #amreading #writerslife https://t.co/w3Br1p3TTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitchickfriday Repost from @melissasarahwee Someone took my photos of the times when I was contest lean ( like thi… https://t.co/HAB9paUkyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Omniscient69 The next time someone questions why I teach boutique fitness, I’m going to reference this]]></document><document><![CDATA[200 Yard Freestyle  Belchertown’s Nathan Dragon and Matthew Stemokas crack the Top 10 along with Owen Oldenburg fro… https://t.co/QmkNHVbQkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Caniacs.. met this woman at the Cary Flea today. She has some cool #Canes inspired skirts. JustGennaCarter  https://t.co/ulLbXbJZbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post breakfast poker game! #Eighth-gradeGuys #WalkingWiselyWeekend #There’sNoFoodLeftInTheHouse! @ Thoroughgood Nei… https://t.co/lkQByqAiM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngusMcPussPuss @catsrule0 @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @SassyCassyCat @BloomNight2… https://t.co/ZMG311JfEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida se puede terminar en cualquier momento. Por eso recuérdenle a las personas que te importan cuanto las quier… https://t.co/iGaaZ9YKLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was definitely a roller skating machine😁 One of the nicest guys. #TheGoodOldDays]]></document><document><![CDATA[A successful capitalist society cannot exist without successful social programs.  #MorningJoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch party for @PeteButtigieg ‘s town hall in Tampa!!! https://t.co/RYDhZbxFI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up 30min before your alarm is supposed to go off 😐 https://t.co/SbnIIr9SQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 minutes in: the hate mail is annoying. Let me set the record clear: this is our new minority, and they're silenc… https://t.co/uuaSPZcbFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost And you were sued for 250,000,000 for lying....your broke and our Trump is still our @POTUS ! Go to… https://t.co/pVFkN1MC1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me happy to know there are good companies that will help you when you fall on hard times... #allybank   Thank… https://t.co/qtJn9CweTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a dog. According to history, it seems like I made a the correct choice. (Also, @monicalmercado this seems pe… https://t.co/gCVugA1rKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where it all began.... (@ Gate 07 in Madison, WI) https://t.co/kMmSrQQld2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going to rain all day today and I’m not okay with it I get scared I prefer the fog than the rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna hear struggle until you’ve had to grow up with 12 as your mom. 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@culttture @JacobAWohl @ali Jacob is a liar!!  No pardon! https://t.co/MUKBkaa20Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world.... #verseoftheday #believer #loveandlight💫 @ Mitchellville, Maryland https://t.co/g2wx6TOJM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRHSHawks Umayyad, Lauren!  Your fifth grade teacher is so proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mass (@ Holy Family Church in Jacksonville, FL) https://t.co/1rNfC1LAXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STLsherpa @RyanKlamen @sdkstl @KDLSsays @sararahmcb @ArlanWasHere @GIPHY @betaworkstudios @stltoday 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizagnaaaa and send me off into the crowd during a nasty bassnectar drop]]></document><document><![CDATA[At #SXSW19⁠ in Austin, Texas 🌵🌮  Learning memory doping tactics to create the best ads with @DrMelW and @DanMonheit 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ensenada 22/feb/2019 - 6:20 am © Alexa Zinola - Fotografía : : : : #nevada #aguanieve #granizo #bajacalifornia… https://t.co/ORce4yGno1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Ask them. Here’s my basic “status of the class” form that gives students a chance to give me feedback:… https://t.co/QmIKmthq4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS @NuseUSMC That’s me, now that I’m retired I can be an active Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foolish4Harry I totally agree !! They need to grace our ears . I only hope we get to see it some how if they do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump At last you finally agree that all you do as a president is lie and harass]]></document><document><![CDATA[No bc Congress can’t dictate to him what he can use where, what kind of wall etc. I hope he pours cement really thi… https://t.co/U3ky7yvgKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was excellent, back at it tomorrow then getting on a couple birds back home 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no such thing as a “tech person” in the age of AI - via @techreview https://t.co/SVSMp83xO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammy73619415 @kathygriffin @JussieSmollett The bullies and the adult haters need to be stopped NOW‼️ Look, how wo… https://t.co/qHLsZGr6Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Hahahahahahahahaha, yeah right fat ass @realDonaldTrump  Oh and Trump’s in Maralago playing golf the day af… https://t.co/tDsdaBtJ7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roykesey It will be like real-life Duck Tales. Except creepy af. https://t.co/oyK1mLdqdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz You're not even in office anymore! Why don't you just shut up, hypocrite!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1920s called, I answered 📞 #Speakeasy #TheBackRoom #WhenInNYC #Brooklyn #NY #SundayFunday @ The Back Room https://t.co/ayvreeS1kN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnakeBadAss This guy I text up and blocked me. One minute we were texting next he blocked. Strange .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulRamone1492 Tulsi is also an apologist for a horrific regime. But she passes your vetting because she’s a Berni… https://t.co/X4HZoOuYFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tory peer gave contract to firm linked to Paul Manafort https://t.co/Bml8IScPEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellystrantz Anthony Scaramucci is now following me. Is this somehow your doing? 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know when u get the flu and u suddenly become aware of muscle groups u never even think about?  Like, right now… https://t.co/s5X6ewU1yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to heal too... fisrst from@the chaos and stress from the progressive left, 2nd I’m Irish American... family… https://t.co/Q9eOnmSDgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Song #2 - my pick. This is one of my favorite songs of all time. https://t.co/eT22pVrCaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tournament alert for grades 4-8!! Email Richard Scott for more details. https://t.co/u2Ucpzl95R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCISLA So excited for this! They are my favorite TV couple ever! @ericcolsen and @DanielaRuah have the best chemistry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting my mom a #birthdaymalt and some lady sees my popcorn she says wow thsts alot of popcorn 😆😀🤣😂🍿🍿 @ Shake… https://t.co/SIeSXd3pha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESOLMentor Totally! I’m trying to spread the word too - The Language Lens for Content Classrooms https://t.co/aLEEudOnId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marquisegoodwin One of the best guys I’ve ever met. I don’t think he ever met a stranger 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @Mil_FANet Republicans treat the military like dirt.  Trump lets his unqualified, unaccountable country cl… https://t.co/RwIF4RWCi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight Savings Time + early morning flight = too early #notamorningperson #gonnaneedanap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I personally love Cactus so for my Valentine day present to myself I bought a few cactus and I’m happy with that… https://t.co/VK5PBuGb78]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to be vegan eat up leave my meat prices along it's high enough as it is!!! Clown]]></document></documents></author>