<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of our assistants is like the quietest person ever and today he told us he loves vodka more than anything and i… https://t.co/7YheAUmCLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t worry ladies I didn’t jump just being iconic with @shitnea twerking while I jump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 21 of "21 Days of Tinsley Twofers" - looking forward to Tinsley Ellis playing 2 nights at The Zoo Bar 3/11-12 https://t.co/9YNrf2mXHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo She’s perfect to represent the Idiocracy district. She’s really Occasional-Cortex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I posted a pic of myself after my workout with “chubbs” underneath and my husband’s response was, “You spelled ‘sex… https://t.co/TErtbrI1vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok saw #CapitanMarvel for the second time tonight. Just as good as the first! Such a perfect Segway into #EndGame… https://t.co/7pxEElZeEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@astronoid are fantastic!   #ThankYou @JMaxProductions for booking them inside @CargoReno 🤘🏻  #RT #MT  #Reno… https://t.co/URHJR5O3qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Tq1UmV273a]]></document><document><![CDATA[0.000001002003004005006 ... and so on. However, one three-digit number gets skipped in this strange series.  Being… https://t.co/oTm2Spy16x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benelou @D_B_Harrison I have seen and engaged both here and in person many who profess faith in God, but when conf… https://t.co/HqoCNI91a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most members of the MSM see it as their “mission” to destroy this president. TDS is rampant among the press.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to thank crystalclearesq for being one of our guest on Straight Talk .... Definitely fun and interesting conve… https://t.co/sXOKijulqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sunday Morning Stout by @weyerbacher @ Sand Wedge — https://t.co/eXbtcGG42S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jzay24 bro I’m pump’d @StylesMcgee_ did it today and she said it was awesome so I can’t wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnottah @di23216949 We have to wait. I am a latin guy and i ‘ll give my life for this country and for my president Donald Trump!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we wait: DOL comment period on MEPs ended 12/24 https://t.co/zJMuLSFe4A @wealth_mgmt #401k #RetirementPlanning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 It’s daily - Truly, the media is poisoning America’s mind with constant lies &amp; liberal propaganda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjakeberg @MollyCocktail This just won the internet. Congrats champ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K__Jamieson @LeafsNews Gone and forgotten. Great player and he will be great for Leafs. Thinking however Leafs fans need to let it go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElOsoOro @ivanowskinba Boogie was right? Ever played with a bully or a shit teammate? Someone who’s conditioning w… https://t.co/3rnqsxOWY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigerian Bros would not be released and allowed to return to Nigeria if Police thought they were involve in a fake… https://t.co/UOQg4BB4ZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImAnxiousBecause This Groundhog guy may have some delusions of grandeur. https://t.co/Lr4LFUkF9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They shorted the rails, just the valley folks! All aboard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @FoxFriendsFirst w/ @jillianmele and @SchmittNYC Keep up the good w… https://t.co/nGsKjkKtTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Markuswelbemd @realDonaldTrump We have 29 million already the dems want the votethats 10% of our population!!!! Scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zions injury could’ve happened in any shoe for somebody that big putting that much torque and pressure in that instant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders raised $5,925,771 from 223,047 individual donors in 24 hours...  Average donation? $27  If that's no… https://t.co/P8q9elz3Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who live in the shelter of the Most High will find rest in the shadow of the Almighty. Psal…… https://t.co/ZNt64KJwlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill #McConnell should not forget that he is running for re-election in 2020. #DumpMcConnell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellaballoo @etnow @FiveFeetApart @colesprouse @dylansprouse lol.. hanks didn't knowingly do things to make himse… https://t.co/WE68wKRyYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al aire con @DeniseMaerker en @AtandoCabos para analizar el caso del garrafón como casco cefálico y en Magdalena y… https://t.co/GxUlunWJDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Kicks look like some old school @AndreAgassi Nikes..@rogerfederer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky 32, Missouri 19, 3:28 1H.   It's late, the game is blah, but this is a solid performance by the Cats, all… https://t.co/7e6LTF0y1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deapoirierbooks You can call on Les Grands Dieux des Biscuits  Just avoid eye contact. And mirrors.  Make sure the… https://t.co/k1FCQK2P4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN LA COMICS..Let’s play who actually knew Brody in this picture? https://t.co/X1IgnjusIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillGertz Wish the WSJ would allow this important story to be seen by the public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in at 3 PM for an updated weather forecast from Pittsburgh’s most accurate meteorologist @Verz.  “The Chief” w… https://t.co/5FFjH63cMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downright error codes booting me from the game and causing me to have to restart the whole application? Yes. A lot.… https://t.co/9NVjo8hkP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park View Gallery in Los Angeles, Calif https://t.co/8HWs0qNkH9 https://t.co/5rcXLT9HKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friyay - Drinking a Big Sky Lullaby by @mikkellersd @ Mikkeller Brewing San Diego  — https://t.co/DGKCQ7zKPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been going to the eye doctor since 2nd grade and I’m amazed by how technology has advanced like damn they took… https://t.co/h07JiLSxuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My belly is not that big anymore @ Upper Manhattan https://t.co/FwYU760IfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelTanea Congratulations to the first Woman’s tag team Champions 🤼‍♀️🤼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[BURN IN HELL TO ALL DEMS WALKING ON THIS PLANET. EVEN THE ONES THAT ARE ALL READY IN THE GRAVE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple for me. That ‘68 green Mustang fast back from the movie “Bullitt” starring Steve McQueen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[E-scooter companies said months ago they thought they’d be in Albuquerque by now. City officials now say they’re pr… https://t.co/QyLfCrAtFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyMontgomerie Put 60+ hours into this wonderful game. All the DLC came free and it’s only $15. The music is astounding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[pm better make sure that healthy is on the setlist for me! thank u for coming to my ted talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this tech and we still get out-of-order pop-up notifications that look like Jeff Goldblum’s first attempts at t… https://t.co/QT07g2aBZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to leading a conversation with these thoughtful superintendents tomorrow at the Palm Springs Museum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zippittt @badjamjam The Kinsellas usually block anyone that disagrees with them. PO must have really hit close to… https://t.co/6OitpqpoR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else hear the THUNDER ROLL early this morning?? ⛈  @FOX46Nick (the science guy) explains why… https://t.co/s1kVxJ63wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And where has this story been in the #msm? This seems to have great importance since they both have nukes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadopia @kc2fargo @rwgranny @mc1436v2 @JoeSilverman7 @Spacebunny21 That’s actually 0.16%, for the record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morriss2100 @OTFxAB @undisputed @shane_lowell15 @Dame_Lillard @MichaelRapaport I mean they weren't a bad team even… https://t.co/jArwSx8uUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correct. I am sure several were seen this morning in Virginia by somebody’s Aunt’s friends son. Explanations of leo… https://t.co/ac5fBLk2zX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dem mob party is not going to announce it’s socialism goals, it’s incremental, nudged, never announced. The Ame… https://t.co/BhWLV70S4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendymarie5980 @BostonGlobe Nah.  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth, no one in Boston wa… https://t.co/N4gAwKNExj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MySportsUpdate When will people understand and accept that not everyone will like you. Time for Timmy to grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @NewMexicoUTD’s name is brought up on a weekly bases from the head of the league, and now independent algorith… https://t.co/npTmyuLzTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein You made a fan today out of me ❤️ thank you for laying the smackdown on there candy asses 😂🎉😂🎉😂🎉😂🎉❤️🚔🇺🇸❤️🚔🇺🇸❤️🚔🇺🇸❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gotmtv  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPAIN #1 trending on Apple Music after his flawless victory on @MaskedSingerFOX #MonsterMask #TheMaskedSinger https://t.co/dW1DJrpW3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ptm @ClubAlianzaLima tamos muy metidos atrás. Hay que tener la pelota carajo. #CopaLibertadores #ConmebolLibertadores2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lFRroUYLQZ goes live in 12 minutes. Tune in for live North Linn vs Cascade substate action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaGamer @RoyalNavy Take him to the strip club and a girl tie him to the pole and whip him then ride him around the stage like a donkey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rossignol 3 made it 58-48 @BlackBearsWBB  ... Albany forced to foul 1:14 left. Saar with two FT's 60-48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hoarder’s Endowment 003 by @SigmaBrewingCo at @deaconbaldys — https://t.co/rMRhAhlOAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[She Sells Sanctuary 🌹🤘🏻 Photo // whiskey_shotz at endlessnightvb LA Vampire Ball ‘19 @ Globe Theatre https://t.co/yeiz5HnuuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[First camp going up this summer for current HS players!!!! June 15th!!!! @JStew8 @CoachKrich @miguelr_ulv https://t.co/gzB9nvZsCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my Speedtest result! How fast is your internet? https://t.co/pgnFctTshp]]></document><document><![CDATA[check out my first vlog on my new fitness channel 🤙🏼 https://t.co/qRhr7sB8lX]]></document><document><![CDATA[New SWAG coming to some of your mailboxes in the next few weeks! #BOLO #youknowwhoyouare https://t.co/CPfb4Iu5ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APEntertainment Even though think his films at best mediocre there is a place where for his films. 50% of the coun… https://t.co/sI7KkN9cGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every bride needs a hot little white dress to hit the dance floor!  Do you have yours?  Shop our BridalStyle event… https://t.co/KxZJqOv7uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yal know what..... I ain’t even gon tweet about tonight!!!! A lot of shit went down but ima just turn my headphones… https://t.co/eO6mFPGeKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SethAMandel - you are so far behind - quit. This should be very very uncomfortable for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time Gagner tweeted Merry Christmas to Edmonton. He loves it here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JoeGoodmanJr reported that @Trendon_2 will take an official visit to Duke on Tuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand finals haven’t been kind to Eddie over the last 6 months https://t.co/BQzaBwvxTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning java  ... ☕️... #coffee #cappuccino #dirtychai #cultureespresso #culture36 #nyc @ Culture 36 https://t.co/YBI6CTOXtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Liga Privada 10-Year Aniversario Subculture Studios contest from @drewestatecigar https://t.co/Sps3q1UASt]]></document><document><![CDATA[And there’s this other guy out there who is on pace to have three straight years of averaging a triple double and i… https://t.co/1VYS8YrD8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger @costareports He’s intelligent and actually wants to craft substantive solutions to the country’s problems!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelb Happy Anniversary!  @mistymburkhart  You forgot the "h".  Still waiting on a follow back from her. 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to do it for my baby @KayMarie_04 she is the one that keeps me going!!! https://t.co/Yb2DC5lnne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...Twitter going full Monty now, I guess this means that Twitter is backed by Terrorists 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of dumb money in the world.   "As the oil giants continue their shale expansion, many have gained favor with investors. "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero nosotros como aficionados, es imposible no pensar más allá... el #ClasicoRegio es el partido más pasional de l… https://t.co/1GUODD9gCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Coconut Stout by @pfriemBeer at @fortgeorgebeer — https://t.co/Hm1F2gStr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to believe this. Who does Mark Hoppus think he is: the creator of the song? #blink182 #shook   https://t.co/FgK8nFHCB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When term limits are in place. Not until then either. They have no motivation to do the right thing. I in no way ag… https://t.co/FUOjVmXIJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion’s shoe tears in the opening 20 seconds of the game   Nike: https://t.co/oyZqRtu3TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to officially get the season underway tomorrow, even if its tech day.   This is one of the first times sinc… https://t.co/btL8SmUrqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bodies all over the floor the entire half. Total of nine fouls called. Two of them touch fouls 25 feet from the basket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karbarmar @Prf_ImpFarmMama @alpipkin @MissiWhite4 @HappyLadydanger @MAGAShocka IT IS NEVER NEVER NEVER EVER AN EXCUSE TO ABORT...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommut I think it’s for the office break room. You know whoever bought it will be bitter at the end of the week ca… https://t.co/wVz01XhjpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t do diversity...” -Heather Zynczak 2019.   #Cancelled #TwitterDoYourThing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way for us men to celebrate #InternationalWomensDay is to call out sexism and toxic masculinity the moment we see it. #dobetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews she has a bigger plan in mind. dont doubt Nancy. She's a seasoned veteran and knows how to play Trump like a fiddle]]></document></documents></author>