<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/N4wS9GK2av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobLonsberry @gcraig1 @meagmc @CRod5100 @rachbarnhart @Hkula1191 @JeffK72 @Caponthehill   HOW DO WE KNOW WHO TO BE… https://t.co/3vaTXGRvPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comiccole He wants to be Mr. Homerun. Not working out for him. Need an outfielder who can hit 280 + and drive in 100+ runs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grist is nailing it!! - Drinking a Chameleon IPA by @GristHouse at @voodoobrewery  — https://t.co/7m99ZRC0sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think coach Gentry has been class A through all of this. It makes want him to stay our head coach. @NEWORLEANSPEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Sadly it won't happen. I can only hope he doesn't get a second term.  Billy Laverne Kellar for President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kroger brand French onion dip is the best French onion dip on the planet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @AZCardinals  have released safety Antoine Bethea &amp; QB Mike Glennon. They also resigned RB DJ Foster to a one-year contract.#NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelSing261088 @konagrl4554 @Seahawksgal81 @JewelLovesBooks @Jane42976731 @VAGirlsmom @lolamare69 @dana_lacie… https://t.co/wg1z8zqpBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wb_thorne @robinhanson @John_Hempton While I would change my mind if someone could construct a randomized controll… https://t.co/IZqiUj5wsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue @BernardKerik People honor slave owners and confederates and people like Columbus that murdered thousands… https://t.co/QHjVYo2hnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRovell2 @renato_mariotti @CNN @SenBlumenthal @ChuckGrassley @SenatorBurr That's what you get around me, talking h… https://t.co/Ca4n8fYEo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[some dumbfuck said i sounded like a white suoremacist. ignoring the complete lack of logic there, yeah, lemme join… https://t.co/IUrQju2YHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder to Jim Jordan, Cohen brought copies of checks...which have been no doubt been verified by numerous prosecutors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexisjosefine @brandyyalize Am I the only one who likes fries w/ bbq sauce ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Clayton will be here in July, we can't wait to meet our baby boy💙💙 https://t.co/kxrzRFxcQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @isaachayes3 ・・・ How you feeling? @ Orinda, California https://t.co/kALZY6AgcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study Shows AMP Can Lead to Increase in Organic Search Traffic by @MattGSouthern https://t.co/kMdgUv2vaz https://t.co/jS6zgJL0Ei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwraskin @RickCarpiniello @NYP_Brooksie And as far as the team goes, the GM has to balance today with tomorrow. So… https://t.co/bEAoalg7AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[445PM: Radar remains quiet for now. Closely monitoring the area in the blue circle. Window of opportunity for T-sto… https://t.co/LOyhw4umlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is never time in the future in which we will work out our salvation. The challenge is in the moment; the tim… https://t.co/6rbN2FZhi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regina Kong’s mom crying is an image that I will conjure for years to come when I must rip myself out of the darkest nights. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got too have one of these to scare off tailgaters. That's some scary shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @realDonaldTrump Your the asshole. A nobody who uses foul language while hopping on a bandwagon of… https://t.co/2eMx7jIP6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Would you say you are an empath, with dead-reckoning intuition? ;) I saw you smoking and going on abou… https://t.co/Lqf1XWlA3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malcom Nance makes the perfect point that our Dem candidates aren’t screaming about the traitor in the White House.… https://t.co/LBkgRp0ATG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cativomachina @RedSox @Patriots @NHLBruins Oui oui Claude   Tu sens pas le vent de victoire qui flirt sur la Nouve… https://t.co/FzrVpsyS9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr BELT STATE FELT STATE GELT STATE HELT STATE KELT STATE MELT STATE Knelt STATE PELT STATE Celtic STATE WELT STATE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBankReform @jeffhauser @CFPB That's a disgraceful display by Kraninger]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOLES GOT PAID!!!!!!!!!  Deserves it man what a man and a football player!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I got out of town for a while and then come home and be so bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy Jackson wins his consolation semi match and qualifies for districts! Go Pirates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Padres can not let @Bharper3407 sign with the Dodgers! I’m not saying we need him on the Padres but we do not… https://t.co/qaMP508Yml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyOrr @theikawong I didn’t delete anything? https://t.co/FMpDHgue5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz That’s because your a liberal blow hole !!! Hillary wants her Dress back .... And Bill wants his knee… https://t.co/8F65xIgCz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonschreier I started watching it at the beginning of the year for the first time and I’m absolutely hooked. In… https://t.co/iVZumVk3o8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamaLava6 @EWErickson @SteveDeaceShow @conservmillen .@CaffThoughts podcast is on Spotify, I haven't had any probl… https://t.co/AcFsODMWom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, I was gonna chill out and let it ride, but nah...  Last night I witnessed @tunisha_strong pick up a crucial t… https://t.co/WqNUCIYWlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @suziday123 @cazij @CaraMiaSG @ja2cook @JackConnie @FionaMorgan79… https://t.co/7VjASPtV7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxFriendsFirst Good Morning and Happy Wednesday🐫 staff, crew, @HeatherChilders @jillianmele and @SchmittNYC Great… https://t.co/RBW39ERxoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You’re plan is a Hallmark Card of a Command Economy as implemented by “Comrade Stalin!” https://t.co/Pep8PgOFQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my selfie with the co-creators of @earhustlesq before they start talking to @mkimreporter on @KQEDForum . https://t.co/dYHGMh0Tnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[when someone tells me I should give up memes for Lent https://t.co/XvQPA6Jrkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Crop Circus by @BauhausBrewLabs @ McLaren Croft — https://t.co/zfDn3jFM7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[17. I’ve had 2 concussions in my life, and I was dumb enough to get them both within two days of each other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everybody tried to put in a order once they knew I was at the mall 😂😂 kut all that shit short fast asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildgirlAthena #athenarayne #pornstar #sexi #model #bape #hawty #bomb #boobs #avn #avn2019 #avnexpo #avnexpo2019… https://t.co/SC4UgI2cIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be more expressive in my love 😂 No hiding the love I feel for this man. And I am honored to call him my b… https://t.co/7aR5fgLUKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillenGenY @indigochildohb @MeekMill But they don’t got money to get poppin, the labels do. They need the labels m… https://t.co/aNIVe4Oc81]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty cool, but let’s also not pretend it’s not self-serving. With players like Embiid, Siakam, Ibaka, and… https://t.co/845sAcEnbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m torn between wanting to invite a lot of people for my bday &amp; invite just a few 😂😂 depends how social I’m feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorobe555 @Mibelis Creo que su "recordatorio" es sólo un argumento manipulador que olvida las muertes de 20 años d… https://t.co/8tLB3WnU60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DietCoke Love these flavors!!!  Gotta do something with grapefruit and lemon at some point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot para nacho en  #utah por @albertolocutor #concierto #emisoras en #newyork y el resto de #americalatina de su… https://t.co/Oq7cvaAHCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimfreethinker @RepLawrence @OversightDems Change my tweet sorry!! Everything senators and congressmen do are just… https://t.co/HCu6T75wTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It'd be something like this raw would have @ReneeYoungWWE as lead announcer with @WWEGraves and @TomPhillipsWWE mea… https://t.co/fUo2Va7XuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationwidePet #luvyoufurever My little girl Ginger https://t.co/LUeVeFJohM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman She does not  deserve be a Congress woman, because she doesn’t understand Americans culture, freedom… https://t.co/qnh5dL5CQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaLRohlik In-and-out the most overhyped restaurant ever. Their fries suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmtgsr @SCooper9 @muskiefan3 If they had 13 losses in THAT conference, might as well discontinue the program altogether.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bendmayer @kasie @mitchellreports @KamalaHarris @kasie has socialism cooties...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @MaireCervenak @MrNunesteach @guay_ms @RitaWirtz @tracyscottkelly @DisruptedTv @melanie_korach… https://t.co/XfTLUcBb6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[They just lumped us all into a 1 classroom, not caring about/realizing the damage it caused. We were hidden from so… https://t.co/xIakjYMeSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Longest nine years, Shortest one day... Loved them both. LMFAO #Prayers]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't care because you only care about your own life and times but I shoveled snow today. This is snow I shovel… https://t.co/zj3EAtLl33]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly cannot stand Enes Kanter.. guy flops then tries to act tough? Simmons’ face as he walks away says it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportslarryknbr So the fact that Oracle Park is about the worst park for a lefty power hitter vs the Phillies rela… https://t.co/ANYwQYPRj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnn watch and learn how real journalism is done. No photos of school buses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainJoeMMA @TravisRuger @RecDiggity @BernieSanders Socialism is corporate bailouts, tax scams that add 2.5 tril… https://t.co/yPkT3l7GHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaLogallmon @liznagy @FightGoodFight1 @ABC7Chicago @FBI And the Clinton’s have been getting away with shit for… https://t.co/TnDroqdwgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleksIsTaken If memory serves, the concerns were around how to visually depict a Star Destroyer so that it was bel… https://t.co/Bo6aUxcyCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier I know you have to defend your place of employment,  but anyone with the sense God gave a seedless grape… https://t.co/6ODcik6hc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of the decades of grantwriting my mom pored over-NIH, NIMH, ALZ.  I recall as a kid her experiencing many… https://t.co/S3wxP9j3cP]]></document><document><![CDATA[(🔊Sound On) Dude ❤️ loves 🐑 #lambchop @ Dude's Positive World https://t.co/f5PTg1C6jN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box | #PavelPlamenev  (… https://t.co/iCidXXsX4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road crews are out making their rounds...be careful if you’re headed out. Tune in to @kq2 Hometown This Morning sta… https://t.co/NtxsbiSU4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThunderChunky37 @AOC Trump has always prove right. Mueller report is coming out, and there is nothing. Jump on board, #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zorroskywalker @GerardoZeron @brozoxmiswebs Tiro directo https://t.co/8KdgvOM006 por recorte presupuestal... Tómala!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swethhh11 @apex_intel @PlayApex Bro my account got hacked on osrs and it was so old I couldn’t remember anything so my osrs died w it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what #9 beating #8 looks like walking off the field. #gohounds https://t.co/PcmWx5ddFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[After another random nap (I apparently slept for 5 hours), I'm awake. Who's up?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Regular Show is honestly so underrated. Too many of y’all slept on Mordecai &amp; Rigby &amp; it shows. https://t.co/b02iP7dmZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’re factoring taxes in why doesn’t every few agent go to Florida or Texas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrNotMe715 So you mean a QB only starts one season and goes on to the pros? Not one good season out of a couple?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell me this is the beginning of Gabi getting her hands on the DiMera fortune]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinGrace10 I think he saw the cartoons I drew about him..I think he commented on my neglected blog, but I archiv… https://t.co/fIderAxVnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECUProfessor @joshstatea At like the first ever Pirate Fest downtown in the Beer Garden, they had these low key fu… https://t.co/gM6EyEAJD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. @AOC and @SenMarkey 's Green New Deal would barely change earth’s temperature. Here are the facts.… https://t.co/oF9hTSu12M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when actors never used this type of language.  Where has our morals gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is a Turkey Meat Stick™️ 4.3 stars - kind of dry - good meat flavor - found it on the ground (free) - will sha… https://t.co/dss7IrKfUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to read the book from the back to the front https://t.co/1FBQuzPuTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevrgallant @gh183654 Stevens is not the issue.  The issue is letting the players run the league.  Silver has to grow a pair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz is a very smart man. Why don’t his fellow dems listen to him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣🗣YESSIIRRRR TODAY IS THE DAY ‼️‼️ #MAgiKCity #TheCeee https://t.co/ScAxjhtqsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many of yall went to college to come out and get a job that has nothing to do with your major??? #ImTrynnaSeeSumRightQuick🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two of my predictions are correct so far, lets see how the rest of this PPV goes. #WWEFastlane @WWE @WWENetwork #RoadToWrestlemania]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedestrians cross the street near the Daley Building on a snowy afternoon. (This popped up on my Facebook memories,… https://t.co/ASkC3ai1YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCommentarys This is essentially child pornography, not a funny tweet.  Unfollowed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[oooooooooffffff  I really wonder what motivated Disney to do a live action remake. I think it could be dope, but be… https://t.co/Jr7tBsk2qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCarey It happens quite often when a certain person breaks something.]]></document></documents></author>