<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@commonpatriot @bigleaguepol Wow that’s not something anyone would want said about themself👀...I hope!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriving to the Beverly Hilton to view the Oscars @ The Beverly Hilton https://t.co/lOnJiJKUvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 days until Auggie Game Day! #AuggiePride 🦅 #d3sb https://t.co/nJM7U5OWA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists These two are clowns performing for their massa SMH https://t.co/qGaZ73xye3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahCourchesne I just saw "phycology is a science because it uses science " and yes that's how psychology was spe… https://t.co/MQLCxaGIq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when there’s a big job to do, like pack—and catalogue—about 2,000 books to move across campus, some amazi… https://t.co/I8qiR0fJhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright that’s the most y’all will ever get from me... to the 4 people who actually see my tweets lol. I’m always s… https://t.co/mR7N8ZN6Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnergyMoment @longhair1952 @MattSteele2 @dbongino @realDonaldTrump Muellers hands may be tied to a certain extent,… https://t.co/8nftVpto6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting goals for our writing by sharing our work with our partners and using the opinion checklist. #AACPSAwesome… https://t.co/JrInZ2iGcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEMRATS NEED THEM FOR VOTES ACTUALLY USED ILLEHALS IN 2016 MIDTERMS..AN YOU CAN BET WILL DO IT AGAIN IF WE DONT GET… https://t.co/wCelyEQiNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat is cold. My cat is never cold. My cat has a bunch of fur to keep him warm. But my cat is cold... y is it 20 degrees outside?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xkhdc Screw that judge. Just trying to assuage his guilt for crushing the carriage horse trade even tho he knew d*… https://t.co/JgIQItyfiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writers_smart Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight.  https://t.co/dV1bRqmseN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aprilmonita Hahaha ohhh good! I thought this was a hard hint to get outta your life!😂😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still wanna meet Snoop Dogg. People gotta help me get bigger. He still doesn’t know who I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcouros I used to use Vacaroo to record my students reading fluency. It was a great tool to share at conferences a… https://t.co/o4aL0g5d5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAX DODGER @AOC wants you to pay 70% taxes but doesn't pay her own taxes. https://t.co/TyIImCT5dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a disappointing announcement to make: the Hot Cheetos asteroids taste just like the Hot Cheetos Puff ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atensnut He won’t he’s got more than half the country standing by his side and we gonna make the dem’s cry like babies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffWTOV9 fisherman rushing spring at Piedmont Lake! They did really well!! Fishing is good!! https://t.co/eSgkUgIYt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Father, Who art in Heaven, hallowed be Thy name. Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done on earth as it is in Heaven… https://t.co/QO6hGO07ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @kelly_clarkson U ROCK, KC! U can understand their sometimes offensive behavior. U are the reigning ch… https://t.co/Go21pWOQjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: It’s a beautiful day to be outside  Also me: Let’s go indoor cycling  #Allergies]]></document><document><![CDATA[A privilege to be part of @pediatricpitch @sxsw judging panel again this year. Twelve start-ups addressing some of… https://t.co/GHG5Oxuqyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill He needs to be charged for Chile and his negotiations there to target American citizens and soil with nuclear weapons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume KAMALA HARRIS IS A CALIFORNIA DONKEY, FULL OF BALONEY, FRAUD, LIAR, AND GREEDY !! ANYBODY WITH A BRAIN SH… https://t.co/I6QEaPL2T4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fat_Matt_32 I register J for kindergarten in a week!!!! 😳😩. Time flies dude!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianJdelumpa It’s a Hallmark holiday anyway, 🤷🏼‍♀️ it doesn’t really count]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieQ82 @ProofBrewingCo @FLBrewersGuild @DannyAller @TLHBeerSociety Give me all the cherry limeade!!! ALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanessaMacawil3 You are very kind. &amp; beautiful outward and inward. Thank you. I appreciate you :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I really just had a breakdown &amp; started crying cuz I realized how old my dog is getting....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefluffa nix that. Lighting back in a serious way and the dog is now under the blanket with me thanks to a crazy thunder crack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1075thegame @_patrickperret @TimHill1075 @WilGunter Will dunks like a cop at Krispy Kreme]]></document><document><![CDATA[#diainternacionaldelgato Hoy en el día del gato 🐱 Velásquez se rindió a los encantos de Los Gatos Jajajaja… https://t.co/0HIBh7Jupx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if #PawfficerDonut is #Flerken?  #PoliceCat #CaptainMarvel  @TroyMI_Police]]></document><document><![CDATA[When pursuing new opportunities “one shouldn’t be just bound by what is asked of you. Always think about what you c… https://t.co/hzodLXo0eO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings you are a true patriot of our American democracy and I thank you🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then someone needs to get on it...fine her arse...better yet, remove her unAmerican arse. Cannot believe US citizen… https://t.co/MTmEMxLLjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonnieWtheJuice bitch i wish unlock your tweets lmaooo but this is definitely us in a couple weeks 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out on the town with my favorite couple.  • Before I left my parent’s house, my mom jokingly said, “Be home by 10!”… https://t.co/qw3h1EqJ5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everyone is open and forthcoming with all of their struggles. Some of the happiest people you know struggle wit… https://t.co/OTax0j9k55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladiosa323 tbh you’ll figure it out. Just believe in yourself . Trust your decision making]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this doesn’t get Clevelanders to accept me as one of their own, I don’t know what will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goal in life is to get invited to an @eltonofficial party. As an anti-social introvert, that really says somethi… https://t.co/GrtgVvMD9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great topic from @re_ross, speaking about #startup life &amp; #WorkLifeBalance at the @dad2summit #dad2Summit… https://t.co/x6VqWbQgSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Shey Looking forward to when the passion between them explodes 🙂🙂💕💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danimichaeli1 I think flash (adobe animate) would be the fastest/easiest (easy to do cycles and stuff)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tribute to Officer Skerski in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/WHZaLDhbbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it’s worth a taste, even though I’ve never tried it!  You need to eat after your ride]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of doctors making discharge recommendations regarding REHAB that are completely different from what we re… https://t.co/967nd3pfwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NievesD50500958 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Trying at what I didn’t hear what the question was about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has intrinsic value. I like to discover new ideas and past good idea. It doesn’t mean what I learn much must hav… https://t.co/wvZlXkygtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackandBrave I went with my @WWERollins Burn it Down shirt.  Got to get me a Beast Slayer &amp; Crossfit Jesus ones next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS @MiamiOH_Skating!! Another Tremendous Accomplishment!!🏆🥇 #RiseUpRedHawks #LoveandHonor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh okay...sorry, wrong thread...I mean to use the one before this one....🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyMarksKrpan @DP_math @SienaDPCDSB @DPCDSBSchools Thank you for presenting and pushing my thinking! I can’t wai… https://t.co/dfwyoeUO8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[US trade deficit surges to 10-year high in Dec. vs est of $57.3B https://t.co/gow4R9FuQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kernaghant Clearly they have no interest in Reconciliation at all. It’s devastating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschofer I have no idea what this means...:except that you are writing a story about spaghetti ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leena_xu @TSM @MissGigglesss_ Definitely with the quality content and brings the excitement TSM would love to have… https://t.co/cZgzG5l1ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMScounselor1 @dms_tcboe @baileymath6 You totally deserve ALL the love! 🥰And, how good is that note “her shoe game is on point”?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When should we take down Christmas lights? Is the tax DEADLINE really for real ect.. I start contemplating the sign… https://t.co/DTgDokEDls]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll stay up til THIS DUMP shiiiiiines like the top of the CHRYSLER BUILDING. #beinganorphanseemedsoglam @ Cara a… https://t.co/ri2theusjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you effing kidding meeeee!?!?!?!!!!!? @MeghanMcCain criying and saying that she is terrified and scared of… https://t.co/QnNQGTNlv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhemNason @astrobri @axfelix You’re right you make a good cheering section]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter storm expected to blanket parts of northeastern US in snow ❄️  https://t.co/k5THiJm9G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland demanded Omar apologize for what he considered a "vile, anti-Semitic slur"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyNoah1 @SharonSharonh10 &amp; sweating out if he was getting STD's😱🤬 #donnie, u r such a dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m mad asl this bitch be running her mouth frfr.. got niggas thinking im childish, whole time ion even speak to the girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpamBeedop2 @DallasStars Just not on March 5th 😉 spare me a game since I'll be there seeing my Rangers. I can't wa… https://t.co/tdH4fao2qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitzgibbonRoss @crogers53 @Fidrocknroll 16 mill for him is not bad at all, go all in win for however long Brady is… https://t.co/5yGj1LDqTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurefireMJ So sad how EVERYTHING is TWISTED. The real TRUTH of the MATTER is that JMICHAEL JACKSON spent time with… https://t.co/B9Gz9nGXMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to live on a hill in Fort Smith, Ar. When my children were small they all thought the sun went to bed in Ok.… https://t.co/EUkpM3nYiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite part of teaching HS is the passion of a student who seeks me out to tell me about all the extra research t… https://t.co/lXDAyMlf2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re right - they all have to be very careful what they say because of potential legal liability. That’s what hap… https://t.co/nWUSWRVK49]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiss’ fave pics 😋🤷🏽‍♀️ . . . PC📸: @quiss_26 . . . #MixedGirlMagic #BlackGirlMagic #Sunshine @ Demoss Hall https://t.co/muTb5RNeJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorbettMini @CNN Yes and it's Trump that has banned them from the military after Obama had changed the rules to al… https://t.co/ntBKHBd5lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Sean Hannity and Conald tRump are both lying hacks and headed for prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVE NO WORDS!!!! I DIDNT KNOW HOW MUCH I NEEDED THIS! 😍😭🙌🏼 #LateLateJonas https://t.co/qKWxUjlkbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DriftwoodRDU @Sostraveluk @thethirstytales @SashaEats @FoodTravelist @MattsRoadTrip @radiantwanderin @GailBenzler… https://t.co/iJJkS2Swnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The many faces of Isabelle Marie 👶🏻😛🤨😄 @ Richfield, Minnesota https://t.co/Y3al9QeIAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂 Yep. I’m almost impressed by how many people say this but have never read the play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this photo I took of damon &amp; beans is so important to me https://t.co/fLFDlWPacQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be.”          Lao Tzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidsMomma @JustKristi @ABC According to the CDC, almost all reported cases of tetanus occur in people who have eit… https://t.co/F6TtrxvP2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IshineBEST @jdsherrod15 This song is from 2017 about her ex husband (I think) she said she “wasn’t paying shit”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_ag_fox_1971 @KariVanHorn @TheSuzieHunter @ChelsaMessinger https://t.co/Dq9AVxlQdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have watched 7 hours worth of 60s rock documentaries this weekend so basically i took history of rock and roll and i’m really fucking cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Santa Rosa: light rain, 53°F 58% humidity, wind 6mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[No presumo ramos de flores 🌹 globos 🎈 regalos 🎁 ni lo que le sigue . Igual no pido nada porque lo que quiero jamás… https://t.co/mVcYdGWfqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[On FaceTime with yvette and this bitch hella loud says “ATLEAST YOU GOT DICK THIS WEEK” mind you my mom’s next to me 😂😭 @yvette_asvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillerrrNatalie Give Me My Points!!! 💯 So proud of these post players!!!  Y’all have really made great strides and… https://t.co/mdelyGWAUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the hot guy that just left my job,  you’re fine AS HELL and i’ll help you bring shit to your truck all day long… https://t.co/n5y830A0Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[yoooo I think about this shit happening WAY too often. nah the 7 train is cancelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littleliinn Oh, I’ve been hearing about that.. I’m going to paradiso in Washington.. stay safe out there.. you kno… https://t.co/2PTwlJU5xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was eye opening to recently learn that only about 8 % of the media is republican but that approximately 40% are… https://t.co/lYgor8hGGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[New hair who dis??? #shag #bangs #bangs #layers @ Wisp+willow salon Yorba Linda https://t.co/kIRYTQAlr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Jared Kushner goes rogue in Saudi Arabia, prompting national security concerns https://t.co/RMbiRDBhoS via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissZindzi In my family the women serve the kids. Then spend their time grabbing bites of food between getting the… https://t.co/c6PVtVwsHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever a Houston Legend! Forever my favorite player! For the past six years I wished this day would never come! 😭😭… https://t.co/HYcUvgjoVs]]></document></documents></author>