<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cdodge2222 If I have this for like 3 more days I’ll be down to fighting weight. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thus, throughout the pages of the Gospel of Mark, there is a growing opening toward the people. In this way, Mark l… https://t.co/VkZHRm6BeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[prom is single handedly the most stressful but most fun thing to shop for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerJ_Cole @CrowleyOnAir @tonyblackburn @RoverDov123 @idriselba @JeffLynnesELO @Par73A @RattyBurvil… https://t.co/22QeF8qRVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I go off for Lent, I will pray more for our country to defend life, that hearts will be changed to love the unbo… https://t.co/uaHzPFp28B]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current mood is Sophie Turner in the new Jonas Brothers music video 👀😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonallendc @ThePlumLineGS @armandodkos Except that in this case she is entirely correct. And #trump will abuse his… https://t.co/dNmQiaIydi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder EXECUTIVE TIME....or a pig out session with a whole stack of Big Macs triple thick and super size that orde… https://t.co/5CqHbe2bX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching all Army when the  #ARMYPEDIA  site went live. We are to cute with our excitement. @BTS_twt  https://t.co/LfLnlCILCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Up Front! 1st place, best vocals and choreography! Awesome job High Impact getting into the fina… https://t.co/llfquHosD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisonkemnerr I tricked Julian into thinking I got another this week 😂🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/vzm6gK0JUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @realDonaldTrump "You're a sexist, egotistical, lying, hypocritical bigot!" 9 to 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animals have feelings!  They know when evil is stalking them. #BeKindToAnimals AMAZING!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwbdimashG @rosy_hinata @dimash_official @WorldsBestCBS Americans love you Dimash! #TWBDimash , #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinemiaSupport @SinemiaApp Hi there, the app wouldn’t let me select my showing tonight so I ended up having to pay… https://t.co/pmnBKQYHiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilAHamOnt Everyone is saying check but it should only be about $30 for extra insurance. I’m not traveling with… https://t.co/rnQEQBJmtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing on the way to work. A beautiful day in the #prettycity! 💋🎶🎤 #TheWeeknd 🎹🎸🕶 #OMA ☀️🚗🏙 https://t.co/JxWEDq4pjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink_About_it Who are they? They should be made to pay that money back! I for one say we the people say No to fund… https://t.co/JsJr3A4ms0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend is texting me about how spoiled and his fiancé is and I’m just like nigga you made her like that 🙄😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 yr ago today me &amp; @thebaileygirl13 worked the worst shift of our lives 🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewHanoverCoSch De-stress! Don't Pop Your Cork On Mondays! https://t.co/swtkwJubBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Discover on Google https://t.co/vb3hb9mYcM Flavor of the week. Khloe and True are better off with your trifling azz gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LittleEmber_ @kensai_official @Gyngerella Anime Expo (Anaheim) circa 2005/2006 in the exhibit hall at a small tab… https://t.co/ZE5OKswVmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaroeNik @TheJimbo64 @WhitlockJason As irritated as I am at your lack of understanding, I’m going to calmly explai… https://t.co/808Uz0fRP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[He followed it up by telling me my boots would look good on the back pegs of his Harley https://t.co/cFGmNjn4KJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yungtrapling I hope you copped that fit, we’re gonna pull up to a club]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nap cat #Chester #catstagram #catson @ Hollywood, Portland https://t.co/pDNy3sePKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un is headed to Vietnam in his special train  https://t.co/WQBIIHInMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to welcome Salata to Peachtree Corners with the Southwest Gwinnett Chamber! Healthy dining is always a gre… https://t.co/W5dRCHHzM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC is a distraction. Don’t turn your back on the rest of the rat pack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 I can't help being alarmed about the 2020 voting machinery and processes. Do we need to ask Jimmy Carte… https://t.co/UeiXssOvJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @theDanforthBIA  -  If you’re searching the hood for pancakes - check out @TheAuldSpotPub where they’… https://t.co/gNMNjVI3x0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky @nitenurse2 @RogueDew Shouldn't Neilsen be more concerned with this than caging babies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muhhkayla watch this dude WHERE are all of these old ass pics this video is a goldmine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s keep to our words pls- Brooooo 😂 @Alex_Sparrow_ @ Bullshit Entertainment https://t.co/WD45jQzYq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need to tour at Miami CAUSE IM FINALLY CLOSE ENOUGH TO SEE THEM LIVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Custom script from today. Thanks Chris! Would love to do more! Email me or call the shop to book. shannonhayward@gm… https://t.co/aZGGoBBZT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun Valentine’s Day Run with the Rise and Run group at Taco Land. I improved on my time tonight as well. @ Viva T… https://t.co/8nSwszPmoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blutospin @3coolkatz @ZombieSquadHQ @GregariousGus @Mygreatredmare @irisesther54 @TeddyTedaloo @TeddysFamiwy… https://t.co/HQTAUOwyQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 what this spineless crew will vote for, especially when it comes to a veto override is a different matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to this dedicated bunch for commuting from across the country for our semi-annual meeting! Looking forwa… https://t.co/WRPrH7S7y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Measles was eliminated from the United States in 2000.  ELIMINATED!!  Travelers with measles continue to bring the… https://t.co/0ibyWlFvxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you put purple and lavender highlights in your hair and it looks natural...you must be a unicorn. 🦄  #beyou… https://t.co/6TgoTfBihF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ars Technica: Microsoft begins work on its 2020 Windows releases in new preview. https://t.co/etRVKNCeEO  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listened to this song tripping and i can’t remember a single word to look it up SOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how my boss thought it was okay to tell my coworkers to wake me up this morning just so I can respond to his… https://t.co/EpwmFRpjTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @Trump454545 She is heavily medicated like marine waters &amp; Dianne feinsteien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people w no waves wear durags more than those who do have waves 😭I don’t get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Steve Scalise: Nancy Pelosi has to remove Rep. Ilhan Omar from the Foreign Affairs Committee |  https://t.co/Agr5SbrY99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unborn Babies are People Too  post  #AbortionIsKilling https://t.co/YSGmlN8zJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[X 100PRE MIGHT JUST NEVER GET OLD THANKS BRUV FROM ANOTHA MUV @BADBUNNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TampaBayDownsFL Tampa Bay Derby win bet on #10 Tacitus and boxing 1,4,10 GL everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sko Chos💙💛 @masyawn  _ Eyes inspired by laviedunprince - wetnwildbeauty Photo Focus Foundation - makeuprevolutionus… https://t.co/jLZSyXmgMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/qNEL35ew9n https://t.co/b4ewtIalDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100_Disable_vet Never use your left hand or your knuckles will be hit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celticriverside We all need Baloo in our lives https://t.co/nQqCVGrVIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChronicTami hey mind signal boosting id appreciate it https://t.co/RQPwCCD8L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I knew there was something fishy abt it when it was first reported.  I'm so glad the Chicago Police… https://t.co/y1MqVYRS9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I love reading...ELAR is my jam! #ThisisCarson @NISDCarson #readingrocks https://t.co/n0qkpRM5kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything cooler than driving to Florida and passing the rocket ship at that rest stop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost crashed, but she kept snapchatting and trapping 😂 #mybestfriend ❤️ https://t.co/iclSuUpTnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lower Body / Core Workout.  Let’s Do IT! @ Onelife Fitness - Rockville https://t.co/FkDrJO99kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm the only one that is always looking somewhere else or grinning at my friend behind the camera tee hee https://t.co/a5XibG5SgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder It’s one in the same. The media is part of the demoncrat party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franmcveigh #studentvoice is CRUCIAL when building a classroom library!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnd200 @Redbunny734 @CBSThisMorning @GayleKing @rkelly Ah. Apologies. She blocked me so, I can no longer see any conversations 🤣🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo who is going to take me to see @gwenstefani in Vegas? I’ve been waiting for this show my whole life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #fox #apron in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa #giftsforher https://t.co/tUkiZySsLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is @j_smoove03 gonna blame me for our friendship being in shambles when he’s the one that forgets to text back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Home Laundry Room And Backyard in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/Lnc7XZasrv https://t.co/ezJVGVMIjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tf are you gonna give us 15 minutes to take a stats quiz with 22 problems?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i always think that being home is gonna reset my mindset but i spiral every fucking time i get here what the fuck is wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD  why do detectives wear uniforms?  I thought they were plain clothed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday everyone! Have a great day &amp; weekend! @cobblepout @PenguinSpinOff @PengyRiddler @MisterPenguin… https://t.co/daZnXMLmEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lukes answer after looking at this picture very intensely was... “some sort of cream” ☠️💀☠️💀😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS INCLUDES DRUG ADDICT ROBERT TRU MOO BULLOCK WHO WORKS AT BULLOCKS MEATS AND IS STUPID ENOUGH TO ADMIT TO DATIN… https://t.co/gTEvlzLVof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a metaphor for how we carry so much on our backs getting little to nothing in return, but if you want to take i… https://t.co/5YZ25ClOzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMalorzo @medpepper @moinanderson @stevie76 @neighlouder @ewannaC @AlwaysChica @A_Badassunicorn @Miss_Lulu1… https://t.co/2V4P3dErvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @quaesivi_1776 @Melly59518342 @greekwarhammer @Linda18319822 @classyprune @SavedSoul1990 @Branko_MA… https://t.co/WWhGWMRTdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexconnorwrite @ampomata @G_Dolman @ChrisPopeWrites @planetearthx2 I know you do this! https://t.co/FQWSNqDbjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please be careful Chinese people’s always want to win but the anointing is the wisdom to make the right decision !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you think you are standing strong, be careful not to fall” (1Cor.10:12). #FoolishConfidence #JesusIsLord]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs I’ve seen memes of Trump pushing a panic button. Please let the mass arrests happen. Even Q posted about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JustLeadersUSA #closeRIKERS Brooklyn Community Forum on 3/20 at 6p.  RSVP: https://t.co/CrM8wkp1SM  #LetsGetFree https://t.co/Z1gHs1RdqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @JCali1967 This Madam is everywhere! The company Trump keeps gets creepier by the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we old timers hear that freestyle music❤️😂 LisaLisa and Cult Jam https://t.co/GVLomYljZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Todos savemos que hay tanta violencia pero no todos los hispanos son hay mas americanos como el que… https://t.co/dVG5S0MIW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly it’s crazy how I actually have time to do things in the morning when I wake when my alarm goes off the first time]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO anyways so let me tell y’all how the wind almost blew my little ass away today]]></document><document><![CDATA[But someone called the police on a little girl in SF for selling water outside her house without a permit WHAT… https://t.co/gaFR0Pr3o3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#womenshistorymonth #poetry #womenpoets Megan DeBolt from "The Girl Made of Hair" https://t.co/GICPsqHvqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriandLarry @GrapeMarbles @LifeNewsToo @realDonaldTrump You are the one who needs to read more. Everything he wr… https://t.co/0FNKWi2ep1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chazfraz8 @NLLBandits Let’s keep that same energy tonight 😂 #LetsGoBandits 🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wouldn’t want to spend an evening with @bbranderhorst and myself? Free beer is also a perk...🌽🌱🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @CatholicPierogi @DavidHarris707 @alexs_ @RosaDeliadelos1 @SeptemberJulie @Jj051301 @mariaemma16… https://t.co/psMQVzvpzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's My Birthday Again!! Pisces Season is here!! You're invited to come party with the Pisces Crew 3.8.19 @[1643872… https://t.co/7iicGqFarj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so I, totally unashamed as a 27 year old lady, love these movies and the 2nd one was SO FAR AND ABOVE AMAZING… https://t.co/AIqoT1ywbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[my FAVORITE thing to say to customers when they ask if a certain watch is for male or female is “well i hope they a… https://t.co/rLUegmcrUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Sanders should give all people 15.00 per hour out of his pocket since he knows nothing about a business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just amusing. #laughter #lol #smile #playful https://t.co/iK8f22lSPp]]></document></documents></author>