<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#JoanMiro is in member previews at @MuseumModernArt -- #MoMA https://t.co/y4x3Zdabn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLeeBlank I would love to have been there! Next time! No doubt you did great, Coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Policy around innovation and technology largely neglects tech’s potential to worsen inequalities, even as examples… https://t.co/HGDr79Wh4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firma de acuerdo con la Cámara de Comercio Andina New York y Gravity Films New York. Taller de Periodismo y Comunic… https://t.co/kEqOeBdOz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghyxion @StuartGrist Hmmmm. Well, there's this ..... https://t.co/d5ISW8IRps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyVol Saw it live on channel 10. That's alot of water, to sink a firetruck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s hella static on stage from what I just seen.  Sheesh!  Or leading up to the stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenGranholm @HowardSchultz @CNN @AOC It’s a pretty good bet that billionaires like the current rate. It’s also a p… https://t.co/DZxh2Sw3TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I ever cooked rice in a pot or a saucepan? No, never. I've always used an electric rice-cooker to cook rice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMyers1971 It’s only fair. @PressSec gets to spread her lies every day. #Trsitor. #Resist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HablandoSana tal vez, por ahora aprovechemos estos días, un abrazo https://t.co/6ANNL0IcOI]]></document><document><![CDATA['You Stupid Liar!': Parents Of Kids With Autism Confront Ontario Minister https://t.co/IAjJj2f8SG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickname2194 @TheMattDowell At least they haven't written a script for this guy yet https://t.co/WWGloGUUCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWellsNFL brought little man down to check out this chicken and waffles thing 👍🏼💪🏼👊🏼 https://t.co/lJrQjR9ohw]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the coast playing guitar for the annual Unwined event at the Liberty theater. Lucked out on weather! @ Astoria,… https://t.co/0FQ85dbrOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willjackson68 @MattWalshBlog I agree. Smollett should be fired. I hope he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin Water crews have now flushed water at more than 900 locations. We continue to respond and perform targeted f… https://t.co/6jFRdN5E9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a fun run!  #AtLeastItsNotSnow!! @ Rockwall, Texas https://t.co/cPukuS24x0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sharpstatus #staysharp #shampoo #wash #washday #booksy #booksybarber #booksyapp #booksybiz #winstonsalem… https://t.co/WZSWwwSPMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic is crawling in #Raleigh on I-440 WB between Glenwood Ave - Exit 7 and Lk Boone Trail - Exit 5, accident at Lk Boone Trail - Exit 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goknickstape @notnicksandberg He didn’t get carried by anyone but the only thing he did better than Bron is shoot free throws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala’s team has be awfully quite today. Is it because she’s being dragging for her breakfast club interview and y… https://t.co/B8rWjC57QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #chiweenie gives opinionated glares while I stay up too late earning some cash cash monies @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/eNU0dNIuxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You coming @ODUParking?  Looking for the Ghent shuttle (at @FoodLion Grocery Store in Norfolk, VA) https://t.co/O29Pn0AZVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELBETOFERREIRO @LaVozDelHEAT @JoePujala @RicardoEMontes @RenatoBermudez @990ESPNDeportes https://t.co/BmJQ0qu0si]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCUniverse Need movie and revive that show now! #Truth I gave you a shock to your system!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actual footage of me watching the last 3 mins of season one of @KillingEve https://t.co/CmqECSNTwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕ Good Morning W🌎rld #HappySaturday ҽղյօվ your աҽҽƘҽղժ 🌞 #ThingsPeopleNeedToLearn 👉 #TrustInHim - #GOD… https://t.co/2H1SQ5u6VI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskBarclaysUS the Barclays mobile app is terrible. The only way to contact other than phone is via twitter. So her… https://t.co/gZbTWeUbnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to argue with what recent society of the past and the present have created.  A derivative of the environm… https://t.co/obdGtuf4Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The importance of water is all around us!   #waterwisdom.… https://t.co/kyvB8qgePR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy totalmente convencido que la vida inteligente sólo existe en la Tierra. No creo que haya mujeres como las de… https://t.co/kbLtI07mGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steaks, a view, and even better company. Doesn't get any better than that! @ Morton's The Steakhouse https://t.co/CKfisa2xA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tú profe de química sube como hacer ejercicios a la web estando en la mierda en términos de resfriado y tu p… https://t.co/LHcoe3IvVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#biotech ☢️ innovations 😷 size L ✂️✂️ B #1OF1 #vintagemashups ♻️♻️ #BWOODKNOWS #NEWWAVE #CASHAPP @ Wood Shoppe by B… https://t.co/nK0WgMLk29]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 players of the Ole Miss basketball team kneeled during the national anthem. What does this really prove? #WPS  (absolutely nothing)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAAF should include the rule...drop kick is worth 4 points. @DAonCBS A fun twist on the field goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just thought of something 🤔catching the Holy Ghost is basically having an anxiety attack 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting day in my hometown. Interested to see how the town handles the players’ response]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlenIII @padigan @billkingDTR This is a great question, and I can confidently say that through @jobsforlife, these… https://t.co/bbUrekNUq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Nervous? White Nationalist plotting to kill Dems crickets 🦗 why no tweets Jr?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my co workers came to work dressed super cute from their dates &amp; im just here in sweats, baggy hoodie &amp; hat 💀😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was the first time doing a full squat workout in a very long time. This was a good day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped pin Near 5948-5924 W 3rd St, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/oz6ibWyxNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Life Time Athletic and Life Spa in Tampa, FL https://t.co/5mXzaykVak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWMN_SportsGuy There are a couple candidates. Don't know the roster too well, but #2 Matt Fink is supposed to have… https://t.co/6PpmdMx9sK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift is the most calculated bitch I've ever seen AND I LIVE FOR IT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I always held a bottle in my right hand in case they got up some courage to ask me 2 much of anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieBEERS10 Scream away brother ! Have @Boogeyman531 shoot me a dm to where to send my half of the bail money,… https://t.co/unquDbqxRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Last I checked, the 3 most populous Muslim nations weren't on the non-e… https://t.co/8TmYlXebIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Somebody send him a copy of Amendment 1 of the US Constitution and a pacifier. Baby's crying again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Critic: if we put this much energy into our movies that we do recruiting we would be gods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayApex Let’s gooooo!!! Thank you guys for this so much!!! You guys are the best @PlayApex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anderson actually has 11 for the Packers.  He’s been dynamite on the boards as well for Omaha South. #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuteSwanTruth @macleans You have zero idea of the situation!  Autism is judged on a scale and what she’s done is d… https://t.co/tzJA9sZiQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1029thebuzz "          ;)             "......... https://t.co/osquLJFQ6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkotscho2 @DespinaBarton @PatrickWelter @OrlandoCitySC @dkotscho2 I think the one you sent me got lost in the mail 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing sky trying to get up to Minden Nevada in the Sierras. The snow was too thick, but the pics were worth it… https://t.co/2EYQOTep6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Water is one of the few streets downtown without cameras, how convenient!   Who carries bleach with them at 2… https://t.co/D1Hcn9PFpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is 5 am. For the last hour a little human has been poking me in the face while singing what seems to be a never-… https://t.co/l4qjwFKR3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_T_3_K @Kellie2727Paula @headhunterchron @acestwo59 @DJNazSD @TimothyKopp2 @DARgirl92 @Buckbeavers @paul7916… https://t.co/yKXFeKYCce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the hats fly!  JC Bele scores again to give @BP_BlackHawks a 4-2 lead with 6:57 to play in the third.  Blackhaw… https://t.co/ghSRZytAKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_nnaheel @Alexiadlcruz Happy Birthday! And nice jeans I like looking at them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speckproducts please tell me you’re going to add some more color designs to the presidio grip case for the iPhone XS MAX #please #thankyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #TellTheTruthTECO event is about to kick off! https://t.co/BFGS1FhPoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have congresspeople like @AOC who fight for her constituents and this country day in and day out, and then we ha… https://t.co/4ACAhJBbQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheistRepublic “It is the belief and not the god that counts.” — Wallace Stevens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prime Gainesville - office - retail- showroom space for lease. Take a look. Former Red Cross location.  More video… https://t.co/qeRMcBpueG]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Merkley rules out White House run but will seek reelection in Oregon: Oregon Sen. Jeff Merkley wil… https://t.co/NRDjxEcTgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codywanner All of the noise makes it happen to standout but if you have a different voice/message from the rest that’s what will stand out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReelTalker @rolandsmartin You’re missing the point.  Netflix’s has a vehicle to promote/push “IT’S” films. Others… https://t.co/hmRZ9QiECb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMickyDolenz1 : Hey Micky. I want to give you my condolences on the death Peter. You and Mike have  a very bless… https://t.co/rcj03VWoqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how you spin this story: 1. Don’t be cheap- it’s a horrible label 2. Put yourself in others shoes and see… https://t.co/99LpcqKwra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sreekyshooter @hestillhere Some people are just looking to start an argument. Can’t reason with them or have a con… https://t.co/xju5Fqvdtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStraightHops @BellsBrewery @badhopper @ephoustonbill @JonMontag @JohanBBT @zappafaye @OkiTimes @Paul_TheBeerGuy… https://t.co/SecxaTA6iJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let all things be done decently and in order.” 1 Corinthians 14:40 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skiers evacuated after chairlift breaks down at Northstar resort - San Francisco Chronicle: Skiers evacuated after… https://t.co/n6Sonjkf7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssReFocus @AnastasiaRoseXX @XFREAXX @legal_porno @TonyBrooklynxxx @antonioblackxxx @yves_morgan @Dylanbrownxxx Love those sexy Heels🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoTheBay @daughters_band @indysf 😍 When do you announce the ticket winner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinoPuccio Sort of. He was like Higuain junior to me. Clearly loads of talent but just a godawful attitude duri… https://t.co/CMrBdo65ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop trying to absolutely get my vote with that kinda talk. One thing at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have a pretty face and a bf who can get me tequila 👽@ChrizzyCream]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biggirlslay The greatesdt publicist  cant help if his client goes rogue in a live interview! Would love to be the… https://t.co/IfZJfxN8ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[She did not create the system she lives with.  We created it, you and I.  We vote for the system.  I doubt she vote… https://t.co/tr3fbEJcPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME UNC: 42 DUKE: 32  Blue devils struggling from deep 2-20 AND without Zion after losing him within the first minute of the ball game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break up with your old job.  https://t.co/BYurPrhqd4 #ValentinesDay https://t.co/wrQflfaXR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just typed “midcentury hutch” into Craigslist and realized that I’m closer to 30 than 20.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VictoriaPBS season 3 finale tomorrow at 9pm in the U.S. on @masterpiecepbs. Victoria will be back for another seas… https://t.co/tybc64nfdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElJefeDeJefes4C @10bvbygxxn17 I usually go to this spot off northwest hwy but they close kinda early and i was hun… https://t.co/kkkRcbQXTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[GEORGETOWN IS relying on the senior citizens with terrible BACKs for a homecrowd to eek out this win]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited, got the first #print samples of my #painting ‘The #Gathering’ yesterday. It will be the first of my wor… https://t.co/woCYuRUkmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a SUPER PILS by @wrenhousebrew at @WrenHouseBrew — https://t.co/xDXK9zqOee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever Mario party 8 is played someone always comes out hating the game😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early Fall and Late Fall are a wonderful times in the North. All the summer tourists are gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelsteadJr @cathmckenna @EcoSenseNow What evidence do you have that earth’s paleotemperature went up slowly in… https://t.co/SJIWjBXNjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what the caption is I will watch this every time! #goodjobgoodeffort Mr. Lesks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my best friends in the world! I love you so much man and I’m glad I get to be your friend… https://t.co/pEi0fMZvCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLBlackhawks Can he carry the @NHLBlackhawks  to the first wildcard spot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_Knight_LOE Proud of who of you’ve become. Happy for you and your future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dnc chairman will not let Fox  any democratic national debates, Shame on all  media for not banning together on thi… https://t.co/L7vf7UBER2]]></document></documents></author>