<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This was a very entertaining two hours and if you didn’t watch or listen you missed some great stuff. Like his rif… https://t.co/Nqzbewh7Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered the @CoolerMaster MM830, I keep refreshing the tracking on it https://t.co/PJ8X99zfMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisissigrid does the rest of the album have the same flow as “Sight of You” and “Don’t Feel Like Crying”? If so t… https://t.co/SGsUtKoSC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelpage_ @ParisHilton @elizabeth_rage  actually @ParisHilton is one of my followers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLCCTurf @glccturfmec Woops it fell the wrong way and took the one down next to it too!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I send my friends me making breakfast every morning and they reply with “you make the same shit everyday” lmao https://t.co/xQdWNuId2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you had won all the Senate seats where you won the electoral college (due to Russian collusion)… https://t.co/M5tXWJ03Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ufffffff !!!   Que buena canción de @piso21music #TeVi 🔥🔥  Y cuando yo te vi, te vi, te vi, te vi 🎵 https://t.co/ZgWMxGnepD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EVIDEGARAY Arriba mis Águilas. Una golondrina no hace verano, gatitos... O como ves pulpi? @ElPulpomo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Craig1140 @Ben11486471 @globalnews You may not be able to most of America does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one open seat next to me in the grand ballroom to hear @realDonaldTrump’s speech at #CPAC2019 FIRST COME FIRST SERVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cxtallena @rosyheejin I don’t mean to persist. I am genuinely curious and come in total peace.  If all Christians… https://t.co/aLBUQjWEzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Everybody get ready #LibraScale  drops 3.2019  ___dezzy hit the #LinkInBio his bio My #brother got some #fire 🔥 fo… https://t.co/TTtyjidnfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dressed for Picture Day at New Salem! #RocketPride https://t.co/11oUNvQAor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badgalst3ph I know he was the only one she didn’t have with her brother 🤷🏼‍♂️ so maybe that had something to do with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need to keep it simple - roasted chicken thighs marinated in lemon juice with rosemary, smashed potat… https://t.co/PWnqw1NcnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[New quote paraphrased from Ricky Gervais “After Life” ......Society is great when people plant trees even though th… https://t.co/8mx1tYcaIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I called Freese’s walk off just cuz of me seeing him back when he was in Lake Elsinore, remember ya roots baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10APG Enhorabuena crack! Que sean muchos más en el equipo de mis amores 🐯⚽️ UANL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/EmtSkI9MWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Salem_Statesman We’ve been locally focus grouping these types of “sex harassment in the workplace” cases. Watch an… https://t.co/hsXF22nxYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenifmuse:  "❇️EMERALD OUT NOW❇️ STREAMING ON ALL PLATFORMS  CATCH THESE WAVES 🌊 2nd quarter! #newmusic… https://t.co/FtRYZq6WjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirensoIiIoquy @bsfarrington If it’s not a Presidential run then it will not be a major announcement. https://t.co/Kjex38ZHYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how being in a good mood can impact your entire day and surroundings man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expect Pillow Guy to be the next Attorney General after Trump bullies Barr from office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be with Rebel Girl on this gloomy rainy day like cuddle me to sleep babe ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all who attended our Mustang Round Up. We are very exited to welcome our Class of 2023! https://t.co/ILgx1GvUd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyUwhat @angiinjackson @clarionledger If you'd given them that idea in advance they might have taken it. But why… https://t.co/HX02RIJyKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer @squash86 @chaosorbFTW You can only play Doomsday if you have Hive Mind out. Done it, feels great 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigunit1865 @RuthSevereWx @MboroSevereWx Lol look ppl a simple question posed from a response already given. Turn… https://t.co/9YNpk2Grjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hospitality of Sleep Inn I-75 N Sarasota always appreciated for Monday wrap work.  An eclectic two weeks at Panama… https://t.co/bU4iQJPZ9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is a Captive Insurance Company Right for Your Construction Business: CLA (CliftonLarsonAllen) - Is a Captive Insura… https://t.co/vIoMoqBI1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need a new phone.... I've changed carriers but still videos buffer... @TMobile sorry for leaving. 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddlandstore How are you guys being beaten by Image? You guys are so much better than them. Both in enthusiasm, p… https://t.co/L2QM8I41Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cody, wtf were you thinking? Ticia, great effort. Whang was just the better fighter tonight.  Askren, hangs I there… https://t.co/cqXa5ERgjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Poderoso La primera vez que escuché esta rola fue un 14 de Febrero en el programa que tenian @ruleiro y @sopitas,… https://t.co/Q63mw6crV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/Sudc0YwR2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me every Saturday night falling asleep to Blues Before Sunrise on IPR https://t.co/48ay2ttdLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielGriffis @trailblazers @Biofreeze Trailblazers are laying well because they grabbed Enos Kanter, strongest man in NBA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No, they’re voting on whether a @POTUS can bypass Congress when it has specifically told him,”No!”… https://t.co/oZ3uxlxMAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big backside hit by @seamans_ila1 #SEGHSOFTBALL https://t.co/ydU8ushX4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time https://t.co/39dnrzYwQ5  #rodeohouston #houstonrodeo #houstonrodeo2019 @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/hMRz9QiaXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my bad ass sidekick @ Memphis, Tennessee https://t.co/CLm5qgM2Pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuff said #nbaallstar #gettingmydrankon @ Sports One Bar &amp; Lounge https://t.co/OLl7Bqnjtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The MSM knows that most Americans know they are corrupt yet does not care]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe not the whole states but at least the politicians and the governors,  might consider adding VA to the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teens and young adults who terrorized black children during integration are in their 60s and 70s today. I will… https://t.co/tHsmD1UQG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s Christmas morning and Santa’s coming down the chimney! Im gonna murder your family !”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hard to put into words how much I hate KState On par w/white leftists!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Michael Powell sounds just like his brother Josh!  @thecoldpodcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @JohnMorganESQ Dude can't even drive himself to work he has had so many traffic citations (wink wink).… https://t.co/ynp4qt5Kol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summit collapse breaks hearts in South Korea, leaves Moon losing face .  ⁦@realDonaldTrump⁩ They sent the WRONG man… https://t.co/AG5VFoJ3zK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakthrough innovation is rarely performed by a single actor from end-to-end. https://t.co/etn3Mg6fVs via @RotmanMgmtMag #innovation]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Flynn is a true American hero just because he supported Trump they went after him ....So sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satyanadella Do you think email is outdated for today's busy workplace? With Microsoft's big AI developments I'm c… https://t.co/4JeU0ou3Bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! I’m running a fundraiser for one of the survivors of the TCNJ Car Crash back in December. Here is the link to t… https://t.co/yOrR5lR6I1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenDeFalco Great way to celebrate Mr Silverman.  You’re a great friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guns to protect Hollywood at the Oscars? Gee! I thought... https://t.co/T5wQkbMoUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kojoshow  per our phone discussion, here is MPD enforcement for 2018. 29,857 tickets written by officers. https://t.co/dzD3eXqN0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatJunkman Really don’t know. I only know he tweeted some crap and then deleted his account. Don’t really follow… https://t.co/DR4Y8uSxC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey Mr Ed, please cut out all fiber from your diet so you will stop spewing out all the gases crap you spew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLifshatz I stopped watching after Louisville cashed 1H and I'll probably be wrong, but 7 seemed high 2H. Everyo… https://t.co/sYirg3x5vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah but you're there as a pawn of communist powers, so it doesn't really count, though congratula… https://t.co/ZhsKOv0XDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvaArachnie @ManyVids Wow your fucking sexy!! I'd love to have you fuck me  While I suck on those sexy nipples!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will start setting this plan in motion. Is there a start date in the future or do we start now? I really don't li… https://t.co/9YVwNppjE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @OutlawedMind @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/hV9bVZ1mqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoofyDoug I tweeted a little recap - food was very good.  Entertainment was fun.  We enjoyed our evening and the r… https://t.co/Qzf9D7r1FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianheadwelch Just completed watching this! Way to be real, way to share your faith. You’re doing more good for t… https://t.co/YBXshxwT1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legit got home today, turned on Jeopardy on Netflix, then got a text from my girlfriend with the news 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBaileyVO @TroyBakerVA Yus! First Fruits Basket and now Catherine? Gonna be a good year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MooreOrion Yeah this is a few picks in, backup plan, sol ring  and the lotus are gone at this point i believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buster_ESPN @DSimonMD Still you are wrong , it’s time for the Padres to spend . , who says they’ll have the possib… https://t.co/3j6BIU6EJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeverSassyLaura @nucleargrrl Unfortunately a nuclear reactor has never been built on time or on budget in the Unit… https://t.co/m9KPTKFRoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost time! Our wildcats are ready! #WESwildcats #WeGotThis https://t.co/b4Piyy4YYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomasoakes I used to balk at how crazy that state is with the death penalty until I realized it results in less Texans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Kentucky / Ohio State Line in Cincinnati, OH https://t.co/IB8GgS06Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/zGdJqkS5jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend just sent me this and I’m upset because it’s basically how I am at the end of every day and he just go… https://t.co/DHFvjCJH0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpOrBust2020 im sickened to hear his voice even ,,,,, whats he gonna say when the shoes on a different foot ,,, namely😎 HIS ...!!!! '''']]></document><document><![CDATA[@CW_Arrow @TVcody I think #Arrow may be fav. @TheCW show right now. Though I'm probably forgetting something. Didn'… https://t.co/t1v3DS4AqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecheckdown How is falling on the ground and getting up a ‘cold’ route? Lol FOH 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simpolism @byrneseyeview Not sure but it feels like a lot of Tesla-related tweets are calls and puts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, who is building your site? The main IMAGE to the story is a screen grab of a VIDEO of a white woman's tear. I… https://t.co/KalMvgfX0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saddened by the deadly Ethiopian Airplane crash bound for Nairobi killing 149 passengers and 8 crew members. #30 na… https://t.co/hIkK76bs6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gordon Central HS (Calhoun, GA):  looking for an assistant coach going into the 2019 season that has experience coa… https://t.co/WgnQLQsiWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on some submissions for mentor placement at a workshop coming up in May. Excited! #5amwritersclub… https://t.co/fxqLr6zczC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for all the Five Finger Death Punch shinedown amaranthe halestorm inthismoment zack brown Ghost band]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/ they will simply turn it on again down the road? Havimg turned off their soul at work, do they think they will b… https://t.co/vl8FU1q4Cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Few million dollar app Ideas I got. Cant wait to get in the lab and test.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSUgym Nominating @mckennamckelley’s floor routine. GEAUX TIGERS!!!!🐅 🐅 🐅 🐅🐯🐯🐯🐯🐅🐅🐅🐅 Btw 💜 the new leos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsruthalica I am sorry we didn’t march more when I was in school.  I remember telling my father that my generatio… https://t.co/twNlxMXyLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got an invite to join some thing called “Who’s Who”. Anybody out there want to tell me what the hell that is… https://t.co/bUCMoMjHx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Cohen hearing is a big waste of time so far. Is anyone on either side going to ask a substantive question abou… https://t.co/uIknYJl5OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completely fucking wrong, douche bags. But I’m more shocked how you’re gonna video tape the whole convo.... this fu… https://t.co/GqGKY2pztJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cute is this? // #Valentines2019 // @LEAP_Spark @LEAPagency @LEAPframe @LEAP_AMP // https://t.co/pcGZySbDyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #flexfriday everyone! Race season is here and with @bengreenfield greek peak this weekend I think you could us… https://t.co/5SfCOifaHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaWatson @RapeCrisisEandW @EVAWuk @emmacharlotte May God help you to repent for your sins or he's doing that to… https://t.co/vGsWTWutRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliensexbean you two are gonna make me puke up my balls pls BE CONSIDERATE some of us are HONREY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeARosas90 Para ser honesto yo hubiera reaccionado igual que Fury xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute discussions with the rising sun before Apache goes live on B-18. Photo courtesy of PFC Wilson, I Co/3-1… https://t.co/mRAZkpijn3]]></document></documents></author>