<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BabbleNow @RealCandaceO Show them this. It's self explanatory https://t.co/Rx0FKRHWOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We ask our spouses and our children all the time: ‘What are you thinking?’ and ‘How are you feeling?’.  Why is it… https://t.co/6vwDu59pTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRashida so Huss money how about your colleagues who use tax payers money to cover up sexual harassment. How is… https://t.co/jtljGyz142]]></document><document><![CDATA[The holy trinity of places to settle your beef with some scrub https://t.co/s1bJUYPS7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasCastingsLtd  We are a specialist manufacturer of tungsten carbide tools that produce a wide range of carbide in… https://t.co/lS0JsTGcxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayy_yo_sean @barstoolsports smart dog owners that are trying to save on dog food, let them get their fill of peanu… https://t.co/KLYrcsPMKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HockeywthHannah @ira This. Street copy of the Lion King for yours truly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid @Jax6655 The first time I became aware of the tactic was, strangely enough, Britney Spears. One da… https://t.co/VBXPCS509N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtinctionR Mass delusion now filtering down to the children. So tragic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me at carnvl next month (4/20/19)! I've got something up my sleeve! Not to mention our team should be reppin… https://t.co/VmZoVhTBly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling with a stick before showtime 💀 @ Smokers Castle https://t.co/yhkuhlytFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great evening celebrating Hospice Brazos Valley’s 30th Anniversary last month! https://t.co/1pCxsAh92p]]></document><document><![CDATA[TREBELLE IS OPEN TONIGHT at 5! (The Lodge will open tomorrow at 11:30) Bolognese, Mozzarella, Caramelized Onion and… https://t.co/PpRgCdQWQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEGraves @BustedOpenRadio @davidlagreca1 @bullyray5150 Ummm. What about your great friends from the Garden State?  🙋🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por cierto, que partidazo dio Hugo Ayala anoche. Llegó a Tigres en el 2010 y juega como si fuera su primera tempora… https://t.co/Btv44dK8PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long day to end the short month, I want to thank all my friends and family who showed support and reposted… https://t.co/Iz3zDwb3pg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganBolton7 @2fan22 @TheCatchFence Glad to know I’m not the only one who does this 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliinkster playing a beautiful par three thequarrygc   Check out the hummingbird in the 1st photo. Swipe 👈🏼 for t… https://t.co/VRmIHqgZgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[top 10 most listened to songs are all fad and 1 rihanna... taste! 😌 https://t.co/9wjQ1L9Iiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's tough not to argue chocolate and coffee is the greatest combination* of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaterWilliams @finebaum I’m not an Oregon fan. I’m a longhorns fan. They beat your precious UGA team. Not just bea… https://t.co/AKHhWGPUht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning everyone, i want to thank jah for waking me up this morning.. bless up, bless up to the most high almighty!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Can you investigate this I seen this on social media someone posted in a comment!  https://t.co/IjNzN1e0gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did shirk responsibilities as far as building this bookcase I bought but eh..... I’ll be aight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcox4council Against, the RCC has no authority in the matter. The council needs to stay in their lane and listen t… https://t.co/tVQxejP9Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Salvation Army Thrift Store in Jersey City, NJ https://t.co/xSwzn6m3Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carlos is manipulative as fuck. Women fall for his bullshit cause he’s got the Mario Lopez look going on. I see right through his antics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is #34 bruh u just letting this just shoot all type of lay ups on you bruh 🤦🏽‍♂️ I know you coulda block some of those lay ups]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go ahead and call into work, cancle your appointment, or miss class. Tell them I said it’s too dangerous and people… https://t.co/PXndCCtruo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wallykurth Never. Don’t tell her I tweeted this or I’ll be in big trouble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Qconnealy19 @bjohnny190 I’ll give him the benefit of a doubt and say working a session 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veedash_ @its_mrsvenus I was just tryna mind my business, sheesh https://t.co/ZIYxsgPqVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If I EVER want your opinion, I’ll have someone beat it out of ya!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOOB VS. PRO!!! ART EDITION (ft. Vanessa Michelle) https://t.co/2oPkbmXECP via @YouTube new video from my son Micha… https://t.co/1pac5hbeFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @PalmerReport? You’re pushing it? I’m not going to lower myself to defensively due to offensive tacti… https://t.co/yZ7bvbXNQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUsportsAcct @Trogdor_gE @marchmadness @KStateMBB @kstatesports Lol at least people are at the games though https://t.co/NxTtmRjrmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrump_1 They're consistent. Was Jeff Hardy's push derailed after his DUI last year? Both Uso's have had alcohol-r… https://t.co/ZXmjxL2jRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a Trap! #TechnologyKilledOurLove @TrapperRocks  (l to r: @SeanKellyGuitar @emmgryner @timtimleck @FGryner) https://t.co/dKkPjDNRT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westy7278 @JohnKincade @KingJames Where’s all the folks that said he’d be mvp and the lakers would make playoffs..… https://t.co/dUoQ3EdOJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody please find and purchase this for me and I’ll be your personal slave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulldog Brushback: Mississippi State might be better than most predicted. https://t.co/5Vd4xDOFJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson Probably not the only one pointing this out, but didn't @JussieSmollett use the @USPS to execute portions of the #fraud?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever wonder why Voip is not a regulated service? @jeffpulver  explains why on this episode of #TelecomDisruptors :]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings from Greenville. Covering some SEC Women’s Basketball Tournament before heading back to CoMo. Missouri ti… https://t.co/8P7jl0RkwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since managing the @smcccougar Guadalupe Center I've had the chance to work closely with the Pascua Yaqui Tribe. Th… https://t.co/xIzIr6mpZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck you. I have lost 48 pounds in four months and my life is improving in all aspects at age 38. Idiot! #keto… https://t.co/FsI1tBqbpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deleted @facebook. Never felt better. Much less screen time in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which one is your weakness? #Nostalgia #GonnaMakeSomePplVeryHappy @ La Esperanza Bakery &amp; Store https://t.co/R70dWnDudp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#grow #growing #maturity #stronger #helpothers #othersarecountingonyou #openarms #youmatterhere #lincolnil #lincoln… https://t.co/5xQO7A8TZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilegal aliens cost $602,999,936 this day. Build the wall would be one of the most profitable businesses for the eco… https://t.co/bq7FhSlnQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This right here? Classic ally behavior. So proud of you, @SSCJoCoKs.  And she brings up a great point, too: pro-LGB… https://t.co/UzJHEFHX8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really hasn’t hit me yet that this is literally it for my experiences with revenue sports as a student college.… https://t.co/FYcyuQ53XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WASBAPPIN I went Red eighteen months into W.J. Clinton's Administration when I realized I had voted for the guy th… https://t.co/d1EUWmjhrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju @Jim_Jordan has no care for the law whatsoever when talking about republicans. Or abusing wrestlers for that matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbaumspeaks @ABaumgarten8517 You sound like a bunch of superintendents !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor Back in the Revolutionary day, they’d be loyalists. They love their dependence on their monarch and all s… https://t.co/y6dP17ywR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshEberley Its not hard...its obvious. PG has jumped layers over Kyrie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Well? What's wrong with that? For me it only means that President Trump is too busy doing his job t… https://t.co/N3UvtRf9K7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess is @Nike will now stop using high fructose corn syrup in their shoes. #zion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJonesRadio And heavily republican isn’t exactly a great description given we have the 2nd most democratic dist… https://t.co/zKczOnuTUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[IQ has been great defensively but man this games a 12 point game if he was better on offense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo retweetfor vets! 11% of homeless are veterans.with ptsd and mental health issues. I am trying to help and use… https://t.co/IiubOhtY80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @DonaldJTrumpJr And it cost the tax payer millions, and the Democrats let it go on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest Have you seen who works at the craft burger place? Twirled mustaches and cat eyed glasses for miles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders defends Omar: Can't equate anti-Semitism with 'legitimate criticism' of Israel https://t.co/ATB6SPRq16]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlurriesNYC @ MTA Subway - St Lawrence Ave (6) https://t.co/M6Gkn0rYl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevis_sundgren @JRC5500 How you like them wheels @trevis_sundgren https://t.co/aPpjbrAxC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/HalhycYIm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never kissed that fan’s phone and told him how much you appreciate having people stick their phones in your fac… https://t.co/2BfQudVVPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a mother…I love this! I was not blessed with children of my own, but I... https://t.co/gYrQxUPI9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @ThisWeekABC @POTUS I base this not on what I personally think, rather solely on what Democrats say on TV starting with @RepAdamSchiff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @Pampeeps The only thing they got was the 1.375 billion for continuation of the wall and some of the… https://t.co/GBdf8o3MnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling in The Hot Tub - Enjoying The Snow - St George Utah  #stevehmcintosh #SteveMcIntosh #McIntosh #Hotel… https://t.co/1IRVSnquDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Thank you, it was nice having you along for the ride! I can't speak highly enough of the Disney cast memb… https://t.co/bCXzcQKQEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyred1956 @grasshoppr93 @cherokeesher2 @girlsreallyrule @sunrainsunrain @andrerucker51 @Rosie @CraigCo62… https://t.co/Od5j3cv9P1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Scarlett13 i will show you my piece you show me your ass cell me on instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tobias31 @BenSimmons25 @JoelEmbiid @JimmyButler 🤣🤣🤣always smile...no worries🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa Ministers of the Crown and @OntarioPCParty MPPs. Resign. You represent a small time hood who cares not… https://t.co/8pWKXdtPst]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlitaBattleAngel was okay, sometimes even good. Empty theatre, though. Rough... good for anyone with a 14 year old daughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SconnieTrader @followtheh @77cyko when does the “millennials killed shitty pizza” headline come out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our President @realDonaldTrump has the interest of our country. Maxine Waters has the interest the her family and h… https://t.co/Ul6x68fVL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm watching Evil Genius on Netflix. This shit is like a real life Saw. DaHell they be doing in Erie?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksatnews They can have my guns ..when they pry them from my cold dead hands !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@istartchangeri @Amica @CitizensBank @Amgen @Fidelity @InfyFoundation @SenWhitehouse @JimLangevin @GovRaimondo “What a great idea!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me - Baby Bell Trail Run https://t.co/eU41OWqJll @rangerrach81 @KeithPaluso @willskerrym @swright0422 @dcsprunclub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffdotseth @DavePalet Looking forward to seeing YU cry when the #Padres win the west, Palet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeggibbs Thank you #cdnmedia and thank you #JWR for creating a self serving scandal which ended up serving only… https://t.co/rvaygC0zl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Raspberry Thunder by @MuskokaBrewery @ City of Kingston — https://t.co/MwmZljQolF]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you don't give it to the one who made this s*** https://t.co/IogBUeCYlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any doubter of solar really needs to go do the research. Leading with solar in California. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timothygiordano I meant to say “year ahead”.   I guess you got that tho. Stay awesome Tim,  I adore your tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone help me understand why ppl listen to music w headphones when they’re alone in their room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Ordered Officials to Give Jared Kushner a Security Clearance https://t.co/DfmQ6fiFgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaKarenina @AvneeshChandra Avneesh I think she's confusing us for each other. Seems racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time #trump opens his mouth.  #Oscars #SpikeLee https://t.co/YBPsnXJJ3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apschuyler Nice try, sport-o. Waiting for @michaelllee7 to drop the mic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting work challenging the narrative of the necessary conditions for the corporation. Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, this’ll be brought in for the G&amp;G gang! - Drinking an Old Formula by @lacabrabrewing at @LaCabraBrewing  — https://t.co/lJ0bbocPji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Idaho Firefighters for getting PTSI treatment under work comp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acknowledgement on this day to... @julieroginsky @LeslieMarshall @JessicaTarlov @WendyOsefo @CynthiaNixon… https://t.co/1UXEfBmtJD]]></document></documents></author>