<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I know this is unpopular. Things are looking up for the Raiders. They just acquired one of the best receivers in fo… https://t.co/oNBJ5khb5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HockeyRenegade Agreed! Despite morning breath, a good@morning beautiful kiss is the equivalent of a Texas sunrise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody know where I can get one of them Professor Xavier/Wall-E hover chairs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judith_IP @1slclarke @DevinNunes When I was a child, straws were made of paper. They still are. However cost is th… https://t.co/cDxqSNUbAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSquawk @RushThroughTime @SquawkCNBC I think @JoeSquawk is overall crankier about everything since Matlock got c… https://t.co/BUsUxRU7PT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyForney3 Are you still thinking sunset is gonna be good?  I'm having my doubts. 🧐 @TravisABC13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExploreWithErin Who in their right mind would ever take them kids to Shangri-La??? https://t.co/5Ib76Kl6S7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEMorin73 @BroadStHockey @billmeltzer @hinx Why would the NHL want small market teams in the playoffs over the Flyers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heelgemini @restmanager_chi Not sure what’s better, the audio or the video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Whoa, they have an Appa POP  @Ormendahlx: That’s that big flying bitch from Avatar right? https://t.co/7BFiisjhNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trodgers_4 .........first of all no you did not. Second of all HUGE MOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can remember when Cooper and Peyton were the kids sitting on top of the ladder, with Archie standing behind them.… https://t.co/QOcWRilZwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertoDruetto Needed to have my gallbladder removed about 36 hours ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Break means I am working to music in some sort of 1989 time warp... World Party... Toad the Wet Sprocket...… https://t.co/3VMydwxKdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Coppell, TX #ProjectMgmt job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: POS / Technical Su… https://t.co/iswmE7Pluu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Pig Day! Enjoy! #fridayfeeing #TGIF https://t.co/9gkWmeOBZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephanpastis I hope this doesn’t end up like the Ham Fisher/Al Capp fued...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAZZIE_AKA @lindsbehonest @BeckyLynchWWE @WWE Yeah, I like the Rhonda turning heel angle but everything else about… https://t.co/41B6CSpIKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patmiletich Wait a minute Pat. This dude is claiming Iowa but those trees in the background are awfully green... “… https://t.co/Q5iQbVYORI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PercyChuggs @matthew_btwins Twins missed out big time on being the home for a Ben Revere home run 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminSolak @GrindingTheTape @TheJoeMarino WOW! What a chocolate starfish, this guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sad to see this go. #pkfab @ PK Fabricating, Inc https://t.co/8wfKhPzzWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I know who this person is - actually met her at a party.  She was intelligent, experienced and knowledgeabl… https://t.co/TFUr1uQmtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words of the Morning  " GIVING THANKS "  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/L9NtJBRr4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca jamás se pensó llegar más abajo de lo que vive el país. No hay precedentes en Latinoamérica con cualquier otr… https://t.co/WsF517mIri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marujatarre Mi padre era especialista en turbinas y mi padrino estaba a cargo de la planta eléctrica Punta Gorda e… https://t.co/nXv6jN97yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRT_92 slightly joking here lol. i did it for 6 months and lost a lot of weight but it’s also a pain in the ass to keep up with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have I been up since 5 am? Because these idiot trucks can't go without using their j brakes for more than two s… https://t.co/ldqSDwYsBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisongesiotto John Adams defended some soldiers  They were innocent of murder. Changed the world.  In this build… https://t.co/S3nbzREc3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechConnectify A 1992 movie called Sidekicks with Chuck Norris and Jonathan Brandis was filmed in Houston. There's… https://t.co/sYIdTLGReb]]></document><document><![CDATA[People with this opinion don’t understand market value and should quit talking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting Dirk jr at college @ Sonoma State University https://t.co/ypW7c2sAx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraynerJeff @MFinHarsh @Tayaiko_ @koojababy @Lakers LeChoke finished that game 4/18.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't have to twist your words, I believe this is the only time you ever acknowledge my Twitter so what does that… https://t.co/Bi8s38NBHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alvilda_OW SAME. At least dive was fun to watch, there were fights. With GOATS we get a fights only when ults are available 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh, my dad NEEDS to stop comparing public school to university. This is the third time recently that he woke me u… https://t.co/IJfo2xhyo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TySmith_6 Man you in Oklahoma, get the good stuff from the states on the coast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elway’s Folly? As options dwindle Broncos acquire Flaco rights Quite late in career #haikuchallenge (late)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think when LeBron said he was activating playoff mode he meant JR. Smith playoff mode smh 🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🚮🚮🚮🚮 #ImDone… https://t.co/er7nQZa4og]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPN_FDJ A Messi hay que darle el Camp Nou (Estadio del Barcelona) y todo el dinero que pida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis . Orlando is not far from Tallahassee https://t.co/Lyg7htOiGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp The Guy in the WhiteHouse lied 9000 times, and you have the balls to call this guy a liar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycSassenach @SamfromSpain @KavanaghVickie @PenPure1 @Debra_McGill @newenglandgrl @SaraMD15 @KarramKaren… https://t.co/HxeeBdh9WY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NYC Dept of Sanitation M-12 in Manhattan, NY https://t.co/yDDtGoD6OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be making an appearance on the show today, make sure you tune in at 1 pm to 106.9 WWSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss iamcalu The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Be In The… https://t.co/R7ZAuZMGo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaFKenney1 I’ve done both. I even did one book in alternating chapters. I kinda like first person because the… https://t.co/LRKevDWkVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leslie Willis/Livewire (DC)  And yes, I'm aware that she's the second character named Livewire on this list. https://t.co/sA2UJZhij0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turtletot43 @CJ_usawtfm @ckshowalter Narrator: "Yes, yes it is..." https://t.co/TZof8WZqHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vitostellino I think Kaeps representatives are just fishing for another lawsuit.. Heck, if he could sue for collusion twice!? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravesBeck Basketball players only seem overrrated because the stuff they do athletically at an elite level is natural and unteachable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would have thought brittney would be dumb enough to fuck up again lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Blodgett Hospital in East Grand Rapids, MI https://t.co/rgOFdRKogZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eduardo_rossal @GOP @PressSec Have you actually SEEN this president?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter Blame the parent.  Entitlement is taught.  Why is he even standing up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was the first time ever Mae has chosen not to sleep on the bed with me, and part of me was so excited to… https://t.co/IbQuCHcFJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tiger attacking the par 5 #1 with a good look at an eagle to go to 7-under for his round 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[also: one time an Instagram thot asked me for a history tour through Berlin and then sort-of said I wouldn’t look g… https://t.co/BegObN8knh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinoyrudeboy @AOC @ScottAdamsSays Its more like this for me.... https://t.co/dFKm5yWt5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[One storm approaching the tri-County is trying to get its act together. Main event still off to the west... https://t.co/ARAIoGsZdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanRobichaud @BensonCowan @JustinTrudeau Um...she remains silent because she is bound by the twin privileges of s… https://t.co/KCHs1LkRHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Citizens Medical Center Run Against Cancer finished first overall #2019 #running #motivation #life #victoria #tx… https://t.co/U5FP6sEX9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at DLA Columbus Fitness Center - @dsccmwr in Columbus, OH https://t.co/AzHHzxQSz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottdetrow @nprpolitics Star Wars, obviously. But for movies about space, I'm a fan of Moon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBull44 Hell nahh i been gone  since we was both there lol out here in Fort Worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar says  #canpoli @cbc @MercedesGlobal @DonMartinCTV @TheTorontoSun @TorontoStar @globepolitics @liberal_party… https://t.co/A3M8I8EMgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to make a drift video that includes me drifting in every state in the country...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erin_cathleenn @MattPiggins Wow. That is nuts, good times. Hope you’re doing well, we should grab coffee soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tues. ATR = @NTRA's @AlexWaldrop, @Silk1900 (LINK: Betting with an Edge ~ https://t.co/APXOIQ8sCb), @andyserling,… https://t.co/a3y2vMTHRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dominic at his after school recreation school program ✨🤗✨🏏⚽️🏃‍♂️ https://t.co/LQSmOdciO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClutchFantasy @JakeAndersonFF @CPatrickNFL @FFPC I think betting on a repeat of the top 3 2018 TE production is a bad premise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkValencia My vague memory is that there's a scene from Shakespeare toward the end that's quite good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ninerfaithful25 @Rob_Lowder I think we should get rid of Tartt. I haven’t seen anything great from him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbbbnnnmm Thanks so much for asking - Momo’s cuddling with our adoption coordinator! She doesn’t know today’s her… https://t.co/VBDMpr1WV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Reasons We Still Watch The Wizard of Oz 75 Years Later| The Wizard of Oz,... #humor #giggle #smile #comic https://t.co/bATc8mySlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have house Democrats now calling for Ilan Omar being removed from her vital committee. We are living in historic… https://t.co/Cv4nRsnYqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris What about Obama bypassing congress and giving Iran billions of dollars and we go NOTHING in return?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord give me the confidence of a contested Oshae Brissett 18 feet from the basket]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her green new deal is straight out of Obama's playbook his speech to the United nations climate change council]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to: @billieeilish - you should see me in a crown #nowplaying #np #LAKings #GoKingsGo https://t.co/TJw7m1jC1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @Lmchristi1 @SealeyGerald @BlueSea1964 @Chrisconsrv1776 @Lady_Vi_2U @PatriotRocker69 @BobFalfa55… https://t.co/xiS66tfdcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @coleyworld I prefer to be alone, actually. Then people say I'm depressed...but that's not the case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC @Ilhan @RepPressley @RepRashida You all could screw up a free lunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯👊🏾#Repost @TroubleBoxing ・・・ Early #TBT with my brother @TroubleBoxing.  We've known each other a long time.  Been… https://t.co/5Tg40bt1hF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Us law abiding citizens have already passed a background]]></document><document><![CDATA[That settles it. @KaceyMusgraves and @sopharela did a duet of NSYNC’s “Tearing Up My Heart” tonight at @sfmasonic a… https://t.co/FHO4vUFZVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelhconnor @amjoyshow @sarahkendzior MSNBC needs to give Sarah her own show. The impact would potentially be g… https://t.co/ssith1IGVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacimoore19 Let you move In  And watched your kid almost daily (while you were working) total bitch 🤟🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gmen_14 I remember when I freestyled to you in summer bridge and you thought I was dope but it was really just a b… https://t.co/Q02A877pr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to use @SpunkLube tonight on a lucky hole! 😈😈😈 https://t.co/EMYQtGmWlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot @IlhanMN @CFR_org Dude covered up a fucking massacre, lied to congress, and subverted the legal foreign po… https://t.co/GAhrpN8RiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must support the people of the Fran🇫🇷 UK🇬🇧 Ger🇩🇪 who’s are protesting against the policies that the Globalist, S… https://t.co/xuqfcYmx2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDynastyMD Idk it's had to no ding rbs who are not productive there whole career, but then dinh others who don't… https://t.co/BRuU2n4fYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, how else is someone to learn and handle you more if you don’t explain a thing? Now if you’re constantly exp… https://t.co/Buz3z4JfV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raywert @garlin @MalloryMcMorrow @NotreDame @garlin is a good Michigan Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaimanTom @ChaminadeHockey So happy for my good friends Joe Watson and Tom Kaiman! They love what they do and it shows!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancoIndian @Azrael2124David @oconnorsteven5 @PhilosophyTiger @PeterCraigBate1 @1SonuvaGunn @BrassWisdom… https://t.co/K6Vjm1E4SM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhccsuper @spartangrass @JasonLTharp @bartonkyled @GCSAA @GCSAA_SE @GCSAA_NE 2/2 Our industry along with others ne… https://t.co/M2PGVeOCrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercial Duct Cleaning! AdvantaClean offers a FREE MOLD inspection. Call AdvantaClean  MOLD REMEDIATION - WATER D… https://t.co/MAHT2w01ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[2013 and now: PLEASE RESPECT MY GLOW-UP (📷: @adahlshouse) https://t.co/MAEKz97Ys8]]></document></documents></author>