<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EvilMarsupials Ok but actually. Out of all the cats I’ve seen around the block, he’s doing better than most 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Hillary was President! This world is cruel under trump era! Please vote the Traitor Trump administration out… https://t.co/bmYYeVJ3vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImFlossinBiTCH It’s for Skylar birthday weekend me her Zara troye khloe and Kayla going to deep creek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_Kuddychris You know, I thought that was hilarious and no one even looked at it .. thanks for even responding.… https://t.co/CRHeMjCGkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[8-21-2018: 💓 #Tuesday #OnATuesday #Tampa #TampaBay #Clearwater #ClearwaterBeach #Florida #LoveFL #FL #friends #love… https://t.co/CCFOCcpYtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's too early for this! Check out @dopeblackness and @lashow_ for your morning fix! No coffee! Drink tea! . .… https://t.co/tNLEX5zkmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... I did a thing.... I HAD to cover the purple up (didn’t want to) but school made me. So I went black https://t.co/ndYchmsVFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunterra1014 @mehdirhasan @zaptrapped @AgentMcNasty @SGNSV_ @kelly2277 I can't even https://t.co/0WK31oGRNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t need to post on ur Snapchat story every time you go to planet fitness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Temper temper Real President’s don’t lie on the floor, kicking their heels and throwing a fit. Pre… https://t.co/uQ2j2wWJp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you bout the baddest bitches that i know , never do no crying over hoes .. we get the doe 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeWhoWait1776WW 😂 maybe. Hadn't heard of that one. "Suicide, dizziness, memory loss, death...ask your doctor if... is right for you."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to see Christian Nelson's children sleep in the cage for months. And then see her reaction to if it's… https://t.co/fMYWIFMUuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s still 6.5 hours left of Valentine’s Day so if any man wants to like, finally fall in love with me and buy m… https://t.co/JaplokxwnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nigel22222 @drawandstrike @GeorgePapa19 @carterwpage George Papadopoulos.  He received 14 days for lying to the FB… https://t.co/xOd8N0ISiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, Joey being the upset in Kyles weekend sweep would be very exciting and satisfying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenBrownII @amosmagliocco I think Biden likes the attention of being a possible candidate, but I don’t think he’s… https://t.co/XX4VIC0oyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this and my Gut said Fact Check  Published by https://t.co/w1W276Jfsm Funded by the World Respected  Annenberg… https://t.co/1tKfVr79mD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yes! I spent an hour standing on line in fairway. I could have been sitting nicely. “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Hey jerk!  I’m a boomer and totally support this. Stop being ageist already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so annoyed I really might not respond to any messages for a few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS YO !🤣 I’ve hella experienced this , bitches don’t even do make up till a new nigga come around bum ass bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be real here, the only person this really punishes is the poor clerk that has to read every page. #wvlegis… https://t.co/rXkQD1D3kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JewishVoice @Chase @IngrahamAngle @seanhannity @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary can you or someone… https://t.co/7RnzyiGZZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claire_atkin @aprilapple @thatajrich @techincolour Thanks!!! I finally did it! I’m a master! https://t.co/50jBqspHIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsofthewest This tweet popped up in my recommendeds and then I read your twit bio and yeah long story short I think we should be friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel comfortable that Rep. Omar will flap her gums again with anti-Semitic trash within the next 10-12 days. Demo… https://t.co/qi0EQm7C7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney playlist. #fridaymood 🐾😎🎶💕 @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/Zc9xfxpNuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been booked with back to back summits and speaking engagements and holy moly, I feel so blessed to be doing th… https://t.co/6FXh9l9bTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Friends” stay talking cash shit like i won’t find out about it. But it’s fine lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[(2/2)   #PokkenTournamentDX @AllisterFGC  https://t.co/CNsigtZXKY  #Tekken7 @Shangleslol  https://t.co/n1rXIzd8et https://t.co/xDb0Y66Uzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m committed to be super positive about aging, so I want to mark today as the official milestone of changing my part to hide my gray hairs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the beach by myself because all of my friends are being lame 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackCarrUSA @EmilyBestler @AtriaMysteryBus @simonschuster Great news!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time for change. Text BetterBeauty to 52886 to urge Congress to pass more health-protective laws in the person… https://t.co/Ry7FBCYNFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBTayor I also looked at his profile and he’s the host of a conservative “comedy “ show]]></document><document><![CDATA[for future presidents, and perhaps governors, too, over “interfering in all kinds of state or federal court litigat… https://t.co/cURkTR5Fdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The work! Without apologies, excuses and full of grace... #LetsGo #RetellingDaBronxTale @cwinkfield @Jonathan_Foy… https://t.co/II054TSI7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally watched Monty Python and the Holy Grail &amp; it’s comedy gold. But you all knew that! https://t.co/kZx4gJlhr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arrowfanclub Thanks!  I believe I'm now very well #Arrow outfitted!😂😂… https://t.co/fyGQFtqlyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you have a more diverse workforce you have more creativity.” #AFBLC19 @AFB1921]]></document><document><![CDATA[livin ma best life without uuuuu @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/pacbwBHojG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to the point in grey’s where Derek dies and I have been crying for the past hour. Legit buckets of tears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CDP_Rad  Have you guys been practicing bank-swish for tomorrow’s game? @UVAMensHoops vs @LouisvilleMBB ? #GoCards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_toomey1984 @MeganGannonTV @BriMacNaught Thank you so much for telling me! I’m bringing this straight to our pitch meeting 😊🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t imagine some people reading the things I’ve written 😂 I love writing and FF is such an easy to way to just… https://t.co/nHnsPmMkUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve already had my annual Valentine’s Day message from “Down Under”. Being, @BexPocklington in Australia. And that… https://t.co/4nZ6X2YG2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[King Darden  It was pretty cool wearing hanbok at the Visit Korea booth at the New York Times Travel Show, even t… https://t.co/39UzrPdN8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS  Great job Mr. President. You’re right. Sometimes you just have to walk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday afternoon, overcast. Me: We have to be careful with strangers. Little: Why? Me: We don’t know them.  Little:… https://t.co/2H3JJLwcue]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍 #perfection @gunsnroses @axlrose @AppetiteForGNfR @TheAFDShow @GnRArmy https://t.co/aGUE2UAYrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karissaaaahines  #spring2015 wirh Marcus. #TBT https://t.co/MHvQe9LMo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone from Indio, CA called me and my immediate thought was “ohhh, maybe @Stagecoach is calling me.” Just another… https://t.co/upftk7AsDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drive past the @SPMIndyCar home base to bring my daughter to lacrosse practices. A happy reminder that @IndyCar s… https://t.co/A9sWpfifQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @daddy_yankee last night on #PremiosLoNuestro was the best thing ever!!! That performance was 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhausske has the CUTEST dog... &amp; he is a very good boy. Hello Finn 😭💕 https://t.co/MgbClXPBTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir thanks for picking up my bag before the other one comes in because they are trying to free up space, gol… https://t.co/Ni4uzCB7ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If you weren't scared you wouldn't be talking, don't worry there's ORANGE JUMPSUIT TO MATCH YOUR HAIR waiting for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @maggieNYT No one interpreted his words!  He said them!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @IAMSUMMERWALKER said that she just needs some dick and some love, I felt THAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewsorg This is how I know you’re my people. I am invisible to bartenders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started my midnight birthday celebration checking out clubshevilsf at @sfpowerhouse! Montyqilla and tasteslikecyani… https://t.co/5jk4ZjLnsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AerLingus Orlando to Dublin. We are in rows 12 and 13. Just to confirm does these rows have a misaligned window? I… https://t.co/SFozjZ1XYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best time with you @DLMacdonald19 thanks for coming to @GDAYUSAofficial @sxsw @australiansfilm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTryChannel @shannonLKeenan @johnsharpson @paddyjmurphy @EmmanIdama @DoyleAnnie @MCluvs2laugh I would’ve eaten it all 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisylegos I would always go in just to get their Thai Bobo tea 😹 that was good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about everyone who sees this #cashapp me a dollar! #SugarBabies #sugardaddy #CashAppFriday @CashApp… https://t.co/5yZsAdgX1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and support a great cause!  22 vets commit suicide everyday.  Service dogs help them in a way that you can… https://t.co/mO1T6dSrvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @ASavageNation I’m throwing up in my mouth just knowing about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ask me, my @ArkansasState humans are the best! Loud noises, but fun!!! So many are at my housse raising mone… https://t.co/I9OeyOK2pK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting your loofa caught on your nipple ring &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; being shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @maddow Don’t know. I don’t watch any mainstream news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeHForrest @CapehartJ Or how much money he siphoned from the many small donations he received.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexrkonrad See also: Could I just pick your brain for an hour? https://t.co/xVoSGDcOtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some deck time! Just warm enough! #fridaynight #spring #dogstagram #cairnterriersofinstagram @ Peachtree C… https://t.co/tvuN6yrf9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonMom98 @MsAFromBK @jimmyreu81 @lno09281978 @SandiMarie79 @SabresFunStats @JustPlainT @ByCharlieRicker… https://t.co/nCM7AL9v1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you would've told me a year ago I'd be trading sleep in the 6am hour for this, I would've told you that you're o… https://t.co/4ovfE1H9Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson #VoicePremiere  okay you’ve got this season 💐go team kelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Criminals get guns - they don’t care about our laws and the sanctuary cities are dangerous and unacceptable as poli… https://t.co/u2k7LviSdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobmaxon How did you know what I was having for breakfast while watching our favorite weatherman?  Mind blown. 🤯🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I want for Valentine's day DM 👉🏾nellievwilliams @sewwhatma. to order please and thank you😬 @ South Car… https://t.co/deIzMv8mvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Charter Township of South Orange Village in NJ https://t.co/LRpVHoW8BP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strictlyHetero @kaizervonmaanen @IKhakistani @zarakayk @JanissaryGuard @Titan05376960 @lArRXJ04NthCLrs @Tokyogreen… https://t.co/Vbnt5yw0zX]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is more important. #Repost @djuanalvspurity ・・・ ❤️Tired of waiting to have sex? Be encouraged....God’s way is b… https://t.co/eD6P1HJXSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamFGaines @thehill Hmm... another one. Those folks did "real" work as they were being terrorized, murdered an… https://t.co/4WYZCT0udI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dig deep to know the author, bias, context- challenge Ss for critical thinking and reading #TALE2019 #TxLiteracyEd… https://t.co/hJh9QzhMgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAX United family &amp; LAWA family so excited about this amazing venture! @flyLAXairport @weareunited #beingunited… https://t.co/zZ0De7Kd1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnhart303 @uswakeupamerica @TVNewsHQ @CNN @FoxNews @TheFive I watched it when the towers went down during 9/11.… https://t.co/ffQtfUpyfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Feb. 22, Willowbrook School went all out during its birthday celebration of 50 years. Classroom parties, a parad… https://t.co/y6JwwfP7iI]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Kid-Friendly Restaurants That Go Beyond the Chicken Fingers and Crayons https://t.co/EFPKflT8TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure there will ever be a time this song doesn’t make me cry. If you’ve ever had a true best friend you will re… https://t.co/RWTbN0lSlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[These ice covered side streets are going to kill my suspension. Praying for a plow and some salt @weathernetwork… https://t.co/ZMBRw7QFHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just noticed that I naturally reached out to all powerful women for immediate help on a societal issue... what does that say?? ✊🏻✊🏼✊🏽✊🏾✊🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryScarf yes they are.. I worked on the farm for 2 summers in high school.. they were so adorable.. the babies w… https://t.co/0RGPjTdbe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well y’all looks like ya girl’s using pto for work that she’s technically supposed to use for a holiday to go see… https://t.co/QP70qxevo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone gifts me something I will literally go, “oh my god.... I love it” for a straight five minutes and then… https://t.co/SIeYtamddN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brennan_elliott I love the lighting in #APuzzleToDieFor. It's sharp and everything is very distinct.… https://t.co/fWksHZOpR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorites by @cmorganmusic , so stoked to get to open for him tonight at milltown_musichall in GA! Less t… https://t.co/tq3tyfukwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi You did not ask my family how we feel!  You are not taking my guns!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day/night was made by David... he surprised me at work with such a busy schedule he has all this week and I unde… https://t.co/WlKl6zQpnv]]></document></documents></author>