<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Animal_Viral @karlapohls  jajajajaja creo que te pasaba algo parecido 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love laughing until I am in tears...they are definitely happy tears...the best kind if you... https://t.co/kqaq1kXb4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winmatt53 @JulieReichwein1 @AOC They (Democrats) are experts in accusing their opposition of what they are doing.… https://t.co/98BxROBDIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Model3Owners @marc_benton @van_essavan I tell people the thing about a Tesla test drive is that the “salespeople”… https://t.co/3QUE55FjBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyBoasso @agavecorn @omzmusic @realDonaldTrump All bullies are the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markhoppus I THOUGHT IT WAS A GORGEOUS PIECE OF VISUAL STORYTELLING THAT CRUSHED ME ON A DEEP EMOTIONAL LEVEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complex: 10 Throwback All-Star Weekend Sneakers You Can Buy Right Now. https://t.co/jsCJvBKrzX  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEgan5 @BrockESPN What's the deal guys? Some pretty good offspring coming from the Puyallup boys. Is it the water? :) Or the Moms?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuttyGyal_ your work is amazing , my sister wants to be a nail tech so she now knows what I’m expecting 😤 https://t.co/II8cCAbIDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ufc and @danawhite for taking a stand in this fight! #sober #grateful #recovery #sobriety #opioids… https://t.co/xk3y5XwoWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What they do is dangle that money over their head like they did with the Thursday night football revenue and they a… https://t.co/A6izYHIVB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/aK1vdpR51b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like yo I legit worked all day from 8am-12 and I have to work another 12 hour shift tomorrow! I should be sleeping… https://t.co/Pj9awZPtjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSouthern_eh I'll be doing that in 4 weeks so I feel your pain. I think we may only do Animal Kingdom and Univer… https://t.co/Dcnd8WStE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just so you all know @TheScopeMMA is running off of no sleep and no GBs covering these fights for @mmatorch he’s a true hero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a wide range of subjects that students used to study these days. #Freeonlinehomework  #Bestassignmenthelp… https://t.co/CWPJGLqseC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got until Friday folks!! I know you have some awesome stuff going on in your programs. So please let us pay you… https://t.co/uuO5AGWY2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2011, Sunday Night, 11:15 PM, you’re in the computer room trying to memorize Busta’s verse of “Look at me Now”… https://t.co/Ehv6U2pke2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live music! (@ The Lion's Den in Stockbridge, MA) https://t.co/RUMcbflEDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️ I think my pussy needs to be stretched out. Idk. You tell me 🤷🏼‍♀️🌙 this is the first time I used this butt… https://t.co/lwdRoBy6K5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsLauraPerry Gaelic has only a hard c. Ker-noonos is how I've always heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coshea9 @realDonaldTrump @SenDuckworth He stands for the innocent the left wants to kill the innocent. Seems prett… https://t.co/6HrVnRYaNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDugudichi 99% liberal, brain dead professors. They are professors for a reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is @AndyDPhillips not the kicker for the Salt Lake Stallions?? #saltlakestallions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't teach speed...brii.tilley finished with the right...commentary said left😂 @kentuckyfirejunior #soccernation… https://t.co/136zk7DO9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roun heah we call this #Pwnd ol girl is sprung hahahahahaha #OpMetalGearReloaded https://t.co/lBEih4kNjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part is the @nytimes makes it VERY difficult to unsubscribe. Been waiting for 10 min for a “chat agent” to sho… https://t.co/bKCfOlbFyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digitaldeath @brickwahl1 I don't know any cool kids. Everyone I know is either retired or dead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Congratulations on your first time going to Vietnam in service of your country, bone-spurs and all… https://t.co/kloLlOFJyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VRWCTexan Unless you travel through that area , it's hard to convince people of what has happened !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy. My first trip back since graduation was a month ago for the double header with Omaha...40 years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orbiteers Full disclosure: AKN has *millions* of pages. But even sub-10K page sites benefit from good content hygi… https://t.co/50peiqtDtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoMckee T’challa stop acting like you don’t know😂 https://t.co/QvmDmMnt03]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Superior Panthers set for the ballgame versus Duncan Wildkats. https://t.co/im2iOhehGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video Game time (@ Round1 at Stonecrest Mall in Lithonia, GA) https://t.co/hkJigiC3t0]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Feliz Cumpleaños @ElsitaRomo!, te mando un abrazo. https://t.co/W1KF1JlKUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[A common response to the sudden death of a young man or woman is "he/she died before their time." It's time to invo… https://t.co/tOUUBDgCtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not even JV — which explains why I’m almost as tall as most of the dudes on the floor. Also, there are five ti… https://t.co/f5EFbfmUKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftdflowers Thanks for ruining my day. Never received the flowers I ordered and u have the worst customer service o… https://t.co/0v5lWHeSJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamEdwards Sheriff Tony Mace (Cibola County)is a good friend of mine and is doing an amazing job getting the count… https://t.co/5uTSv50zyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice nod for Hilton. (But they do need to figure out faster checkin. Took me 1 hr once at ORD Hilton last year.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspirational steps at my secret Monday location #allengittelson  #mentalwires… https://t.co/G16O6FKFlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably should start yielding on trade restrictions and patent reform or you’re going to have yourself some price… https://t.co/MVz9GDYvX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Blah, blah, blah, blah blah! Blah, blah, blah, blah blah! Blah, blah, blah, blah blah! Blah, blah,… https://t.co/3F0M9pIXkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Casper College for the first day of the 4A State tourney. Kelly Walsh girls trying to keep their season ali… https://t.co/ctePUmkYTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing community we live in.  I met so many new neighbors and friends today who were here celebrating all… https://t.co/FDBLI2C4Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@augustburnsred doing a 10 year constellation tour would be amazing if it comes to Wisconsin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11rcombs @marcan42 Uhhhh, the heuristics for that sound impossible. But I'm not that smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home opener for @OrlandoCitySC v @NYCFC was a good time.  We got one point. Maybe next time we will get three.… https://t.co/3rjWbB8CNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I think that you need to force Joe to take some time off. He's clearly still grieving and not in his right m… https://t.co/ZSE1K3qazC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @AOC lol Matt Gaetz is a national treasure! What kind of treasure cant follow a law that simply states… https://t.co/i8etZS5RLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yeah, it’s kinda cold and wet out here.  It’s a nice extra level of difficulty for @westvikings #ScienceOlympiad… https://t.co/jHORryR8q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah you good. The bottom shelf of my fridge look the same &amp; I be chilling bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hhoover @rosskukulinski It puts the pod in the cluster or it gets the hose again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti @bigjimmurray @985TheSportsHub If they don’t sign sale now he is gone and the Sox are left with not… https://t.co/kFujp9iI8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo tengo que revisarme el patriotismo porque la canción esa lo que me dio fue sueño...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL Gun to your head do you think Miami tries to snag a QB round 1? (Haskins or Murray?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music out of Iceland! @vokmusic - In the Dark Released March 1st, 2019  #iceland #vok #vök #icelandicmusic… https://t.co/3n6Wdtb0ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a part of something that changes lives. #warrior #warriors #warriornation #warriortattoo #militarytattoo… https://t.co/SNOY2RLCTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Nick Lopez, Regal Opry Mills manager, for letting my dumb ass in the movie even though I bought tickets for yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t believe in ghosts but when Willie Lightfoot hit the 3-pointer to tie the game going into overtime versus No… https://t.co/souSailW4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s late, but I definitely had the best Valentine anyone could ask for, through the good and bad. I love yo… https://t.co/jexqz0tcQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucasbavid you’re one of my biggest inspirations follow me king https://t.co/NPwaBDVahf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tzipshmil @jkfecke @_waleedshahid @FoxNews @justicedems I’m with you 100%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aviation_Intel @BurkhardDomke I don’t think Cuban was being dense. He just asked the airman (a bit clumsily) to el… https://t.co/FGGxg4AevQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee @MartySmithESPN @ESPNRadio @Mc_Driver kept his Helmet on. Smart Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF!! That’s all we getting is some mf picks!! And they not even no first rounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imaginography71 @Tom_Bricker Camera gear in backpack, clothes in suitcase.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curriculum contest at Murray.. great. I thought I could enjoy a nice quiet lunch at a restaurant while getting some… https://t.co/FUtI3aoNAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackYou81312821 @BarstoolNate @RobbieBarstool I bet your 7 followers really enjoyed this one. Keep up the great co… https://t.co/L2F2fplbvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk how it’s possible for me to crave 2 birds literally non stop but i do 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear my Bitmoji gets laid more than I do. I should live my life vicariously through that bastard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richjohnston I mean, if it’s upsetting, then it off obviously...but only a few bits could really be considered ups… https://t.co/awXGmi69uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Austin: mist, 48°F 100% humidity, wind 14mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL Admittedly, I was thinking the same thing as that guy but that is also a perfect response.]]></document><document><![CDATA[them bare titties on ya skin to skin be therapeutic feelin as hell whole time]]></document><document><![CDATA[2legit_daquit you can get these grape 5s for tha Low😂😂😂 @ Elrod, North Carolina https://t.co/bVsB61erWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech N9ne - No K ft. Krizz Kaliko, E-40 https://t.co/s8qFDWi2bu via @Stork🌾chipotleregina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex The brothers should be charged and get jail time too ,they are just as guilty....😎😎 https://t.co/hkJKkip1v2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elnuevodiariord @digesettrd Esta bien la buena intencion pero es muy peligrosa he sabido de casos que se le han ro… https://t.co/kOo2XoI8uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodWebber @caitoz Let's make a bet; Bet I can list things she believes: The entire US Intelligence community is ev… https://t.co/8mpeqCQVBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AliensAreProbablyThinking what a shitshow that USA country has become. Let's steer clear of them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my girl who she was texting and she said her boyfriend. I forgot I’m the side nigga LMFAOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllMyTeams @cutespartn @PaoloUggetti its pure something... genius isn’t the word i would use... and you’re complai… https://t.co/mudHwxHbsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting downstairs doing a bit of work for #secondshift (or the #nightshift — what do the cool kids call it the… https://t.co/QZybl8bNsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won’t stop working because I refuse to let my next escort be to my grave]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickyCarmichael I road raced and public practice racing most the rest of time over 10 years a #1973TwoStrokeYAMAHAR5C Too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“TITTIES!”  — Sean Connery, if “Tithes” was a Saturday Night Live Jeopardy category]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Hobknobery! Subscribe for some awsome #LinkedIn Tips! https://t.co/UgiHmSvKcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait why do people say being single is boring? i’m over here having the time of my life 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Crocodile Tears coming from Republicans for "not playing by the rules."  LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 7th St/Metro Center (Julian Dixon) Metro Station - @metrolosangeles in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/QnXlA7PoOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Gee I didn’t think Sara was smart enough to come up with that conclusion....(a bit of sarcasm on my part) well done Sara!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubbyBurgess I haven’t studied it that closely, but Fields at #15 is laughable based on ‘18 performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedGunny @NonWhiteHat Really not funny. I am a physician, was interviewed by ATF and federal prosecutors over… https://t.co/KNtOO90VE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen This is proof that MSM is just a self congratulating liberal echo chamber. That, or Fox News is compl… https://t.co/26tylVSO3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the issue with Fred coming back and talking to the team?  He did it before he was the coach, he’s done it for the football team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington Square – Tigard, Oregon https://t.co/dg7fTnSehh via @YouTube #TigardOregon #Tigard #OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprende a hacer las cosas por el gusto de hacerlas, por el gusto de compartirlas, por el gusto de ayudar.  Por el g… https://t.co/4TGPuAHGJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇩🇪👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss pezsiii The White RACE German BLONDES👑🇩🇪Women Are The MOST Beautiful In T… https://t.co/1mNhQRuxC8]]></document></documents></author>