<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sweetlifephoto @robintallfish I don't get why he would sit down for this interview. Are all Trump associates STUPID.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such a great time at the 20th anniversary of #10thingsihateaboutyou in support of #ourtism at the #wisdome in… https://t.co/9xZWnWAOmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night that I agreed to a job interview, but when they were trying to tell me about the time and… https://t.co/3JHYRn8WqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear how my guest @edenxo may have inspired #ladyGaga #oscar speech plus #SisterWives #LoveAfterLockup #jordynwoods… https://t.co/QgHcC4UHW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You just ensured John Cornyn's loss. He's proven to be one of your incredible outstanding hacks. Tata Cornyn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue whales rely on memory to find their prey, this could become a problem if the oceans ecosystem changes drastica… https://t.co/FlYwrn5Ibi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmichaels20 you didn’t answer Nicole’s FaceTime tonight and I wanted to see you and remind you that you’re the rea… https://t.co/l9uYPSpm0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh heck no!  How do you know she isn’t going to pull a terrorist actin the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We stopped drinking, my husband has been tobacco free for 4 months now (almost 5) - we’re feeling and looking our b… https://t.co/jLxp81WkXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @jorgeramosnews Incredible, what is going on. We have to get that dictator out of Venezuela. These peo… https://t.co/ehaiW3ZBsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me -goes to mall without makeup- Worker @ Sephora: “Are u looking for prom?”  Me: “No i’m starting my master’s in t… https://t.co/gveFk45cBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @realDonaldTrump #AClearAndPresentDanger @marcorubio @hughhewitt @LindseyGrahamSC @GOPLeader… https://t.co/TvyuMxCNCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @CNN:  You have let this administration turn your network into a 3-ring shit show. Im tired of opening the app… https://t.co/NNJcWobzHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possible minds: an evening with @AlisonGopnik, @rodneyabrooks, @kevin2kelly, John Brockman and Stuart Russell fil… https://t.co/zgYGmw0Sx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PigottTur @Canal22 @GibbBarry @Brothers_Gibb You’re Welcome ‼️  this is one of my most favorite photos, because it… https://t.co/SuvolFXFhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost davidlawrencebyrd • • • • • • Last night at Superboob. Missing @rainsupremeny @tinatassels mandarinemoon @… https://t.co/5V2o16Q8fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostrar a Portugal que a Tauromaquia nao é cultura, é tortura - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/kZ2MONC9v4 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trouble with reporting these #scams to @Twitter is because the rip-off is detailed in the super, super fine pri… https://t.co/6BDApj7tsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mactavish No but Google those things together and you’ll see what I’m talking about. #Revolucion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet ko 'tong Tañada na 'to. Magaling din syang sumagot. #Harapan2019 #RoxasTayo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsandiego Hey NBC 7, what happened to the @Jeopardy #AllStar Tournament that’s supposed to be airing tonight? Yo… https://t.co/DvOYBHjOLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into Nate and the ex taking my old dog to the vet. Haven't got to give her love in a very long time. 💜🐶🐾🐕 @ Pet… https://t.co/FxQBXNzw0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollandTaylor @MsSarahPaulson my best friend of 30 years drunk called me from MARYLAND to wish me a happy Valentin… https://t.co/d5CpA9t752]]></document><document><![CDATA[well i’ve officially had to resort to whispering because my voice is deciding not to cooperate :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamaraletter @ozimokn @parrishn18 @PrincipalKKane @DrJacieMaslyk @AnnickRauch @TaraMartinEDU @Rdene915… https://t.co/33103qZp1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: sometimes I’m lucky to get 6 hrs. If I get more then 8 hrs, my mind is blown #runchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Der Zug läuft wieder und ich hab heute morgen den schönen Sonnenaufgang gehabt! Irgendwo in Nebraska! https://t.co/tkHtFS4k0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another gem by @Catlin_Tucker! Let’s revisit purposeful homework and grading. https://t.co/OIsM7b1SYK via @Catlin_Tucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexico to close massive migrant facility on the Texas border https://t.co/uvqOG37gdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephmilford12 tokyo jetz at the moment. i been city girls, trina, now im her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4ny0n3 @Leo_CCJ @SoloOtroCarlos Ustedes las crean ustedes las destruyen, por eso no soy fan de nadie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveBriginshaw @avalara @lotusaccts @CathyIconis @EvelynIvyCPA @rfchambers @samrotberg @edkless @BillSheridan… https://t.co/WAWOb7FPgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[lesson learned. dont brake check black trucks if you have bad luck. they will end up being a cop, you will get pull… https://t.co/Ez5X4Vn4q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The vibe you get when watching the #B1G women’s swim meets are insane!  I’ve never been so hyped especially to be i… https://t.co/81drrVpDPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiFaircloth  Have a wonderful weekend, my friend!! 🙏😊💞⚘ https://t.co/HB5qyy6WUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[New face. Who dis?  Preview of a #photoshoot today!!!!  #whatwillitbe !?!   #chameleonmodel  #mystique  ? @ Baltimo… https://t.co/cQS13zoPBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 1st vegasgoldenknights game! 🖤💛 Thank you @kelrm 😘 #aboutlastnight #vegas #win @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/KQVS8hyryY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presentefect @JamesShawJr9 Im wondering if the Hindus use drugs to reach that state. In my case there were no drugs involved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello i am having an allergic reaction and i called my mom and apparently i am alLERGIC TO A LOt MORE STUFF THAN I THOUGHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to hate #saturdays . Turn out, I was doing them all wrong. ⛰🏔🏞🌄❄⛄💙💚💛  #hike #hiking #hikinglife #hikinglover… https://t.co/PsuACjJQiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTown_Jaime @ALGThunder @TheOCAA @AthleticsSLC @ctvottawa @ottawahoops @TSN1200 Good luck coach!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay Santo Dios, can it get any colder?  So done with winter. Snow and cold are overrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m listening to an interview with #davidleeroth and he just quoted #doubledutchbus. I’ve never been so in love. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBelfiore1 @IngrahamAngle @FoxNews I noticed this too !!! MAYBE she’s NOT actually sworn in and can be booted to the curb !!!! 🤔🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mich_onelove Oh yes I like a lot of people because I like all different kind of songs. I do like Bruno.   Shawn Me… https://t.co/2Aqmm1hXCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJHammy Yes, you are but that wasn’t what you tweeted!  Be careful what you say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Around - 34.1 3rd place Bestie Eliy took 4th place @ Lancaster Mennonite School https://t.co/QLVl6jtnrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ennyuh @PopCrave @LiamPayne @piersmorgan @KylieJenner That's Not Nice ...Please Don't Be Mean To Liam...He's A Ver… https://t.co/KmcQ7FGgpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got on tinder for the first time in what feels like decades and it’s already going amazing https://t.co/2VAAtCvzWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know some people find it silly, or even creepy that a grown ass woman loves going to disneyland so much, sans chi… https://t.co/fOXQti30jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you 'Uwdisa Falddays @odeth_valdes for liking our show! Happy day friend!💙💞🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwightMiller @MalcolmNance All of the time.  The worst group of people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@germano____ @politico Do you think thats by design? Ivanka has 100s of new trademarks with China.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Izzo Ave..... Hershey Highway..... makes sense.  #WhatILearnedToday @realBradStaggs @RantsOfIzzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw This is what unglued looks like. Just wait. Pretty soon his heads going to explode!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terril49 @MeghanMcCain @TheView I really like watching the view when Megan keeps her mouth shut. Otherwise I have… https://t.co/ywIV4kEqSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kazweida This pig hit on me when I worked in a SF airport bookstore, 2000s. I was mid-twenties, he was in I guess… https://t.co/S2lCC7MsBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST TOUCH DOWN IN MIAMI !!! @ Miami International Airport - MIA https://t.co/n49eMXdy1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[For every house is builded by some man; but he that built all things is God. https://t.co/3BlSMPlaUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[to collect £3,000 from IS sympathisers. Captured after the Brussels airport bombings, he is a subject for analysing… https://t.co/WP4cf28SEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’m bout to tell you a story about what my high ass just did.   So I’m at my friend’s new apt and idk where a… https://t.co/CUnx0wwSDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg Conservatives don't care about life. They only care about a fetus. Gunshot victim in the ER: https://t.co/p29DEdAqv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @LoriMoreno @eatchirps @SashaEats @GailBenzler @jflorez @ja2cook @Fit_life360 @Irish_IreneB… https://t.co/kF9wPxvFm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an absolute blast at the Mehndi Night party!!! #AzmeenaKhan #GoingToTheChapel https://t.co/ievHBChEOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow A "mission."  I abhor people "on a mission" unless they are in the military.  Mission people tend… https://t.co/3yOaH0KGUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shipyard Maple BACON! Stout. With ‘Beef Brisket Burnt Ends AND Smoked Pork Belly Slider’ #freshepcot #epcot Epcot F… https://t.co/TxVlgS139G]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s about damn time! Facial recognition poses an enormous threat to racial equity and civil liberties.👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 https://t.co/g8MhLQEm9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't take 100 selfies on my iPad if you don't want students completing an assignment on the green screen to create… https://t.co/727wwZ0TX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Pisces season and I’m taking a bubble bath for the past hour at 4:38 am, don’t tell me astrology is not real..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on Mercari! SPIDER-MAN T- Shirt … https://t.co/QdgRhqLVlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom why won’t you let me sleep #dog #dogmom #domino #life #latenightvibes @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/JRDBUAuWBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chance_Manning7 ethan and I watched a few years ago and he looked at me, dead ass serious, “babe, what would you d… https://t.co/mEuxCRQjNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is something about McDonald’s sprite that just makes my world go round]]></document><document><![CDATA[~How to watch the game ~Starting pitchers for both teams ~Arkansas' pitching plan beyond the starter ~An in-state k… https://t.co/84IerV3zy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DodgerDegen Oh my god, yes!! That would be amazing to be able to do this!! 🤤😂 I love that movie, even if tho it’s about the Sox.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @repectthe2nd @AOC Because SOCIALISTS...LIE and spend whatever the HELL they want on themselves 🤦‍♀️… https://t.co/fbVjB5uMEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched West Side Story tonight and realized I’ve never seen it all the way thru.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Tim Tebow ever makes it to the majors, that’s all the information I’ll need on how the Mets season is going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrispco I miss flour. My doc was straight up with me that given my numbers, gluten will significantly increase my… https://t.co/8Vl2SsX7lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we have this #YouTube channel and @Wally_Hawk is putting in WORK making exclusive videos every week on it. You s… https://t.co/Estly87K0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeyGeeeeeeeee @ramplate @captainbrent75 @JanLandy @ZipptyDooDaa @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @nytimes Yeah, and l… https://t.co/zzoiNPasLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en AmericanAirlines Arena https://t.co/zhpXhShIWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[coming home today, but i won’t see my little brothers until monday... that’s my main reason for wanting to come hom… https://t.co/CGSRpIfbXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericnamofficial Happy Valentine’s Day,and best of luck with the tour!🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myfish #neon #betafish #japanesefightingfish   This is my final fish Neon who just had his 1st birthday last month… https://t.co/2JWTU9y24E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! It aired! Say hi to my new cinnamon roll, Hayato, in #JOJOsBizarreAdventure, on #Toonami! I know he only poppe… https://t.co/z8j21x6i8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the girl who wakes up desperate for just ONE good day to find herself crying by 4pm... it gets better. It WILL g… https://t.co/WE22QMFaya]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been and am immensely lucky to be supported by incredible, brilliant, generous, kind womxn. 💗  Today is a da… https://t.co/1N8cRJ4tO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aric_Almirola @SmithfieldBrand @DISupdates @FordPerformance Yayy pulling for you Aric!!! Give em hell Sunday🏁u got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[AirBnB books (1) @ Lycoming County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/M7ApcjMLq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerberKawasaki I think there are enough of us happy owners willing to sell for them..for free. @elonmusk , have no… https://t.co/lUpiBqqQXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.. he's thinking about the workers that have families to support.. that's the only reason Pres Trump signed this… https://t.co/hElGGLwDIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear my parents watch at least one episode of Ridiculousness every night😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyAlperin @NJAHPERD @sarahbenes12 YES!!! I had a group hang out after it was over, thanking me and asking thoug… https://t.co/KoWb8F2bwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I could take my sex back from certain ppl I would bc what the fuck was i thinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the acting defense secretary think he should overrule the president if he chooses. I think he should be replaced if he does that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s try this one more time. I WILL be volunteering with honor for the #DNC in my new home state of Alabama. Could… https://t.co/Sg0R13TEfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecottagect Not enough adjectives to describe a perfect bday dinner last night! 4 at the bar...super fun and grea… https://t.co/MptTzVQ5QM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes i use organic Apple cider on my clients have you booked yet or walk ins are welcomed… https://t.co/1Uq3Xnjxh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MedicareforAll #healthCare is a #humanRight So is a healthy environment.  #climatereality @ Washington, District o… https://t.co/696jkhNNCL]]></document></documents></author>