<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Kristen’s story on the comeback made by @ike_book to reach career point 1,000, just in time for @bballstjoe to make… https://t.co/ZDn2vECdSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigga said this that real money not that drug money 😂😂 niggas be mad trappin never worked out for them😂👎🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleebb21 @creaturelives33 @bj_flemming @ZandEDad @addysdaddy181 @bingley567 @DadFiction @fu_dad @Kyle_48… https://t.co/ulW0qI7FvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[TransCounty Title is a proud member and approved agent by the American Land Title Association.  The American Land T… https://t.co/XuNMSVVyQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLCHS_Athletics @CollinsTitansBB @shelbycountysch @MLCHS_Principal @HLpreps @kyhighs @LesisMoreSports… https://t.co/abcLR2JsBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMarucci I appreciate your feedback John! I’m out of my comfort zone with Towing, RVing etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[all of the Democrats running for president have sign onto this New Green Deal and support it...if Hillary was presi… https://t.co/PXIrLxfxcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about it, football is a game of inches ... and every third time Thompson touches the ball, he got you a fresh… https://t.co/2CIySpJ3Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VassyKapelos Thank u Vassey WE don't need to CBC to tell us what we need to know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to take a while to really take in and understand what the long-term implications of the @Samsung #GalaxyFold will be #Unpacked2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieandStoney Stoney, his girlfriend got pregnant from another dude. They should have gone to Vegas. 11 brothers… https://t.co/MqfJxtYpW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[May have struggled this season, my mind wasn’t right. Time to get in the gym and get ready for AAU.✊ https://t.co/2sj5sQNIAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrianrambo Wait this was a dope reference but also very literal 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody wanna play defense tonight @NHLFlyers???? #LetsGoFlyers https://t.co/HO3q4J0L0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[nascar with budaman, intermediate track so there is some laps to lead,tires are gona be an issue if they run too lo… https://t.co/xorAISEO5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bredrew2 @Candypooh This storyline does not explain or justify Melinda's shitty behavior towards her sister.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Opportunity Red by @AAleworks at @aaleworks — https://t.co/qHvaJ7gNZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficeOfMike Reminds me of an episode of WKRP in Cincinnati when they try to sensor rock and roll]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching videos and this girl goes “why should I have to try to convince someone to love me?” and I can’t tell you… https://t.co/dBqQYPlMk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Iamfitness Memphis By York https://t.co/FBiu59EWYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myyaya7 Nope...  ...@realDonaldTrump is the only Wall between Constitutional Individual Freedom and Globalist Serf… https://t.co/Ljanv2pXor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshhart @OfficialNBARefs That’s not a foul there’s nothing to explain]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Tú y Yo by Ana Gabriel, from #SoundHound https://t.co/xb9jEasHdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malteseh @RickFreedland @kayalbasi @Pappiness One of the smartest guys I knew at Princeton was in BHO's class at H… https://t.co/MMnqmZSAfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @8M1LLY4 must of worn black air forces haha. #moreswagthanmcgregor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase My Father is a retired psychologist, but kind of hard to talk to your dad about how f'd up you are! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRC: UNT is up 16-13 at the end of the first quarter of its game against Florida International. The Mean Green have… https://t.co/Z7UGwiQDCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Karma 😜👍 Sit down and watch ! ~CJ💯 • • • • • • • •  • • • 💭 #quote #quotes #lifequotes #quotestags #toptags… https://t.co/C9MQULbX7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @OutlawedMind @JaackSchitt @billcrowley3rd @Al_Gorelioni @atl1tm @Rastech919 @SpyTheLiar @Dannaja64Danny… https://t.co/nFBBLLXVNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow what a play by @reavo7five almost leads to a goal. Play physical boys!! Let’s get a strong @GoldenKnights push!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayInslee In 1996 3200 hundred scientists disputed climate assessments as hoax😡2000 years ago the atmosphere conta… https://t.co/KtyKP5bwMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Your fired asshole!! You helped set this up the first week of January 2017 when you lynch Obama an… https://t.co/v9O5XFN84O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 20th birthday, “Back That Azz Up.”  New Orleans is forever grateful to @juviethegreat and @manniefresh]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLB on Fox fans must love paying $100 for a ticket to sit in a tiny hundred year old wooden seat behind a pole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusWMorris @PaulaPinelli @Oprah @HBO LaToya told the TRUTH about her pedophile brother Jacko! "My mother showed… https://t.co/5b9kIriwh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are rocking out for @drseuss #readacrossamerica day @ Lincoln Elementary Performing Arts School https://t.co/p7PJIilMoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening (archaic); or anagram of two synonymous four-letter words. “What the heck? Die, evil crossword editor!” Cal… https://t.co/JxqfZu1UZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay tuned today for the ULTIMATE Ford truck comparison! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s R… https://t.co/z2pTLoCKNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalNiederman @GotNoSperm And this guy has all of that to offer him! https://t.co/4OoNfIFnhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of work I have to do in credit recovery to get from a 58 to a 60 is fucking absurd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t tell me what you support. Tell me who you’re willing to sacrifice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olivierday Bro.... ann kite deba saa. Mwen te dil jis poum te fe yon “blag”... gen moun ki pa Menm gen smartphone.… https://t.co/9Vs8hpCPBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Walnut Belgian Imperial Stout by @raisedgrain at @raisedgrain — https://t.co/f5tdairjLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsom wants to spend $40 million to hire more firefighters. Why some want to double that https://t.co/QfjdmzceIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteBrydon @realDonaldTrump @ReneeCarrollAZ If by saying I'm in the type of minority that will vote Trump in for a… https://t.co/e9EDknggeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Patricks Day Parade Asbury Park NJ March 10, 2019  #asburyparkstpatricksdayparade at the starting point of the… https://t.co/ab2ooNFtTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reroll @KatTheHammer1 @KamalaHarris @southernwayjim @Tweets4MAGA @christianllamar @TrumpOrBust2020 @SiddonsDan… https://t.co/3kpEFpWz7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillip1224 These ISIS deadenders make a great case against repatriation , seem to “put paid”  the idea they will… https://t.co/efXXbf7f4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMNASCAR #frontstretch @HermieSadler who complained more? Single file train no passing or tandem hookups ton… https://t.co/OqaNeimAGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherryhank and I, got the Win and Big Fish in the #GoodyearBassClub tournament at Harris today! @ Shearon Harris L… https://t.co/9EKuuTEddD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpimienta_ @DA_LIP_ Shrek is love Shrek is life https://t.co/0A3FHj6ZW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely @BrittMcHenry #Dondraper is one of the three most influential/entertaining TV male characters of all tim… https://t.co/SLGLRw6ZYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es increíble las muestras de cariño que recibimos por el mundo!!! Gracias en Las Vegas Nevada https://t.co/kwUVjtMO98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aftergambling Exercise hands down. It is meditative, allows me to build my body, release stress, and gives me an a… https://t.co/eq8NlktEkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Someday” is not a day of the week, you won’t find someday on the calendar. so stop wishing for someday and start  working for it TODAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoheatha @_JRobles71 @Louisx209 Who turn is it for https://t.co/JoCulZS0Ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jumpwiremedia @instagram @Pinterest @gavinmcgarry @deSouza_palooza https://t.co/OOEBWJBkCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trev_theissen That’s exactly what we want. To see Dwayne Wade in Milwaukee one more time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve won my girl a bear at the rodeo for two years straight, I’m gon make it a third 🤞🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tg9288 That other football league is just so cheesy and cheap looking just making a comparison]]></document><document><![CDATA[That look when you are on your last snatch and have to give a little prayer to the oly gods. My plate math was off… https://t.co/07cSy3Iq4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palita_40 De nada pAlita e igualmente para ti saludos fraternos de regreso ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSTwinCities I actually have plans for this weekend so I'd put the percentage for a significant event as 100%. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaWR8 @SiddonsDan @Goz_1911 Not just Christians, or a few people  "ALL"  means everybody. Even you non-believers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommishMThomas @SIRIUSXM I was soooo excited about the KISS ch on 30. And now it’s gone. #reallydisappointed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarsynElledge3 @USACNation @FloRacing @Speed_Media_ @LaurenStewart9 @TMCTRANS @BrandtRacing @TBMotorsprts… https://t.co/4l9Ev3C3CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorizonsOne Those aren’t recursive acronyms. I’m not sure what to call then, though. Referential acronyms maybe? I… https://t.co/kohO1Y2PRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacenomad_ How was your weekend?  Went to Deja Voom in Mexico, saw all these dope artists, got top from the 11th… https://t.co/xREbIrSWA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LKlu9BB5H8 Our experts at ATT customer service are verified 1-855-436-9666 #attcustomerservice… https://t.co/3aGZBmEzOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[* @coltonnicely requests a song. The second the song starts “man, this song is annoying” -also @coltonnicely]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invisible force of no good.. @UnitedWay a system prideful to t.. get it.. raise money lie lie lie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I shouldn't be so angry Becky Lynch and Charlotte Flair are wrestling at a Smackdown house show but they're c… https://t.co/H9tu9xZ7yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoomBuck80 Watched the race. Not bad,at least thier trying. Harvick, Kurt bush, Stenhouse, Truex, loose. During in… https://t.co/kJA9YWFfsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home to find a gym membership sitting on my bed. My mom just informed me I have 72 hours to find a signifi… https://t.co/HTdSXAeDfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMickFoley @BustedOpenRadio @BeckyLynchWWE @metalHAGEN approves this message https://t.co/wqqKKujLvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST TRYING OUT SOMETHING NEW AT FORT LAUDERDALE COLOMBIAN RESTAURANT I KNOW ITS GOOD 💯 #Oneshotradio #DinnerFlow… https://t.co/PX3LR58A2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshclarky316 @elenakoshkaxoxo I know the feeling she will be my crush in this life and everyone after this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing the #Hornets playing with a sense of urgency.  Desperate for a win, they hold the Rockets to 41 in the first.  Solid effort.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad news for the Black Wolves.  Encouraging news?   Its next five games are against teams with a record at or below… https://t.co/ZlcyX8r5Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayLoucel @MLBONFOX I agree, MVP Baseball 05 unforgettable performances by Jon Dowd!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyEnder @Adriastea Un asesinato nunca se debe legalizar, digo yo, aunque hoy en día decir esas cosas es de locos!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a fellow Canadian i will certainly vouche for the authenticity of this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a wonderful reunion at Pensacon pensacolapensacon with a wonderful gentleman and amazing producer and human bei… https://t.co/SJDNRiIz6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunnflores I think she messed when she was answering their questions/trying to defend herself. It’s like they put… https://t.co/FM82xnn6Hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Brett Baier, the guy whose integrity we keep being assured is above reproach by other journalists. He had n… https://t.co/N9HXHt1Csg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this fish gives you a notebook do not write anyone’s name in it, OK?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWS ggrtureyylkhjejururutttutyutuueehherhrjghjhjmnnvhghuuutuguuhjfjffhdhfyytyryfyhfhhhgtututututut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisCreates Just noticed that Barta's smile looks like a jack o lantern. He could eat an apple through a picket… https://t.co/ik49zFRdgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[How delightful to be able to recover a lost #apple ear bud in a pile of leaves! Thank you for the integrated recove… https://t.co/S2ZQI01Ser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hensonaf When a guy asks to sleep with your daughter who is a child, the answer is no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being called a great leader where all decisions run through him but not knowing what happens to an America  prisone… https://t.co/JsNBtv6S0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand when people don’t use periods properly in their sentence structure .  There shouldn’t be a space betw… https://t.co/F6s3rcdosr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptraughber @PeopleProtected @MattHaneySF @EdReiskin Back from September:  "The Rapid Response team will ... implem… https://t.co/hP26992Nmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferDolin @Loralynn42 I'm glad when I get to hell I'll have company because we wrong as hell for this 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulipsinJune I follow you and you are direct and it’s what I enjoy about your tweets but it caught me as lacking e… https://t.co/jeGtBAbmX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of times I write up something to say on here and delete it bc I’m not tryna get into any twitter politic… https://t.co/kkIdjEZhpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tha_jerk2012 @captainmarvel @DetPikachuMovie You rite! I was just looking at the amc app. Thats when tickets go sa… https://t.co/w9ioWxK3CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I bet a bunch of old guys on Twitter and Facebook complained the game was fine, there’s no need for change and… https://t.co/F3bzG0pt15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelvis221176 @Obliviouzsz @ETECSA_Cuba @MayraArevich @DiazCanelB @JorgeLuisPerd20 https://t.co/olMeDQzS8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndyWillis I come alive when the time changes back...and today’s weather was amazing!]]></document></documents></author>