<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What an incredible day in the sordid saga of the so-called tRump administration! The #TrumpCrimeFamily is going dow… https://t.co/s1KqDH3ZDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anoche dejé la ventana abierta ahora mi cuarto es una extensión del desierto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my husbands closest family members told me I posted provocative pictures. So I’m gonna post 4 of my most rec… https://t.co/5gghjL46Ap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye to work, grading, classes, and exams for the week.  Time for a vacation ☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC It doesn’t matter where the workers come from. The government plays the important role to creat an business en… https://t.co/O32dDZVo3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryPea10015905 @LisaMei62 @OrbHalo Whatever. It was a terrible, ridiculous commercial filled with actors who needed a job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinityResists This is NOT a good thing‼️📣😡 As I have been saying all along, Trump and his gang are about to get us ALL killed‼️😡📣🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrealacavex Dios te va a ir capacitando en las áreas que piensas que no puedes, pídele que te guíe, te de sabidu… https://t.co/QwsqRv4V8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkuemps35 appreciation tweet! He's just as much - if not more - to credit for the run the @ArizonaCoyotes have been on. 🏒🥅🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for both of our #smallbiz and love #kc for acknowledging and supporting them. #we❤️KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t answer your call the first time? DONT REPEATEDLY CALL ME unless it’s an emergency. I will call you back.… https://t.co/hKJltaNtoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanessaKing98 OmGEEEEEEEEE I frickin flippin fracking love YOU ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know where TF this song FLOPS. I love PLEASE ME. why they try so hard to trash her and we know they're a go… https://t.co/L8hJLgwBLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstroLovesCodey @trailhead They really do need more levels.  My friend is a 6x ranger.   I have no idea what they would be though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live footage of Micheal Cohen in his starring role as “Flipper” 🙃  Thank you @RepCummings for brining this hearing… https://t.co/8otOo8myMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lol2Linda @BoschAmazon Yay!!! Let me know as you go through the episodes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin’s new fire chief, Joel Baker, also getting into the #ValentinesDay spirit...@austinfiredept #firefighters… https://t.co/2NmUdIexu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 Ways to Overcome Your Anxiety and Panic Attacks (That Drug Companies Dont Want You to... #hilarity #chuckle… https://t.co/hkxCZruLB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandsomeAnHeavy Y’all niggas really like spaghetti sauce touching your fish? https://t.co/kWahFES4RI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreedomForVenezuela  #GodBlessAmerica @marcorubio @jguaido @MariaCorinaYA @beatrizbecerrab @AmbJohnBolton @POTUS… https://t.co/hpIvEmF6zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Agustin1Chicago @shawnglinski @Samer_Kawash @AlfredoGLM @ErikMobileGLM @TomMonahan10 @gigem96r @brianjshay… https://t.co/cYvyrq5SfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to the wonderful UCI Writing Project for introducing me to this strategy! @uciwrites @CWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a gal friend who’ll be boring w/ me watching true crime docs + eating hella snacks while lover is busy and gone. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting, specially when you compare to https://t.co/mwYu7kWDlw #BigData dead? What’s the next death? #ML replac… https://t.co/COhlEwRtfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLUG INTO JESUS....porn, sex, $$$ will never satisy.... https://t.co/aeSTrSSGpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyft driver’s air freshener smells specifically like Lip Smuckers Bubblegum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Monday again #HappyMonday #MarchForth  #MondayMotivation #MondayVibes https://t.co/dWPSMLVbpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day ❤💄🎈❣🌹 • • • • #goodmorning #happyvalentinesday #funnyvalentine #morningvibes #besos… https://t.co/Iv05z7Bxmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve became that one mom that actually enjoys watching other mom vlogs lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been unfriending people and leaving groups on Facebook this morning. Sometimes you just need a good clear out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan I think their arrogance is going to bring the whole damn thing down around their ears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya tengo mi próxima ruta para cuando regrese a Europa, nada más me faltan 70mil pesos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 He’s an angry little weasel. Has zero redeeming qualities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii 😂 it’s the alcohol talking… She is a raving alcoholic, it’s obvious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadreMetiche Jajajajajajaja 🤣, pero bueno ya me quedo claro que eso no se hace.. 😅 todoooo se regresa 😱 ya... seré… https://t.co/5Om3qrWEwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude down the bar from me keeps banging his hands on the bar.  It’s super fucking annoying.  Shakes the entire… https://t.co/wWEwKHxL1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crashing waves before high tide! More snow tonight! #Sunday #surf #weather #storm #seagull #RyeNH https://t.co/IvG8uhVVjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell Ugh. Accusations of lying (and victim blaming, etc.) are so infuriating and are why women don't repo… https://t.co/dOY8IwKK2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jupiterboy99 @britin17k @realDonaldTrump I got some therapy for him, DEATH ROW FOR TREASON !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerosLyre @jrhodescook @hannahemarks She keeps saying she would take bullets for any of the dogs and I am trying t… https://t.co/RURMEvVi0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadGrayMar123 @6OnTheWay and the same thing goes to servers. Bartenders are servers too. If you choose to work in… https://t.co/3ZYKj7D9Kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are my Poplar Bluff buyers? Have I got a deal for you! Click the pick or call for more details. Chrissy Gohee… https://t.co/LkxHl6wW5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi chamba de hoy consistió en  hacer una investigación de un tema que me gusta un chorro, o sea literalmente aveces… https://t.co/aH5zJ2xfZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbsings @netflix My fav...the tartan shoes!! LOL Yeah baby!! Have a great day Michael ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jan and Liz Schopfer start another puzzle!  #puzzle #puzzles #puzzleaddict #puzzlesofinstagram @ 1009 Kingston Drive https://t.co/KuQcn453GS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzardmillerr RIGHT they are the best things ever and make a huge difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great book. . Honest and shocking!  Gives us more insight into your corruption!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Cl out of Toms River shout Amber for processing !!!! @2Daveferrer1 @ritasprintnyc @brittblade 🌹 https://t.co/MbvvQPdU23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thesupercole @SavannahSoutas I have watched both of your journeys unfold since before you two were even together (… https://t.co/ISYNH7nspX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherylpostlethw @LionAndy2 @PatGrant7777 @saladesvertes @AAvallones @sikandarmirza10 @M44582166 @robtropper… https://t.co/k3YYIaeOxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TISDDPES for inviting me this morning to read to your first graders to celebrate the birthday of Dr. Seu… https://t.co/LezYT1k06C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/mWmO6OggU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems What Up? Why R U Trying To Censor Rep Oman?Have U Seen The Tweets Of J Jordan Kev Mc Carthy On Sorros,Steyer,B… https://t.co/gT8YSfkuQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving for Hawaii tomorrow morning so nothing can bring me down today 🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both @SMGAngels  and @GuerinCatholic made the list.   My kids are happy and thriving, thankful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I knew it would eventually snow in LA bc of climate change, I would have just stayed in NY ⛄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great community building! Thrilled Jack is part of this awesome classroom.  Thanks @rachellstanding #relationships… https://t.co/sDC2ynbZpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TiffanyDash @YaraSLove @AdahliaCole @MsStJamesXO @YasmineRosexox @Only1Saldana @hellorobingreen @SashaBenjamin_… https://t.co/SIXm2qafVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the cast and crew of #dazzlebeast which screened today st #cinequest!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went on a date at Texas roadhouse and I thought my man ordered two baked potatoes.   Fell in love immediately.   Tu… https://t.co/lasIuztvHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[La magnifique ville de Québec vue à  partir d'un drone. https://t.co/7WqEIsSyyl #taxi #uber #vtc #quebeccity #Quebec https://t.co/aUHa5u2vwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does my stomach hurt bc I was exposed to norovirus today or because I’m nervous that I was exposed to norovirus???… https://t.co/z3EZHZP7Iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’M OFF THE DEEP END WATCH AS I DIVE IN #Oscars https://t.co/HdFDCLfN30]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am terrible at shoveling snow and getting batter into muffin cups. Thank goodness the snowblower should be back t… https://t.co/7YYiseoAYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really typed in JADE joint into maps like it’s actually called that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrific article. Makes you think what screens are doing to our children and ourselves!… https://t.co/3BI5QU6fmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised at the turnout. Neighbors tell me they’ve been waiting for months to speak with the mayor. They’re ho… https://t.co/SqrO8YLSzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllysonApsey @burgessdave @burgess_shelley @TaraMartinEDU @tamaraletter @mradamwelcome @TechNinjaTodd… https://t.co/NXN0uituBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "Creole and Community Mardi Gras Bash" https://t.co/PXRvX1ucFU @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RISDAcademy @RISDCouncilPTA One day of meeting with State Representatives and our Senator...#Priceless… https://t.co/qw1SMqTtIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever feel like you need a good cry and then you can get your life somewhat back together? Cause same]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ya walk outside at 6 am and begin incoherently jibbering nonsensical words....vaahsahsahsa it's cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrdync Also Jim pulls my least favorite romantic trope of BUYING A HOUSE WITHOUT CONSULTING HIS PARTNER!!! Having… https://t.co/6kjdYyF6FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo I swear when i’m high, my mind goes CRAZY. I think TOO many thoughts @ once, like my brain is mf running 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Grove City, OH? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/DSlwYcsxGG #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday sucked. Today’s gonna suck. Tomorrow is probably gonna suck. Life sucks lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyhannah  .‧／ ﹒.　★﹒.　   ●　 ●  ﹒.★　﹒ +　　_/█_/█_  ￣￣￣￣￣￣￣√√ √√￣ https://t.co/HeCHpLjoy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these people eat out like 4-5 times a week and look the same whereas I have a bad meal and boom 5 lbs gained!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you haven’t heard of @statusserigraph then you are missing tf out. these are insane 🤯❤️ and now he’s doing a col… https://t.co/wj9OyjsGVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt me in Los Angeles at the Standard on Sunset Blvd in 2016, before I moved here. @ Thousand Oaks, California https://t.co/dRk1A22SWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a special treat this morning at the @wchs8fox11 station! It’s a quartet with the Kanawha Kordsmen. We have… https://t.co/Cub2RbbmDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Also says she's the first person to run for president without these voter laws.....um wasnt there anoth… https://t.co/LxFvn8h50y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTown_MrD @Google Start a new class each time. Reuse one assignment at a time. Don't be filing cabinet guy. Be mor… https://t.co/1paNGahPuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can u just pray for me thanks 🙏 these are pictures of me in the hospital these past few months with my colon cancer https://t.co/gENXxifbP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoreLikeBaeJ Bruh I’m not coming when he cries. That’s a grown ass man...milk in the fridge brah lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter repping you all the way from McLeod, Texas! @JODYHiGHROLLER #sr2018 #belmontuniversity #sr2022 https://t.co/QQzjcn9nbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our son's graduation from Basic Training at Fort Jackson, South Carolina. October 31, 2018. @ Hilton Field at Fort… https://t.co/3G8Y33MPwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunching with #myboys 💙💙 #mysaturdaymorning #brothers #bloodlines #myeverything #myworld… https://t.co/FFLEuCC1qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Magnolia's Dental Fund. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/ES8V0CKAoA via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ NCA &amp; NDA All-Star National Championship https://t.co/wG1uH3DrWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[o no someone at the bar has engaged Rick in a Messi v Ronaldo conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #3 @11_kyang ❤️ on the corner kick and assist to goal!!! So proud of her - Go Horses 💛🖤💛 @CHSWomenSoccer https://t.co/4WLHeZSb2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever had an ex that was more immature than a 15 in puberty cause same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pennypasque You’re the best Penny! I appreciate all of your support — for myself and our entire department!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin prisa, pero sin pausa, construyendo día a día un sueño que al transcurrir los meses, cada uno se hace realidad  2/21/19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetteWest @Lyricoldrap Happy Valentine's Day Bridgette and Michael ♥️♥️ https://t.co/pr1CCs04df]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never understand adults that choose to live with their parents. Why? That’s the last thing on earth I would want to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Monday, Celebrating you!!!... Can’t wait to see all of our Wildkats this morning!!!! Have a fabulous da… https://t.co/eozTKC141L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bariweiss Find me someone on the left that has ever shot up a Synagog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hungry and I should just be going to bed but I feel like grabbing a sandwich]]></document></documents></author>