<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @syleisw Yes. I’ll even get off my 64 yr old ass &amp; protest. That would be treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a few people helping someone dig their car out of snow on a busy road... we’re good at that in the Midwest. 😌 N… https://t.co/i8SozefxF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my faves talking diversity and relationships in advertising and media @MercyC @prgirlindc. Great panel host… https://t.co/x7ZsT0sRc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this is an art show I can enjoy! Too bad that its last day was yesterday in Galveston :-/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/nJs0d19Ng8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Year's Supply of Omaha Steaks #giveaway #win https://t.co/ddYnqlTMwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Godric likes to try and get my sister’s fish. He had no interest until recently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazycatkid @thecjpearson Yes.  Standing on the sidelines is no longer an option.  We all have to start kicking an… https://t.co/ZcGaAQeQJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not the most fun night for people who are just meh about Qu-en. *collar tug*]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/19/19 8-10 PM CST Tonight I'm speaking with Mali Obomsawin from Lula Wiles! @lulawiles has an Amazing Album Out N… https://t.co/aupauMAs85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne Congratulations to him. That is a lot of hard work and dedication.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard on PBS @NewsHour by Mark Shields: "Bernie Sanders is cranky, he's not well groomed, but he connects with vote… https://t.co/lgrg3RBgpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Pow...@christiancowan  Christian Cowan NYFW 2019 W/nailsbymei &amp; https://t.co/y2l7hJb9yr @ Spring Studios https://t.co/9tQzMXKGjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must commend Lena Dunham for producing the Girls. Written and directed (partially) by her that captured an audien… https://t.co/NXTkLM28NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UNHP has assisted hundreds of #Bronxites apply for #AffordableHousing - it’s so good to hear that someone has bee… https://t.co/HzZYCR5agG]]></document><document><![CDATA[More snow has arrived tonight. This is near Jamison Square Park in NW Portland. #FOX12Unstoppable #FOX12 #PDXsnow… https://t.co/f24ndNZ5XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews "It's like the bottom of a female lady. That's what it looks like!" Uh... "female lady?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me?! Everyday I’m reminded of just how talentless I am 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It bothers me when moms don’t get all into charro days with their daughters .. like brush their hair , do their mak… https://t.co/grRXqyC13T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Right. As his guest, however,  in his FL mansion, you were so much more heavily involved- you pedophile,… https://t.co/SERsiZLTkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since 2015, the Seaport Economic Council has invested more than $33 million across 38 communities, and last year… https://t.co/XBiTcoasWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Florida massage parlor owner has been selling Chinese execs access to Trump at Mar-a-Lago https://t.co/Poj1ebWOaP via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna read about how to use my pendulum but can still do tarot readings for those interested. https://t.co/8navb4Hy55]]></document><document><![CDATA[La felicidad es una actitud mental que sucede en el presente, en el «hoy» y tiene que ver con nuestra capacidad par… https://t.co/zitxvSyAI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audimait01 @Perpetual_Now @Gina660 @realDonaldTrump I see what you did there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all i’m scared we getting mid april comeback LIKE WHAT THE HELL ITS SO SOON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a lot of scoring in this last stretch. Clemson leads 14-11 with 7:54 until halftime. @WHAS11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keknowlton @VeraMBergen @Susan_Hennessey I worked for a Fortune 100 company and that was also the policy. I don't… https://t.co/szvCEfoB49]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The day will be what you make it, so rise like the sun, and burn.” #WilliamHannan • • • Some days it feels extreme… https://t.co/xcRcTCnVBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  @CNNnewsroom  WHERE IS @marwilliamson ON  your Democratic Presidential coverages?? We all want to see all Can… https://t.co/qKJlPCM7yC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenKatWrites I'd love the recipe whenever you do! https://t.co/t2ouyuXSdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_chart_life hi ian good morning , does your work support into wb now or ..have levels been violated? thxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to stay relevant? He’s trying to undermine a duly elected administration, after his scheme to rig the electi… https://t.co/ZwgwbIUghR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think my biggest accomplishment in life is that i have a 600 day streak with timehop]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does everyone have these professional photos of themselves and I’m just over here struggling to take a selfie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi: The Rolling Stone Interview https://t.co/9KrsQcGKwk via @RollingStone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaibatsuNews No, they were pressuring her, presenting idea as a life or death situation she “must” respond to dema… https://t.co/Hq4BityMgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTDojo #cbdstransforms what a great opportunity for leaders to meet and teach the talent that is our future!… https://t.co/zGgPKt3Ft2]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMĢGGGĢGGG  Today my sleep talking 4 year old just  said "Let me help you from the vultures"  AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts me when my sisters are hurting, I wish I can protect them at all times and never see them sad😟]]></document><document><![CDATA[.......to inform you that I can no longer continue your tenancy at 2905.....  This reminds me of when I was "....… https://t.co/ampiaZcdNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRange0917 @blakeshelton @SmithworksVodka I got one right after his kansas city concert https://t.co/8X6hDo17Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream well actually a nightmare last night I was at work in the restroom and was holding a positive pregnancy… https://t.co/LNCI1esslh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls want attention. Women want respect. #PutSomeRESPECKonMyCheck ◽  #MondayMood #PutSomeRespeckonmyName #Blessed… https://t.co/tllUn05OIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCFBasketball Facts on Facts on Facts, Cousin! Have a blessed &amp; wonderful day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S TIME!!⏰ Get your rockin’ body in check with our Spring Break Slim Down!!! 🌴 With the Prolessa Duo, the Probiot… https://t.co/eaTlJWg2ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔟 DAYS until #gathf2019 🔥 time to get your discounted tix while supply last!!👇 https://t.co/Q0dtVjghOg • Georgia T… https://t.co/xuKAcZPJqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper Beignets, But I Live in Washington State! So Blueberry Pancakes w/Bacon &amp; Real Maple 🍁 Syrup]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is amazing 😍 Thank you for sharing and including me amongst such greats! #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @SenFeinstein What an example to our children she should be ashamed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRoosPE @FusionPhysEd @physedreview @MrSpringPE @PhysEdDepot @justybubPE @Mr_C_PE @CapnPetesPE @OPENPhysEd Is tile slippery?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada As I tell my son, our actions always have consequences. Mr Manafort is now having to learn to deal with his.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy! I’m so excited to go back to state music contest with you! Love you❤️ https://t.co/JmEJYoXTyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Witch hunts don’t net 17 possible charges against the president, do they? Or how many indictments… https://t.co/djYvXCRN3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official- from now on, I will end ALL emails, professional or personal, with “Stay Spooky”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a baller! NOT!!! ⚽️⚽️⚽️ #greatpyrenees #bigwhitedog #pyrproblems #dogsofnyc @ Jackson Heights, New York https://t.co/HlfnbeAIXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@classact84a We carry on business as usual except for the parking restriction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the pleasure of photographing the Fabulous Roper Sisters at the 2019 Hudson Polar Plunge this weekend. Sister… https://t.co/NBPBNhwIBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was... on the only format that dedicates itself to the sport!! Seriously if your a wrestling fan... you have a F… https://t.co/mF0pNC5dlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from #MAESP2019 starting our day with honoring productivity w/@FCPS_adminUES @FCPSCESPrincip1… https://t.co/NqBGXpLQ75]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and @108 made omurice!!!!!!! i drew scary faces on them https://t.co/iC5lf29nKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #WinterWonderland is back on the market! Enjoy #lakelife year-round, from your own private pond hockey rink in… https://t.co/h1EmeCVDMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am committed to getting in touch with my local Democratic committee when I get back to Memphis @Shelbydem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you can join us @ghcorps to shout them out during our #WithoutThisWoman Chat kicking off at 9am EST!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are back, Khloe is FINALLY calling Jordyn out, what a way to start March let me tell you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hebron High School will be conducting a lock down drill at 12:15 pm.  This is a drill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just up at 4 am editing video for no reason... acting like I don’t have to be up in a few hours. Who do I think I am, @emmachamberlain?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for warmer weather.. NOT ready for the mosquitoes and other critters that come with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The annual @Apollo_JH faculty vs. Richardson Fire Dept Basketball Game is happening tonight! #apollogearup]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see the hearing open to the public @RepSwalwell @RepAdamSchiff @RepSpeier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSFlagstaff How are the road conditions in the area? We are flying into Phoenix and supposedly driving into Flags… https://t.co/s3jq9BEtlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everyone who follows my mom on IG... I’m sorry hahahaha my singing sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, behind some hot shooting @WindsorHive opens up a 9pt lead. 37-28 5:30 remaining. #bfairfax #fwsu #vtplayoffs #vthshoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you don’t even wanna have sex but just wanna eat some coochie]]></document><document><![CDATA[A room without books is like a body without a soul.  Marcus Tullius Cicero]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fourth grader just told me that if I google “xxx” I can see porn.   Good Lord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told somebody Happy Thanksgiving today :( lmao that’s how tired I am😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in. California's alternative energy push. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels START HERE -&gt; https://t.co/AsD49ceoZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how this shirt color gives it that chalkboard look. Friendly Neighborhood Hookers unite at… https://t.co/OTOOjUkZL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @AOC She's better at everything including being a nice human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my arms, chest and back are gonna fall off. My trainer ain’t have to do me like this https://t.co/SfzLXKZuLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nate_bowling Again with the whole "more than one narrative will threaten cohesion" BS. There's a lot of narratives… https://t.co/BSOmCbFjvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on some perler beads and I love my family and friends I hope everyone have a great day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laundry ✅ Grocery shopping ✅ Now to head up to the hospital and visit the mama. She seems to be getting better (tha… https://t.co/SXm1KYRO1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shwebb29 Thanks for explaining that. I learned something. If sherry had had the surgery last year or mid season co… https://t.co/E4dN61yuB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herokeeper @Jeremy_McGowan @SenSanders @AOC Not there hard, there’s plenty of people here illegally. Immigration i… https://t.co/8iUIcaPLPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who has lived in Michigan for awhile should know better than to get excited about spring in March. Yes it’s… https://t.co/FIXR1xceEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eringilfoy really just dont know what this is amd im scared .. the statue in the back tho😏 https://t.co/OJkUMfiV1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines day LIKE THIS TWEET FOR THE LITTLE FLOWER 🥰 #valentine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @ChatByCC @jhcyogini Cohen is A turd away from being A enormous piece of SHIT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinLimMagic Awesome on Ellen! I can watch you all day! You are Amazing!!! Love ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jr. has proven Einstein's theory  @joeblow745 @smfehir https://t.co/V0IEl2pGpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBHomeTeam @TBTHSBasketball @PlantCityHoops And to be more clear- the officiating was not good or fair last night.… https://t.co/ED6bz86KJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaNorris4334 You’ll be fine. I felt the same when my old house sold lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sound on....... Happy 8th birthday to my blog!! Oh the journeys we are going to take this year!! #TQOFE #blogger… https://t.co/2ehSt1GnAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy opening, "Blood of the Land"! Thank you everyone involved for this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity 💛  ... Shir… https://t.co/iLmj8ukHNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[All tue watchmen respawned just as I about to zipline down  Now I have to walk on the pipes and churn more ammo shooting them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magssca @CompaTiger @gio_designsla Guess I gotta go to Vegas for good burgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BertoldiRoy @reddogsusie Thank you for the tweet to Foster that is great and again thank you Anna Roy!!🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tristan ain’t shit obviously but that’s still her babydads and Jordyn’s story is sketch to me]]></document></documents></author>