<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_mendez17 Que mal, que dependiente de la tecnología https://t.co/egRVLqv62J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary  AYEEEEEE🤣 10 years on this hoe https://t.co/SEuSjZjnmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol this chill busker dude named Alejandro with legit mad talent was just on, he blew the judges' minds and they as… https://t.co/TKDSbeCSfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Prepare For Glory - on Nitro by @InsidetheFive @ Inside the Five Brewing Co. — https://t.co/IGVXZNEtWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[They revive that sign and still looks good  for 60yrs this pizza giant is still going strong now that's the pizzeri… https://t.co/ffZ9tPn1Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm glad I decided to get this model 😍 Thanks again to timmyko1992 for the transport 🙏🏻 #Nanoray900 #YONEX… https://t.co/7B0sx0pFYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lexington &amp; 52nd Street in New York, NY https://t.co/6gIfpCpEv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[MacDonald and Gudas are such liabilities to this team, we'd probably be better off playing with one less defensive… https://t.co/EBpLqxau6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my girl “wherever my son go I go God appointed me his personal body guard it’s a lifetime position!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@815_boss @Chaz824 Actual factual I love and respect a non selfish individual such as yourself GOOD PPL GO A LONG WAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanoAlkurdi @DavidSandum @ktboldy @annkullberg @FrankHilzerman @movie_gal_10 @BlueMountainBB @rm123077 @muz4now… https://t.co/IFmtuw17fA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPNewk The Dodgers and the game lost an amazing ambassador and a better man. So lucky to have a short conversatio… https://t.co/XM0OCOciJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[[first day as a detective]  me: you can see a set of footprints in the blood there  cop: what do they tell you   me… https://t.co/pqKySZIQzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JarydWilson I’ve done it both ways. No badge this year, but you’ve got to plan ahead to make the most of your badg… https://t.co/jX05060rTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a reminder that a maga hat isn’t just a hat. it’s a bold and hateful political message, one of racism and bigotry. expect a reaction]]></document><document><![CDATA[*talking about my wigs*  Daniel: how do you even put one of these on Me: *takes off wig* Daniel: https://t.co/01ZqjaoVrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heydebigale @AlexFGoldberg Also as long as I’m free-associating, caramel M&amp;M’s are awful—probably the worst candy]]></document><document><![CDATA[from last nite’s date with #sharonvanetten @ Crystal Ballroom https://t.co/NRyQqGuWBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thousands of years of human evolution and you’re taking a pic with a Jaguar, amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kayonnaaa_ I’m sorry, I didn’t know you were a student there, or had a degree from there, or arctually spent more… https://t.co/cxYCUlAWOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the three candidates nominated for a Mexican supreme court position, Jazmín Esquivel, declares herself "in f… https://t.co/PaSVqcUR0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjoneswriter @BillAicher 2/2 If I saw that woman today I would have all sorts of things to say. 1st among them is… https://t.co/gKIDSUt1nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conorsen Wonder even what his name recognition was at the end of campaign. Most ppl I talked to here had no idea who he was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Photos Of Young Leonardo DiCaprio Showing Off His Emotional Range #hilarity #tee-hee #grin #cute https://t.co/HY7tiykM4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrispolitico @dexybailman Proof these nimrods live in an imaginary world in their minds...]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Hawks rookie Trae Young ejected for taunting Bulls guard Kris Dunn”  https://t.co/NCpRxkL49W]]></document><document><![CDATA[in emergency break glass 💔 #bwoodknows #madeinnyc #swish electric 🌈 @ Lower East Side https://t.co/n4t4g51TNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse I can’t believe you are stupid enough to even post this video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been the same since I loved that hoe I haven’t been the same since I lost my bro , I get high I love to smo… https://t.co/pW5sqB3zd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL MUST GO!!! 25-50% Off #vintage #collectables #quirky #antique #modern #art #furniture #decor #patio #chairs… https://t.co/9IlBKRRjXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluezNewz Lol I completely feel you. Would’ve loved to stay in bed and do that today myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone has just dance and is willing to let me cop for the night lmk immediately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictrixPro @TK_Pickle @MKTekkenGod @TheNewCastro @PnoySD @Dankadillas @TryhardJB @BracketVision coming in clutch! I appreciate it bro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was nice chilling and working out with these cats today! @ Wisconsin Brewing Company https://t.co/ogH2JRGSbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time since I can remember (maybe 201) I'm covering a baseball game. Tonight Monterey hosts Odessa Per… https://t.co/oSxPpveSVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/2SFb07PVRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregLeBl_nc Donato is going to be a stud I think. He's been a stud at every level he's played in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry Dead at 52, 'Beverly Hills, 90210' Star Didn't Recover After Stroke https://t.co/SnS3zAmtGy via @TMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The forecast for today is snow (2–4 in.) until evening. 18ºF/-5ºF. Exciting! #MorrisMNWeather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh cut the crap ya don’t give two shits about it one way or the other !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious to know what had better ratings last night...the @TheAAF or the @NBA all star game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaxFootballGuru @FanSided Luv it almost as much as #HappyEndingGate https://t.co/QrhYePTEGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #okstate faithful has got to be better. Playing a ranked opponent at home Wednesday night at 8 and you can’t su… https://t.co/yjoITy9auE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMomNoms @phillee_58 Oh yeah. I don’t have a college degree so I don’t qualify for a lot of jobs. When I added u… https://t.co/MmPxy8eyuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photojournalism, man. That eighth photo...wow. 👀👀👀 https://t.co/exVDl8IiBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malik Hawkins won UD8...fans thought draw or win for Gledwin Ortiz deserved it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a short break from my #Oscars2019 marathoning to have some coffee and a corndog. Actually, I’m taking a mome… https://t.co/66KJnGxBqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitzFox5DC @MVZaGoGo @MOMaGoGo90 @StevieVanZandt @joanwalsh @Moments_Later @TeachRock She’s recording now all the… https://t.co/fDRgM9564Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate wrote his goals for this year down. This is said goals. 2019-200k 2020-no debt 2023-house 2025-invest… https://t.co/YRXZOkXwPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever is down to play me in an iMessage game hit my line... I don’t lose 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajp01961 @TomiLahren Actually, it was written in its entirety long after he was dead. The Bible was written by men… https://t.co/x9KIWYqBmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#party #partying #fun #TagFire #instaparty #instafun #instagood #bestoftheday #crazy #friend #friends #besties tagf… https://t.co/6Rn1kzS2hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Did you know violent crime rate including homicide is down by 50% last 25 yrs? During this same peri… https://t.co/FGT9Jyf09t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooksFoster_1 it’s ok brooks, just bc we don’t see each other every day doesn’t mean i still dont love you the sa… https://t.co/XnMX4GQkWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My office for today. #arthurmurray #arthurmurraylincolnshire #ballroomdance @ Loews Chicago O'Hare Hotel https://t.co/5CMEZfPHzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrakeDietrick @MusicMan1730 @michabittner77 @stuart_borland @klotylda69 @Kelanu @KarlySnarly @GuardMyHeart1… https://t.co/wGrhyts4D7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLynneKenney @SVAConcussionCl Great Stats Dr. Kennet...  We really need to do a better job educating both health… https://t.co/5xNeIcJCZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSSerik @mattmurphyshow Sorry. I don't see it. Whatever. You're opinions are yours; mine are mine. Have a good day… https://t.co/j19TYOU4nB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note: Mr. Trump has broken his oath of office to defend the Constitution of the United States by bypassing Congress… https://t.co/7AehsCiRVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the family outing that we planned but a really nice daddy-daughter night out... thanks for being my date kassid… https://t.co/xKMEKWzjHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LOTPpodcast @TB_Times @Disney @DisneyMoms @wilmanorton Maybe she can explain which days are not excessively crowde… https://t.co/IYsK5xb0jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toronto @MarkUkLeaf Oh he'd be there if he could be, rest assured. Get well, brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its date night...at Costco, with a couple cute little chaperones. Love family life! #citydads #familylife]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say it every day, but I’ll say it again:  The world has lost its fucking mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeBold ⚾️⚾️⚾️⚾️ don’t forget the the #Phillies still have this bad ass @rhyshoskins 45 / 112 this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corvette683 @SLessard This is a patently idiotic take. But what am I doing arguing with a Corvette, oh well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course- another question is why an 18 year old Tiger Woods was allowed in a bar...:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl could sing!  Space Taco &amp; Friends 2/28/2019  #SpaceTaco #karaoke at Jimmy's Famous Seafood #GetFamous… https://t.co/fGk6EK4zjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JavierEnrikez @elrenecito2 @tonymarquezroon @drmonteverde @levantamiento1 @nhaiper @CARLOSEES @arielvmachado… https://t.co/ik19SF3Lto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asalciunas975 @jasonmyrt they key to get around the high prices, I live in FL, so I will get a series worth of tic… https://t.co/cQhUly137g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobTG4 @provideplatform @kylebt @ethereum @mi_ayako @VitalikButerin Why would someone make this without those prop… https://t.co/YySrmrF3zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[De nada —   Having a gay friend makes you a better person...(according to science)  https://t.co/LOKopNa3nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that rational argument and actual science could possibly change the minds of anti vaxxers, but here is the bigg… https://t.co/oA5BYzYXSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#essence The essence of democracy is the #freedom to choose. https://t.co/kqFpyfrH4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieSage Thank you. That is nice. I tried a joke yesterday which was reasonably funny , but most would rather get… https://t.co/FVgNmTYqau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriteJones @bt4bbs @Trump @TrumpScotland That's awesome? Guess no one in the US will cover this story!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside subway station where @MTA conductor attacked overnight a steady stream of people needing help for drug use.… https://t.co/n1Df6f7P6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joefaz @ellievan65 You are right. The GOP received 99% of NRA campaign dollars last year. Ryan never brought a gun… https://t.co/csoDRu9mAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElephantGripe @BBCSport White folks stay obsessed with race.  Look what folks history when it comes to black peopl… https://t.co/ay9QmaqOi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Not good when you have anti-israeli followers and antisemites following you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedChasen Sarri said it wasn’t tactical it was miscommunication between the Medical team and the coaching staff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume @SaraCarterDC This vote is SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SAD SA… https://t.co/4TfVWEJ9z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“#AlamoPromise is the moonshot our city needs to reduce generational poverty &amp; increase social mobility”… https://t.co/4LyZd2NPTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkypeSupport Half of the problem was the barrage of non-sensical questions at the start of the session. I launched… https://t.co/f1IbgfulW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yuckband Right now I’m listening to @wingtipsloat’s compilation, Add This to Rhetoric. Amazing 90’s DC indie slack… https://t.co/fkSr4BvX1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing old @AustinTech colleagues tonight https://t.co/S7hYEGDnH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're supposed to give me your phone number I'm going to check your phone number every every single tracking log t… https://t.co/YVMJcCKMo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldschoolKM @AmericanAir As far as I’m concerned, Wednesdaysare for Pink. Maybe they’re having an All Pink wedding 👀😆😆💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamLover69 @advice_birds Oh, good.  Ford couldn't prove the goods with their towing capacity so I went to a Chevy… https://t.co/zIb4jFYInY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Member Services Representative, AA Credit Union Branch Operations -… https://t.co/ijdbYQqitG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was fun to hang with this guy last week at the Western AA divisional tournament. @jtkemper gives his thoughts on… https://t.co/8hhPOCCSr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatkhalid Just saw your first song on SNL. For some reason the first thing that came to mind was, You and Adele should do a duet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolynMack21 @MrOzAtheist @bobmadras @charliekirk11 This is your fantasy. You shouldn't be okay with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twice in the second half Tacko Fall ended the contested part of a contested rebound by holding the ball above his h… https://t.co/uJBflGkIx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to see last week’s adoption board at HATS so full! You may recognize the names Isaac and Sonya as stars of… https://t.co/UL5v7gMP3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pegstur1005 “Sixty Percent Nationalism” by William B. Turner https://t.co/gP98iM4Iid]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird how frequently anti-Semitic, “America First” MAGA folks quote Ayn Rand.  They must not have noticed that… https://t.co/gW3tI4FMUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I have a love/hate relationship with this picc line in my arm. It’s amazing how it works but omg dressing (… https://t.co/fgf3z6acjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egavactip Have you heard the original “You are my Sunshine”? It is hella dark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaetz isn't even a member of the committee. What's his "dog in the fight" here?]]></document></documents></author>