<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[That I don’t want to go; I don’t want to do nothing. That lazy love ❣️ 📸: @erynnnnnnnnnnnn  . . . #PhesKemmistry… https://t.co/7JO7uZucYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I am happy that I did not die from brain cysts and insomnia but I wonder if I will escape this hell… https://t.co/tQWFs9q6Q9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO Isn't that like the kettle calling the pot black.  @DineshDSouza got prison time for much less than Rosie did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSBVB2HIM @andyblack @JulietSimmsALL Nikki Sixx’s charity, that Andy and Juliet have promoted and supported, is th… https://t.co/ar7RHG3Awx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice beginning for a rainy day.  #sunrise #calabasas #california #losangeles https://t.co/7hYTYPpzaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[After everything that has happened and all the eyes on me... all I can say is...stfu and enjoy the show, only god can judge me. #realTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sharon99366516 @modafalla @Talena23472 @NVKelpies @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/WTl7PYorTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[making solar great again. Rofl Making California a leader in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy ST… https://t.co/ePqUlEpcfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Charlie I will tell them, if you don’t love this country get the hell out. None of them have moved. Hollywood libtards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuzSalgado_R Busca una Embarrada donde te puedas asilar cuando se te acabe la IP y seas enjuiciada X Korrupta. The… https://t.co/1sWp4nKgxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: Leadership principles may be taught in courses somewhere, but principles are not “action” or “put into practice… https://t.co/LQ8tH9a6D8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tssssss Happy Birthday to los compas @pollomalo and @_RichHomieKevin 🍺 #itsmodelotimefool]]></document><document><![CDATA[walked into the men’s room. shit smelled like a sewer. said fuck it and walked in the women’s room. shit smelled like mints and flowers]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is wisdom? https://t.co/pSqjfwtECf. A deep relationship with Jesus is necessary for access to the wisdom of God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Failure to condemn anti-Semite Rep. Omar by House Democrats is a profile in cowardice.  https://t.co/nCjNzWxwwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien quiere hablar y aplaudir esta atajada a mano cambiada salva tragedias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbarkley Easy, meatball sandwich from subway with sweet tea and salt and vinegar chips, I speak and read child very well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To put into context this is preceded by compassion, kindness, humility, gentleness patience and forgiveness 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love serving with my Rotary Club...Rise Against Hunger Event #riseagainsthunger @ Crystal River High School https://t.co/FtQBjdbfIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freeBikerBot1 @RealMattCouch That’s not something you the government to do when an American does or says something… https://t.co/UTl3vnH1WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cat85082413 Strongly Urge you to take a look at what I wrote. Probably the Most Important Education in a Lifetime!… https://t.co/61oNuX4ARn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Fries @MJ_for_IA They’ve often times lacked mental and physical toughness. When it goes south, it goes south quickly. And it’s UGLY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw 2/ crimes - some of them in plain view - taken together, comprise a vastly more widespread and complicate… https://t.co/2wnzxoAuJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raasmitty Daddy. He goes by daddy or at least that’s what I would call him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeGrove @JamesRoweNL @AFTVMedia @clivepafc @MartinWengrow @ltarsenal @LeeDixon2 @1kevincampbell @adrianjclarke… https://t.co/Clls8I4FR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO EL SOL SALDRÁ PARA TODOS, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/ScHJzwzAVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“COMMUNICATION” OUT NOW VIA @complex x @complex_uk x @JamesMBKeith 💕💕💕 happy Valentine’s Day y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me win this stunning ring from Viv Storms Fine Jewelry! ❤️ https://t.co/j6kfPbff1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conselice @astrophysics @Thomas_Connor @CarnegieAstro I like that idea! I’ll add it to my calendar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a fan in the 70s and 80s of the comic, bringing the @Daredevil story to Netflix this way, with these artists, is… https://t.co/lnoDvbojO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynnoftrumpland @BellaInxs2 @BMcAdory9 @tibbs_cindy @NeensCa @PowerTaking @ItoniLl @Caliicoder3 @lulump007… https://t.co/UuumKa89wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reddit's Testing a Tipping Option to Pay Creators on the Platform https://t.co/5N3mHl5RC8 via socialmedia2day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen a lot of weird/awful stuff covering courts but watching Abducted In Plain Sight is almost too much to han… https://t.co/nGZkJ9tgzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGATOURLIVE without question his autograph. The care he took in signing things goes to the core of who he was.… https://t.co/H3iTcpwA2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dscc @dccc @SpeakerPelosi @SenChuckShoemer @GOP @USSenate @Scotus @thejointstaff @USArmy @USNavy @AFPAA @NATO @EU… https://t.co/6WG2yjtH7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frigay13 @MGnPpodcast @GidgitVonLaRue @theretrocinema Just in time for my afternoon commute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signup today and you can bring someone to share the pain for free!  #sandiego #sandiegoliving  #daygo @ San Diego,… https://t.co/LXIyQLlquy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gileadmedia It’s the only shelf, yes. But floors are shelves too kinda right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why @HouseRightProd is the BEST!! If you are looking for a partner to help improve your ministry, services… https://t.co/Qxz0c5A6ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Chelsea Manning faces contempt hearing after refusing to testify before grand jury: Chelsea Mannin… https://t.co/UkxYCjCOSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But God will redeem my soul from the power of the grave: for he shall receive me. Selah.” Psalms 49:15 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaireBLang #DialedIn Back in the day I chose Home Depot over Lowe's because I was a @TonyStewart and #JGR fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re still gathering opinions on Rowan girls basketball player of the year (or co-players) and coach of the year (… https://t.co/W6DJ2PiduS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatEarthOrg Time zones!!  i have flown from ny to california if its a flat earth than it would be sunny across Am… https://t.co/QIOzlNmTP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hermanntertsch @CristinaSegui_ Si señor, estaría encarcelado desde el minuto uno.......aqui en Estados Unidos mamadas las justas.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hutchike @jc00ke @lucperkins @jacobrothstein @rubinius @MagLev @jruby I admit I have not dug into concurrency in C… https://t.co/fM8k5g9WV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a snowy, foggy, temporary waterfall kind of day at Zion to start vacation @ Zion National Park https://t.co/IEoQ0MvpxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karkarbinks97 &amp; i’ll be here to turn that frown upside down boo don’t trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly half of Canada's incarcerated youth are Indigenous, according to Statistics Canada https://t.co/4Fr560Y1GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Stroop @NegateTheChaos The bottom line is money. There will only be enough academic freedom to hire professors.… https://t.co/ECGoI7ooRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynamicFoxtrot Can we put it in front of Frisco’s stadium. https://t.co/bUJKH3BtuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this live with my dad was a special moment. More of the same this weekend, Wales 🙏🏴󠁧󠁢󠁷󠁬󠁳󠁿. Scott Williams… https://t.co/FCEFTDHItf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madilongo Do you know that bitch blocked me after I posted that reply. She can open Twitter on her phone and shove it up her ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi to all praying and enjoying xm sirus radio chanel 30  countdown 1000 classic rock songs by them  where at 895  v… https://t.co/vrc1JjCnGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closed up for day  #solvang #california #californiaadventure #adventure #roadtrip #vacation #fun #tranquil… https://t.co/TfUIrqEdf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance "Safety of the American people", is SINGULAR, donald j trump!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boylen: “I’m taking our clock guys to dinner. That’s the way it’s supposed to be.” He means doing whatever it takes… https://t.co/LDvgMr0C7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I do not understand when 44 @BarackObama Sign a deal to give Israel 35 billions for their ntl secu… https://t.co/tZRocgnWqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Eldorado Resort Casino - @eldoradoreno in Reno, NV https://t.co/cNAcgNvOAF https://t.co/ah4Ykieqt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SailorSlob I was royally pissed about that cliffhanger at the end. I stayed up all night beating it, only to get t… https://t.co/LkXsGbUQYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariansauter1 @Atheist_Dragon @gehrig38 @RjLeBlanc @charliekirk11 Two references to a book who’s authenticity is q… https://t.co/nelEhWE6w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UWF season opener April 7 come watch us get #Uncilivized b4 you watch the PG stuff   https://t.co/PYZ3sEeolc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scottie Pippin said it best, “Lebron will never have the tenacity MJ had and he’ll never want it as much as he wanted it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roofusdamas @ObamaMyPresid @funder @realDonaldTrump @nyjets i am sure that is exactly how it happened, or maybe by my 72 @MiamiDolphins  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i retweet my friend’s photos because everyone deserves to see their beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[People: Me: “jumping to conclusions” @ Broken Ankle Crafts by G https://t.co/6WBSDvWxBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/07ez4qoovN ("Better than UltraExpensive Doctors and Pharmaceuticals with Side Effects!")]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pridegrinn @ABC The most dangerous place in America is trying to stand between @HillaryClinton and a TV camera]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuing upon their 6-0 run to end the first quarter, the Stormin’ Pointers have started the second with seven mo… https://t.co/k4UTupipVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dressed for CCTV.  Part of an ongoing series of work exploring the #hoodie  I am fascinated in how the hoodie has r… https://t.co/gEtueHBfUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all have probably seen me RT their podcast each week and heard me plug their podcast on our podcast, but can y’al… https://t.co/bnra3SGR4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wake up at 4 am vs let’s say 6 am every day for a year you’d gain about a month of time. Time is money people, get on top of it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacramentoKings another tough loss , this one to the team with the leagues best record , bucks 47-14 , but hang in there ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThebestPML @adidas @MLS I hope that someday MLS lets the teams get their own kit contracts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kellie_Pryor That was actually one of the reasons why I unfollowed him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinamash I’m sure we don’t agree on a lot, but, I knew you were a good guy by the way you questioned Cohen. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStation enough shilling fix the game before trying to upsell it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimelordGenius @MissAmyNelson If I had been doing some weights, I would think so.  I am getting back with my train… https://t.co/E504ObkAil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@privacymama I don’t know if I should be in awe... or deeply concerned...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BuildTheWall   #BuildTheWall   #BuildTheWall   #BuildTheWall 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸💥💥💥👏👍👍💯%!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure who was more excited at shoot around this morning...me or the girls?? Haha!! #BetterTogether @ Cassell Col… https://t.co/ukjxajK89i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing more ironic to me than people who don't see a problem with our healthcare system retweeting GoFundMe pages… https://t.co/EtavMLNh2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at New Orleans @MarriottNola in New Orleans, LA https://t.co/dkJZWrWfm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Sad Rappers by Tom MacDonald https://t.co/S2PL3XF6Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Sorry u sleep with dogs u wake with fleas!! Start scratching !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Barrel Aged My Only Friend by @ocelotbrewing @ Fitness Room at Madrigal Lofts — https://t.co/o1m2VLWdG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Metallica. All 9x's I've seen em. #10 is coming up in less than a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP mindset: Investigate Hillary. We didn't find anything. Do it again. Still nothing. Do it again. Nope, nothing.… https://t.co/gv0iriz32F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonGordon11 I am helping organize a teacher conference for over 200 and I am looking for some fun give aways. Woul… https://t.co/V2BYdPWtUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your Sons Picture Portfolio this MONTH 🔥Link N Bio🔥  Haircut + Photoshoot Bookings Open on my Website 💥Link N… https://t.co/D3WhlCHsSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarabethUrech Best athlete in the building  Not to mention the hottest https://t.co/ZDYbj8MjKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impeccable timing as always 💥beccagt   VC: johnnycaretakerdetailing  @TheAtcoDragway  #atco #dragway #carjump… https://t.co/LHO7RqBgov]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eagles secure one of their own, #Eagles and Jason Kelce agree terms to a one year contract extension #FlyEaglesFly… https://t.co/j75eIx76v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRider444 @Kokomothegreat @AudreyGarden Any student of history can say Trump using same propaganda methods Hitle… https://t.co/zSq9kEayIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They need their extra paychecks, you know those tax free ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si vuestros pecados fueren como la grana como la nieve serán emblanquecidos @ Othello, Washington https://t.co/knUb2x7YKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had listened to @jayair's advice earlier! Peer #mentorship works @IcubeUTM! ☺ Sometimes the best advice… https://t.co/1DE9fCdmni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awealthofcs One thing about housing affordability, real home prices vs mortgage rates made it where housing afford… https://t.co/15OdDWLbzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[His power starts with 26K followers vs. your 8K. He reaches more people and they enjoy his humor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DimeUPROXX Slap on the ass or slap on the head ? Shouldn't they both be gone.]]></document></documents></author>