<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[18 years old  3 exes  1 piercings  0 tattoos (will change soon) 4 hair colors  0 cats bc i’m allergic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really think its awesome that @CW_Riverdale is dedicating all future episodes of the show to #LukePerry its certainly well deserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agarzon Mudaos a México para que veáis, con tú seguramente amigo ideológico AMLO, al comunismo destruir en vivo a… https://t.co/gtZkh2sYYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 That's convenient for you. Also an unplanned day, except it is an Official coffee/tea chocolate ch… https://t.co/SZOFLOiXnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomMorrisJr1 Peaches and Herb...my song in high school. Dang I'm old! " there's one perfect thing and sugar this o… https://t.co/pYEF5i0tR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mans reaction should be like James  #NewProfilePic https://t.co/apoqAsux5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A book is a dream you hold in your hands.” - Neil Gaiman  #ReadAcrossAmericaDay #bibliophile https://t.co/UlRp67No85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin @DMNCBIRD Everything could be tied together -- explains why Graham and others are so fucking scared a… https://t.co/tc3SDUFeGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKatt93 It’s worse at Halloween when people hang sheets from their trees and I’m already a tad jumpy and exhausted 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever has my voodoo doll please scratch its back, I have a rash and I’m not allowed to scratch it myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won the first lawsuit so imagine me winning another one just because.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love me some #italian ❤️. #littleitaly has really blossomed. I remember the early days and reporting on the ideas… https://t.co/o2oWp8O8Nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of decanter tags found new homes last week. What would you put on your decanter tag? . . . .  . . .  FOLLOW… https://t.co/N45l5zWtqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs It's the free everything...they have debt from college, job prospects based on education weak...cant af… https://t.co/Ff9XT5PhTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danaeward @sianoresist @Mckabe3 I had a chunk taking out of my thigh by an Australian Shephard. Id been hanging at… https://t.co/1fLfYnklU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day off vibes....  Thanks to our wonderful hostess with the mostest! @ Connecticut https://t.co/tKN1zLLSNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a joyous laugh just now enjoying a Popsicle. In the freezing cold. One of my dads favorites. One of my favori… https://t.co/bLlRXv5j5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are all toddlers. They want their instant gratification instead of holding out for the best. Real security whi… https://t.co/NFyNDatDi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quisiera con todo mi corazoncito una rebanada de pastel de chocolate se vale porque tengo una semana enferma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayari Just saw Sorayya Khan read from City of Sin. Tomorrow Young Authors Academy, then b'day party for a friend… https://t.co/r3vSUP7N24]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought about that night when you told me about your big plans and all the things you were gonna do And I knew I believed in you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicxleelizabeth I HAVE CLASS AT 8 AM BUT I THINK I HAVE TO LISTEN FIRST]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to #Whataburger , I have no self-control. https://t.co/f4ZTf8P6HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting back into running and I’m really excited because I’m going in with the mindset that this is something I… https://t.co/l9DtKdhVi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who pissed @alisahigham off but liiike LOOK @ HER...can someone piss me off? Jesus hot damn I am sweat… https://t.co/qqUbmOK24w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hungry? Get $5 off your first order on #Uber Eats with my code: eats-johannah1589ui. https://t.co/e49OicDWdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2000Bored @leeleeb50 No more like a National Embarrassment. https://t.co/kaK6gSH3zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving our Author Panel: Aisha Saeed,Alan Gratz, Jay Coles, Always ce Faye Duncan, Corrie Wang, Jessica Khoury, Der… https://t.co/srTA3UrTjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only national emergency is that our president is an idiot” @AnnCoulter https://t.co/ZbkIuJjIxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moxies_official  we are never eating at one of your restaurants again. Ever.  Unacceptable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I super excited to be at Skender-Newton Realty. The TEAM work and MARKETING plans are unlike anything I have experi… https://t.co/V2bbigg4Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Education is my craft, not my work. I love what I do.” @PrincipalKafele #closingtheattitudegap #equityinschools… https://t.co/Duz19IFkjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s @ATLUTD #FoundingMember Chapter III supporters’ gift was glorious and majestic. So proud to have helped bui… https://t.co/RKPLhCnVUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skijoey I feel like a very large whale lol..my due date is march 31st 😊😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to the love of my life ♥️♥️ @weaseltea #valentinesday #marriage #mygiftishumor… https://t.co/ZIuW5gof9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[He tells them not to make any assumption about Ferguson because he is in custody. He tells them not to speak with a… https://t.co/OIlzxSFet8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump The fake news said Obama did it, when in fact it was a result of a long and brilliant ef… https://t.co/kaHb0CgXDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a hypocrite!! You are concerned about pregnant ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS yet you voted for the new abortion packag… https://t.co/mGjSyOHdc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M2Madness Oh yea!!!!!!! Alcohol too. What the heck, they are no better than anybody else. Random, perfect. Does a… https://t.co/YcHD5Q8N3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CunningSq16 @MisleaderC @GrandmaVeteran @brandon7nettles @JanMPerry @Barb81146 @AussieDebBell @Carlos_Can_Do… https://t.co/AV7wDXgi4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 Productive evening mentoring and learning with fellow commissioners. #CommissionOnTheStatusOfWomen,… https://t.co/aCeBkG7jOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Policial ajuda um (homeless) sem teto a se barbear para que o mesmo possa vir a trabalhar ♡ #Respect and #Admiration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GohfR @Goldkart88 @Amy_Siskind Those kids were approached by him once again. They had absolutely every right to st… https://t.co/SgYh0a49Xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m no longer forcing shit . If I’m not receiving the same energy I’m giving , that’s about it you do you and do me .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbMcQuade @maddow @msnnc You always make everything understandable. I am envious of your law students, although… https://t.co/2aeo6ZhyO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Billeting has been a very rewarding experience for us, but with every end of season comes a bittersweet moment when… https://t.co/SeN98yLXrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coffee slowly gets stronger. This must be what being an adult is like😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Judy used the word obfuscate. How many people who go on that show even know what that word means? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re a city girl when you get to a crossing like this and carefully and automatically avoid stepping on… https://t.co/lqaZLHgpbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am convinced all of life's issues would be fixed by getting another dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, what? Why him? I don’t think I’d like for him to be the coach of the Lakers should Walton get booted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aIyssastephanie I thought about the THINX panties before for chilling around the house and when I don’t feel like… https://t.co/54If6xhKBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @brysontiller’s Exchange will forever be a classic love song to me. What’s crazy is the original sample was… https://t.co/eczjJ19qRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍓Beauty begins on the inside.  🍇Start there and work your way outward.  🧘🏽‍♀️ #BeautiesEatBerries  🔮#DreamInColor @… https://t.co/AuEr6cU5bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou If you are, then so am I.. I stopped following @VanJones68 awhile ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMCAgencies @cgilbeysmith @SamBaileyREAL @albanytheatre @officialFST I can see it now, it's on for sure!!!@SamBail… https://t.co/m8MhQdSHLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a moment that shows how freakin easy it is to attribute financial competence/generosity to men, when in fact w… https://t.co/grOwPXuNIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsmerrymerry @ImWatchingToo @PascoSheriff I just went on there went thru album she ain’t on there]]></document><document><![CDATA[R KELLY AND MJ ARE PEDOPHILES AND ABUSERS END OF STORY BYE #LeavingNeverland #rkellyinterview]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKidFromKent Dave Grohl is a better frontman, but never a Nirvana frontman. Plus, who knows what was to come if KC had lived past 27.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What beautiful &amp; Patriotic ladies.  With .@realDonaldTrump from the beginning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see @Luke5SOS @Michael5SOS @Calum5SOS have a shirt with their dogs face]]></document><document><![CDATA[i finally get to see my cats again today and look forward to being sat on every day :3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@menicuretti Los vínculos de Facebook son conocidos. También sus promesas en el Congreso estadounidense de ser fiel… https://t.co/TyiEDIr1WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing I think most of them do. They distract with cartoons or other unrelated interesting or humorous scenes… https://t.co/7hjY3TMvns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynneCamp4 The puffiness could be cheese burgers and fries. But his actions are bazaar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to throw this in here.  The book ‘Why We Sleep’ 😴 provides a great overview of how sleep affects memory a… https://t.co/Tyg1DOaWyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Brooklyn my son’s 6 year old friend told me she loves to go to Connecticut Muffin with her mom and wanted to tak… https://t.co/kr9J8J0Pro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeHowardnc @IngrahamAngle If the vaccines work—anyone 15 and under should be covered! And do a bit of research, i… https://t.co/nXK0FkMunw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_drazzari @boozychef @NetflixCanada2 Well I'm not going to pull a finger over this one 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday in the A.T.L.! It's 62F. Sunny. Blue skies. Time for catching some Vitamin D. I lloove riding bicycles!!! https://t.co/hQhf3kRQ9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would have thought that sniffing pure lavender essential oil could help ease anxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve made some friends. ❤️#horselover #riding #horse #colorado @ Clark, Colorado https://t.co/erNctTYRdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is @JeffreeStar gonna review the morphe foundation and concealer or is that some kind of conflict of interest???… https://t.co/gTnnSwXNin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland And let's talk about the lead poison my dad did not survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody ever allow me to get my nose pierced again.. i’ve had it pierced twice already. i just recently switched to… https://t.co/KTcwalyTfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @AndraDayMusic #riseup and the #micdrop to those who love her and can tell her.... read her fan tweet… https://t.co/yUGKyY5m7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson @Betterw05759703 Engaging only once and Then I will block you. Yes he did. There documents and film foot… https://t.co/0Mx43sjcPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyricSaysWhat1 That sounds awsome and you will soon just keep working hard and be patient 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youth can learn in elementary. Real changes come/happen 1st from farmers' change of heart, waking to intelligent st… https://t.co/Z74Xfp01Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I joined LA City Council President herbjwesson in recognizing @thaGeespot for #internationalwomensday &amp;… https://t.co/cTuvswZdyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jae_quellin @hcohenpoet Isn’t it the most perfect thing you’ve ever seen 😭🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what other women do you DM me “You should come see me” expect to be ignored. Go get you a chick that’s… https://t.co/MIgqWI6VuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many feelings about #bubblegumalley 🤨 @ Bubblegum Alley https://t.co/nPN2ouWrrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Autumnbaby_NYC @RealCandaceO @William61150861 @CNN @JussieSmollett Dang Straight! What does he think he is an actor or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  hello Mr President. This is my first tweet to you. Is there anyway you can stop  this silly time… https://t.co/Q7u8LVN6x3]]></document><document><![CDATA[you call me up again just to break me like a promise, so casually cruel in the name of being honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Tracee and me as we discuss the physical foundation that is so important for balance, alignment and sports per… https://t.co/mlW5lkhhCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blgtylr I am the exact opposite. Could we get an irresponsible surgeon to swap out our brain lobes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE MONSTER IS T-PAIN!!!!!! I KNEW IT FROM THE FIRST EPISODE!! I KNEEEWWWW IITTTTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu sou uma pessoa que é a primeira e segunda instâncias judiciais   Teclado me chamou de chave de cadeia, mano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have been on the road for ten hours and still have a couple to do and I get way too introspective. I’ve listened… https://t.co/qwOZtU7VX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity That's not it Mr. President, not it at all. We ( most of my friends and many millions… https://t.co/VhrLRohQwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly have no idea how people deal with daily commutes anymore.   What a stressful waste of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[URGENTE: Decenas d autobuses dirigiéndose a Santa Elena de Uairén llenos de colectivos y pranes armados comandados… https://t.co/KKwOv2thJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My manger got me a chipotle gift card cause she knows I love it there 🤧 #mymanagersloveme]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hoipe that these Martzs and Dibbles that I found know some Ilniskis and can find me and take me to an Ilniski family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nice to drive to church and to hear the familiar voice of Jean Vanier on @onbeing - "what is important is to bec… https://t.co/YIrbXg8Sc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[”The cost of fixing our subway should not fall on the riders alone.”  I could not agree with @NYCSpeakerCoJo more!… https://t.co/LqJ8gfVLgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErrolNazareth @BurdockBrewery Fierce is right! It will be intense at the Burdock too.]]></document></documents></author>