<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So good news everyone! The doctors have lowered the price of surgery for us and we met goal! Ginger is going in for… https://t.co/06as9z5wwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyAuCoin77 @skyatlantic @SHO_Billions So, for the UK market, does @lewis_damian do his lines in his native (English) accent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late disability #FF @RebeccaCokley @AsieduEdmund @AndyAUCD @DrKaraAyers  @Olas_Truth @maria_m_town @Keah_Maria… https://t.co/bnujkzsvNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And let’s be honest. It’s been 10 years since Mississsippi State has been in the Tournament. Expecting to end a dro… https://t.co/ATWeGycM0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVDExcel6 @repmarkpocan Agreed! Fear of one's own Shadow is not a strong campaign strategy @dmarain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitchell White started the Austin Half Marathon! https://t.co/uIdBeInoES #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to live in a world where we see a sign that says “butts” on it and immediately giggle. #liamraydonovan… https://t.co/yYp3AvxBTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just told sara I loved her and she replied, “whatever, perv.” And continued playing animal crossing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimminyKricket He has a huge national network of supporters across the country thanks to @ninaturner and… https://t.co/GBmFlT1jVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd Holes inkinri ray_ce #holdsteadytattoo #holdsteadytattoos #tattoo #tattoos #piercing #piercings #ri… https://t.co/Wjh5zgNbgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneymag22 He’s up eating breakfast getting ready for school...oh, my bad.  The other Reid.  :-)  Sprained knee… https://t.co/jl6ejHITXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWrightEDTech @anthemgame Thanks for stopping by! Always great to see you :) #esportsedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacabreracardio @CarinaHardy4 @crpisani @Dr_Santangeli @LuigiDiBiaseMD @adribaran @aalahmadmd @MuhieddineC… https://t.co/2MDAxdoWVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[La #radio. Mi primer gran amor y mi primera conexión con el periodismo. https://t.co/AKkzRgSUtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Traunsteiner Zwickl by Privatbrauerei Schnitzlbaumer at @zumschneider — https://t.co/9e2dA5AXFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreeTristanThompson when your girl won’t let you break up with her and you’ve tried every trick in the book to get… https://t.co/zrAEznUY5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[My view for the #kellyclarkson &amp; @KelseaBallerini concert @LCArena_Detroit https://t.co/AutJRJQuhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erynnshea You do an amazing job for your team and Husker Nation. That support network is there when you need it. ✊️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonteMcNaughton Nevermind your grandchildren https://t.co/uZ1cXFkZHy  #ClimateChaos #Fridaysforfuture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to Ken Dulin, and vote Trump 2020  Bio Non Degradable #Indie #Country #Rock #Blues #Singer #Songwriter Hear… https://t.co/7DhOUu3C06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking Saturday off (and aware it'll get me killed by my Exec Chef) to divvy out my check to my bills, hit a much n… https://t.co/XykhjnDWUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your car detailed today! https://t.co/YzD8CM8PgL Dm for pricing and availability today! #Wash #Wax #Sealant… https://t.co/hUCWp2lHQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you’ll go.”… https://t.co/ZxWSU7PM6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Majestic Star Casino &amp; Hotel - @majesticstar777 in Gary, IN https://t.co/SQdj2Wr4se]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS 1st REGION TOURNEY (13-18) Marshall County-31 (22-7) Mayfield-35 Halftime.  Marshall Scoring: Tyler Powell-11… https://t.co/ydrYSd9gUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m in a strip club for a lesbian bachelorette party pls send help https://t.co/JMRXBF7dMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hooleil @abrowntable @kplunketthogge @roopagulati We were talking about bad experiences flogging books. I was doin… https://t.co/mmzhdgnkGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metal Elitist:If you dont listen to Extreme Tech Death Slam porno grind you're a pleb!  Me: Man I love Chiodos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @guardian We now know our focus has to be on building machines that take CO2 out of the atmosphere.  Use for m… https://t.co/uYmwzwpWWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really proud of KG. Great to see U of M leading the way with development of surgeon scientist. Dr Gallagher great c… https://t.co/E9La2rINxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsnelson I had my first arthroscopic surgery for a torn meniscus in 1992, and several since then. Now there was… https://t.co/22h93h0nX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/ReVRwAhNZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IJayHawk @gma_dawg He did not play above replacement level what are you smoking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHAQ About To Kick Him Out The Studio 😂😂😂 @NBAonTNT https://t.co/37pLq1TBjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love bug still slaps!!”👏🏼👏🏼 @jonasbrothers @JKCorden  #sideeffectsmayinclude #jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorJohn2005 @JRob_YP Looking forward to welcoming her to this world! #grandparents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok- if you don’t know about @rIVerseLive yet, you do now. You’re welcome in advance! Just like we so badly need div… https://t.co/7QmVrrPMfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad that Mueller report might be delayed. I prefer that trump and pence both be inside USA, in case bad news comes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oodja @JustinLibrarian Nice, might get in touch with you about something I’m working on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennanokc @DSOWrestling but this is the #NewEra where we're the authority lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real difference is that LeBron plays excellently while his team still finds a way to lose and tom plays below a… https://t.co/6BCUQ45p0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAURAZAPATAM Nombre a veces creo que son estupidos a propósito. Hacen todo lo contrario. Pero en fin que se puede… https://t.co/vFX8MbqK3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally have a week off for work haven’t taken one off for almost 3 years the dedication lol and thank god for pto but damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y entonces el venezolano que está afuera, se mete en un baño público, revisa Twitter y llora. Dios protege  a… https://t.co/GXtvZaBCG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Maybe the United States should bomb every #Chinese #Coal burning power plant and every Chinese #oil… https://t.co/ABL6LW13L3]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is so awesome to give us all the pathway to Heaven and we are so happy to accept His Grace and Mercy towards us… https://t.co/FivCKwZm8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official I’m throwing it 🥳 now I just gotta decide between Los Morros Del Valle or a Banda 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Im not buyn it. This economy is hotter than a $2 pistol. Everything Trump touches turns to GOLD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricCross04 Would you ship Xander and Justus for Adell? Already have Gleyber and Seager in a dynasty league and my outfield is lacking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nhl picks feb.23 washington capitals, new jersey devils, boston bruins, carolina hurricanes, florida panthers, san… https://t.co/bky9ACF1Z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey coach, this thing is really tough. Do you have any tips?” “Swipe” “So keep doing what I’m doing?” “Mmh” jakemc… https://t.co/vQVYfh3amE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCMayor  https://t.co/gFQSzv77gF. Blame the idiots in your own party. Their hate drove Amazon out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...*Not* necessarily via a path to citizenship or even permanent residence. Guest worker programs etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[28 सो वैसे ही मसीह को, एक ही बार अनेक व्यक्तियों के पापों को उठाने के लिए बलिदान कर दिया गया। और वह पापों को वहन कर… https://t.co/LV9Ltli8dR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@specialtechie I'm still thinking. I haven't responded... yet. How would you respond, @specialtechie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Music: The Gentle Wolves' "Do Not Be Afraid"  https://t.co/LB4dI50GnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just passed on the box bc this chicks toes had no polish. ISSA NO for me dawg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bullshit you fucking miss me there I said it talk to you in a few months]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s better to sit there quietly and have people THINK you’re stupid than to open your mouth and remove all doubt.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendabaak @aztezcan @ashtroid22 @ProfMattFox @HarvardEpi Don’t know if economists have equivalent of no exposure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavy fine #snow falling in Gainesville...  Grass is already covered residential side streets starting to whiten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu ainda não posso acreditar que namorei uma pessoa que não gosta de pudim. Quer ser pau no cu? Beleza. Mas não vem… https://t.co/OBX1AW1UWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New congresswoman @AngieCraigMN “hit the ground running” - talking about broadband access and the advance of specia… https://t.co/BFCAmih98j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLiberteChan Erin Myers and Montoya never seem to answer back have a great day let them do the cold days 🧚⛸️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_dmg04 @Cozmo23 @DeeJ_BNG @DestinyTheGame  middling reaper motes? Can these only be used on tier 2 of the reckoning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iluvketo_admin @Lone_Star_Keto I made sure my wife saw ALL the same video's, lectures etc. I knew she would work i… https://t.co/UTAlDzCfBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#onyekaForParadise #TheBachelor - yeah I’m just now watching this weeks episode - anti insomnia sucks lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gungor's final tour. (@ Dimnent Memorial Chapel in Holland, MI) https://t.co/QRt63wUtTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so cute how much the president and First Lady love each other 😍😍❤️ #HappyValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/ODLmP3Uwkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swiftie01 @JustinTrudeau "teachable moment" implies that Bozo is failing badly at an Apprenticeship Program for Prime Minister of Canada]]></document><document><![CDATA[This young lady is an amazing content creator and deserves a lot of recognition and praise for what she does here o… https://t.co/57G3sofxgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vilma_Meche @Patria_ve @tuiteros_vzla @NicolasMaduro :—)))))))))))))))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackMitchellLNK @zpeters73 Im a legit bulldog!  Wife should be proud 😜🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffAHamilton Nvm, Louisiana. I have a serious case of jealous atm. Have funnnn!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[con habré de poder erradicar la pobreza;  pero la pobreza solo se puede erradicar con buena educación, con salud, c… https://t.co/jBsOJWXTeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctryboyleosprtr my pleasure to meet you my name is Brandon Teague deputy sheriff of the Tulsa county sheriffs offi… https://t.co/xkCl4AgYih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCR_HemricFan21 @CopaCavanna @BubbaWallace @TylerReddick https://t.co/xDycgb4fOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[ur mcm doesnt have a cool and unbothered aesthetic, he pronounces the X in hunterXhunter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what some of my colleagues think..... who are your winners?   @TorelloSports @MikeCairns5 @Olivia_Stacey… https://t.co/5bHaJJf8Ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t waste my hard earned money on another ticket if we’re in this kind of mood while losing]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Civil Rights Hero in a nation backsliding into oblivion...hopefully we can get that Zeitgeist back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished another! Spanish tomorrow and a weekend of @ECUBaseball and me and @RylieO107 @caseyimbasciani will b… https://t.co/8r0KySOFdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herrmanndigital I tried articulating this on that pod with @EcommInfluence and @andrewfoxwell a few weeks back.… https://t.co/ua9rcY5CeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m “I can’t enjoy the Mr. Rogers documentary” level of jaded at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else notice that most Girl Scout cookies are just candy but in cookie form?  Thin mints- York Pepermint… https://t.co/9cLBc58cO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @kelly_clarkson @PrayVoteResist  snowflakes cupcakes they don't know what's right or wrong can't see through the bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimbcbs4 @ebruenig Whistle blower rights were a lot better 200 decades ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just donated to Los Angeles Fox Trot!  Help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation for Parkinson's Research today! https://t.co/0rdCqznxGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't that just a little too similar to what the people who supported that little man with the funny moustache wrot… https://t.co/FOhDXGZE32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please talk about the bad ass @WuTangClan gear Shuji rocks in @pen15show - bring’n that #90s #HipHopMusic to… https://t.co/AcTxiGzhih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Ladder I’m not on subways as much as you, but definitely agree. Where they going? Who they got to see in that next car?]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump’s Border Security Victory-https://t.co/JMmC2M3Sdy Statement by Pres.-https://t.co/GyyLJz7upm… https://t.co/AOJCNc0abT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccpecknold We found out, according to the experts, that @FatherRosica #CSB is an academic fraud, 20+ yesrs. The in… https://t.co/NFrcdFvWAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji Holy shit Kyle that one is great. I’m adding that to my list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nine years ago today the world lost a #beautiful #creative #soul and extraordinary #songwriter and #recording… https://t.co/DFBW3rvGXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great road trip for the #Blazers Won 3/4 games they should, 2/3 games they might. Weird losses happen. This team is getting better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Other Night Freestyle Travis Gotti  #FromGunRueToLA. Contribute to me getting signed to a major by sharing my r… https://t.co/9wgB5g1CxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabian  deep cleansing and hydration treatment 😃.  . . . . . . . #hairbyangel #davines #hydrationtreatment… https://t.co/QKSraFFziE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all analyze Kawhi for every movement he makes and then laugh at it. Let the man be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeshe has PROVED HIMSELF MANY  TIMES OVER in the successes he’s had in two years!   He has had so many clowns in th… https://t.co/1flbZo7Ond]]></document></documents></author>