<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When I take the time to get ready, a pic is a must!  😁😉 👩‍🎤😀😛😎 @ Denver, Colorado https://t.co/d6OCta2wpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh no, whatever will the “Catalina” hurricanes fan base do?????? :/ https://t.co/lcbtuPWH89]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone else just randomly say or think “BUST DOWN THOTIANA “ bc same 🥴🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; if this morning couldn’t get anymore interesting....... I get a knock on my window 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so the magic begins (@ Westchester Playhouse in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/vKut0p5Q02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump His panties are in a knot because Newsom doesn’t put up with his shit !]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went to sleep at 730 last night and honestly it was the best decision i’ve ever made]]></document><document><![CDATA[But then again, I always make people wait for me cus I take forever. It’s just so damn annoying 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mykingdomforad1 @bvanhool @MoishesMom @RepTedDeutch @VernBuchanan Thank you for the info. Lot's of ppl asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @ali @AOC You're just gonna spend too much time on this huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu @HandmaidsOnHulu Yes yes yes!! One of the most inspiring shows out there for Women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron needs to move on from those damn jeans. Otherwise this outfit is fire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again @jax_persists @SaysHummingbird @UROCKlive1 @lisastark351 @mmpadellan @navyspook77 @ProudResister https://t.co/hQUeuX1YGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltzul581 @nonimussi Exactamente, convenientemente, se dió  cuenta  antes de las elecciones que el gobierno frent… https://t.co/aA4W01pd8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Leph21 @ArtemiaWhite Jajajaja acá en Monterrey si pasamos los 40 en verano, en invierno solo llegamos como a 34 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetimtalksalot The walks from work to my car are suspect as fuck, especially PM shifts lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to SXSW like a local: think about going to SXSW and then go to the lake instead! 😎 #sxswlikealocal #sxsw… https://t.co/Nfk8VyF1Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: people do not care/want to hear about every single one of your problems on twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasan de hablarse todos los días a no decirse ni "hola", de tener tanta confianza a ser extraños otra vez, de ser t… https://t.co/EZfV2RSJCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romans 15:4 For whatever things were written before were written for our learning, that we through the patience and… https://t.co/ZhkjY6dtZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of you Miss Danica Rose @ Walmart Clearlake https://t.co/G3tpTK9JQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay rooted and grounded in Him ! Blessed and happy Sunday!! @ Brighton, New York https://t.co/CMtwDnbanL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiftyminus2 @patwrench4 What the heck? That's just crazy. No one has negatively commented on my appearance. Yet. Now I'm scared!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jalal_Camargo @shnsf I wasn’t there but from what I understand a child had a seizure and a parent shouted for help… https://t.co/vo8c1g7ocM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya casi olvida mi sudadera en el Gym 💪🏼 le tomare foto por si se pierde 🤣⚾️👍🏼 #SlowPitch #AlertaAmber 🚨 en New Body… https://t.co/Nmpjsidy81]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet didn’t age well and I couldn’t be happier about that #JonasBrothers https://t.co/0F4Hqf93mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton #NightShift. Probably won't  get to see @chrissyteigen's bubba  @johnlegend on @NBCTheVoice Well I… https://t.co/mV8RS04D0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachlusk99 @briannawink I just wanted this video to resurface. just excuse me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VuduSupport has the vudu app been removed from @SamsungSupport blu ray players?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mare_ravs @jwsolovely101 @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @LivePDNation @Sean_C_Larkin https://t.co/fLUDiDSMVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KyZfjyn2vs  Yep, I broke down and wrote a (bad) #fanfiction based on the #DeadpoolMusical on YouTube.… https://t.co/eRsAz5AEIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time to Hilton Head and Westin Resort is BEAUTIFUL!💕 https://t.co/4fMDY3aAIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can make it there, I'll make it anywhere. It's up to you, New York. 🥰 https://t.co/MGMsjcKXfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annnnnd we’re back with X-Men The Last Stand, and I want to give a shout out to how much Patrick Stewart literally… https://t.co/BllwPOaCSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to subscribe to the email newsletters for the city of Clemson? Here's the link: https://t.co/m5DhuI9W9r (Ma… https://t.co/Cu4c8z4R7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[A recurring theme w all my friends is that we’ve all been thru tremendous struggles, n I think that has a lot to do… https://t.co/jwgOf05qZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IainMcKechnie @OurWorldInData Thanks Iain! I've been looking for this exact type of paper for a few years. I'll add it to my reading list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I’ll never blame a kid for leaving for the NBA after a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow @chrisbharrison this is already the most dramatic season yet!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZSHOTS I was at this concert and yes .zebra blew away Aerosmith away!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the way to the top says @ptbrown skinning with my friend #vailcolorado #skinning #getoutside #protectourwinters… https://t.co/kmQ7DjjCo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo Zulu 2 long service medals CPO2 Bramwell PO1 Huestis https://t.co/OYQyw4RcLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatildaAlistar Happy Woman’s day Matilda!!! It is a big day in Russia/Europe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take advantage of FREE Metra rides and enjoy a day at Maggie Daley Park. Skate Ribbon open till 8pm. Only 3 Sundays… https://t.co/3QsUYMzkU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fu¢kn Heavenly= #graveshift #BBCAN7  #survivoredgeofextinction  #bingewatching]]></document><document><![CDATA[how much of a dumb hoe do you have to be to put dick over dignity?   @jordynwoods I’m asking you..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laura24fan @ToddTPrice24 @chevychevelle48 @JudyJ31830202 @JoePalmerJr @JLee418 @DaleJr88FanNate @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/7OKYtO6iUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone please explain this to me? It makes no damn sense 😂 https://t.co/K4XCslLHvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BOSnow  Somerville 5:20Am 03/04/2019 Temple ST. https://t.co/lkpiWLEdwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Amen - a good word from @dbsoaries about celebrating #BlackWomen👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[No network can shove this debacle under trumps shag carpet,Fox is done,it's close to cartoons,but not amusing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanSamFreak @rolletti21 This is when I did. Just those two words: “yes, ma’am.” I’ve been hooked ever since. https://t.co/m8pbM9vzyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Someone suggested Gaetz is Roger Stone's mouth piece now that Stone has been silenced. Sounds more than plausible to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaP1234 Definitely! Tears were flowing here. I was so happy to hear her words, then they made me 😢. I will never… https://t.co/HtW8aRAwvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROBOPHOBIA https://t.co/gab4jl9MI0  #technology #socialmedia #InternetOfThings #Robotics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention...today is my birthday...you may now resume you’re previous activities...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyMRitter @EdKrassen NOW THANKS TO MR. AND MRS. DUMP THESE POOR INCARCERATED KIDS ARE TRAUMATIZRD!!! BUT MRS. D… https://t.co/OK7ByI220G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually no, it just makes it harder on someone who was really attacked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic @realDonaldTrump You are the most vile person comparing our President to Hitler, You do no know history if you do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dimafadma 💕❤️ seriously so thankful we have connected. Thank you. You give me hope!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your church flamingo brings a friend....... #vidamingo #kidmin #sundaymorningvidakids #pastoraspropsandtoys @… https://t.co/5HaE1C3hTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Executed at 22 years old , how could anybody in NYC ever forget this? 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alejandro Góngora talking about teachers’ hard work and endurance in his closing statement. #AisdProud #Adelante2019 https://t.co/B6278WNQ8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best parts of ep 3 of @provos_eligible #Bachelorofprovo (SPOILERS): -Colin flossing -Colin loves dresses w pockets… https://t.co/CZjcT6Fmhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[the women’s division is the same three people, same three matches with the same three outcomes. i’m beyond bored. t… https://t.co/RrA0qb04rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[After work tomorrow I’m going to see ‘A Star is Born’ for the 5th time and I’m so excited it’s my favorite movie💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmswildcat @BrianTome @TheKCSD YOU are doing GREAT Things at Woodland Middle School. So Proud to call you Friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strap in folks. Mercury’s retrogradin’ tomorrow https://t.co/ktGVBj9Zr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[come to the conclusion that i can’t delete pictures, i am a total memory hoarder :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 1 of 2 of a personal challenge of mine recording some fresh material. A couple of months prep went into the pr… https://t.co/AtQ797Lsof]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was photogenic, but instead I look insane in about 89% of pics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DyaneHarwood It's an old picture. I still look like a squashed bug. Here's your Daily Hayley though.… https://t.co/XDpORHwQuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta look at shit from other people perspective to 💯❗️it ain’t always bout you]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 14 y/o cousin asked her followers on insta to use a scale to mark how much they thought that she liked them, the… https://t.co/7uIeY5ENcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[SATURDAYS ! 2 BRUNCHES! That’s right TWO 10am and 1:30pm seatings! More fun and wild entertainment! And… https://t.co/yShjFIzjYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Querido hijo, aún recuerdo cuando naciste y te pusieron en mis brazos, cuando te cargaba y dijiste las primeras pal… https://t.co/T26FUHGdzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Hospitality Manager / Restaurant Manager - https://t.co/Clfs7b0MTi #Restaurant #BatonRouge, LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JPvPNgPVws Please keep this story trending! Cody is an AMERICAN citizen just doing his job!… https://t.co/fhXvQtQgHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FawcettErika @TheAuthorGuy Lamb is so incredibly brilliant.   All his work is amazing, but my goodness Lamb was something else. 🤓😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ouais ben une chance que j'ai un 4x4 à matin parce que la gratte nous a pas épargné en frais de remblais!  😬😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRhonemus Balloons/beach balls. Pickleminton Tournament for 2-5. Look in OPEN PE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Democrats doing their job investigating the most corrupt White House in history of our nation, yet convention… https://t.co/wOxdoXoobl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jandira_feghali @zehdeabreu E a bruxa @jandira_feghalixo se deleita no cuspe nojento  da @zehdeabreu  porco chauvi… https://t.co/wcQp6K4QQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bamabone52 We are. But I never want to be on that side of a bullet again. Bullets were zooming past us. And we cou… https://t.co/lPjAikV8ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 You mean they haven’t locked up Steve Brannon yet? And how, I asks would America vote him in a second… https://t.co/ZmLL7vqqQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @Lrihendry Moron Hypocrite....you defend a man that admitted he likes to brag about sexual assaulting wom… https://t.co/1dm5KOhGzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eminem @netflix Seriously! The best series. It was too amazing to go out that way. It deserved a season 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmgeorgic @jacobysmom2 @no_late_work @brownbagpanty @ockinger @Takethatdoctors @SciencePharmer @thereal_truther… https://t.co/tRVgxXn9v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiersMorganLive was to busy making up with a20 something  young star that he was beefing with.  He is nothing more… https://t.co/UDa9tHn74r]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were always going to to have lunch together, but now you’re in heaven and that lunch will never be....… https://t.co/0G5KRW004V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t move too much or talk I’m actually doing pretty good, but the moment I do either of those things I start… https://t.co/6S65cgGLQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your 30 second Zen break  #meditation #forestreiki #bringthetreesinside #energyhealing #coaching #cravingscontrol @… https://t.co/OW93JCt19G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportSleepDoc @BethSkw Also, a huge number of the terms are Greek.   I think people should take both because they're fun and awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND THE POPO HAVE CAUGHT A TON OF DRUG DISTRIBUTORS OFF HER ACCEPT STREET TEAM PAGE FROM 2010/2011 WHERE SHE COMMUN… https://t.co/MyU06MsZSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[He evicted his last tenants a few weeks ago because they were 7 months behind on rent, and according to him, dealt… https://t.co/JnrEACVB5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping up with @PaulCalafiore_ driving almost across the country to be with @CaraMariaMTV is one of the greatest l… https://t.co/BiLAQ4eV9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billybaroo39 @GopherSports @GopherHole Start ‘em young and they’ll become #gophers fans for life 👧🏼💛🏀🐿〽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHAgotabigObutt @Srt8John @cocaineelaflare 😩😂 ugly don’t be my exact words. I just be like “awww that’s unfortunat… https://t.co/1zGFMYFFiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break down their altars, smash their sacred stones and cut down their Asherah poles. https://t.co/GHODKc3YDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corporate What was that quote about hangovers lasting 83 hours when you are over 40? Please meme it! I am in despe… https://t.co/ynNrqjK5xu]]></document></documents></author>