<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@yungkrampus @3onyourside Who wants to live forever while eating cardboard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wisdom is everywhere around you if you stop it look for it.  Believe then go to work.  God will provide the row boa… https://t.co/eUBhTSr7yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conmebol por favor, ayúdenos, era solo una minucia, la culpa es del sapo, nosotros NUNCA nos equivocamos!  - no pen… https://t.co/9j202FvQ9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjkamensky “There are no cats in America, and the streets are paved with cheese!” #americanTale]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BernieSanders needs to go away. Doing more damage each day since 2015.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the Full interview with Daniel Perez go to YouTube page 730 pm est https://t.co/xEctMzpoGG  #fakenews… https://t.co/6rgSjBRpKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This was @amazon’s arbitrary decision.” @BilldeBlasio, NYC mayor on @MeetThePress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were some high-profile Power 5 decommitments in the 2020 class during the month of February. @RivalsWoody han… https://t.co/f5wJTI2EsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow the Final Table from our DeepStack Extravaganza Event #31 $800 NLH (8Max) $250K guarantee @VenetianPoker by… https://t.co/dXCtl39Jqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye man, usually when I day dream and visualize for months and months  about something I seriously think I need for… https://t.co/qph4EwQPPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS Those in the White House in the Trump Administration remember you go down when he go down remember you will be called out]]></document><document><![CDATA[the world of fashion lost a legend today, no matter how you felt about him. RIP Karl Lagerfeld, your influences shall live on forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALSO REMEMBER ALL SUSPECTS ARE INASENT UNTIL PROVEN GUILTY IN MY LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE COURT OF LAW.  LYERS… https://t.co/u7icU77MzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRMotorsports @PilotFlyingJ @TMCTRANS @JRMotorsports @TMCTRANS @PilotFlyingJ @Switch @BrandtRacing Good Afternoon… https://t.co/D86CmisTFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned that once u replace your fear w/ passion you’ll see yourself manifest.   Being alone won’t kill you.  Peo… https://t.co/zRCAGjMeiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnywasntThere @maximaxoo @apod Planex X And the reason scientists have not discovered and studied this planet is… https://t.co/ZT2OuzqQuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbudman @nbcbayarea Then why aren’t the streets paved with gold. Instead of pot holes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notre Dame vs UVA. Mike Brey vs Tony Bennett. In other words John Taffer vs Reverend Lovejoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I have one amazing woman. Watching what I saw yesterday had me in awe ❤️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sir_ali_floyd @goldenpipette @saimamaysidik has used this character in her presentations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌🏻😊🏃‍♀️🏃‍♂️ #runhappy #runningmotivation #ultratraining #runningwithoutmusic #running #clubrun #lovetorun… https://t.co/YBMgvFlhLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Jenkins was one of the all-time greats and a phenomenal Fort Worthian as well as a TCU 🐸. I’m so grateful for h… https://t.co/sHjZ94ESp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@what_speed @TeresaTeredo @realDonaldTrump Hate?  Don’t see that. Sorry. I respect all opinions though.  Good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand Isiah Washington not playing at all.  Just don’t get it.  #Gophers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USParatrooper73 You put your government first,  not your country.  Don't get it twisted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're All *Stars* In God's Big-Show!  A Fact. All Of His Precious. Children. Should Know. Everyone Matters. It's Th… https://t.co/EQXA8GEDKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC How inept are you? You cost a low income area 25,000 jobs. You have absolutely no idea what you are doing and… https://t.co/QB0cFWJZGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri @FakeNerdBoy Add a few bottles of Pepsi and that's my tried and true kit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official! A church in TN voted to take us on last night and another promised! That’s 8/20!! Only 12 more to go… https://t.co/zqXdqhnM2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LONGER_DRIVE There are no grey areas here. It’s either black or wh....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valerieromeo07 @oscargarciahh I like how this was 4 days ago and your ass is replying this late 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LSU moves to No. 13 in the AP Poll   Tigers host Florida Wednesday followed by No. 5 Tennessee on Saturday in what… https://t.co/48905uqSi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[And most importantly, step 8- never have done anything of substance or value, and tell everybody else what to do wi… https://t.co/mBj3iVItyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulsenDave you wanna go to Nats/Phillies this spring? You scoop the tickets, I’ll scoop the hot dogs! #BryceHarper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisSturr @DazRazzle @BernieCare4All @crookedmedia They don't oppose Medicare for All, except in the weird sense… https://t.co/4zehCGE3Kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[By far the best way to cook potatoes!!....#campfire #potatoes . #bushcraftcooking #optoutside #überleben… https://t.co/kVDQZltJac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump We the real American’s will believe the Report]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Wayne was born in 1907, only 40 yrs after the civil war and end of slavery. Are we surprised he was racist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome your new sister, Lincy!!! ✝️ “And as they were going along the road they came to some water, and the eunuch… https://t.co/IDFp3CamFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the story will change, Jessie will sue hospital n PD. He'll get slapped on wrists, no jail time and will be post… https://t.co/Vzixx2Pbxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice slow 5 miles checking out the Mighty Mississippi... @ Hotel Napoleon, an Ascend Hotel Collection Member https://t.co/Zk1tU4BFL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So wrong between periods of the Knights hockey game they are singing Sweet Caroline 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman Familia stinks! No one wanted him other than the Mets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subject  Verb Identification~ This 88-slide PowerPoint makes learning fun!   $$ #comedy #chuckle #smirk #funny https://t.co/vFpSCkqF4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SemperFi Marines! Thank you for your dedication &amp; service to our coup. Godspeed to all of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all.... turns out, he was just talking about taking a 💩.  I CANNOT!!!!!   https://t.co/tkwSDL1kod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beautyrest has done it again! 2019 models have unbelievable feels for factory Direct prices at @stlmattress in bea… https://t.co/rCUraq7XLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnimalRescue I actually believe in the death penalty for animal cruelty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyracuseCrunch @NY529Direct @conhockey19 @syracusecrunch @conhockey19 how about trying some @Gilligans_IC ice crea… https://t.co/ltrLx94Gzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we play for all the world to listen 'No One’s Leaving' by Mark Stone and the Dirty Country Band at 10:31AM an… https://t.co/jfzhJew5B3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last 5 hours!! Fill out or DM if you want to be my prom date! Winner will be notified privately so if you don’t hea… https://t.co/JBEpcOVHvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dook fans just take your L .... 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂TAR !!!!!!!!!!! @ Durham, North Carolina https://t.co/4aO7ygpfHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hits home because I am currently on my death bed. Everyone please remember me as an idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fr though, who’s trying to go to Arizona for a few days in March? No plan just a destination and time to explore]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has the right to remain silent, he should really use it. He is only going to digging a deeper hole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major medical life insurance and more email aaronbrowninsurance@yahoo.com https://t.co/RmUOLUtsW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[♡ ℍ𝕒𝕡𝕡𝕪 𝕍𝕒𝕝𝕖𝕟𝕥𝕚𝕟𝕖'𝕤 𝔻𝕒𝕪! ♡ #HappyValentinesDay2019 #johnlscottrealestate #weloveourbrokers #weloverealestate… https://t.co/04frs7wNLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcenters John Mullaney does a great bit about this. (Hint: teacher might have been hungover that day)]]></document><document><![CDATA[INCREÍBLE!! Y el inoperante de @MartinVizcarraC sigue sin hacer nada,se la pasa de promesa en promesa,va a terminar… https://t.co/fTY3Llql4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between Carlson and Pirro just this weekend, id love to see what all the very serious journos have to say about this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Years ago my wife and I saw Brody Stevens MC the side stage of local comedians at a festival and he kept referring… https://t.co/RFj65cJCCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real quick: My reputation with the gays of chico is that I’m a hoe. Yeah I post slutty pictures, yeah my Grindr pro… https://t.co/4Lo1tgS6KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccionNacional En el senado te tenemos para trabajar hipócrita, preocúpate por la nación mexicana, por el.estado d… https://t.co/BnKEm03pY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@explorethesouth @VisitMSCoast It is a great photo. Looking forward to a stop there in a few weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanleyRoberts Kinda reminds me of the famous SNL Christmas episode of Schweddy Balls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersNation @Trevor_Lane @LakersTalkESPN Who cares They make it what then? They play next to no defense.  They're… https://t.co/X1z2LrRoEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K12obinson_ Hi, We can definitely help you in design and development of your website at an affordable price.  See… https://t.co/l8j6n2fvhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting at a large table by yourself waiting for the other 5 people in your party to show up is real awkward]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is Tommy SHAW from @STYXtheBand ... the internet thinks he’s part of Tommy SHOW. Bluetooth Mystery Solved,… https://t.co/S79oWmijNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super barato o @havaianasBR @havaianas recomendo a todos do Brasil vim nos EUA e comprar. https://t.co/mRBlNxJ2s9]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. If you ever choose Bieber over Cohen you're an idiot. 2. Dance Me To The End of Love is a Holocaust song...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryRitzxMP Realistically in the short term it's all eyes on the US / China trade talks and whether the arrest is… https://t.co/LutuYcaVs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Jan 27, I’ve spent 11 nights in hotels. It’s been a crazy month. Columbus, OH. Duluth, GA. Atlanta, GA. Time… https://t.co/isujWR3y3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[ngl the only thing that makes me happy nowadays and joanin tf outta mf with my niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[A truly inspirational coach and a massive influence on me as a person and coach. So sad to hear this news this morn… https://t.co/XP49PxUJS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Online student @mikejgolf launching his wedges more like two time major champ @zachjohnsonpga #controlfreak… https://t.co/CIDgSBFrsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrissleMcThorn1 @lauren_lilith @SamSeder She owes her career to the murders of George Moscone and Harvey Milk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio @BilldeBlasio , Totalitarian Elitist who sends his kid to @Yale with armed Security, shares an opinion on baloney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victor Nguyen presents...   VS "I'm Too Sexy To Rent FRIDAY!"  Call today to reserve your spot.  Victor Nguyen Real… https://t.co/SACXMxCz3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMGGaryde @nancy_hamm1 @realDonaldTrump Happy Sunday to you too. https://t.co/xT1ddoaCsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @SimplyAJ10 and thank you for his. Still the highlight of my 11 years on Twitter. https://t.co/x7cQHxVy9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Tim Hurner for being inducted into the Florida Citrus Hall of Fame! Very well deserved! @UF_IFAS… https://t.co/wJh3BXhgcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Hard to say, since none of them have any shame. You have to have a conscience to feel shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until next time Florida.. 🌴🌴 @ West Palm Beach, Florida https://t.co/BvD497fs7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClownaldTrump @renato_mariotti @TIME The facts do not show that, the facts in fact show the president breaking law… https://t.co/DpqprD5sOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelweinerwp @maggieNYT Hardened and broken down criminal....... Donnie... Help https://t.co/nktnERH2bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realtaternator @HuffPost You realize she was talking about Ruth Bader Ginsbergs movie, right? Maybe don’t be so tr… https://t.co/MhJqJ95qMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ma527681 @PhillyFireDept * STEP FOUR Stir in peas. Add shrimp, halibut, and clams nestling them in cooking rice. C… https://t.co/CrlLqEtI7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And let us not grow weary of doing good, for in due season we will reap, if we do not give up.” Galatians 6:9 ESV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you look closely, I can pick out some of our PE teachers from Roosevelt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnubacon It wouldn’t be a Wolverine discussion without blaming the ref’s for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyRotzoll @jhill641 @VMUGAdv That’s your ticket to start my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattagertz @LMsilverlake @Planning4LA Got it and lucky you. One of the many perks of the private sector is being a… https://t.co/mDuFm5Gnug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jermainedesign Nu uh... how about getting active and studying with the kids, not put all the blame on them. If the… https://t.co/hvunvFlTq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You truly aren’t a NY local until someone on the subway has tried to sell you cheese. #SubwayCheese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettHolcomb8 @Phillies @MikeTrout @Bharper3407 Yes,&amp; he would be happy to play here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom Christians around the world please join me in Prayer that this demonic spirit of Antisemitism will be p… https://t.co/vjKT5lqyC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionTedPride @Zigmanfreud @Bitterman59 I don't know if I should laugh or cringe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least I haven't had to talk to the cops about any neighbors in  *checks calendar* ...about two weeks, so that's something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me in #ILiveHereIGiveHere! https://t.co/ih53tC6wkw #austin #atx 🙏🏼]]></document></documents></author>