<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[HACKING UPDATE: Statement from Tampa mayorРђЎs spokesperson after hackers took over his Twitter account and posted x-Рђд https://t.co/ZPiMltCzBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janetlynne211 @Rubiconski @dollyslegacy @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_Рђд https://t.co/2r0WF8t5xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mosesbread72   Patriots defense was ­ЪњЇ worthy...            Now?          SHEEEESH ­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ­ЪћЦ https://t.co/m4YBVDm3UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheZWhite @VibeMagazine Stop hating and stick to the story you are replying under.This has nothing to do with theРђд https://t.co/oe0vavetT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol just when I thought Barstool couldnРђЎt make it any easier to hate them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Specter, 2019 #sterlingruby #art #desertx #desertx2019 #sculpture #palmsprings #coachellavalley #modernartРђд https://t.co/gI5HAXkbCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROBERTOSILVA87 @lechugaec Por el otro lado, Cabeza de Chup├│n, el ├║nico puntero derecho del mundo que no puede pateРђд https://t.co/cH4WcH27WX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not have the opportunity to work with Coach Stucky because his health was on the decline by time I started. IРђд https://t.co/mELmXZbTGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I would bet until this "hoax", most people did not even know about Jussie. With good luck, no one wРђд https://t.co/F44x8YScY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerPaley YouРђЎre so funny and quirky and cute talking about buying a pet monkey with your live-in, serious girlfrРђд https://t.co/ztQUAFfdyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLMonroe33 Shooting 60%+ from 3. I swore in the first half they couldnРђЎt keep it up. I was wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tratar NEFROPAT├ЇA DIAB├ЅTICA va m├Аs all├А del control metab├│lico o hemodin├Аmico (cuadro verde); las NUEVAS TERAPIAS dРђд https://t.co/Y6LzjgVsrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Korean ­Ъљ│ РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ РађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађРађ Рюѕ№ИЈ Korean Air Lines Co. РђюKoreanairРђЮ #HL7621 ­ЪЏФ 10 MAR 19 Seoul, South Korea (ICN)Рђд https://t.co/NuCBIlSk2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeVeonBell mr bell. As an eagles lifelong fan, we would love to have you. This city would appreciate your talents]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he were smart Kuchar would also "quietly" buy Ortiz that laundromat he wants.   Wanna  bet it wouldn't stay quieРђд https://t.co/I9QTmUvC91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caruso in the lane, 63-60. Renfro couldn't stop him that time. The Italian has 13.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 Under the heading of the big so what?   It wonРђЎt haunt them, it will haunt HIM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton and Im closer to your age than that driver. I'll be 33 this year. Oh and I think your mom and yourРђд https://t.co/ZcdBSnJ9H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUPER FACTS bob.sumner! SO WELL DESERVED FOR SUCH A CLASS ACT! BLACK EXCELLENCE PERSONIFIED! CONGRATS @ReginaKing!!Рђд https://t.co/1hhm9Gq6pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyScholesCNN you forgot to mention @ATLUTD playing in the @TheChampions last night! Next leg in ATL on Thursday. #soccer #takingover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretStephensNYT @UrbanAchievr @IlhanMN Pointing out that the Israeli lobby, like the gun lobby, or pharma lobby haРђд https://t.co/lAHIPt1jYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, they've gotta bring back "Passions," man. That's the only soap I really got into -- and I was a freshman in higРђд https://t.co/MDJ749fHRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[LetРђЎs face it Donald. The world will never know the truth about your meetings because theyРђЎre always secret. YouРђЎllРђд https://t.co/i8zZxDVlT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders LetРђЎs quit pushing college onto our students. Many graduate from college with massive amounts of debРђд https://t.co/BdB9or1x60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcchristianson To be totally honest brother I have a missionary heart and I want to go to the nations of the worldРђд https://t.co/FDtcEPtVsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vintage_Utd They canРђЎt even manage their American Football team properly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Socratesino CРђЎest pour ├Дa qui si on pour changer de DG autant le faire tout de suite. Que le nouveau ou lРђЎancien sРђд https://t.co/Xp9O1PMCbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColonelRPG It's okay, I've been quite aware that they always land right size up because I've had a pair since chilРђд https://t.co/v32LlT8Kgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulling in experts in #construction, #realitycapture, and #customersuccess...honored to be working with these three!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammorril Yeah...if you lean into her and say "are you as hot as I am right now?" she may just end up calling an anonymous tip into the PD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend every staring at the same few screens I did for the last several months. Just now the screens and I have moРђд https://t.co/uKl9xWtEZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christo66611498 @MurrellDan When it comes to more "pop culture" questions he has been known to be more smartass whРђд https://t.co/msdq1c71iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss these ladies, great times in 2012 everyone was cool everyone was freinds..  "DIDNT YOU GET THE MEMO" ..... LРђд https://t.co/RHiNEZKGDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreynDaCut BriaРђЎs interlude on late night car rides..... been that way since datpiff days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveFultonWrang @NCMarrk @AllWaltrip I think both these are from Рђў85. I got the Wrangler one off eBay several yearРђд https://t.co/4gT2ymuDwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalanmiller @PatrickTimmons1 He certainly did. That is why it was so miserable when it happened. As I remember it,Рђд https://t.co/lrGSZeWL75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 3-CPO by @Redhornbrew/@HiSignBrewing @ S-K Home Рђћ https://t.co/0IqXFJOkoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron Black gold Texas tea. I'm coming to Texas Jed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ascarborough @MizzouSoftball @ArizonaSoftball @byusoftball @AggieSoftball @UCLASoftball @UWSoftballРђд https://t.co/XFvH3WgYIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[23 people who are changing what's funny right now https://t.co/SnjcC33Db7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurBoreman LOLOL. At 5 I pulled a fire alarm emptying the Wichita Hilton that was holding my paternal grandpareРђд https://t.co/akLNIEK1Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albolte Drove out to Scottsdale a few days ago and it wasn't bad so I'll definitely be doing PHX this season.  YouРђд https://t.co/SbCaiMtyUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a #film camera thanks to @xoxonova | #canonelan7 #fujinatura1600 @ Caumsett State Park https://t.co/lSBsE0EnPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюOk IРђЎm sorry, not to be... festivist, but if you havenРђЎt been to a music festival you canРђЎt possibly know whatРђЎs iРђд https://t.co/48Ks29fIGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was around the time the @Cloudflare Austin office started really taking off.  We didnРђЎt do it by moving sustaiРђд https://t.co/08iP2GIjDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CitySceneSTL Amazon played cities like St. Louis. They never had any intention of moving here and wouldnРђЎt in anotРђд https://t.co/qaUqQfQQ3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiChiro @samstein Great ­ЪЉЇ news on selection of Milwaukee by DNC to host 2020 Convention. Knocking out Walker was fРђд https://t.co/bmj5Vl1PkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xdeliciousdonna Yes I would cum and get naughty with you babe. Also kinky too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 of the 10РђЎs UCLA has earned and deserved. Not all 3. Kyla got away with one on the Vault]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full disclosure IРђЎm a republican.... hope thatРђЎs not a huge shock. But @AndrewYangVFA was impressive and sharp onРђд https://t.co/KH7uxZit3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @TheDailyShow She did have a successful clothing company]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewOnTheRadio @TheJohnSenning @SethKush plsdo read the comments onmy earlier twt. Sorryso choppy. i really feel tРђд https://t.co/5WUk0NKKwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being catholic in Louisiana means crawfish every Friday for the next 6 weeks unless you give that up for lent. ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonfavs @DLind @sung_minkim @seungminkim @Jon_Favreau @xwaldie @SenMcSallyAZ Where @MattGertz in all this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to help mom clean the mold off the top of the wall around the shower and top of the door way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose to be fair Rolling Stone will have 4 Republican women on the next cover. Yeah right! ­ЪўА]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slycoopster @kayleyraee1 @madisyn_young03 He was sitting back knowing he had a plan for them! Look where they areРђд https://t.co/yrIfkCJjSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[­ЪјХРђюGroove is in the heart.РђЮ­ЪјХ Last nightРђЎs Joy Machine at @the1111space was elating. @rubylewla masterfully closed thРђд https://t.co/21RMLY09JI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is no one nominating me to do that Throwback athlete picture thing on my instagram story? Are sidearm pitchersРђд https://t.co/S2LlDk2Q3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just submitted an article for consideration to @nytopinion. I don't think I'm sleeping tonight. https://t.co/gRibbi6bjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to everyone on the @LUL1onsAthletic Basketball teams for the All conference honors­Ъњф­ЪЈй­Ъњ»]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/Xmsi6aAKMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSteveCox @johncusack and not that itРђЎs illegal to do so but IРђЎve never belonged to any country club of any sort #poorassumptions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year was a complete embarrassment from him especially in the playoffs. Anything less than a top 3 MVP candidatРђд https://t.co/S2oy312uTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_a_bell @PotomacRC @Sam1Fleming You donРђЎt think Republicans would rip the Fed over a higher target?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh...the raiders have so much tradition, no matter their record, itРђЎd be hard not to want to play with them, but @Vikings still the #FAVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a PERFECT example for the illegal aliens came to our country to sucking the system and Rapes our women's anРђд https://t.co/Q6ioDjr54A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ahmed91Gooner As long as youРђЎre prepared for this to get ruled out as well. Or we could just scrap VAR and acceptРђд https://t.co/rmazVQhhyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleJoeRadio Mock if you want. All I know is I saw it and it made me want a rodeo shirt, a bolo tie and a duster so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justdeplorible @shanehardy58 @SheriffClarke @realDonaldTrump Call them rhinos...­ЪЉј]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTyler78 @DandMe_MomOf5 @RichP222 @KristinaNadia @judyohtweets @Dapple_TXUSA @LifesStyleBlog @riapanacea U tellРђд https://t.co/y03InkpC9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @adidassoccer, I want to #UnleashSpeed on the pitch! Tweet one below to learn which cleat is perfect for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#properglassware - Drinking an I Miss the Old Other Half by @OtherHalfNYC @ Fanwood, NJ  Рђћ https://t.co/RndkGrHREE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tigerlilyteddie @becausewecare1 @markwafer @wyo_advocate @therealgynomite That's very random and contributes nothiРђд https://t.co/J2kWAc9hMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful and lovely @Bluebunny_03 is online. Stop by to say hello and follow at https://t.co/92KDayJ5QR DonРђЎtРђд https://t.co/IbXSJeoNa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib this is all part of the Muslim plan to overthrow our Constitution and instill Sharia Law. You can pasРђд https://t.co/KyXPqJpPEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bravo1recon6869 @charliekirk11 The uninformed believe what Lying Charlie Kirk says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget about @AB84 , @LeVeonBell you coming to the @Ravens or not?!??!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cam Lard to Nick Weiler-Babb #SCtop10 #Cyclones #Big12 @sctop10 @espn @CycloneMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamivalentinaaa I went there seeking training in a very specific field and he lied about which rating I had to choРђд https://t.co/L1Q0Gng3im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lil_vino_03 Take an 800 Motrin and 2 Tylenol followed by a hot shower till you run out of hot water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But there's evidence that you're a terrible President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBurgess74 There are just some things you cannot unsee https://t.co/N1yhA3xCIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@U12bRed @YouthHockeyHub @sahahockey Regional assignments are a joke...but congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goes to Apple store and spends 14 minutes with genius addressing SE battery, spends 45 minutes on iPad Pro. @ MorriРђд https://t.co/WT9qV4hTSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon, WesterosРђЎs preeminent bookworm, the Three-Eyed Raven, an  experienced blacksmith, and the Mother of Dragons wРђд https://t.co/4ujm3GFdZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felissa_Rose She is definitely her motherРђЎs daughter! Looks just like you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: USF Dons blow late lead, lose in overtime to San Diego - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/YyYjQG0MI5 @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[More likely than defeat, this business owner thanked his lucky stars that this group of socialists came to the foreРђд https://t.co/yLAiW6aaKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Hope Springs (Movie) Ecard: Let's celebrate the day you gave up on finding anyone better... https://t.co/mI3cVrWWIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more tweets like this. ItРђЎs out there if we take the time to look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday February 15 - Axios AM: Mike's Top 10:    Why Trump is declaring an emergency;     Scoop: Virginia book;Рђд https://t.co/ZAN13EAyTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting a batch of gumbo together today. Sniffed up a cloud of seasonings and now my brain is melting. @ Kent, Ohio https://t.co/mTz3Moi5dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blvkkhvrt If you do what you love youРђЎll never work a day in your life Рюе]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of my night was definitely this angry chicken. #atlhawks https://t.co/iXkO5oRHU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmichaelDave Is it two dollars for the first minute and one dollar for each additional minute?]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL that if it feels like I'm out the door a couple minutes early, it's probably because I forgot something. Like mРђд https://t.co/vBGmQinlSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @SheetzJobz @CNN https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/Bm9sxycXnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self-love is the best love! ­ЪЦ░   Dr. Karas (@Falconsdoc) gives a tip on how you can show your body a little love thiРђд https://t.co/Qzf8EVxerr]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I'll remember about the game tonight was that stupid waffle guy who wasn't even watching the game, just makingРђд https://t.co/jf9jCrwcLW]]></document></documents></author>