<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The #ChesapeakeBay’s Role  in the #UndergroundRailroad  https://t.co/33Zma5Llfo via @OurOcean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missouri is the only state without a statewide prescription drug tracking program. House members voted in favor of… https://t.co/ZRwbKLcpys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate a plate of quinoa with nothing but hot sauce on it washed down with black coffee #whatveganseat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder what's gonna get us first zombie apocalypse or global warming. Maybe both]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shouldn’t be on social media this early. i apologize crop top girl I’m sure you’re a very nice person. You’re just insane is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all construction people can’t drive nothin but them damn cranes they can’t drive for shit on the road]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyraej1979 @JennyMcCarthy @ChicagoMacky @Wahlburgers The only person I have following me is Donnie. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3:30 am moment where your ready to rock your cardio and realize you forgot your keys. Drivebackhomeandbacktogym… https://t.co/czggSZXA7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny comics | Dump A Day french women, funny comic - Dump A Day https://t.co/qZQfa4qOUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBigBossMang @Cafealait1 @mmpadellan That is laughable. Watch the Dem Convention again. Look at that sour old pu… https://t.co/SG9KilXjmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelquigs Trying to do meetings and it’s ridiculous, I’ve got the mega croak. 🐸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MahoganyShannon You can fly into Phoenix or San Diego then drive about three hours to Yuma, AZ. Or, you can catch a direct flight to Yuma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @fleissmeister bruh how are you seriously gonna pick a new Bachelorette before airing this episode. You KNOW we n… https://t.co/SeEddK5wvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost I am beyond shocked that the #Bibles didn’t burst into flame. https://t.co/KvpXQcgoYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okie dokie. I'm outta here. Gotta get ready for my doctors appointment. Ugh😟😖not looking forward to that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOGO Free Chemical Peels all month long! ❤ #chemicalpeels #lavishbeautyandskinbar #betheskinyourein #skincare… https://t.co/uVg6DhVsLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tarotwithandrew , I found your cape.... 🥰   Etsy: ConjureKnits RSN: Lynna SC: Lynna729  #goals  #gains  #gainz… https://t.co/ngXwAKa7OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virginia church pays Howard students' debt https://t.co/qCXeGieF14 via @houstonchron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skybar01 @ThePinkPuck Thanks! I appreciate you taking the time to read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debj541 @ArthurSchwartz @DonaldJTrumpJr @RepAdamSchiff https://t.co/wbbeB0OBot]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE JONAS BROTHERS ARE DOING A REUNION TOUR AND IF U THINK IM FUCKING BREATHING UR WRONG I CANT BELIEVE THIS IS ACTUALLY HAPPENING]]></document><document><![CDATA[That astrology app Costar is my biggest supporter of embracing my problematic Scorpio tendencies and I need it to stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this girl! She is so talented and puts in so much hard work into her videos and her creations. Check her out!… https://t.co/Dd5d5NTszj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hi_meh423 Lmao you joining? Cindy and i are probably getting pho and ice screammmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker This one pays to sleep with sex slaves #RKelly rapes children. #Epstein too. What[s the story. men?]]></document><document><![CDATA[FFA Seniors!! The Ohio FFA Foundation is awarding more than $27,000 in scholarships to current FFA members. One app… https://t.co/a7LMqo6Nka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMoody28823955 @TheHighFIveHero @SusieNCharlie @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump God you are stupid. Which is precisely… https://t.co/4qdOdHlxUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturdays are for racing with dad #Benjamingage #skidmoremoments @ 405 RC Raceway &amp; Hobbies https://t.co/dMw7L6lWRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I beg to differ. I've been aware of the evil of Trump for over 30 years but nobody would take me seriously. No blin… https://t.co/yw6PsFfnWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special counsel Robert Mueller notifies judge that Trump friend Roger Stone posted Instagram image that could viola… https://t.co/3qhzXJdkA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because #ColumbiaPictures makes money worldwide on 25 ways to monetize out #Movie in 18 languages now they have a g… https://t.co/gZjhbUg9U7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fried rice anyone?!  When I do food prep these days I make a big batch of "something" containing carbs, fats and ve… https://t.co/fCfSpu6mhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump AG Bar needs to hold the entire Cabal to unseat our duly elected Prez brought to justice including… https://t.co/qW1nXqeHr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: if your partner gets their specials fully waxed 🥺for themselves...but ESPECIALLY if they wax bc YOU like it, y… https://t.co/LHsdUhoe6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of the time @DarrenKibler cracked an egg on @kilmer_amber head🤣😭 while we were inside a house🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You still don’t have a majority and never will. 2020 is going to sink the 3rd class Trump ship and… https://t.co/EQ2iaArgkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidErosenko @HillaryClinton The Clinton Foundation is still "open" because EVERY dirty bastard in our Government… https://t.co/c6vLvwOVxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Caturday 😻 These beauties and so many more are available for adoption from the Réseau Secours Animal in Mtl… https://t.co/N1xaWFdpGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 challenge  from @SueEnquist she challenged me to post covers of 7 books I love:no explanations, no reviews-ju… https://t.co/lAXifQmauP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1AlexEveryday I can't wait to get this tattoo added to my @AllTimeLow tattoo montage 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, I LOVE this. And Alfonso looks to be winning again tonight.   ¡Viva Mexico! 🇲🇽   #Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[the irs is making me do some identity verification bullshit and their website literally just doesn't fucking work]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wrote the words “shoot your load” in an actual essay at The New School. anyways how’s your day going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating a good sound trip to Nashville that is all part of Urban Loft’s growth. So incredibly grateful for my a… https://t.co/e29p0IbzOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinthede Gworl hush. I don’t doubt for one second maga supporters aren’t capable of anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[kaitlyn &amp; i haven’t stayed in on a saturday innna minute and lemme tell u it’s so relaxing 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow #ProjectionJunction! #WhatsYourFunction?? #ProjectionTrump'in! #BeVeryCareful?🎶💣💥 https://t.co/XxTbRkAkqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is Art...Art is life. Cosmic Self Portrait.  #everydaymagnificent #highvibrations @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/YcUE8F3snX]]></document><document><![CDATA[cause it's been another perfect day witcha, wanna lay witcha, spend the night with ya, then spend my life with ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobBrinson1 @Rightwingmadman @shell0131 @MaryLuWiliams @roderunner01 @brainburp13 @Aug1405 @GC6155 @Freedom2713… https://t.co/ZSKi1ndIj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nar001 @Cesiasmith Me too, Natalie.  I'm inspired by the way the @WDMCS educators are IMMEDIATELY implementing str… https://t.co/QW8zp4exYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert trying the medieval book wheel. @ River Campus Libraries https://t.co/CGHoCXVvZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan almost peed his pants asking my dad, could you imagine asking four dads? #cringe #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a renter on 1798 Abbey Road # 102 #WestPalmBeach #FL https://t.co/ZhrQB24efd #realestate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyParker138 @KatieCzachor So sad to see you leave us, but so happy for you! I’ve know you since you were an ass… https://t.co/Uzyu3H0v12]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my first ever trip to California and I didn’t have time to get In-N-Out... So... Did I really go to California?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone @ShopCrystalMall and @Starbucks wanna bring me a latte at work lol need caffeine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksjkollam Wars never ended terrorism,as historically proven,If wars ended terrorism,there’d never have been anothe… https://t.co/0ua12FMyNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“#Reparations is about repairing what oppression breaks: relationship and people. What’s the alternative? We all li… https://t.co/1UxBnQB2zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhhh Upward Facing Dog.   -  A basic yoga pose I believe all who are able should do everyday. 🍃  -  This pose help… https://t.co/R9f9vsdm24]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an amazing product out there for you to appreciate and enjoy.. It's Josie's Coat Of Oats... You can prepar… https://t.co/qzfcOYeucY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch @ToddGre94875758 Mitt is despicable. So mad that I voted for him once.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blugardenia @EdKrassen Throw Sarah Sanders and Donald Trump out with the baby bathwater]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennnnj @KNayyeh Seriously! Granted, all the ones near me close at like 10 or 11]]></document><document><![CDATA[(\__/)    ⠀  (•ㅅ•)       My grandma when my   　＿ノ ヽ ノ＼  __    mom yells at me   /　`/ ⌒Ｙ⌒ Ｙ　ヽ      ( 　(三ヽ人　 /　　 |… https://t.co/tupKlhRcGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealstylesp How To Build A New Reality | #BodegaRun 336 ☕️🐢 https://t.co/W4yHoLp9iu #SundayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freeloaders?! Aren’t journals the actual freeloders here? The reviews system is buggy for sure but asking scientist… https://t.co/N52jOsVPm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jschmid87 @RepJudyChu The cabbie lives in Canada, presumably legally.  How does your comment relate to John’s cab driver in Toronto?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren Liar you didn't struggle just like AOC did not live in the Bronx her entire life. Keep your hands off my… https://t.co/lab4fsUFg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__NoraSantos that tweet might have been the most sarcastic thing i have ever written]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @AOC @CPAC Well,  if that is the case,  since it is white males who do the most mass shootings,  sh… https://t.co/j5D4ffT8S1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leah’s gonna get me a noise complaint at my apartment by screaming about a girl named Carol in a Jersey accent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Saturday night plans: A new @DMRegister/@CNN Iowa Poll on the 2020 #iacaucus field drops tonight at 7 pm CST… https://t.co/bu9rvrPMyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xander6981 @UmbrellaAcad Ooh, no I haven't as of yet. Will have to look it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost from plentyboutique using repostregramapp - We are so honored to be featured in a 10 page spread for @sunset… https://t.co/M3DMTXufNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[As for how Worcester is viewed on accountability, I’d argue that we’re running on muscle memory, and it is fading.… https://t.co/Wde5dU6PM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like spontaneous trips and thanks to California providing so many wonderful places to see. Visited for the first… https://t.co/kXqoscMdTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Friday morning Twitter. Have a wonderful day 💙💚❤️🙂 https://t.co/g8nXLwyLON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon as the sun 🌞 hit the horizon! Outside he goes #screamingatthebirds #mickeymousehat #nikeairmax #runnynose… https://t.co/v4J0vExWJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadieKnowsBest @wutweetclann Sadie girl, I haven’t even showered in a week lmfao #baristalife #espressoformydepresso ? 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[PHOTOS: Channel 2 Action News honors @KarenMintonWSB as she retires: https://t.co/gQ08lUZrEN https://t.co/x3KRdQFHGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS Thank you President Trump 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 https://t.co/LMWg21YHZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse White House doesn’t speak for the Democrats so doesn’t bother trying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a dream 🎶 Another lovely night with the @cltsymphony and Tchaikovsky.  #clt @ Knight Theater at Levine Ce… https://t.co/rM6OLj5zFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalLoveYourPetDay #AdoptDontShop  Dreaming of warmer days. https://t.co/NnnIetSWWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA is the worst. They proudly brought back TYFUS. THANKS 2 THEIR LIBERAL VIEWS ON LEAVING SQUATTERS 2 SHIT… https://t.co/016ZWkAcL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifewinning What I did? I quit in the middle of the school year to work for a public library.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlaina_smith @marcialrod165 @AmandaKincadeSE @CarrieHalas We will miss you lots]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed my Instagram live while I was cooking the pan-fried gnocchi with spinach and marscapone, go ahead and… https://t.co/sNXlLrq7x0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the past Public Advocatea: Bill de Blasio, Letitia James  Some more background from City and State: https://t.co/gkf83zol1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC Tell U What, When RW Corp America, Gives Up Their Socialism Tactics (an discontinue having u folks, sell the… https://t.co/PCSNCcdivh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @Will_Bunch Don't forget, he reneged on a deal to bring the Pat's to Hartford and the city had put a lo… https://t.co/P5q6kX8yhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My upstairs neighbor just came down and said it’s his babys’ birthday and I’m thinking “wasn’t that 6 hours ago” #sorrynotsorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TN5Telenoticias Porque no se preocupan por los hondureños k estamos fuera del país por ofrecernos. Oportunidad de… https://t.co/RNXIEfF75X]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's inspiring to work with @marshallu and @WestVirginiaU Professors, Physicians, Students and WV @MomsDemand to op… https://t.co/3jeIIjf8OG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Leave me alone..” Lol 😆 I always laugh at this song! @ Hawthorne, California https://t.co/WJ4j8katUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue Jackets acquire Ryan Dzingel for Anthony Duclair  https://t.co/WfH5X1QHbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam😘 #SamHeughan #VanityFairOscarParty  @Sheugs @GHJNancy @barbaramills1 @mary_markssngr @sarahjaswim… https://t.co/x7yDot3sI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your tanning booth is playing @FLAGALine on repeat👌🏼 #memories #feels #feelslikesummer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riddle me this, how is she doing so well in a country she is trying to undermine.]]></document></documents></author>