<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Anni_Bruno @cairstine @danagould @williamlegate Are you selling drugs ?  Or  Are you a Prostitute ?   That will be… https://t.co/KEBubrovxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnDelury This shit is negotiated before a summit, not during one. Amateur hour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to make it back! (@ Watershed Kitchen &amp; Bar - @watershed_ktchn in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/CVFO8biuI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane Why would he. He picks and chooses when to help. Right now he has a good relationship with the islanders, nets and Yankees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diamondruby246 @CoolGreenPines @Reuters @bisquiat I have no time for mindless ruskie trolls.   Bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are “loved by the Lord, because from the beginning God chose you to be saved” (2 Thess.  2:13, NIV).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go LeBron! Down 16 to the Nuggets and “your” team won’t make the playoffs, noble work you’re doing there.… https://t.co/RDfi4N9aza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albertoreyes84 @MarceloM12 @GarethBale11 @Benzema @isco_alarcon @ToniKroos @raphaelvarane No estoy de acuerdo, Flo… https://t.co/GqrHaEOB0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple PR’s and seasons best this week! Nice to have after several days of bad weather. #trusttheprocess https://t.co/GZXG2BPWZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathrynGChan @LailaNassMD @AlimPardhan @MacEmerg @ImRakeshGupta @TChanMD https://t.co/3cjtRA0sVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who voted 'no' on resolution to condemn bigotry, anti-Semitism.  https://t.co/xVUoDm6gHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGSU_Hockey Love it! Boys, make sure you give them a BG Beatdown! #AyZiggy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear Peppermint Patty is suing York for copyright infringement? #CartoonWaterCoolerTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[B6: #UNCW now with three runs and no outs. Cole Weiss’ 2 RBI single cuts the deficit to two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkpanther39 @LosAngelesFanz @ScottKaplan @Mighty1090 @ScottandBR @alexpadilla86 Are you just pissed that San Die… https://t.co/Kz82FFH9nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russian say they have weapons aimed at us and no news nothing  that’s crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/7Wo7UnC7Gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the Parents’ Meeting for my daughter’s crew team and the moderator just asked the parents to… https://t.co/LWtQGQoLUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so proud of our Tigers and they sure weren't shy about throwing pies at me for their efforts! #RESROARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case y’all missed THE TAR HEELS BEAT DUKE 88-72.         TAR     HEELS      TAR        HEELS      TAR        HEELS]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes. I mean EVERY SINGLE CAT.  Do people who think sphynx cats are ugly have rights? Discuss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: ✅ Apply for scholarships ✅ Check your college/university’s website. They may have scholarships specific to your… https://t.co/WMabwjcg7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to be celebrating #InternationalWomensDay by taking girls from @girlsincla to see #CaptainMarvel for… https://t.co/hMcYNpdlJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeannaLorraine7 @FoxNews @TuckerCarlson @realDonaldTrump Thank you for taking the time to share your feelings! I agree 100%]]></document><document><![CDATA[”Not to be occupied with thy sin, but to be occupied with God, brings deliverance from self.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[You fantasize about things like this but never know it’ll actually happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Black and Latino youth are criminalized for the natural rebellion that adolescents of all colors engage in.” @LizaJessieP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldschoolsig @pjay2000 Eh, El Paso is also close enough to New Mexico to get some of that really weird influence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made it.  So Good! - Drinking a Mother Tucker Chocolate Coconut Porter by Mother Tucker Brewery @ Mother Tu… https://t.co/V7E3dYMMkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victormirica @Candrade828 @realDonaldTrump @SenWarren @EdMarkey Exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every way of a man is right in his own eyes: but the Lord pondereth the hearts. Proverbs 21:2 KJV https://t.co/VkiiYzlld6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chioreya @radulf_310 @SAMA_Zac @CGE_SLP @eleconomista @ElSoldeSanLuis @JMCarrerasGob @DiputadosMorena… https://t.co/3CKZE7DbvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aarcraft9 @ABabip @Bags4HoF @RoundRockTim @HistoryEarned I mean if you goal is to be wrong, sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatGermain76 Think about this, when u have the draft they don’t do the last place teams first then 4th place teams… https://t.co/jhb5bo3BYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Rockwell Pilsner by @CollingwoodBeer @ The Cottage — https://t.co/VZg2wyNv3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 of the 14 Sunday show guests are white men (31% of US population, 86% of this week's Sunday show guests) https://t.co/fLrQx4bFTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Are you ‘?Speeding?’: New ?Speeding? sign on Laurel Canyon Boulevard. https://t.co/YgpeKFRYiQ… https://t.co/osicrGppWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachglen If he could win in the NFL some owner would have signed him !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I LOVE REALITY NOT ALL THIS  WALL STREET TALK ABOUT LOVE FOR CAPITALISM ,,WHEN THOSE FILTHY A HOLES DROVE AL… https://t.co/rESQljHer9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Mall at University Town Center https://t.co/fCWODCvCs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you tweet about this Kardashian business unironically then we have beef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CozyStudios_ @SonyElectronics I think that they are stereo but I like Bluetooth wireless headsets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the message and activity of Jesus we see an alternative social vision: a community shaped not by the ethos and p… https://t.co/oRlbZ2HA55]]></document><document><![CDATA[you already know what you should be doing. the answer is within.  quiet your mind. quiet your body. quiet your spir… https://t.co/KGpWQ92JtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[For ALL of the women in my life Happy #internationalwomensday #bebold #beyou #fridayinspiration @ Fayetteville, Ark… https://t.co/k3Ycym8iFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrian_broaddus Saw it in a Bar in New Braunfels!  The customers were making fun of El Paso about the first goal o… https://t.co/JY2CG8TQ5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un vaso de agua siempre es rico. Pero ese vasao de agua por la mañana despues de una noche de beberle. #QueCosaMasRica]]></document><document><![CDATA[CrossFit Games Open 2019 19.2 - really wanted to hit the 3rd round but no, didn’t make it. Need to push myself more… https://t.co/0QVYZQVsgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Penelope_358 @Javiercampossss He walks in my room too without knocking😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stg females will suck ur dick like this and then be confused when ur in love telling them you miss them]]></document><document><![CDATA[#سودانى_فى_فريجنيا_حول_لوحة #سيارته_لتسقط_بس  وهذا الأمر ممكن فى امريكا الشمالية مقابل رسوم سنوية اضافية https://t.co/v0GjeKncAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 arrested in buffet brawl over crab legs @danielvankirk @DPTpodcast https://t.co/6EMX93BurU via @KMOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @poroshenko @ashrafghani @NATO @jensstoltenberg @POTUS Those leaders hate Trumps guys.  More lies Mike. You make Jesus sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrskcj @spur4trish @ananavarro I'm a professional Jazz nerd and couldn't get into La La Land, if that makes you feel any better...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I start my day by hijacking Robbie’s Fortnite account since he somehow used my email address to sign up? Y/N? https://t.co/1H6YtSymzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The call it 6th MAN I like to call the Lou  Williams 💯💯💪🏿✊🏿🦍 https://t.co/B1njAxj4dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorge Rodríguez negó que el presentador de Univision y su equipo estuvieran detenidos y aseguró que Ramos llamó a M… https://t.co/dqYYGkwOdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyBlueDevil7 @cdotgunter I’m pulling for the Blue Devils today. #Wahoowa https://t.co/VRcy2ASfqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be pair with the lovely ladies of @ASTphiSLU they don’t know whats coming, just saying! https://t.co/IMtxIAHk8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhweingarten @DonaldJTrumpJr Schiff needs to answer a few questions under oath in public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[came to believe itself more powerful or important than any one man or any single nation. At what appears to be noth… https://t.co/rVmzZZuDyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPost_Mets Avilan didn't help himself today. I know he's lefty, but I like Tim Peterson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No need to name names, but I don’t think I can conceive of a more depressing way to spend time than by watching one… https://t.co/J0JsukFeJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @gtconway3d News Flash, the president can appoint whomever he wishes. You are a mouth piece for th… https://t.co/rNCTsxcWBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPLC gets a 25% rating on its NAME: It IS located in the South, but it’s NOT poor, it’s lawless, and it’s anything… https://t.co/1xdKDM38dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So he says. But as a Senator, he fought for the $1.5 trillion F-35 pork. https://t.co/Jnse0pgYXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports THE REAL BOTTOM LINE IS THAT ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION IS JUST ANOTHER WAY OF SAYING THAT “WE ARE BEING… https://t.co/frCKFbAOls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada semana me abro la rodilla trabajando en l parodia de aventurera..no se ai celebrar cada año de representacione… https://t.co/501nVrlQJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/HeGVA4iduI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HisPriscilla @jennayyyy210 @RedRoseGoth @KHOU @chitakhou @SallyKHOU11 @MichelleKHOU @JanelKHOU @Countrymedic1… https://t.co/Vkz4Hhifux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerusalem_Post How come we dont hear about all those Catholic sex abuses in Europe? From all over the world? Is Am… https://t.co/lJGa6potlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OKBJGM Authors: Dumas, Tolkien, London, Crichton  Comics: Spider-Man/ Marvel  Movies: Goonies, Jurassic Park, Brav… https://t.co/3yqEy3SADj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tag Team Motherfucking Wrestling.  Between last week's Dusty Classic and tonight's Triple Threat here...it's creepi… https://t.co/2J8MPNntcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You only meet your lifelong friends once in a lifetime.” Alfalfa #montneyboys #1967 https://t.co/P9udKqzz4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NACTO @SwansonAnders @kteschke @schlthss @tooledesign @USDOTFHWA @Dutchreviewing That guide is actually what promp… https://t.co/XTeqhH8Yrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mixbonodj @mgalvann @juanelo1950 @marianazac @calbert57 @EDUX77 @pattylopezdelac Eso ya estas demostrando como en… https://t.co/JIxaqFRvJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgingerkid39 @CardinalsTake Let’s be fair: Arenado wasn’t an option because he never hit FA. Stanton declined t… https://t.co/LtgZjh73Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleLuvsBJs So I was on a water taxi in Bimini in 1990 and this was playing  Everyone on the boat knew the son… https://t.co/DjBHjlZseQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening Day 2019. This year Jake's an Astro # 8. Lets make this season ours. Bring home the title boyz. @ Serra Mes… https://t.co/fknjVkVjLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cranston_Mac @JFalk56 Believe me, you don’t want one of those nails up your ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teardrop Trailer in the California Route 66 Museum in Victorville… https://t.co/0fVqocwTBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥🔥🔥 @Disturbed tonight at @WellsFargoCtr #ROCKMUSIC https://t.co/BG7SzyXvbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaidersHLP @realDonaldTrump In your life have you  said a guy that plead guilty was railroaded? We never take the… https://t.co/9lHhHTRK18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sistema control de peso @ Glendale Heights, Illinois https://t.co/OlFDY25oRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebChickadel @blueeyesblue8 @thedailybeast He is not on trial dipstick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLeach971 @davebirkett How many illegals are you two going to support?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbingham0320 Not if the cops watch the video. It’s pretty evident there that he was within his rights to defend himself there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally a Saturday night without rain!!! #nofilterneeded #lakewylie #firepit #relaxingevening @ Lake Wylie https://t.co/mHblZRDenG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@istockhistory Devious plan - persuade drug cartels to launder their assets in MexIcan scientific projects. The car… https://t.co/5F8eQxZhBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legendary @Lake_Athletics head basketball coach @PTickelson at work.. https://t.co/oUXBCzUGxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. News &amp; World Report: Where Can I Find Affordable Insulin?. https://t.co/GG599n0n3o  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the girls are in Solvang and ur stuck at home, have urself a  “Stay-Cay” 1.5 oz of citron vodka  .75 oz of compa… https://t.co/mSboYaBddk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @AggieAdmin92 to post pictures of my 7 favorite books...no reviews needed. Each day I wil… https://t.co/EKDeZxs38I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlesrmonroe @katiet121 @realDonaldTrump Like they didn’t play around in New Orleans or the everglades ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gambusino_69 @epigmenioibarra @FelipeCalderon MIREN A MI AMIGO JESÚS, DERECHAIRO RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dailydoublesw @gabe_prewitt @TheMeadowlands @stevegrammont Good luck Steve!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky Senator Needs to Worry About “What’s Right in front of Your Nose”! Primary for Kentuckians “The People’s W… https://t.co/9ggDXyiBYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @GOP That is a good question? Why are they soft? Ask Rand Paul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I am a HUGE Drake fan but I honestly don’t care for his verse on the Girl Needs Love Remix, I just feel like he… https://t.co/1P6fE1uKPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“After these things the word of the Lord came unto Abram in a vision, saying, Fear not, Abram: I am thy shield, and… https://t.co/Y88Unmwu4m]]></document></documents></author>