<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dicen que en mi caso el dicho va “Échate a dormir y hazte fama”. Más de 20 años después y se acuerdan que no tengo… https://t.co/BGIVj2cMw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Cinemax for so many wonderful movies 🎥 many make me happy 😃 #movies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways the moral of this story is find something better to complain about Captain Marvel than it’s pacing issues b… https://t.co/TCZFtfDBmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CynthiaRamirez @russellcrowe My son was there last week... Can't stop talking about the trip.. beautiful people,… https://t.co/jfonw21auf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detox Day March 2 @ Pieces to Peace Massage Therapy Call Kelly 615-987-1209 to schedule your prepaid Ionic Foot Det… https://t.co/qCuhgCthO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreymunson @USARugby @usmlr @glendaleraptors @Austin_E_Rugby @rugbyunitedny @warriorsrugbyut @TorontoArrows… https://t.co/MqxCIndWFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wspd1pio something happening in N Tacoma?  Lots of WSP headed N in a hurry!  Be safe!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManfredArcane @DavidRutz @IlhanMN She is unfit for the job based on her hatred of Jews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Cities! It feels like we just celebrated 3 years yesterday 🌇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Billtokyosaka @lina_abz @CleverTitleTK So is it Christian to raw dog a porn star just after your wife had a baby o… https://t.co/a2wtNReinF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The movie "Get Out" was literally based off what's currently going on in Seattle.  Please do the city a favor and f… https://t.co/iKVT2Uz9cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so freaking sore from carrying laurel around yesterday so if someone can lend me their kid that’d be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a bit of Santa Fe architecture to inspire calmness to all of you having a hectic Monday. The soft adobe corn… https://t.co/a53Z2O6EBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“this is the jankiest thing i’ve ever seen in my whole life” – twitter user @ericgeller on his first 35Xperience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan @UndergroundSch2 Yes, appears you Donald, have committed treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you females are so weird. you gotta pay me to beef with me 😘 that takes up time... time = money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinvshley smh u told me to beef it up !! I gotta get it a lil skinny this awards + presentations + affiliations sections matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkunta__ @TheFitMarshall You can always give this a try... https://t.co/lQmKxedeM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[publicly traded entities, including AFI Development Russia, which focuses on development in that country. In the Un… https://t.co/axMHJhUBKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullpenbabe @liddyloree Right?! This just made me giggle! 🤣😂 gotta love the Franimal!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m steady walking around trying to figure out how to be a light in a dark place and I am just as dark as the peopl… https://t.co/NbDE5lm4Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's my morning coffee, but I also see a basketball. #coffee #basketball #marchmadness @ Yankton, South Dakota https://t.co/8jF4RrLh4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Great team of modelers at Critical Issues in Math Ed conf. #iteachmath @ncsssm @mathcirque @MrHonner… https://t.co/KwTMW42bv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCheverere @JesseWillis93 @WilldeFries @circlingbackpod @dcarterruff I can’t believe after all we’ve been through… https://t.co/tYbhQhhrGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if @DevinNunes had to recuse himself I think @RepAdamSchiff should also. #CohenCongressionalTestimony #EnemyOfThePeople]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kc needs to get these potholes figured out. Its honestly ridiculous @MoDOT_KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel and pray for those that these days catch off guard AND they don’t have any arrangements setup for their kids… https://t.co/9OFVgyX37L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flea market finds! (@ Raleigh Flea Market in Raleigh, NC) https://t.co/MfI4gSUjmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible day of music and mantra at festival of Colors USA Los Angeles. Join us tomorrow at Whittier Narr… https://t.co/LtDTr4G7oK]]></document><document><![CDATA[He shouldn't  have done it but it's a reflection of our poor  race relations.  BBC News - Empire star Jussie Smolle… https://t.co/heZiEg1IbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ultimate_swords I’m starting to think all those times I can get myself to cry during sad breakup songs when I don’… https://t.co/rVhpRqDtrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louehlouehhhh @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #Stilltheone @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitzyGirl326 @McDonalds The last 2 times I went to mcdonalds I ordered a sausage mcmuffin with egg...they forgot t… https://t.co/fybJkEwIHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolRoots @GalacticFunk @NYStateMusic @brooklynsteel @themotet @HighMightyBrass @NOLAfunkNYC @wwoz_neworleans… https://t.co/PQtxkA8HBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laura88Lee Depends on what kind of brownies your talking about 😎 p.p p. 💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WanderingLydia @realDonaldTrump Trump bashes and tries to grade the Democrats because he’s a coward. He’s afraid o… https://t.co/dbLRoWiA6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelnabors @vanealvarezocho @WWCodeDFW @GdGdallas @WomenTechmakers She is a big fan 😁 and spoke about your publi… https://t.co/Q2p0sS6tcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CajunBlueAZ1 @Gary_ARSC @phyllisj1003 @FixesItself @D_resists @PollyPapaya @tlccourville @CIAnderson3 @BlkSantaX… https://t.co/5fXJIaaOZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe i really stopped drinking soda , if you know me you know how much i love soda and how much i drink a day .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nathan Fielder, star and creator of one of the funniest shows on television, Comedy Centrals Nathan... #comedy… https://t.co/cLfg7zBTpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My West Orange Office in West Orange, NJ w/ @drronpsych1 https://t.co/NjokNcraxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlgitw1 @TWillmc @AynRandPaulRyan @realDonaldTrump Nice try 😂 Here’s your wall! https://t.co/PqTkg1PmUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSalz24 @TheWeirdTeacher @LEGO_Education @codeorg I’d love to know more about your CS exam, if you don’t mind! (I’m grades 6-8.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @Radie_ann Guess he wants judge to feel sorry for him. Do the crime, do the time sucker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titusbicknell Has Hell frozen over? This morning @PandaPearl said, "Wait, I need a coat - it's cold out there!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tax reform changes to fringe benefit deductions affect business’s bottom line https://t.co/uGawj0g62i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicolett_16 Happy Birthday bby! Hope your day is great! Wish I was there to celebrate! 💙 love you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please euthanize this puke. Nothing can rehab a person who would do something like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinCogan @mcwilmot @sarahoerther One of the things I’m confused about is that there is also a Chief Medical Offi… https://t.co/9qO4eumwKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWelshDad @GraviteaUK @PeraltIsGaming @MissAliCatt @TwistyShape Sounds like a good one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imagewords @sandyroche13 @nvbizmag @NevadaStateBank Congratulations @sandyroche13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to CFA today and not only did the time change but it was Sunday 😅😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[when your toys are the same size as you 😂 #cuddleandkind https://t.co/qpdld3lZON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @BEERGUY201 @The_Fool_Monty @TennesseeChris @Shawn172510 @Nick23929445 @MelissaFincher @gr82btnvol… https://t.co/7vDHVfXTvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If our garbage people cant get this right when they are suppose to pick up our fucking garbage, I’m gonna come ungl… https://t.co/cuO2hVvP7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man, guys, I almost forgot to tell y’all about this: I volunteered to sponsor a Gay-Straight Alliance and it sta… https://t.co/14ZrM0woCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGlapaGrossklag Haha, I was the one who added that to the list! Have fun - wish I could still be there with you all. #azoer19]]></document><document><![CDATA[has appealed to a court in Moscow to move Calvey and several other detained executives of the Baring Vostok private… https://t.co/5FwdIqIufC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hootsuite Q4/A4 It’s important to pay attention to trends, while filtering out information that isn’t relevant to… https://t.co/mvGDFau5Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Gibbs sounds like he needs a Xanax. I cannot follow his train of questioning that is clearly off the rails #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funnynicotweets you need to watch Abducted in Plain Sight then do a podcast about it. It's one of the  craziest documentaries I've seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celestee3ee I went on Friday and had to take a shuttle to get to IKEA 😂 its brazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[You go Sen. Tillis!!  As a military spouse, now retired - having lived in military housing can’t imagine this or th… https://t.co/uPfThqRprm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waterparks y’all I’ll give u all my organs in my body to sell for Baltimore tonight!! Sarah Brunelle 👉🏻🤠👉🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveChapman13 “People are more alike than different”. That was her slogan for everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost that time! Tomorrow starts Music In Our Schools Month @LOMESLions @FCSchoolsNC #MIOSM #musicmakesmeNC… https://t.co/EhlseIoJbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[by people fleeing the hardships of Venezuela's hyperinflation and severe shortages of food and medicine.  The U.S.… https://t.co/DXaJwB4ouT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fridayvibes  #Repost from @bringrootoo (@repost_media_app) https://t.co/8Sgd9MnQNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question today is: Will @adsroundtable and I lose our usage of Kevin gifs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariodz @CHAYANNEMUSIC inicia con la #2aParte de su gira #DesdeElAlmaTour por #México #Oaxaca este de 27de Febrero https://t.co/rWvKq5rNHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support these great girls in their Recognition for Relay mission as they work to increase donations and participati… https://t.co/UNPUqFwuor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7: I have accepted a challenge from @sleuthacademy to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no review… https://t.co/g8bi6OkIi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to strong women. May we know them. May we be them. May we raise them.  -Unknown  #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to stop on your way home from work for Lucky Charms 🍀 because @nesharon04 is coming to watch your kids tomorrow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Calling 🙏⠀ #jesucalling #february17 #reading #dailydevotional #inspirationalwords   #20likes #repost… https://t.co/8j6JlxjzNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I watched a guy get fired in a Hampton Inn lobby. Happy Valentines Day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DucadiSpalato @StevenDJBaumann @TBombinski @iamAtheistGirl Hitler was a creepy person to say the least.  However i… https://t.co/uBmQsnDcWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re live at the capitol this morning for Day 1 of the teacher strike. We’ll be following picket lines throughout… https://t.co/s7lqGzuEpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WuffyTheDog @rebeccastaab1 @erinmyers @joybenedict @dogtv @alliemackay And to this I say AMEN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d never be able to go on #TheBachelor because I can’t really pronounce the word “vulnerable.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on everyone Jane is getting the tax returns - non issue https://t.co/8mAlJer7Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why yes, I do love having the stomach flu, fever and sinus infection all at the same time!! Especially when I have… https://t.co/LPPOnrXZzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m home in Key Largo visiting in-laws and lost my wedding ring and my dad’s wedding ring that I’ve worn since he d… https://t.co/LUdUB3Mgub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICameAsMegan_ @Malia_Milligan wait til the end, I’m not saying it’s something we would do, but I’m saying it’s som… https://t.co/Vb7YazSUVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you worried about looking “thirsty” you too young for me. Grown niggas don’t give af😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigDApplesr Come when it’s warm and we can eat them on the boardwalk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JhennaMariie You’re a goddess and I love that song 🖤 my boy frankkkkkkkk 🐰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but the woman that walked into the so called tortured bedroom did not get upset telling her story of… https://t.co/JZgk1mi8kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished the Nextflix documentary on flat earthers— that group of grown, publicly educated people that think a… https://t.co/8nHvuwyG29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 @MichaelGMcdona3 @tcoley1 @beauxvisages2 Say, his aim needs improvement, 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[However, this is possible only if we take the path of repentance by giving up our old way of life and exchange it f… https://t.co/GeeudjqZt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseStym 💗 #lover #bff #MissYou countdown to #Muskoka and #Harbourview #summer2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could today be the day?  Request your vacation now for this fall/winter when you can experience Star Wars Galaxy’s… https://t.co/bppf2SYriX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @MyPeakChallenge Donated twice this evening as hope to win as would love to hitch a ride on the back of… https://t.co/oI6wZMqeR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Stop by the local HUD office and get as much literature as you can. Essential to learn all the term… https://t.co/mNR4qFvJPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good read on VC differentiation.   “We would argue that you have to distinguish yourself with an authentic and valu… https://t.co/AhjNt9eVJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling great this morning after my #hypothermichalf yesterday... slow going in the packed snow though!… https://t.co/HM8djmLulv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican Rep Green is reminding everyone that #Cohen was very much like #Trump while protecting  Trump. Who knew?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah, I was pretty sure as I was reading, that you couldn't have written this statement on your ow… https://t.co/kPsBOQwUHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we just clear this up and establish that fuzzy blankets are better than heated blankets??]]></document></documents></author>