<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump Hey David, Are you going to set up fake Twitter accounts and get banned as well?   With… https://t.co/o2l1ZE7ICB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Tricia @FOX19 @TrustSteve19 @FOX19Jason I was at work and didn’t get to 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thermal fuse, control board, and drain pump work out to $200 of parts, so it seems worthwhile getting someone to pr… https://t.co/Qi6Yoaj4zF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CesarCermeno @Wilsonbarrerar4 @yamisaleh @LORENT_SALEH @PoliciaColombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinikilig ako at wala kayong pakialam. Totoong totoo ito.   My Maichard is real. 😍  #ALDUBxADNStrongHearts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmugele If there is anything that medicine loves more than redundancy it’s specificity]]></document><document><![CDATA[En la vida no hay nadie ni nada de segunda categoría, ley de mecánica del engranaje... “Mayor es el que sirve, que… https://t.co/ply1qMv4No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonSaysMoo We only got a dusting which has mostly melted already but I guess we might get more significant snow… https://t.co/VlKbwMWJCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss legit won about $1500 on slots.  I won $50 and lost it again.  I give up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[good for the most people..." and I hate that slogan. I then checked some luggage and my price was half of the guy's… https://t.co/zja6qZeLvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barracuda_Bella @ImabitcSumtimes DemonRats are so desperate to outdo each other there isn't any of the Ten Command… https://t.co/Iz619zEMKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffalo_alice @thegur It was FREAKIN GENIUS! And major kudos for the lyrics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar And we thought Clint Eastwood talking to an empty chair was delusional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is ridiculous...we @JoshVernier610 @StephenSerda had a conversation on #ShowAndVern dealing with this a while… https://t.co/5myPd1bVLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marihelenblue @SemNuevoSonora @tonoastiazaran @EGandaraC @felguimor @AlanCastroParra @ClaudiaPavlovic… https://t.co/0wcpOSPzeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drboycewatkins1 Because that shit is part of their culture .. And this cant be debated....  Want to argue? First f… https://t.co/At58FcVG7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibiHakim Now that the popcorn is finished, do you still support your Liberal Party Leadership?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How U Doin’ - so glad our girl @WendyWilliams is back! #SILYMI https://t.co/KV1nLygyWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alsboringtweets  Al, the discussion on “See-Low” was odd. Is he not working there any longer? Seems like a great fit to the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a couple you should own:  -8 big bath towels in varying states of disrepair from hair dye and face wash  - 2 set… https://t.co/u8TGi0E4cP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeuristicLineup @CarmichaelDave Yep that’s what I told him...apparently he cares about karma (but only in Hawaii 😜)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump You should investigate zipping your fly, Corncob Sr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbsaustin AND..this is what happens when spineless, whiny, sniveling cowards like #TedCruz get re-elected! Way to… https://t.co/KABTt05dGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanDuvalier @NYGovCuomo They do already, any bottle not returned nets NYS $ .08. This is really about filling the… https://t.co/6bmEfoPc5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga I love your performance it was really breathtaking perfection now you will win many more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aceuswa @TheBSD405 @BelReporter “Equity” is different standards for different demographic groups, based on the pre… https://t.co/fGlPR6C7nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to make our pics again!!  I’ll take #habs #Flyers #StLouis ! @DarcyWhyte4 @TLOMitch @RidinPineShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prncezpuzz @Tradermauk @hicks_william @cmpuzz @LilPuzz96 @CoCoBlaise @danipuzz It really is. And to compare the sp… https://t.co/4lR4bbJDq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dictionarycom @SayMyNameBeetch @hedpe @forteisgod @MarcoNunezJr @PolestarCars @IAmNoWitlessOaf @BNSFRailway… https://t.co/AiuRnflA96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your jazz on with me!!! #chordprogression  #itsavibe  #jazzyemotions  #multitalented  #neosoulkeys  #lutherkeys… https://t.co/7uxROEJ7hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our PTA founders day honorees Britt Norris, Bruce Reed, Vivian DeGennero and John Zucchero. https://t.co/y9QLrw4uW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN STORE and ONLINE STORE SALE!!  PLUS 15% OFF STEAKS IN STORE ONLY!! https://t.co/klIRFglA2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechive #deploymentsucks #deployment #mil @ Fort Hunter Liggett https://t.co/4AuUD0tNxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the one thing that you don’t have to give up for Lent this year? My CherryPickin podcast series! The link… https://t.co/6t4OWTqYHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanksKendyl On the other hand, the bluebonnets blooming now are definitely presented by Bluebell]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a white person, I was on pins and needles hoping it was not an asian NYPD cop in a NYC precinct]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @laneygirlsbball 37, @hoggardwbball 24. Bucs are back-to-back MEC Tournament champs. Not a dominant performa… https://t.co/X0tNWFCGKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad times here at @universityofky 1. No more Bowl. 2. No more Cliff. What’s next? Who knows? One thing for sure is… https://t.co/Ijteg48Bjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump DJT isn’t a tough negotiator or deal maker, he’s a spineless twerp with no moral backbone. He’ll d… https://t.co/8XJRP4qq6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue your technology and service are subpar. couldn’t get boarding pass from the app or kiosk. your service per… https://t.co/AsXDdsxdfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[USC coming a bit unraveled here in Set 4. BYU leads 15-8 after a back row attack error. #byu @BYUvolleyball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you tweet, maybe you should think to yourself “I should shut the fuck up.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomasTroncosoJr @JLMendoza_ @josetomasperezv Pero Pero Cual Corrupción?? Preguntaría el Jefe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews LOL 😂 . Have you seen this unfunny idiot? Speaking of diarrhea, he always looks constipated. Exlax c… https://t.co/B3DiMDRbN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing time at the @edgewoodelem 2nd grade Living Museum #eesbestme #dreambighwd @ Edgewood, Alabama https://t.co/hFUgnYGHDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder If she did run it would be to insure NO Mueller type investigation would exist, but she would represen… https://t.co/RuBHpbFBaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LG_Shawntrel I literally said dont patronize people, and you proceeded to patronize me. 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAMN, my brother preach. The old Jim Crow laws are still being used and these old bootlicks / immigrants just look… https://t.co/rMvB22ILo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ossumasilanna I find it fucked up, they do it for personal gain and want everyone to notice they’re a “good person… https://t.co/FQ42bhr0Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turfmonkeyboy @LBKCR Serenity after the madness of our new water feature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ St. Peter's Church &amp; World Outreach Center https://t.co/m1b8EtCNJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at the University of Arkansas! Thank you @coachdustinfry for having me! #WPS https://t.co/79S8363Tm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan You are despicable.  Un-America.  Enjoy your one term.  You’re done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The McKee’s @ Minneapolis American Indian Center https://t.co/Wzref4yf0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about the home-grown, convicted felon who was still able to buy a gun and kill his coworkers yesterday? You st… https://t.co/GLGFpLucU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[City to spend $300M on new boilers for NYCHA buildings: https://t.co/yqGtIiw33T]]></document><document><![CDATA[42 days to opening day. Just clearing the path for the staff to get to the building!!! https://t.co/zAsYNpbgsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benj_robinson @brandonjrosen @BenLindbergh @ringer Jewish baseball Twitter is my safe space]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet #FakeMelania #FakeMelania #FakeMelania #FakeMelania #FakeMelania #FakeMelania #FakeMelania… https://t.co/HxEm3PmuZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taymarieluhv @dylanlewis_16 @FullmetalAF @Blvckouttt_ @BeticSaiyan @CodyBeecher22]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S. There is a tax advantage to Trump if the hush money is repackaged as legal fees. The IRS recognizes legal fees… https://t.co/A0qwfvY1Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone these are the only links to my new podcast #Medicated. If yours has a pict of What’s Going On This Week yo… https://t.co/awOF3NuIgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else think about drinking the juice out the bottom of the noxzema pad container? Because I definitely don’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Lumbao (2022 LHP/1st Base) came in an inning to seal a close 5-4 game...struck out 3 batters for the win. He… https://t.co/wNqYZ5D2EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the band back together..... @ChicagoDemons 16U team members. https://t.co/PfmxLwUWwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an extra ticket for the Wichita imax if anyone wants to go with me this Thursday! https://t.co/Gty92x6Rn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir thanks to the staff  Dulles to LAX 3/8/19  flight 1089. You all were amazing, cool, calm and compassiona… https://t.co/beOsg6q4p7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCJO_LABMOM889 @DaleJr I'm not going for jr. I've never been there. I don't  chase driver. If I run into him all g… https://t.co/JW4blfUBx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CavsScreamTeam, @CavalierGirls, @CavsSirCC and @CavsAhmaad are here to sign autographs and take photos at the… https://t.co/Ue4RXJGpFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night Cody made eye contact with Luis Kenzie and I amd waved. After making Luis fan girl because he loved his shirt 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So where are twitter censors on this one, come on, this nut did not fall far from the tree and even a broad minded… https://t.co/gYvq4Cm0of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GemmaParadiseXO @WeAdoreVeronica @stellabardot1 @roverr777 What are PUAs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[need to be writing an essay but i’m dancing around &amp; admiring my own booty in front of my bathroom mirror. so that’s how today is going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So trump declared a state of emergency for the wall. I new it would come down to this]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember, at 6 yo, I wanted to be an archeologist/paleontologist... And Aquaman #Aquaman. Or Captain Kirk… https://t.co/lpdbL0Qtjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[small vintage Allure Dress shirt/jacket Black Hearts Tulips Cherries Doves cute https://t.co/IsYxILr3T0 via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's #MarchBreak and the family is away, it becomes #TakeYourDogToWork week at @magic1061 https://t.co/SBwiolxWuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach brother! Also, gr8 job on your last video "Kamala Harris Busted" it was very informative!  👍👍👍👍  #ADOS101.COM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spoiledxrottxn I'm going to start a Twitter hoe-war with you. THOT my sweet sweet ass. ... #🍆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGrahamCTV The clouds fell from the sky this morning. https://t.co/iWh9fRtqMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Zenkov is an inspiration for educators and advocate for all children! One of many great takeaways at the Clinic… https://t.co/F1CDUgCrF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xavierdaniel999 @Passeng05817024 that's by Annie? doesn't look like her work usually does... new maybe? (my little… https://t.co/b6GwKICfAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[People at work keep interrupting me while I’m listening to Mastodon like they don’t know what a concept album is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenPage you had some really brilliant scenes in @UmbrellaAcad. Thank you for bringing the immense range and dept… https://t.co/nq5blXOIHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sandwich generation is that simultaneously caring for their children and elderly family members. Here is a look… https://t.co/qeOnCMMTZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Schnucks - @schnuckmarkets in Bettendorf, IA https://t.co/xx1hNuBUS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny shiz, but ... Is it a meme or a big-standard joke? Only your millennial knows for meh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also very late to the game. Frozen 2 looks great! The score and visuals feel a bit massive in scope. Kinda excited for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlohOfWoe That’s a key thing—how does that get “ported” and made available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brett just spreayed me 10x with cologne after i asked for “just a spritz”.  I smell like a gigolo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josnoss @ItsJeffHudson waitaminute... you were able to type an '90s emoji w/o it turning into a yellow smileyface! wow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Happy Birthday to the one and only 🎊🔥🎁🎉🎈🎂#happybirthday #dramadupree #trailblazer #instalike #instagood… https://t.co/AEZISXfYPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyENicholson What's the first hat called? Summer is coming and my neck thinks that hat is a good idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings! ...just some more Tsunami Tuesday Action!😎💯💪🏻🏋🏼‍♂️ https://t.co/acLPkmP773]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asstheticpeach @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse She's not kidding.  She's as serious as a Nancy Pelosi heart attack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I comment to all the "talking heads" on Twitter .... you know? The only one who responds to my POSTS is President T… https://t.co/xgtfPckFak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horte_rdz @Mildredojeda @AndredeUle @jaliluly @carolinaleo66 @Sollalli @irene46mx @chrisandhielly @marantehernande… https://t.co/DTuTL1eWIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonrmcintyre @RapSheet Then why did he play only just over 1/2 of his snaps in coverage. Has become more of a run defender]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Basketball Without Borders Global Camp has kicked off in Charlotte. We broke down the rosters and previewed the… https://t.co/AtMDKAf9rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 30,000 Islands by @trestlebrewing at @hccbycarmens — https://t.co/Br6KByck5k]]></document></documents></author>