<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bluebird Space Center in Mound, MN https://t.co/ySJdDiE5Mk https://t.co/2xvXAtvfYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corrcomm @GayPatriot @TheO2 @JCinQC Unfortunately for you, Imma guess she's nailed it.☝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Not Enough Hours In The Night by Doug Supernaw https://t.co/yGWi0pOYr9 #dougsupernaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2020 election is far away but if this is any indication, @KamalaHarris is using the same "all style, no substan… https://t.co/uvadFROfJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganmac20_ with the sweet fade away towards the end of the third. After 3️⃣@DuncanvilleBB leads @HebronHawksBB 69… https://t.co/UdfaQPnj0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmmmffaaaoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo "Splat"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job Eric, it was a pleasure to work with you and @CarleyMcCord @SethLewisInc and @rdoyle79 and the rest of th… https://t.co/zQ2ieH6FaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebarstool @NewAmsterdam One of those couples everyone else is envious of...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading Strategies, Blended Learning, Fostering Student Agency and more! Great to start off a Saturday morning with… https://t.co/KvuT1ItX0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier I agree, your product definitely speaks for itself.  Every single day.  🙄😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got hella clothes they just not going to class clothes. Y’all get what I’m saying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity She would be surprised how many lists she is on ! None good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who watches airplane takeoffs and landings on YouTube super late at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should of gotten my ex girl knocked up man at least I would have this kid yo remember her by. She keeps trying to… https://t.co/qlInbouabm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregRickford Stop your whining, you have no pipeline to build and you won't so this is all hot air with no basis in fact!! #onpoli #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wtocjamie @fly_SAV It seems the weather is one of the best conversation starters going right now with our local #moodywinter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s true. Also a popular answer, “Oh my (uncle, cousin, distant relative I’ve met once) is a pastor. https://t.co/aGZZ3XqrQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is also an issue where “dance” risks making me feel like I have to perform and won’t be good enough, etc, but… https://t.co/4BTLZdYnzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The only thing that matters is what’s in front of you, and what’s in front of you is today.” - Major Warner]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ParkRDU Economy 4 - @rduairport in RDU Airport, NC https://t.co/xLrplAtDWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seen a tweet that the United States can't jeopardize the relationship for the murder of Jamal Khashoggi.  The dea… https://t.co/sbsjnR52Dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday girl. #piston #juicebox #happybdaygeorgie @ The Piston https://t.co/4uytNG065c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia Hanging out in a lodge with 20 friends in hood river, OR https://t.co/rzUZtTol9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWStream Y’all forgetting that blondes have more fun? https://t.co/SV8BqCncRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Abortion Pill  | Planned Parenthood Video https://t.co/wHZwNJhCee via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubinafillion @Martina @AOC @SenWarren @SenSanders Yes, factually (sorry to have to use that word @GOP because I k… https://t.co/dmmQlR6qd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jerry Gist, Mayor if Jackson, highlights City Council meeting - story at https://t.co/D83zgZLjgW https://t.co/0SyjniHaJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuzzeePundit @bluevirginia @HalaAyala @VAratifyERA @ERACoalition What rights do men have that women don't? Equal o… https://t.co/CpFpghek5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeshua_porvida @unashamedojesus ““Moreover, when you fast, do not be like the hypocrites, with a sad countenance.… https://t.co/S0CHjqLw5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had this on a flight to Paris on United. A very good beer. - Drinking a Hop Peak IPA by @BreckBrew @ Boeing B767-30… https://t.co/kR5zEvOPJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 men graduating this coming Tuesday. Join us 7pm in person or online strongtower_ @ Strong Tower Ministries https://t.co/0TxTqemX8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ. I often feel as though I'm the only one who's on my level.  "No one I think is in my tree, I mean it must be high or low."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KD_LeBrons_Dad @WTA_Ballers @LakersReporter I agree. Don’t get me wrong, it does seem like he takes some plays off… https://t.co/bGoZYj2TEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This account supports Calvin over Thomas on the eschatological end of non-intellectual created beings 😤😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want something that affordable and has a sports look to it ?? Look no further than this BADASS lookin Nissan !!… https://t.co/zjuJsxdOcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than A Week #Sxsw #sxsw2019 #austintexas @hdiaz1989 mymixtapezapp #showtime #perform #concert #onstage #rap… https://t.co/bdvWMHqgle]]></document><document><![CDATA[is not the fact if she died or not when you made the post but the fact you put a grim reaper next to her picture is… https://t.co/frzi0mcrAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIRLS BK: Anadarko up 41-38 with 5:30 left. Taylen Collins back in for Muldrow. #okpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuam2007 Turn on #WWEFastlane and you’ll see me. It’s kind of like being together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrozner There really wasn't much to see. Booths that failed to explain their products. Giveaways and gimmicks galore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great game between two really good teams in the SoCon championship right now.  I saw both teams play UTC earlier… https://t.co/BXpjOPsP0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaxterDingo What about AC or MFF?  If you’re going and you have any left over I’ll gladly buy one from you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitCza @TheMobyKeech @BonniedaWestie @XPets1 @paddyscousedog 🍻🍻🍻🍻🍻Here pals! #XPSHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPSBrad @TheChadColby I have heard the aerial spray guys call it an accidental landing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgreene do you pronounce it "ex" or "kiss" or "chi" ? do you think it's some kind of humorous imagery, "tiny dimen… https://t.co/ZQBRUEa5Tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBaronTurbo Don’t you dare slander the good name of Van with the R Classe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day someone asked what if the person I am with turned “Fat” I responded. They wouldn’t because we’d workout...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohMar2010__New @ells_stevens20 @FryToastFrill @jrdancerr @beyondlife7 @Treyarch THATS THE PASSION I WISH THE CALL… https://t.co/y4OyLhtWH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days you just need a hug from a hungry grizzly bear. #TuesdayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a #tbt to one of the shots I took while in New Orleans last week. Have you been on any exciting trips lately… https://t.co/oWbJaD35CB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of the Lady Bulldog Soccer family. 3.55 team GPA for trimester 1, all while being in-season. True defini… https://t.co/YwQsKsKAEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wowwww looked like a whore all day at work and I was hella talking to customers... ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hill Country Barbecue Market https://t.co/ybDGbhwP2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheodoreBNolan @NewYorker @JaneMayerNYer Because Fox is not just a right wing media outlet (which would be perfect… https://t.co/KcCMEygLVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to think how different generations are; e.i. mostly none of my friends/peers are married. This includes peopl… https://t.co/rtexENGx7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twisted_twins @littlemissrisk That would be amazing! I hope David Cronenberg shows up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo: Keeping up with Mullen sports, I was in Eagle last week, in Pueblo on Tuesday and will be in Montrose on Friday… https://t.co/JPARfD5Yyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeresaS91 @unpopularr @SweetToothTosha @zandiethegreat I remember this video so well 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dantefowler Your benching was a blessing in disguise. Brought you to the @RamsNFL were you made a huge impact!!! #LARams]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I saw when the Lamb opened one of the seals, and I heard, as it were the noise of thunder, one … https://t.co/F4sEClQUqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are so dumb when they drive in mall parking lots like my god🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RampCapitalLLC You had me worried for a minute there Ramp. https://t.co/za38FDEeZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all hear one thing and start hating look at what he’s saying from his perspective said real shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend 3 is done and we’re halfway through this incredible/amazing/fulfilling journey with @NLC_LA. #NLCfamily https://t.co/YGtOot1a7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNCFB @dkmetcalf14 @Brown1arthur @obj @God_Son80 What’s in the water at Ole Miss ? These Cats are ripped !]]></document><document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character.  - Tesio… https://t.co/UCHqgeMABS]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWAC MEN CAGE CHAMPIONS PRAIRIE VIEW A&amp;M UNIVERSITY  CELEBRATING ON "HILL." https://t.co/ktruq7CwCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[four images from an installation of work by a group of ten Brazilian artists in the installation, 'Recipes for A B_… https://t.co/ezJsFpPRCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HectorAstudillo @JaimeRdzNL Gobernador @HectorAstudillo  enviele unos tacos de camarón bañados en oro puro; y vera… https://t.co/ozHjEz5Mw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam How u gonna shit on that mans name when he can't defend himself he is dead and was aquited of all… https://t.co/Bi7HI9dsEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los amigos se cuentan con los dedos de una mano y aun así te sobran dedos. Los amo perros 😘  Ya mas de 8 años y con… https://t.co/4GfT0SvuXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: County Officials Open Up New &amp;#8216;Gun Sanctuaries&amp;#8217; in Opposition to Anti-Gun Law… https://t.co/kHqx6Os3sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigdamnband @WashboardBreezy Terrible. Just know that your fan base has your/Breezy/Max’s  back, always.  As we di… https://t.co/IJbJYUut9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@borolefty Oh sorry, didn’t realise you were doing that patronizing and exquisitely off-putting thing whereby you “… https://t.co/pn5ZQNJ5tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Maybe their parents ask themselves how come they let their children get into this crazy debt. Presuma… https://t.co/KfmjcQvSW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very informative population based study in elderly pts with DLBCL. Age is usually just s number. #lymphoma #lymsm… https://t.co/46wErpHNM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Florida massage parlor owner has been selling Chinese execs access to Trump at Mar-a-Lago https://t.co/qZE8SU0LTi via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real funny thing here is that Sonics traded Alton Lister to GS for a first round pick that wound up being used… https://t.co/B5zM6JGmyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Be In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/l9CDyP5Cex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIGOP @AP  democrats don't start controlling her I can't wait for 2020 to see what happens https://t.co/XoyJMsMQFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchyGallo Shut up Mitch! Nobody asked you you salty vertically challenged bitter young man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celestalon @candacerthomas are you making her a birthday cake or trying to kill someone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[USL League Two SF Glens announce schedule, starting with tough western confernece opponents - San Francisco Examine… https://t.co/Be7jltqPlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dayton_slifer @_reillyhenrich @hannahkbrown11 I liked how she was straight up with everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel what everyone is saying but I still think it’s fucked up nobody feel where khloe coming from lol I mean she… https://t.co/pcpberHgZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAK THE SILENCE ON MILITARY SEXUAL TRAUMA AND PTSD! #scarletlettervet #bts #AirForce #RT for awareness!… https://t.co/9x3L8nSFhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson The crane operators are awesome.  When was this fence funded?  Likely before January 2017.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_fontana_ @NGrzybowski11 @newbalance You’re making up your own definition of the word then 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BackyardTreat wildflowers creeping, funny pastel purple hue, revelation grasp  #HaikuSlew is the #NewBook only ava… https://t.co/WgkEtmTYmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another night  in the warehouse @HarborFreight #graveyardshifts https://t.co/QMpVoxwW9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a workout! Worked up to TWO big bench press all time PRs. Also big thanks to @CBum_ for spotting me, no big de… https://t.co/qZMOU0H8Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[After several weeks@off @asburyjukes hit the road this weekend starting Friday at the Stone Pony in Asbury Park, NJ… https://t.co/EV7mJElLby]]></document><document><![CDATA[At work thinking about how far the area of Forestville has come n how far we have to go but we lowkey making history lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit altså. Husk at knuselske jeres danske vintervåde grønne linoleumsfolkeskole, næste gang I afleverer ungerne.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Livingstone continued: “The predominant sense is of baffled silence, as if the magnitude of Jackson’s crimes is so… https://t.co/VPbVFjQqzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Benedict College on https://t.co/TqZTXqjM7B. The 2019 Home Depot Retool Your School Campus Improve… https://t.co/l9FnCVsUal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Libertea2012 @kellyhart57 sad! PLEASE kick upside head to release rneck! https://t.co/gXwmz1udMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guatemayabyesi @sistervpaul_ @DYNAMITEDORK @jamesrgoodman @CatholicTroy @1207go @DavidHarris707 @PrayHard972… https://t.co/oa6C6CSafm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, so I left my room to go take the trash out and I came back to the Flyers scoring two goals, so basically I… https://t.co/kND2GHU4Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Hillary lying to Congress?  Like college professors lying on their resume and or application?  Hypocritical Ms… https://t.co/QCUG2ZxQ0S]]></document></documents></author>