<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sc08960854 @DoingRight1 @BobBrinson1 @Danie1607 @kritter1963 @SahaisleyKelly @Birdle2963 @BundyGP @ouchinagirl… https://t.co/9FoAWohzAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just amusing. Funny Workplace Ecard: Retail Annoyance #23 'Do we have a bathroom?' No sir they make… https://t.co/ssTNBocdAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDLockett12 @VirginiaMason You are a unique divine expression of God💫⭐️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support Latina business! @vivecosmetics #makeuptacoproof #vive #BesoProof #dontaskmehowmuchispent https://t.co/gMRVBwMQWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate the fight for these students in Acadiana! Thank you @Nancy_Landry @LCTCSpresident @KimHunterReed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For the love of everything that’s sane what is wrong with you you’re rambling like a mad man just… https://t.co/HX1Ye1dYA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredthSalenger @JoelvsMonstruos @pattonoswalt Sounds like my husband. Some of get lucky enough to find one of rar… https://t.co/9UKc6gJgZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I cling to you; your strong right hand holds me securely.” Psalm 63:8 NLT #HeHoldsMyHand]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet has no point other than me being suddenly concerned about how pale I am and being bummed that I can’t we… https://t.co/Z0Mt7FHOUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Roots.  #marianneknowshomes #SimoneOnHomes #birthdaycelebraton #theroots #worldcafelive @ World Cafe Live https://t.co/V90gL8Lu8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like is anyone else sketched out because I’ve watched toooooo many zombie movies/shows to know that this is how it starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyJohnson @realTRUMPERLAND Listen to YOUR heart beat, now scan the mother's womb, if you HEAR a HEARTBEAT that i… https://t.co/NuzeQMLBot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SookiArt - you should paint @theofficialmads from Polar with the eye patch and cigarette. He (and I) would rea… https://t.co/iMUzp4dWqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithfieldMusic Got my tickets for @JoesPub!! Can’t wait to see you guys!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The measure, brought by Senators Ted Cruz and Tom Cotton as well as Representative Mike Gallagher, cites concerns a… https://t.co/AuU1Sm5stf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#onlychildproblems   When you want to do your favorite drawing tutorial with friends, but you're the only friend wi… https://t.co/BxXJ6Y98Ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq @AynRandPaulRyan @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Agreed! Some in the GOP Have set a rude precedent that it… https://t.co/lMZTM4QTOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaynicolez @VanessaVanjie Okay same but forever team Brooklyn Hyteeees @Bhytes1 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @mommypoppins for a wonderful morning. Wonder Park was splendiforous to watch! #wonderpark #MPmademyday https://t.co/eKUFUbPdde]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have me morphine. Or however you spell it @ WellStar Kennestone Hospital https://t.co/Q984KD5izT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaandtito I can't help myself..say..stick to your wheelhouse donna...but I can't...cause evidently I'm connected… https://t.co/HOCAqyxE1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest birthday to my fave @BobbieJoAllen2 !!! Ily bbg!! Thanks for being so goofy with me! Can’t wait to tear up… https://t.co/nZda5Fi7ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @RepSusanDavis She is smiling at others tragedy and cheering at killing babies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel would you consider donating / tickets to show for children’s pediatric charity? @specialove_org]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach was right. I think this is pretty much every Sounders fan’s idea of Heaven. #EBFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like the Republicans on today’s committee are nervous about something. Especially @Jim_Jordan #CohenCongressionalTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonastyMN 😂 we can do it together, I have extra crowns if Faux wants to borrow some]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @LukePerryIII I am sorry for your loss of a great friend I remember you and Luke as Buffy and Pike!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rp_ananth According to Moz, the average site is going to see a 16%drop in DA.  What's important is whether your co… https://t.co/3aNHn1USMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_defender @realDonaldTrump Your not very bright are you. Are you one of the mental handicapped donny boy would let have a gun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love dinner💕#familyvalentinesdinner♥️ @ Everett Golf and Country Club https://t.co/UvgH9ytDsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a few weeks ago, but boy, can my kid ski!!! Oh yeah and total props to my hubs for taking the video WHILE skii… https://t.co/HKeue5fGW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merib @theShopForward This really is sad, she enjoyed a book, that has ABSOLUTELY ZERO to do with what the… https://t.co/US0Oyuiw3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPC_HQ @divergentdeb @MaximeBernier @peoplespca 1/ April 2009: Harper appoints CEO #SNCLavalin to Obama's Climate… https://t.co/HiEigg3AN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday awhile back, my parents treated me to Thai Flavor. The curry was delicious. The waiter was also ver… https://t.co/Ff5WtUfroe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to real questions   I’m pho with lots of chili. Classic but fiery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can listen to Trey songz Ready deluxe album from start to finish it will forever be a banger]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You guys are like a sixth man to us out there.” Marques Townes addressing the fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Not Ok I'm just Going Be Sobbing and Crying  in  The Corner  Almost Graduation Time https://t.co/bfBvkMt0v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Wanted - @SecretaryAcosta - do you stand behind the DOL Labor Certs?  #releasethevisas #savesmallbusiness… https://t.co/gyH6waQLTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I am watching the opening hour of the @MichaelCohen212 hearing yesterday.  Does anyone know what the hell… https://t.co/3acTM4MRV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mate more kite  @mainedcm  / Maine Mendoza / Stacy  #DADDYSGURLTinigNiMarikit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to see Carley and Lucy for a second earlier today and it made my week so much better. Those girls mean so fuc… https://t.co/lrxCopJFjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatScott1991 I think that says -- Satan. Cursive is so hard to decipher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started my period on the school bus on the way home from a field trip in 5th grade. Everyone was going to a girl’… https://t.co/rDjumjiUqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilbert_maddi That's what I originally wanted to do, but adulthooooood. 🙈 Booo! Ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mumble’s colony is Donald Trump’s America: -Denying human’s impact on climate change -Ostracizing those who don’t c… https://t.co/CgVCg1Ba6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our lyft driver was hammered lastnight leaving the show because he too was at the show 😁 this mans pulled his whole… https://t.co/o5Crh5Ci9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking as a former Bernie Bro  Those of you who have spent the last few years bitching about HRC need to STFU and… https://t.co/n5LmFh9nmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWRiverdaleNew My heart is so heavy. God bless and comfort family, friends and fans. Rest peacefully Luke. You are already missed 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikitaKitty @KA0STHRY @LocoPresidente @ShizTradersSay @EddisonKirkland @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/69KYtmCUpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 and we have forever more to go ...   we look like such babies. Nothing much has changed 😉😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever a person is white, really shouldnt stop you.   If them niggas wanna hang themselves over a white bih, Let.… https://t.co/VdONHHUG1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pela primeira vez na vida vou ficar do lado da torcida do Galo. Quem diria. Esse ordinário comunista provou do próp… https://t.co/LbKnUJFojw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud is an understatement. @ClarkChargers @Kbj_vi when pure love shows it’s beautiful. ⭐️Special Olympics⭐️ Specia… https://t.co/zgehRZOj2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiamWonderPug It’s too bad you didn’t know her. She could’ve told you some secrets about mommy! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkpiscesmoon @pinkpiscesmoon  I sorry 😐 I don’t understand excalty what you said please thank you 😊… https://t.co/RFL8kwwgBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I woke up and instantly started sobbing for no reason. And then I couldn’t stop. Hormones are weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living with three boys has taught me I need to wake up super early to get ahold of the bathroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS:   There is a correlation between vaccinations and autism!!!  “Kids who got the MMR vaccine were seve… https://t.co/2m6ddZDTxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think I’m taking a loss God blesses me with something better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pence acts like a dummy I don’t know what his role he has but he has no idea what he’s doing and he talks like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this literally me when somebody isn’t getting something that seems soooo simple 😂💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I need to learn to start baking because you know you girls are getting old and I’m gonna have to bake for my nephe… https://t.co/dGUjJDmXfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[burst out laughing for some stress relief. Humorous Quotes #provocativemanners #humor #snicker #grin #ludicrous https://t.co/71Y3v2fwkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So she called the name of the LORD who spoke to her, "You are a God of seeing," for she said, "Truly here I have se… https://t.co/xWgqCF7wJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a job where I can get paid to snuggle Alex in bed all day because I would happily do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseyHatzell @NSFGRFP @NSF_ENG @NSF @VUEngineering Woo hoo!! Exciting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelMiner1 Went to hospital fearing I had stroke or MS, it is cancer and I thought of you and your positivity. You are my inspiration ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sephora is getting new uniforms and I... I can’t. Like to who’s funeral I’m I going to!? https://t.co/wm65IZIn9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow I always end up behind alpacas when I drive to Columbus. https://t.co/fbvW17WF75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanStapleton Coming from someone with an MFA in graphic design, yes. The style totally reminds me of a Saul Bass m… https://t.co/12s9eXBGbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Montgomery County, Maryland https://t.co/XCA7vpB5HS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama is gone and she expects me not to like her mama??? Wtw.. CHUBBS @ Madison County, Georgia https://t.co/VZfk1df5ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this cool website! It’s created by a group of scuba divers, who noticed the damaging effects of plastics… https://t.co/Dd7oNzaUQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The price of grapes when they ring up always surprises me but then I remember how much I love them and it is 100% the $8 a bag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpcowgurl @thesaucyliberal @ChrisToTheW @strom_annette @esadah @TeaSippingBarb @Momof2in1year @brandon7nettles… https://t.co/yH9pr1f3Dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardStern , why waste your airtime with a POS like @BTLSRadio?? I had to turn the station. He deserves all the s… https://t.co/tKcNo5sL4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CancilleriaVE FUERA INVASION DE HAMAS; HEZBOLA; ETARRAS; GUERRILLEROS; CUBANOS ; CHINOS Y RUSOS LADRONES; ESPIAS E… https://t.co/OQDQJo1seG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@driverminnie @GayleKing Yasss! She is an absolute queen. The looks...ohh the looks. “You lying and I KNOW you lying but imma let you lie!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3peasinmypod the day my son came home from the hospital he slept for like 7 hours. I was panicking and a nurse tol… https://t.co/0Up9GIa0so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndependentRed4 @BH_JBalan Deep condolences my ass. This is a war of greed vs the love for the animal in a fame it… https://t.co/BLryiVtCGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un gran placer poder volver a Ciudad Juárez después de tanto tiempo y reunirme con este fantástico equipo! Estoy mu… https://t.co/LzRHpqzn9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a day I will never forget. It was such a joy to experience the brendaniribe Center through the eyes of Kr… https://t.co/PAJIRSUOtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are the friend that took a video of me and the kid that I sang sexyback with tonight at @Crunchys please dm me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWoodWelder @NabholzCorp @JCPSTWEETS I was so happy to see that these were saved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akomama_tm @AAvallones @Jilliemary @BeverleyGlazer @fahadma45457790 @monicasloves @Jonshon32999975 @LivePDJacob… https://t.co/nRw1eEMeg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idothisforfran1 @fordnation @MacLeodLisa @AmyFeePC We will fight for our boys and all kids in the autism community! The deserve the world!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepChipRoy @nytimes @CBP @RandPaul  Look at the crisis senator, please don’t fight against the declared national e… https://t.co/KkpumH7Tit]]></document><document><![CDATA[*angrily drinking water bc I ran out of wine yesterday and haven’t gotten more yet*]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Hawkshroud Knight lancer made with parts from @taromodelmaker #gamesworkshop #minipainting #hobbycentral… https://t.co/85pJ9wNRG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@castaneda_ny HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! ❤️☀️❤️☀️ hope you’re enjoying Cali!!! 🌸]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats need to start now running ads confronting Trump about lying about social security and Medicare with t… https://t.co/g4LBZid8ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sephora matched my face and I got some new @fentybeauty lipgloss. Yes yes yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frajud12 @Westview_Al Also I think people are becoming gun shy of the nastiness of high level politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is everyone for the real life resident evil? Bc I’ve been ready since 99]]></document><document><![CDATA[i apologize to @SimGuruLyndsay and the other's for tagging them in a couple tweets, but jeez you guys... give the G… https://t.co/tFACrXm6DS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have been asleep like 4 hours ago....instead I’m hooked on PLL. I just wanna make it to the season finaleeeeee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolecieux @EMfys_Nest uh yeah that's how you know theres enough! it needs to permeate the whole house or just throw it away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The  movie #BeautifulBoy should be shown in every middle school. Just take out the one sex scene.  I grew up watchi… https://t.co/15zUpfXSUG]]></document></documents></author>