<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Donkere Dagen by @HeistBrewery at @heistbrewery — https://t.co/MECnqk6cqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landshark805 @johnabbottnet @FoxnewsTV @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Keep being a #trump #cockholster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder White folks have done it for centuries shall I provide you with a list 🤔...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love coming home after work and reading u guys   ....U all make me laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HansAllread @bkstrull @Evan_P_Grant @DJY2J @SusanThatsMe He got this far in the majors my man he for sure is getting it from somewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpshiloh Arecwe goingvto rehash the election again? She lost get over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernanGomezB Mmm, sí. https://t.co/lqYZWMKpQl Me parece que eres más inteligente. A lo mejor confundes la ética y/… https://t.co/AzlkbFVB9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't realize I was in the shot last night. I would have at least tried to crack a smile. https://t.co/cGPWjxOMvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackquelineTai and hi JanSam to you, too.👍🏽👋😍At the end of my "hi" tweet, with your name in caps, I had accidental… https://t.co/9HRtRtEu57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MexicanJanimuc @DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump Then why does he keep signing budget bills that he hates?  🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[How old is this guy ever expect to be the president of the United States of America when he hates 2/3 of the popula… https://t.co/1omyGzDHIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who we found! We see you @KGHOPE, @willweatherford and Robert! 👋 https://t.co/yg0e70ttwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#keepshining #dontstop #yougotthis #shining #thislittlelightofmine https://t.co/NaEVfZhlug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonJ44257163 @jilevin Yes they are centrist as well. I really like Kamala but in 🇨🇦 socialism is not a dirty wo… https://t.co/tmuTMOG1UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PreetBharara Do you think Roger Stone is trying to be throne in jail prior to his trial? #askpreet   https://t.co/KOsIxhNEBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Head Hunter IPA by @FatHeadsBeer at @winkinglizard — https://t.co/dhax8QeLRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen Offers Documents in Bid to Show Trump Lawyers Helped With False Testimony https://t.co/tZYKuoWxDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[you were the right person, but at the wrong time, been 2 years, and maybe two more will be the right time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The unveil of Sunset over Maui here at @pwatcorporate @pwatclermont by yours truly! #pwatclermont… https://t.co/hCInTA79dV]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: 2018 was California’s worst year of fire ever, federal report confirms: No state had it worse with… https://t.co/Aefgnuntpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OklahomaTli @OKCPS @Stv_Gilliland likewise! We will be in touch! I’ll connect you with the right group 👌🏾 https://t.co/MYxnaiIvy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, you’re correct; Pierre Poliviere far, far from least among them👍🏽🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews @JxhnBinder Immigration is needed to make up for the declining America birth rate.… https://t.co/EZe0klzwar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice pass by Peters to Perry, he puts it up and in plus the foul, he'll go to the line after this timeout.  11:45 l… https://t.co/W23ljVQDDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Thinker_Bell__ And why would an endless field of poppies and porterhouse steaks for everyone be such a terrible thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geraIdjr Yooo it could’ve been anybody, you’ll get a girl who deserves you soon !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rummaging through the video game collection of my childhood. GBC works on AC adapter, not on batteries. Mew still i… https://t.co/Zeb9hlZgbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamKantrow Understand, use it as a learning experience- looked better than anyone else’s!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcool40pres @chicagotribune You hate fake news?  Check in ya schools, not on the news. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770 Bo… https://t.co/hKBUzoScys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cameron_neaylon Not time yet, it’s never easy or everyone would do it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A large school district can run many campuses and try to ensure everyone gets the same quality of education because… https://t.co/b2VIQy92ZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning run with my sweetheart Ruby xx @ Vanderbilt Beach, Florida https://t.co/Sg9Ek0J0bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila @macsloth Pit Bulls.. Of course.5-year-old child bitten in face by pit bull at Portland Internation… https://t.co/Xtgkxq2G02]]></document><document><![CDATA[My granddad used to tell WWII stories about Iwo Jima. I wish I would've paid more attention. #hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[After three days of work we have something resembling Walt Disney World’s Castle with a Disneyland castle size. Hav… https://t.co/F2w1XkHzHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachaelRebecca_ @Matt_Camps Yessssss! I wining up on di grung and Dey say I loose. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need new good music so y’all go follow me on Apple Music and recommend me tingz https://t.co/CCKyrYQbh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marked a monumental day… I had to create a map of our new studio so people don’t get lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFAN660 😂😂😂🤷🏼‍♂️ so a already rich ball player just got even richer - but won’t ever see the postseason ever again… https://t.co/bILoAd8Iv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyCBrown @courtlanw @derekwhurst Ever do "Tour de Franzia"? https://t.co/kApdsOSFUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Bears couldn’t possibly sign a worse kicker than Cody Parkey right?”  Ryan Pace signing Chris Blewitt: https://t.co/LprTstSHsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephanneuhaus1 I don’t think companies do it to be jerks (I think they do it because they hire in-house GC’s who… https://t.co/334cLeefiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[May I recommend the bathroom at Rudolph’s in the sarasotamodern for your next Headshot photo shoot. @ The Sarasota… https://t.co/jZqM4uc2ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClarkDennisM Hey I found this live video stream from the $tsla forums https://t.co/MX3b6PGZq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[An absolutely incredible thread that articulates so many things I haven’t quite known how to. It’s a long thread bu… https://t.co/poImtblw0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TlrWorldWidellc @KavalonThatsMe @BenedictoLozano @Kugey @Hiqutipie @Marg1010 @twizmwhytepiece @hortkoff3 @RooferXX… https://t.co/y6wkC0RESx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Creating a conservative base  Having a picture taken with a  person likely to burn the Republican house down  Priceless]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't gotta worry about who wants me if I want you and that's a fact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triple checked @JohnCornyn's feed as well as the context of this tweet (there is none) to see if the Senator has an… https://t.co/iXSv0lqL7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos están cordialmente invitados, prevenidos para que se enteren de cuando se darán los accesos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got it in early...off to church @ St. Mary's County, Maryland https://t.co/DoxPaC638U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guardian_Elite @DavidJHarrisJr @w_terrence @lyft @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @POTUS @VP @Scavino45 @SebGorka… https://t.co/aGaLah5lom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomjyang @CallieField @jgebing @blueprintTMO @Aejaz_H All credit to dj Brent for the deep cuts, sick drops and thumping bears ...fueled me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siguen reprimiendo, matando al país y a los venezolanos, cómo cabe tanta maldad en esos cuerpos? Ya basta!!!! Son 2… https://t.co/NTVU5JvMRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i could not talk to someone for weeks and weeks and then all of a sudden i’m the bad guy because i’m minding my own business 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivalajayxoxo I’m dead ass. Like seeing ppl put in they work. I don’t mind supporting. Just make it easily accessible. N I’ll buy it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in #Vegas do you run into one of your closest friends from back home. Great seeing you dude! It’s been way too… https://t.co/goLesCYGx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estellatse: Artist, dreamer, and multimedia poet - but her best quality is that she is pushing for a more thoughtf… https://t.co/gVJjcy9GBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at MHS grad @TrevorHudgins12 with the pass.  He’s a dude. #RollTribe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weston_lee2 Im a Redsox fan so that aint hurt too much lol i still pulled for em tho, that delay fucked it all up 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonMiketa the coward's way.... but the only way to truly win.... i respect this]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going straight to the heavy bag as soon as my shift is over.  I need to let off some steam. I feel like I’m go… https://t.co/c3vpV0Onml]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is art, she made me feel something, feels like it was all in my head. I should delete the messages. ☹]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #MissMartian I wanted her to look very modern while still feeling like the alien martian superhero she is! . .… https://t.co/oXZwxew5bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyslayer Yeah Schmeling got a bad rap for what was going on in his country at the time. He rebounded well, was a… https://t.co/RdlH7CztLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re gonna out grow people that hold you back. You’re moving forward while they stuck in their comfort zones]]></document><document><![CDATA[me at @SlanderOfficial:  “IT FEELS LIKE IM FALLING FOR THE FIRST TIME!!!!!” https://t.co/2s0KZqKo11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where they found his tooth!!!! One of the strangest stories of the week, is also our last of the week. Coming up next. HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseybigjim @HillReporter Agreed. It’s all rhetoric and speculation right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GodMorning  #logic #emotions #control @ Oakland, California https://t.co/tQbNmKrgeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bizarre_ry @GameOfThrones @ceekaybee24 @justdenni I’m ready for the heartbreak 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I forgot to say, shout-out to the amazing @smokevyday. We're 35 deep. Happy birthday to everyone. Roll with us or get rolled over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it to Sacramento. Back on the road for Hollywood tomorrow. @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/9cvrX8Yhy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bruno1980Mike @ArthurSchwartz @tedlieu @brhodes @McFaul @IlhanMN I mean omitting information on a sf-86 is a felon… https://t.co/DyrPFCplbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[once MPJ is healthy next year, the Nuggets will be a big threat, and he’s winning ROTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do u ever have a dream that makes u sad &amp; then ur just sad for the whole day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[12. Bilberry Pie. With a little cream. Though I am really missing a proper Roast Dinner with all the trimmings...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosramirezl3 @VIKINGOVZLA Ya dijo que todas las opciones estan sobre la mesa, para mi esta claro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol what do u get for winning? Answer: NOTHING! The main reason this show sucks now. And judges r afraid… https://t.co/lVl47g5c1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Funny ,I am a veteran who wants to commit suicide in a large part due to you being in the Oval Office]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for Britain.  Im proud that they recognize trans kids as human beings worthy of respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mighty1090 @RJBBQ35 @BenAndWoods On the hill today!!! Can’t wait!!! https://t.co/aNrnl9Ok1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumor has it that @mascdonna got us these shirts for #ValentinesDay2019! I truly have the most amazing man on the p… https://t.co/T5WNeGC6eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve never tried to get to the gas station on zero miles to empty while waiting on the crawling train are you… https://t.co/DCPaslpKSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam If I run for POTUS someday, the platform will be competent, ethical governance and permanent Daylight Savings Time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I ask out women I just met in the produce section at the grocery store. https://t.co/cFdp8KYDXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home and dan’s wearing a wife beater with his chest hair pokin out and he’s working on the car loooollll gonna get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spaceRESlux @davehuntsman @ispace_inc I applaud their pioneering efforts. However they need another space artist.… https://t.co/g2CJlG3Dqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your "outraged" over the way @SenateDems treated #WilliamBarr wait until you hear about how @SenateGOP treated #MerrickGarland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sqldbawithbeard Goes for paid people too. Well, the last part anyhow :).]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CHANGED A COMPUTER BATTERY INVOLVING 16 SCREWS AND SOME WIRES AND I'M THE MAN. https://t.co/1lrWHWOPiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raiderneil1 They traded up for this guy AND he acted like a typical rookie. He's going to get a prove it year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FamOly_AbOveAll Most def...I’m glad she stuck with her stance, he admitted he was wrong, she admitted there are ot… https://t.co/5OhsuSHN3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a message saying.. “Adam give meet n greets away to @SabrinaAnnLynn next week”   Soooo you ready ? https://t.co/xvgIAza67m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's!! Glad you agree to do crazy fun things with me @ Pomona, California https://t.co/XOyCbzBeoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damondominique Oh you meant towns. Cerbere, right on the border of Spain was cool and mysterious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HR8 just passed the U.S. House! Proud to join @lucymcbath and so many others in voting for the first major gun-vio… https://t.co/ykcy1riOxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just landed. No word from @MichaelPlaxton. Is he rewriting his book already??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FangirlHave Oh, I forgot you invented listening to emo, short round. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluelinedana Probably get a better deal if you brought a snow shovel 🤣]]></document></documents></author>