<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@gabyzinhaa2015 @pucca11112005 Tem fake esquerda CHUPANDO intervencao gringa com jaguncos brasileiros tambem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GUjackets Tough loss but the team looked good. Some outstanding points for the Yellowjackets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittlePubGig @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Unfortunately, there is such a thing as BOTs injected into the political… https://t.co/T27kHodN2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SENTAL_Hamburg Hi,how are you ? i sell fiber optic patch cord,drop cable,splice enclosure ,welcome u send us inquiry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenverWestword @realDonaldTrump Don’t wonder what they’re thinking, read it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinCrespo1 @WhovianLeap Okay... Never got into those kind of books.  😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampagneKirby 😂😂 all week dude! Just stay home. Don't go out for nothing !]]></document><document><![CDATA[See... THIS IS THE KIND OF AUDIENCE YA'LL SHOULD HAVE HAD LAST NIGHT!!!!   Never go to Lafayette EVER. AGAIN. #SmackDown @WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can't go on pretending day-by-day That someone, somewhere soon make a change We're all a part of God's great big… https://t.co/dJdtnixnRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algorithms and art with the amazing Cornell Tech K12 team @diane_levitt @kelpowers5 @designNPS @ada_ibe https://t.co/g4K7wtrspf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of @EthanDolan and @GraysonDolan doing ice skating tricks.   https://t.co/Jv98CkFEkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barnini Only the beginning! Amerucans would rather watch our UNITED STATES on clean-up duty,then to watch dirty mo… https://t.co/0hkGzIItEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VE6AEQ @Ez4u2say_Janis @dlintaman @VestsCanada Yep I’ve been having the same thoughts. The whole thing feels creepy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Go to N. Korea and run your mouth about it bozo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to 7 Trails Restaurant in Damascus for feeding the Varsity Boys and Girls Basketball Team before heading to… https://t.co/Jh1vxNeCHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX @Team_Penske @RustyWallace @keselowski @KurtBusch Brad all the way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Advil Even four towels could do, if you have a washing machine onsite.  Reusing bath towels is fine, of course, as… https://t.co/GjlQoNP2t7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Does an Oath mean jack💩 to donald trump?  Ah, no. That's a rhetorical question; he's already admitted… https://t.co/3U2RlqTiIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentuckyDiane @jeffc0618 I am praying tonight for a lot if needs. I will add Jackson! 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maibortpetit @colominaM @jguaido Ah OK. Entonces que ayuden a parar a sus aliados de Manos off Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happens to me but usually when I’ve been flying for about 10 hours lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crash course life lesson I gave my little heroes:  you DO NOT ask or whine. It is given because you are good.   Hon… https://t.co/3v5mEyKKys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in such a dark place that you wish you had a toxic person back has to be the worst feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud to work with this amazing @Presidio team! Always moving forward in what’s best for their customer’s busine… https://t.co/56GTb8b9wK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DearSong #DearEverythingGoes You were released to the world the day before my son was hospitalized for the first t… https://t.co/61Wem9usnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aretha Franklin, the Queen of Soul, has died - CNN https://t.co/1oDBpQjfUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some mirth. 10 Hilarious Ellen Quotes: https://t.co/yAzTLRqZ00... via @Guyism.com.com #comedy #chuckle… https://t.co/I1zw1Dz5o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s legit times like this where I start missing the one person who didn’t even give a fuck abt me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikSperling @isaiah_kb Funny isn't the right word. Interesting, maybe. I had several great conversations on here,… https://t.co/06tiwGnsls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BastardProphet Set my daughter's math teacher decides to have a discussion with the whole class about this b******… https://t.co/mxdqZ2sQSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravusWhite @ZakKondratenko Ca t wait to go help pick one out with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diaper777 @GhostOfTick @SeniorBoobies @HavokHawk @LeonWhi63670221 @WillTrumpYou @Atheist_Dragon @truckrogers1… https://t.co/7NYt1uttDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleCuthbert @Queenofthe80s @NickBeggs  has always had a unique sound.. master of the bass and Chapman stick, He… https://t.co/wBHteSiOwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When something your man said two weeks ago doesn’t add up 😂 https://t.co/A0eQoK7eCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition Bigger question: who told him this? No way he has access to cohens inner world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Hideaway #TX  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/ylP3Fu9lpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Custom DePauw charm bracelet. ❤️ . . . . .  . . .  FOLLOW @seizethenight #seizethenightdesigns #handmade #boutique… https://t.co/O7BpJrgFD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Savvvvvvyyyy @rileypaterniti no i have it!! last time he was in my car i had the speaker 😂😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live now ktla5news #malibu @ Malibu, California https://t.co/ezUE0K7DhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Senquiz_Jr @yoshimon_7 @JakeShow0 @JacobLaureano https://t.co/vRYHlEUlWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[ON OUR WAY TO NEW YORK THE DIXIE DOLLS DRILL TEAM OF MIDLAND TEXAS OF LEE HIGH @TODAYshow CAN'T WAIT. https://t.co/VXaHXLlJqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night I’ll never forget! Having a table with Lebron James and marshmello 🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the  #bookchallenge continues📚❤️ For 7 days post the cover of a professional or Children's/YA book that you lov… https://t.co/NnEWozz4PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So traderjoes wouldn’t having the whole sandwich exactly double the amounts? Just sayin’ #badmath #goodsandwich… https://t.co/t6jk94BI8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Spoken by someone who surely knows how to not use resources when needed!   And also had many lucrative dealings with Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at that stage of my life where i keep myself out of arguments even if you tell me 1+1=5 you’re absolutely correct, enjoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose I could avoid the mud and take to the road.  Nah! That's no fun.    #weekendbegins #trailrunning… https://t.co/59Hv0NaEjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOTICE: this is NOT the apt she CLAIMS as her address in the Brooklyn  14th district....where the neighbors have NE… https://t.co/uCpJ204Qtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 5:44  “But I say to you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and p… https://t.co/jtJlifzhKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernerSays @publiclandlvr Love driving roads through the open range parts of #Montana! You never know what bea… https://t.co/leSSIBnHUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I believe she's trying to lead us into a related story. Kushner going back to the Middle East to meet with MBS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only go into urban outfitters for their home section so I can pick things out for my imaginary apartment]]></document><document><![CDATA[$20.00 7 inch #jewelry #wolfeboro #homemadejewelry  #beaded bracelet #black bracelet #boho bracelet… https://t.co/83sdVm6T2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@William_R_Hart @kicranston @respecteconomy EXCELLENT idea!  Twitter or Facebook LIVE.  And you already know the numbers it would draw 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teacher tomorrow- "So whats your excuse for being tired today?" Me- "I decided to start listening to the entiret… https://t.co/Ts7bBd9YEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahjwise @aneripattani 🙌 Yes!! Similarly this was the first article I ever read about the effect of mindfulness… https://t.co/rWlrVG4Gff]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all these years, I have found a plausible reason for why Leela decided to stay with Andred. To her eyes he pr… https://t.co/rSLHmeTvMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claybwells10 @GAFolIowers Just a dillusional cracker living in his privilege. As usual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault Can’t find my car in the parking lot as it gets darker and nefarious people start coming out of the shadows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polluxe @LondonMarathon @nycmarathon I saw that.  Are they bragging or what's the deal!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz see I semi disagree bc everyone knows to lock their car doors, use an alarm, park in well lit areas...  But… https://t.co/PBRqHho2mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When clients get creative to not get tangled in giant puppy love 😍😍😍 @ Adobe Pet Hospital https://t.co/hoS6VRKpup]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk if I wanna go on vacation or if I want to put my money towards a festival 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered that I have a bunch of grading to do. But will probably wait until tomorrow. Maybe I’ll finish that… https://t.co/LxcBF5KsN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @MemoLopezHD putting on a great start to DH appreciation week! @rebekahbunn5 @DHRM_mjackson @TammyThd413… https://t.co/eCtPNJFHDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittAnderson09 @keweidman8 @JeffreeStar Listen to your Aunt, because you'll roll your eyes at me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i haven't gotten my @PlaylistLive merch package yet and i have a premium pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris @DonaldJTrumpJr Even her own father has walked away from her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao! Andy fell asleep on the couch while we were watching a movie. But he pissed me off earlier so I didn’t wake… https://t.co/QPrEAz8bpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first world problem is the decent breakfast spot I go to has awful coffee. Which means that in order to get my c… https://t.co/WngMfi6aT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse THE ART OF THE DEAL, if you're not getting what you want ... walk away. Even Nancy Pelosi did it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been 4 years and I still can't get over how much I love @tameimpala's Currents. Every time I hear it feels like the first time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmfaoooooo i’ll block u for the rest of my life those supposed to stay exactly where tf they at bai]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrueStory #PedicabStories  Tonight, I came across a couple who said they got "rejected" by an #uber #driver becaus… https://t.co/uyYub8gaWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entrenando 💪   W/@iTonio____ (at @24HourFitness in Chula Vista, CA) https://t.co/0ntsSgIbRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyBlueDevil7 @keyofD_ That's that good NC livin.👍🏽. My family is from there. Split between Duke and NC fans - th… https://t.co/Qegp4iHpKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenDuckworth Nice that we now have a female rainbow connection in Congress from all sorts of backgrounds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyVNV @BubbaJoeJimBob1 @mvj737 @busbee_deborah @ChuckKeller14 @ashau68 @cspippin @Hell_HasCome @deepdvr1234… https://t.co/BiqnDRfVft]]></document><document><![CDATA[just woke up!!!!   one of the best parts of grade 12, is to sleep for an hour and re-charge yourself, then wake up… https://t.co/WP48Mp7YX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hkh11d @FrankLe19255990 @3TimRice @AOC Oh, I thought you meant actual facts and figures on how much her "Green New… https://t.co/OZC0SgDcBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fan favorites (lol) #Edina and #Moorhead #TheTourney19 #tourneyson45TV https://t.co/OVzk09JRkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#scarletthalo: So need a Vacation! 😪 📷: jchchechenchenchen @ SOUVLAKI GR https://t.co/Ra8jZvNLHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying an evening with Maria and Johnny watching The Loria Brothers.  Like old times. @ Spill https://t.co/bolQ3VVFKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @theColor13 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2… https://t.co/1UejtfuCjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalCerealDay has me all nostalgic for Saturday AM cartoons w/a big bowl of #LuckyCharms. Which cereal was you… https://t.co/oIhyssjexL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zappa Was thinking of Frank today and wondering how he would do with Donald Trump as President. So many times I ha… https://t.co/GZXESg2Bms]]></document><document><![CDATA[delivered to this guy and all i said was hi are you doing and he immediately asked “wow are you from england?” like… https://t.co/J0xkpXEsBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nearcorn @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump No can do since they are the real liars, deceivers, crooks, and Russia lovers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleEWrites @JennyPerinovic That’s awesome! We have a very active @SCBWIOK group with many things happening ri… https://t.co/J6NOx0sJqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonypuricelli so my problem is that when i wear headphones all day i get a bad headache?? this is true for any kin… https://t.co/K9x5TRx88E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#youngprofessionals talking about how their @awwa section promotes student #membership at #awwaYPtraining.… https://t.co/C7EQ8KILLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arlene, Well said~because if we were all the same...we would be boring... 💞😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presidents’s Day sunset on point 👌🏼 #NoFilter #Sunsets https://t.co/zOYLSoncpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m the US may also adopt this practice. We’re currently in Year 3 of the Trump era #Culture #Japan #Heisei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun at the @spurs game. 💕🏀 Blessed to have amazing friends to share these moments with. Sometimes when… https://t.co/4KlW1E4Lsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erndawg56 @PlayChoices Lots of people are saying that. I agree. Something really bad needs to happen to the Duke. Poison perhaps?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream is to travel the world to help kids but I barely have enough gas money to leave R.I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Supt_comalisd Yes...alas, middle school and yet, all I see is this... https://t.co/9Zc0YIN3Zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoolOfGod Thanks but Tim says he “prefers to take the sandwich factory outdoors.” Meaning the grill...😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can go and represent central Minnesota? @dianafenton1 @jmenth22 @sjmathiason @31madi @TravisColgrove @nagorski1… https://t.co/yG2GDlvYAW]]></document></documents></author>