<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The PERFECT stripper song  Dope - Die Mother Fucker Die https://t.co/WxffiEuuE6 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay in 1936 the world’s first superhero #ThePhantom, a cartoon strip by artist #LeeFalk, made his first appe… https://t.co/5VX4O23Y9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[can I get like a signal? Even a smoke signal would at least something 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[scouting some new work/eat places in the city... this place has a decent menu and good coffee and other drinks and… https://t.co/gDoaXxJWF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r_saunders15 @BaseballBros Lol what? He literally called time when the pitcher started his wind-up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting morning with @MorningsMaria discussing Trade, Automation and the Economy @ROKAutomation CEO Blake Moret https://t.co/HCGxranlAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Estacionamiento El Nuevo Mundo in Monterrey, Nuevo León https://t.co/YtmGL4hLp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingAlfreddd @bet365bingo Jackson is a more original character, who sang original music live on set.  Rami lip syn… https://t.co/9duAf6FHBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just make the most out of it. Turn a bad night into a good one. Make some mistakes while we're young]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmGolferBlog @Maxfli_Golf Snapped the head off wedge on approach to #1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see the sun for a bit today. Gives that glimmer of hope Spring is coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlevolf @desbfit And being wrong is something you’re apparently good at and ok with.   Which is fine, being cor… https://t.co/rFAfe6o1yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - Morning Briefing:    Trade deficit hits $891.3 billion;      Facebook promises a new focus on us… https://t.co/Sb57T7dSCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boounds I played league play then scrimmed then watched VODs what else u want me to do once my team gets off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman It’s more about staying active than just going to the gym and your body needs rest if you’re feelin… https://t.co/rctADRE4Z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBled2 congratulations on your new contract and your big game last night! Happy for you and glad that you are a pa… https://t.co/cYfqqsYbqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runwithskizzers @Dina_at_Disney @dsantat I mean, Dina you would be a perfect Janet 👍🏽👍🏽 https://t.co/B60YsC3AZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting closer to showtime just over 24 hours away #IamDSM https://t.co/uSInqsh39g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris And who is to pay the outstanding monies owed? Tuition fairy gonna make all that money disappear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate going into stores and knowing more about the collections more than the sales associates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotel138 @HPOUTX Also Black Tar Heroin was found in lead officer Goines car at tge raid sight and NO ARREST have b… https://t.co/wxu0eA2rEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, You’re my best source of help. I can trust You with every difficulty that comes my way. I don’t need to wonde… https://t.co/XbpEh0XFKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavonWade1 Trivia: which one averaged 13 point per game last year and has a career high of 34?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get asked by #customers all the time, #everyday if I speak #español and sometimes I'll get a #rude reaction when… https://t.co/bLyWQ9iwWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning folks. Headed to the swamp again. Why this time? #staytuned @KarynTurk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCAfrica I did know you were lying and my wife asks me “why are you flipping him off?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Memes #memesdaily #progressive #dank #dankmemesdaily #dankmeme #crossovermedia #tampa #miami #orlando #capecoral… https://t.co/0xygSe9EVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMankiewicz Creative defense lawyers around the US will now check if any koalas have escaped from zoos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding work by the @NAHLHockey media team at the 2019 #TopProspects Tournament. Thank you and bravo to… https://t.co/Byik28JvAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to see @WaltDisneyWorld is already getting ready for the opening of #GalaxysEdge! https://t.co/iUc7ye4QBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Yes, because these kinds of comments are exactly what elevates the debate and makes you appear clear… https://t.co/jCcXGhyPxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to many people upset that Marvel won’t make an R movie. Look, if a film’s value lies with extra f-bombs and an… https://t.co/EEVISMskNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[JFK looks ready to handle some snow. @ JFK International Terminal 4 https://t.co/kSfUt0xw6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless Tame Impala pulls something out of left field, album on the year. https://t.co/mmtXZAwU3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattlsteve @DarrenDreger Not in a million years is Foudy part of it. Expect him to be on ice w/#CBJ⁠ ⁠ center rota… https://t.co/RVY1Ahcuzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google could do so much better. I'm still hoping they will turn it around for 2019. I turned in my pixel 2 XL yeste… https://t.co/9AcdW2gMYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: For Democrats, the spotlight falls on Biden and Sanders: The oldest candidates in the Democratic r… https://t.co/ORF799Bsq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday #ontheshelf whittierpubliclibrary californiastatelibrary #castatelibrary… https://t.co/zHusxl1ff1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full moon 🌕 to end a long weekend. Hello workweek 😩. @ Peet's Coffee https://t.co/t0kf8tgWvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimhalliburton @bryanbehar @Indyria57Maria Every week?! It feels like every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant help but to cry on each nominated award percipients speech. Got to love the passion]]></document><document><![CDATA[ORGULLOSO de mi gente que a pesar del hambre y las necesidades demuestra su calidad humana. Nuevamente GRACIAS “COL… https://t.co/pPLKt7T3aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so damn hyped for this movie 😤 #DetectivePikachu https://t.co/L948Pj9FIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh oh...the movers will be here in less than 2 hours to start packing. Looks like I have work to do. @ Belleville,… https://t.co/LPmpf9Y3d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second verse same as the first. Kinger with a 1-2-3 inning. 3-0 MID2 #VandyBoys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltccc_levon @Lrihendry @Liz_Wheeler She would probably be a half-decent stripper ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all #rappers that need free #beats, https://t.co/oDUMHCQiQo — you’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EllimanSummit was one for the books. Elliman agents across the country had the opportunity to experience the revea… https://t.co/xuKpuW2rAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to wake up so early tomorrow. I'm so tired, I'm gonna just go straight to bed  Me two hours ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give yourself some extra time this morning! If you parked outside your car is going to be coated in a layer of ice.… https://t.co/TyqaCMS42w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakaktaSouth The numbers don’t mean shit to me, I already know for a fact I’m not gonna die young. The important t… https://t.co/yPUVEiqux1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSmith4680 @andrew52220582 Simple truth the demoncrat's need a devided AMERICA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill If you can’t get it done IN the @whitehouse, might as well get OUT of the White House. Fool me 10,000 time… https://t.co/cnntJdnpFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoke 'em if you've got 'em 💨🔥 . Maiden voyage of the new @sightmark Core Shot A-Spec LQD. Just got this little guy… https://t.co/v32biF8v7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeWerkinThough #HighFreQuincy @ Tree4ort Live Comedy https://t.co/HV51u4fesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @HelpforBear The world is so not ready for that kind of lifestyle !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off from a long day of work! (@ ARTIC Anaheim Regional Transportation Intermodal Center in Anaheim, CA) https://t.co/d2olAtTByr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenSinek This is an incredible piece of work. I love it every time I see it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Friends,,,    It takes four positive experiences to overcome a negative one. Use your energy to be as positive… https://t.co/vu6g1Joibj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy 😭 my two favorite places. I’m itching for some adventure. https://t.co/Mh14hNlXXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinnetBlue Captain Shakespeare and Travis Bickle are the same person, too! 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Registered Nurse- Lake Tahoe Surgery Center - https://t.co/vEgHMO4K3O #hospitaljobs #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump @mmpadellan GTFO of our country, you don’t belong here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckShots @P_Funk36 I don’t see Greek getting any DPOY love from the media tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day - 93 Pics #laughter #snicker #smirk #funny https://t.co/knYeRftLei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradenSaich41  wanna do karate in the garage I’m not that far away homie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and Happy Sunday! Please take a look at my column this morning appearing in Prayables! Subscribe, it’s… https://t.co/04aIPBQ4TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my #GalaxyS9Plus The new 1UI update Is so awesome, my #alwaysondisplay looks super familiar.  You might see date… https://t.co/UsEh3sfgpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews You know it's legit because it's sponsored by Dinty Moore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama The #parklandtempleoftime built by #DavidBest and #TempleCrew and the community, survivors and familie… https://t.co/zQ83rlI0YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #VoteNani will make the biggest impact on Opening Weekend. #MLSisBack https://t.co/EZvqhXgBCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garrison_wrn Dawg what get weak is there subtle hints like no i didn’t catch that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Will you apply the same standard to the @realDonaldTrump? https://t.co/oNZsEfOpOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@destinyisbright before you go to sleep.... would you like another cookie cake? https://t.co/KJA75FOiG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Time to recant and take this false cry for attention and Twitter applause down and maybe wait for facts… https://t.co/esiJlVdMBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzz?!? @anthemgame // My name’s Erik, and I’m addicted to playing in my Colossus javelin. #shieldgang https://t.co/a28Lbigp6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Very well said! All these other morons and idiots can't see this because they are b… https://t.co/ievL93M0Fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The only time I am social is on social media or buying some one lunch.Socialism in the world fails… https://t.co/r738rbeQo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Klaus figures out how to revive the dead or at least get others to see them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieMetz6 There’s something in that name(Rachel Maddow) , can anyone figure it out?I know what her pblm is, do you?CLUE, it ain’t men!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRyder @newbeverly Gorgeous print... delightful picture! https://t.co/PVigKh8ITy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dope #relatable #epic #monetize #lit #beamaverick #youtube #doitdifferent #entrepreneur #logang4life #trending… https://t.co/HD6ZAlqcF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless Robert Horry, he was a key piece on some title teams. He’s nowhere near the player Tobias Harris is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood at my house after 7 days of rain...   @BigweatherABC11 @HohmannABC11 @BrittanyABC11 https://t.co/OnKXuqf5sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Please Mr. President do not sign the bill the people will revolt you’re giving in to a democrat s… https://t.co/fXXRJ3kl9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sortirpoubelles @Antagoniste_net Ça serait plus simple de lancer une enquête sur le dividu qui a dit la vérité.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrlind With no Jim Ridley to do it the city needs an elegy on the Gold Rush from you. But you should quote him on it heavily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LH1_Era 🤣🤣 this is exactly the reason why I prefer to stay FAR away from public gyms. I appreciate your service to the public tho 💪🏼✊🏻😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake &amp; Steak! Porterhouse Florentine. @tambournyc  #steak #carnivore #carne #meat #beef #beefitswhatsfordinner… https://t.co/r61DUVmopX]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT NEW PRICE!! This is what MAIN LEVEL LIVING should look like!  Loaded with upgrades and quality finishes: - Br… https://t.co/cSiXWkdHjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiveRights I’ll tell you why she gets a free pass. Bc the GOP has no sack whatsoever to do anything about it. All… https://t.co/8kvOfymDRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldmanengel Because even marginal pass rushers are wanted. You can find a spot for a guy who gets 6 to 8 sacks a year. Fowler isn't great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah detective pikachu finna be a hit and the Pokémon movie franchise finna be in full swing over the next few years]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot begin to describe how fucking delicious this place was. Definitely coming here more often. Definitely get… https://t.co/UTpXIt8W0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's laugh a bit. It's weird to say, but putting this on Facebook or something. - for more amazing wedding... https://t.co/HFEobgJRhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacsmr @TrueFactsStated @BetoORourke You know that's actually false.   The El Paso fire department has estimates i… https://t.co/kAEHe2lLVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 1st  Notre Dame 6  Peebles 6  It's been a very physical contest. Both teams playing excellent D.  Katie Dettwil… https://t.co/6nFuTcdV7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the “Black Citizenship in the Age of Jim Crow” exhibit at the @NYHistory -ical Society today with my studen… https://t.co/wufoct6pXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Olympian Kelly Catlin, 23, dead in apparent suicide: https://t.co/9PJzyxLQNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who haven’t seen the progress of my front piece https://t.co/ZSbztuXaEz]]></document></documents></author>