<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Nisey72 I can barely hug people I know.  This would probably put me over the edge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voted to do.. If they take all that hate and rage they have for our President and help him can you imagine all the… https://t.co/VqSM7k3Jde]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not tired at all 😞 but I already know I’m gonna hate myself for staying up this late !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karrrebear1 @BCECC_DAYMAC Love the activity AND the looks on their faces!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert Might be worth it for a centrist temporarily jumping in, just to rid us of Schultz.  Is Chelsea Clinton 35 yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taxes are extreme. I would like to leave because I have an adult son who is nonverbal with Autism. If Infanticide i… https://t.co/9EGPmWxnIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @LindaSuhler Liberals all practice the #JussieSmolett movement]]></document><document><![CDATA[It does you a disservice if im dating you and I DONT PUSH you to be BETTER than your BEST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g3rrity *whispers* Also, professors/instructors at elite schools are not inherently better at teaching, and in fac… https://t.co/MhdHKbxOJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gator971 @pissedoffctdem @ArtMurray1 @ProudResister Amen to that! It's about time someone said it! Thank you. We l… https://t.co/v4EYE94oYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to quit skipping class once a week. buttttt sleep sounds better🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moewissa Now catching up on this weeks sode of This Is Us. Apparently a good day to clean out the tear ducts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texasstarfan @maddkat57 I'm surprised how low the price is that they're selling it for!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living that #Pink Sand #Gloss life!  #crueltyfree #unitedstates #Australia #Canada #Mexico #NewZealand… https://t.co/zBfAffeoIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #followback #instagramers #socialenvy #tweegram #photooftheday #20likes #amazing #smile #follow4follow… https://t.co/apxkX8moHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @GeeGeeAkili @realDonaldTrump MOOBS?! PERFECT name for them!!!☝️😁😆😂🤣🙌👏👏👏👁❤IT!!!😁😄😂🤣👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @eltonofficial We saw him three weeks ago in Mpls. Pure magic! And everyone should enjoy their work as much as the drummer! 🥁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MookieMaliowski @Vidette_Sports @blainelew3 There is one path to the dance and that is the MVC tournament. Not ide… https://t.co/nyLxdtCI1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon Perhaps NC needs to remove a number of legislators as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the girl who’s changed my life! I hope 2️⃣3️⃣ brings you everything you can hope for beautiful. I… https://t.co/BIwowQ3yVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @realDonaldTrump Credit for what? Humiliating the USA on a World Stage. N Korea never honored their com… https://t.co/pYHKGt7cEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TotalWireless wants to send you to the @iHeartRadio Music Awards! Enter daily for your chance to #win!… https://t.co/7qMnXKrBvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson What man would have sex with a crazy person?  Men must start protecting themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrillScottP @UncleChaps @ZeroBlog30 Cool then I probably watched navy beat him when I went to every single army-na… https://t.co/MzopakQxto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continued: February’s wild cat stripper strike at Crazy Girls, shot for thelosangelenos. 📸 #photojournalism… https://t.co/jY5rprrJH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Spring Break! Emalyn has jumped in the pool! Brrr! @ La Coste, Texas https://t.co/YaKfiYE8uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #2 of #NASPA19. Did our presentation, then learned from others. Ate amazing food and of course, saw palm trees.… https://t.co/FC3yxR5rR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaBosw16 Do you have an email address for Shirley Smith or Annette Chambers-Smith Smith? Please]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people who line up to get off the @OnTheMetra train are definitely the same people who stand up as soon as the plane lands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cannibalststegd See y’all take shit too serious lol. This used to be me and Brandon. All jokes and playing pranks… https://t.co/2wzjcXt6WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[As days go by I find myself happier and happier. With age your time becomes shorter so enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I guess not only did we lose the chance at another super bowl but also Shawn Mendes :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #TribalCamp in South Texas Is Vowing to #Resist Trump’s Wall  😃😃👍😍 https://t.co/z6V4yn6lTQ via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I was standing in line to walk out of gym class with my thumbs hooked into the belt loops on my hips. A gi… https://t.co/FfXLYT2Fxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[hold your head up high, and know God is in control he has a perfect plan for your life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at National Car Rental - @nationalpro in Windsor Locks, CT https://t.co/bU7y7SyFfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $40 Roblox Gift Card Offer  Win $40 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,  Sign Here:… https://t.co/q0ZhMMp6gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Nashville is the 13th fastest growing Real Estate Market in United States 🇺🇸  (Zillow 2019) https://t.co/1A1XCiEji3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodEditorBecks @OatlyUS Cattle and grasslands equal biodiversity equals birds and bees and other wildlife! Then t… https://t.co/FQczcetqxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer Walker Thurs Mar. 7th @ Exchange https://t.co/NbCq8dd8aA https://t.co/AvwjOFhT8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByRosenberg @GManfan64 I guess we are waiting until he kills someone. Hopefully not a child]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again, @sleepingatlast totally crushes it. From start to end. #eight #enneagram https://t.co/TKApK2ONfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Bean ** The PopDot Artist ** Please Join me on the Twitter @AlabamaBYRD &amp; Be... https://t.co/6vVPcv4KhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This fabulous show is coming to Rochester this weekend hosted by the fabulous @aggydune and @KashaDavis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceRobb_ Judgemental know all bitches have judged James Reid already, before the show have yet to start airing.  #IdolPhJudgeJamesReid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Grateful Thought: A great "Tuesday-start" to the week! :-) #TGT #todaysgratefulthought #bepositive #thinkpositive]]></document><document><![CDATA[The woman infamous for rhyming speeches at @MDCPS school board meetings is here calling for a realignment of Browar… https://t.co/bltEjDfTG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @AmbJohnBolton @Almagro_OEA2015 @realDonaldTrump @mike_pence]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the World is going to shit when a Nike sneaker explodes 😳 #Dontmakeemliketheyusedto #Solesforever #not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfonso just told me to bartend and I’m like idk how to make drinks I just know how to drink them 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you want to post something cute for Valentine’s Day but you can’t because the person you want as your valentinesday isn’t yours 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill @MICHEALRAPAPORT I can’t see what he done 😭😭😭😭🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/dZ42raV1BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UbaldiniTia It may not be the best source BUT it makes some very solid points]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victoria's Secret to close more than 50 stores https://t.co/qk9hw7jHnx https://t.co/6LAhQHQAtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karenimustbe @Kristenkelso23 @MeganBurger4891 @thx4thesave @sparcharge @JT419 @charlib1983 @toolsforbalance Gm😊💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say I have a loud voice! I want to say make your loudest “s” or “f” you’re not so loud now are you?… https://t.co/Uoec6K7XN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman Will have to meditate mid-day to deal with today's news dump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending the #GenderEquity in the #workplace session at the League conference in #Lincoln.  Such great information… https://t.co/ve9c9D4t9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too true. How many times have I rewatched season one? Netflix could tell you tales...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danyturcotte Je ne peux pas croire qu’il peut y avoir autant de méchanceté parmi les québécois...j’ai honte.😡😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would literally cry my eyes out!! My heart and soul. Cody is the loml.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleiKing @PatWalkerWX @SusanneBrunner LOL 🤣 🤣 OMG!!! Mr. Pat!!! Hilarious that those two have this little rivalry 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Square @Twitter #investors #bitcoin #cryptocurrency #cryptotrading @SEC_news #investing #investments #stocks… https://t.co/MofPypQBrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[ill have you know, i shoved SEVERAL skateboards up my ass before this picture https://t.co/H5RVKEYlwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows YOUR PARTY EXPECTED YOU TO ACTUALLY DO YOUR CONSTITUTIONAL DUTY NOT A PRESIDENTIAL OPER… https://t.co/yA4J2MGymy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaneeB @LindseyGrahamSC Well you believe the Q , so that says a lot . I believe in God and my country , and my st… https://t.co/GkhomnqgKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tnWFp7nVkj WHO IS THIS CALIFORNIAN RAVING LUNATIC? AS A LATINA WOMAN SHE DOES NOT REPRESENT ME..ESPECI… https://t.co/GERMjaCMP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several Attempts In Learning...SAIL!  Failure is part of learning!  Happy to be learning at #ICE19  with @amyphs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are an awesome American Patriot !  Republicans are color blind, everyone needs to realize the Democrats are del… https://t.co/xnaXyuraH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.....If this is how they start a season, imagine how they gonna end it! 💥💥💥🐗🐗🐗❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[HILARIE JUST BROUGHT THE CAST ONTO THE STAGE AND INTRODUCED KATE WHILE I DON’T WANNA BE PLAYED AND THE ENTIRE CROWD… https://t.co/1rDrQqb0n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 My 3 year old is the opposite. He is the one who gets the road rage. He’ll just yell “Go cars, get out of our way… https://t.co/g1YbAS8iJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @HillaryClinton Maybe so but he is PRESIDENT  not killary]]></document><document><![CDATA[If dating is just doing what you do at home but with someone else, marriage must be doing the weird shit you do whe… https://t.co/ZbHzqmFsEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mimiros9 @JSaintPastour @LilianaSnchez9 @delosangelesbe1 Gracias Mirta .  Saludo cariñoso para todos queridos amig… https://t.co/E1pDm8OZ5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend said he’d buy me vans whenever ONLY IF @VANS_66 FOLLOWED ME PLEASE FOLLOW ME OMFG PLZ 😂😂 #vans GUYS HELP me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman yell-talking into her cell phone on this AM's @CapitolCorridor:  "YEAH, WE'RE DELAYED BUT I'M SITTING IN THE… https://t.co/6jWVVyxRYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently watching two drunk dudes race running the opposite direction on a moving walkway at DTW #puremichigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilmjj @MJStarOfficial @JusticeTrublu I'm with Wendy. Michael was robbed of his childhood and I don't believe he molested anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSherrodBrown Vote to build the wall! Please help stop the pipeline of drugs coming into our communities! #BuildTheWall !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched a guy put TEN creamer cups in his coffee at 7-11. What’s the point of that? Why not just pour yourself… https://t.co/ISixXF7Sqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imcorinnemec No pants are the best pants (only at home, of course..) 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! Pleasantly surprised to featured as the first guest on the initial episode of stil… https://t.co/fsI0RCtTDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamdovico @TechNinjaTodd Did You Carry The Flag Today,  Charley? by Rebecca Caudill I think if we could locate th… https://t.co/a8BwPuUrA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheToyInsider @YooHooFriends Thank you and enjoy your weekend ! #AuroraYooHooParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elijah Pricebrook knocks down a 3 with 30 sec left in the first quarter to take Desert Oasis to a one point lead ov… https://t.co/sNjobrwN3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Carbondale cat can look both ways before crossing the road but some SIU students can’t https://t.co/OZi0B2UlnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[do i miss thailand or do i just miss a time when i was confidence enough to wear a bikini n no makeup every moment of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not wrong  Even before tumblr started flagging “nude” pics Michelangelo was flagged and had to cover up all… https://t.co/WBzPOFKh6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindie investigation... S’s ask, is the perimeter the same when magnet tiles are shaped like a cube and then adjust… https://t.co/pTq3SMyLNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[an Ounce of prevention is worth more than a Pound of cure.  #Facts #realtalk 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPCS_TN we celebrate reading!! Thank  You  @HPCS_PTC      For the yummy popcorn snack! @HPCLibrary @mrsjmchenry… https://t.co/xQth0tBElq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t a joke. That’s the scary part. Everyone - regardless of party affiliation - should be disturbed by this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet and outgoing client owns a top salon/spa in NYC and drove down to see me for her initial session + touch-u… https://t.co/aI2OFqKd3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lala_lou_ya @LilaGraceRose No federal money funds abortion &amp; hasn't since 1976.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of 7... Day 1 of the 7 day book cover challenge. Today I nominate @jfantinato Post covers of your favourite b… https://t.co/xGNULYFmHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4 I finally gave up on trying to find a certified @DemeterUSA biodynamic Italian wine even at @silverlakewine in L… https://t.co/rvFxWRwfCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm quite sure I was born in the wrong century. What I would have become...I mourn the possibility. Value, quality,… https://t.co/i5A32YyUjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmoon61 @keeshond81872 @BethlpweLowe @deannakaytv Hey......you are pretty NO MATTER HOW YOUR DRESSED SIS!!!! 😁😁😁❤❤❤☠☠☠☠👣👣👣👣🌹🌹🌹🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[My long hair got brought up yesterday, and here I am at 5:54 AM ON A SATURDAY looking at old pics and wanting to gr… https://t.co/vhy0ueZLDw]]></document></documents></author>