<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Now they can’t call me the ashy white girl at work. #brazilianbumbumcream #lotion #sistergift @ Old Allentown Histo… https://t.co/p3W4klUL7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzPatterson I have not read the resolution but the fact that anti-Muslim is in there raises a red flag when this… https://t.co/LJTRxWuftC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you as the family I miss, I love you as the sister I always need, I love you as my best friend @PennyPax Hap… https://t.co/XfQieojAep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heather_rose What about the non ASD Disabled KIDS?  They ALL need help...they currently get $0   #ItsNotJustASD… https://t.co/FMcalnyklR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Monday” Acrylic and spray paint on 20 x 20” canvas all dressed up for her trip to The Other Art Fair LA. Ticket in… https://t.co/QcOV2WQmkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYTStyles @DrJenGunter Not surprised. We’re far too practical for such shenanigans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand My understanding is that that, this is a statement, not legislation. I know what has to be done, let’s go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring @StPeteFL and St Pete's beach @VISITFLORIDA #beachlife https://t.co/Y09elqnJSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill @MannyMua733 @TeenVogue @Snapchat I love you both so much 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @Allegiant! This is getting annoying! Stop pushing my flight back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews You can’t believe anything put out by the current White House!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my mans!!! Everything is right around the corner. It’s crazy! #bittersweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s flight concludes my travel for February! 7/7  This month has been a movie and it’s only the beginning!   Th… https://t.co/oxfqLLtPv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂🤣🤣🤣 I can't believe this shit happened!! Funny Shit I was watching it on my phone⚰⚱possessionmovie.... I CAN'T M… https://t.co/96K7nbn1fF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you over hype feelings for someone and it turns to pura merida]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't go hard for yourself, how the hell do you expect someone else to!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to go to the doctor for eating too many lemons. i burned my stomach lining (dentist wasnt too happy either)]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; at the top of my list of things I never want to do again, tell somebody they have to move into a nursing home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deezy2_Blessed NP! I think seeking understanding is good, as is understanding that we do not and cannot fathom God… https://t.co/LAUcWACVMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hair isn't about age... It's about attitude!!! My lovely 97 years young client Lorraine proves that! #bluehair… https://t.co/AHsLTvEvNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazytimewJay @Celestee3ee Smh no I have the damn flu &amp; was throwing up blood 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhlstef You don’t even follow me yet you look at my Twitter every single day to see if I said something about Kink… https://t.co/r7t7yi1DFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[you are seriously the most comedic of this entire franchise. I go on twitter on Monday’s for your tweets… https://t.co/ic9QMVuRNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dark_Wizzy_ @DizzySesson @fhyrrain feel like he would def be a hyena 100%]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lil TLC because to me, it’s the Thot that counts, so love and self care are very important. 😂🥰 @ Los Angeles, Cal… https://t.co/SlNb4mF5zF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko @DrCherylBrodie @JoelMartinRubin Show us your TAX RETURNS MR TRUMP if you have nothing to hide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ran a light that was dead read and scared the crap out of myself 😭 God really be w me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS You? Of all people, challenging women to be strong leaders? You? A lingerie model who whored herself for mo… https://t.co/Hhdg6PzZ3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[These McGee’s are nuts 🥜I tell yah, talking with the kids about adult stuff 🤷🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️… https://t.co/VHRAv3OYmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_grauer17 @Coach_Mul @AMCAT_Football @coachjalicea 🔔🔔🔔 welcome to the family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieGeist @christinageist Wishing you a birthday filled with fun, laughter and surrounded by all those you love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budex2k @adeyanjudeji YOU should be more fearful of a ruling Dictatorship than a few soldiers and thugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun is out ☀️, a beautiful day for Jump Rope for ❤️. @Heritage_Hawks @DrLemosTeaches https://t.co/FZsz6PblrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruthless_Regg This is nothing usually he has his hand INSIDE my shirt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirPatStew @DesylvaL @RealHughJackman That's so awesome. Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeepsonly2 Sending prayers to you and Frankie. Always hard to lose a Furbaby 🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmUltimatePred @roc2391 @RGrimaldi23 @StorybookColors @Jeremysfields Jealous! We 💙💛 Rocco @@roc2391 &amp; @IAmUltimatePred!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rae_laynee the only thing Rachel’s food pyramid consisted of in 8th grade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @SenateGOP @SenWarren please stop pandering to Women, you're Embarrassing Yourself.... you know damn wel… https://t.co/YQwVQjGOPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’m simply IN California, I’m superior to hundreds of millions of other Americans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StSenka Shared on https://t.co/86PHKTevUs  Which institutions care and which do not? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will create frame tomorrow. @ Lady Hahn's Art Oddities &amp; Curiosities https://t.co/P5Am3eqfz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancerbychoice7 It really is insane!! Animal agriculture is leading cause of climate change but its shoved under t… https://t.co/zWXVrO9NEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MarkSutcliffe @erindavis @Writersfest Wish I could. Have another commitment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warner_timmy @skyspeciale28 @AndyNice69 Are you fucking dumb? It’s literally so easy to be like “hey don’t post a… https://t.co/0F7crjnZgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calancooper7 Chace on mound @diamondprospect scrimmage. https://t.co/0tPgzddunT]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - SpaceX Dragon demo capsule returns to Earth https://t.co/PNjYGKoYGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenNick72 @GiantAKS @tokenwhitedude Andy from @indycdandvinyl gifted me this EP...so on the set of Singles, Chris… https://t.co/Eu4iiqX3IO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw #captainmarvel yesterday! Waited so long to see Carol Danvers on the big screen. @ Ocala, Florida https://t.co/SUCl2fSKdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones A great article telling it like it is. Segregation still exists!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING I’m at the Dekalb County Sheriff’s Office where Sheriff Nick Welden just confirmed that 11-year-old Amber… https://t.co/dCtq20GJ8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blames Sandra for stealing her shoes and it may have been lovey, that took them, that's possibly why lovey didn't come back to the shelter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[báhn mì-style burger with sesame-roasted broccoli. thomas grated the carrots for the pickled topping like a total p… https://t.co/3rnaFO8UIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#healthyliving #salads #veggies #health #alkaline #cleaneating #milwaukee #saladsbydarnell https://t.co/zgIGq8clet]]></document><document><![CDATA[WV teachers are striking because they care more about the future of WV students than they care about getting a raise and that's just facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigricanman You damned if you do your damned if you don’t! Everything offends somebody these days. People need to… https://t.co/xVDcOV6Qju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progress is being made on second floor!  Looking great don't you think?  #renovations #puremichigan @ Traverse City… https://t.co/S9cGs6TCIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods can’t be a homewrecker if the door was open 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisC25265543 I shower! I mean, when I galavant over hill and dale between hideous rampages I DO run through cri… https://t.co/7LBGmdLs6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Local Officials Siphon $...Bernie? https://t.co/skfszPtAR5 via @SDzzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK WHO CARES ABOUT ME BC IVE BEEN SITTING IN COURT VERY QUIETLY FOR 6 DAYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter LemonGello Jr hes got so much soul in his voice I love it #AmericanIdol]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you work in an ER when your wallet is mainly coffee receipts and used sticky notes 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[i couldn’t be more excited for spring break omg it needs to get here already 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SophieRunning And the political statement should now be absolutely clear as a deterant to other terrorists. Right decision made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secme’s mousetrap car brainstorming stage... we’re getting there! @BrowardSTEM @Professor_Erik https://t.co/m9JIw2XPfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidOAtkins @amyklobuchar You are clearly a mansplaining bully. Go harass another woman please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonVegas22 Awesome. We appreciate the support. Keep in touch, and we’ll do the same!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I’ve felt like this since my father died 8 years ago.  😒😪💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parker (my dog) literally has a better/funnier personality than 80% of the humans that I know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault May I ask Ron who?  It just occurred to me that it could be Ron Weasley.  I always thought that kid had an edge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESSCOntario @LUESS_ I met the students after 7 pm on the 2nd day. They were all excited, energized and in a great… https://t.co/TxmKtQrPvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonStiles77 @Jason1Goff Dude, it’s unofficially Black Thanksgiving. Quit trying to be that guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You are no different than he is how dare you even say anything about him. You are… https://t.co/2Y0nyLwkjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[me pumping myself up to be productive today only to fall right back into it an anxiety attack https://t.co/CGhirBuAxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Storm Warning mode #fasnachts #weareready #whatelsedoweneed #maybewine @ Bethlehem, Pennsylvania https://t.co/DN8IychCyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITGeekCT Thankfully she was strong in her faith and would never leave the Church due to something like that, but t… https://t.co/zbbdSGdD3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Valentine's Day. Its for Love and treating your sweetie like a King or Queen, by doing something special as a… https://t.co/kRWnUwOsRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annalunoe new song #303 is dopeee if you haven’t heard it yet check it out😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrestMetaph @vasinvain You'll be saying WHAT the whole time but it's worth a crazy watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one whose fascinated by my boo while he’s sleep?I b listening to his breathing &amp; heart like a lil weirdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sisters.... Birthday for our sister 3dlecia... #hottub #singles #fun @ Oasis Hot Tub Gardens - Kalamazoo https://t.co/CRLGoNRe8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hooterboy @ZombieSquadHQ @WagATudeTags @waggycampers Congrats,Oswald.:-):-DYay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Thompson190 I can’t stand her, and if we have to listen to her annoying voice all season again ima be so pissed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmanasan my dad stopped getting me chocolates a few years ago ☹️ and like i’m upset but i don’t wanna say anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ John F. Kennedy International Airport https://t.co/eHK07mKMSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin13263461 @Xquisite_imp @SamDaMan723 @benshapiro Good luck raising all your kids, Kevin. Unless you’re celibate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this girl! Hard work, sacrifice and dedication paid off!  (These kids are a blast!) #thefutureisbright… https://t.co/pQlZLwShgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnstoppableSeries . . .  Don’t forget to tune into Facebook or IGTV tomorrow to hear Jess Markt talk about what he… https://t.co/L96GOzyM60]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bad bitches link” should be more of a thing but for the actual friendship part 🙈 https://t.co/DH0FiXoMaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are looking to live vicariously through my spring break trip add me on sc: mariahpruitt  Insta: m_pruitt #pastaparty 🇮🇹]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s more to this world than just what’s happening today. There’s always tomorrow.”  Thank you @BradleyByrne fo… https://t.co/HXoPUAMbyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anti-Kaepernick Store Goes Out Of Business https://t.co/uzw46mKeOi via @YouTube #TakeAKnee #Kaepernick #Nike… https://t.co/km4C4rsX0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mental Health First Aid training for the counselors in the district! @MrsScottFMS @FoxC6Secondary @FoxMiddleSchool… https://t.co/URHIFtAPE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[this month has have to be one of the best months i’ve had in a while 2019 doing me good so far 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch. Just to be clear: I never met Melania, Ivanka and Trump family. No idea who they are. I am like everyone els… https://t.co/me3kBzw0Zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is quite possibly the best thing  😂😂😂😂 I love and miss Vince so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've just come back from outside where it is pitch dark because I felt a compulsion to fertilize. I got a whole sac… https://t.co/KmIZtXJhpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i like all music but country” oh i know you haven’t heard the weight of these wings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe When I was in college years ago, a person ahead of me in the drive-thru for McDonald's paid for my b… https://t.co/fsryTmiJOA]]></document></documents></author>