<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Reading a good book in my pajamas with my wee babe asleep in my arms is literal heaven 🥰❤️📖 #amreading #mistborn @BrandSanderson #momlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPittBrooke @Independent #buymybook #dudeweedsavedmylife @amazon https://t.co/oJt8CIrN9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[This fluffy jacket has been in many of my pictures already but idc 🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/yyp1CLMx31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench Justice system does fail sometimes. Brock Turner's victim has to live with his brutal attack the rest… https://t.co/KEVSeVXb1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkelly SOMEWHERE ELSE WHERE PEOPLE ARE NOT GOING TO TRY TO SELL YOUR LIFE OUT BECUZ OF THEIR GREED AND RACISM...PE… https://t.co/zBNLxJWcgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[📺 mom and dad got a new tv and i helped set it up. ac-cord-ing to her, i’m the best assistant! @ NoMa https://t.co/PUeq52door]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on a great season Edina JGB white!  Proud to have sponsored you. Graduating 5 seniors - you are all first… https://t.co/NkXrrOaw5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up with my eye almost completely swelled shut soooo guess who gets to go to urgent care when they open?! 👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for all of the times I’ve been redirected from what I thought I wanted to what I truly deserved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump He has no clue what “proper decorum” is, Trump has “no class.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing plants in the @CabrilloFUSD Science Lab. We are learning so much each week about what plants need to grow.… https://t.co/Oo5ra1U8pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silentcar Adding a few of my favorites: @_nahoni  @rlmcgowan_  @yanitzaninett  @Suzy7131 @PonsMaite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I agree with @JL_Kdiamond. BTS is the best K-pop boy band the world has ever seen. They are kind, nice, humble… https://t.co/jCZr5cukob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monicanum @sajidcdevaca @GlodeJo07 Oye si no me acordaba del ritual a la madre tierra 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments Not happening millions of us support @TuckerCarlson https://t.co/5fyZo40u5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[You praise Fidel Castro and don’t forget we have a video advising Castro how to defeat USA ! You praise him and wan… https://t.co/jKKSVG2YRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE COMMITTED FRAUD TO CIRCUMVENT OUR LAWS  SHE IS NOT A VALID MEMBER OF CONGRESS SHE WAS ELECTED UNDER FRAUDULENT… https://t.co/RQIWuv4Gb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations BE Huskies! So proud of these girls. They don’t quit! https://t.co/9sOzWocNx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this looks like just a muddy little creek, but it's a muddy little creek that hasn't run for years......… https://t.co/PgjWekQRgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very timely affirmation as I struggle w my #impostorsyndrome while writing a personal statement for a summer cour… https://t.co/Y19K1Qqkou]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Loki: India got my spot in the bed, by my human’s head, so I had to sleep at the end. I am not amused.  @ Seff… https://t.co/arhu9B5KMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to share a special crossover edition of #NoLimitspodcast with Skimm’d from The Couch! Carly Zakin and Danie… https://t.co/jWe7Kjw8uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCAN @GovernorVA @RalphNortham That’s the problem...I think the MOU signed by then Gov. McAuliffe for both MVP and… https://t.co/Uv5bAxn3CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsall4thegame @Mark55964331 @Buster_ESPN Right?! I’m done with his shit!!! 😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments @chrislhayes You should listen to this top rated climatologist: https://t.co/1ZLH1wxog0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdle_2963 @tillinghastpat1 @BreitbartNews This Brennan guy is a traitor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonDavisBD the kingdom gives me life. the show needs some life once in awhile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshnorthsouth I smell like canned lavender, my flight seatmates are going to be making that same face]]></document><document><![CDATA[... or she doesn’t have to do any work...?!? ... either way, WHY are we paying her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blykat @StormIsUponUs Serial Brain May have decoded that. It’s all good though. Trump is looking out for us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHGGuru Is this your own infographic? May I share on other platforms, please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So whats it gonna be can we work on you and me, im trying to get back to how it use to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Había oferta o descuento en los hoteles ayer? Vi que hubo más de 5 bodas en Panamá anoche 😂 y hoy también]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriTheBull Me and Pj’s first date was to see Princess and the frog. 10 years wow. I actually watched it today &amp; still love it 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamwithfaith @JillWineBanks That's great !!!!  I've been following @FilmmakerJulie @Betsywest they are nominated… https://t.co/4ClBUn1adN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. TRUMP DO YOU FORGET THE IDIOT'S AND GET THIS COUNTRY RIGHT. MY HUSBAND IS AN ARTIST HE PAINTED… https://t.co/VWKx6xL34B]]></document><document><![CDATA[i heard it doesn’t matter what time u post on twitter what y’all think    model - @amazinglasagna https://t.co/5NYVqdb0tI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the patience of a saint.   🐶 😇 🐶 😇 🐶 😇 #doodlesofinstagram #doodlesofinstaworld #doodlesoftheworld… https://t.co/ZRjw8GIsiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2:20 am and I’m supposed to be writing a paper about hierarchy contributing to violence but instead I’m eating… https://t.co/7jZtnoz2Ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stressing myself over something I shouldn’t even have to worry about. 🙃🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to buy a shower cap with cats on it but lexi told me she’d move out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe this kid almost let me miss out on seeing him for the first time in a tux. I guess cause he knew I… https://t.co/cN0ELDsCp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, @michaeljackson I will always be there. 💋💖👑 @ Old North Sacramento, Sacramento https://t.co/xyhF4TQl4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Is there really any point to these law suits? If we win China won’t pay, if China wins we won’t pay… https://t.co/mtFx9v8fob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I get to meet @CalliNorton, I HAD to celebrate 💛💛💛 https://t.co/dB4e2w7aMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of the women before us who endured belittlement on a daily basis but with steely determination - broke thru… https://t.co/xnX2Qy1C2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh no! #aquaman just died on game of thrones?!? (#got #newbie #obv....) 😫😢😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex96Pietersen Yes, I should take a break from tweeting. And also, yes, you will miss me? Hmm. Does this means th… https://t.co/p8By2K0o0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teddy Graham has climbed in his bunny bag for the road trip to the UMN.  We are hoping all our friends come find us… https://t.co/hf2BdGTGde]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pride and joy being a #GoodBoy prior to bustin' out one of his most endearing qualities... His uncanning ability… https://t.co/MdaU0DY2LZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Becike_Claude @Fillannoeuf Dans mon coin de pays pas grand monde en faisait. Je suis de la génération ou on jouait… https://t.co/FHwfU0jrDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBenanti I hope your daughter is much better. (I saw the play in November. I teared up when the Macy’s parade… https://t.co/D2bLjraxH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsking @LaurieHalverson Absolutely! Check out this link for ways to take action: https://t.co/rsm1Qg8Rdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[YouTube video coming soon ima start with a q&amp;a, so start asking questions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job to my wonderful team and my wonderful bff! I did pretty good myself, not to brag or anything, buttttt gues… https://t.co/KZa9dm5tdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one plays as much golf as I do! No president EVER watched as much tv as I do! I am the laziest most unread guy h… https://t.co/0SR5BL3leH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve evolved as a person so much in the past few months... it’s honestly kinda scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[My iPad autocorrects “LFPR” into “leprechaun” and I feel like it just doesn’t know me anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is treating me so good rn. I have an amazing ass boyfriend. My car is officially paid off. And I just finished… https://t.co/NlRGYCe8fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but I also think hockey moms aren’t regular moms they’re cool moms so https://t.co/zfXIkKXzah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunrise bicycle ride after an awesome Sunday afternoon with very busy open houses. Looking forward to a g… https://t.co/U7wmMKe1ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cin_ismos En Netflix? Fíjate a nosotras si nos ganchó jajajjaa le seguimos hasta las 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out Miami, here we come. If you are in the area, join us April 18th at Florida International University for t… https://t.co/7qASZYFwjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ni hace tanto frío y yo exageré con mi mega chamarra y con mi playera de cuello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerito_ Te iba a decir “wey con ese capítulo llore demasiado..” pero no quise darte spoilers 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searched for “pence curb” just to make sure the internet was doing its job and of course it was. #thankyouinternet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldbdancer Fresno?  Asking for a friend...  Also probably not.  Should’ve been arrested back then for draft dodgin… https://t.co/3KuOguem5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CosmicBrace @ImranKhanPTI @zooinspectors @anikasleem @sanmarino397 @orcatm @dianacmb4 @raccoon_mama @born2_wild So… https://t.co/bBwk95GDbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I literally ached in my heart for my Kade. It got weighing on my heart that his dad doesn’t deserve him.… https://t.co/YbvjPzPvDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off on another adventure...... This week, I got to spend one on one time with each of my boys. Today it's mini me t… https://t.co/TS11dcFOVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i’m walking around campus, about 99.99% of the time i’m blasting banda music on my headphones w/ the volum… https://t.co/k7ENxLdqvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jc5502 @DrDenaGrayson @PeteButtigieg @VP @realDonaldTrump I use the word “anathema” a lot these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always loved sending and receiving cards, but I have a whole new appreciation for the greeting card industry a… https://t.co/wnisrWqz79]]></document><document><![CDATA[That hair Colton #TheBachelorFinale #thebachelor https://t.co/xq0U1vZaMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisForrestEDU @dbc_inc @mandyeellis @burgessdave Absolutely loved this book and could not put it down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now if we could only get her to be a guest star on Sabrina, that would be great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr President , don’t let all these negative remarks , faze you, your  a great President,  doing a… https://t.co/qcj1Ciubj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowinatx at @HOTELHOTBURRITO #austinmusic #atxmusic #sxsw2019 #athvssoto @ Hotel Vegas https://t.co/5nmE0cdoVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swanky? I think so. I absolutely ADORE this place. #Martinis #NewYorkBeerProject #NYBP #InLove #Upscale https://t.co/hQ9FoimfkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[HI I AM SINGLE AND TOMORROW I WILL START DATING THE BEST PERSON I KNOW: ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez gets fresh criticism over Amazon as new billboards in New York emerge  https://t.co/1KSCFQQvWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillippa22 @Amanda_Alston The carriage horses have it great. No worries. https://t.co/lPw7RDCYiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@localghey you need to Lizzo out and do some wild piccolo vids https://t.co/EC7ZKIKO4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much I only ate Takis all day! 🙃  Later that day my grandma call me saying they got me Takis so I got them a… https://t.co/WuIT67AOBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarleyFortune Not to mention - why do we refer to them as layoffs? No one is being rehired back. Those talented pe… https://t.co/7UrLzABUDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dbacks Could you post updates on workouts today?  Pushed back/cancelled due to rain.  Don't want to drive an hour TY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markwahlberg @NKOTB Add that!!!  And while you are adding things... how about adding a @Wahlburgers in Columbus pl… https://t.co/eJDoedj2fC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theboxerdeli @thedailybeast @camilla905 @AOC @morninggloria https://t.co/xMXLEAs68X]]></document><document><![CDATA[By not voting she's approving it, we are not that stupid! Alaska surely has more morality than this woman does. Vot… https://t.co/nMRI59K6Ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men will really use a 8in1  Body wash Shampoo Conditioner Deodorant Mouth wash Toothpaste Detergent and  Fabric softener]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ibelieveinthoselovesongs #jamesingram #lovesongs #valentinesday @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/kNt6UwSr8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[These babies need immediate attention. Can you provide them with a loving home? Please have your pets spayed and ne… https://t.co/PsopGjVb6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go_jos_go C'est pas si mal, je vis avec des chats depuis plusieurs années, ce que j'ai pas réussi à faire avec les… https://t.co/L5U9MVp8bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iosthisshoe //Like a Demon Dean? Because there’s a few roaming around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idesignforreal @RachelBearden7 @TNedu I look forward to this every year! 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Silent Professional - Charlie by @TatteredFlagBSW @ Tattered Flag Brewery &amp; Still Works — https://t.co/c2gmF9xOiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@56peggy @fordnation @SkellyHamilton Yea it’s actually quite a serious problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@convoice @Rosie And what did the kids do? The damage is to the kids, detaining the families together be simple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expecting Baby #2 👶🏻 #MendezPartyof4 @ Fairplay, Colorado https://t.co/pdEgeAOpOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also sad that idiots are pushing people to eat #fake #meat and sludge that is now printed to look like meat. F… https://t.co/Vz9S16Gkbi]]></document></documents></author>