<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Subtronics @SullivanKing @heshmane @squnto @ziasounds @_bluntsnblondes @egan_jpg thank you ❤️🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been reading about climate change and might go to med school to play the system since we are going down in 12 years now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz One old Method Man to another old demented man Tim Cook probably couldn't even hear him]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an FYI #apchemchat Tweeps, if using @FlinnScientific Le Chat lab kit U can replace seltzer with @GiantEagle selt… https://t.co/eKmIWppTsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed presenting on behalf of the great work we are doing @CADeptEd @TonyThurmond and what is yet to come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDEA is clear- parents are the child’s primary expert and educator, yet time and again their voice goes unheard!… https://t.co/vZtJvXiVgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was #Luxurious. Thanks again trevorjez for the fun night. 🍊🎰🎶😘 @ Gwen Stefani Planet Hollywood https://t.co/4LLeRoXXra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, our campaign for #WeHo City Council was endorsed by the LA County Democratic Party!! @ Utla Plaza https://t.co/BUXxrR7zm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop He had no chance of getting one since they dont give out ones based in lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find something new every time I listen to the @Pink set list. #glitterintheair #twodays]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have had some interesting #California weather including #frost on the grass  #photography  #winter #cold #ice @… https://t.co/GGLxnDLsd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solarpulse7 @WAdailyreport @AOC I wish we had some way to move enough Democrats to enough sparsely populated red states to move the needle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was not raining today—- so after my regular sessions, I ran home and was like everyone get dressed, we are going… https://t.co/8iejsKf2GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is so good. Going through such a difficult time but I can see him at work even still. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carly_Clarke Thank you Carly for the kind words.   Congrats on the win last night and I wish you luck on Sunday.   Sorry I can’t be there🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bros_menkichi I sadly do not unfortunately 😔 but congrats to whoever receives them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I ask people if they’re on the dining plan and they go “uhhhh . . . I don’t know.” Same as when I ask i… https://t.co/kHCjMeOJYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadkonik9 Chad Anthony, didn’t I ask you yesterday about going to Doctor Lefoer, like the ER Doctor said, plus yo… https://t.co/AN5oEjTy6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running for Brightech's giveaway, check it out! https://t.co/8fDN215O1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wasn't able to attend the vigil last year, which made tonight so much more meaningful. seeing everyone come toget… https://t.co/Y5RYyoxr1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblondeMD Girl you do you! And anyone telling you that you are “complaining” doesn’t get it. #surgeryresidency i… https://t.co/jwdl4pKDRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new @PotteryBarn furniture arrived! Thanks Brandis for the great delivery experience. Love my newly updated spac… https://t.co/R38F7QvKzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Congratulations, and lots of love to you and your soon-to-be husband, Ana! Wishing you a beautiful wedding day! XO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eileen75192329 @thunderbolt5523 @AndyOstroy @realDonaldTrump Lol! https://t.co/vdI7IVGhE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh if I count the money after it come out the ATM what makes you think I trust to bum ass ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO so my dad always comes to eat during his lunch at the house &amp; sometimes he brings food https://t.co/FBVhhOBAHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be presenting with @TheDODifference about Osteopathic Recognition at the Association of Military Osteopa… https://t.co/Ts48gKlUvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers Robert Jeffress isn’t pleased with his evangelical brethren who oppose Trump. He calls them morons. He… https://t.co/9KyFep5zcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @Sekusa1 @RobertJohnDavi I think that's a good idea that way the Democrats and Republicans know what we t… https://t.co/ujXAVHolOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@____PiNK__ @TheSuperNupe Eva gets microlinks...her hair  will always look like it’s hers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnBarrasso as your constituent, I want you to vote Yes against Trump's National Emergency!  You swore an oath… https://t.co/cujf8qqxQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_maryann10 Paki hi nman kami sa knya Ann! Miss ko na yan kahit snob hahaha  #POPSSSS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of us (me included) have given bums second chances without even having kids involved. I’m sure she’s realizing… https://t.co/y2LBq7fHjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished the best online math PD, Math Games Pre-K-2, with Dan Finkel!  Can’t wait to use these with my studen… https://t.co/C3rSCRueWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ana_r_quintana Still in Indonesia. Still deciding on who to have transport her back to the US. She legally has to… https://t.co/QENW7pKXhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any candidate actually mentioned  #critlib in their cover letter I would jump on that train so fast 🚂🚂🚂 Librarie… https://t.co/lgUNFvqkoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day. Made. Great seeing you Dr. Helen! @ Old Dominion University https://t.co/Fzp4Wt4Xjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodC1997 if it won’t for IG I wouldn’t even know what you look like ☹️☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[niggas actually listen to this song? like without doing the little dance shit???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind “Right to Fail,  Frontline ProPublica ["'mentally' ill adults" are victims of  Capitalism, suffering biochem… https://t.co/jOJ61iBeFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Our hearts break for you. I am so sorry for your breath-stealing grief]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAJOR COKE BUST AT ATLANTA AIRPORT: How agents busted a 24-year-old woman with 3 lbs of cocaine at Atlanta airport… https://t.co/7yGXlrkoEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abrightercloud One of my very very favorite things. A girl can never have too much chocolate. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[living proof that you ain’t gotta die to get to heaven.✨ https://t.co/HPLSW2MfL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg @vagrantcow Irresponsible reporting like this breeds fear of science. Makes us look like we do our ex… https://t.co/S7ozQbVANU]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a man who sings opera on the floor below me ,but he’s so good that I don’t even mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are almost there... @UsherCollierES https://t.co/zZjkQnKUmx  #CrackingTheCodeForClosingTheDigitalDivide… https://t.co/YzIryK78Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN you are a disgrace-should not be representing any US citizen - and you havePres Trump wrong.get your facts… https://t.co/ru4lQXPbub]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to go to #AAHHE19 so I can meet all the people I follow on Twitter IRL 😂 I was reminded by a friend that we… https://t.co/zrnqmLZcYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slurpieboy70 @RPIC_IBIC It was very nice. Perfect size for the crowd too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A ver si no resulta en anulación del juicio del Chapo https://t.co/4HTUGdRlLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @ABC @TheView @MeghanMcCain @GovernorVA @Comey @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Everything U have written shoul… https://t.co/KvVLfLP49R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XeniaKaepernick @thethirstytales @Sostraveluk @TouringTastebud @monstervoyage @always5star @Adventuringgal… https://t.co/fK0x1KF40L]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re sleeping with somebody 4-6 years younger than you, get some help 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!!  I was called in all wknd, this makes it better @ Poly-America, L.P. https://t.co/o70qAc060P]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY in your Congress folks: - House voting on resolution to end the national emergency (at the border) declaratio… https://t.co/IlJzDuilnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs @MrDane1982 PEOPLE REMEMBER, how he made SURE to keep the Democrats divided at the convention by w… https://t.co/WIPQIGuxJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very excited to share with you guys my @noh8campaign photo I had the opportunity to pose for last month here in… https://t.co/rPxxASlTnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m afraid I’m slowing turning into my dad... woke up before 8 on a Saturday and turn on RFDTV... 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women’s day!   This was a valentine I did for @papyrusbrand a little while back.… https://t.co/iDCm7Nusif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ornyadams @HollywoodImprov Funny ORNY ADAMS! I want you to know you were the LAST ONE ON MY BUCKET LIST !!  I can die laughing now 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We should all be very worried right now that this president is thinking about bringing us into a military conflict… https://t.co/i8emWeONWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viciously attack me.  In a precautionary tone of voice, Barbara Walters said, “If you’ve had the measles shot growi… https://t.co/7C8reKJ8FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break up with u're GF, cause I'm Bored 🔕 ......... ... .... .. .............. ... ...... .. ✨Motto,Lembeh Island,No… https://t.co/DHBbMq7PVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color correction orange to a beautiful natural haircolor @ Allison's Hair Company in Sola Salon Studios https://t.co/lnuK6eJRdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadCINNAMONbun i saw it on an instagram ad! lol but the website is https://t.co/bZXMzbUAM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @Mikel_Jollett Everyone should stop using “socialism” because it’s going to mean death at the ballot box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[andrew’s passenger seatbelt smells like his gf’s fave perfume acqua di gioia and when i asked him what it was  bc i… https://t.co/d5TStCgTZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gonny_aarts @cookiegigan @essie @ShopprsDrugMart @YorkdaleStyle Hi Gonny, yes it was a great evening! Thanks! ♥♥♥]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I feel about the below zero wind chill and snow on the ground in March. https://t.co/yjuZC4WflM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever been to the rumpunchbrunch? You missing a hidden treat. Customer service is superb, food is phenomenal and dj… https://t.co/aJUZjk1X9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little girl had the best time at a mixitupkitchen birthday party yesterday. 🐼 cupcakes for all! . . .… https://t.co/XjabMevSSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never heard of T-Pain!  I don’t like rap &amp; don’t listen to it either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakeItWithCal People are know-it-all dicks. You just have to ignore their shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ugarte_amy @ceciliaalanis Mi autoestima aún no ha llegado al punto de necesitar fotos con filtros para sentirme qu… https://t.co/Xr9B3Y00Os]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomas_Verde @JFergusonAU @SaraPalczewski I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS. GUESS NOT SINCE YOU DIDNT INVITE ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTestyTarheel It’s sad that someone told she was more important than she is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great place to work off site! (@ Garfield Park Conservatory - @gpconservatory in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/8xKVvzENUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting in a coffee shop working on my med microbiology hw and I started crying out of nowhere lmao , hi how are ya???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends fox and friends??????? https://t.co/onQ4aLSQCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen up @usacurl @TeamStopera! You’ve got to start visioning tomorrow’s victory against Scotland. Visioning creat… https://t.co/FTrobbqlVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[But if we get free college won’t we have to still pay for it with our taxes? Is it really free?? 😐 doubt it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano I love your tweets!!!  You always make me laugh when it comes to AOC!!  🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[To cold to go get my bobby-pins from the car, so now I have a paper clip holding my hair up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olderdandrt56 @BellaDonnaGagn2 @YoshikiOfficial Pbs,is how Bocelli's career took wing in the US!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I’d like a full version of this thanks. @5SOS 😍😭❤️ @Calum5SOS @Luke5SOS @Ashton5SOS @Michael5SOS it’s so beautif… https://t.co/mU0xSe5pIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you have never played pool with your hands and got them smashed when you were younger and it really shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one asked (rude) but *while* I'm posting decor photos I *might* as well brag on my beautiful bookshelves. https://t.co/63R84Gv2L4]]></document><document><![CDATA[See it all started 18hrs ago... and it’s been so much that I don’t remember lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember that one time i did this for a boy and he bailed on me hahahahailovethat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man people be sooo secretly not happy you’re doing better than them stronger than them happier than them and not in… https://t.co/yTd6r92Hn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨•@ABHcosmetics - dip brow/stripped •@MorpheBrushes sweet tea liner •@EsteeLauder double wear foundation •… https://t.co/kIehvgPhqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t ask for much. I just want to be discovered in the grocery store while singing outloud to myself and go onto… https://t.co/ED9v838Eix]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t nobody make me get over anyone , i am going to have to want to do it myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just absolutely blown away that the parking enforcement officer isn’t there writing tickets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that @discoveryworld is also providing a version of the @smithsonian’s Mornings at the Museums model - we cal… https://t.co/nBw9xRwRwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone PLEASE edit this to be only his screaming and his facial expressions omfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[if astronomy 101 taught me anything, it’s that daylight savings is literally useless. the sun is out longer because… https://t.co/RjkX1yT6zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm so proud of you. thank you for everything. thank you for being born this way.💗🌈 @ladygaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s bring it home boys! @FCDallas #thisisourhouse https://t.co/4ukn008NYf]]></document></documents></author>