<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC AOC is a true Communist, she wants Government Control Of Every thing . I’m apt to believe that… https://t.co/qJd2v4ONx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussBeenToolin @downwithBKing @magusbeast @srecupero @oneill173 @madameatloaf only 4 months away https://t.co/HocCpZxjkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did find it to be far superior on the story standpoint compared to the spectacle which is fine but made the smaller… https://t.co/9GweZ7lLsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT love this düde. Jay Freaking Smith. Ripping drummer, amazing family man, and a brother. 🎶🥁🥁🥁 @ Huntington Beac… https://t.co/9ubdhiCB7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OntheRadarHoops @JonesMandez @ahmirlanglais @Terrell_Burden3 @bderavine7 @MarquaviusJohn2 @Dalight35 @penny4_U… https://t.co/RFoY3LTdUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NYYankees#AaronJudge Judge for yourself. Aaron Judge autographed mint 10 PSA Certitied Cards $500 for both https://t.co/P5TWMZl83R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 51st Birthday to former St. Catharines and Toronto Blue Jays infielder Jeff Kent! https://t.co/S4VgjS8dRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 3 and still a foot of snow on the ground and NOT MELTING! #FunFact last year we hit 43°, 20° warmer than toda… https://t.co/U7mOLfcsBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewYork #Chicago #Illinois #Florida #Texas #California #ColoradoSprings #Colorado #Arizona #Washington  #TampaBay… https://t.co/zwFak1SLXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast So, what would her Secret Service name be?  POTUS FLOTUS COITUS  ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 45: Reshape your destruction! We already have the pieces! We must spend the time to make ourselves whole again.… https://t.co/v2oOsBeLqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[With #BryceHarper heading to @Phillies all I can say is...FINALLY! This saga dragged on waaay too long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In today's #USC Recruiting Rumblings, we talk to fast-rising 2021 Honolulu LB Mason Tufaga (@MasonTufaga) about his… https://t.co/lSMa5ZVzuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, if you're sure... Better be... GRYFFINDOR!!! https://t.co/pton16O4Jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley Right, I’m sure the media will turn on him any minute now. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WellingtonBrew Used to get this out of 2L pop bottles from your place way back then!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pablo_cava @NicolasLucca Volvé al taxi y laburá honestamente, cyberbully de cabotaje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgoold @t_mac_duce4 @Ben_Fred @markasaxon Exactly. Spring numbers mean absolutely nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This organization now truly a book you can judge by its cover. Smh. cc @SeanWebster13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarekS98837118 To są jakieś specjalne wydane parówki, dla przemytników :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Everyone hates you. You're a tool of the Russians, and your own country thinks you're a menace.  Your useless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrozenSicleGirl Did you get another cat or something or are you trying to tell me your cat lady because you did no… https://t.co/DpkP0QVvK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[May just make a Tinder and say I’m in the Military so I can get married next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmarticac @jpalacioposada Le faltaron 4 años más para borrarlos (terroristas), yo se los daría.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally sitting down watching this Antonio Brown interview... its speaking to me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julathomas Where did this happen? I think I missed that one on the news https://t.co/Gq9PgJL7Fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewOnSeeAIR @EdKrassen I don't see it that way. Senator Sanders did not infiltrate the Democratic party, he inv… https://t.co/WlR4yLk8PB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Muse was amazing best concert I’ve ever been to. @ The Forum https://t.co/kG3mLgECUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad made the change and came to Oklahoma on my well to run these boxes 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevieNicks Ms. Stevie Nicks, Is there anywhere to get a signed copy of this picture from the Gypsy video? It has… https://t.co/opMlH7VAGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[While training I lost Poochie!! #OmegaRubyNuzlocke https://t.co/dMPp7EDImh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is election day here in Los Angeles.  It's a small election for LAUSD school board, but an election none t… https://t.co/pqc4vGOJc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a Great @SouthernMissMBB Win Tonight Over UTSA And also the @SouthernMissWBB Win also Against UTSA, Let’s keep… https://t.co/69v3tneGWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bogie711 @JoshDrown @RyanKoenigsberg @Chiefs @PatrickMahomes Nope you don't get to use the choke narrative anymore… https://t.co/amRnEkgYac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheels rolling to Mount Olive today for a three game set with a top 20 program - time to go to work! #BusinessTrip #PunchTheClock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget that Plastics made from #hemp are biodegradable. The future can be bright if we are willing to create… https://t.co/rfAbwjKLTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shopping with my wife and realized that not only am I her emotional support animal but also her guard dog carrying the wallet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUDDLAW @PuebloAPuebloPR @TorresGotay Nunca en la historia del Congreso ha habido ese aval (pero nada esta escrito… https://t.co/97lymYH8C2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalWomensDay — thinking of you: Melone, Glenna, Shay, Kit, Marcy, Constance, Kim, Abbie, Myka, Gab, Lyd… https://t.co/CpGpf5KPvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had an iPhone for like 3 months and tbh I still have no idea how to use it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ssjb4Brandon @shane_holmberg His own fault. I don't envy him for one microsecond. #NeverGoFullHolmberg #IfYouDoYouWontRecover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Cr8 @DanGrazianoESPN I am pretty confident in Mayock’s ability to identify talent and I think Gruden will listen… https://t.co/wutWEEhlH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTimefurlulz Comical.....YOU are the one that doesnt know what political science is....and I am the fool......You… https://t.co/e3q25e0Uus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OWENSCHEEZCAKE This is fucking awesome! I would of made him more yellow but still this is awesome. Also belt looks great! ❤️😭❤️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad you enjoyed Mark. I will trade you one Season of Life for a copy of your The Little #MeToo Book?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxScoreInsider Having an option to play at home in a huge playoff game that you earned the right to host is a no-… https://t.co/X1W16SPBG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Theresacaputo is a liar and a fraud. Totally full of shit. 1000000000% Cold Read this you feckless cunt. 🖕🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Goals ***Boyfriends Talk Long Distance Love https://t.co/Eqi0lQpg09 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love people on Twitter that hesitate to use their name, state, bring it, A man doesn't know How long a shadow he… https://t.co/lU4TcGcBS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KQ98TonyNight you're right, I'll just cite Siri.  Thanks, the older generation knows everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelaninLaced @ANGRYADVISER @NagaKarat @cpm_rulz @_Uranus93 @AOC Privilege doesn't exist, what you got to do is get… https://t.co/YkaUXhQ4mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @QuickenLoans I used your loan calculator - STOP CALLING ME. if I was going to refinance it will never be with you. Annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarianGoodman tympanum taut to eagle vault as aught the author https://t.co/rmPOr6gMbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksusportsfans @Jahdrum @nate_bukaty Wait? Is this idiot talking about the 80lb kid who ran in to the 200+ lb ku pl… https://t.co/0KmFzEims0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC presents as a tax scofflaw.  My intuition is that this was a scam subsidized by tax dollars which didn't succe… https://t.co/1ir0rXrKtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RaiderNation    What if the #raiders traded the 35th pick for AB and then traded the 27th pick OBJ!  Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @Trump454545 we send food and a down there they burn it I think that's a disgrace to America when will we step in]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Six Favorite Springsteen Songs: 1. Janey Don’t You Lose Heart 2. Tougher Than the Rest 3. Out in the Street 4. N… https://t.co/Nov0VnKLbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onthewinside The worry is valid. We have to be supportive for her to gain experience and be able to make those mis… https://t.co/c4ZjYswtNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CliffordAsness It is incredible how limited the critical analysis is that goes into these pieces. I guess we shoul… https://t.co/bw2sRuAvD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #valentinesday2018 to me My wife rocking my @alleniverson jersey 😍 #beautifulwife  #mywife #couplegoals @ Dec… https://t.co/OQcymrn9j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjmoudy in case Mason forgets, I told him y'all better bring plenty of bug spray to the Bay. Gnats will carry you off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[5G will help close the wealth gaps as the poor get net-based education and medical services @FareedZakaria]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN But you ended up with a Texan...that’s a victory my friend. #EIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's almost like MLB teams don't start the year playing markedly worse teams like they do in the SEC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timadkins1_tim @TCS37 @Sasquatch80 @KMowery11 @anghell1992 @JimmysSeafood Hit me up when you get in town. I live d… https://t.co/EGlp2Oo9rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torrancew @arrdem @david_ @jmpspn But... fear the guy dual wields, cross holstered, gators!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinScheidhau1   Your Cameo for Kevin is ready! https://t.co/pQi7lwtZUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukefan9207 If he’s smart he’ll sit out the rest of the season to protect his draft stock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @CarletonCollege alum @jimkchin and Elizabeth Chai Vasarhelyi for winning an Academy Award at… https://t.co/cPr4xqy5VC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everybodys success tweet have to start with... “I was sleeping and woke up to..” Or “I was out doing somet… https://t.co/zJYQPvftEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diannaeanderson @NaomiKritzer I don't know - windows look completely different]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas used to be outside from 9-5 like a job. Not going in unless I’m thirsty. And I might jus drink out the water hose 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayingPolitix @MelissaDaly326 @Carolchapman192 @Kookman123 https://t.co/Jie6k6T9Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#civilwarhistory #civilwarpainting #GeorgeCochranLambdin https://t.co/RuUttvB10j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanonymousMan Talk about great drinking deals, Bucklands, SUNY Oswego on St. PATRICK'S DAY  .5 cent beer starring… https://t.co/Uuff2u4k1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winthrop 50 Saugus 48 Vikings get the win vs a well coached @SaugusSachemsAD team! Vikings we’re led by Jr Engjell… https://t.co/44CHop4hwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear HS athlete,   S/O to all the High school State champs over these past weekends! It’s such a great honor and Hu… https://t.co/eywrbT3WVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVOUUUU! ❄️ ☃️ é felicidade que não cabe em mim, gratidão! 🙏🏼 https://t.co/pcB6PAwPED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debbieballentin @shayneholl @carrieunderwood I think what really triggered you Nashville folks is that we don’t pl… https://t.co/cJfKJ0BZpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does this chart suggest about loyalty to party among House and Senate members? https://t.co/ZJgeYrmoZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compressor Before Equalizer or After EQ - Highly Recommended Pro Mixing ... https://t.co/Wkdv6eDEMA via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay! Today and every day, let’s celebrate the innumerable contributions of women and girl… https://t.co/CFCCRBPC0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que triste debe ser estar en el lugar de un chavista, mas de todos esos que salieron del pais y ahora dicen no querer al gobierno actual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamDefness45 Bro I spent 600 on wax last night. It’s tax return season but still I gotta stop lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice isn't blind. #PaulManafort  The Latest: Manafort sentenced to 47 months in prison https://t.co/ygSN1Wjtul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Madrid without their leader and talisman tonight. A man they turned to time after time during the last three s… https://t.co/RHsakB6DdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now more than ever I appreciate President Lincoln for his efforts to hold together the Union.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoxofWhite I am all for a change in the healthcare system in the US, but until then insurance is key]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a nightmare, where they found Rook dead and I swear to god if that’s a preminission I’ll snap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT Since you’ve taken “free HBO for life” away from my Unlimited Plus plan, I will soon take my Unlimited Plus (a… https://t.co/jACXLuPgVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyrayb467 @mike_balentine @lailoniroberts @MauriceRoberso3 @travissbarton @melaniepayneTHD @JasonGDHRMD228 Welcome aboard!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahVH And that’s true whether the contractors are private prison companies or county jails that charge ICE more… https://t.co/FYJLXWiEAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two shows left people! You have two more chances to see @ETCplays presents American Idiot. You WILL miss the BIGGES… https://t.co/6XdogBUNUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreamwatts Quirky is much better, it along with whimsy, and serendipity are 3 of my fave words. Well done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Apocalypse Dreams by The Eighth State Brewing Company/@ResidentCulture at @StateEighth — https://t.co/qFPTbkrLmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingNewsCo So she is doing the major storylines for the women of wwe raw and wwe smackdown live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Islam is a political movement masquerading as a religion.”  Admiral James Lyons, U.S.N.   https://t.co/dn5kwXybNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can do all things (God wants me to do) through Christ who strengthens me..”  Phil 3:14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of our national emergency ... IS THERE ENOUGH KETCHUP?? https://t.co/s3U0fx2wrW via @HuffPostPol #DonTheCon… https://t.co/d94b4MtN6f]]></document></documents></author>