<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The general public really believes that “going straight to Netflix” is a bad thing..... broke people not in the ent… https://t.co/3HPLwsYGJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamuelAdamsBeer @cameronsaenz More then half of your variety packs wouldnt https://t.co/iFpCIPh9gN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Program Analyst - https://t.co/ixj9KRpLER #WomenSTEM #aviation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_fairywren Garupe. From Silence. Not sure who he should be paired with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @USS_Alabama Battleship Memorial Park in Mobile, AL https://t.co/iUhlPN9qQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Jussie Smollet did is effed up on so many levels. But don’t let his act of selfishness detract away attention… https://t.co/9sgSpRUV9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you come out of your comfort zone, you find peace. 🙏🦈🧜🏽‍♀️ 💙 Am I right willsmith ?  #sharks #scubadiving… https://t.co/ylTtujzAaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post walk snuggle with my lil buddy Lola. #dogsofinstagram #papillon @ East Sandwich, Massachusetts https://t.co/JfjjP0eN6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BJB_Outreach @pinpuller @JustinTrudeau Can you mansplain or to me I clearly don’t know what it means. https://t.co/XCkfMv0DwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macrockets @JohnnaCrider1 @FitzsimmonsK @28delayslater @rm_natasha @NuovaRealta @alledrive @S_Padival @Rec1pr0city… https://t.co/1OVT1i4yHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful weekend stay renaissancephillyhotel #hospitalitydesign #interiors #renphilly #interiordesign #hotel… https://t.co/w6LKrdcfKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinEnochs @dylanmatt When I was 3 I was quarantined to my grandfather's farm for whooping cough. He had corn ras… https://t.co/nYNbMUrHEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leanne67403488 @SickNotWeak @heylandsberg Then you’re not on the right ones or the right dose. You have to work cl… https://t.co/2zzc0Yn2UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙 wow, year 25. Can’t believe when you were 25, I was turning 3. So blessed with a dad like you. Happy birthday dad… https://t.co/MoAX9gWbtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobsimpson42 You mean because everyone in South Dakota had to Google what is a derrick operator?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently reading Awakened in bed and casting my vote for @jamessmurray in the #ShortyAwards. Eek! So suspenseful!… https://t.co/pWcmeO2Tp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m sure it will be a giant dumpster fire of a campaign like last time 🔥🔥 #txlege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this horrifying account: "I've witnessed the devastating effects of Trump's Global #GagRule: Congress must ACT… https://t.co/tP0qkkfUIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest job you will ever have and so many resent and belittle it. Makes me sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marmeaux @wolfblitzer @CNN @realDonaldTrump I think it's just the idea of his name on a wall that has him so excit… https://t.co/DLqCETdEBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have surgery in 3 weeks and then have to have 2 weeks minimum off work. Company would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally someone mentions this hot, hot line. Tegan believes the Castillos are going to kill her and she figures OK… https://t.co/PibeR7Knki]]></document><document><![CDATA[I currently have too much on my plate. I don’t have time for negativity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox 9 anchor Jeff Passolt sues state for a slip and fall at the Capitol. Cvhttp://strib.mn/2TNjFUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I think my dad is a Kim and Ron shipper now lol We watched a few episodes together and it was the one where K… https://t.co/ZhSIlRtpS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone just asked me if I always go back to “Lebanesean” (aka lebanon)....bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @abracadabraNY This is BS.  If Jane really did them, she would open the file print them and release. What i… https://t.co/DDgrEHdVzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elquenoduerm @MadeCaracas EL UNICO AVE DE RAPIÑA, CARROÑERO QUE CONOCE EL MUNDO, NO NICARAGUA, EL MUNDO, ES EL CAR… https://t.co/DZlOzLEUNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tu_Pueblo_Grita @JMVivancoHRW No solo la verguenza...debemos los Venezolanos levantar la voz !!! Nuestros Derechos… https://t.co/Fb8MfOxmZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys really need to subscribe, there are some really amazing podcasts coming your way soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @FionaMorgan79 Glad you are feeling better Bri! And you slept!! Everything ok now Fi??? Dry those tears...😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles @Eagles @greenlegion @BleedingGreen  That's my QB! https://t.co/Z0Z9PEbufI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Spike Lee's.speech. His grandmother saved up 50 to put him through college. #Oscars https://t.co/TLMlyBgMA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting impatient @colton when are you gonna jump the fence ?? GIVE THE PEOPLE WHAT THEY WANT 😂😭 #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want anything.. But if I can have 1 thing I’d want you to keep your promises and seal them with a promise ring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekPa56710094 @meerbakker @Edgaston1490gm1 @dahut07 @Alexa17101614 @maype7 @LOYALFAN1 @ollivier_yves… https://t.co/4NiDTAl2wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipotlecoyote I think you missed the point of the consternation. Most people who don’t want to use Word are using… https://t.co/NY5dBHfGje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also here’s this because...we’ll just because, okay bye. @GraysonDolan @EthanDolan https://t.co/RyNKIzTXbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimccub I have no desire to watch it but just some quotes from the interview I’ve read in articles he sounds like… https://t.co/l1HwwdumSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ass just tryna be more involved in the gay community but my town got nothing goin on ... 😭🏳️‍🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC Please tell me you are NOT supporting a bill that will take someones guns… https://t.co/PDWbXw4ks1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And took orders with the manager watching. Then he started adding money to their donation wall.We sat down and eat… https://t.co/pe8mEle339]]></document><document><![CDATA[ENTER TO WIN ***2 FREE TICKETS*** TO EFOREST 2019 + $100 GIFT CARDS!!! 🔜💫🌲💜🌌 Forest is SOLD OUT! Last chance to get… https://t.co/T3T8sotbEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maxim_Journal @veritasmaximus7 Face Book just  blocked me again and I told them they are a NWO organization that l… https://t.co/g1dyqXDpJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosybud123 @Fetal_Mistake Yes..and they were ugly as hell!! She just automatically thinks everyone wants what she… https://t.co/33vjzm7Epe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking news to wake up to. The #AmberAlert may have been startling but it was to try to save an 11-year-old… https://t.co/qTKgu4O46I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Curry_Barbie I just tried a whole new recipe and swapped it with pink Himalayan salt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheweeee!!!  I feel good!!! 💪🏼🏋🏼‍♀️👊🏼 75 min workout and 13 min in the sauna....and no, I couldn’t stay in that thi… https://t.co/uU2smQu1DJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sabotage” is now #trending on @audiomack . 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾 Stream it now!   #thedimeseries🏀 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/nV0Fw155sY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahLemmm Ok!!! Maybe next weekend we can do something for St Patty’s day!! Just text me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriminalShow 106 are my numbers for today. This is FUN! Thanks for doing it and the prize is awesome-Phoebe’s voic… https://t.co/oTittrgmUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATTILAga // @FRONZ1LLA // @chrisattila // bryanattila // @kalanattila 😈😈💯👽  (staysickrecordings) (@vicesbrnd 'Hell… https://t.co/xpyR2ZOzMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJakubiak @joshgriffith59 @YandR_CBS @CBSDaytime Excuse me? Lot”s  of what coming my way?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Cioccia completed the Princess Half Marathon! Time 03:04:06 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/Y8jRGbSeAM #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[The older I get the less I care about having friends 🤷🏽‍♀️ I got one real one dassit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moonsta40363784 @plumperpass If you’re going to be negative about the porn you don’t pay for I’ll happily block yo… https://t.co/ECsC6rhsOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder - today is the last day to order MEMC gear (March 10th).  . . A huge thanks to everyone that’s ordered, I’… https://t.co/PsO2K9VfCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilydoesntweet I often do this as well. It's my typical Wednesday night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Data suggests journalism and PR jobs didn’t go away - they just changed their names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about Twitter? Back-to-back posts by folks with totally different opinions/perspectives after watchi… https://t.co/Bm0L59FpBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you biggie, my sunflower sister! 🌻 I love you lots and lots and miss you bunches! College wouldn't have been… https://t.co/bDfhHonUkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharedMotivati1 @leeleeb50 Historians will basicly treat Trumps 4 yrs like the accident it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever YOUR friends tell you in CONFIDENCE, especially if it's PERSONAL does not and should not be told to your B… https://t.co/yTJCbZipcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[CASUAL REMINDER FOR MY FOLLOWERS:  -I drunk tweet   -I’m 90% retarded   -I like memes   -Zionist   -conservative… https://t.co/fK3iwWFC3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, Room 35 was awarded our 6th attendance award for the school year! Last week we had 100% attendance! It m… https://t.co/CdvYUlVmHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A joyful heart is good medicine, but a crushed spirit dries up the bones,” Proverbs 17:22.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The "Location is Everything" episode of @DocumentaryNow gets me everytime 🤣🤣🤣🤣 #DocumentaryNow https://t.co/S7zVcjZG6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weinsteinlaw @funder We can use thoughts &amp; prayers.... that’s working so well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eager to see the next move in this fiasco. @Puglaas will you hold a press conference?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the biggest bully of all, the greatest pro when it comes to harassing others is whining that he is being harasse… https://t.co/ttRHYThU67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massive fire breaks out at DeKalb County office complex; business owners say they've lost everything. The details o… https://t.co/CIISUMCOf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airess @PoliticalShort @michellemalkin @CPAC Treasure?  No.  More like fools gold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UVA fans remind me of NOVA Dallas Cowboy fans. #UnlessYouWentThere #OrHadFamilyWhoWentThere 🤷🏼‍♀️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting with area Mayors/First Selectman this morning to discuss the Governor’s proposed budget. https://t.co/bfkhg9kJnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @GoMocs for the shoutout to @TA_FutureReady during halftime. @tyneracademy students and @UTChattanooga,… https://t.co/jGMnRoYm2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if Obama had called for a #FakeNationalEmergency to enact the Affordable Care Act. We'd have seen Republican h… https://t.co/7kff9WZRDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Colour Red. Source: Tumblr. Describe the color red without using the ward red. #funniness #snicker #smirk… https://t.co/lbUJZag59h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beverly Hills 90210 is on Hulu.  I’ll be binge watching and sobbing for the next couple of days. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DanCrenshawTX First, thank you for your service to our country sir.  #HR1 is bad public policy!  The Dems are met… https://t.co/5m0jaFJVcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend and I have been saying this too. Let's start from scratch and fix the toxic things that have taken o… https://t.co/jLAMeuitA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkempcpa I'll be surprised if anti-semitism isn't named and made prominent in some way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadianLabour No point writing to mine, Elizabeth May. She doesn't believe in unions or support workers' rights.… https://t.co/qGIC24t3VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, what a good cat! And he’s getting spa treatment daily, huh?  Well, ginger cats really are sweet, and I’m sure h… https://t.co/hYZ4J7FfTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a certain kind of sadness that accompanies eating the last bagel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FisherP22 @emmie_cowie @MikeCrawshaw4 @westcottpiemont @RedSoil23 @tgminish @darty_sp On the bright side it could… https://t.co/7Tyl7W1UpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking for a friend if anyone’s free tomorrow night, currently taking applications]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flylabrock @user47 Y’all in TUL are great. I wish others would take your lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes sense... I do not understand why women get all upset if a doucher hits on... https://t.co/y5LcO5TZqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is upon us and that means April is near!  Which also translates that  Winter is coming! I can’t wait to share… https://t.co/e3hEj4i6f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you “model your math”, does it look like this? Why is it important for your Ss to know how to model their math… https://t.co/YTIzOChZGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Maher I am a middle class American proud of it, don't seem to fit in your world.  Your comment about us middle… https://t.co/OkvkC5CBtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Civic Theatre of Allentown - @civicallentown in Allentown, PA https://t.co/E7L2b6q45H]]></document><document><![CDATA[***ROW HOMES/ Townhouses available: 350pw for ((75 prims)) 3 storys + Basement ***SPACIOUS STUDIO APARTMENTS (worth… https://t.co/7ValIHkG4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niaphotography @ImNathanBennett @BEACASSO @ItsThreeSixty I know what you meant boo don’t worry 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mijisoficial Mijis le hemos admirado su valor, su tesón, y las ganas de defender sus convicciones. Solo le pedimos… https://t.co/7bv9Sqvtko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovAbbott during #WBCA luncheon said he visited South TX as a priority when running for gov. Said he was in Laredo… https://t.co/RESdkGULsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s dinner was made exclusively for #teamallende by non other than @familiaallende aka #cheflouieg #prokchoos… https://t.co/a2q9hIqYnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir #flight523 this crew is the best!!!!  Will and Dennis are first class professionals and made flying t… https://t.co/1whwbdpGXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're not supposed to be here for another month! #surprise https://t.co/dZ5z9w7rkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIDrunks @SIUC Well certainly much less than I guessed. Thank you for the information]]></document></documents></author>