<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TeamJuJu HEART TRANSPLANT WISH hey my sister age 35 with 2 kid is a die hard steeler fan.she would love to come wa… https://t.co/t9Yau5yN7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @Eddieonfox @uhbroncofan @raider_rob24 those to r Kelley jokes almost made me drive off road last night… https://t.co/78d9bG6GbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@314Hoops Hope he is on the Hoosiers radar 🤞#iubb #HoosierNation @IUHoosiers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismcquarrie please cast me I do my own stunts too https://t.co/YXiGH7I6aS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Campbell crossed 5K. Time 00:30:51, pace 09:56 min/mile, est. finish 11:23 am https://t.co/T7QUnbiVun #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xdeep13 100% I don’t agree with everyone saying it’s honorable that he’s waiting for his friends suspension i just… https://t.co/fQ1YbhS73v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovingtonAHS @neller_joe Your article said blue collar people do more difficult math. So now I am confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my mentor, boss and friend @_clow on your retirement. @ TBWA\Chiat\Day Los Angeles https://t.co/T14F5yfj2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a popular cereal called LIFE. I don't know for sure, but a cereal called DEATH probably would not fair as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__gizmo97 @CharlieDaniels Nice to know but are you really going to vote for something like that? Because no matter… https://t.co/HfkKRrFa6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina is 21-6-1 in their last 28 games &amp; those 43 points in 2019 are the most in the NHL over that span… https://t.co/p7mZElAt52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Sale! Great Prices! Order Today! Dragons, T-Shirts, New Stuff! Oh My! (https://t.co/z2JZiw6LLR)  Please share… https://t.co/2BOqU2QwUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWE has effectively cooled off a potential mega face heading into WrestleMania in back to back years. Braun last ye… https://t.co/IsZmpoIJ5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $2,289.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/V5OXb0VdK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It astounds me that you can take an ordinary Starbucks, put it in an airport, and it suddenly runs 80% slower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They put some huge fish in that lake ahead there. @ Drayton Mills https://t.co/hdZwBuijDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newly listed Victorian in Atkinson, NH for $799,900.  Let me know if you would like to see it.  https://t.co/moABY6UBvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, the digital de-aging technology, especially on Sam Jackson, is SCARY FLAWLESS. 😱🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TropicalOdouls Crazy bro I had an intense dream about my epic battle of Go Fish. Hit the opponent with the checkma… https://t.co/clEYEPBXhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Huddle_House56 @DrRJKavanagh @juliedawson2802 @MassRoots @GreenCultureMMJ It's only probable cause if THEY smell i… https://t.co/CkULqDXEXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This came up in my Facebook memories this am. It's me and Clay County's Richie Farmer, around 1987, I believe.… https://t.co/AiCnGoOFXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HAIMcrown @HAIMtheband They respect mainland Europe more than this lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[An American Tail: Fievel Goes West is a enjoyable nostalgic fueled movie. The animation is still fantastic, wonderf… https://t.co/cn3Kmzbgak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemBourbon @irenecolth @NaveenMalli @DanteAtkins True. However Detroit's population also dropped 24k in those four… https://t.co/2RRvmmdoXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyjanefox "Is a dream a lie if it don't come true, or is it something worse?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good read.  Nine Inch Nails' 'The Downward Spiral': 8 Things You Didn't Know https://t.co/3z4URDqKjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reduced to one lane around-the-clock til tuesday 2 / 19 in #Durham on Roxboro St NB at Geer St #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What God is great like our God who works wonders. Who bathes the skies in beauty and pours grace under.… https://t.co/opp1WfDnCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year I want to remind myself what it will be like to be an old man and have to piss every 15 minutes, so I go… https://t.co/wNjQmZAaVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maleandproud @atpopticon @Shxndhim @RyanAFournier @kanyewest Lmao yeah, I’m sure you’re a big fan of the oppressed… https://t.co/k4JGPwNzwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asanderford @ErinGraceOWH I thought same thing went I went to pick pizza at @MamasPizzaOmaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cool_breeze26 As long as we agree raisins have no place in a civilized man’s trail mix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is something I’ve not seen before! @ Bonnie Springs Ranch https://t.co/eRIllaYEW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSchremmy Nice. I'm embarrassed to say that I haven't had a beer today. I'll have plenty on Saturday's bar crawl.… https://t.co/0Ru1e2FF0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samatki84191469 @ahptik A documentary better than Nickelback: The Road to Success is unBeliebable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon @itsBayleyWWE @SashaBanksWWE @WWE @BillieKayWWE @PeytonRoyceWWE @NiaJaxWWE @TaminaSnuka… https://t.co/jwWAupfSNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDPattillo @cadenceofmylife He’s a damn fool ... @POTUS @WhiteHouse https://t.co/xRIKc3RaFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_R_Berna @MARINE_99ZULU I agree w/ @RepDanCrenshaw here, I am a lifelong Republican and individualist/conserva… https://t.co/JcqLXiepTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alita: Battle Angel”. Eiza González #alitabattleangel #austintexas #moviestills #ricotorresphoto… https://t.co/bdU1hLGXqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $25 Rush tickets for #AliceByHeartMCC  at @MCCTheater on @TodayTix! Unlock here: https://t.co/D3g01xfJOm #TodayTixRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCBO @CorbySW @TheRecRoomCa Done! See you next week! #Irish #Whiskey #Toronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Liberals didn't see it coming. Most people with an ounce of common sense saw it. I guess the gender appr… https://t.co/vVDtJ0PZW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hoping that this expensive wake up call stops all the fake news that’s rampant in the country!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteSouza Because other incoherent, illiterate and insensitive persons voted for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lucky to be able to DREAM. But most important being able to see em.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poole: We can disagree on opinions, but we need to agree on facts.  The fact is that Alabama’s infrastructure “is d… https://t.co/i5B14rDzWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did we get #Tulowinsky to wait for DiDi if we were going to go after #Machado? And aren't we a little top heavy… https://t.co/6TSlCZOQ1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanneBrunner @AaronNolanNews @dj45williams @NatWaltersWX @PatWalkerWX @KARK4News @erniepaulson Just me and my fi… https://t.co/TCkPVv1xz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman Her resignation would be a blessing for this country. But I assume it’s a fine and move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why we can not have logically based discussions. The “Shut Up And Sing” mentality can not sand man.… https://t.co/g31PlLBwqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon world, guess what came out today?  That’s right - - THE SUN - -  remember that!!  Seem like a month… https://t.co/SMCy7KyusO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren No thank you Lieawatha. I will nvr vote 4 a Socialist @TheDemocrats = stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirleyhenrydc I need some advice from you my wife is a victim of her employer they file the I-9 form checked box… https://t.co/r8DrSJBtj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Girardi and Adam Erne we ebith day to day. That fully explains Jan Rutta’s emergency recall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a beautiful child. Lorazepam and God keep me happy I saw a neurologist today but you can do this on your o… https://t.co/LY6gnVgJLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wi11iedigital @DebsianTM @KateDavidson @chrislhayes Define "modern". I'm really afraid you'll make me pre-modern. ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPGChile  Un fuerte abrazo en la distancia ! Cualquier cosa GRANDE O PEQUEÑA q hagamos HOY por Venezuela y su pueb… https://t.co/Du6MudGhLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @Alyssa_Milano Keep those talking points coming. If you repeat it often enough only you will still believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to take the time to thank all our Freight team! All were helpful with our new associates, creating stro… https://t.co/IdCD3ETgNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump I vote yes! If 3 million more say yes than the naysayers, do we still lose? The a… https://t.co/rtQG6brX8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEJeepMafia koozie works south of the border as well. #jeepmafia https://t.co/XFVxdxv6bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulRoundy1 @GeraldKutney @PremiseFalse @curryja To me that still leaves the question of early 20th century warmin… https://t.co/GOTnjKgrMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is happening. But no hearts for faceoff dots now??!!! @FWKomets @ECHL @KalamazooWings https://t.co/6xjE62Kb8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rots_ricky @ReduxitSpem LOL his plane just got back to Ottawa Wonder where he was?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone needs a bf you can gladly have mine....so done....so don’t have patience for him anymore......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ These kind of people need severe psychology help. Their way of thinking is a sickness. They have no concept of morality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a constant struggle of wanting to not be alone and wanting to never leave my bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebWiest Just a small timer here so no catalog yet, if you want price sheet and more info I’ll send ya a DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously I checked spoilers and know the outcome of #CBBUS2 but I’m only watching the finale now.. interested to s… https://t.co/3s47F7srug]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to have one try this with me. Normally I would try to deescalate, but for this I would make an excepti… https://t.co/oCbWmRymWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why! What is the mainstream media if not an advocate and cheerleader for the left?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cd_theguy @BabyFatMackin It’s not official yet 😂🤣😂 gotta make sure my reputation stay up]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has added yet another layer of confusion   https://t.co/yhZWUIXDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been asked if I was a sociopath 3 times and I don’t even know what that is lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grapesbygarza See Matt that’s where you are very wrong. Most of those “making bank” have worked their fucking asse… https://t.co/x7dnoJcly1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please ignore my PTUs but turner brought home his first artwork today and I’m beaming proud https://t.co/z48lgKbC8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond @MaskedSingerFOX @accessonline @KitHoover @iamscottevans That’s why we don’t tell little Sisters anyth… https://t.co/dWF1zpMQKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate mean people I’m always the person to talk to the person that’s literally sitting alone at the club. Y… https://t.co/tcBK3spFyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/cs1pq8hNUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So damn happy for the guys. A gritty, gutty, home win. #Nebrasketball #GBR https://t.co/neGnddXv3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lent season is the only time I eat Filet-O-Fish at @McDonalds and I can’t wait to eat a couple of them on Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinsonjoel124 @NRA @RepDougCollins You’re white white Americans owned slaves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades para el ser más perfecto creado por Dios ❤️❤️❤️❤️😘😘😊😊😊🙌🙌🙏🙏🙏👩👩👩 en Nassau County, New York https://t.co/BKyGXL9L8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/QCJspk5asy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice little pat on the back today - #SXSW can be a grind but it’s great to see the bands appreciate our efforts. https://t.co/uhcUDJRbcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mofo done had his bag of chips for 2+ hrs. https://t.co/VTRJ832S4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycweboy Hate to mention this, but it's going to end several political careers. It's the "win" that kills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahBeetham Meanwhile, people are busy working to remove &amp; relocate more Confederate monuments! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatyTuya @Mty_Leones @AdrianDeLaGarza @PRI_Nacional @multimediostv @TelevisaMty Lo que no está lleno de baches est… https://t.co/yHGc8BzaiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patimoma56 Muy buenos días Paty y feliz miércoles saludos cordiales cuídate mucho y que disfrutes de este día ,!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctrozier11 @a_wilson958 If you chose velveeta you grew up with too much money]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your parents got you the ZooPals plates when you were a kid, you were spoiled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a few names here that probably represent sincere objections to use of Executive Powers.  HOWEVER there are… https://t.co/3GfPnWkUL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIZZSHAYBABY22 @realwhitegirl1 @loveandhiphop @IAMSAFAREE I don’t see what’s wrong with him giving them a heads up… https://t.co/HFiB82WN1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stepped over a huge mental hurdle today, it’s only up from here .. literally 🙏🏾🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann @Crunk5454 True   A conservative President named Donald Duck wouldn’t change the 30 year old talking points for Democrats to use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregNorberg Why does anyone listen to her?  I mean, really... why listen to a nitwit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody on Twitter is butthurt about one political view or the other. Butthurt about what this person thinks or t… https://t.co/6THn2rW0Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well American Crappie Trail pulled out a hidden gem to most (I’m sure the local folks don’t like us saying this).… https://t.co/QeS3DUNuP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can still remember tons of Steeler Fans hitting New Orleans for Super Bowl 9.  Probably were just a hand full of… https://t.co/GX55LBT2hT]]></document></documents></author>