<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Omg my brother in law just decided to act the fool after like 8 years .. Ugh. Men are trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is #WomensHistoryMonth! Want to know some ways you can celebrate these amazing women in history? Start here: https://t.co/rh2QzhHjDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiii! Who are you today? I'm a musician / poetess / artist / yoga teacher in Mpls ♥️ https://t.co/kPW9M51nVk  Fresh… https://t.co/B3KzVeSqlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeCountyDA Hello @LeeCountyDA I hope Lee County is safe. I am a video producer with The Associated Press Has anyo… https://t.co/w3NuOJofDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always be open to learning! #SundayFunday #SundayThoughts #SelfcareSunday #learn #selfcare https://t.co/CGWIQO2ScA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rich people probs 😪 glad he found the asshole. Imagine living in a house where it’s sooooo big you hear crickets ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raremaester Probably because he had a great chance to follow the rules , get an education and a provide for his family 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WalkingDead day everyone! I’m excited-but nervous also-The Whisperers are so freaking scary!! #Alpha is horr… https://t.co/MaxlPEjCmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[my radio show is back !! check it out wednesdays at 1 pm est - 91.5 fm or https://t.co/cv0vIlFwaJ !! i put the play… https://t.co/2n9riyz2Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr #LockThemUp #TrumpLies #EqualityForAll #FAKENationalEmergency #FakeTrumpEmergency… https://t.co/mWVjECZ0WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Brian, how false are your teeth? Looks like lying comes easy 4 u.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @mizj626n Adam, stop airbrushing Ronald Reagan.  If the political climate in the 80s was like the cu… https://t.co/aCOrwa4KKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when talking to your own kids! 💔😞 @ Harlingen, Texas https://t.co/3KMRhvsE8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrzphd @eveningmag @teatro_zinzanni Bless you!!  Let me know how I can #Volunteer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, this is the most honest and intimate @jennylewis interview I’ve ever read. Killer job, @jonahweiner. 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always ask employers what’s key to hire and what are the qualities that they look for in candidates.  I was prett… https://t.co/HdAPrer3pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Valentine's Day in style. @ Maggie's Farm Rum https://t.co/SWeNt9wIWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be getting ready for work pero aqui sigo acostadita y entro alas 8 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see me in bowie you don’t really see me just look the other way 🙃🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @DIYGirls for inventing a solar powered tent backpack prototype to help the homeless. #LHD2019… https://t.co/kJ3oPI9Wxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What @LindseyGrahamSC is really saying is if you are a Republican what is good for the goose IS Not good for the gander.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight #MagicKingdom — I don’t know the exact time but I do know I’ll be seeing you again this summer — just sta… https://t.co/PILKHu76MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reba not wanting to believe this is a scam, but am getting concerned. Any ideas on how to actually reach your customer service?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Jordyn and Tristan scandal is nothing but the work of Kris Jenner https://t.co/NF77BckGqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriaLeibig VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥 LI… https://t.co/Sjqomu011h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher how dare you put down republicans the way you do. you are an arrogant, pompous wind bag! #proudredstate]]></document><document><![CDATA[END 1Q  Mahar made a small run after being down 11-2, but the Senators climbed back to get within three points befo… https://t.co/5rl6CgsuNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_hedlund @arron_hedlund I love ❤️ you have to let others help me out with this please thank @Kimberl32110716… https://t.co/QkguG5vRJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@OtterClaire describes @jeremydeller’s “We’re here because we’re here” project to commemorate the Battle of Somme.… https://t.co/JiCAAFsFkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Lyft is an straight Rice Rocket playing house music and I am living  my full San Francisco childhood right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillip_mhlongo CHANGE 4 THE REAL GOOD IN NOW TIME CUS THE OLD GOOD BECAME BAD ITS TIME TO CHANGE FOR THE BETTER I… https://t.co/JYwH0ewQL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marnely_Murray @freshnewengland @DestSalem True!  The Salem Film Fest is one of the best in the country. And Salem… https://t.co/l7dwuBwRWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_mathias @KenziDreamBigTs @a_dawn1102 @SheriffChody @lt_gray @JamesCraigmyle @PenceWilco @08_kenzi Yay, Jill! Hope to see you there!! 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Have you seen the statistics on your lies?  That’s disgraceful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found out over the weekend that i won a sort of big scholarship for college next year and i’m so proud of myself,… https://t.co/Ro48ATWFSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my least fav #oscars look: Roma Star Yalitza Aparicio in @OfficialRodarte. Sorry, I know she’s young and a newc… https://t.co/scITybHE71]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh. Drove by Jiffy Lube on way to doctor, no one there. Come to Jiffy Lube after doctor, everyone is here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Look at her imported election. She is a good thing because she is so stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to have been admitted into the @UGAGrady Master’s in Journalism program!! I will be serving as the… https://t.co/YiO23IbPWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how the El Chapo trial shows that the wall doesn’t interfere with drugs crossing the Us-Mexico border, q… https://t.co/J7xhlMnYgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My manager is out for two weeks so I have to fill her position and it’s going to be one hell of a ride so cross you… https://t.co/s53uStt6vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago this man changed history with a gran discovery 😳 https://t.co/smYFj6cMUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My anime collection is slowly but surely growing I have the Studio Ghibli movie collection, Juni Taisen Season one,… https://t.co/TPgwP4VeFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel I honestly think this deserves an unfollow.  What are you nuts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que FALTA DE RESPETO esas declaraciones de hoy en @lafm del tal William Agudelo, sindicalista de Fecode. Definitiva… https://t.co/rGJUKoqTCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvgtweets Do you have a connection to Maine? Love to see stories set here 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no regrets about sitting on the floor of that brewery with that bulldog in my lap. - @me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Watch_Momentum @Mike_Anthony13 @BauerOutage @MiguelCabrera @MLB @Indians @tigers Great story, Clev! 😆😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be unapologetically you. ✊#MondayMotivation from fequalshq #Repost @makerswomen🗣 . #makerswomen #roar #courage… https://t.co/otb6R8qKQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick Cream of Mushroom Soup https://t.co/Ire06ENVjA https://t.co/EkZpZ3SYLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s day to all you sappy bitches out there. *dry heave* @ Little Portugal, Toronto https://t.co/AeAMA8rCYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardseaGrnFilms @MauriceJohnMoro @RocktheCatwalks @KusyKayla @nickbelial @ToAvenge_Film @Dee_Wallace… https://t.co/sTQ2wgvlwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Monday I sat down with former Presidential candidate @hillaryclinton to talk about how women candidates must be… https://t.co/Rapv0tmnQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/2MFoefzZEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 17th bday allie rue!!! hope your day is as wild as u 😜 love you to the moon💖🎈🎉 @allieeruee https://t.co/kFNmjOiDIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silver key wrapped in red garnet chips and a few crystal beads to catch the light.  This key hangs on a 24 inch lea… https://t.co/kX5RIi44t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKSubban1 @Simmonds17 @PredsNHL Heartbroken about the trade but I think Simmer can do great things for the #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re all friends here... #bestfriends 😋 good lookin’ 👀out pablohassanla for the celebratory dinner tonight!… https://t.co/g48bIgQBSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_DSchulte 2/2 We clean this out every trimester so that it’s manageable. I find that without this, many kids hea… https://t.co/4gvkxW6Lvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#9PMRoutine,  #LIVEPD,  Locked up 4 the night on this cold rainy night DOVER DE settled in patiently awaiting 4 the… https://t.co/Ed5EFyhlCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewAplegarth Thanks keep grinding and make your goals you so deserve it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Illinois Gov Jabba the Hut raised minimum wage to $15 an hour so prices wi skyrocket.  He's trying… https://t.co/U11KBPQG0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Well there's South Jersey but Newark is not next to Atlantic City. I will check my Monopoly Board   Se… https://t.co/RuVXppG1CM]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we just acknowledge the fact that Nick should’ve ALWAYS been the front man?! He was 100% the hottest, most tale… https://t.co/DC77N1xC2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nurse practitioner treats NKY’s homeless population, starts a bigger healing process. https://t.co/eGF8TmcXAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA I watched the interview with Martha on this issue and the angel seemed satisfied with the teachers a… https://t.co/IhGzwL4YJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oomf on snap is judging me bc I’ve been eating eating -_-  Should I delete????]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 is gonna be a big year for me. 100th year of women’s suffrage, maine’s 200th bday, my 21st birthday, my 1st pr… https://t.co/nqjlq1jVvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re an absolute Friends fan when you go see a musical about the best tv show in the whole wide world! I… https://t.co/jZpCXqxOOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York como me gustas!!!! #tbt #2017 #esqueesasi en Grand Central Terminal https://t.co/utBQSrU33r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think RUP where's pads under his jackets to make him look masculine. It does nothing for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 @dmewing47 Oh, tons...just none I can say in polite company 😣😝😲😭🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he should be brought up on charges winess tampering obstruction of Justice among other charges ARREST HIM IMMED… https://t.co/epDOhjnFyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fuck...so happy for @ariana2525 and @TomSandoval1 on their house #badandboujee #feellikeaproudmom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, 10 years @TwitterNYC @Twitter a lil picture is all I get?! Come on now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenna_moody first @GoldenKnights  game! #vegasborn #goknightsgo https://t.co/cebnKHDx6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde el vamoosebus eumbo a #dc #aad2019 en West Side, New York https://t.co/1eX6XYNZP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got told o could sky dive naked. Let’s just talk about this for a second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when people say they’ll pay money to drink someone bath water , I believe y’all &amp; I’m disgusted 🤢🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Major_K8 @TashMillz Now they do . Yes . But originally they both was doing the same shit &amp; that’s why they can be compared]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Little dogs. When I was a kid our little dog got bit by a big dog. I was able to carry him home. That… https://t.co/COggLZnUJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SellyMSantos2 Omarosa is just another low life publicity hound, she wrote a book, remember? Must be time to get attention again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s just bc I haven’t eaten corn in literally 11 years but whyyyyy do people put that shit in everything is so gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @AOC @CoryBooker @BernieSanders @KamalaHarris 🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out new episode of 2 Da Max Girl Talk w/mbodiedllc.....link 👇🏽  https://t.co/UTKRkKNdk7  #internetradio… https://t.co/NjNlTkx0Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: how often do we even talk about social media in our classes. HUGE MISTAKE if we aren't regularly. Had a convo w… https://t.co/CZ8Teo7ztk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many other issues are coming out, but we can't let this issue drop. Babies are being murdered every day.… https://t.co/Gw4LK5p9Om]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broadway street in Music Row. #nashvilletn 🍺🎤🎸🎼 @ Broadway https://t.co/ppb4rodsG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valencia Trail runners are in for a change of scenery this year. With the weather we’ve seen this past winter seaso… https://t.co/Tew4MwaNF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸This Offer Only For U.S.A👌 Get $1000 Visa Gift Card Now!👉 To get a free $1000 click on the below given link and w… https://t.co/7r0ceFdRiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day 😍🥰😘❤️🧡💛💚💙💜❣️💕💞💓💗💖💘💝💟 #Valentines #ValentinesDay #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OleMissMBB Had no idea kneeling was disrespectful. Someone better let churches everywhere know kneeling before the… https://t.co/MDcEGz8aTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadAboutMeghan Enjoying food and eating for 2. Love her. So real and so classy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes, @NJTRANSIT this suggestive erectile disfunction ad with a woman smiling at a banana IS what I wanted to stare at tonight. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take: if you don’t post about your significant other on Valentine’s day, you could still love them and be grateful for them 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to keep my hands out of the cookie jar 🍪  . . ED trigger warning.... A couple months ago I finally acknowled… https://t.co/KTLCQl4uRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ask a two part.     What are three words that describe how you view yourself at your core?  What are three words… https://t.co/oGHSQFXiGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you even bone broth, bro? ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ We’ve been full steam on the #konmarimethod in our home - which pretty much… https://t.co/S2ajVl2t7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone send me proof about Trump University lawsuites? I am having a disagreement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders says he'll bring a lie detector along when debating Trump  https://t.co/Uc3apjoTpl]]></document></documents></author>