<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@luisbaram @cathmckenna I don't believe in insulting people directly. But I'm not above a subtle dig at their complete lack of intelligence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really grateful to @GMmcmahon and the entire @hyattatlanta team for being an amazing community partner in so many w… https://t.co/g7GLGThdm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonjaReiners @SHODesusAndMero @AOC @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib She’s 100% stupid ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenWern What you are writing scares me because it will incite his base to create havoc and civil disobedience.… https://t.co/vC65NKHsLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duck. Here is the picture to go with the last tweet. #DrunkPete https://t.co/WJSdti14hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLeeZeldin Amazing.  You really believe that a failed trip is a good thing.  I thought Trump was the great deal… https://t.co/g0ePANH2Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORNING......... 😂😂😂😂😂 @ South Laurel, Maryland https://t.co/jirW64wDrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DozaEric @scoopermomma @IHboog @BootscootinGMaw @birdfarmerswife @dbatie @FarmChicJodi @GardnerKatyg8… https://t.co/ZMnZDlHiZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 #beat / #instrumental  https://t.co/kKiTjNNzvC  #producers #needbeats #rappers #rap #hiphop #rhythmroulette… https://t.co/OcbBHusPvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unaiamenabar Estoy seguro que hasta los hijos de los jefes chavistas aborrecen sus apellidos. Son execrados hasta por sus familiares.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missjennnie no one should deal with that type of emotional abuse whatsoever. leave asap even if it hurts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching “ A Private War” and remembered the best, bravest, wisest reporter/writer I ever was lucky enough to… https://t.co/nWgrTLUo7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone will say it better than I but #ClarionLedger’s sports gaffe today is a doozy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero este señor lacalle pou no es abogado ??? Y si así es este otro señor es un nabo !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Cause when you’re a democrat, you keep people unemployed. It’s what you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone driving from Spokane area to the Seattle area on March 8th that has an extra seat? I will pay 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolevasquez17 I doooooo I am feeling a little discouraged right about now 🤯 they pushed my situation back 2 more months I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I’ll be back for what’s rightfully mine. Tu tranquilo y yo nervioso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Suck it warriors hahahaha WADE shut that up real quick happy for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @BlaneyTucker ! Feels like you’ve been 21 for 3 years now😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcmack03 Teams with marquee players are always going to get more attention.  Then people rationalize their points… https://t.co/c2dtlxcuEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molly_knight Are you being serious? Please tell me you are being sarcastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobyVPhoto That looks so pretty!!  I love the rolling hills that are in your part of the world. Always fills my mi… https://t.co/b8m3HEdZw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGarafolo You know who has a winning situation and an upper-echelon QB ... https://t.co/ghqthwHaWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elliebach_ You can come spend time with Izzy and Harley anytime you want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sunset this evening at Calumet Waterworks Park in Calumet, MI. #PureMichigan #KeweenawPeninsula #LakeSuperior… https://t.co/zspE0xYtcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teotihuacan from @NSKNGames - WOW! https://t.co/0Qil2g7Fo0 https://t.co/WybTOs7IYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia help me get to level 8? username: ohmychurro #HQSeason2 https://t.co/k07c2wEIKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love that Brandon Parker is living with Gabe Jackson in miss.that is going to be huge for him. Can’t w… https://t.co/qRwhIOeogZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏃🏽‍♂️💨 ✌🏽 see ya guy queencitysonics #FastestHasselbeck @ GameTime Training Center https://t.co/yJSxG2bcta]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never in my life understand why people feel like cheating is EVER okay.... like who raised you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTFxG This game a wash. I’m waiting for the real best rivalry in college ball to start]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend...Tumbling meet. #newburghtumbling #$75togetinthedoor😳😳 #uebasketballfloorseatsarecheaper @ Old Nation… https://t.co/NTDsla7PTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump putting on a show for supporters.not anyone else.Porto Rico are California are Texas and Har… https://t.co/KktKbfgKQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I want to wash my car cause it’s filthy, but it’s supposed to rain all next week...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Why doesn’t he say where the discovered it?  Was it perhaps because it was found at a legal border cr… https://t.co/DZmiKsFugl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okdiario Jajajajajajajjaj LA MAFIA DE SÁNCHEZ Y SU GOBIERNO, TENGAN CUIDADO PORQUE LO MISMO QUE HACE ESTO EN LAS E… https://t.co/eMlQgcsGBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmanuelMacron Already two of your spec op guys are watching her.  But I am really nervous, Sir, I made a bunch of… https://t.co/gipcttVbGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @johnlegend @itsjulianking I hit rewind a thousand times that night, jesusssssss boy https://t.co/M2GRYDaqjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jo_meek @nycmarathon @Beta_Running @scottrunning @GetInTheMoodNow @komfuel @squirrelsnb_uk @symprove @LedlenserUK… https://t.co/rbCk62QWIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I admire the wonder of a sunset or the beauty of the moon, my soul expands in worship of the Creator. -Ghandi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a @Coles_17 winner too i believe, curious if he has something to add.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For what it is worth, the #TucsonCouncil has twice backed budget goals that added 20 new officers (above their curr… https://t.co/GWeZPC888U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craig_7T2 @ehmarchand This is why in off season the focus is signing a number 1 LHD to take minutes of Weber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re need to rewrite the narrative on Al Jolson too.  And Charlie Chaplin.  And the Marx Brothers.  Etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @RepJayapal He so much as said he could get away with murder. Getting closer to 5th Avenue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattmiller3135 I can definitely see you doing this with your kids and loving every minute of it. I could see you doing it with Chance too]]></document><document><![CDATA[His medical is taken care of, he has a scholarship as long as he’s on campus and his professional value has only ri… https://t.co/i2kwJYS5QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll always be a Sox fan, but right now I hate every member of the front office. I don't even want to go the Opener… https://t.co/Q5caKjO3Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[| it’s what you do in the valley that qualifies you for the mountain top. 🎿🏔⛷| #motivation #inspiration #dreambig… https://t.co/pK7BJ9k91O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRisch @ChrisEvans When you going to jail ? https://t.co/pbP0al3LWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Todders14 @mandy7n Agreed.. not calm but passionate and that’s cool,  maybe I read it all wrong .. I’ll apologize… https://t.co/qKkQVRzaAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarialShayok Very happy for you and your loved ones. So great seeing you in those "old"  pictures today. Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world’s biggest travesty was that the Emporers New Groove was only 1 hour and 20 minutes long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flat_iowa as a one time Iowan... I approve of the fun you are poking here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told my mama I can’t live w out her , now I gotta live w out her 🤞🏾Happy birthday ma #rip 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roydanroy square root of the cost of the simulations in the submitted paper!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadBoiDiddy Lol bro two of them lil fruity drinks you get make you retire]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring a gay 29 year old is kind of weird, I see many of my friends having babies, creating a family or growing thei… https://t.co/SARnvcCJ3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been two days since America has been under a national emergency.   Does everyone have enough ketchup for their country club omelets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotAlexis I'm in DC for the ATL game tomorrow. You got 🍕 recs in this town?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Yup‼️👍🏻 He’s true to his word and doesn’t squirm out like: LBJ, GHWB, BC, GWB, And BHO, all former Presid… https://t.co/6tbTUkMzqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dayidayi Venía llegando de la embajada de EEUU, me acababan de aprobar mi visa de periodista. Había un ambiente fe… https://t.co/NC7mu02r7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[•Islamist groups are, by definition, extremist in that they are totalitarian, non-pluralist and anti-democratic and… https://t.co/O4N0UgsTl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t believe he took this shot with 10 seconds on the shot clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[....damn this made me want to post my dad falling asleep then I remembered I don't have one .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heated toilet seats in this hotel. I’ve really out did myself. Luxury living.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come for the records management, stay for the views. #Oakland https://t.co/5fYKpBIqqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I successfully got this high last night and went to bed at 8:45 and woke up a new man https://t.co/6B1x8LC5C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Px con ataque al estado general, tos sin expectoración, refiere dolor en espalda baja derecha a la altura de su riñ… https://t.co/uSN4QLxVUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ngl I’ve been wanting a bullet proof vest for fashion and now I have an excuse to get one😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so damn lucky. Hall of Fame photographer @Starshot9 took this amazing shot of myself and @BillyJackHaynes yest… https://t.co/nUJB0XFLzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing that @dish anywhere sucks so I can watch 3 seconds at a time of the @USUAggies basketball game. WiFi wor… https://t.co/fgLUrMrVVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancylee2016 @Mgv19118 @BreitbartNews DO IT....sick of fake racist propaganda!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merging delays in #WakeCounty on I 40 WB near Hwy 70 Byp - Exit 310 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump Let’s see how hard they will fight to not protect America. Should be very enlightening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone can have a great idea... it’s the ability to transform that idea into reality, that’s what counts. 💡  • • •… https://t.co/7aHWBteVl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump GOD BLESS YOU JERRY FALWELL JR....AND GOD BLESS OUR COUNTRY..]]></document><document><![CDATA[58-52. East Troy over Turner. 105 left. If things get more interesting I will periscope. East troy ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, I am simply starstruck at the amazing people that God has allowed me to meet in my journeys. #wednesday… https://t.co/YugXb8i0w5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Foley Field - @ugaathletics in Athens, GA https://t.co/RdnOrDTvbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[See Lady Gaga in Las Vegas //hot1047.com/contests/sweeps/see-lady-gaga-in-vegas/]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing stopping me in my Spanish class from being the top student is that I suck at spelling in general]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks fun!  Since I'm never going to get enough likes to do all of these, feel free to comment with a specific numb… https://t.co/GpZ2Pxz5h8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm pulling for Warren, but I'm definitely glass-half-full about Sanders. I'm hopeful he'll help frame some of the… https://t.co/SdHpjPmYA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsianJoeEvans @sharon_rues @Bugahabart Of course! 😂   You're still showing up later though, right Joe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Start the Real Politics  In India Because of Air Strick 🤩🤩🤩Look the Picture🧐🧐 https://t.co/oJuQet0CXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neta que no sé que me estresa, me andan brinque y brinque los ojos jaja 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarianaAmador_r 5 minutos?, creo que no fue ni un minuto... máximo serìan casi 2...  CITA DOBLE ARISTEMO  MUSICAL… https://t.co/F0yE04aLjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t LeJuan James tour or have his own tv show? Bc if I had 2.1 million followers you’d see me in every state in the country belee dat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyTurrill I'm curious if you think this view is applicable beyond big media corps. By this measure, does any… https://t.co/uV8hk9ZF13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chicagofan76 @richland63 @alex_klemenko Robert wont be in Chicago. We have Jon Kay and Adam Engel platooning in CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@931JACKFM @BonJovi Makes sense, considering you give love a bad name. And everything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@march1studios An ICANN WHOIS lookup reveals that both domain names are protected and registered at the same regist… https://t.co/rhGx92YbT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing the #LeavingNeverland documentary how do you ever listen to “Beat It” the same way again?  I mean, it… https://t.co/OIa8xxxOJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donchetoalaire #porquetetatuatis asi es viejon pake los agarre con agua oxigenada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robotic umps? Ok I know I’m gonna seem like a grumpy purist but 🤬🤮🤯 I am curious how they’ll set up the strike zone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm at a red light this morning and as I look to my right and I see an ex GF that I haven't seen in a long time… https://t.co/Q3OMS4UybC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pat LeBron James is set to pass Michael Jordan on the NBA's career scoring list  https://t.co/vbumuty8qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenLRossman @writesloud I don't know if it's weird. It sure is meta.  https://t.co/ewlh8M9tP0]]></document></documents></author>