<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just saw #captainmarvel and contemplating buying a ticket to see it again in half an hour because IT WAS SO GOOD OH… https://t.co/Fj7ZfGDcHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger #FakeNewsByPresidentTrump #BreakingNews #YoureFired]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody at work is jazzed up about the Jonas Brothers and I feel like the puppy who lost his way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HECFBlog Very close. It is RAID -1 (a RAID 0 set that somehow has performance worse than any of the members)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennnn___ @_yourstruuly_ 🤦🏾‍♂️😂😂😂 “Whew Chile “ you should’ve discussed that then this another house now]]></document><document><![CDATA[privebklynlounge NOWWW‼️‼️‼️ @ Privé Bar &amp; Lounge https://t.co/zTph2JA8M4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRSBenji @marymarybeaches @Pittpatva @willfleet @justme2andu @rfmmoran @nancylees @Ehukai411 @KirstenPowers… https://t.co/uSqoH0CylV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally didn’t believe it would end until I physically saw it happen. This is remarkable and really really show… https://t.co/W986s4uvdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinGunther36 https://t.co/GRnWN1Laaa #IStandWithIllhan it’s not anti Semitic to criticize a war criminal soooooo… https://t.co/FtlAcKckh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como mejor película #Roma de 3 que he visto de esta categoría. Seria #YalitzaAparicio la primer mujer actriz mexica… https://t.co/SmH1z8XYvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacmo360 and his date are dressed to kill for the SMA Sweetheart Dance! https://t.co/Td2WterDms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iammiketodd is an awesome pastor! If you guys like his little messages you see on Twitter, check out his actual se… https://t.co/CXtH6QMoz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thunderbrd1 @Powerscorerpg @KKRP2 @GreyhawkChannel Only if he plays to his potential!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: Jessica Carrillo with the layup! SC leads 7-2 with 7:15 left in the 1st Qtr. #swordsup #kcacscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNBARefs explain the blocking foul they just called on Mike Conley please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like writing 3 pages &amp; a video presentation due March 10th on #ErikErikson’s #StagesOfDevelopment &amp;… https://t.co/1PKDV2qCPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, ese estadio es el Tec si me hubieran terminado las 2 plantas altas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny @UKJBB @AOC #I love it Expose the Republican Bull shit and Thievery going on way too long ! 10 damn years .]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hay derrota. El propósito de restablecer el hilo constitucional, sacar a los usurpadores del poder y a los cuban… https://t.co/t4eOsCs8q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downtown-bound. (at @CTA - O'Hare in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/2kzPNoYRoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherry_sjarvis @BNMarathon @FtonMarathon ‘Therapy dog’ :). Doesn’t look like he/she minds 🐾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @The_Right_Half Illegal Aliens have no more right to vote than I would have voting in Italy or Fran… https://t.co/G1QE2pKvpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiskyLiberal @ananavarro I luv that ( Tucker's White power hour) ,😁😁😁😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than an hour away from our first academic conference! Follow our twitter account at @burleighsoc for live upda… https://t.co/fCxkKyom1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeionSandersJr @DeionSanders The words of Jesus after teaching and being scoffed at in Nazareth: "No prophet is we… https://t.co/NF3xjwzK68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xamanthaspeaks @MalcolmNance Which is true and seldom brought up. The users/buyers are here within the borders of… https://t.co/CQlr4cTymP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cosmoboy33 @AMErikaNGIRL07 Age of media. 10mil yr on phones.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1U… https://t.co/pfUJnvfrUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romeo Langford is an interesting player. Archie’s offense is not great, but romeo doesn’t move or make himself avai… https://t.co/LtXjWIc5p9]]></document><document><![CDATA[IHSA has Lovejoy's enrollment at 21. That can't be correct.They have 15 players dressed for varsity basketball game… https://t.co/xiWqzM37DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes, let’s take a dictator who leads a totalitarian state where almost everything is monitored at his word on Ot… https://t.co/d6HlRcw1jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Toronto folks! I’ll be running a play test (or two depending on the amount of folks interested!) at… https://t.co/tkZaBkuwsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aarrrgggghhhhh3 @philemon_owona @BlueRobotDesign @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch https://t.co/XL6ncDF0wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncdemography @state_of_things Will listen to the podcast, know Dr Tippett’s presentation will be very informative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, the trolls who have accessed my accounts want me to work as a software engineer at Intel.. strange to r… https://t.co/34Kw68lm1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[She will continue to grandstand wherever and whenever she perceives it will increase her political fortunes among t… https://t.co/7wgL5c2fyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once I hit #Saltair In Salt Lake County it was like a switch had been flipped and there was no snow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ?☠️ ? Who was it that said “ Take No Prisoners”...?☠️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Stunning, her face is directly out of Egyptian nobility. Some in that line were a positive influenc… https://t.co/6F45DWwILK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont put “student athlete” on your bio if you don’t go to practice everyday after school and then come home and do… https://t.co/rdngg7Kn8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3: I have accepted a challenge from @CentralYorkATC  to post #7BooksILove: no explanations, no reviews- just th… https://t.co/okyQi2xW1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother said my 21st birthday gonna be a “mf ball” 😩 I wonder what she got planned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now they’ve made us a grilled cheese &amp; soup lunch! 😋 https://t.co/P8FZdcexo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been waking up so early lately for this orientation for my new job and I’m clearly not a morning person, nor… https://t.co/W4ZZEJJut5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into the homie @el_presidante today!!! @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/mbGlkvfRmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The inevitable result of putting public money into private hands. #EdReform #CharterSchoolFail]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great to hear @RealMichaelKay doing Yankees baseball again. So great to see baseball again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buddy Cianci -- brought down by @SenWhitehouse   https://t.co/LXYmlSeWM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wells_InThe_360 #i was gonna say walrus but I didn’t want @CalebTheWalrus to get butt hurt so I threw the sea 🌊 li… https://t.co/yMJXSAUrx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themichellewie Will this need more surgery?   Get well, I love watching you play!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weeeelolol @Breaking911 Yeah but I am on that give it awhile and we will see LIST...👍👎❤️🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders will not be president because we already have our favorite President @realDonaldTrump . So this young l… https://t.co/5tnbdkcyhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very sensual. #NowPlaying Vuelvo Al Sur by Gotan Project. #tango #downtempo https://t.co/l89GF3TGjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: 'Look at my African-American over here... https://t.co/vkVE50tRff via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t need this or that, won’t stop me from being me at all. I’m letting shit happen how it happens and ain’t try… https://t.co/O1hGesai2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im a work of art and nobody is gonna tell me otherwise #littleprince à Los Angeles, California https://t.co/wRNfRCeAWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burbank_Law @PardyBruce @globeandmail @docamitay burbank sees nothing wrong with the Law Society requiring a Lefti… https://t.co/eL9AYl83AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baton Rouge! In one week's time I'll be joining two of my best buds thehitchhikerbr and @jasonmartinband at the hom… https://t.co/7akVV9OTm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisborregoa Buena pregunta..... Es cuestión de control..... Pero en tooooooodos los sentidos.... Más los dos que pensaste 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accept all of yourself, your strengths, your weaknesses, your surroundings, your present truths, and know what tool… https://t.co/DpMPG1TLHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1standsassiest Kevlar? Like bullet proof vest Kevlar? As....as her name? Forever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of volunteers tonight from 6-11 and Wednesday night from 4-10 to help with Agave Week setup and breakdown a… https://t.co/EAyqblKC8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Amazon pulling out of NYC. Says it is not reopening search. Read its complete statement below. #Amazon… https://t.co/1ErifI7oVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump I do not see failure to not agree on a bad deal. We did that in Iran and Cuba.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pahred @Rey_Sistance @RavenResists @KikiAdine @lfkraus @B52Malmet @ellievan65 @EmmaFrostResist @LunaLuvgood2020… https://t.co/S9YgQ8Jxpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The New York Times has always been a slave press to the kkk Robber barons , they silenced the holo… https://t.co/dqcrlBag2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Orange Brewlius by Drafting Table Brewing Company at @OneUnderBar — https://t.co/tODGESHpGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure how I missed this news in the past couple of days...a true legend...RIP...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realhublife @SenFeinstein Never,ever have I ever seen such derangement. It's truly  time for those that survive ca… https://t.co/hwYPVKoEyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just dropped off at the @MedBridgeEd studio and looking forward to having a conversation about this important t… https://t.co/LQoXRPevSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good question.... @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @TheJusticeDept @FBI @dbongino @Jim_Jordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #NACADA19 proposals are submitted and regardless of whether they go through to the conference or not, I am exci… https://t.co/JXFfyMJqRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[At halftime, the South Medford girls lead West Linn 30-28. The Lions with a huge first half from Payton Shelstad. #opreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Intangible Tides by @burlingtonbeer at @burlingtonbeer — https://t.co/qYtSpeCXRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volleyball: Set 5 Edison 7 @ServiteSports 7 #ProudToBeACharger @ocvarsity @DailyPilotSport @ProfessorTurner @latsondheimer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop smiling. All my cars have been beaters. But today.... 2016 Chevy Equinox. Hard work pays off so much.… https://t.co/MUkGcBN1TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Enterprise Holdings team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/3UM6kXz5BH #Marketing #Cary, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has been giving. I just got  French toast sticks from Sonics and man oh man..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simpsonwhnt @SharifaJackson @WTVM Might wanna put a team on that task. They should have plenty of time, since they… https://t.co/SSirmOl0W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howl at the Moon Philadelphia https://t.co/sEjTKPyalp]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a trend of breakfast plates that come with only one egg. This needs to end. Two eggs is the appropriate num… https://t.co/yhh7bSwH7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sundays are my favorite!!!! @ The Rock Faith Center https://t.co/VOZ40Qjijm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeathMayo I get it:  According to the alt right, conservatism now means:  Nazi, Nazi, Nazi, Drunken Whack Job.  It… https://t.co/L5FG9Doxle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I could do this project with a transistor but RELAYS are "MORE FUN. " (Clunk)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dabble by @sixpoint @ Patrick's Beer Haven — https://t.co/JMe0zYoCMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was dope to be in Brooklyn / NYC on March 9th. Every spot was mixing in some biggie and cars were blaring that shit in BK ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeVeonBell Whatever dude...260 lbs...a year of not playing.  $25M/year? You live in a dream world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i rarely ever post on my ig stories, that’s how u know i was bored bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[De inmediati! (@ Aeropuerto Internacional de Miami - @iflymia in Miami, FL) https://t.co/cYyvZPzpMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swearyG @MrReali05459432 @T__E__5__L__A @T__E__S__L__A Hard to wrap your head around it but I think you nailed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Country hit song has just written itself!  https://t.co/edTlbekwjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls think drinking wine makes them classier but let’s be honest y’all still gonna end up wine drunk twerking on t… https://t.co/yj38KVLojy]]></document><document><![CDATA[? How many post does it take on here to make a fenceSee this Instagram photo by @conaway.terry https://t.co/SYJkdshKwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace It’s been “Mission Impossible” all along, at every level… Trump “conspired” w/Russia a… https://t.co/4TVnd7EY04]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the bus that all of the seditious and treasonous players in the swamp that they are throwing each other und… https://t.co/k5LhAqLL8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[#chicks Hey did you fart?? Lol Lol Lol 😝 😆 😂 @ Brooklyn Park, Minnesota https://t.co/RXKOKN4ZGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three spheres of influence of the designer: within the designer, toward the object of the design, and the impact of… https://t.co/7prSUsXXBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh! Today is “drive slow in front of @DamnPhotoArtist day”. Somehow I didn’t have that on my calendar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrocNessMonster Nope. The only time I went up there was for her graduation. Previously hadn’t been there since the… https://t.co/GShzBHZkL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In context.  There's an earlier letter that introduces the term to his family. https://t.co/A1C6t3mlu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shnikkles The same thing happens with me at work! It can be pretty frustrating to have to drag work between monito… https://t.co/IbQYxlexbj]]></document></documents></author>