<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am not going to fight Shanel Balogun. I keep the peace. I hold no grudge against Shanel Balogun. I help Shanel Ba… https://t.co/Xb1qYO4Pva]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am proud of the #company I have built. My #purpose driven woman-owned #foodtruck has a #mission is to save the… https://t.co/1IpeGgiVHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[gn i just vibed out to @TheDylanHyde 's snap storyyy 😴😴 https://t.co/SnSCwcHXWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @DrKels50 and @spahouston for hosting us, we @kujawaeagle had a blast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are do proud of the whole team, but even more proud of @_jayynicee and all that she has accomplished the past 4… https://t.co/cV5vSR8xi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired of doing everyone else’s work so they can leave work at 3:30. #internlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team LeBron should have never been down 20 in the first place. Change my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thread. Not sure I entirely agree with it, but it's interesting to see how series 11 backed off treating the D… https://t.co/oP1VkGA6Mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson Corruption runs rampant in the Dem party!  It's like it self-selects for these thieves.  Gotta kick them out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to my good friend coach Diane Decker @esuwbb for growing the love of the game and giving this awesome kid an… https://t.co/SCOGKw1fL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamtheBullFAN Chico is very relatable so are you Bull Dustin and Lima are divas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set It Off Midnight Tour 2019 • • • • • #concertphotographer #torontophotographer #torontophotography… https://t.co/jTV2UX90DZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm only 27 weeks but I swear you do not know how uncomfortable it starts to become! I want my baby here already!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[*tries to go to sleep, is immediately consumed with anger about NHL player safety, how our society let's misogyny i… https://t.co/H8UOalE0aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Greece or Italy, NC I love good food, shopping and the beaches !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely evening listening @trishayearwood new show on #Garthchannel #Trishacafe’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimDuy @lehnerjw Info is for the community. Josh is doing a service. https://t.co/6Y34i9d5a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's my second weekend straight in the SAC at @uofl. @gsquaredky, can you get me a cot over here? https://t.co/toNmUG3cf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Missjadeeb You just gotta be accepting to the love that’s being given to you. Of course, in the appropriate manner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends are photographers so that’s why I have trust issues when reg folks take my pic with a phone. Y’all neeee… https://t.co/r48dfCoMum]]></document><document><![CDATA[David said I can get my septum pierced if he can get a tattoo and I said ok you can get a P on your ring finger lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hubs: You need to clean up all these toys.  3: NO! I’m still playing!  H: You have 5 minutes. After that, I’M going… https://t.co/LLaXAR9CgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off in Spokane tonight and the next 3 days... what am I even going to do with all that free time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobyS2 @PeteThePlanner I haven’t been to any dealership that doesn’t try to up sale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the wrath and ruin and rage running its course until the goddess collapses into exhausted grief... https://t.co/9SdaMovCIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlondeWineGirl i love you and your wealth of knowledge girl! i’m deff gonna go snag some this week! 🙃😝 xoxxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Reality: I’ve never watched this show.  Silver Lining: I have no opinion, unpopular or otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday @ajalvarez27 !! i hope your day was just as amazing as you are :) i love &amp; miss you soo much! 😇💞😚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1AccordFitness @CBSLA We’re all still here!  No word yet on a reopening time, we’ll have a live update on CBS2 at 11AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I redeemed my E-GIFT Card That I Earned watching Videos on #watchback App Y-a-y 😎💞 @ Burger King https://t.co/70CgGf2ihA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cachirula @trish_regan @Karinabarbosa @AOC ...meaning she was not a politician and her spunk is 100% for THE PEOPL… https://t.co/FQxzJhzDIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudiGourmand @poetixtrip @thethirstytales @CourseCharted @FoodTravelist @SouthernerSays @GalsWander @KaraDiDomizio… https://t.co/aIsB4wJQZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope I’m not cooking tonight! #boiledseafood #crablegs #crawfish #boiledshrimp my own personal #mukbang… https://t.co/paYkn5dOXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hspoils @ginou1010 How do we know which one happens first? Someone saves Sam or someone hits Jordan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work flow (at @Walmart Supercenter in Ellicott City, MD) https://t.co/qnSVONecmA https://t.co/hglfvi9M2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my #highschool girls and boys: What are y’all saying besides Gucci and Stan? #amwriting #teenthriller]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Do you follow the Charlottesville gang of miscreants around with a camera? What they did was far worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're at @OldTownCam #Beer March prospecting for the @TOChiliCookOff and Craft Brew Fest and OF COURSE… https://t.co/Prb8CE8Nje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickRiccardi The "spotlight" is focused on what gets clicks.  Remember, always, that the media is most deeply vest… https://t.co/7MLdAEfjFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeRMcDonald9 @PredsOnFSTN Just changed over to the game so you should be good to switch back to Hulu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usna_admissions appreciate the invite for my son but for all your summer session dates he is still in school....so not a chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went from going to Houston for Spring Break to going to Cali 🌴  So excited 🙌🏼   @BriiRenae @BesosBritt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickeybevington @BankofAmerica @WACATL @makessenich @KwKevinwwilson Great to see you as well! Thanks for moderatin… https://t.co/Ve7sdf3xCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyGibsonNCSU @bjsrestaurants I hope the PACK are treating you well.  With all that Red and White you’ll be looki… https://t.co/uBvLc0R6Nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just tripped and fell. I’m fine. But I’m #atthatage where my life flashed before my eyes and I thought, “So this is how it ends.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer and Bible Study. Philippians 4 (@ Greater Ebenezer Ministries in Detroit, MI) https://t.co/kfPLrMa5pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crucifalex I wrotetHalsey but you also have tons of followers. I truly hope you see this. I think ur platform is a… https://t.co/L6M7pTDhXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gold on Copper Balayage and Drycut ✨ . . .  #beforeandafter #hairmakeover #balayage #blondeandred #hairideas… https://t.co/288cPJjCyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw on GMA that Serena Williams husband makes her breakfast every Sunday morning. My son- law isn’t famous, bu… https://t.co/ZSS42d8agi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now is the time to think about crabgrass prevention in the form of preemergence herbicide products. Visit… https://t.co/891Nn5WzTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[jajajja antes mega amigas y ahora ya ni me sigues en ig se te sube se te sube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m balancing being gentle with myself while also pushing myself 🦋 . It’s hard trying to strike that balance but I… https://t.co/kHnIKDGVon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindseyadler @brian_heyman tbqh I care not for baseball as far as the bare minimum I need to know for my job but I… https://t.co/uJISAYFJwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slmadmom @Andy @stassi @MusicKillsKate Horrible choice of outfit. And the big chunky necklace did not go with the… https://t.co/beSR3GD3A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don't ever ever give me  Alcohol. I don't act right. @ Lindenwood Diner https://t.co/3MelKLnA07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@signetweets @coachegge @TheRickWilson Thank you - they can do that right here:  https://t.co/fDdC5O4VL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if McDonald's is so stingy with their ranch because they want their supplies to last for years. Like what is t… https://t.co/PgKxzlcNBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“we’re all set for coachella. airfare paid, house paid, &amp; tickets paid! happy early 21st!” best news to wake up to 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Support Staff Needed!" at Kelly Services, then look for people you mig… https://t.co/xBdX6muwTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas get your crap together for spring break!!!!! we aren’t trying to swim in frozen ice!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's an excellent skier but more importantly a patient partner. I'm so lucky to have someone who challeges and supp… https://t.co/oCFHNBg7Yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting cannon fever..been off work so long I hope I remember my job when I return..lol few more days few more days]]></document><document><![CDATA[FashionShow come meet me 2019 today  Ven conocerme hoy @ New York, New York https://t.co/RdvTKzcWBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gkhaarmann it was great to witness greatness at your senior night. You rep #JCHS well! #onceajayalwaysajay… https://t.co/WTIBT7g7Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appropriate. ❤️❤️  #mysupermidlife #lovemyboyfriend #blessed #valentinesday2019 @ Traverse City, Michigan https://t.co/3aEXIN6YPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseyKimmell Yeah o think it’s been almost two years since my last one! I was about to get another one and then… https://t.co/yCbSrbgvLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my haircut for an interview tomorrow  you could say I’m bossin tf UP for this possible new job]]></document><document><![CDATA[#finallyarrived at my #destination . #endoftheroad . #lovelyscenery #bikepath #walkingpath #mojavetrail   #longwalk… https://t.co/plowS8kIAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but my friends are my soulmates, and 4 of them I don’t see too often and I feel like I’m missing part of me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sky is falling! The sky is falling!  Again....and again....and yet again...  @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJ_Taylor Great! I sent an email your way. Let me know your thoughts so we can iron out the details. Thanks!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself It’s so disturbing. At first I just laughed at his ignorance, but now he’s sounding like a coked our tyrant. Not good. 😢😢😢💔💔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some screen grabs from the live stream of #GC2019 as the circle around the rainbow flag on the floor of #UMCGC grow… https://t.co/sOcZVzEyqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Then don’t wear that” oOoOoOooo we don’t wear clothes for you we wear it for us hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdwed @melisrichmond @runningstart @LauraCoxKaplan Auntie Thank and love you @pdwed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigGolfGuy @ESPNHOOKSY One of the best compliments I’ve ever received!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @the_rock967 Can’t stand the sight or sound of this lying hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great season @AUMensHoops student-athletes and coaches! Great fan support as well. Bring it on, spring sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I wear Blue today! My sister @buildershe my community @coloncanada https://t.co/bLz4h9nhul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it love it Fox being banned from debates is outrageous. This is America and they  want to make us a socialist co… https://t.co/EG9LWtnz3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EducatorWilcox Thanks!! We are a great team! Better together @EducatorWilcox #lovebooks #readingforpleasure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judging Miss South Point Pageant tonight! I am so excited to be a part of such a long running tradition! https://t.co/Ke6zVjjAfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog ate a whole pack of beauty blenders and lemme tell you she been shitting them out for 3 days now 🤦🏼‍♀️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great running into our #Intune #Customers and Team. Great to see everyone. Have a wonder #CCP event]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nafsnep I agree. Refs never called goalie interference when they knocked Jarry down then scored a goal against. Yo… https://t.co/k7tmSKehBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KTrz4nVyG0  #alstexas #sunnystrong #alssucks #als #iloveyouthemoses #raredc2019 #lougehrigsdisease… https://t.co/xNUYAFHHjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babies taking care of me when I've got the flu. https://t.co/7BfzQZk7JO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 1:30 am &amp; im at canes with Micah in my pj’s &amp; she’s dancing around. Send. Help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAOOO YOOO this is literally me. Ive been on a water only diet but i still drink alcohol 4 times a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartPrest @EmmMacfarlane ACTIVELY BEFORE THE COURTS -Jeeesus, you incompetent goofs - talk to at least ONE lawyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s formal date is this bc it ain’t mine 😂😩💀 if you do see him at formal tho mind ya business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for joining the jam! I had a blast with you all, inspiring to see the awesome game designs 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone says “love like you’ve never been hurt before,” they aren’t ready for love. They’re only capable of re… https://t.co/77Tm2Y9ctb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about the drug problem you have I'S it even safe to visit? I am concerned as my wife was talking about VACATIO… https://t.co/4sUoF9odgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is my birthday.. starting to reflect on the past year that has gone by way too fast. 23 in less than 8 hours from now. 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Laramie, WY #Nursing job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Noncertified Nursing A… https://t.co/LGBe7XQzWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrizzliesOnFSSE @thefishnation @brevinknight22 @ChrisVernonShow @memgrizz We cannot hear Dillon Brooks. He mumbles. Please work with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyhourallday #jcsonelpaseo #kitty #meow #bff #babies #adorbs #bestofthebest #vote #bestsundaybrunch… https://t.co/EV6qyohru4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristaAllen @AnnaMariaPdT did Cake TV actually happen or did i imagine that show?? everyone i’ve ever asked has n… https://t.co/IJgNZjr0rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobNelsonABC7 Can't you make a IRA contribution @RobNelsonABC7  $6,500. ?]]></document></documents></author>