<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Someone please send me pics of like puppies and kittens or something cute as shit cuz I really wanna cry rn. https://t.co/DDaHAgYzd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Now she is going to start a foundation and make donations to charity 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[1:51am is a strange time to get ur life together but guess what i’m doing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Three nights ago, Ihad a very convoluted, but fun  dream/ nightmare  along these lines, Wherein Barr’… https://t.co/ijtiuoJP06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to remember this. My morning reading included story of Apostle Peter in chains, miraculously set free. Today i… https://t.co/rAUb7NoWKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tropixalloccs wait cause why you lookin @ this while we in pre cal 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most accurate thing I’ve ever seen. Also “unlimited unpaid vacation” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I fling my flute around as if it didn’t cost me an arm and a leg. Who do I think I am? Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ LUZIA by Cirque du Soleil https://t.co/1ibahyaGeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam 🖤⚪️🖤 great pix of you from Saturday! #SpiritAwards  #BnWSam  #SamHeughan https://t.co/hesJxxCpGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even after the anti-vaxxers have been thoroughly discredited, the ableism behind the anti-vax movement continues. T… https://t.co/IP2hWHwBf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s real low if u gotta bash someone for retweets and likes But I’ll be the bigger person always have been why w… https://t.co/uTgtXiOquZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madi casually having enough money saved up to comfortably buy himself a new car is the kind of financial responsibility I aspire to have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton A set back for your Margaret Sanger &amp; Saul Alinsky agenda.  Thank God for President Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piratemonkey7 @BeaverBaseball Hey that looks a lot like my view. Great game today (even though it was so cold).… https://t.co/bn3RVD80Yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con Sue Photography and Design  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/LT8WDlQRnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Millionaires funded by billionaires to tell the remainder of Americans it’s immigrants who are the enemy.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_jh2009 @59NationalParks @wildtribute Hahaha. Great idea, Tim. I'll suggest it next summer when I'm up there! #parkchat #foodtravelchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awe, ✅ and submitted. 💪🏼 Off to bed I go for some much new beauty rest 😴 I must 🏃🏽‍♀️ in the am. Good night… https://t.co/30m43lnpYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is why I hate depending on others... I like to get what I want WHEN I want it 🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan You are a cartoon. What's with yelling and raising your voice? You lack decent questions. You certainly… https://t.co/ehrS0sTNy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aborddelimpala My take: Ruby knew Dean hated her so she didn't let on who she was when she opened the door.  She k… https://t.co/n6OY7KYcN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna start Gilmore Girls for the first time ever and I’m super hyped]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg spiderversemovie ’s Gwen Stacy looks just like me irl rn... well finally I’m not so regretful about dying my ha… https://t.co/x7M6FhZKpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sybilstarr @sindnwf I can’t wait to work with you more, it was so great finally meeting you💛💛💛 safe travels!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve said it before and i’ll day it again   IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN IZZIE AND NOT GEORGE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinCe_BouCher @watcher_war @Mike4372Mike @g_meyer32 @AprilF815 @Terra_Nulius @wiseoldsnail @ReichlA22 @laxman0317… https://t.co/mT13L6WNFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @RepGosar He really is one sorry SOB , No doubt about it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a photographer, that lives to paint and occasionally writes. Here’s my latest poem...                    By Mar… https://t.co/sEah9gvm7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been real Chicago ✌🏻! I’m headed 🏠 for a week and I need some good podcasts for the drive this afternoon. What… https://t.co/cp6qLin7r9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@werthc: Check out @thewatermain.  @mndnr needs to connect with this @MPR initiative. #WaterIsLife!! https://t.co/MuS6QE6pW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @Liaisti_1 @VictoriaD6363 @Jilliemary @mabel_carrera @AAvallones @PapaPorter1 @SUPERGOCHOo @malekalby… https://t.co/ef7uNb6Adh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys. My last workout was FEBRUARY 26th. TEN DAYS AGO. Between a huge work deadline + the stomach bug that plag… https://t.co/PFFaKOOuxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rogers I was charged twice on the same day. 17' waiting to chat to a representative...]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to be on @kfbk with @kittykfbk to discuss my collaborative art show this Friday at Groundswell Art Gallery!! https://t.co/qUmMyem3Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG absolutely outrageous!  These Americans are being held by tyrannical terrorist in Venezuela!  These innocent fa… https://t.co/OSufew4xiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I adore this collection of the abolitionist poet, John Greenleaf Whittier's, poetry; it's so beautiful and, as alwa… https://t.co/qO1k4yxSkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilslenarz @AmyMek @realDonaldTrump OK then which is it? Are they "funded" or "denounced" by DNC? Don't answer, everything is a mess here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so no Wickens segment between 7a-8am on @GMA. What they heck?   They're now doing a SECOND R. Kelly segment. D… https://t.co/loMLRMtl3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews Can you even get a real job?  Sitting and trolling your lies al… https://t.co/hidfKVyjbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Account Coordinator"? What did you like most about that job? #Accounting #Woburn, MA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rye_journo @Jennifer_Hiller @Taylor_Paige13 @rachaelgleason @TessaDuvall @Cassie_Burton51 @ViannaDavila @emilieeaton So nice of you, Rye!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trace left candy on my windshield today while I was working, imagine my surprise 😭😭❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[About our free winter coat giveaway... wearecym This is our second year loving on our families in Crestwood Forest… https://t.co/3wqa1x57No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan @Ps4Sto You are bragging about your friendship with a dictator who doesn't give 2 f?!king shits ab… https://t.co/oBfzmm6IMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ironhorse76 A Q idiot had me put in Twitter suspension yet they said worse than I. Trump altright people  are also… https://t.co/v94G96qjQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for liking my column Eduardo Oliveira @Eduardo73607370 Happy day!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #BusinessMgmt jobs like "Process Executive" at Cognizant in #Jessup, PA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasuremile was wondering how long it takes to receive a check from your casino? I won a few bucks the other day… https://t.co/uwYVeiCSj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @RepMarkMeadows Thank you for the first true converging act for our country.  @RepCummings, your sens… https://t.co/x6v5x8qTCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[...which happened because the Pike drains into the little pond by the library and the fire station. Yuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabbed Frisky’s bed and placed it on Jose’s side. Lol. We know who runs this house, and it isn’t any of the humans… https://t.co/1XKMlXtrUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[my housemate’s playing the same song out loud that i was listening to on my airpods dam this is meant 2 be &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful carved tree of life accented by a  Vintage carved tall pedestal! Eclectic bohemian furniture and decor at… https://t.co/4Qtsjqk8FM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t stop me lovin’ myself. ✨💛🌻 en Daydream https://t.co/2unYi3NT5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing trip so far! Loving the stadium. Three generations of Brewer fans!! #CactusCrew https://t.co/Tvjul8G4Cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think anyone will ever understand how happy I was to see this beautiful person ❤️ || Fresno ✈️ Houston @ Ke… https://t.co/1DnUWkNns5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kehlani was WWW removed from Apple Music? I listened to it ALL DAY yesterday and I’m being told it’s “not available” now 🤔🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when our furnace breaks (yes breaks plural) and our landlord won’t answer 🥶‼️🥶‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalvinRoberson No, but really. I, like many others here, disagree. It's disappointing to see that you and the othe… https://t.co/eHwe2E992E]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends have genuinely helped me and gave me the strength and mind set to get my shit together this year and I c… https://t.co/J3hdif24an]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vampire Diaries really be having me watch it till 5 am almost every night 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the outcome we wanted but still a fun game! @ Times Union Center https://t.co/CQukpTAkhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putin’s Puppet is afraid to respond!  He has his speaking orders as Putin tells him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dai tè alla salsa di cipolle è un attimo 🤢 #FindingRospa https://t.co/w5n8A0SYzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Structural systemic barriers impact many people in our society.  How do we impact them in a way that gives everyone… https://t.co/c6hWKQYG2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be so proud of myself when I get around buckhead without gps, knowing back ways, all that. I’m comfortable now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpHumpers are so f**king NAUSEATING.  #AntiMuslim Poster at West Virginia Capitol Tries to #Link Rep. Ilhan Oma… https://t.co/CoMAAX5o5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Old North Sacramento, Sacramento https://t.co/hYmIaEo5CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a world full of Kims, be a Diana. #snowday @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/cXObBroQtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharmingHand It's all the same to me, a person can think they're right in committing atrocities. I think ever able… https://t.co/60mIyqPt1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill When I was ten in Catholic school a boy bullied me so I chicken-fought him on the monkey bars and nea… https://t.co/6nJsvKus7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreaCros Yea.... I try to keep up with it and balance things out by wishing people good luck when they mention the… https://t.co/KFSJtdPAFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging w/my hubby and waiting for Bonnie Raitt and James Taylor to begin. Date night in the middle of the week, go figure. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like i personally know the people i pass everyday going to work but i don’t even know their names. Ya know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne So sorry for your loss, heartbreaking ... thank you for sharing your pain to help others much appreciated..… https://t.co/VeZfW8yrqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spider in my kitchen this am. Caught it in a glass &amp; took it outside. Anybody proud of me for not killing it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump The law is coming for you Princess🖕🏿 #JAIL #FAKE  #FECKLICIT  #FRAUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth noting here: @Bakari_Sellers has talked often and openly about running for #SC06 at some point. A couple mont… https://t.co/LhGJ6WSWPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin Garnett you look so Secy I That Red Velvet Jacket🔥💕 #NBAAllStarWeekend #ATTSlamDunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of @flow_witMe i had no choice to read this thread smh... These kids acting real TRUMP like out here smh...… https://t.co/OyfalkSXNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s National Peanut Butter Day and Pam made some delicious chocolate cupcakes with a peanut butter icing, pretzel… https://t.co/VC24ObfnTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does your business need a blog? What good will it do? . . Follow the LINK IN BIO for six key benefits of adding… https://t.co/AywAHS0N68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hnsmith14 I could probably sing Sharkboy’s dream song to you word for word]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles Yo hi you can find my portfolio at https://t.co/KCjPXdmh1K and my Instagram username is @ samanthabakerfilm. Let me know🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets are on-sale NOW for @PghTacoFest at @highmarkstadium on June 1st! Visit https://t.co/dxx1ZC6VkF for info an… https://t.co/2PNDIqefXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My momma really be saving some of the people that cross me JUST bc she knows how to calm me down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyKempson He's a poster boy for pitbulls...the perfect young pitbull. He'd help cure PTSD...someone pull him.… https://t.co/cNEMj7eFIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gdeguzman99 @kylegriffin1 Interesting Shitler didn't deny hating the US]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland So I can't recommend this book enough. https://t.co/nq8O3o2Sa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philadelphia phigure rmarsc01 is not only a @paballet @pmayoungfriends and all around philanthropic mover and shake… https://t.co/dBgEMWT1yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[we ❤️ goalies #smashville #GoPreds  @PredsNHL #juusesaros #pekkarinne 💛🏒💙🏒💛 https://t.co/GhpK9uyrGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is real good cus I get to work with some of my best friends,,, thank u @OUDaily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaharZRashid I think... I think I’ve got something in my eye... both my eyes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’m living at home my family is finally seeing me for who I am lol I was editing a video RN and my dad ask… https://t.co/gfybqLjV4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends st #ACPA19 : I have terrible vision so if you see me, say hello!]]></document><document><![CDATA[43rd UN CONFERENCE GENERAL ASSEMBLY LIVE NOW HERE:  https://t.co/7uFB9Lh3GI]]></document><document><![CDATA[to look for the trooper's firearm.  Court documents also detail the moments right before the shooting.  The boy say… https://t.co/44EsDQhdxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yen dips as it is known as the "Dirty floater." Its currency will be a lot more stable when most if the world goes… https://t.co/xpiYxlTM4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii So very sorry, but I'm glad you are able to spend some precious time with her.]]></document></documents></author>