<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[後閑信吾 - 江戸時代にアメリカに渡った侍達が帰国してオープンしたことを想像して作ったバー「The SG Club」を渋谷にオープン https://t.co/ZLMcSiIZv4 via @highflyersjapan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnGrimesMN So are you mocking squatch believers? https://t.co/tHTjWz83ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagining me in that situation. Then imagining how far she would’ve been falling from the side of the building afte… https://t.co/Qhuz5EikEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauraingle 😎😎😎Follow me soon You will make me cry if do not.  Media is board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we just fast forward so I can look forward to going to my own house after a bad day.😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump The only thing you will see in 2020 is a democrat as president and hopefully democrats over the senate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liar: “I lie a lot to get clicks.”  USA Today: “Put this man on the front page immediately.” https://t.co/XpT4UnsYoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally send olive a tweet every other minute tbh. How is she not annoyed of me yet lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rabbit Rabbit.    #SantaMonica #CA @ Loews Santa Monica Beach Hotel https://t.co/q1iri6e5JQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly my friends deserved Oscars for pretending to know I wasn’t gay when I came out to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad commentary on distracting the military from their mission. Oh, and let’s stop wasting treasure and lives in AFG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaders gpnoco with their pastor claytonspeck having the needed conversations to get the plan right! @ Grace Place https://t.co/nwaViwlu9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t completely fuck up the bok choy 🥬 lol it’s sooo good. I halved it, seared it in bacon grease, with onions,… https://t.co/mTvC6VG9tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't care but you know NYI fans are going to make a huge ordeal about it regardless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino I gave you grief a while back for the out of date tease photo that Fox and friends used for you. Happy to… https://t.co/V9GLfXaoP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wish I was a better artist and didn’t push all my friends away while I was struggling early on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the wife to work at Bryan East last night. Picked her up this morning. Took us 45min to get back home. Bryan E… https://t.co/l6x78rkDQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MartySmithESPN  https://t.co/6Z862KTnuG  Might be a little much for hill billy headlines, but I thought I would pass along....]]></document><document><![CDATA[7am Monday. Measured 3.5 inches here in Newtown Twp, PA. Heavy wet snow. Some tree damage in the neighborhood as we… https://t.co/wc4eElRjOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steezyxgraciee @djohnkms @Diamond_Noire_ GET THE FUCK OUT🤣🤣🤣🤣😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[More bathrooms than bedrooms?! Do they have a Popeye's chicken in the thing too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magic971fm I would love to hear 'With You' by #MariahCarey on your station today! It's one of my favourite songs c… https://t.co/DfdXMupVhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardio day: 30 minutes on an elliptical  followed by a 3-mile run. Legs feel real heavy going up stairs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @RepLizCheney Except that the so called president is a racist, race baiting pig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By winning the argument, Buffalo was able to start as an expansion team with its first pick, from the wheel spin, H… https://t.co/PLti8206ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Go back to bed, Not Funny Archie Bunker. It’s way too early and you should still be in the bathroo… https://t.co/al7x4RRy97]]></document><document><![CDATA[People, I just want to say, can we all get along? Can we get along? - #RodneyKing  #OnThisDay in 1991 constructio… https://t.co/5ifVonQoRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's bring the obstructing bastard #BrianKemp  down.  People in Georgia should have voted in @staceyabrams.… https://t.co/YrVw1aO4eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1Q, Rochester private school CG Finney crushing Middle Early College on the boards and has 19-14 lead in Cla… https://t.co/7vEWcuauzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped pin Near: 👇Cal Tramp 4 THE TRAMP🗨👷🚧🖕🖕🖕🖕🖕🖕 https://t.co/acBtRkvd0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's necessary to have time for yourself. It releases stress, gives the body rest, and provides a "reset" for the s… https://t.co/MmFEtFb70b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurs fall to the Nets. Final Score from the @barclayscenter. @spurs: 85 @BrooklynNets: 101 #SpursVsNets #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the inclement weather, tonight’s FHS girls lacrosse game against @OakHallGirlsLax has been cancelled. https://t.co/M69k1Prf2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll give it to Matt, yeah all his friends talk shit about him constantly, but at least they’re talking about him.… https://t.co/3SXI9NhQlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I’ve been inflicting my boring chip choices on my wife and son because I do the food shopping, and no… https://t.co/OVumUjQ7Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go jeff Hoover @GovMattBevin or whoever else needs to make this happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EasyVC @RealKevinNash &gt;all plane crashes are fiery explosions where everybody dies has to be a double work]]></document><document><![CDATA[El efecto cobra, o porque el "Hoy no circula" y otros programas no sólo no funcionan, sino que empeoran el problema… https://t.co/H3a41rw0qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesleyIan10 In that case, i am now accepting signatures for my petition to give Joanna Gleason a MacArthur Genius Grant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BjaminWood @jonesnews @BYU Study it’s history relative to students suspected of being gay. The allegations of surv… https://t.co/zhLHGhLArD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USParatrooper73 @Swazi4 Rednecks be blocking and denying...  https://t.co/lWAiRDRZiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be afraid to be uncomfortable-get used to it and make a difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimyaNDennisPhD My colleague in my department was his childhood friend... Has great stories of them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking in some #PremierLeague ⚽ from across the pond all while having a 🍕 #leicstercity vs @CPFC https://t.co/uOriJoJkoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepalladium you’re one of my fav venues, but what’s up with the sound? Felt like we could hear everyone’s convers… https://t.co/8q92J8nW5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doubleuefwhy People think that their dog is perfect and...yeah no.   You ought to see how amazingly well-behaved C… https://t.co/TLzoHDXRSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protestas y toda la información sobre la visita de Donald Trump a FIU en @aurelio02 #Miami #fiu #donaldtrump… https://t.co/9HlKWWyQKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Night 2/23- . . . . . #music #bakersfield @ Bakersfield, California https://t.co/VbmPnz2kVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarieAl @Turki_AlOwerde @RealthingUlli @B0RedS1 @305local @Alkofide @ceasere @awwadsalotaibi @travlnjak… https://t.co/47ctUm7kbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christian__24_ Lmaooo, i didnt tell anyone... so the whole morning i was like : https://t.co/mrPW27oWdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jonz970 @Docacct @PoboySr @PRheydt @2501Wolf @cmcsurdy @clovis1931 @jhawk2467 @MoPopskull @Bigbillshater… https://t.co/h3mi4xCxzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elverkonge @mtaibbi You want the government to spend 150K per student for an education that could have been gained for 1.50 in late fees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msdanifernandez Sorry. Just now I found myself imagining you letting out a classic Godzilla rawwwwrrrrr!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetalMastodon @DarylMcGoldrick @themotleyfool Some truth, with creativity there are ways to eat and be healthy whe… https://t.co/wiUQELQEqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The eyes in the room followed me as if they could see my every thought. It was that moment I noticed they were all… https://t.co/WCc1KxZeSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I'd stomp on one finger at a time. This little piggy ya know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDumaine They’re not all that bright. They just sorta amble from place to place, here in the Gulf of Mexico. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two types of people By kyle.coughlan  ⠀ How you look and feel are the results of your lifestyle CHOICES and HABITS.… https://t.co/Y8LxyyhACM]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW... she screwed up... the guy had his hand down reaching under his chair... she should have called for help at t… https://t.co/6NnXQfmYjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was two but a,,,,, hair of ,,,,color,,,king,,,,,,, can work,,,,, understand https://t.co/gRrQ0itpG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoltageSpike42 @amahnke What sphere? I'm in there too. You do realize that this is going to get a load of support for this guy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made it to Dallas. This drive to and from el paso gets worse and worse. It's so damn boring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind ... and he will hold that spot until the end of time - last that is. Amazing how close this is to a su… https://t.co/HqJs6ykcDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't sweat, I sparkle!  This is how I gym...how do you gym? 😜  . . . . .    So for those of you that know me you… https://t.co/HQYzH4cwxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s flippin’ great, Judge Judy. #realtor #kellerwilliams #kwstudiocity #tuneindropout @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/qt9Jc5EjwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments Why would anyone want a perfect representation of the horror the Republican party is today to get f… https://t.co/HR2gQ1XNII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greek grilled chicken salad.  Only 370 calories. (@ Newk's Express Cafe in Newnan, GA) https://t.co/2ojnqfhomM https://t.co/NSb5hdFXli]]></document><document><![CDATA[2.28.19 #Drawing: The doorway and rails at the 19th century-built 257 West 11th Street. https://t.co/eOad3tTD3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelZaker1 @kaysintBB @TaggartRehnn @someone_1958 @woodywood1999 @JonAnthony7 @wolflayla420 @tianjin1980… https://t.co/wz0NxQHUj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Malinowski @CoryBooker And how is this Nincompoop going to "unite all of us" when he throws MAGA supporters under… https://t.co/Ze0VRZXzp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ROOTSPORTS_NW when will I be able to pay an annual subscription to stream your content without having a cable/… https://t.co/Pw3uq70Ysi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The game is essentially what would be the prelude in a normal CtL game, with less "you've been captured and torture… https://t.co/dmiefQSYrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECrumrine Blocking him has been the best thing for my sanity. No need for that nonsense on my feed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Liberalism is common sense defiance. Lets take 300 lbs of fentanyl through the border patrol. How do you think it gets through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoscoMoon @KenNunnemaker I don't think anyone can say you are transgender Mosco - not if they can see correctly. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani Always tough to see these type of results when a combination of factors at work here and not the leas… https://t.co/sqY4tLPyFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[💘 Valentine places in Redding and surrounding areas. 👇Click below for links   View 202 #View202… https://t.co/IyG0UZ8BGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool #texas #map Join my Adventures  #WilcoApproved #Survival #Facts #Outdoors #Camping #naturephotography… https://t.co/sNE9ATuRpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bicemusic @WatchTheBreaks I’m so sorry for your loss of your little girl. Prayers going out to you brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s Valentines Special.  Free Sharable desert when two specials are ordered. #eatlocal #drinklocal… https://t.co/BlfuUtDhX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanemcmahon doesn't want to interview with @KaylaBraxtonWWE #WWEFastlane #WWE #WWEUniverse #ProWrestling #WWENetwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[What dumb fuck doesn’t know that if it’s raining your headlights are supposed to be on]]></document><document><![CDATA[«En nylig svensk studie (3) viser at i løpet av de siste ti årene har spontanabort økt med 50 prosent.»]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, @Inc, this is ridiculous. I have yet to see a single shred of evidence that Eisenhower created or used a so-cal… https://t.co/ixhZfgFnS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Well, I am adopted (my mom remarried), so I think there was a court appearance. I don't even remember.… https://t.co/KYlS2nTBCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyChaser @kickstarter You’re very welcome I’m glad I could help as much as I could. Best of luck to you guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEC Chair Clayton has such close ties to Wall Street that he will preserve its conflict-ridden business model at al… https://t.co/dU2yjH2lfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicamreyes @netflix Assuming you have already watched Ozark on Netflix. If not 5👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSportsSoccer Cheick Tiote’s only PL goal... #MyPLMorning #hwtl #rip https://t.co/uu7W9xW1Ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WX1BOX. Trying to get a pic for you on Bridge stteet tree incident. Reports via FB that trees and wires are down a… https://t.co/7SkSy2C2uY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pencerm @Bengals It’s to the point where I actively am rooting for them to move when the stadium deal is up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uglykiddave @FrankPeteani @TomStoup @spookymilk @TorchMcMahon Maybe I will check that out when my kid peels himsel… https://t.co/3l5vKUjyMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend has a little bit of land in Leavenworth, every time I’m there we hear noises so I’d install it to get a l… https://t.co/eooZAqwz30]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m kind of embarrassed to have been baptized at this point Catholic Church.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @TMCountryman This Fake New Network simply cannot find the good in anything.  How can any outlet spread such negativity?...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_frank5 @KamalHaddad @GwashburnGlobe @JMooseRHP3 Alex Cora on Coach Frank: "He needs to get better "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prospect_zgint I’ve always enjoyed them. Don’t like them as much during the season, however]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our President is an idiot” - Anne Coulter ... probably the only thing I will agree with and that’s saying somethin… https://t.co/GUn3CZ8wkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me my boys! #blessed #fatherandson #family @BbernardBbj luis_valladares__ giovallar @leethongkham . . . #grateful… https://t.co/fLOObWPIJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darren20041950 Did she say "Put your gun away" it was about to get really real at the 19th hole....]]></document></documents></author>