<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A school staff member saw me reading my Bible this morning and said “Bible study?” I nodded and said yes, he said “… https://t.co/u25dwwmoEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanOfArgghh @sahouraxo @HouseCracka Chavez/Maduro were/are extraconstitutional dictators. Most of Venezuela and t… https://t.co/60Wdc1ktXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but if you’re 30+ with no job and no money because of your bad choices and mooching off your parents and… https://t.co/2KImtq4GJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew_Ruiz10 @whatcandicesays Okay but we weren’t the ones calling people filthy fucking casuals lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fernaandagpe 😱😱😱 NOO ME HUBIERA ENCABRONA SI ME HUBIERAN HECHO ESO CON LA CAMILA 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Thank you, thank you for standing against #traitortrump   #EnoughIsEnough]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Whenever I’m about to do something, i think “would an idiot do that”? And if they would, i do not do that thing” -… https://t.co/svxkjRflWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[99% of girls I know with naturally big boobs hate them and try their hardest to make them look smaller]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even want to go to sleep now, ugh this is scary &amp; it’s freaking me out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don't have the guts to release your tax returns, tell the truth or let the investigation run i… https://t.co/x0q4UXNNCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be courageous and be comfortable with having uncomfortable conversations. @NellieBor #sxsw #responsibleleadership #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen: Trump described his campaign as 'the greatest infomercial in political history' https://t.co/lxI8syfydU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop listening to @MyFavMurder podcast while walking louie.falkor in the dark. Louie actually barked and… https://t.co/IUQV3PUErw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsmeEddieC @sak_shoes @LouGirl502 @dodgers_randi Correct. So correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do women keep their jackets on their shoulders without putting their arms through?  What is this witchcraft EXP… https://t.co/7c4JyB3yL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rishi Sushi Kitchen &amp; Bar in Columbus, OH https://t.co/YINSFhkPTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmpressPivoine Can we find out who she is and expose her. Why try to hurt someone and hide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOverCurtiss @RyanPoptart @themenzingers We need to keep this thread going. 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Bachelor, we don’t need a season recap after that WTA. #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuJunc @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Little Hitler supports no one but dictators and himself and criminal family! #worstpotusever !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me da arrechera que me dejen un sticker en visto. https://t.co/jDYA8RMci8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my melatonin in my parents rooms so my depressed ass isn’t sleeping 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nephew, Henry Morgan Kenyon, arrived this morning, quickly and sweet as pie. 😍😍😍 @ Springfield, Massachusetts https://t.co/0ByhcGm9re]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be no business dealings between U.S. citizens and Russia. It should be a Fed offense if found out. Blo… https://t.co/oJdi0FImZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @MattWhitaker46 You mean he won't be held accountable for perjury, just cuz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your mother should have taken birth control. It’s obvious she hated you. #Narcissist #LiarInChief… https://t.co/gR78yCDRY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff It’s too late.  They’re grasping so at straws because they know their world is closing in on them.… https://t.co/j8dllKfdUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh this performance was FANTASTIC. He sure did show those judges what David could do. They loved it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CestLaVie504 That’s too damn much. David’s Bridal got nice dresses for all body shapes for $99. Just pick a color there and let them live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special thank you to @cj_emmons for having me last night at @luxecitycenter with the #NextLevelLive Band presente… https://t.co/6WvnExfAQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorresHadley @cansadissima_ @666looeesa @RWitherspoon I love this book! It would make an awesome movie! @tjenkinsreid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Peas In A WOD take 2nd at #WinterDuo it was a blast. Glad My man can still keep up with the youngins and compet… https://t.co/4KpajTMC01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to counting calories &amp; attempting to track macros. I’m NOT good at this but I’ve got to practice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson Remind the guys that you have WON the voice 2 years in a row!!! That's quite an accomplishment!!!! #guysforteamkelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being watched @ #Notchbrewing #pidgeonpose @ Notch Brewery &amp; Tap Room https://t.co/OPQwTmLu6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJellyman @bodyfit67 @PizzaPortBeer @ArrogantBastard @2ndChanceBeerCo @badhopper @zappafaye @JonMontag @lhtetrick… https://t.co/NBXGkMbiyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently at a Fleetwood Mac concert....if you know me, you know I’m prob peeing myself rn of excitement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 1004 Leeward Way # 1004 #Solomons #MD  #realestate https://t.co/rww0E51ZFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us today @magerkshorsham for @SportsRadioWIP #BirdsTownHall The entire airstaff will be here throughout the da… https://t.co/sTj1CHUUMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez: Trump is ‘Scared’ of Socialism https://t.co/sdMvMbM2fK via @LibertyHeadline]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Nobody really has the balls to maintain a problem with me.” - something an awful contestant on the bachelor said that resonated lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is fueling all my Nightmare Before a Christmas/Coraline fantasies, oh my god]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioAttolini Un chairo apoyando su argumento en un periódico chairo. Pues, qué ardidos... https://t.co/3ID4MSQSUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRAYING4 our soldiers....rainDancersPrayerWarriors united...holding hands 24/7...... https://t.co/AiqZUu3ZSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re moody for no reason stay away from me. I don’t need that energy in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful ❤️🌈 Wednesday! #DrewCrew #DES #iloveschool https://t.co/oFCV9eyQ9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abortions hurt the mother. Do ADs asking,”Now that sex is so available, are all your heartbreaks, worth it? Killing… https://t.co/dGt182sEIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why I woke up with Fergie’s “rendition” of the national anthem stuck in my head 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paused my treadmill: “I drank too much wine last night for this sh*t”  The guy next to me has not stopped laughing for 5 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @espn @SportsCenter I 100% agree, that man at work trying to do his job. There has to be boundaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My honey really do be putting down on me😭 not wanting me to go no whereeee🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gee it’s ok if Obama did it, but if it had been Trump it would cause a riot! Wonder who paid for it when Obama inst… https://t.co/s5yKdB7MuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@get_higgie I’m sorry that theatre doesn’t get the recognition they deserve, but that doesn’t mean you need to talk… https://t.co/AENSrscadX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad when you see “Breaking News” on a muted tv and it’s a car crash and you hope that the Premier in it. And b… https://t.co/OhvCm05kgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ew people fr be like this and it’s disgusting.. I’d be fine with my man giving me lint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolf744 @emimartinez28 @roxyrm2014 @Cabrosa18 @baladonEve @fabiannirv @luisrolando12 @HuronPais @jgamorin @bugabea… https://t.co/6fGXyfcOF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE @VegasToyCon Hopefully, They won’t stop The Man from coming to Syracuse on Sunday🤨We got the signs..… https://t.co/5oBsXPpdZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanDolan You do what’s best for you guys❤️❤️ Take some more time if needed🤧❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correcting the Record: District Spending on Teacher Salaries https://t.co/MgsjJUwBGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your trying to teach church people you have to speak church language. 1 Corinthians 9:23 @ Chesapeake, Virginia https://t.co/g5XXiGFzmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceDiaries @theanchoredblog That's the Tinmel Mosque high in the Atlas Mountains - it's no longer used and is som… https://t.co/xB53Tji1Hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird because I love looking at videos of dogs. But now I can’t even watch them without getting physically sick...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s reverse your tax bill.  That would be a better start as it would positively impact more people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y my baby come out looking like a bulldog tho 🐶 (if you don’t roast your kids are you even a parent) https://t.co/GDzgj03lrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me basically closing on thursday nights and opening at 6:30 am friday mornings 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PEARLS put down their electronic devices and enjoyed learning to double dutch.They took a deep dive into creati… https://t.co/82U7WUYum5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterarnie Holy shit! Two of my favorite things clashing! ❤️ That's pretty fucking funny too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but I’m really testing my luck driving knowing damn well I can barely see]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinesherry I dunno a cold shower probably sounds pretty nice if you’ve been wandering in the desert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F5_Jackson I may live in Fort Myers but knowing U from Canes football 🏈 let me know what U need. Maybe younger people like U can bring hope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sullivan704 @CIAnderson3 @NewmannMichael @AwulKimberly @fuckthewall2019 @TheMoralWitness @TheyAreWeAlso… https://t.co/SSN43yjz9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElvisDuranShow I love the saying “what others think of me is none of my business” #picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I start spiraling I immediately go and buy a bunch of jjong pcs and stuff to make me feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerMeltdown This place is an absolute dream, I am so excited for this year. thank you guys for all the hard wor… https://t.co/fY5HEUMqxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhMyMithrandir I've definitely ranted about him before, hes the reason I never wanted anything to do with that community]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always look so short in touch up pics 😂 Lip touch ups on beautiful bride mrsmaggiebaker on her #nyewedding… https://t.co/TvXNHdN8M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dominic__Smith That being said I don't blame you for deleting his comments. Flat earthers and anti-vaxxers massive… https://t.co/HSyL6LL3J7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeMistyB I'm sorry. Sending you positive energy &amp; extra vitality... I feel you. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SushiSanSays @regledujeu @cmclymer My first thought was “let’s do a go fund me.” You can get a solid used car for &gt;10K.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justin_Marks_ so...dare we hope for a season 3 elsewhere? Counterpart is such an achievement.  PS the brilliant Ol… https://t.co/WkQ8U2E6no]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so inspired by this image. I cannot even imagine what she went through. That’s why I wanted to share her stor… https://t.co/W7UfGYsXbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It means robbing the diligent to finance fools it means subsidizing sin and bad Behavior and punishing the ambitiou… https://t.co/fhV2NXyK5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great quote from my new friend and great leader. Thank you Kelly @KellyCardenasLV . LEAD ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigrickgoblue @KamalaHarris Privatization to College that’ll get rid of the low hanging fruit and stupid classes like Lesbian studies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Protoje @RebelutionMusic Portland, ME ❤. Check out Bentley's207 delivery while in town. @weedmaps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenville’s family Steam night was so much fun! Mrs. Mack and Mrs. Wolf had students create a chick house for thei… https://t.co/cdihbok9VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We look for something in others to make us whole. We neglect the inevitability of exploring and touching every corn… https://t.co/ffpcq9cuZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[VALentines or GALentines? 💕 tag ur boo or ur bestie!! // what are you doing to celebrate? i’ve got a GALentines par… https://t.co/38KUINcm3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday already!? #sponsored When do you typically start your week - Monday? Sunday? I know for me it's different ea… https://t.co/iOhRvit83A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t coach losers. @MikeCoachk tells his team to motivate them!   Best #duke comeback in @DukeMBB history!! https://t.co/wge7210XIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all stay begging (and I said what I said) for money on this free app... I am always curious where are your friend… https://t.co/gljIg9CIQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rewind #Vacation #LastCall That moment you get busted using the Elevator Lobby for a recording studio 🤘🏼😆 #Maida… https://t.co/W5ASYeN8Fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algebra and algebra 2: CR 23 closes tonight! @emlong_1 @Bri11Hansen @Jstouttt @Carolynfitz2 @JoshuaHoyt11 @AjPeck220 @duesler]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all my fellow analog buddies! I’ve always just used @ILFORDPhoto fibre paper but maybe I’ll try something new n… https://t.co/MuB7AroOMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethAnnCarney and #dynamath acts as a station where they read articles together and then work as a team to answer… https://t.co/asrgBcJ620]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatWitchUKnow @TomiLahren Yup, but she shows just how irrelevant she is with those thoughts.  I am a Veteran, I d… https://t.co/2oK1DeBCDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisEngle @Mondoisbool I used to bleach my hair all the time. I cringe about it (I get it professionally done no… https://t.co/msr7Ar8zoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting tickets today means i’m expecting a good month March...........]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michyah_ Facts! They buss but she trynna tell me Burger King nuggets better then Mcdonalds]]></document><document><![CDATA[For many reasons, I feel I’m not great@at driving around in FL. Making it work though. #SpringTraining #Florida]]></document></documents></author>