<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday so you know @YounglifeAUC is back once again with #themove tonight at 8:17pm at @morehouse Kilgore Facu… https://t.co/vyUglVbRfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueKofi you definitely deserve a WWE Championship title run. Lasts night performance inside the chamber was aweso… https://t.co/ql9JY76AqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 1 at Class 1A Westminster Christian Regional: No. 8 Westminster 11, No. 10 Elgin Academy 8. #DHpreps https://t.co/EczaMUaSH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not up to speed on the news surrounding this guy, and this is *maybe* an unpopular opinion but nevertheless it is m… https://t.co/uPvRrDmOl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WarrenBuffett Says 3 Decisions in Life Separate High Achievers From Mere Dreamers @MarcelSchwantes https://t.co/EbQ6EMTh94 via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCRadio The next Pats № 2 WR is going to be some undrafted FS who was ready to begin his new job at a warehouse… https://t.co/jxg0p6nIwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchBenn It's gonna be no deal. It was always gonna be no deal. There's no coalition for anything else. I expect… https://t.co/nb1x9DuM6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimgeraghty You're concerned about the picture? That which neither physically nor mentally incapacitated no one?… https://t.co/uizP05ssjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveinDiego @GOP @realDonaldTrump That’s exactly how you know you have it! There’s a world of difference between h… https://t.co/bpGRiUjD9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me finally mustering up the energy to come out of my room after 36 straight hours:   My roommates:]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA TAXPAYERS.IF YOU ARE ABLE TO READ THE ENGLISH GRAMMAR AND SCRIPT.CHECK AMERICAN S… https://t.co/xFswmSifWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rushlemania Krillin was one suprise after another in the dbz universe https://t.co/EbYOatmxGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the face of every fan in #LakerNation 😭 https://t.co/r7ixruTSK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the Space Force Can Restore Our Edge Against China, Russia | The Stream https://t.co/sqJs3CRrTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyeMartinNBC so much easier to find the open lanes with this bright Snow Moon this morning! https://t.co/V2lfrrlBvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diputadospan Soy Panista;  Uds.  q han ofrecido además de estas descalificaciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkinSawyerr @JasonLaCanfora I don’t think talent is evenly distributed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LusciousLips_36 @BigMeatyFlaps2 @BabesPromo_2 @Honey_B69 @I_luv_reds @PantyWatch @Real_Girls6 @gspot1177… https://t.co/RcQb4MNP5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going on at the border @Acosta  The guns used are from Fast and Furious. Mixed in with the ATF gunrunner pr… https://t.co/EN6gYUyq25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny Acosta has gained at least 4X the density of his gray matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JHarry The people that say this would last 12 hours max if they were in the book Hatchet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣 This one cracked me up hard😂. I remember a realtor who would call any ceiling a high one. Thinking about it now… https://t.co/2TS8BJG6ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kell_M40 That’s just the way the game changed...it still took Mike 3000 more shots...and he’s averaged less assist… https://t.co/1sPqJUkVI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[❗En MONTERREY También lo estamos deseando ❗ 🇲🇽 🤘🎶🎸  Showcase y #FirmaDeDiscos de @HombresG En @MixupTeam… https://t.co/TktytbXT8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceyWalker91 @RondelWalker @mjwarrior03 @pcWESTbball405 Now that some good stuff!!!! 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredcwilson @Sams_Antics @juliagalef Amen sir. Having regrets over becoming a parent is a really sad proposition.… https://t.co/hb0HE2taii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_BLACK19 @D_Lowe2 Haha. Nobody noticed and no none cared about the guy who is absolutely OBSESSED with BYU 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well anyway does anyone want to make snowman ,go sledding or make hot Chocolate because I don’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mensah clear MOTM for me. Zack for the PK save I guess is the other choice, but no other field players have done much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 4: Challenge accepted from @wstemlibrary to post seven books I love —no explanations, no reviews. Each time I p… https://t.co/VqNrsVBFBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvnkoo @AmerUrological @UrologyCareFdn Flying in tonight, any tips for a first time attendee?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillionsRefs @SHO_Billions @DavidLevien @BillionsWriters Wow. I can’t wait to deep dive later today. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRINArockstarr Yes you look good in gorgeous in beautiful in  sexy yes ur Trina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance4gardener @Beantowndougish @JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @lynn_maryellen @FrankBenXXXOOO @MynameisMok… https://t.co/1TTtzleYfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaner5dude @jroc2210 @23MattWatts @krsaundry @jwattzzz @ProFootballTalk What?lmao the team “owns” that players rig… https://t.co/vRXfdSB7wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know these nice folks, give them hugs today!    Congratulations!     We love helping families make homeowner… https://t.co/QlqqSKpXgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Utterly pathetic, needy, sad really.  A broken and miserable man is Trump.  Right Fat Pants? @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamLover69 @espn @SpectrumSN I wonder how many reliability awards it had won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 12:15pm... Light Snow has moved into Omaha. Light accumulation under an inch is possible. https://t.co/W53IJyrn6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rick promised the money would be there when it came time to land a superstar FA. If him, and ultimately Jerry, fail… https://t.co/VBs2HU1hI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekjohnston @PaulLeeTicks Trump Jr. is in a constant battle to maintain his status as the second-most despised person in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it’s written in the #content   -  #essentiallistening #prodigy #thelawalbum #whatanalbum #ripkeithflint🖤 @ Earth https://t.co/eiRzModlIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcrim13 @counter_culture Haven’t even seen the film. Just love the song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gizmodo: Over 100,000 #Lego Bricks Were Used to Recreate the Final Battle of #StarWars: The #LastJedi.… https://t.co/k6LOT78vfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manchu89 @STEPHMHAMILL @RashidaTlaib @LynnePattonHUD @RepMarkMeadows They are what’s sad in America today! Nasty people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwyllys We have one in Wisconsin Rapids. They play in the stadium where the Twins A team used to play (a long time… https://t.co/BRR7sM3DtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My distinguishing marks are wonder and despair.”  - Wisława Szymborska, from “The Sky.”  Via @DavidKanigan  https://t.co/rFmf46MqOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mustread 💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎… https://t.co/gUBtWH1WFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you use your time, talents, team or treasures to help others live their dreams? Had my friends at… https://t.co/sqr41cTrnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[SeaQuacks, you're a running team there's no need to pay tons of money for a 1/4 back , let R.Wilson go  someplace e… https://t.co/kGLYyooLB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prksxo @marklopeztkd @RealDeanCain The little lights aren’t twinkling clark]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazyCommie @laratablog @bennyjohnson @NancyRPearcey @AOC @Amtrak Exactly and it works for them, come on what count… https://t.co/5PXYdmwHEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has a bad day, you never know, especially when you are targeting someone in groups, when a person might sa… https://t.co/mwz8vvFfzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for you recognizing this problem. This is why @SpeakerPelosi  should be POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interstate 790 Utica Marsh on 2/23/19 https://t.co/FNXmN87VVG https://t.co/16RjYAPBYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just farted hella nasty in this Lyft, pretty sure he’s pissed and he’s gonna give me a bad rating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my bro @jcwheeler14 after a great workout today💯🏋️‍♂️💪 https://t.co/pAPGAxoRfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 But it isn’t clear, baby!?  How is it not clear to them!? They all have great insurance and should all be… https://t.co/HJ7gp9I601]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kentuckyweather 4 Years Ago Today On The South Side of Lexington Bro GO CATS. #BBN #kywx https://t.co/jjFV2BogXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What looks or materialistic things have to do with treating a man or woman right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @govtdude This idiot thinks tax avoidance is a bad thing. #TaxationIsTheft]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InTheBooth for @hplax action on @GameOnSportsPro https://t.co/wiaQQK6JWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m only scared of 2 things.                        1. Sharknado.                                               2. Communists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously you put the other heisman candidates on that Ohio State team and they lose at least 4 games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff I think the donuts that @realDonaldTrump is eating  @ #MarALago should file lawsuit requiring #Trump… https://t.co/9KvLGJTJer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobGrozandTom just finished yesterday’s show on the podcast page. Absolute gem of an appearance by @DailyHombre]]></document><document><![CDATA[A snippet from a solo I did recently on tour with @itsdorothysucka at @regenttheaterla - shot by my mate @johnbach… https://t.co/A44kyPIybL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacksonlutz @MadduxThomas10 Man i know how much you ride Beal so I had to make sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blong311 Thanks! Hope life is swell for you and congrats. on the engagement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerGehman1 Nah, it's cool to just run up on the concourse and fetch balls, seemingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@empiresesquire Ive been learning how to trade stocks and I’ve learned that they Can be manipulated by any news lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce @HousefromDC He should refuse the MRI. Not show to any workouts. Declare for the draft. He would still go 7th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I've lost, I need back and then some! Ask, Believe and Receive! 🗣AMEN and Good Day My Peoples]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LaLigaxRCN en 1986, gol de Juan Manuel Battaglia, media distancia, arco sur del Pascual Guerrero a Millonarios. Un… https://t.co/TxFTpItbJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[PR chain out in full effect at the Wildcat Cup! Monica Ruelas in 800m, Shaelynne in javelin/200m, Anesa 100mH, Jack… https://t.co/Ae347Zx2Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zauberkraft1208 Yes. We'll all at one time breathe the cold air. A week ago I bought a new winter jacket. Tomorrow… https://t.co/IMYcii39jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started the day off earlier (circa 4:35am) with a practice session on the #bagpipe practice chanter! No better way… https://t.co/6LUV9l8lB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Godsgirl158 @cnnisbiased @Catywood @DawnFVanCise @TrumpsAsianChic @PTSD_SURVIVOR @sfrius @CharleyAustin… https://t.co/OV2GDRnh3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikPlenty @UfoSunday @RokStarrMom @WhitleyStrieber Everything he’s ever said about it has been wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last sasha and bayley were ring together at full sail it was nxt takeover respect and now they back  were it al… https://t.co/9kNNnMudqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished episode 2 of @tntedtech love to give @Raspberry_Pi @ascollins @Dana_Augustin @KyleJwilke and I a shou… https://t.co/nONDpD5koU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VBarCaracol @JulianCaperaB @SheylaGarcia07 Mejor mándala para el alargue que está pésimo desde que Diego y Julián salieron]]></document><document><![CDATA[New study looks at why Neolithic humans buried their dogs with them 4,000 years ago https://t.co/1Ywh4DbJPi via @SmithsonianMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to remind yourself that everything will be okay. You’re going to be alright. Life is crazy sometimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Digby_C @EricBoehlert That's not a bad idea.  I watched ALL The 2016 Debates on C-Span.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFTCommenter  girl on live pd just got arrested in an alstott Jersey. Apparently not enough grit. https://t.co/6oGBAGd6QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! Each miss made me cringe. Like seeing someone put milk in before the cereal! @OhKemoSaabie @altemus13]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 - DAY 52: What goals did you set for today? What will you accomplish? How will you use your 24 hours, 1440 min… https://t.co/3zfnAtEf2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalanstr @NevadaJack2 Whatever happened to the Democratic Party? Disgusting - plain and simple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistwire @chuckm @QuinnyPig You must have been in some Latin American country when you heard it and started laughi… https://t.co/Bac3aw8QTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTFox5 @kevinsweather @DCAreaWx Massive snow flakes falling on Pennsylvania Ave NW. Roads in the area are compl… https://t.co/dNacZan3EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me tomorrow refreshing the Twitter timeline to see if the @GoldenKnights make any trades #nhltradedeadline… https://t.co/gdZsqD8562]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at the "Belle" for birthday mimosas! @ Lani Kai Island Resort https://t.co/tWrRe9zNAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bohicasis @IanMargolWPLG @doug_hanks I have learned that venues just want to make a fast Almighty buck. The same n… https://t.co/EBNPoOYOfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a handjob is like eating a granola bar for a meal, sure it’s satisfying a need, but...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending regular season with 1 last game in Vermont! #UNITEDINBLUE #PTM #RIVERHAWKNATION @ Gutterson Fieldhouse https://t.co/pur6UeIRPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched A Star Is Born today. Did I cry? Ya damn right I did. Felt like @Chris_Hawkey]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got me ! I shouldn't just drop off. I found out that people dislike sign offs and yelling !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Levin3 Yeah the push notifications w emojis might be the worst/ most cringe thing they do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escalators showcasing the team loyalty of the Statue of Liberty in Las Vegas #dasvegas2019 @ New York - New York Ho… https://t.co/iS219Dbsr4]]></document></documents></author>