<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to think I have a slight band shirt (and definitely hat) addiction... ❤️🎶👚🧢 https://t.co/gnXR4t5A4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCageRepo @HappyAndFreex13 @PhilliesMike @jonmorosi @Lakers @MLB @MLBNetwork @Bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBINSIDER_… https://t.co/hEGaORLkws]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is shocking in Canada. A pro gun abusing a patient governance process against a doctor who literally saved the… https://t.co/Cpu5ViaS7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill The NJ state senate should work on the taxes people pay there and get off the national stage until that's… https://t.co/xCEKOhhb6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going with God’s version of my #story.  #WomensHistoryMonth #WeAreMoreThanAMinorityParticipationGoal… https://t.co/Y40Q8Lh5fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamLedger Wrong the America people do not want an Non America on any committee. She is a bad choice for Rep in her state. Get her OUT!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ Scary! Only God can judge you. Never live for people r, fake people.  Be real with God. And than be… https://t.co/6hlGEWim5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolvesforKamala @PhilDaTrainer @LisaTalmadge @nocompliance1 @KaylaraOwl @KathleenSoprano @Chrisnotmypotus… https://t.co/EVREIBhJcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antler_express  Junior-Senior parents join our @AntlerPostProm page. After Prom costs around 10K to provide the ki… https://t.co/193uVN6H1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposting @jaq518: - via crowdfire  #quotes #selfcare #motivation #wisdom #truth #choices #life #selfworth… https://t.co/huD8nqagux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZJudkins @PreetBharara I got it from a reliable source. 😂 Look at my feed. I retweeted the source where I got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who’s heading to Flagstaff to see her brother play some spring football?! This girl! 🏈🌲💙🏔Let’s gooooo, ginoca… https://t.co/rKy0N6hsKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Gate B28 - @atlanta_airport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/nqw5CSGqVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It grosses me out that anyone would ever microwave leftover pizza. That is disgusting. Don’t be awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que fácil decir te quiero cuando estamos solos... Lo difícil es hacerlo cuando escuchan todos... ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you don’t have any games but some of your boys play tonight.  2 games in the same gym and cheering for 3 teams… https://t.co/mwR83NcEVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveRamsey For sure. Just bought a car for first time with CASH. even though had the cash and the plan, still stun… https://t.co/s5IHJlUjKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Okbabyyt @taylor_meenan @BallingerMom You guys too? What the heck! This is ludicrous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's laughter all around us. #humor #chuckle #smile #merry https://t.co/A5YRaqCHJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock It Girl! OWN IT! Like only you can. You are you're own competition, stop holding you back 🙅🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/v5iJ18tsfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christraynor I’m fortunate that my children , my sister, my brother, my father and my step mother all love me! If… https://t.co/RPiUNnugUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your inconsistency, reaks of uncertainty and fear.. Don’t worry, I’m not afraid. But I’ve realized, you may be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@co_rapunzel4 @keanothedog @HMiglino @kaysintBB @BlueTsuni @Thedude67111 @ldog562 @Freebearphil @EveScottGarner… https://t.co/y0KCv5M6R1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics I am curious as to why the black woman that stood up as mark meadows denied his racism allowed herself… https://t.co/2YVyjPo3Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealThndrMonkey I love Finn and Rose, I just don’t think Finn feels that way about her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cont’d: 3rd graders in #JMCSS recently read Peter Pan and wrote a 4-paragraph Book Review, including: the title, au… https://t.co/p8AsavyEMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I got to do laundry, go to the gym, and then send some nudes, i don’t know”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapiLady52 @TheAnuhart @NewDay Hold ur horses. I’m asking a question that’s not harassment. U said he’s not a Demo… https://t.co/9ebvhLXc3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeNewsHuntres @DonaldJTrumpJr He takes after his daddy. Maybe they can arrange for adjoining cells.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im at the stage where my microbladed brows are scabbing over and all I want to do is scratch them 😬😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump reminds me of the person who jumps at the first opportunity to push another's button as soon as they see a po… https://t.co/W8DiKhZeQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Score got 4000! Can we get to 5000 this next week before LivePD next week! @JAKE61697355]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who will win the big bucks? Announcing the winner soon! Fun day with all the finalists at #MITFinTech. @MIT… https://t.co/5pFtAb3H8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my parents were dating, my mom let my dad drive HER car from South Carolina to Atlanta for Freaknik while she… https://t.co/0eOx6dqYIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My azaleas finally decided to make their appearance in the back yard. 🌺  #azalea #azaleas #azaleacity #flowergram… https://t.co/IDvJHLSjSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are off work and kids are off school but I still have to fucking come to school 🙄 what kind of bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSN Why is anyone surprised? Trump does not deal in facts, nor does he tolerate people disagreeing w/ his gut (i.e… https://t.co/k4abtv2KDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all of our members and supporters who attended the Virginia Glass Guild's 2019 Member's Exhibition hos… https://t.co/EPEbR6WLuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[my French friend is in town and wants to go to Magic City lmao let’s see which of my guy friends wants to sponsor the evening...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherity1313 Put a cup over it to keep it contained until someone else can take care of it. Or just be like me and… https://t.co/rJ55NGoOIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalNappingDay falls on a Monday. This is either a great idea, or a cruel joke. I can't decide!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder if chicken loves me as much as I love it. And then I think, chicken can’t love, then I eat it. The end]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some comedy. Cute Dinosaur card - T-rex I love you this much, love card, Valentine's Day card, Anniversary.… https://t.co/HrzKxf0elf]]></document><document><![CDATA[watch a million little things &amp; hulu right now &amp; once you do pls venmo to express your gratitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kassii_x3 😂😂😂😂😂 sameeeeeee lol &amp; most definitely man 🤘🏼 it was a struggle but I’m forever grateful ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this episode of The #Jenallee Show to see our top 5 #fetc Take Aways! Be aware, we may sound like an alie… https://t.co/goWIBOJaf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Grateful for #MyLife 💓🌨🌫🏔☃️❄️🎉 Keepin’ it #Real since 1969! 😁#365DaysOfGratitude @ Colorado Springs, Colorado https://t.co/27T6Pt7M7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[imma buy a ticket to neon indians dj set and i hope I run into someone I know bc imma be alone on this one lol  I j… https://t.co/SM1xp62Mfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point Michael Cohen needs to be hauled bodily in front of congress and questioned publicly. His excuses are wearing thin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningJoe 2/ Barclays was ugly. Lots of fights lots of lawsuits but eventual buy in.  Ratner the Developer was he… https://t.co/csViMIaTWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked for preworkout ideas and of course @MariahGaffney replies with “coke and i mean the kind you snort” 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LingZhiTweet @mmpadellan I don't think this is really about the misinformation.  It is about the company she keeps… https://t.co/Hmnu0VjfdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever a boy you dig is telling you he’s picking up a “sweetheart” from the airport because “he’s close” lolololo… https://t.co/JlV9waxV2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you sit on my couch, there’s an enormous chance that you’ll have a warm fuzzy thing snuggle up into the small of… https://t.co/i5XwmOktbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mawa de visita por las oficinas de @atrasalante   #Atrasalante #petfriendly #Monterrey https://t.co/8U6SjKgZGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge: Paul Manafort, the president’s onetime campaign chairman, lied to federal investigators after plea deal.… https://t.co/LzFBQPwJoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[A PRIVILEGED, BLACK and GAY man tried to not ONLY blame our @POTUS , but cause a race war, when there was no need!… https://t.co/hwsC3QfW4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids were thrilled to meet @erinhamlin and @jterdimanUSA today... Team USA 🇺🇸 luge Olympians!!  What a great event… https://t.co/dtuJ3McjUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[All clinicians should read this! Purdue Pharm infiltrated “Pain: the fifth vital sign” into hospitals and Doctors o… https://t.co/UIoC5O4FhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son, @Tom_phly, is so happy right now! And I am so proud. 😊 Mainland has two very dedicated teachers/overachieve… https://t.co/M7h9LjBsGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CellaredKatie I would’ve missed it if you didn’t point it out, but I totally see a blue whale! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better late than never - couldnt join last night but reflecting with my PLN at bfast #waledchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BawlingStevn @mkraju Oh bullshit. Leading up to the 2016 election Trump was front and center every single morning… https://t.co/87IxLhHTFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m loving all of the biopics of bands from the 70s-80s coming out. Queen, Elton John, Mötley Crüe, &amp; whatever may come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profkarenpski @jayasax Every San Franciscan but me has a Robin Williams story. But lo, that *might* have been him… https://t.co/KD7OhW7T3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flooring Specialist Alexander Lewis teaching our Wall Tile Do-It-Yourself workshop today @HomeDepot store 4003!  Gr… https://t.co/UFvT36QGlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lakelife #lakelbj #texaswinter @ Highland Haven, Texas https://t.co/pROZRpK9gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn @ManMet80 F-you, Bernie. Not sure I can take months of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEVELOPING: Flames of Liberty forecasted to reach record heights as @AP4Liberty joins other notable Libertarian/Rep… https://t.co/MgwBkbKzhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FairContractNow #CTUACTSstrike #CICSGreed #WhereIsShaw #CICSSchools #KindaBigDeal #AreWeCICS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is arm day. - @bradleymartyn . "All kinds of gains." - @hodgetwins . "Keep moving forward." -… https://t.co/94JAhHHkzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Virginia lawmaker Eric Porterfield has advocated for discrimination against LGBTQ people, compared us to the K… https://t.co/hvj8nYDTPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gunna brag for a second I taught my first lesson in my class today &amp; it went amazing / better than expected! Couldn’t be more happier!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t take her long to become corrupt! She’s only doing this for the money, as much as she can lie, cheat or steal… https://t.co/U9zPGjGpvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of those 2 men for speaking out. It’s not easy to come forward after having to lie to themselves for s… https://t.co/2uQ8qnwHbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All kidding aside, if everyone did yoga, we would have world peace.” Rory Freedman Midnight yoga is a fun way stud… https://t.co/oy9orqCS9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "ACCE Inustry Networking Event " https://t.co/Yuh8Efil05 @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The next time you hashtag, the next time you tweet, think about the power your click has.” Incredibly strong endin… https://t.co/opBdmYbg4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Kelton House in Columbus, OH w/ @jelisalovely https://t.co/5FQxkreF7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @politico Why?only goes to show that something STINKS in the WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@west1stsouth2nd Hi, Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swithout p… https://t.co/sveetcTbWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fantastic Goodwill find today - a Ruffwear sleeping bag for Ayashe. He seems to be rather fond of it (yes, there… https://t.co/lY7I7l2g6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Monday brings a 3:30 wake up call, this mug rings truest.  #ICanNotToday https://t.co/Nop51u2c8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSHS_GirlsBBall @coachblake_zito Congratulations, Coach. I’ll come to the next home game! 💜💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachballard I thought I remembered you. My dad was the principal @ Lakeview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shell_bee1231 @xbellebear @gabzirra But seriously MJ helps with pain relief for my back and shoulder when I was in… https://t.co/WdxAnSrpdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aninsanemetsfan @MLBPipeline @whitesox @scottmerkin @BhamBarons @WSDashBaseball @Intimidators @gfvoyagers How's th… https://t.co/EwlbiRYdz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh The ONLYthing he deserves credit for is being #THEWORSTPRESIDENTEVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaegenic Don’t let people’s negativity dampen your awesome. Congrats!! https://t.co/WgctnO46Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gee, I wonder Why? Fercrissakes, let’s stop using that word “meddling” in reference to Russia’s attack on this coun… https://t.co/S1CHUfOFDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[hold a baby here and she is a slave inside of the Nation of Islam who want to control other people's life; therefor… https://t.co/Yw4SIateVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMsales15 He’s going to keep on and that guy will find his new location down here and then proceed to report the authorities on him 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrenIShiKiddo @jerry_sypek I thought there already was a law protecting babies who survive abortion. One that says… https://t.co/OQajasazsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always ask me, “what do you eat on trail?” Well, here it is. Breakfast is usually a chewy bar dipped in off-… https://t.co/H7gdja8qAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We hope your Sunday is full of what you need most. Rest well, Friends! #ErikaWardInteriors #EWIclassicStyle… https://t.co/M0yI4zhkBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TouchByXavier @SylviaPlayhouse Come in anytime after 6pm or DM for appt ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tombingham707 @amyrbrown12_amy @AboardFor @EarthSciNewsInt @OmarAlfonsoPR @WByng @selc_org @FromtheAshesDoc @AP… https://t.co/KoTBr9Rz15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJudge3 @WTCRams @emeadowschools Can you make another one of these happen???? The juniors know I LOVE Moe’s!!! Sorry I missed it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids say the darndest things! Cute idea for fathers day! Free Fathers Day Questionnaire Printable https://t.co/ZBhF7vNNvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of #internationalwomensday 👸🏻- I gotta give it up to my mama ocjudymom // I’m so grateful for her and who… https://t.co/AeHYD96c4f]]></document></documents></author>