<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[so... now that the season is officially over, here’s a 3 minute recap of how it went.  PLEASE WATCH, YOU WON’T REGR… https://t.co/61ppyimtm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of what time I set my alarm I ALWAYS wake up 10 min before it goes off fml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, 4:30 am, can’t sleep,  worried about someone I love and just not sure what to do. Open twitter, first tweet I… https://t.co/iz7yqE7AAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to throw your ultimate dream party from @PartyCity? Enter here for your chance to #win! https://t.co/LzYQOUGdoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deaszia_Chanel That’s a good problem to have! I think I’m the opposite 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1MinuteMotivation || God Wants You To "Hold It," Not Control It https://t.co/mhee5XtJI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrMatthewLC This is actually hilarious and this person definitely made up this story. Although this does happen, a… https://t.co/Ue6od8YdYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was team #TheBabySittersClub Read just about every book. But I did enjoy watching the #SweetValleyHigh tv series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the pain is definitely WORTH it, my eyebrows have been so thick every since I’ve started getting them threaded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotTheRealEarl @GiantAKS @Schultz975 ‘how’s that working out for you...being clever?’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Day One of #DeathburnDoesntDie, my daily workout posts set up to annoy your timelines and keep myself ac… https://t.co/PtY0ae6XrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2bGGqs5U8F #AnnieBananieTours #Tanked #Tour #Fun #Safe #Memories #LasVegas #Vegas #Tours #ThingsToDo… https://t.co/kp5tnnr0sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on where I live: some girl covered her ex’s car in gasoline while trying to run him over. I’m ready to move… https://t.co/Iabuy4GkjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krystine210 We probably had more fun than he did. Bless his heart! #formertomboyslol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InfoAlternat @realDonaldTrump May god forgive you. Bow your head and listen up God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleRay @TMobile @MetroByTMobile You and your guys do a fabulous job Neville.  Keep up the great work. Looking… https://t.co/9mrtGbSbT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, you guys all look so handsome!  ❤️ these special photos!  #LetsGoPens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FleerUltra @isaiah_kb I loved that movie, but now I can’t tolerate Victoria Jackson. Still love the parts without her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Interstellar for the first time (yes I fucking suck, no I don’t care) and I’m having an absolute existential crisis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@definients Hi Haley, Openwave offers you oodles of experience in delivering customer-centered and excellence-drive… https://t.co/BbJWTBeePe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTown_MrD @Google If there are no active assignments the topic is hidden.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amid Washington’s partisan battles, Trump and Democrats find rare common ground on Venezuela https://t.co/ZB17pu85nJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the building while participating is activities based on the book What Pet Should I Get? by Dr. Seuss. We incorporat… https://t.co/sXr074lJRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for #SOTB2019 while it’s not my first—it’s the first w/@galeabrewer as my #jefa @thevillagernyc @TheTandV… https://t.co/II0uBqu2Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdistaso @NHGOP How embarrassing! There was  a time when the NHGOP was a  thoughtful organization. We know how Gor… https://t.co/WmRKkAXgcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, I love ryans mom 😩 she’s really the best y’all andddd she’s letting Ryan go bungee jumping with me!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[My camillia seems to think spring is coming!   #alwayshope #springsoonerplz 🌼🏵️🌸🐞🐝🦋🐦 @ Fourth Plain Village, Vancou… https://t.co/HI14oQepno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCNetwork @QueenWillRock @adamlambert We will be watching!! A family thing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO EVEN IS GALILEO. ...guys I have an idea for a one shot #Ponderosadnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes conversations just don’t need captions https://t.co/St0dOBJVPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed with dance battles and now that I live in nyc I need to make it my mission to find some of the undergr… https://t.co/dZViEkZ15k]]></document><document><![CDATA[is eating when you’re sick even worth it? i could be eating grass and have no idea what it tastes like]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BulldogAleHouse  bulldogalehouse  @shanonlersch @princesskk1210 tiffipoo225 @MrBill667 #family @ Bulldog Ale House https://t.co/oU8ZpAh3iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This post is about the other half of Asia Art Tours: elliot trotter. The man behind our website and a great deal of… https://t.co/PoOPoiy96W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlaySkin  Eve was fallible. Ungrateful ways are not the benefits of graces. Path 31 Page 129: accede, accrue, and… https://t.co/zUJJ22xedp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arushi1411 great lightning presentation talk tonight. You had some great points for anyone progressing in their career]]></document><document><![CDATA[His love swoons me every single day... #valentinesday365 @ Hyatt Regency Valencia https://t.co/uIAOcU6SH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[100k+ Twitter followers 2000+ Facebook Groups  Over 6500 Facebook fan page likes Over 30k Instagram followers 1300+… https://t.co/K2xRsZ2PAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[JP/AP challenging my taste/maturity with beer since I chose Terminator. Says I’ll be more sophisticated when I love… https://t.co/43EFh3cpQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ernemogollones @unplebeyomas Y si nos ayuda a salir de esta oeste pues bienvenido...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @AB84 U dont have any time2waste.Ur best bet is2stay put.The grass isnt greener onThe otherSide.Worko… https://t.co/ZhK3ePHCaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferReynaTX At the rate of road closures your going to run out of roads to report on! We appreciate you Jennifer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultrahottie2000 @Joanie_Vinson @Tyler2929 @ericmartsolf Yeah and chloe being in the middle is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes! Bay area politics trying to regulate every tiny thing about our lives!  https://t.co/w4LTcqXzbY via @sfchronicle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @VP @realDonaldTrump What fucking matrix are they living in. #Bogus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorTwellman @MLS @JonChampionJC @ATLUTD Dang it! I was just a few sections to your left! ☹️☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Him: “you heard of zoom?” Me: “no” him: “well it’s like where you can visually talk to people...” Me: “....... like… https://t.co/SaF5QtiMP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what is going on in my physics class, this should be fun 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrenndaOlaldde Jajajajaja eso significa que están igual de hermosas 🥰🥰🥰🥰😘😘😘😘🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[So disappointed the youngest doesn’t feel well enough to go to school 😜💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norfolk weather straight tried it! 😂😂 Glad i got the @SouthwestAir app and changed my flight quick 😂😅 I guess I’ll… https://t.co/r7psEiSrad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaustiniMary Please verify.... Chocolate was on the saved list...true or false? Life or death.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @rocknrollgolfer Actually not strange at all. Commonplace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellCares oh  this beautiful Dell looks destroyed just like my Mac got destroyed]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one talk to me about this i cried and it's embarrassing https://t.co/iHnRCrIs3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madagascar Carnelian freeform stone; Chakra Alignment: Base, Sacral; Healing crystal for Creativity, Individuality,… https://t.co/8iYBMxt9RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’m pale my skin looks worse lmaoooo get me some fucking sunnnn please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for letting me be unapologetically me @phluidproject  • • • • • • Stylist: https://t.co/lZwbfIKSn0… https://t.co/ImPIaaJOvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time when I was really little, my brother had a fish. I didn’t realize they had to be in water to breathe and I… https://t.co/iMjtfX6s0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our own NOVA Cavs Josh Abtew of Fairfax on being selected as 2018-2019 6A Occoquan Region Second… https://t.co/NXw1ATzsJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can she name one instance where a wall didn’t work for what it was designed to do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started to read ‘The Truth About Men’ by @DeVonFranklin  And wow! I’m learning so much! Such a great book. Amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay!! @iamRuthECarter won! Whew, glad I don’t have to burn anything down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HES_Principal Can’t think of a more influential or important profession! Big ❤️and gratitude to all of our educato… https://t.co/7UooktAW6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 @RodneyClaeys LOL The pup is adorable👍😍💓💙🌈💜💚🍀❤️🔥🌪💘❤️💜💛🧡💚💙💓🌎❤️🐾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouDrivePoorly @MSignorile And this other thing happened 10 years ago. So what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am to work “you can do it now” into work conversations as much as possible. https://t.co/rCYDgSsY8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m almost 8 weeks pregnant... my mother bought me maternity jeans already...😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qweenjazz Plus the fact Jenny knew . I was so blown haha but it’s the biggest shocker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatgay_bitch I deleted FB.... it’s a cancer. Breeds negativity and hate. Downfall of ‘Merica.]]></document><document><![CDATA['A model for America': the criminal justice reformer who inspired a generation https://t.co/VirK8JWubH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeGregEaton @RobinWashut You better leave those 402’s in your bag or you’ll be hearing from @atr52 !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habitreynoville @AlfredoJalifeR_ @marvinicio @norma22flores @PerezrobJ Ahora va ser titular, lo van a sacar hasta… https://t.co/lEVhMDRdbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ll tell you one thing though, these compression socks feel GOOD”, I said to my fiancé at age 27 as I turn over to go to sleep at 9pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so happy when I get pics of cabochons and pendants they like from my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a birthday treat! Happy Birthday to our greatest Nana! https://t.co/VjOic4DMtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally me when we got caught our sophomore year @lashellevanay_  @jackson_drezelo @MilliganRory]]></document><document><![CDATA[But not the word of our intelligence agencies. How un-American is that? #InBedWithDictators #PresidentAwful… https://t.co/Gct5eXtKqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[You go first and I hold you - ok buddy, hold on tight!!!  @RedeemerOCSB https://t.co/2z91nc2Cd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalwomensday #heros 🦸🏾‍♀️#friends 👯‍♀️ #mothers 🤱🏾#daughters 👧🏾 #visionaries 👩🏾‍🏫 #queens 👸🏾#rulers… https://t.co/yyIUrG6Rwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be mad at the world too if I been in the same financial situation for the last 5 years !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf😳😳😳😳 who ask you to jump when u know u can’t jump? @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/iZ7fXegpL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I’m genetically programmed to be a killer bc of my “culture of war”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLinWood @FitLwyr It is seared into my memory. It was perfectly awful. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gangster @SenFeinstein husband is pretty badass also Dick Blum is “hella” rich with his company private equity bull… https://t.co/78RJnQvfQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just curious, do they even teach the strike zone to NCAA baseball umps anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MccahanValeen @Kulinski_crat @NateSilver538 I’m ready for a new era. 2020 can’t get here fast enough. #BERNIE2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited to be off tomorrow so I can use my back castor oil to treat my hair✨ it gonna be a treat yo self kinda day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SteveREverett! Thanks for the follow! I'm getting ready to go on #tour across America in celebration of my lat… https://t.co/qf8TkOpeRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMuller11 Nice. I might try it out. We just switched ours last week and I like it so far. I have 27 (awesome) kid… https://t.co/CQK7k5Gukz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Functional art is the perfect solution when you already have your home filled up with beautiful pieces!  For purcha… https://t.co/2YkBuNEj77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joanna_Senyszyn @MilosawReczek zmniejszy sie amerykanska turystyka do Europy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly they do not! Did my 2:50 #cupidplankchallenge 10x10 push ups and sit ups done ✅ too! #T4U10X10 @MelindaHoward4 https://t.co/xF9o5op9A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shodrewshirley Must’ve been when she broke up with Jake the hot handyman... who happened to have previously dated… https://t.co/k0hL2CNyDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[May have gone a bit overboard on the milestone pics this month 🤷🏼‍♀️ Sidney is 5 months old today! We love this swe… https://t.co/XpPCxN6HR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Love Day to Everyone!! Meet me under the bleachers 80’s and 90’s party tonight at Zebra Lounge! Bring your sw… https://t.co/fzRmjB51NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poet I am free as a Bird 🦅 2B myself.I am not a Monk who Will meditate on Black History Month. My Ancestors didn’t… https://t.co/GFHjgLGso4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My therapists office door is locked and no one is in there so who wanna be my therapist today :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind your own biscuits and life will be gravy. 😊 https://t.co/SdvjOnKffT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's infuriating that there are so few options for families in this city in general. Adding my disability to the mi… https://t.co/KjyZmcKhtA]]></document></documents></author>