<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@fox_duke @BadgerMHockey @ChrisDilks Competent and Michigan are oxymoronic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please! Release the hounds and start ripping and tearing azz! Then the real actions start, like arresting the real… https://t.co/8eMGO19hDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signed the deal yesterday. I cried too. Been through hell to get here. Finally. You’ll hear about it soon. 🏆 https://t.co/Tr81BndQac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alkoohejii23 مرة طق عندنا ثلج و تكنسل الدوام يوم و نص. فكان في دكتور كوري يبي يخلينا نداوم يوم السبت تعويض، لكن ما… https://t.co/uiAVE6ttk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioRek @dcunited @ATLUTD Acá casi que no hay comentaristas ni relatores americanos, en idioma inglés son ingles… https://t.co/nGKA8ZYl41]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's taken long enough but I've finally done it! @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/gn1nJqrqFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A salmon sky in the east. (That is NOT a flying saucer in upper left corner.) https://t.co/fyutlOWdUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melynn44 @WhatInTheH @TonyReali My solutionis to prosecute everyone who committed a crime. And to encourage people… https://t.co/pXkA1bzEv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mykingdomforad1 @MY_BORDERCOLLIE @Rubiconski @shaunwalters041 @speabud @rich752913078 @kirkconnel @creekbear… https://t.co/KrBHQzG8hF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chhhhchanges  'Houston #Texans: Fixing the offense key to 2019 season' via @fansided  https://t.co/VVu4heI93a]]></document><document><![CDATA[My relationship ended last night, so I’ll be in my funeral clothes for the next few days...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't Miss:    Viaduct gold rush: Big money flows into area around doomed Seattle highway      Via @seattletimes… https://t.co/GxLzSX0uyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soderberg the shootout winner in the bottom of the sixth. Avs leapfrog Dallas and into WC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me a week ago: “Who is this Kacey Muskrat person 😒? How did she just album of the year?”  Me now: “IM ALRIGHT WITH… https://t.co/difU0CqgEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future of American #DOAS #ADOS &amp; all of us depend on re-electing @realDonaldTrump #MAGA2020 thru 01/20/2025.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tip for you gun fetishists from the son of a deer hunter: don’t point your gun at people, even in a “joking manne… https://t.co/EyqtTegUO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dangainor Most representatives wait until they have a chairmanship before they rob Constituent Services in their D… https://t.co/ngQB54dloj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taydert0t I'm learning that a brand I love and have worn with pride for years is sponsoring all my favorite people… https://t.co/46oIqgvNqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 29.917 in, Falling Rapidly. Temperature 57.5 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 96%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even #Basketball players need their @CharlieLapson #accessories and #bling !! 💎 Had a great visit to The… https://t.co/2v0Ijts1oK]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE SHARE Come and network #RoyalStarrFF @royalstarrff royalstarrfilmfestival #RoyalStarFilmFest Filmmaker commu… https://t.co/9IYaqn8Qbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Catholic Academy Of Waterbury - @bsswaterbury in Waterbury, CT https://t.co/xEB85T1BKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[... and, one could argue, that those other entertainment properties rely on print comics to continue to develop new… https://t.co/ULcjPfWd7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayvachon @MarqeeMarie @Coheed @DirtyErn12 Oh I should mention Claudio AND Ern edited that. But I didn’t. I think… https://t.co/y4iP4gVqHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Terrible. If the evidence of wrongdoing is there, I hope the House of Representatives has the guts… https://t.co/TmSz189x0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congressman blasts air horn at Trump official who said seismic air gun tests don't harm whales https://t.co/M8nGJHfGmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTChelps How is that that the 88B route for stop at 12 Thorncliffe Pk Drive is 15 mins away and 2 buses at that ba… https://t.co/PVpj5E7g40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larrygloverlive Duke UNC,UK twice, UT twice. This is the same LSU team that lost to OK St. that’s 3-13 in Big 12,… https://t.co/VSbcKqpPBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenawilliams thank you for your commercial during the Oscars. That message was empowering. It’s no wonder so man… https://t.co/0itrF0JzH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWENetwork We want All Japan on the network!  #AllJapanProWrestlingclassics https://t.co/EbNBXY3wSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if male strippers make nearly as much as female strippers?   Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 Troll I don't know if this is a real person or bot or a person whom is bought but when you read the responses of… https://t.co/aLUITCGPKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primary him out. If he makes it through the primary... Don't vote democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not "bored" yet! 😜🍺 - Drinking a Tickle Creek IPA by Boring Brewing Co. @ Boring Brewing  — https://t.co/58QjyZX8Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all see the delusion. And y'all wonder why I hate men. This is the most disgusting chauvinistic comment I've ever… https://t.co/VuwPNx4OER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC We all have skeletons in are closets, they will find yours one day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greg Bird vs Luke Voit #Yankees Rd1  (Via @Eric_M888 aka Mr 4K)   https://t.co/lr6vBK93qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one understands or respects how bad this man was to people. The Dallas one is the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBobb20808476 Not from any reliable sources. Just Trumpers trying to win b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I have no idea where they go from here. Don’t sign guys like Josh Harrison or Adam Jones. Just let the guys pla… https://t.co/bA9viWyJbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If AOC and Ilhan Omar is leading the Democrats in this direction...what is the Democrats future agenda concerning I… https://t.co/EHyPwRIKi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me get in on this. There’s NO way Everton get anything out of the derby today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok...I know it’ll never happen but I want Meryl, Sissy, and Jessica Lange to present Best Actress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolynporco Or BURN up an entire city. Not a good idea.  Also, why put solar arrays in space (aside from powering… https://t.co/OjiDgmDI3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can read this, you’ve helped me reach 10 followers. Thank you! This is so amazing🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩🤩😀😁😂🤣😃😄😅😆😉😊😋😎😜 https://t.co/8mMnDDNYM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sentinel_KabFGC For me it was just a show I never got around to starting. I was catching up on jojo but I just had to give this a chance 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said on Saturday it would take something crazy for St. John’s to hop into the 2nd seed in the MIAC.    Sure enoug… https://t.co/f5YY5mAJDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestCoastVino Yeah, I admire the enthusiasm, but 1 star is a very big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.9.19 #Drawing: “Work in Progress: Commercial” on Gansevoort Street. https://t.co/y38kM6IWG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Air_Rhodesia @GOPChairwoman @benshapiro If it happened; it's not newsworthy.  Happens every day.  What we all do for love . . . or money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadBunnyFrank @coleyworld Nothing cultish about that at all 🙄 #Cult45]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget Janet Jackson is a musician. Not shade, I just wanna know why that information isn’t imprinted on my brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Ya, the train to nowhere, how much did it cost the tax payers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presiosaaaaaaa1 @ClarkCountySch I grew up in Minnesota. If humans got sick simply from minor changes in temperatur… https://t.co/6zE8tU7gJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samorukov gets too cute with the puck and Gafreffa scores.on a breakaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bvtdidyoudie @NHL It’s the only way this turns out to be an acceptable move]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gedeon This really is specific to evangelical Christians. Denominations rooted in deeper traditions don’t generall… https://t.co/7bvoRaB2R5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being someone who thought neither of these movies would be successful or went out of their way to use stupi… https://t.co/0KD2QOMsBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeLaSalleMexNte Una verdadera mentira. Y los valores lasallistas, apa? Pero esto no se acaba hasta que se acaba, e… https://t.co/HRgpkwEqrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry Manilow had the best performance of the weekend until I watched my Dad jump off the #Stratosphere...monkey se… https://t.co/Ehd3eCa86h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aballinga @TorontoStar Back in the McGuinty era, Ben Chin proposed gov't payments under the table to Toronto Star… https://t.co/9MlSE7ISkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Natasha_Crain @alisachilders 1. Progressive Christian proponents are numerous. What sets Nadia Bolz-Weber apart fr… https://t.co/98QEGZXUKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class 2A Area Brackets via @OSSAAOnline   #PrepHoops https://t.co/UNOqD3ceh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[HS BB - 9C tourney from Havre - GIRLS Fort Benton 65 Turner 51 Final #mtsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeroFlawgem @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/UA1GxfN0ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Coppell, TX? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/aJ0XAa9Hhn #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[I donated to 'Support for Travis Hayes' -  https://t.co/RENdHktzdN via @gofundme My buddy Travis has been diagnosed… https://t.co/1Cr5wltt1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyTurko @drbulentdogan I love the recruit aspect because almost everybody is on social media and its a easy wa… https://t.co/VckUpbLJqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiMathis @thehill Or a better reply "Alexandria would love to respond but she is busy crawling on her hands and… https://t.co/zhJHO2y3AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess this is a challenge for a few men which is very strange to me. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting look at the AB situation and the lack of accountability for his actions. More about things around him i… https://t.co/6x5JLbdnl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ziyaziba @TeamPelosi Nothing surprises me with this 300 lb pile of orange fecal matter.. He cares about nobody but… https://t.co/gAwde9TwiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA['The Way of The Shinobi' (Movement Montage) has been approved on the Community Creations page!  Of course you don't… https://t.co/7NdYVfOuqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to our outdoor season with double p.r. for our junior Alejandra Rosales from Marina  Discus133-3 (40.61… https://t.co/HAeUqVfFAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh huhhh! (@ Juliette &amp; Chocolat - @juliette_choco in Montréal, QC) https://t.co/az9tEsS5Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in simple, easy to remember quotes.  Jim Koch said unless you are better or cheaper, you are fooling your… https://t.co/y6K7U6AEak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBonvoyAssist I recently got married and I sent in my information to change my name on my account and I haven’t ba… https://t.co/uDhwmHKEj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sir_ALeX_HooD @SorteoFALSO @pesforever10 ¿Es el mismo? Vaya hacer cosas productivas en ves de estar molestando a l… https://t.co/gxgsc9sYoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is always beautiful. Surprise invite is extended to see #tracyletts new play #LindaVistaPlay at the… https://t.co/OrLY8zU42O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @USTreasury @DEAHQ @USEmbassyBogota @usembassyve  #laundrymoney #corruption #Socialist  #Deportation.… https://t.co/1nBxjFrlRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlobenson #whiteparty #minneapolis #mpls #inviteonly #party instawhite #social #white #connect #instafriends… https://t.co/1wcckiY7MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you tell which @ASCDconf pre-con to attend? They all look amazing! Here’s an idea: bring a team to @ASCD Ch… https://t.co/tet0o3orHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIsDesigns Was working! Flew into NY this morning and almost back home now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono The bill had nothing to do with inhibiting abortion you liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattP_MN @TomPelissero @nflnetwork I heard they're trading him FOR Brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gasca_janneth Or... And hear me out, you could be the generous angel that we all know you are and get one in medium for @king_jackson43]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does the message say to you? #weare1crossland #gradseason #earnyourcapandgown #nohallwaydiplomas https://t.co/jTAGLJYv6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithgavin84 Thank you, Coach. I enjoy seeing the success of #PittWrestling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty much every game I have played so far of Apex Legends outside of 1 game and that one I ended up #2 sq… https://t.co/GQrCghZlTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I believe the @aafiron is the best team in @TheAAF. I can’t wait for the @aafexpress vs @AAFFleet because I t… https://t.co/d6CqknWkAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wisdomandgreen Ima size 11.5 so imagine how ima look 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/s8XccRKAcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And he called the name of the place Taberah: because the fire of the Lord burnt among them.” Numbers 11:3 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonlaw_wx @venmo I judge when their emojis don’t tell me why they paid someone. “Oh they are using just a wink… https://t.co/uOifI0BNhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougkammerer Ok so if I’m hanging in Baltimore tonight with friends, what time should I bounce to make it back to… https://t.co/g023upaBsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yodelodwho @ddale8 Yeah, but I can't write out the thousands of offenses with every reaction I tweet. In ADDITION… https://t.co/M8m9yFWGwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of fun  🎉🎈🥂tonight at pop-up Store #armaniboxla 🎁💄gala in Hollywood 🎥 on Melrose Place also hosted by… https://t.co/2ePQWjIoAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fisherinvest Why do you have "guaranteed income" in quotes. Annuities can pay guaranteed lifetime income. Right? I… https://t.co/bXYZPqHlIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigCatCountry No. Just no. Please don’t even think about putting this idea in Dave Caldwell’s head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a new resident of North Carolina who has a friend in sports media, I am REALLY hoping the @Panthers sign… https://t.co/Tk9xKyxEPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not love the world nor the things in the world. If anyone loves the world, the love … https://t.co/PoHS39B3oh https://t.co/QWjPP4mkNG]]></document></documents></author>