<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i hate word searches more than anything in life, and i’ve been to a bowling alley.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankiLoveMusic Went to Church, battery in watch at Wal-Mart, downtown library, and grocery store. Then home to watch a movie then TV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh Not even 5 mins into hearing Gym J. Showed himself what an angry bitter fool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannongilroy I have a hard time ‘liking’ this tweet, but congratulations!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wasn’t hella poor and could actually dress like I want to it’d be over for you hoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember i got pulled over with no mf L’s no nothing right on sunset strip high af and they let me go 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[*wide (I’ll be the happiest @Twitter  user on Earth if they ever allow editing on posts!) #CFISDChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since Dorian and I went to look at models homes and I explained to him how I wanted an island counter in our k… https://t.co/cq8ukKcQ9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing message for all women ... young or old.  Go after your dreams! Do not apologize for your skill ... or succe… https://t.co/Rg715B4vZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pumpkin will be all up on me for like a long time but if I just wrap her under my blankets beside me she’ll curl up… https://t.co/cWUpgPb458]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #sxsw #paneldiscussion on #healthjustice and the healing process when the soul is disrupted by the reality of… https://t.co/9mcFkz6HAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid is headed to state next weekend!! #keepmovingforward 💪🏼 https://t.co/M1CHVxLkUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[These so called men are so full of themselves they cannot see what asses they look like. Such disrespect earns disr… https://t.co/xWnVm1tp4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Maybe because we have more people in our country than any other time in history?]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING work this group is doing with the best teacher/mentor guiding them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por fin llegué al punto en el que me volví a enamorar de mi cuerpo y estoy demasiado feliz por eso😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[complicit if not directly involved in the violence against the Rohingya.  The events that followed the riots were l… https://t.co/1LbiNb93cr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of #40bagsin40days and again the mom station needed a redo.  Hoping that this year I’ll be keeping this place… https://t.co/lPkhACj0bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sis brings her entire makeup box and her new palettes and tells me to create bc she’s gets inspo from me 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad lil vibe 💕🎶 #LA #Cali #vibes #chill #goodtimes #lit #lounge #WhatILikeAboutMyself https://t.co/mCqakf6547]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessevondoom I totally agree, Jesse. It’s easy to forget sometimes. I will be spreading a little extra love today. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarthaEPulido @TABSE_Texas @katyisd @Sundown_e @konda_14 @kellymconway13 @shellyrzaruba @ElizabethDPaz13 So excite… https://t.co/X2yQMJz7uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun with Gina and the pets. @ Altamont, Illinois https://t.co/KuyA7zthYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericaschnitzer @jonlovett @megangailey @TrevellAnderson @michaelaWat Same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really anyone’s friend rn bc I don’t have time to be. Got bigger shit going on that I gotta put all my focu… https://t.co/Fd8eejCrWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the exact reason you mention-we want it to be a bottoms up approach and we want to work with a broad cross-sect… https://t.co/Tk4sSsMFiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracyminajjjjj @zac_yuh Ignore her and treat her like garbage not ignoring, they eat that shit up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @NatlGovsAssoc @POTUS @WhiteHouse Proper English usage is “joining POTUS and me,” not “POTUS and I.” “Me” i… https://t.co/siUMwQNU9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sourdough grilled cheese veggie sandwiches.  I used coconut oil and garlic salt for the outside of the bread to get… https://t.co/hMrdBsfGKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noahvirgile @rachsyme there’s NO way that’s $600 no way no WAY that is a FURBY on a KEYCHAIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 2AM &amp; i was looking for Goat Island 👀😂🤣🛸  Much needed laughter on a #RoughNightWithPops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aarondgettinger i am a resident Of the 5thward. And i am and alot godS followers support William calloway. Punch#61]]></document><document><![CDATA[worst part about going on vacation is making myself be ok w taking days off from working out 😭 not a tool, just fin… https://t.co/P0wIYCWbc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandalsResorts  #ILoveSandalsResorts #SandalsOchi I wanna WIN! @ Mattawan, Michigan https://t.co/LZPxEOpT9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astro_puppy I remember this! Still think I have that sheet stored around here somewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinCHannigan @krystaharden @mansara @emmyruiz @maytownsend @shewhoeatsmud @Beyonce Back at you @ErinCHannigan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesashley @ickydime @slukas @EXAmusicVR @zachkinstner @BadVR_Inc @felixandpaul @funktroniclabs @FutureSightAR… https://t.co/5EgWp6mo7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eld9716 @PatrckStatic @markiplier I’ve only ever had Baja Blast once. I was eating loads of Ice Cream and Slushies/Smoothies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleeevelasco  this was the prom after party when the cops pulled up 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Soul Sophisticated Tour! Raheem DeVaughn and Lyfe Jennings put it down here in St Louis, Mo. @ Stifel Theatre https://t.co/FPdZxMcbNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gayer_Than_Thou Gaaawd. Pretty much what every guy is on Bumble. #modernman https://t.co/UOC8nTPfWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add Coney Island to the list of places I’ve had a mental breakdown this week,, thanks Ed Sheeran]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help bury this young man who lost his life to gun violence. Burying the dead looks different in the internet… https://t.co/CCeepY4339]]></document><document><![CDATA[accomplishment i never set out or wanted to succeed at : was awake long enough to watch the time change for dayligh… https://t.co/iYSPmxR4Sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish i had a relationship like this with either of my father figures lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday’s quarterfinals matchup between Tipton-Rosemark Academy and Goodpasture of the DII-A Boys State Tournament… https://t.co/GModeMfGRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudyLynnPresto4 @Michael_Hudak @nyetengale @2ThumbsUpTrain @zoothorn69 @TWEETNMAC74 @GrandPiJ @farmerkevin1… https://t.co/T360VEe3Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel That still seems high for the simple fact that he has not done jack💩 but lie and talk some uneducated 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in College Park, GA? https://t.co/6viwaSknHh #aviation #WomenSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍🤩So proud of our WHS cheerleaders and coaches! They came in first place in the nation!🙌🏻 #eanes https://t.co/ubXVT719oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my GoFundMe campaign: https://t.co/LUTCrZNV0d @gofundme https://t.co/3wj9LQsZNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is so disgusting and makes my heart hurt! To think that woman had the AUDACITY to hit that man! My blood is bo… https://t.co/AYo0pUHko2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Black_C_Patriot @realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff New information “developed “. Means a new lie made.!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to thank everyone for giving me opportunity and platform throughout the years. I really hope to see all… https://t.co/XDqgV8pbKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Autocorrect just corrected my name from Tanya to Ya Ya, and I’m just here, giggling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 days post-op and I crutched across campus for 20 minutes to get Taco Bell. Totally worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JANEICEMTHOMAS My dad used to always say a stupid question gets a stupid answer. Next time tell they dumb asses ye… https://t.co/Emi63xlsMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson it’s been over a week but I’m still thinking about your concert in Tulsa,OK!!!! You are just so mag… https://t.co/ZCokp9ppuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #ComeBackAmanda on @TyltEnt—Amanda Bynes has been through hell and deserves a comeback https://t.co/bM0GexLJE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshmellomusic @CHVRCHES This is 🔥🔥🔥🔥 I'd love to see more collabs from you guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bella reunión de Cumpleaños de gardeazabalbeatriz. Gracias por tan linda invitación. 🎉🍾🌹 @ Key Biscayne, Florida https://t.co/SrWCXUKRFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been wanting to use these three words together, well done 🤷‍♀️😹rapacious, moldering, disingenuous @davidcrosss]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tongue-stick-out selfie is the new duck face. Put your damn tongue back your mouth. You gonna be SORRY in 5 yea… https://t.co/T8fQgllBog]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FEEEL this answer @AnnaSeavey whenever i would try to fight my siblings their answers would always be “i was born… https://t.co/XPfNKjdWQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahfosterr @megannpatterson Omg it’s so hard bc team Stefan but what happened to him wasn’t his fault but Damon’s… https://t.co/smTSfodioV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday I find my purpose in life. Man god is so good to me and my mine ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seekupTx I LIKE TO MAKE SURE THEY ARE NOT TROLLS THOUGH TOO! LOL! SORRY SO MANY ANSWERS! THAT'S JUST MY METHOD! LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[....in other news, chad has been sleeping all night so peaceful looking and I’m actually angry rn but also happy Bc he won’t be grouchy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidents hier soir  #R109 1 jeune femme de 24 ans décédée   #R117 Parc de La Verendrye : 1 décès  #R117 Accident c… https://t.co/rLMgZ913Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i slept all afternoon and now i cant sleep 😡 someone let me pick them up 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saysroxy @aravosis @realDonaldTrump He’s a real nut job!!! Why hasn’t his party of traitors done something!!??? #BASTA this is insanity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must read thread of the day 👇🏾 Who are you honouring for #InternationalWomensDay ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you join us 7pm CT Thurs for #BoostingAchievement?   Spread the word! @JennyVo15 is leading our thinking!… https://t.co/Msfx4TUCsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Nauert withdraws from consideration for UN Ambassador - CNNPolitics https://t.co/mhPdHp7ilP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dukeabarnstable #streetart #outdoorart #publicart #wheatpaste #urbanart #newyork #kisses #streetartphotography… https://t.co/sQmnFrGecA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonReflexiones Pues hay un remedio  🙃 cuando te des cuenta que ya no...se agradece y se retira en santa paz, luego… https://t.co/rnUE0N2FNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @SteveScalise Haha - how about removing Vladimir Putin from our agenda, Rethuglicans?  Republicans can't give… https://t.co/ZBYoQbtnpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[we appear to be very grateful to God; but what of those occasions when things go contrary to our plans and desires?… https://t.co/cqEEukKdeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflynnfswildcat @BGDN_edbeat Publish Bam Carneys reaction.   .....  Grudge Government]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heck yeah! #wonderwoman #targetfinds #i #love #target  👊🏻🖤👏🏻 🎯 👆🏻♥️ @ Melvin’s Coffee Stop https://t.co/oAbpQehGOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPRCodeSwitch Even as a kid, I knew those crows on Dumbo were supposed to be Black. Good episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headshot goals. Take a look at the lovely @KarenMintonWSB through the years: https://t.co/CS9fhYrA5v  This is the l… https://t.co/ADdnxycUBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would really be great if all my social media platforms would STOP suggesting my super abusive ex as a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[♀There’s a strong chance that a woman is behind the content from your favorite football team. These are just a few… https://t.co/ah3lTJH6LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KISSOnline @tommy_thayer @CenturyLinkCtr Have a great show,  Tommy.  :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at #pigglywiggly to get beer.  27.49 for a case of bud light.  What the effing eff people???]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Better Day than Valentine’s Day To Finish Out Strong 💪 and watch it rain ☔️ Purple 💜’s in Columbus. Let’s Go Boy… https://t.co/KnXlledaeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stubbornmuse @Kvoss1313 @iamreal2019 @TwitterMoments Then they need to get rid of the majority of their members of Congress..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hey_butter @landscaperstev1 @andrerucker51 @DudekLinda @fishersusa @Itridpm @SarahGould_SA @evilgrrl @poppij… https://t.co/uMHHM7gNZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY! We need #WynonnaEarp back on our screen! Let's go @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment!… https://t.co/oNE50ebZMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how stupid these sentences are on Duolingo!  Believe me, the Norwegian language one is even funnier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP applying for credit in stores knowing damn well you won’t be approved. Just to get that sucka ass 15% off… https://t.co/Zpi6xA5QG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen B 🐝 || Side note: This is the exact spot I met my new girl crush happilygrey! Thank you to… https://t.co/cJQEArIeLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I was taught not to believe the words "always" , "never"  or similar words because they are exaggerations.… https://t.co/xgH4myrH7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Athleta can I use my fitness professional discount online? Or is it in store discount only? Thanks 🧘🏻‍♀️🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darosyndy @LadyBlackTear @Cat31s @Dzsozi22 @DeannGoss @heiba11 @HWolson @saladesvertes @VampireEmperor8… https://t.co/UPInlDODbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstig78 @TribeCalledCubs @darkhorizons @pfac51 I was wondering about Arrow and The Flash. I left around season 3 o… https://t.co/aOKFCPNIds]]></document><document><![CDATA[New appreciation for #kpop and redvelvet.smtown 💕 @ The Fillmore Miami Beach https://t.co/2nZbtyT656]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t have to believe me, but as some of you know, this new #technology will keep my #energy #sustained and my… https://t.co/KYZLtCxNXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do really have myself, this has been the most messed up week of my life]]></document></documents></author>