<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not the worst place for a wedding venue in Austin. https://t.co/wItGJxgDU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A true smile is worth a thousand words.  I catch myself unconsciously giving tight lipped little obligatory smiles… https://t.co/KOficQQvjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this, it won't be long before #Nike shoes are sold at Walmart next to Shaq's, the rip off Jordan's with two g… https://t.co/bGGXhzP4Z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a bird... it's a plane... it's Zion Williamson https://t.co/Z6m6i4cEbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss out only 25 seats left for this intimate evening of great music!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurfeeJake The holes next to the mountains have a solid 24-26” snowpack since they don’t see any sun. I believe we… https://t.co/e95YI4vXDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I predict it won’t be just the money that is kompromat on Graham, there’s something else that he fears much more on… https://t.co/MTSdKUV6d8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie On behalf of all square dancers i protest this clear discrimination. Giving preference to one form over… https://t.co/F7WZBlakLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly why is it not a crime to incite violence against reporters? What’s wrong with our leaders and our media tha… https://t.co/p8KmQbs4r6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa If the Democrats are allowed to continue to stuff ballot boxes, we may never see another Republican elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Orr still at DOJ, McCabe not indicted, Mueller crimes continues with new AG in place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philliesgirljma @GutterTheGreat And not a moment too soon. https://t.co/qYAf8Cz2Or]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis Robert Kraft got in touch with his inner Charlie Sheen,  he didn’t pay for a rub and tug, he paid so he could leave!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best take I’ve seen in a minute 💯 EXACTLY why they will NEVER win a title]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Retribution? What kind of retribution do you want? Should the writers at SNL be arrested?   Actual… https://t.co/BzXyILEP8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops @Bill_Morneau   Budget watchdog says Liberals can&amp;#8217;t account for $2.5B in infrastructure funds https://t.co/KnSFv80JpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dylanhawk5 @FilthyFranku_ @AJ_Ariondo @BasebaIlKing Yeah but the difference is trouts not about the money, so he w… https://t.co/vk5iJFKHgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This type of leadership is the reason why the Rice Lake local sort leads the way in so many elements.  Thank you fo… https://t.co/ca9slCf0Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh, I know very well. How the secrets beckon so sweetly. Only an honest death will cure you now. Liberate you, fro… https://t.co/O1YLsREm1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[The saddest part is that whenever I make this point to Trump supporters, they respond “source?” And I’m like “uh...Donald Trump’s mouth.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberlasskick @ItsIzzyMania That’s awesome you guys being a wonderful wrestling family. That’s the best 👍😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golf_gilly @DrewMikePodcast @TrudiDan @marcfell I bet that dog makes some awful feces   cc @Sub3BFish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCPLibraries Campaigners warn of 'book poverty' as UK celebrates World Book Day. Today is World Book Day. https://t.co/QRBtSJVjJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pobre del narrador que de alguna manera tenía que disimular Laguna normalidad dentro de la anormalidad. Aplauso de… https://t.co/uXFQhnqjZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[while ur all here check out my self-published series “tournament of royal seats” available on Amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best case - awesome balance of BOTH, but that is the job of the Principle to apply discernment in interview.   Skil… https://t.co/Xr8w5voiJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronwikso @AOC Not to mention a job multiplier of 2-3 jobs per direct jobs created.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Costco can you please expand your tire service to also do quick lube oil changes.  As I own 2 shares of your stock… https://t.co/hdf7fq1RI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenOlivierMD @ARRO_org @RTendulkarMD curious how do you use the in-service at @CleClinicMD #radonc?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Moana soundtrack is really getting me through all my homework lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Infantry0300 @MalcolmNance He is a waste of oxygen. It's horrific he has the power to hurt so many people. https://t.co/9XNNYhsL4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Miami #design #district #florida #usa #vacationmode @ Miami Design District https://t.co/HntEXw8vRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My personal Twitter reach is (much) smaller than my FaceBook reach, but this is where I am finding the material I h… https://t.co/p635heiEpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahGragson I really enjoyed the late 90s to just before the Car of Tomorrow packages]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwyattsports @dawson_knox @baeagles @OleMissFB @Avengers @Titans I’m begging you...AND I CAN NOT STRESS THIS ENOUG… https://t.co/4CsUEFocl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Narcing on someone When it helps save your own ass Happens all the time  #collusionhaiku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Momoa (Aquaman), Nicholas Brendon (Xander), Matt Ryan (Constantine), Amber Benson (Tara), and a sketch of me… https://t.co/nmECnJmrbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave him there until we can use it at election time. Point out the complete hypocrisy of the left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Los Angeles.  #rain #la #friday #losangeles #california @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/8V13uPZVI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you being deadass but she think you’re joking https://t.co/r5lIMlA711]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed “Giving Back” being Dinner Sponsor for The Journey of Hope Grief Support Center in Plano.  #givingback… https://t.co/8kTTw3hkDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSPEEDZfit Right like a nigga haven’t threatened to shoot me before. Sir sit down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well it’s @POTUS Day. I would like to say @POTUS @realDonaldTrump God Bless you please stay strong… https://t.co/7IfibrMgwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsbllnbkns Bummer. Why do you hate La Posta? Their CAB is awesome and rolled tacos are great. What more do you need?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be politically and practically impossible to decarbonize the economy without radically restructuring it to… https://t.co/utnus3dXOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superfunkykris @David56798816 @KiloCharlie237 @onesarahjones @mmfa I retract my "have a good day".  Have a shitty day.😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see @LocomationAI shape the future of autonomous trucking. #outofstealthmode #humansandrobots… https://t.co/SuASizBd89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaturesBakery Can’t wait to get my hands on the new @NaturesBakery packages!❤️❤️❤️🥰❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biblical ethics in 2 verses: “Thus says the LORD of hosts,  Render true judgments,  show kindness and mercy to one… https://t.co/SuukRKhOW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiGlitterGrl @PanakinCaboose @lockhart_jesse I’ve gotta sit this one our]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbttychmbrs1 @DavidCornDC Sort of reminds you of Obama’s romance with Putin doesn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lee Snodgrass is running for 2nd Vice Chair of the @WisDems. @SnodgrassforWI is amazing. Ran a killer race for Stat… https://t.co/GVP1A0bfYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndiFouberg @SDState I do the exact same thing but usually I’m the one yelling! https://t.co/TiLZ4q0O9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw that fake ass LV x Supreme bag in the trash! Broke ass mothafuckas need to respect those of us who actually s… https://t.co/YMp1GEIqVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 50+ action emails for the day are all sent out and I’m heading to bed for a few and will be up for opening bell.… https://t.co/YchdILxRgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCNews The gene therapy is a treatment for dry (gradual) AMD, not wet (more sudden onset) AMD- which is currently… https://t.co/mvldciX73m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarBombBoom13 @TheFlintor Back in the 70's  "Rag it" meant control the puck, kill time, basically play keep away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yii!! Boss Shiii!!! 💪 Morning Vibes!!! Check ☑ IN..🔥💪😈🔥 . . @jayd3vill 😎#Moneyseason 💰 #Wordz 🙏 #StayStayUpBlessed… https://t.co/ICitml9OJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes the glorious art of falling out of bed and sprinting outside shoeless/shirtless when you hear the trash truck coming down your block.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeVinluan @DrizyDom @__anthonyyy18 @olerwillims  Let's flip this bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @jtc475. I’m working on our @isanet paper...with a Vulcan Rye IPA. https://t.co/JnmWbXORrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Phlebotomist (PST) Float Southern Colorado - Varies -… https://t.co/ruKijK6S9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...but if you #strive for #humility and stay #close...in my book, you're #good to #go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBenassi Check out Mike on the @joerogan experience. Incredible interview. It’s amazing to see Mikes outlook… https://t.co/bFpN94DA1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to welcome jakesarnoff to #PrestonsPutting! Thanks ugp_neil for putting us in touch. Excited to start prepping… https://t.co/Vdkvi2paix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi the democrats had 8 years under Obama to do something for America and you almost destroyed it now be… https://t.co/JwjR4ZUArg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to decide what’s more ridiculous here; the tweet, itself, or the responses. Either way, here are six minutes o… https://t.co/7l2Pg0FT6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@me4871 @Doaja @Alyssa_Milano Pull your head out, and quit making excuses. https://t.co/W53f8DEM61]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked down to the first floor that turned out to be a basement. The entrance was on the floor I’m parked on but th… https://t.co/GFa8DggNZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have fond memories of Babushka Day at the the Pirate games . We need strong women who’ve got the style and guts t… https://t.co/qM9mJhPjIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐥🐥🐥🐣  that's ok now lose yourself in your work, and remember to have fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyle_scanlon04 @tgshepherdvan @JTheMightyAtom @NerdyTastic @_MegMuckleBones I’m sure that can be made into a thing… https://t.co/gZnvE56ExN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate @JimNorton @ @notsam @jimandsamshow all weekend have been singing stupid Larry hooper #thesunisshining #ohhappyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefbrosen @chefbrianyoung We'd love to have you both on our #TopChef Judges Roundtable podcast at Reality TV… https://t.co/IC0VOle1pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExmormonReddit BIC, Temple Marriage, High Priest, Counselor in BR. My shelf broke trying to defend Joseph Smith an… https://t.co/UwCjL8rJtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on a different path! Featuring jochampagne #newyork #pittiuomo #ghana #pittiimmagine #gq #lifestyle… https://t.co/Hh8qclKlJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never be too serious at your own party. #Photobomb #HiMom #KansasCity #Q4KC #Cupcakes #chiefskingdom #LegionOfQ https://t.co/DivCQBlnn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JochyPeralta1 @SusanaGautreau @CorcinoMaximo @PLDenlinea @JCRodPLDBK @WiltonEMejia1 @TonyDeLen4 Comparar a Danilo… https://t.co/peDyflQxzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Peoria #AZ  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/nbXeHl5QvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ronyewest Yeah man food was good! Are you planning to go to those 4 cities this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @CNN @realDonaldTrump @AOC @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib @lsarsour He got his money's worth. They're doing a great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danarel @IlhanMN If you honestly can’t differentiate between what a handful of Nazis said and what conservatives h… https://t.co/WRHannUxVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNoahRing @siestabuffy Pipe dreams..how bout rugged individualism, grinding it out and making it happen like everybody else?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent article on @BobbyHolmes11 and the @CoastalBaseball family by @alanblondin. Tick tock. Tick tock. Let’s ge… https://t.co/nGxArChaTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sckntrd1 Trump is racist. That’s not up for discussion. Smollet  needs to be punished for what he did and how he did it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@readnallthetime @4everNeverTrump @realDonaldTrump Trump’s use of reciprocal tariffs aka Obama’s Mythical Magic Wan… https://t.co/Jd65ZOC8nV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 @toney2020 She not saying that..She saying absolutely no IMPEACHMENT he is not worth it...that put… https://t.co/nlYtIwQOkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The odds for this hint at knowing unique things about Bran and Littlefinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adedejisuyii Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh... March... Where brackets are broken, history is made, and Cinderella dances! 🏀 #MarchMadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes: "so we hear young people are excited for Dems to aggressively address climate change in 2020 and beyond..… https://t.co/cEimQEKtOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WithIceCream99 @EmojiSnakeGame Do we have enough room, even if we snake around?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ NBC - CBS - ABC - PBS - New York - Washington Post “   “ THE GREAT DIVIDERS “]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 years ago @WWEApollo  wrestled against Michael faith for my company in sherman Texas. Texoma Pro. It was a good n… https://t.co/REAyvnQ42g]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of the day life is pretty simple.  Give me my best friend, some sunshine, a pair of ripped jeans, and I’… https://t.co/sfR47uSvl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can we let the happy endings we see at the conclusion of a movie to be the only time we get a chance to view that result.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our actions will carry just as much weight as our words, but people will remember  what you have DONE long after th… https://t.co/JZHpJjJMF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jserio52 @OriolesFan727 @RapSheet @Cheeta1024Chris @jeffrav123 Neither did Michal Jackson!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieDawn3 @reesepaxson I know ... but Teespring is gonna need to stock up on stickers and shirts. There's going t… https://t.co/GuhbYoFMwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 630 N Wild Olive Avenue #DaytonaBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/Fxo4ZIGDbF]]></document></documents></author>