<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I hit the jackpot in the love department. Just unlucky with time. I waited 38 years to meet the love of my life. We… https://t.co/sPOuCvaZv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @morningmika   I am SO proud of the reporters at the Rose Garden conference.  They are true journalist… https://t.co/aBPN1MhsI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are the New York Knicks tanking the dunk competition, too??!! https://t.co/dEs6lfuFB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang jolly. Cracka lackin'. I'm sure I've pinned this before but it is quite possibly the best joke... #laughter… https://t.co/kiZRFQLIHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning lovelies !! I forgot about the goodies I bought at my cvs_beauty on my #skincaresunday  — One of my very fa… https://t.co/jAsqIMPcQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo viendo al Ex jefe de grupo con 4 hijos y yo llorando porque hubo 3 cumpleaños in a row en zara y cooperación dia… https://t.co/gT14slPRCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClassicFilmDame As a gemini, I don’t wanna give you this, but there are worse options 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruetenik @zether @ArktinenJenkki Wow, that’s quite interesting. I wasn’t familiar with this. Thanks for sharing that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got to see some scenery this morning! @ Saguaro Lake Ranch Stable https://t.co/vAF4gIoCEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spend a leisurely Saturday morning catching up on Room For Improvement! New videos popping off now! (Link in profil… https://t.co/HySMXW7Yci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woken up TOO many times by the nurses who didn’t know their ass from their elbow. Then LEAVES the fricken light on. 😤😤😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOKING FORWARD othe wl praised           BUMPER? Start off with associating on AGDAY https://t.co/hjSOUMkhVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there an option where @FCC could investigate and possibly yank @FoxNews license over being another wing of… https://t.co/KZdZJSxp7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @BakerBitchBakes I get it too! When I didn't get my epidural with my second child, I was kicking and a screaming in pain. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time I see a dirty martini 🍸 on any menu I am going to tell them to either add pineapple juice or hold the oli… https://t.co/yYVpILwGVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, it feels better not to talk...  at all... About anything, to anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 60 Minutes interview with McCabe was compelling, and that particular statement attributed to Trump was astonish… https://t.co/2b38rmWDFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #27 I'm grateful for the breakthrough with my kids. @ Bethlehem, Pennsylvania https://t.co/A6J3Vsshxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAInside_Stuff I’m 12/27. That’s straight outta Compton all thug for a win]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you take the “what would you do if you woke up as the opposite gender” question too far]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time (at least in a long time) flying Alaska airlines and geeze, they were full of surprises (in a good way). Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochesterTA Maybe next time we make the decision a bit earlier as many of us have long commutes and were already on our way!🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephGrisham45 @RealSaavedra @FLOTUS @POTUS @TheView What a bunch of stupid jealous women. Sickening]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the deer that I see frequently on my way home. 🦌🦌🦌 #worshipwithnature #doyouseewhatisee #throughmyeyes #deer https://t.co/xUIhtDuXwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que vergüenza fuera malditos comunistas cubanos asesinos ladrones larguecen ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMPbeisbol @ClubNaranjeros @clubtomateros Como peloteros, ambos fueron tremendos! Pero Benjamin tiene "ventaja" de… https://t.co/pRSzFJBeHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es una semana antes de cumplir 30 sabes que algo no anda bien pero nada te puede preparar para lo que vas a escucha… https://t.co/em7AMmEUps]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Philly to Nashville to Phoenix to Oakland 🙃 #PrayForTheWickedTour #panicatthedisco #patd #PFTWTourOakland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there really a reason to have a better body then me https://t.co/uRGops694e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Maxine, apparently, you can’t read. Stop embarrassing yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCatMalice @LordGraydon @JoyOfCats @DonnaLeeThomps8 @carolineCMCE @SassyCassyCat @Boo_Panfur @3coolkatz… https://t.co/kKgrjZ9vvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BB_Updates First time I ever picked the winner and America’s favorite! Congratulations! #joybellskeepringing]]></document><document><![CDATA[A perfect ending to another fantastic Avett weekend! #avettbrothers @ Donald L. Tucker Civic Center https://t.co/gNZ2G2SLuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein It’s pragmatism — that’s the religion that buys its power in government &amp; Trump is the president you can buy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a bit of joanjett on a Monday funday at tootsies_orchid_lounge 🤟🏾🤟🏾🤟🏾 @ Tootsie's World Famous Orc… https://t.co/tHDHzG4JTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cierrrraaaa31 Tell me why I say the same thing about him and he’s not even my brother 😂🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just Pushed The Button. Vote for your favorite #ABGT track at https://t.co/GVEaPAZEqa via @aboveandbeyond]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida Sorry, En esto si , Difiero contigo. La vida es un regalo invaluable]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Sleep And Dreaming by Steve Roach on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/sJ7ObfgCBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how my coworkers are shook that I left on my scheduled time and didn’t stay for OT ✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really love what I got on @Etsy from leahbeequilts. #etsystar https://t.co/AUFg2ldHGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I know what you mean if I didn't get enough sleep I've got like Samsonite luggage under my eyeballs he he he an… https://t.co/fHuDKf11dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess he didn’t forget! 😉👏🏼Reinbold/Underwood racing is on a roll so far this season! So happy for them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read why leftists hate Vakentine’s day... frontpage had it.  You should look at it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Common Sense 101 - I’d also make an appointment at an Apple Store if you need help with anything tech related. Ther… https://t.co/nVUiKRFFET]]></document><document><![CDATA[me going to sleep rn knowing all the hw I have due tomorrow isn’t done https://t.co/7hO5GjsLfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man does this thing where he brings me bomb burritos or tacos if he comes across it through out his day. If that… https://t.co/0m1vlykwfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acai berry, hemp and fruit bowl fun on  Saturday. In what way can you nourish yourself today? #BMARadiant #CBMANext… https://t.co/A9nS40Bx7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are not as nice as you think you are if you have to tear someone down. ESPECIALLY when they’re trying to share something with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to exchanging #ideas and #experiences about what works or not when communicating #science to a… https://t.co/0U1Xjh4qBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MortalManRaised Yeah I kind of wanted to go yesterday but you stole my moment and I fell for it thinking it’d be easier if you went.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, at 7 p.m. TCM will showing one of the richest, most rewarding films I've ever seen - Martin Scorsese's Hug… https://t.co/eoG9GxvGrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGlobalGoals  or @TheWorldsLesson might be able to help! #GlobalWarming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Watts The Dream Life He Gave Up https://t.co/QXGQbdLz7p via @YouTube  For a mistress coworker. He did just as the devil wanted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @barb71 @laker477 @OldSmokeEater @TeriHentschel @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong… https://t.co/qGboLzPay6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you find yourself a person that really loves you you’ll understand why it took you so long to find them😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cha51brolll19 @NAudrey_ST @MisleaderC @MelissaFunGurl @chefrocky413 @strom_annette @Barb81146 @esadah… https://t.co/yvVH2F1pF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiSixx @james_a_michael @DjASHBA It's been a long time coming so I'm ready as hell and sooooo excited to hear t… https://t.co/v9IF2qdzic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @lm3din to post pics of my 7 favorite book, no reviews needed. Each day I’ll challenge so… https://t.co/wUMLEsz48W]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been to over 20+ @jonasbrothers events over the years it’s not stopping me now😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonnetseven @skipandpete @macenroc @Tia_Lunes @quisqueyana1102 @Sammy_Markle @StephInSuburbia @benzie55… https://t.co/H03rwmDaGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, we deserve to be in the front pocket. Not the back pocket of another pair of pants. Gentlemen, take notes https://t.co/pgeIbNuZKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend A man that defends his woman while also complimenting and worshipping her. What a man 👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night after sleeping with your boyfriend the previous night sucks assss. I just wanna cuddle with my boo, esp. in this cold weather )):]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; my bf been laying together all day in the same bed &amp; ain’t said nothing to each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am done I am thinking about just packing up and leaving this house for good Im serious I will just hitchhike to places]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the read. Not the kind of national news Michigan wants to be featured in, but there's only one direction to g… https://t.co/OlFb1bIX6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church Family  Friendship  Growth Bold  Faith Love Strength  These words describe what this woman IS! When you trus… https://t.co/TCf2k8Wi33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice pack on my face and heatpad on my lower back . Like wtf. https://t.co/lxAqNJfCIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Delameter24 May we all get a little “hysterical” from time to time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite kind of “stay in pajamas and play games with the family” day... 💜 @ 19th Ward, Rochester https://t.co/i8vhRDXmE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see us at #Superfine! LA Showcasing artists from #Dallas #Texas   Joey Brock Present.v1 Mixed media on Yupo pa… https://t.co/NUDSameh4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#twitterstorians and #rhetcomp peeps, I'm looking into researching Post-truth and I'd love if people would name-dro… https://t.co/qE5KyR3Ykt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlboardman @PittsburghPG Not too late to contact #cps.   The daughter needs help ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Trump is a con man and a illegitimate president a liar a criminal who has a corrupt Administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you Seeking for the First-Class CMS #WebDevelopmentSolution? Choosing Openwave will help you to hire the expert… https://t.co/LsH0kNfFSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Ordered Officials to Give Jared Kushner a Security Clearance   via @NYTimes https://t.co/MAlNh6OjN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGNNegovan @BenBradleyTV I knew it from the start...I told my middle son n my bf...I had this feelin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little is finally active AND isn’t she the cutest???? 😍😍😍(Can you find the cupcake in this pic?) https://t.co/bWVTCFdS0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a showdown between schools for @lead4ward supremacy!! #DHSthink2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Painsomina... wonder if I'll get any sleep. I even took pain meds. My belly is distended too, ugh @ Maumee, Ohio https://t.co/B2ZeiY3jrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m not even saying this out of anger or even frustration... I’m  just... mystified. And don’t understand the t… https://t.co/lmEBM0N5ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Good God, it's almost laughable to see you drag out "tax and spend".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TucsonAirport you knew this snow was coming. Why didn’t you have the right equipment brought in to clean off the p… https://t.co/OxVySU0C2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tired_oftrump @whyknotmeagain2 @h8Wankmaggot45 @og_dbl_lo_g @PollyPapaya @PerfumeFlogger @callkurt @KristyLyn11… https://t.co/eu0je46FgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSchettig @SirEviscerate And, I really wish I could remember who it was, but I remember around the time this… https://t.co/98ZF9XwxY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just fashion show things (@ Mikarose in Orem, UT) https://t.co/2rWCbmx8VG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you dig into fighters the response is throw something or break something. He should have kept me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swipe 👉👉👉👉 #Repost @Iralicious_ira with get_repost ・・・ Hey People Another New Week For Another New Song's On Our To… https://t.co/Q0z2qoLQ4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[my cat I had since I was 8 years old is horribly ill and I am not ready for him to go to kitty heaven 💔 pls let him… https://t.co/rQG11KGYCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je suis en train de jouer au 7e joueur sur https://t.co/nSHi44i2Tj. Joins-toi à moi ! https://t.co/edCtDmZn28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Travel make happy because I forgot all the hardship, all the fears , all the struggles and I enjoy some… https://t.co/VYJQmCR965]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used. I bought 1 brand new it was a lemon. It was in shop 6 months out of 1 year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picked up a few plants this week from @AldiUSA as I begin my journey of plant parenting. 🤞they stay alive!… https://t.co/UhTN0DnZcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally so annoyed of my facebook timeline being “if i get 600 likes” ....... you know the rest😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @DetectivePat @DetKenLang @SchoolerLA @westernagent @DaytimeJustice @JusticeNetTV @forensicfiles @LtJoeKenda @tvdetective @SugarFreeTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a real opportunity here to invent new kinds of (#climatechange) stories. #Climate #writer #author… https://t.co/jdXZn2CWaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaLuvgood2020 Rain and cold, again, in NorCal 😬 but there’s always wishes and plane tickets ! 🌴😋🌴 https://t.co/1tkfVz93lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[ZaQuae first pass 👍🏾👊🏾🤸🏾‍♂️👏🏾#whgfteam #hcz #tntextravaganza @ Indigo Gymnastics Center https://t.co/PhjfyT0ovN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OzzyOsbourne @Bernie_Torme I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back waiting… https://t.co/sbDvpZsCFk]]></document></documents></author>