<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Padres_Farm @poglankford @ParkAtThePark I read it just today in Friar’s On Base!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NUFF SAID..... HAVE A GREAT DAY!!!! #inspirational #motivation #inspiration #quotes #motivational #love… https://t.co/WoT5YH68Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattOverton_LS Congratulations Matt, not only did the Jags re sign the best long snapper in the NFL. They re signe… https://t.co/a4XYOYFDFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs The venom is coming from the likes of Trump and Stephen Miller, not to mention breitbart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbradlee @EmilyGoglia @MAURICELAMARCHE @yakkopinky @AdamKubota @MartinDiller @PMJofficial Fantastic work every… https://t.co/9pShZKSxaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Sierra Canyon claims second Open Division state title with win over Sheldon: Chatsworth Sierra Can… https://t.co/bam7KBPZzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealzevgood (Also: It's great you've had success with folks buying copies of your books + leaving reviews (!),… https://t.co/rTUCeMyzJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peston This whole situation is just not how Westminster systems are supposed to work. A frontbench with no real su… https://t.co/v5xACG5tRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankr0d @ColbyTuckerXXX @gaygringo_ @Naked_Sword @mrPam @FalconStudiosPR @DJChiChiLaRue @MrDimarco 😝 yeah buddy!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judicial Watch: FBI General Counsel Talked to Hillary Clinton’s Lawyer about Comey’s Letter on Weiner Laptop Clinto… https://t.co/xbgR4uNK30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Lynn and Bethany hit the road today for our first spring admissions visit, starting out at the home of the sta… https://t.co/kJV0jWZ7IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[because when their happy, I’m #happy. @ The Ritz-Carlton, Amelia Island https://t.co/z4jk6S5ZGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuta este burro fascista de candidato actúa hoy así , si llega a ganar nos fusila ⚔️⚒. Renuncia mejor no necesitam… https://t.co/e8QWaIEEPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTSB y’all gotta do something about these ELD’s for oilfield truck drivers...it makes our job a real pain in the a… https://t.co/ZjovvJparJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey uhhhhh, let’s not pretend that 85 year-old people should be in charge of governing our country]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOMEONE claiming to be a Director with the #Ghana Commercial Bank contacted me on Facebook and offered me half of $… https://t.co/EHwp2KKbno]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/cx7kRPUXbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol  Technology finally made it I can talk to my phone and it will text for me :) I say to my phone :) and it makes a :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Can’t Touch This”  Model: shardea.w for @EllementsMag February 2019 Editorial  #StyledByMe Photographer:… https://t.co/AdMuZ5NBLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirMeeech @AntsTweets_ i know, i was suggesting lol it’s so fucking good]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 year old is obsessed with the word poop.. and naked dolls lol https://t.co/CQBYcHT0Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot believe this crap. Find legislators that's handed over to the courts to decide after all you want to be eq… https://t.co/JE1VCfJDtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPerschino @Zalman888 Is anyone worth $185,185 per game, even if they actually play the next 1620 games -  and pla… https://t.co/Dqx1RVa8by]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to this beautiful woman. She’s a mother, soldier, women’s victim advocate and has seen me high… https://t.co/lQXyIWXIM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear you gun toting hicks aren’t from this planet. https://t.co/9DtpwCpo9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HClaytonWright #LGBexit #TakeBackPride Recognition of The True Gay Community in June by @realDonaldTrump is impera… https://t.co/FPuY5wCnVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeJo660411 @briansflood Look at the crimes, look at the drugs in our streets, look at the burden on our economy!!… https://t.co/kSl00DHdRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forbes though... healhaus the brothers on tgis shoot were super dope! @thebernhardy and fam! @ HealHaus https://t.co/v58A3IotOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Boone really means is that Cashman hasn't told him what to say yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're a rich girl, and you've gone too far 'Cause you know it don't matter anyway You can rely on the old man's mo… https://t.co/lV7tdMyhEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marybeezzz I would love to see something like this happen soon in the #Philippines when the 16mn #Filipinos realized they been had]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catherine_fulop @jguaido @FabiiRosales Feliz Cumpleaños Caterin. Dios bendiga tus sueños. Gracias por tu lucha x Venezuela.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts mean nothing to people who are demoralized for one reason or another. We see this manifestation daily on soci… https://t.co/wYXHkTywtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyQTu18 @15_DakP @dallascowboys @JasonWitten Or not running your route when you know they’re not throwing it your way....]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever say "well it's getting late" I'm asking you to leave cause I'll stay up until 4 watching you tube videos… https://t.co/VZY5kvNXAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No big deal, just sitting in a car next to a huge box of samples for the @DRPinot dinner at @TheRainbowLodge in May… https://t.co/trlyIG7izG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkimreporter Mina Kim!   Great to meet you at the @cwclub yesterday. Have a wonderful show tomorrow on @KQEDForum. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonMillerinDC Wondered if #Covington MAGA hat wearing Trump Pro-Life Republican Nick #Sandmann knows #Parkland M… https://t.co/bCAquEUymq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather here is so hot and humid!!!! I feel like a ass for complaining about California weather 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARonNBC  There would be no Kyle Busch if it were not for the King.  And maybe no NASCAR.  #KyleBush fan. https://t.co/RaclrZkBAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Client Patient releasing some #Stress on the Punching Bag, doing Wheelkicks. #Disability #MiamiFl #Florida #USA… https://t.co/AxpqKAzecp]]></document><document><![CDATA[19. I don’t care nor do I see why this issue is even close to being controversial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WePodAndWeKnow @TheMightyEROCK That’s the first thing I thought of too lmao!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely nothing is more important than salvation! #jesus #salvation #eternity]]></document><document><![CDATA[referring to yourself as an alcoholic bc you like getting drunk on the weekend is weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @rawhidevelvet on @KOKEFMAUSTIN and nursing this hangover!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Music Label Spotlight February 22, 2019  Celebrating 15 Years Of Cosmicleaf Records  The Omm Sq… https://t.co/o9QngcztFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0xMatt If I'm not mistaken, you'll need 20 count 50w solar panels to charge you car for about 7 hrs to get it to d… https://t.co/PxMSMFlAkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodTrouble Malika you are making me cry 😢 #GoodTrouble https://t.co/1K1qTttRkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston Dynamo dirigido por Wilmer Cabrera venció 2-1a Montreal. Mauro Manotas anoto el gol de la victoria, llegó a… https://t.co/Du9yDGOvcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the biggest betrayal involving anyone named Zach since Kelly Kapowski cheated with Jeff the college profes… https://t.co/urf1sFtmQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so many cool dinosaur bones under #Antarctica that we haven’t discovered due to the harsh conditions, among… https://t.co/Ny3hJ3dWWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#frozenTuesday #iceonsidewslks Good morning happy Tuesday its freezing out @cityofmarkham ice on sidewalks… https://t.co/bOIOtAOBeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLostOgle One time I walked out in front of a black suv that Jolene Chaney was a passenger in, I was almost struck. It was terrific.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see Brexit destroy Britain piece by piece, is modern day Treachery. Trump's treason is parallel track. Both are… https://t.co/0FlDHX81L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hotgaymen4 @dilf2050 @HungTwinks @new_gaywanking @HotMaleStuds @HottieMcHotStuf @LUCAS__LUCASS @paupratodahora… https://t.co/oomoNtXk8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatiePorter Stick with it. These pay day loans are legalized extortion! Plain and simple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valtisse Should have smoked less weed and skateboarded in high school and i spoke on this‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic in Manhattan, what traffic!? @ 5th Avenue https://t.co/Rw2603q9iE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha I'm now a fan of @tiktok_us. It inspires me to be more random #LookOutWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found an old SD card recently. Been trying to color grade @ Big Sur https://t.co/B1j6XjeLiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[10k words for your first reward?   More like:  • Open Word: Go to Disneyworld  • Get the margins just right: Compet… https://t.co/WcyR9pWY9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indigo_channel @SmallStreamersC @TwitchReTweets @SGH_RTs @FatalRTs @SupStreamers https://t.co/fVyzhwuzZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charles_Leclerc  and @ScuderiaFerrari are less than 0.1 s off Hamilton’s Barcelona pole time of 2018! @alex_albon… https://t.co/vRxEoQNB5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADRIANAAZZIAS Y que me dicen del zulia Maracaibo ese estado a sufrido muchísimo pueblo que ha pasado con la electr… https://t.co/vzzFfMWtLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sydthekid087DFS Its 30 seats... not sure how many races before Sep.1... I assume somewhere in the 20's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_joshburgess Rats. Well I have it queued up.. I really like a lot of the cast, we'll see how it stacks up to season 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Don’t obstruct my view, Bro. https://t.co/dboz8HP5Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been quiet, other than a disallowed Steven Scott goal. Westcastle earn a CK, punched away. 83’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefanielaine @JoeDunman This is a major reason why Crash beat Brokeback Mountain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got $5.09 back from Earny - you have to use it as well :) https://t.co/QUJiUwDKDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting out of bed to start and finish a homework assignment 6 hours before leaving for a cruise is exactly how I w… https://t.co/1QnfViRnzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's up with producers showing whole bunch of non-nominated movies here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Novus AndDo declorum And security for public viewing. Again requestion upon sitting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ataud Aqui en mi rancho...Mexicali BC.. Verde...tomatillo Rojo.....tomate Hasta aqui mi reporte 😎✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all due respect Ryan space, I would say accuracy is an important trait. I would make the argument that Parkey’… https://t.co/78VhAaS5gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody interested in working with @_caguinaldo and I?? #RootedInOakland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly felt so good to get back to playing soccer, especially after taking a dub!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis The veil of the Tabernacle is a type of Jesus' flesh: "Therefore, brethren, since we have confidence… https://t.co/ELS6Rqn7Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait is this guys serious. What the actual fuck.   Ughhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh we need to do better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio Ryan may want to start his victory shirt strip around halftime. Should take a second half to get tha… https://t.co/r51O21wqpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Goats On Boats by @PontoonBrewing/@ScofflawBrewing at @tampabeerworks — https://t.co/eZ1raBnIpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson saying &amp; nodding "yes" during Lady Gaga’s speech is a mood for 2019 #Oscars⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n1ngnuo @IceColdColeman @AndrewDBailey @jackfrank_jjf The next time the Mavs have a better season than the Jazz wi… https://t.co/JC2RA59eir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choppingwoodpod Didn't catch that last one until my Return rewatch. I fully screamed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visita a comercios del Centro de la Ciudad para otorgar circular en materia de uso y regulación del sonido y contro… https://t.co/hVv3QRzsxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Obama coulda send that to the Angels for Mike Trouts next contract smh https://t.co/6wkSsyunkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus you know he has very soft hands. Fellow prisoners will like his gentle touch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markmurdock5 @drewmurdock15 Keep up the good work...Mr Massengale was a great gentleman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little bit of GoPro action from Saturday at ISM Raceway #nascar @ ISM Raceway https://t.co/jGgnE9HU3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited for y’all to hear some of these new tunes I’ve been working on. Thanks for keeping in touch… https://t.co/aRDTZWGSII]]></document><document><![CDATA[I experienced so many cool things in the last couple of months. I'm gonna receive my clubs in a couple of days. I j… https://t.co/oB9hztLepc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMcElroy This tweet sent me on the journey to just now learn that Surf Ninjas is NOT a 3 Ninjas movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgcoughlin @nowthisnews Hey,1stI agree,than say1st we get on right TRACK!Starting were being poked,punched,stained… https://t.co/W4YLGhD4cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior David Nunes doesn’t need a straw to be a treasonous sycophant. https://t.co/0KG6kh4xxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_Dubagner @Newsweek You do understand that without the perpetual lock vote of the welfare society. The Blue wo… https://t.co/I5YyLsL1eF]]></document><document><![CDATA[0-1 '27 Pjaniç Napoli vs Juventus #SerieA #SerieAxESPN #Italy #Domingo #Futbol https://t.co/AYXXdY4S9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these #articles 😎✌ #writerscommunity #writing #amwriting #writerslife #justwrite #liveyourdreams… https://t.co/1aYbTAtTBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diannadawnbby super glue!!!! it sounds weird but it’ll stop the wound from spreading open]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly do not know where we currently stand on the Jussie Smollett thing, it just keeps changing.]]></document></documents></author>