<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not always the case I left my ex and he wished me the best but still the same garbage]]></document><document><![CDATA[There ya go!!!  He’s in clerksvintage 1552 Columbia ave Franklin. $225 #salvationfurniturebytammy #boothsvt @ Clerk… https://t.co/HdKswIIUYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The R.Kelly interview rant looked like a lost scene from Trapped In The Closet.  #rkelly #rkellyinterview… https://t.co/P2mSPIRaxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m that super extra friend that tries so hard to be the first person to say happy birthday to them :))))]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss asked me to check out a book yesterday...  This. Is. So. Horrible. I do not understand. I really don't. ..… https://t.co/Qj2zmqeLRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st day back at #w work... #warrior #washington #washingtonlife #thisismylife @ The Spot https://t.co/6jO74XTwyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #LLMEA County Festival Orchestra conducted by Ephrata SD’s orchestra director @violaman1973 which included 8 ta… https://t.co/zXp8dXyHTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my... this might take the cake for KS posts... https://t.co/fKu0odIQzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaureanTitties @xx_Betty_cx Imagine the cost of that hoe when someone in his family does resell it a close artifac… https://t.co/XAEVMAh0oR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m like literally 10 years late for the twilight saga train but like ... breaking dawn part 2 was wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're time is limited. Don't waste it chasing someone else's dream.  #Time #bigwatches #upthebiz #2CCX… https://t.co/9lPDze5eui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am like the biggest baby when it comes to having my blood drawn and a needle stuck in my arm 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you have the smell of C Diff and a Gi bleed in your nostrils, it will not go away. I need to snort bleach/shower in bleach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist I used to live in chandler and Peoria. Miss the Arizona winters!!! Going there in June can’t wait to go back and visit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinerappwx @KDVR @channel2kwgn @PinpointWX Just saw a 4 car accident near my house in ft Lupton... thank god… https://t.co/NbzdOi6sHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yanksfirst @mayoushtak @CanadaInPeril @Dontvoteliberal You base this on what evidence?   And your biases are clear.   Have a good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Besides, according to all reports, he is a criminal and, according to Trump himself, we don’t allow cr… https://t.co/SOOQKrRKMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZumbaWithATwist is live with Dance Instructor deme_dee on every Tuesday night 7pm-8pm beginning March 5, 2019… https://t.co/8JnfhAUcm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karen8newsnow It’s scary how many people drive around Vegas drunk or stoned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY @tammyduckworth @NewPoliticsAcad I would have to say YOU and all your female colleagues who, I’m sure… https://t.co/sAykfqO6SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_XENAKUMA Oh hell no ive had that shit happen to the homies hella often. Gold Spike is wack as fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martywalsh @charliebaker @senatorwarren @senatormarkley As someone who for years prides myself in "recycling" I am… https://t.co/gw0DvNGKQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really enjoying the surplus of snow until I looked at the road closures... so here’s a throwback to when the… https://t.co/FDukNiQ01K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EbenOfficial who hurt you? currently adding When Did You Know to my let’s cry playlist. i wasn’t ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is true.  Why don't you laid back controlled Republicans stand up and be the leaders that you need to be and b… https://t.co/J2d7EvsZjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your dog tries to disappear into the couch...👀 #love #lovehim #rebel #dogmom #minpinstagram #minpin… https://t.co/rCBozlkgG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danni79jo I am so happy for you! I saw the YT video and the title and gasped with excitement! Congratulations! ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dion 4 , about to be 5 . I’m done . They can’t be far apart in age and rn I don’t see myself being married anytime… https://t.co/SO87dTLH8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You actually like the LEGO Movie?”  Yeah are you actually fucking stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedDeutch Thank you for your speech on anti-Semitism on the House floor today. It was pitch perfect! As a Refor… https://t.co/haMMuFz6FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neil1275536276 @Chrystal_loves I will... Someday. When I can afford it :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalaiLama Like always your Holiness we are honored to receive your wise words. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always impressed by people who play the harmonica!! https://t.co/2Fy0B0vQSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been so happy &amp; appreciative of life as of late. almost 3 weeks now. im so happy to be alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TiE SoCal event last week on the topic of cyber security was awesome! Good turnout (65 people) and crowd participat… https://t.co/e4W5cePFZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmcshea @mad_asa_wet_hen @Jaeandthecity @MuslimIQ There are many many young black men sitting in Riker’s whithout… https://t.co/0voTiycdUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRachelFisher She used to be married to Gavin Newsom!!! Here they are in their old house in SF (while he was may… https://t.co/kRDrIthsxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar So much executive time, isn’t there a tee time he has to get too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously Even I know that I need to hang up my Chefs coat with using the rest room]]></document><document><![CDATA[my first ever boyfriend was a big ass goofy honestly I’m happy he was so mean to me bc it made me who I am today I’… https://t.co/GbrBXmzFlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the models I painted from the happyfishofficial fashion show on Tuesday February 26, 2019!  #Repost alexmtzp… https://t.co/O6CAFaaR7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[My left eyelid has been twitching all day long.  I need to sleep so damn bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get paid tmrw &amp; I already know all my money is going to be wasted on things I don’t need but want 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejusmekamil I’m so shocked idk if it makes it better or worse lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So our car/home keys going missing today has been absolutely wonderful. https://t.co/t584Ia5imb]]></document><document><![CDATA[When happy moments, little successes and the little things that spark joy add up, we are reminded that life is worth living 😌✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is the best memorial to Luke Perry I’ve read all day. I’ll crush on you forever Dylan McKay. 😢❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t even stop people from murdering children even after they are already born now.  Our civilization is backsl… https://t.co/06ZqAEwGyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7: I accepted a challenge from @karamieszanek and @Edtechnically to post covers of 7 books I love: no reviews,… https://t.co/BTE28adMkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSmith4680 @ROHLL5 Hey congrats… Just as many illegals that came into the country this month…😊😊🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Billywires @fromthe108 @Alyssa_Milano How you gonna hate on Courtney Thorn Smith?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nancerrr26 I only have 2 😂 and they’re both on my forearm. I just have not had the funds for more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying quiet reading in the library.  @HicksTigers #WeAreHicksElem @HicksLibrary https://t.co/l0sDYy4EPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light. Aristotle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than a Coach Bus Ride to STATES! Especially after an early morning skate. Let’s Go JAY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PointyFaces I’m so sorry. 💔🐾 I’m glad you were there for her at the end. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m DIFFERENT different, so if you sleep on me - I feel bad for you ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poetry using Clips @GarrigaElem  #Garrigaproud @AppleEDU https://t.co/TGCB2bqp1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never compromise on your #paymentGateway! Get it made for your online business from the best - Openwave! Call us to… https://t.co/fuUZL7lwJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the type of girl your momma wants you to bring home, she’ll want me in the kitchen gossipin’ and helpin’ to mak… https://t.co/BGwk6Jlcmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home. 🎉 Thank you, friends, for all the love and support! Super sore but at least I don’t have to stay overnight!!… https://t.co/DQTlQzMCp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is ??¿:(¿¿¿?:/??? these days but red rocks is only / / 5 0 D A Y S / / away so I'll be just fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Order up! 🍻  Come visit #NERevs specialty servers @jalil_anibaba4, @JuanAgudelo and @bbknighton at @BansheeBoston u… https://t.co/2tDNMv7pat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @GigEmAggies97 to post  pics of  my 7 favorite books . No reviews, just their covers. Each… https://t.co/igWeSntC5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my tits is bigger than the other. Can you tell which one here?  Makeup by @xxxMakeupWhore @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/Qyk2j2pX0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an honor to hear poet Rita Dove today at Wheaton North.  #alag https://t.co/Ppc8FvRMDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurathorpe5263 @proudmawmawof3 @hallmarkchannel Absolutely we need season 7, season 8, season 9 etc. etc. !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi How much alcohol did you drink on the plane? Did you take the military plane and all your family? Ho… https://t.co/QIl9G0oMY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates In the 1938 play, from which the term gaslighting arose, there is a happy ending. The perpetrator went… https://t.co/GXofpfKGh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T__Donald__ I better sleep during the day cuz at night is gonna be a no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @Riley_Woods13,  @TaylinLong, Brenda , Karina, Julia, (Erna and Alexa) this weekend at State. 🤼‍♀️🤼‍♂️💪💪 Go Bulldogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrizwaldMusic Ready for this... in the fall (almost) all of our freshmen college students will have been born afte… https://t.co/SVrovVvPJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanMaddenRose1 Now there is a word I love teaching people, the USA is the most powerful thalassocracy on record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine carrying a child for 9 months just for them to become a snake main]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam Husseini: "It pays to recall this is hardly the first go around with someone trying to stand up to #AIPAC. The… https://t.co/FXHJXfm1FI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where can I get a refund for all the times I spent 99 cents to download a song 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss my sister so much since today is our birthday and the first year apart. HAPOY BIRTHDAY SIS #NASTY19 https://t.co/HB1dtDo0Ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard it through the grapevine...  https://t.co/dwCef3a5uP #winenews #wvwines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my dad owns a couple convenience stores, he’s going to a convenience store expo and he’s so excited 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is going to get people killed with all his "enemy of state" bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialWren Congratulations to Wren’s own....Michael Duffie...on being in the Top 35 of The American Rodeo in Bar… https://t.co/KU81RlBHGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lalalala lalalala Elmo's world 🎶🎵 Happy Birthday Addison! Thank you for celebrating with us 🎈❤ ashstuy #MyGymTucson… https://t.co/fUMnJaHZE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t hear that but it’s horrible news. Is this to get Trumpists to watch @cnn KellyAnne working there is anothe… https://t.co/T7Q3fEZvIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to think that just this time last year I thought I was not worthy to enter into the house of the Lord, little… https://t.co/rwXE5Djzpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe birthdays should be celebrated all week long! So today’s post goes out the beautiful Erin 💕  I met this a… https://t.co/brbA6wJnae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reginaschaffer @RachaelEdu @alicekeeler @rec54 Thank you, perfect talk to show teachers. #K12STEMReady]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silver_fox9 @BlueSea1964 @KamalaHarris She doesn’t care about any one but her on agenda - everything that spews from her mouth is a lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always love coming up to the @idyfest!  A beautiful locale and great people who run it.   I’m looking forward to… https://t.co/tgJfOnsDk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj We have been hearing about Voter Fraud from Republicans, for some time now......Now we have people getting… https://t.co/Qlb24pho9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BibopGGresta thanks for the #follow ! I’m following you back. Checkout my exclusive fan page for never before seen… https://t.co/9wnmUjUxPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Gates says wealth has made him happier—but 'you don't need a billion' to get the same result https://t.co/3i2UOq98Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean really what’s the point of yelling at people that are preparing your food]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss her all the time, so much, but especially when life takes a new, meaningful turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superinspired67 @LoudenSwain1 @scoutstiel @RobBenedict @BorjaBorja1 @Billy_Moran @nerdsandbeyond 😂😂😂 Yesssss!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @SebGorka @realDonaldTrump These people are running for office just to bilk their followers out of t… https://t.co/hSjXnR8G8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just submitted the first draft of chapter three to my adviser. I am still working on analysis so that section is a… https://t.co/XRyUTyNTqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielaBlqz Jajaja las tuyas, las de @elypuente29 y las de @trigo_mar sí me las chuto porque eso es amistad jaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1AaronRiley “They did not pass” - I’ve never seen a memorial quite like this. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SVP quelqu’un a le GIF de Souké quand il dit « Idiotosss » dans Bobodiouf ??#Urgent]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a 4w5 which is why I don’t think that you are going to make me feel better.   Haha! Indeed. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>