<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can't get comfortable enough to relax and sleep....  Gun under the pillow....]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I found this picture from back in 2009 🙈🙈😂😂@jonasbrothers https://t.co/WEdxCyOgmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoNyamweya @XULA1925 Aw, shucks. Thanks for sharing your light and love for my school! #LeadOER #textbookbroke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dreamy imagery for #Saturday! 🐙🐠 #SaturdayMorning 🐡🐬🦑🐳 #HappyWeekend 🌊😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I loved Dumplin. In fact someone asked for a recommendation and thats what i told her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I buy another Bob autograph and do a giveaway at some point? I usually do it when I see Ricky, and I’m think… https://t.co/2w48cEuTpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sitting in my car eating this pepperoni pizza like it's my job.  I know how turned on some of you must be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimJlr2 @PatrickMcGilli5 @mick719 @mysterylyricist @CrowTheArkn @TWITMO_INMATE @oldscool18 @lostandlovinit… https://t.co/yojqVaM5NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahMarais ik this isn’t really about the amazing new song but I just really need you to see this #ColdInLa https://t.co/e3WUcYncHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking dead...hilarious.  This chick is really annoying me in the last season....unsupervising her child in...… https://t.co/rxvWYeOPzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍀Open House Today 🍀  Rain ☔ or Shine 🌞 1825 Erie St. In Bay Park - San Diego 92110 12PM-3PM More information… https://t.co/coAPKOCra2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: How will you repair the division between parties? Castro: "This is something that has been going on for a… https://t.co/tiLY5Tan9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJopinion This is an absolute disgrace!!  Fire the cronies hiding in the government, then elliminate… https://t.co/y940t7aUbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for my #Writer friends. Have you ever struggled with writing on a subject that was incredibly personal (an… https://t.co/OzDizqKd21]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever have a day when mechanical demons attack your house? The fridge's freezer died, the printer isn't speak… https://t.co/byhNTjk3UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FriscoSmoove Mostly library. I don’t wanna always have to pay for stuff lol. Definitely have headphones. Sometimes… https://t.co/dDSYP10Wg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long over the last week and a half, Mercader said.  Nicole Acevedo is a staff reporter at NBC News Digital where sh… https://t.co/g2O3WdtgX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeRuckus i fell asleep during Crystal Skull...two nice young guys woke me up during the credits, ‘Mr. Forner?  The movie’s over’]]></document><document><![CDATA[After more than a year of needing guidance I have discovered a reading and free workshop held once a month five mil… https://t.co/CyRbJht3hZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought I couldn’t take anymore heartbreak life hits you with the “HA bitch cry some more”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi cuerpo sigue siendo un mundo frágil, lleno de batallas, pero ya no hay caos en mi mente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to get #published? Happy to join Paul Brodie, MA on his Get Published #podcast. #authors #consulting… https://t.co/Z0rSUiFCKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/amxLN583lZ https://t.co/ajemoHrw7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @JeffreeStar for distracting me from the pain of cardio.. it goes by faster watching your videos 🙌🤩… https://t.co/crpdfZ46V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t put your cart away after you’re done using it then you’re a piece of shit. 💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lfc123456 Stunning Beautiful Ladies...Happy Birthday to your beautiful Daughter.....xox🍰🥂🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not being able to help someone I love hurts so much. I’ve honestly been crying all day and can't sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always dealing with bullshit when there is bigger fish to fry #priorities]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great way to celebrate #presidentsday. Sofia has my vote! @andreabeaty #davidroberts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasSanders YO, I’ve noticed that too!! Whenever I buy something, the money in my account goes down. It’s really… https://t.co/zNa2HzrVpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre- and post-workout. At least with orange lighting you can’t quite tell how red I am 😜 Happy 1-year (other) Ashle… https://t.co/MJU2110QDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwschattle281 @BaylorGirl2003 @pastorjezer @michelledel3 @m3tnog5 @brainardjill @denman_teacher @EdeGonzalez5… https://t.co/YNRiHEvOrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping that's not all they discuss. Hopefully Putin will present Netenyahu with a plan out of the debacle he has go… https://t.co/VugNmq24ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helenhs @AdamParkhomenko @ChloePolitiCat Nope , because it makes THEM  look stupid for backing a crazy President..… https://t.co/BdKgBu4gxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[another year, another rodeo season 🐎 @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/RY9FltUs7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt @thecadillac3 @CharlieDaniels You coming to Ohio anytime soon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok after extensively listening to 2010s hits all day its time to put Dial Tone by that kid ayesha erotica and slayyyter back on repeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle-thanks for all that you do for WiT and @WLNtmobile. We are so proud of your leadership and pumped to have… https://t.co/93vtdpJzyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iSHEED @STVMAthletics @RomeTrav @KingJames Great times with great memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[goooooood morning, cleveland!  are you ready to party today? #sayyestotheseth @ Hilton Cleveland Downtown https://t.co/ykMQZnkKJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrawlAmerica @hawkeyeinmd @MaryUnderwood9 @THEJeepMafia @TracyGanci01 @Thejeepboss @CCrawln @steelecreations… https://t.co/u1q8lEIfUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelemccarrol @hallmarkmovie I believe it airs again on FEB. 24. Not sure of the time though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold outside, I suggest the “boots with the fur” 😂 #PresleyDay @official_flo https://t.co/dAax7PGkd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpcowgurl @CunningSq16 @strom_annette @thesaucyliberal @ChrisToTheW @esadah @TeaSippingBarb @Momof2in1year… https://t.co/5TbLfeIBGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen What a weenie tRump is....I can only believe that tRump doesn’t realize We know that #tRumpDraftDodger hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so incredibly PROUD of @Christe14099673, @haileyyyp14, and Noel for their confidence and bravery in the… https://t.co/vz3VQa0UBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s your chance to make a difference! Tomorrow, for Poly Gives, give to your favorite thing at @CalPoly (organizat… https://t.co/DT1Cmr4bZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartHyatt @JayBurleson @DwayneMendez666 @kwzombi @Troma_Team @VadaCallisto @lloydkaufman @TromaBen @tromafanatics… https://t.co/EfNs8TFpql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyleDiMarco I interviewed Joe Dannis last week and asked him how obvious it is when a hearing person acts/signs an… https://t.co/628zZuHNQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big THANK YOU to all of you that have signed Steven's petition and those that are still signing!!! We cannot tell… https://t.co/08Qw4gGSX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad that @itsbl0ndie is moving out of SD. Was really hoping to make a trip down there and see if I could meet her once]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leemeade77 @InlawsOutlaws @realDonaldTrump Nope. Trump can’t have Cinco de Mayo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just sat down and read them all. Every card. Every letter. And seeing her handwriting was the most comforting thi… https://t.co/mNLRGMtVg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NitrateDiva I’d need 3-1/2 years to deprive myself, forget sweet tea exists, and train but... https://t.co/wqc9cOvjpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a great morning for coffee and kitties!! @ Seffner, Florida https://t.co/sICrw1TjEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdmar3 @MegaNinetales Neither tears nor the lavender soap from Trader Joe’s makes it go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[forever impulsively ordering new books from amazon prime as a poor attempt to fill the void of having no one to tal… https://t.co/zQk6QIkQcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @RoverDov123 @DavidDiehl20 @sheri_lynn95252 @Bren_O1967 @DrJimmyStar @greg_dabbs @KFearri… https://t.co/nH2yZmQAoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows FIGHT THE MR MEADOWS! Use the House Rules and Procedural Processes 2 STOP THIS MADNESS!! I’m done w… https://t.co/gbs7kOJoaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Levitt_Matt Similar to what is happening in #Isreal  (a Jewish country) where Arabs are not equal to Jewes and don… https://t.co/5sDCOCShFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much great news coming from friends that I can’t handle it! I ADORED this book and I can’t even imagine the beau… https://t.co/hOT50nqVeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to announce that I have joined The Trentham Team at COMPASS!  Thrilled to work with such an ambitious,… https://t.co/QORWc9380F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weedouthate @funder @willwitwonttwit You said a mouthful ther. I agree totally!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I play? "This epic 3-day food fight in Italy involves hurling tons of oranges"  https://t.co/ol3vTMgOt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiah_kb @ErikSperling He muted me because he tried to smear me and rather than retract, it's easier to be an ass… https://t.co/HBhzQhtKB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I’ve watched the office from beginning to end 30x &amp; I still can’t get enough 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[writing papers is 10x more difficult when english aint even ya first language &amp; you keep making grammar mistakes🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nitedog137 No apologies needed! Please take care of yourself and Ali; that’s what is needed!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate people I can send ugly Snapchat selfies to. You guys are the real ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot Anti Cow Cortez was caught eating hamburgers along w an Aides! Hypocrites!! I don’t eat a lot of meat but I… https://t.co/gQsyCuOl8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working 0630hrs-1900hrs! (@ BlueCross BlueShield of WNY - @bcbswny in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/rIHe1yEpgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorealBeard @BlackCraftCult Speaking from experience get any kind of bag you like. Doesn't have to specifically be… https://t.co/PXpqytjKnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying my first meal out in Manhattan at the Waverly Diner. #bicoastalactor #treatchoself @ Waverly Restaurant https://t.co/7gJmwQumy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve reached a point in my life where the waitress at denny’s knows my order... i think i peaked]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is some praise to be grouped in the same company as @DFriesenGlobal and @PatriciaBoalCTV @ctvottawa. Thank you… https://t.co/9PsCBKC4gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to anyone I’ve known for more than 5 seconds  https://t.co/5ZbxEN0XVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one: my professor: im mostly straight, but have you seen chris evans with a beard???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland “I’ve seen the cages,” the lawmaker said. “I just want you to admit that the cages exist.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend of golf!  #4 109 #3 94  😏.  More practice. #legend #pinehurst https://t.co/HVHmVbY4ZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghanhackney @poolhoneys okay I did not know others like me existed !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why i’m crying about the mars rover. tell me. i demand to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimbo Mathus and Alvin Youngblood Hart @JimboMathus #jimbomathus alvin_youngblood_hart #alvinyoungbloodhart… https://t.co/tRGkLIsBnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what God thinks I did to deserve the people I have but apparently I’m doing something right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent Valentine’s Day meeting visioning about the future of supportive housing in the region with my collaborat… https://t.co/LcFoa4A8EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[congratulations to EVERY SINGLE PERSON, CAT AND CHICKEN that worked on #BohemianRapsody you all deserve these award… https://t.co/dzfRnQkft6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever grateful for having you ❤️❤️ #HappyValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/mHs6dxhH96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audubonsociety @AmoebaSisters Carolina Wren! So much personality! And they love exploring human things! https://t.co/s9NCqCeykC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do men not know what personal space is or do they just not care? Sitting at an empty airport gate and you need to s… https://t.co/JT3cq0ck7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Release orcas and beluga whales from the “whale jail” in Srednyaya Bay - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/9lcLiaamcL via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for spring ⛵️ #northforker #northfork #greenport #longisland #nofo #eastend https://t.co/AdgEqiDl18]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶😉Check out Run Run Away by Slade on Amazon Music😎👍😂😂😂 https://t.co/oKHweWpEAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow @mrBobbyBones Everyone deserves a second chance give her the benefit of the doubt she may of had a hard week 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForestKing5280 @mornews @pattonoswalt @PublicEnemyFTP Straight out racist the sucka was simple and plain, motherfuck him and John Wayne!👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break legs to the cast, crew and production team of @CaryGroveHS musical, All Shook Up. It’s been a pleasure creati… https://t.co/I32v6FXTF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreKnott Indians won by 11. Hopefully that was enough for the negative nellies. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAttyHuber @doj And you are putting which men into jail for trying to overthrow the government? Rosenstein still… https://t.co/D9vU1EOrz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[its nice to know that i am no longer struggling and have a home of my own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTonDrump @Prosperous1776 Hey Ton, if Mueller had anything it would have been leaked by now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening Now: Mayor Weaver announcing a water giveaway in Flint as part of #WorldWaterDay https://t.co/M0ddYHOQiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably the closest I’ll ever get to @kelly_clarkson but I’m not even mad was totally fan girling #notsorry 💁🏻‍♀️… https://t.co/rtAVDIy0O7]]></document></documents></author>