<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When this game starts, we gotta have the loudest LGI chant the NHL has ever heard k?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: the date when so freaking well!!! He’s a little different but I like it 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GonzalesKristie Welcome to spring in Austin. People complain we don’t have seasons. We do Hot, Hotter and Weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @SPEXcast @Robotbeat @John_Gardi @SpaceX But there is no @Starbucks on Mars. ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntSanPhilly @NHLFlyers @penguins @NHL With the pens set to start the 3rd on the PP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like economic retaliation. Independence from European nazi superstate will rebound withno eurozone taxes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know we do "I can't believe that person was still alive" a lot on here, but I truly can't believe Stanley Donen was still alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Brothers Keeper!!!! @ Redemption &amp; Recovery Restoration Ministries, Inc. https://t.co/TY5kawkqTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry ¯_(ツ)_/¯ ; N🚫T !  🙃 @notsorryapparel 🆕#ad • 🆕#notsorrycrew • 🆕#detroit • 🆕#notsorryaf ➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖➖ 📸 By 🔥… https://t.co/K8dUDiOYHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Delta aircraft are equipped with toilets as well. That is infinitely more useful than a goop channel. Rethink t… https://t.co/tMq9JOnKbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent my poetry books to Mary Oliver almost a year ago. I wonder if she got a chance to thumb through them before… https://t.co/UmmOo36P0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to keep my King Gay Rool profile pic but also i love my inkling . dies]]></document><document><![CDATA[We accomplished the Dream 😍 Top 5 DoNgS 💪 https://t.co/m2QK0kkNYH https://t.co/liyAluVZww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarlingPNikki I get it.  But how y’all know what someone got off rip? Or do the ladies wait it out to see ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OKCNightCourt @awkwordy Used to be a Quick’s. Remember the one at 59th and May, was just like it. Was a Long John Silvers. Miss it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @AB_Owl Lots of people who haven't learned to function around others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W6SIX6 @Karah_Wilson I don’t know who that is, I didn’t make or design but around 20 familiars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy MTN DEW® at Dollar General® to earn Team Rubicon gear #DewGeneralStore #promotion - Ends 12/31/19. While suppli… https://t.co/jQrNU4b4H5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have not and will not stop fighting to protect our drinking water and watershed. https://t.co/D8ysJlY40u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/waSWpdRU3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luggage tags for Magic Express have arrived. So have the matching Disney t-shirts. We are major Disney nerds. https://t.co/vS6bAIc6NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new "How to Effectively Draw a Charge in HS Basketball" training video is out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to 23 🤙🏼 #BdayMood @ The Cheesecake Factory https://t.co/zxcXEDo73B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es que amo las IG stories de @danielaacallee 😱😱😱😱🐢 que ternura es Calle 😍 https://t.co/daY2lK0lgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[mattshore__  kicking off @ Portsmouth, New Hampshire https://t.co/L3B7FAbn8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@echo8o @bourbasted @crmerck @jbuck0 @dbongino @ananavarro I think you're a joke. Real racists find racism where there isn't any.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bachacalupo @HopkinsMedNews @Trib_ed_board @chicagotribune Smoking--related illnesses kill more than 1000 Americans every DAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, some folks are using the local FB yard sale groups to slang dat pussée https://t.co/YaX7HQjG0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most dystopian shit I’ve ever seen in my life. Nicole Sherzinger full on shedding a tear at the end wha… https://t.co/bYTaNUDAdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notbasketball Me too.  I'm probably gonna kill myself if i don't get a gf by 11:59:59 PM on December 31st, 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#projects shouldn’t just fit in and respect social and community #context but also add to it - #design… https://t.co/sd3RNVwWMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisGlzArtea Las Ligas de Holanda y Portugal son de desarrollo, de ahi brincas a las Grandes Ligas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday in heaven Pops! This pic makes me smile 😃 especially your hand writing @ Rossville, Staten Island https://t.co/t8m5gCnO3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Eddyboy,  does President Trump not taking a salary mean he’s wants to save money for th… https://t.co/i2B5PZjzM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Your Boss is The Best and Gives Me Tickets to @dallasmavs Last Home Game Which Could Possibly Be @swish41 Last… https://t.co/glnr2eX7Mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m opening up the service in an hour so lift me up in prayer if you can :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Arum Warns: This is Now or Never For Felix Verdejo - Boxing News https://t.co/07Z0okkQTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @ShatOnTV , when ya gonna come out with the preview episode for @americangodsus season 2??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffSchuler @Boxmenot @mimetic_ @Just4TheCause @TakeThatCDC @itsmepanda1 @Eventhedogsabo1 @drfixus @VeritasEver… https://t.co/XXOVY10QyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have @realDonaldTrump coward ass on video taking K Jong Un word that he had nothing to do with Warmbier death. Y… https://t.co/hT1PvdZSgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to check out the new @JustinColeMoore record for @nashvillenoise today. If you grew up on 90s country like me,… https://t.co/duVR9nQBVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Termoeléctrica de Morelos va.  Según @lopezobrador_ los resultados de la Consulta hecha en Morelos, Tlaxcala y P… https://t.co/QVFXfQvV1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, clásicos should be a national holiday.... just stop everything you’re doing for two hours and then get back to it right after]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun on the horizon is a good sign for a Saturday adventure. Let's go! ☀  😁  💚💚💚💚💚💚 . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .… https://t.co/YMolmOkxUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Madrid out, surely the greatest story remaining is just how far Cristiano can take Juve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video of the snow in Fountain Hills, AZ!  @NWSPhoenix @MikeOlbinski @JimCantore @weatherchannel @MattPaceWeather… https://t.co/UKvOa4dcUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[better, stronger, healthier, smarter, more caring person. So here we go. Just a quick line or two about each of the… https://t.co/Ymu0QR1sma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii No that’s their method of money laundering to their campaigns!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pacific Swordfish, Golden Bear Ranch beets, red quinoa, carrot butter, crispy kale 🥬 rosewoodlodi  . . . . . . .… https://t.co/c9tTMMGyLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO Yeah she is a Swell Looker when she’s Pissed Off..... like a Rhinoceros in Heat]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dance cause its my escape from the crazy world around me.  To be free from the thousands thoughts that go thru my… https://t.co/FmPzqnUE1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly NOT a knockout @ScottHanson but oh well lemme get away from this onion it’s making me eyes water… https://t.co/SdMAeVYf4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iam_ifeanyi9 What do the Neville brothers horse face and you have in common? All Cunts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeJuan Blair getting some court time with Austin! The veteran big man has been a part of six NBA playoff teams https://t.co/rpDHvXY4HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximumdragons @SenSanders I'm saying references to his age are irrelevant, ageist attempts to invalidate the seri… https://t.co/hx0iFbxDG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGB331 Thanks JG. you’ve got boys so you know what you’re up against in this world. I am very proud of the men the… https://t.co/XOWacl4woz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fox5Kyle You have to define "sports town" Is it Boston, Pittsburgh or NY? Absolutely not. It was a total Redskins… https://t.co/OYk3fynSkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish more professional athletes gave back instead of spending their insane amounts of money on bullshit.. wishful thinking right ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @DebbieC50234788 @SusanSarandon Thank you Susan for helping get Trump in office, said Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withrowzone Do you think SU gets Duke again Saturday night? Without Zion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must be at Liberal Party Headquarters. Fake Feminists https://t.co/RTJl5PfMvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MittRomney Said to a friend of mine just recently who was asking why I was hanging out at her station, and I absen… https://t.co/Ig1o0kKSEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoppeanduknowit @Icelandair @scottsflights Yah ... they are often three stops or with gnarly layovers.  I like Sco… https://t.co/9MFUtqZsBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseCardenas1 Son obvios los resultados que pones en tu encuesta. No podían ser de otra manera. Te encanta el chay… https://t.co/XamDWPbuNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialist Student Gets DESTROYED on Live TV https://t.co/YsWAIsHIRv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson Worst negotiator ever in both Baseball and Basketball. @Dodgers @Lakers Keep Magic off the negotiatin… https://t.co/BCWTpFVJrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give a round of applause for Ray Chase everyone he is officially the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterAlexander When nobody loves you, you have to pretend like everybody loves you.  (Sally Brown, Peanuts(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have people not been talking about John Legend’s new single “Preach”?! It’s amazing🙌🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tanks!   #birthdayweekend #tanks #canadianwarmuseum @ Canadian War Museum https://t.co/Amcz2qfV55]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I still lift weights at 41? So I can bring in all the groceries in 1 load and not feel like my arms are gett… https://t.co/FfdxMIzOm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @MadAsHellatIQ45 I will forgive them but I will never trust them again]]></document><document><![CDATA[3a) Old trick of the dishonest: if they can't creditably accuse you for some "sin", they accuse you of being "soft"… https://t.co/vTaxBsTjtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremynewberger Well dang all this time we have been doing it wrong! So when our favorite sports team wins a game… https://t.co/k56F8JpfxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rondober_ 🤣🤣🤣te mmste y un wey tapándose la nariz...son ustedes weyes que huelen de la verga😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Hollywood Walk Of Fame Stars Get Cleaned https://t.co/1a5ufmKxdf via @laist.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Great FA crew on AA5214 to GSP— friendly, happy to be working, and providing great service!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Region of Waterloo mayors headed to Queen’s Park to lobby province on transit, housing and other issues https://t.co/kRIYs2p88E]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could I not surprise @AJVoelpelCG with YO!! Wedges. @CallawayGolf @HarryArnettCG https://t.co/OqtFSSTDZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need them to come out with a naturally radiant moisturizing formula for their foundation and im sold on ever… https://t.co/luYYcMgLsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repulsive_cut @jasonlschwartz @doritmi Terrified scientific community, unable to publish the truth..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im very proud of myself, I pushed myself harder at the gym today. I’m finally getting out of my gym shell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump probably shouldn’t be talking about treason. How many of his people have been locked up and or cha… https://t.co/Ig1j1dn9K8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want thanks @djEFN for tickets! The movie #cominghomeColumbia was awesome! And also a great look how we all… https://t.co/pDg2rIrgDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[El grado de irrepetuosidad hacia los creyentes en internet es impresionante]]></document><document><![CDATA[All u fools is wack. Sayin I’m right but this whole time been waiting in a reply back from her. I lose everytime. I… https://t.co/GkgMMYuSem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell If the Dems can't determine a way of supporting all candidates while choosing one favorite they'll lose in 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont like how low his hands are. He may be trying to avoid the bodykick with that stance which makes sense cuz i… https://t.co/WoWRIaugMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a No Crusts by @FunkyBuddhaBrew at @funkybuddhabrew — https://t.co/E4DOG03Sc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Act as if everything depended on you; trust as if everything depended on God. — St. Ignatius of Loyola]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGNNews Prediction: Case dismissed. Athletes knew (or SHOULD HAVE known) about the pay differential when they signed contracts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please it’s because he’s the only one dining for the country not like democrats anything they do is for THEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three boys. One birthday celebration. All fun. Happy Birthday to some of my closest boys @tair_kadimchik and… https://t.co/mQstzcPAdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:24.2°F WchillLow:15.6°F Wind:1 mph Dir:NNW Baro:Rising slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:62% UV:0.0 @ 05:00 02/26/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[That haircut ruined my whole day bruh I want to smack the shit outta him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electricyvr Very nice! Will have to check that out on my next visit. #transitdesign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realonlinejack @SportsCenter @DwyaneWade @DavidFurones_ Imagine hating a person who doesn’t even know you exist En… https://t.co/ECtdhQ6THA]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it turned out Ryan he was right on every thing you have.said.  the dems and Adam Shiff were lying and trying to… https://t.co/M6qvU2OS3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uranus_seraa ايه والله متخلفين حيل، مدري شلون يفكرون، وش بيضرهم يعني لو حطو الليت فالسقف ومكانه الطبيعي، وحتى إذا… https://t.co/kosxKmdjJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeckledEdges @TT197 @tdanjones1 @dave451972 @johnflipside @NRAHillbilly @WillOfThePeopl5 @J_MAGA @QProofs… https://t.co/qHYYvNaKHI]]></document></documents></author>