<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My moms having her 40th bday party at Casa De Chapa. Be ready for the Puke]]></document><document><![CDATA[***The Vanilla Godzilla Channel*** 5,000+ liked videos, 600+ song videos rock, pop, disco, jazz, standards, novelty… https://t.co/nAqdHJ7a0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fightgameplay3r @JakotsuReborn When you're Charlotte, you're never more than a few months away from holding a title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To do business with L.A., city contractors now must disclose ties with the NRA: The L.A. City Council passed an ord… https://t.co/L9bFlPJM4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carpy1130 @maggieNYT I think that’s “catsup.” Just to create another controversy. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PVLWarriors @FuckNjTransit not one Rockland train has shown up in Pearl River so far today. @ChrisDayNY @NYGovCuomo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricG90850975 @luisjoelm @HomeDepot @Jeremycoster2 @LoganMassillon @OvidioGuzman77 Congrats To Honys On Sales Asso… https://t.co/2JXqyqv02I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Rush Limbaugh has never made any sense I used to listen to him for some laughs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if @TheCarterrj would make the trip across the pond for Homecoming this year? 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay ! Today is Officially My Birthday 🎂🎉 Thanks to Everyone Who Has Come Out to Celebrate with Me Sooooo Far !! I'… https://t.co/SAvKg6hKuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure they're feeling a little threatened with the potential of AEW, but they really shouldn't be. If it forces… https://t.co/UbROdVJbAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrtablaze But don’t try to mute me. I’m “of color “, a female, and a DemonRat. Therefore, if I call you a racist, you must be!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sodbusterk I was looking at fertilizer but it comes from a retailer, supposed to be current products.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made hella memories at SXSW last year... I'ma sit this one out this year lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody thought @realDonaldTrump would be so awesome. #POTUS45 #POTUS2020 will go down in #History for making… https://t.co/vSgSGfiixs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snewb22 Lol, I’m just humoring myself at your expense.   Snow sucks no matter where you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[US airstrike kill 2019 24 Somalians 1/31 https://t.co/SQPhVEBypz 8 Syrians 1/30 https://t.co/BnQJxeyqg1 13 Afghans… https://t.co/0bJHhmDyux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomsan106 The focus on games and tournaments starts way too early and clubs are trying to teach tactics to 7 year… https://t.co/uqhT8ln0QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docsander30 He has to be careful on the line!! Toes looked a little on the blue😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the war on drugs. We the people are the enemy. In this case, a sick person in a hospital room was the targe… https://t.co/1dPJoQjekL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today and everyday, I’m humbled at the amazing women that are a part of my life. To my mother, my wife, and my sist… https://t.co/639ObwUJhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When is NOME 9!!!!!??? @urltv @Jayblac1615 @Therealtech9 @SMACKWHITE #ATW #URL #HTOWN https://t.co/HIY2RJis6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonoCobos @NoticiasdlCielo @_LASNOTICIASMTY @gaby_lozoyag Ya con café en mano para ver a nuestra guapa compañera y… https://t.co/Uic5C9lMzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRideshareGuy @AlexRoy144 I second that.  Was at SLC airport and had a “15 min away” for 20 minutes ... canceled… https://t.co/wToPhIKkGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imtrapbitchwhou Ion won’t no ties to this nigga I just can’t wait to JuJu get this ring for us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the street bands are the best! On #RoyalStreet in the #FrenchQuarter @ Royal Street https://t.co/3WNTyVmpE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't have to face today. Today has to face your Jesus. #victoryinJesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[loudounrugby Terrific JV win today. #saturdayrugby #saturdaysarefortheboys #kidsports #rugby @ Grizzly Sports Compl… https://t.co/Qct8LwM6FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exjon They are simply not worth that effort. My rent-a-lib place lets me sleep in on Sat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarzolaMagic @One_Punch_Dan @YaSmiity @JohnVicars1 @lalo_827Marlins @ArianFoster @MisterRoast98 Paid for one or tw… https://t.co/iUiD6vC8tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así las cosas en NL , en una semana tenemos todas las estaciones del año https://t.co/r6LnXOIWvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "Living Black Studies: Reimagining Black Canadian Studies" https://t.co/xq29jLAWLB https://t.co/riqT4jL3PT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mind is a plentiful toolbox.  Belief is its most powerful tool.  #LateNightMusings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRMarathon I’ll do you one better! Thank you guys for the awesome 127 Days of Medals! https://t.co/21uCe9NDep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know how to feel drinking Tito’s and cranberry in this bar with Switchfoot playing... let me pray... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met this awesome couple Frank &amp; Pat in Joshua National… https://t.co/B1ImfpO6WZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A decent debut for a new MCU character, but just not a great film. My review of #CaptainMarvel is now up. Link in m… https://t.co/AglzEsLPGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@901terrell @the_jamesbrown My puff balls are receiving toooooo much slander from a nigga that look like Wayne Brad… https://t.co/mNIwX6JjcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungBoselli @markfromjax The bigger issue is likely ease, not cost. It should take no more than 3 minutes on a mo… https://t.co/ID0HmFSULE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @EveryKWB Big difference between hate and seeing through everyone else bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cole_Freshkorn I’m gonna be pissed if we don’t get rid of Bob and/or Panarin and get bounced in the first round or… https://t.co/tsAgTKr1Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah absolutely no chance any of these people are security professionals. #CheckTheCrocs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This piece of art is single handedly the best thing I’ve ever seen . Both in skill and representation of this shith… https://t.co/P52nDXuuF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robgreg1975 @AOC Well not only do they allow idiots like her in Rob they also openly support planned parenthood. SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pedal2DMetals @magagary687 @RobinRoberts @JussieSmollett @ABC @GMA @TheView @CNN @MSNBC @donlemon Faking a hate cr… https://t.co/85WTGi5nix]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had the choice between ending world hunger and ending winter right now I'd chose to end winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The1stWright @SibbieBoxing @Im_gr8nss @TheKidIrv24 @UnkhanciousAmir @JackAlterr @SmokinYungBruno @Yogi_CapAlot… https://t.co/XGp41whr6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one with any common sense expected it too change. Demand drives the supply.  El Chapo Is Behind Bars, but Drugs… https://t.co/UhU4GoHTCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought @lindsaylohan was a twin when I saw her in the Parent Trap. @DisneyStudios I blame y’all for the d… https://t.co/9YCOnz8TKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews So you lied about getting Jared a Top Secret Security Clearance? https://t.co/RvCj1jXkBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week I scored a perfect condition North Face for Taylor for $5 and a perfect condition Patagonia for $40 for m… https://t.co/GWem0SUmjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenbino @_auutummm that that time in the gym just to get clapped by my 9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pray for my grandmother❤️ they found a lump on my angel and have to do some work to find out what it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigresOficial no lo heredó nació Tigre, vamos con todo en el clásico 1️⃣1️⃣8️⃣, los apoyamos desde Kansas https://t.co/upqK8nZd14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theodore cried for a straight half hour. Turned on @ColterWall and he fell asleep almost immediately. 🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW TO KNOW YOU’RE A MILLENNIAL: OSCARS EDITION  This made you think of the closing credits of Mighty Ducks 2.   https://t.co/GvXBmJz6iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bible study (@ Pitman United Methodist Church in Pitman, NJ) https://t.co/b2hCOTM6OQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quickly didn’t run into a screen, he ran into a brick wall.  #GoBigBlue #BBN #UKvsMIZZOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[(4/5) The Point! by Harry Nilsson. A concept album with spoken stories throughout about the only round-headed perso… https://t.co/s30QsHlaLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people don't reply to your messages but make the effort to keep the snap streaks.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se faire réveiller avec un bon café sur ma table de chevet.   "Bon matin chéri, les enfants aimerais manger tes crê… https://t.co/bvOHelE7KQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNEE !! Que comparación tan absurda !! Cuando un periodista va de capa caida, inventa eee tipo de comparacioes ab… https://t.co/mhoMqnH2Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCComics @JimLee @geoffjohns and Dan Dido, can we please get more one shot stories like #WonderWoman51 by… https://t.co/3IZ7go1pEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 12th Wedding Anniversary to this boss-lady right here. She’s the one that makes things happen in our family.… https://t.co/Rv9bKpu2qU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldrocka @consmover I’ve even found myself blocked by conservatives &amp; have no clue why. #TwatterShenanigans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicahTheBrave Can't agree more.  I teared up a little durring that video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how it’s almost 2am and your searching for that perfect Pistons starter jacket on eBay and the all the sud… https://t.co/gpowEzjknb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandon29us That’s good. That’s not the case for most though, I’m afraid. My refund is going to be better but my w… https://t.co/0cJCRmLoiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something tells me we're getting a @PodSaveAmerica live show in Milwaukee in July 2020 &amp; I'm totally here for it. #DNCinMKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I suppose we should be grateful that Jon M et al have focused in on Trump as the warrior for their white suprem… https://t.co/3qGbFHMB16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie is 100% not ready if she can’t even express how she feels #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarAyub32 Westbrook KD and Harden were on the same team. Still boggles my mind go they couldn’t figure out how to… https://t.co/JIkMEiZ43E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackamrita You seem the type of person that says “you shouldn’t punish a girl if they made false rape allegations” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does this girl think she’s the shit again? not sure what makes her feel like she’s so much better than everyone… https://t.co/qBdTVPg5TH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite a show tonight in the Texas Hill Country! #sunset #texas #hillcountry @ Guadulupe River https://t.co/ZwUPVPCMGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the responses to this from Notts fans are hilarious. Calm down lads, it’s only a newspaper. Don’t buy it if… https://t.co/EUpO7LoUmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wongmjane Just saw a few of your recent tweets. I’m really sorry you have to deal with stupid people hiding behind… https://t.co/GkqF5KNJlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annendil @FixesItself @lovemyjessica22 @verocruz @bfosterls7 @MisleaderC @Carlos_Can_Do @CunningSq16… https://t.co/oovJk2rxU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nutellaaellaa_ @YoungStaccs47 @you_know_why_I_ Pure ??!?! https://t.co/Fcgj7OsQFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything can happen but I am going to predict right now that the Democratic Primary comes down to a two way or thre… https://t.co/N5yZE6hZRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyOJr is proving once again that he not only talks the talk but he also walks it. Stacy will be the first Afri… https://t.co/cKxy1nhjk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t even know how this is physically possible to do and not get a single kill? https://t.co/bL0hNzogut]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your phone unsynchs with your car. First world problems. Plus I have a VW. So I can't figure this shit out hahaha 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pegobry There’s a lot unpack here. I also want to know, what are the key issues?]]></document><document><![CDATA[if this was my kid... i’d be whoopin those other kids ass. idc how old you are, you ain’t getting away with hitting… https://t.co/KAJnvGVIQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[UFC fight in espn. Idk how this dude didn’t go down. Big props to the official not prematurely stopping the fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's be honest, @HawleyMO was in Senate campaign mode the duration of his 20 months as MO AG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarperSimmons19 @ECUTigersFB @ECUCoachKMac Congrats brother 🤙🏽#codymandellprodigy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnWDean Well, you know Shanahan, the Secretary of Defense, will now face a barrage of assaulting tweets and disp… https://t.co/4se23TYVsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrleansDarkwa did you just run my squad 7-0 in pro clubs or is that an imposter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emptywheel The WALL was a 2016 campaign gimmick. The WALL is still a campaign  gimmick.  Trump is asking U.S. taxp… https://t.co/ArdHqivOma]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 1/2 hrs until tonight's @AmericanIdol #SeasonXVII premiere w/ @RyanSeacrest @katyperry @LionelRichie… https://t.co/zwW2KM33S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t know who Sophia Turner was before the new Jonas Brothers video, just drop off the face of the earth fam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more big names that enter the democratic 2020 races, the more likely we are to get 4 more years of Trump. The d… https://t.co/87w2mfEN5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurieLhahn @TOLBERT_PE2 @TOLBERT_PE1 @Tolbert_ES Don’t worry, we did adult Hungry Hungry Hippos on scooters at th… https://t.co/CrFbsufCcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisvire (What else is there to do in Storrs, Connecticut during a blizzard?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perallmytitties Even if it happened pitching gets you to the promise land]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up, @BetterBaseball @baseballout podcast with one of the best hitting minds ever, Reggie Smith.… https://t.co/DexpyIg8g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_HUD_REPPIN @KikiAimerito @takeyourchits i think you all need to meet some cooler people]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to the guy who said “only I can fix this”? Oh, I know, he turned out to be a racist, con man, and a c… https://t.co/fX7JMRdbF0]]></document></documents></author>