<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My baby fever is so bad and I have no babies in my life to love so this sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mari Bishop was headed to Hubbard w/her son Mathew when they slid off the road. @storycosheriff Lt. Lennie picked t… https://t.co/8GqCdvuUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princess             Eugenia ..      Admired Around The  World!  Most Promising  To England .. To The World!! https://t.co/2D2i7DOIaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirginiaRoseXXX I went to Panama to jungle school when I was in the Army. I’ve never heard anything as spooky as w… https://t.co/QHAbwKg5C8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landmark Equal Pay Law in Iceland last year, the United States can learn from‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MascoGB Pssst, they’re just Chieftains. Athletes can be either male or female. On the other hand, if you call the… https://t.co/gYN0jSc19Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christy Chafe - The Independent Author Network https://t.co/XS6Rkl88mE #ian1 #iartg #author #amreading… https://t.co/mjPGOoW0YK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLysowski Fair enough, Lance. The number of Wawas in Florida is really impressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my upstairs neighbor appreciates my @ArianaGrande shower concerts as much as I appreciate his vacuuming at midnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[When she said turn off the machines, I thought homegirl was about to start pulling all the plugs from the wall inst… https://t.co/RRQSjdTKvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last interview slot on a press tour usually is not ideal. Thanks, @americangodsus’ @MrRickyWhittle, for treatin… https://t.co/vlp629Fk86]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point wouldn't practically anyone be better than the embarrassment @POTUS we have in office now. #2020Election #ImpeachTheMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Day 2 &amp; I’m ready to Battle Beaches!!! ♥️🌊🌴👌🏽 #BATC #LETSGOFAME https://t.co/6yxUBFUqi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @HouseGOP Your plans to try to discount Cohen’s testimony by calling him a liar to protect Trump is terr… https://t.co/SY6JEs85PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rphillips912 @Panthers @CameronNewton Do you work on your "craft" or do something to improve your career during your off days???? 🤔🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re not intending to be together, don’t go wasting my heart. #taylerbuono 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reasons I work out: 1. I live alone so I need to be able to carry all my groceries with one hand and unlock doors w… https://t.co/Ncji5AR4Bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STRthruMUSIC @technobaee @Fonziie @brandonvree IT SMELLED LIKE SYRUP!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨”We can learn from each other’s resilience.” Come join the dialogue #Miami! Buy your tickets today, link in bio!… https://t.co/HsDqr3Ic6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Hmmmmm.... thought you were making statements about Global Warming 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV’s turn! ⚽️KK with the GOAL, Sarahy with the 🅰️! 1-0 with 29:05 left in the 1st half! https://t.co/VG0BkVxkiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Anonymous Girl by Greer Hendricks,  Sarah Pekkanen https://t.co/E3pS4GlCnM via @juliesbookshelf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aidan_Always Dynamite with a laser beam, Guaranteed to blow your mind...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My nieces and nephews are people of color” are the next words out of his mouth. So Yes exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am declaring a snow day for my kid #WinterStormWarning #NYC #WeatherAuthority City Mama Bear 🐻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrybutler9 @TourismIreland @IrelandChicago @iahcchicago @GameOfThrones @DiscoverNI @NikonUSA @IrishNewsChgo Brea… https://t.co/yt4NJd8KvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This testimony is incredibly sincere—to the point of sympathy—and incredibly damning (of Trump).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Define soon. Not sure I can take more waiting for this boil on our republic to be lanced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old coworker sent me this video of a house i designed almost done.😭😭 It’s an amazing feeling to see something i… https://t.co/fmt6oef5Yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was feeling better about myself all happy ! &amp; now I’m back at square one 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re not mature enough to handle it. Sometimes it’s best to keep your mouth shut and let them do their dumb bitc… https://t.co/373IAVrcvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QUnitedWeStand2 What this has to view with my message? Be tolerant and liberal. There is no crime in being success… https://t.co/YtT6cxWXHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I got to my car and realized I forgot to tell Scooter how much I love him so I went all the way back up to… https://t.co/9wZ1oGzCYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys! @mikejoy500 + @darrellwaltrip + @JeffGordonWeb = great fun to watch this AM!  #DAYTONA500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHATUPRG dude!! Album it’s on repeat!! 🙌🏽 this is soo awesome! 🔥 https://t.co/J7ZcVuNKoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shut, and I can’t stress this enough, the fuck up. Steve Irwin did more for animals than y’all ever did. Why don’t… https://t.co/h7O19cd7Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christipedigo @FlappersComedy Thank you for the lovely post! You and your guy were an awesome crowd! Hope to see you again😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challenge accepted from @Corona1515  Post covers of 10 albums that make up a soundtrack of my life: no explanations… https://t.co/jFFZeMIqPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is broken tonight. If you have any thoughts of harming yourself please tell someone. The devil is a liar a… https://t.co/m6oG9DW9Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[That describes a Rethuglican who is not a coward. There is no such person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alovablenerd And, I love reading those cookbooks.... fascinating things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampionsTour @Braves @CologuardGolf I am happy for you. I am also a colon cancer survivor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Billionaires can spend their money as stupidly as they wish. Now that you worked to help keep Amazon out of NY… https://t.co/24SwO4bGxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those yeezys y’all be wearing are ugly and just shows me a lot of y’all are followers.. there’s about 80% of my res… https://t.co/UKIxuHDQxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson you put on an amazing show last night. Not sure how anyone could not pick you as their coach.… https://t.co/pPdegklloW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft situation aside, we are on to 2019 https://t.co/7gS3kPR0rW via @patspulpit]]></document><document><![CDATA[in my defense i miss pmore so much and after laughter tour so it’s not my fault i kept singing]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has her Poppop's ocean blues. #CosimaMoment https://t.co/7oAxmMHj5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @LindseyGrahamSC What the hell! They're all whacked on opiod or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i appreciate/celebrate women everyday not just on #InternationWomensDay  🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing job @AlanaMReynolds on presenting solo on trauma informed practices at #scamle2019 @UofSCEducation https://t.co/qol4YTJQXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoomarang @cspanwj There is a cure for Cancer...But the money is in Treatment...Not the Cure...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shamsud Ail who is Frank Miller used William Sampson's body with Sam Darden who is Frank Giancana's son.....this is… https://t.co/MUEjeBuMGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaxAcrocat @AmazingAcroCats Nah. She followed the rules and gave Tuna space so she didn't get swatted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that it was national margarita day and i wasn’t able to have one is truly..... devastating and heartbreaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is #Trump in Vietnam right now? Meeting with Kim Jong Un??? Bruh....he's not coming back SMH  #CohenTestimony @NBCNews #LIVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another night of being babysat by my Lakeland Bestie!!!  Let the good times roll! @ Lakeland, Florida https://t.co/EniFNh0R4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferWexton recalls male legislator asking who was watching her kids when she served in Va House of Delegates.… https://t.co/HUu9MLUiW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean you roll down your window and bellow Moo! Right?  And when you see hay in a field, do you point and yell,… https://t.co/iET0w5SYWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help us close out Black History Month by celebrating our black educators! On Feb. 28th (tomorrow) from 5-9pm a port… https://t.co/QNPZNcUkx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowday #snowdays #adultsnowday #snow #snowy #snowfall #wintery #winter #winterinontario #winterincanada #tree… https://t.co/e4dqvzGkax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast @arelab13 If the Gov. of VA does not have to step down after saying it is ok to kill a baby up to birth th… https://t.co/kdKS0P3DLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renegade_Fusky I wonder how long before they run out of money again lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siubhan_H If that makes you feel better, Judy. I don't know any white nationalist "anti-vaxxers."  Many ex-vaxxers… https://t.co/Nr54xCMwx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklaureano989  the compassion and empathy you showed to that gentleman last evening shows everyone the person you are. God Bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YOAdriennekv23 @HighAltShootout @dsisneros23 @ciscokid96 @reneekriv Ugh.... why did you use that picture???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#musicalmondays #cocktails #weho #singoutlouise #thedavidaaron #TheRageWeHo https://t.co/qbKqH5iFVH https://t.co/lerbaIW3w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekerGuerrier @MusiquePlus Bouge de là, la seule émission qui jouait du hip-hop avec rap cité à mon arrivée au Qc. #MusiquePlus]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe in live in a world where ppl are offended over the word BULLSHIT but not the fact that they are kil… https://t.co/u0T8hOqdTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_silverfox1 Truth. And has to be one of the most quotable movies of all time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only does God forgive our sins but he forgets them. That is such an assuring feeling know our sins our forgiven… https://t.co/UoDcErLa4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woolley_geek I know! She almost didn't zipline. But she trusts me still. She did it and I'm so proud. She's a great kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MA LE PERSONE DIETRO LE QUINTE CHE PASSAVANO SUL PALCO MA GENTEEEeeeeeeEEEEE #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicholas read 1,000,000 words and already on to his next book! @APSGardenHills 🏆📚📙📘📗📕 @twilli721 https://t.co/b1vmRQAmBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see your best friend 👋👋  Panic! At The Disco // February 15 // Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/8Uclvn6Vxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve wanted this jersey for so looong! ’ rynesandberg23 Huge Cubs fan it acsnssndjdnn @ East Lansing, Michigan https://t.co/OIzSOCsSj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A woman's body belongs to her, Tho some reps want control and have caused a big stir! But women are watching and kn… https://t.co/dFrUODlinY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markiedotpunk Oh shit hahaha I didn’t see the previous tweet, my bad. Either way, thanks for watching?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nakamachirabu @MaxKennerly @nycsouthpaw What is she doing? I’m afraid to google, enough rage today people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel the need to clear things up right now: @thestarlinernyc is not a boat. 💫 Its just a really cool bar! 🍸It’s n… https://t.co/KCJyzN7hCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix I loved The #umbrellaacadamy Academy and just started #NorthernRescue Rescue episode 2 and I am hooked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te va a costar un par de lágrimas aceptar que no es para ti.  Pero lo vas a lograr, y gracias a eso vas a encontrar… https://t.co/8JqCOg02NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone to give me the whole story on this Khloe K sitch. I’m so behind and I’m too old to be investigating.… https://t.co/pG3VcCO1KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWTThisIsNow @RealSaavedra @ReaganBattalion @GOPLeader @Jim_Jordan @realDonaldTrump Republican Steve King made one… https://t.co/QLPVSHnkP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Or is it a concerted campaign to get her out? I think it might be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALIAQUINTA As long as your solution includes you fighting more, I support it all the way! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teazomboii @decider It was before twitter and Facebook. Y’all are brutal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I'm not pretty,but who are you in the first place to tell me that I'm not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashlon3Jackson this shot was so sweet! I'm so proud of all of you! ❤️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncanGina @krassenstein Spot on, no distractions, just pointed questioning. If no satisfactory answer, she asked… https://t.co/hY3fhfqZpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MovieMarshall That’s a huge feat.. not to shabby!! https://t.co/QPbCUFhEYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bestcaiacount Haha I've seen this in real life!Mama trying to feed her babies! Had to let the rabbit free..]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song has been on replay all day. I now regret moving from La to Alabama @corbynbesson @JonahMarais… https://t.co/w3pinTI5Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp , I’m up and awake . I should be asleep right now ... #nosleep #needablunt #justahit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vozefego2 Didn't say they were. Boats and planes are also used to smuggle drugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your #NUTimberwolves official Spring schedule! ⚽️🐺 #PrideInBattle https://t.co/1ALWRA2dVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s slick out here. Accident on 31 near Tipton. Emergency crews put one person on a stretcher and into an ambulanc… https://t.co/H9rimwLHM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proctors @atProctors &amp; Capital Repertory @theREPny Announces Their New Seasons of Shows 2019-2020… https://t.co/633J5a6bBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate that my lash tech rescheduled my appointment today. Fucked up my whole plans🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico #rogerstone is the conceited boy!  Raspberry!  Are you, roger stone, ready for wearing your black/grey striped prison attire?]]></document></documents></author>