<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:31.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBAM7741 @TrumpsDC @Jamierodr10 I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Qui… https://t.co/gfIL9XdJ9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kent_Wilson And it would be nice if the PP1 didn't look like they were total strangers playing together for the first time even at 5-on-3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great max Miller's clinic in the books. Came away with a lot of new ideas! https://t.co/YwV1qWK2wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_caruso @HeyHeyItsConrad @83Weeks @EBischoff Speaking from a “the business of the business” perspective, that’s hard to argue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give the #TexasTakePodcas a listen: Ep128: Trump vs Beto, and the Secretary of State apologizes https://t.co/2R5Sp2jUXM @TPRNews #txlege]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for some Firehouse! #firehousesubs #subsandwich #dinnertime @ Firehouse Subs Burlington https://t.co/VSh1xDRLmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbruptlyDc @USNavyMomPA @realDonaldTrump Really? Sounds just like liberalism to me.  Liberals are some how able to… https://t.co/1GxVHp1BI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePhightins33 This morning's car clean up (two cars) was only hard because the stuff was heavy and reaching to th… https://t.co/k7r4q8rV0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[#luxurylifestyle #luxury #lux #palmbeach #palmbeachchic #theharris_gainesgroup @ Palm Beach, Florida https://t.co/twZ9Tegj7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so many college mutuals I’ve encountered on twitter that I know would be great friends of mine if we ever m… https://t.co/6GerIdy3dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, of course, that throwback Russian hockey Jersey with #45 on it.  https://t.co/AwhmfO3mJT  😘👌 #chefskiss]]></document><document><![CDATA[How stupid! Fox is not your friend, DNC. They will exploit you. It would be like Hadassah having Hitler sponsor a D… https://t.co/CRSyDwczn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBPipeline He should be their #1 recruit and it's not even close.  The kid has potential out of this world and he… https://t.co/GixczSyUMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome!!! We finally have million dollar robots to jump over boxes awkwardly and put 10 lb boxes away on shelves.… https://t.co/4RKDHqdk4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AintitMarvelous @RooferXX @collectibulldog @Sunleil @KVajpayaee @SafetyGirl100 @awlasky @Kugey @GroErb @BYU13681… https://t.co/Asxbee1asD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a bit (more than a bit) upset that @DCComics and @Marvel are leaving comics stores high and dry... they were th… https://t.co/dn5JZnQij2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AShapir50667530 It’s been a while, but I do remember it as a very sweet affair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @Pajjr2016 Yes for too many reasons to enumerate. #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpLiesEverytimeHeSpeaks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Shots of the Week - Sunrise Skyline Panorama @ChooseChicago @NikonUSA #Weather #News https://t.co/ArezjcTpHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey man, we need a cover photo. Put on this blindfold.  "What's going on? Are you putting lipstick on me?"  "Don'… https://t.co/qNOgMNgKBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Stop Lighting Cash on Fire with TV Ads and Spend More on Digital”  ^^ is the title of every digital strategist’s campaign memoir ^^]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice interview between Peter Brady and @johnltrautmann on Masters Track and Field at https://t.co/VdoXGlka4U https://t.co/yUzVuF1B1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breh. Smh foreal, me and all my dogs could’ve really been eating. But aye, sayless. A 🐎 recognizes a 🐎 Getcha bread… https://t.co/OlVCovdmMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel weird saying important feminist thinkers are hot but google image search Shulamith Firestone or Susan Faludi… https://t.co/FcaRu2vRvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baldheaded1der @kendh Dear god I’d hope that was an end to Duvall and not Culberson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/KzBazTADH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haiti Africa  amaya  to the world  u are the youngest  boss of all bosses  in vloggers  greatness  showing  ppl the… https://t.co/PaWPM5FO0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update. They followed me downstairs to the bathroom to make out with his new boy right outside the bathroom I was in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferSpicer4 @Gnfidz @pukears @mBohlega @BonuraErin @Armstrws Nope but I do not have a lot of experience with Q fever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reinke_farms No, I've had a lot of poo spread this year...even around the house 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink_About_it Now all you need is heated floor tiles in the bathroom! 💯👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WPXI visits the @HyperloopOne test track. They’re the company that’s proposed a Pittsburgh-Columbus-Chicago Hyper… https://t.co/LnuSSRQ1Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePM1221 @NBCSports @Phillies @NBCSPhillies @NBCSPhilly @Dodgers @NBCSChicago @NBCSCubs @Cubs @Bharper3407 Kyle… https://t.co/E9j6gHU1lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ml_roussea @HuffPostEnt No adult asks to keep a 7 year old for a year, you don't ask to sleep with them, you don't… https://t.co/UizPdi71o4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @JakeSherman @CNNPolitics @GStephanopoulos @matthewjdowd @mccaffreyr3 @SenSchumer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foone I worked for a Baby Bell telco in 2001 and we had a DEC-branded WORM jukebox for call accounting records IIR… https://t.co/CLQF1pc7zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to this amazing dancer 😘❤️ https://t.co/aONMX0y3Rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lnick11 @tannerkuyk @TBlaize17 😂😂😂 let’s just be thankful I was there to catch ole buddy running out the back door… https://t.co/sPgikNYQzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atulbutte @chrissyfarr It’s not their data to share, unless you give them permission by not reading the fine print… https://t.co/Bv4XLJyBc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great seeing my colleague @FernandezAndreC at @ILSroyals career day today. Our careers are so different yet… https://t.co/oSSUHn86jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakoutStocks ... $TIS hit target breakout of $1.15, then retreated back....Looking to buy now at $1.10....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find the Seton Hall v Indiana arguments really entertaining.  This adds a new dimension to #RivalryWeek ⚔️🛡🏀🔥 👎🏻👨🏻‍🌾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes please continue to show me pictures of the pet Tipi you bought for your animal and refer to him being a “...our… https://t.co/stGj6z5GCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #InfluentialDBG - Dorothy Butler Gilliam - shares her story of being the first female African American reporter… https://t.co/54MWi2Zetd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Green New Deal is a watermelon,green on the outside,deep red communist on the inside.They want to take your pic… https://t.co/YL11xS2Q8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandypsj @tsouth @SicTransitPHL Makes sense. Suspect it was a function of separate companies, which went broke hau… https://t.co/cQ3O8vtwqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchreckQB12 what’s it like never getting laid? I wouldnt know because I get laid a lot by women who make more money than me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rezgirlron That's 1,000 times stressful! Knowing my luck, I'll catch something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmthofficial - Shadow Moses  the forum  Inglewood Ca 2/13/2019 https://t.co/u8EpECZhxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you don’t need a stick. | 17 Times You Needed More Wonder Woman In Your... #laughter #snicker #grin #cute https://t.co/CNOXq1mDUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi i’m releasing music on soundcloud tonight, please check it out https://t.co/VK4lAJIhsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just my TV or does it look like a lot of people sitting down?? #WreckEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Storme @buzzbrainard @MCSiriusXM @TommySiriusXM after baby Christening just got to Jeannes Uncle’s house in the Ha… https://t.co/nq3EJbS5mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science teachers... this workshop is part of @kscorn curriculum that just won a national award! Seriously consider… https://t.co/Nj37l686xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Absolutely a Power move by President Trump  !!!  Thank God !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/4mtg1mq5KH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a lovely time we had! Although...... After midnight it seemed like the crowd got younger and drunker and bolde… https://t.co/3OzeL4Mzdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going Bowling for my birthday on Tuesday at 8:30PM at AMF Savannah Lanes on the Southside. Pull up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSCapitalLLC @RampCapitalLLC Well, the Reaper shows the number of times Ramp said something outlandish about the m… https://t.co/Fxb3AKvYIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades Senadora @LillyTellez hoy más que nunca se ocupan personas firmes y dignas frente al Lobby Abortista   #SiaLaVida]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously foggy... @ Thomas Crossroads, Georgia https://t.co/MGSBaV4tTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[9450-9430 W Olympic Blvd 9450-9430 W Olympic Blvd, Beverly Hills, CA 90212 https://t.co/NoDvqxOpQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Servers make $2.13 hourly cooks make $12 hourly, and corporate offices never want you to give people 40 hours becau… https://t.co/bHuoDMbRlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARRESTED— The man accused of killing my cousin’s stepdaughter in Aurora, CO has been captured in Mexico and is now… https://t.co/3HCY81Iewy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeamusHughes Legal gun owners are the real threat to America #DOMESTICTERROIST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV please tell me your doing the @DukeMBB @UNC_Basketball game tonight???? #UNCvsDUKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_jotajota @lamambanegra17 Yo sé quién fue jejejeje tiene un negocio de café,  ahi para que le compres y financíes su whitexicanismo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melt_Dem So probably Corda.  **BUT** the "right" answer is: in 5-10 years all real Blockchain (yes, also enterpris… https://t.co/eYBbbzuqpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[SELLING  3x 5/12 Chicago Sec 331 Row 5 Seats 1-3  Original price will transfer via ticket master  Venmo or Paypal… https://t.co/ku6NAs3GLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m no engineer but wouldn’t a large brush that the busses could drive through be more efficient?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@channingj @respect_4 @RubinReport @JCBBK4 They point to a man of poor character, a liar, as proof of Trump's racis… https://t.co/rdHQ7cL46O]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Duke wins without Zion the media will portray it like Duke beat the 97-98 bulls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cabreja_adriana @TMobileLatino @JBALVIN Y entonces porque siempre invitan a artistas de mis tiempos sabes por qué… https://t.co/TApUdygIFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin No not really he's got the ball rolling on a few items all at the same time plus a 20 billion dollar contract from Boing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious what my network thinks... Bitcoin price exactly 5 years from today.... #btc 🔮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM @drafthouse Dude, you host parties.  I AM the party. https://t.co/ixPtORU4iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exchange Club Pancake breakfast going on right now at BGHS - all you can eat! @BGSchools @JeffDeverBgcs @BGHS_AD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MavsManiaac84 @AOC @RashidaTlaib @cthagod this has to be donkey of the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_White Hey...Good Morning! Thanks for sharing. Prayers you, your @TheRealPWM @ndccOrlando team and families h… https://t.co/am7btx8spW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I speak with businesses and business leaders all the time about using Omni channel performance based advertising to… https://t.co/cJAGtVPHGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muere 'El Llanero Solitito'; símbolo de la cultura y el activismo https://t.co/m4OAm6WiLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BStupich @CardinalBCupich He didn’t say he was president of the Usccb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMargolin @johncusack @KamalaHarris @SenBooker @amyklobuchar Hard to support Harris given her history as a pro… https://t.co/FIuu43jg4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccs_anna Toda mi familia está en Maracaibo y tengo poco tiempo que salí para poder mantenerla, porque los socialis… https://t.co/MP7CEuESsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Why is it continuing to be a problem? You keep saying it’s not a national emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They knew dat tho!! I’ll be Hype when y’all boys put it all together for a full season wit no Slips Ups]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually wait for @EamonJavers to pronounce it but I’ll go ahead and take the honors today: Weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allaboutboxing Do it. I smashed a printer last year. Got me a new printer. No problems printing ever since...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my_chroniclife @DianneandDaisy @lisastark351 This incredible work ethic from generations of immigrants is how Amer… https://t.co/T6GZNvBCS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrookedIntriago Fuck that, I'm putting my shit out there right now!!, oh, we were talkin' about music!!!???? https://t.co/YzTDrbUvqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our guys are great men.  Very proud of you all and a very nice gesture @CoreyDavisJr_ @strailer77 @UHCougarMBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stormy_loves_u @lattescafe But I think your beauty and inspiration for others is so much closer to perfect than mo… https://t.co/o55lx1sS4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawrencedonegan @NoLayingUp @dougferguson405 I take back my "oh" because you were very personally rude to me. Good… https://t.co/tqzrdh49eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record, I am hoping they make it back to playoffs. Even if it’s an early round exit again. You learn a lot… https://t.co/Ydonxt9Fpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[70 Years of #HumanRights in #GlobalHealth: Drawing on a Contentious Past to Secure a Hopeful Future In @TheLancet… https://t.co/Q2rAjlKzmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wemakemovies @WeMakeMovies @MsThiNguyen gets feedback on #MyFriendJesus @ms_sapnagandhi moderates https://t.co/yVNnuMkrvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend cares too much about his dam car mileage, it gives me anxiety..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always encouraging when you get a text announcing that local police are enforcing a tow ban due to snow. #wiwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Monday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/fQVCAhclz3]]></document></documents></author>