<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Pretty happy with my progress in the gym!! Huge shoutouts to @mariodevon for keeping me in check, powerthrupain for… https://t.co/JqzDfMAStv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isnt there hot wind? "Its currently 3°, due to current wind conditions it feels like 25°." We need that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneunderscore__ Or even confronted YouTube about why they made a press release saying the content being reported,… https://t.co/1oMY4Kl8Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseBWatters Mr. President: These 4 or 5 Socialist, muslim, radial freshman, Congress Women, are trying to destro… https://t.co/evdIORcohg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC TRUMP HELPED CREATE THIS IMMIGRATION INFLUX OF HUMANITY FLEEING GANGS BECAUSE THAT FAT ASS IN HIS DUMPY WHIT… https://t.co/8QzgzEKwnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MepsieM Thanks brother, that means alot to hear and am glad you enjoyt reading my blabberings, lol. I wouldn't kno… https://t.co/dhp3iPbh1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovWhitmer Hi Governor...my thoughts on your road repair problem..Instead of a .45 gas tax, why not a 2% raise in… https://t.co/XWw0CcwlEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support Would have appreciated you taking a look months ago when I emailed you about it, but I'll send you a DM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeirony @marcinkulis @WabKinew @AOC And for the record the two-party system isn’t working but most of you were t… https://t.co/t16AY66q6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ptmurf1016 @SamuelP84463985 @AOC No but the physical location and infrastructure can be used in other ways to gene… https://t.co/QPepRXMzwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fulani herdsmen resume killing of innocent Nigerians; human being are nothing to these terrorists, You have not see… https://t.co/Zr5dNuf7BT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A kid found my Instagram today and he told me I was hot. And like I know I do look good on IG, but point is I’m private now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out and having a blast with my AA....LOVE YA @ Buffalo Wild Wings https://t.co/YZns5faxwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOUT OUT to all women around the 🌎 Keep kicking ass!#HappyInternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@20committee American justice moves slowly, like an iceberg, but boy it's an unstoppable b*tch when it finally lands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole51223772 @TimMcKenna130 @GregoryMetzler5 @Leeshabelle @DRIguy2017 @kyleraid @Russell16308803 @HRAngieV… https://t.co/ItNdBdIpoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gruntjeeper @Melissa03807728 @Pro_Dextre @attorneygsb @iambergie @DonaldJTrumpJr Trump is a traitor. This game is fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Android next time you do update the Gboard app could you please expand the spell check to scan the whole messa… https://t.co/c8hpqqsvnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianKru @tonyjenson @NateSilver538 And fails to keep his promises?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue planet 2 is probably the worst thing to happen to my social life🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics The Isis sympathizer should shut her pie hole her mental illness is showing https://t.co/yUUTPYx4he]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Bohr @LDNews @ACAthleticDept @NL_Wrestling_ @colin_leonard12 @CcfalconW Dave please add @DutchmenWrestl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #Windsor today to talk about #ClimateChange and the #OnPoli economy while we #MarchAcrossOntario - with Hon.… https://t.co/xgJj1RJG8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is making me lasagne &amp; I am sitting on the floor with the dog .... #heaven #diningaround https://t.co/n1CGRxAiUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fearlessleader4 @itjhsbands @ASD4dsmogor What’s funny if I was just going to post the same album.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyBeltTX We also got a Better Defense with Coaches!  We got a 2 time Rushing Title Winner @EzekielElliott.  We… https://t.co/aCWZoaky6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Día del Amollll, @angelri60797074!!! Espero te hayan tratado bien, pana... sip... https://t.co/cmfqyPkx0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god it’s about to be Spring Break this weather is so brutal https://t.co/nxdFNK7KrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #WakeForest on Rogers Rd &amp; Granite Falls Blvd near Main St #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivingInAJar @big_john819 Gonna steal and use in my own tweet when the timing is perfect. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[NUESTRO SISTEMA JUDICIAL: CUALIDADES Y DEFECTOS https://t.co/NU0eJWBihm  Invitados: Lic. Cuitláhuac Castro y Lic. N… https://t.co/ISSJdZAdBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo vine por una hamburguesa jaja ! en Five Guys https://t.co/Vy6gOCLE2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[i totally appear to be the only one who plays pokemon on my nintendo 3ds at the gym. What gives??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus, with CNN hosting the debates, their favored candidate will get the questions in advance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage @LBSymphony #concert #piano #quiet @ Long Beach Terrace Theater https://t.co/egbi3dlPB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump THAT'S GREAT GIVE BACK OUR GOVERMENT MONEY... AND WE WILL PROTECT OUR SELVES... SO THELL BE MORE M… https://t.co/9UtZatcjq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleD35 Multiple ones actually iirc. Black Panther, Luke Cage. The latter in an interracial relationship.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChanningWINK @Twins @SunHarvest_ You look so fucking how in those clothes.  🥰😍😘😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Flint is a great example of why keeping business  is good.   Not everyone can work for the government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Hogmerica! Christmas In February - OPENING DAY! WPS! https://t.co/yeWz9P7xYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexcess2 @severestudios @ScottPeakeWX Climate is constantly changing. How about a little respect for those who are… https://t.co/gHuaCv8DwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedDirt, #Roots, #Americana  It's a vast underexplored world of great storytelling and song Dig @sarahshook… https://t.co/U8LZWNC7TG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Nothing beats capitalist national standardization for cost and service efficiency. https://t.co/CpLPXCqxeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know the cases when people keep their guns and kill; we don’t know and can’t know the cases that didn’t happen b… https://t.co/41jlHjQmQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The1J1 is going to be ALL over the field next year. Pumped to have you with us man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejasonhopkins @DailyCaller Obama declared 12 worthless National Emergencies and not one grunt out of these nasty… https://t.co/EHM9l6XTW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Chris Pratt, and now Eric Porterfirld. Why are all of the best looking men in Hollywood homophobic?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furman goes down to UNCG in the SoCon semis.They were on my board all year but unfortunately have no path to an at… https://t.co/XNvvkwi9UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @CDPUG member asked me if I knew what the @PlayhouseSquare Broadway shows were for next season, so I showed her 👉… https://t.co/on0cWRz72O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I imagine a world where we all simply just exist as we are, in infinite variations, all as celebrated and enjoyed a… https://t.co/CmO3N3IXS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens if the weather changes and gets worst earlier around 1pm or 2pm before school gets out ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to call my mom real quick cause a bitch ain’t know wtf I was doing in the kitchen lmao 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Vuolo We treasured getting to know these folks during our time in LaGrange, WY where they lived]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day off-ing my way... Stop 1. Alpine: Nelson IPA.  . . . #cycling #cyclinglife #rideomata #beer #connoisseursclub… https://t.co/sMRRdqadsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeyMick @BarstoolBigCat Mu grandpa had a pear tree. Getting them fresh off the tree was delicious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reddsaidit If only there was some sort of internet movie database that told us who was in every movie or show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atlanticPDX How is like, every opinion wrong? Also there aren’t rye chips in trail mix, you’re thinking of Guardinos (sp?).]]></document><document><![CDATA[imnotabouncer on point backstage @ Bethesda Blues &amp; Jazz Supper Club https://t.co/xTz06ygrfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Original_Gio @samesfandiari Lol they were 2 mins away from winning a ring with Moss and Welker and won 2 with Gron… https://t.co/TV6i9Dz4tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealmutoMVP2019 Don’t you know that this is all a part of the brilliant Padres front office scheme to throw us off.....lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything better than late night drinks with good tunes on the Bose? Sure isn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tschwing32 @SteveFields18 @joeybbennett @GCDWPruett Oh yeah, maybe so. I can tell you that there won’t be a need f… https://t.co/KsvzkEho6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I Don't Actively Invest On Public Markets: I do not actively trade any stocks or bonds on the public markets. I… https://t.co/ij5MUHBtjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carla_Pereira2 At ten I just figure Ronaldo is on tv https://t.co/5L8TQ20SV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoisalexjacob @Jeopardy Somehow a 4th podium shows up and it’s @IBMWatson and he crushes the competition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please stop reporting stories until we have the facts https://t.co/DvZfWDBLTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Double Double vs Garner Magnet by Carisma Lynn on @hudl https://t.co/Lee17eulnV #hudl @mchsbball… https://t.co/PdW4SvaL90]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Jackal_Tenebris Happy late birthday, hope you had a fire ass day brother 🥳🍻‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgressNowNM @NMAlliance4Life Wow, you guys are racist bigots! Anyone who doesn’t support abortion is a “white su… https://t.co/O8wvXH50hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frank Rossi, PhD and Tom Cook #Legendsinturfgrass https://t.co/QFQUeZmZiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenGranholm @GeorgetownICAP @neal_katyal @mamoonha @stewart @arikbenz @jgeltzer OH GEE JUST ANOTHER LIST I`M NOT ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE!!!! @RAlvarezclary I know you’ll be close to the due date for lil baby AC but I NEED this fanny pack!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My in-laws are dope. How did I get so lucky? #hashtagblessed @ Marcel https://t.co/YL22S1Ohux]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the reading of the Law yesterday at @missionopc - Deut 10:18-19 "[God] executes justice for the fatherless and… https://t.co/4MbfUbeTeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kotd AJ #Retro V #Black/Metallic #NikeAir #Retro5s #sneakerfiles #sneakerfiend #sneakerhead #jordandepot… https://t.co/Ttp4DKSyGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally spent the night last night and tonight u got 2 different boys over cool cool :)))))))]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE @ChicagoDemons ARE HOLDING TRYOUTS FOR ANY GIRL IN THE 9-12 GRADE INTERESTED IN PLAYING FOR OUR HIGH SCHOOL GIR… https://t.co/MiADwpXVeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Why do you take your suit coat off at a hearing on the hill?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LogTechEric @zackkanter I’m more impressed with the other Democrats, so it’s not a Trump comparison for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the last @donlemon visit to @SaintAnselm. Look forward to hearing five of my favorite words: “Live from Saint… https://t.co/90oYqXRuQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letmewhisper Yeah, go on a show where 1 guy dates 25 women! How is this ok? And no, I’ll be sane you’re not going… https://t.co/sYtl3BncTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am always bragging about my job and that’s cause I love what I do. I am so excited to watch Belleville East Lance… https://t.co/gFhGt2SjPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulitawilhelm @JoshJeanB In 2019 we’re unapologetically out here trying to be the very best, like no one ever was… https://t.co/DXxN42bLCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Malkin's speech today was brilliant and spot on👏. At some point the gloves have to come off and the niceti… https://t.co/4l61hBOIQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[El mejor presidente en los ultimos 40 años. #AMLOnoEstasSoloMexicoContigo  #amloelpuebloterespalda… https://t.co/WIuZzQ4JIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swap Toews with the better JT who Donns the same number. And we all know who he is. (Hint: he recently passed Gordi… https://t.co/asQITHV4dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju Come on man. Context. President has to have security. USSS paid rent to Biden when they were on his land. This is not unusual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The universities have been brainwashing kids for 30 years these kids have socialist leanings and are the Marchers a… https://t.co/q5FcxQL80t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredOstu @Burt1Lafleur @LaurenUnderwood Confiscating guns from PEOPLE LIKE THE AURORA SHOOTER! His foid was revoke… https://t.co/hBd63xv8tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The off-road Mercedes that became an urban status symbol has gotten a complete makeover! Can you tell? No? That's t… https://t.co/w1vKRqFIo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masuda_matt2 @oliviaanc Same here, that's why we need some prank vlogs🤡.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbucktales u can send ur kanto pokemon go transfers to the game instead of transferring them into the abyss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn kousin,  its krazi how you was just in my car a hour before you died.  And you ain't tell me bout no beef with… https://t.co/XslOs58zbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Los Rieles San Nicolás https://t.co/P4nDEEwILb]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Saturday, WE VOLUNTEER!!! On the way to the ALS walk in downtown St.Petersburg with my slim+ in hand, so excited… https://t.co/AwMMylpfyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this guy didn’t think I knew what a Orchid was and I was like yes of course they last forever if you take care o… https://t.co/67QpkBBBLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impcapital If they made the service free I wonder how well it would compete with Uber and Lyft?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosferatusaint @CarnivoreCrypto @Cynwel73 @dojoman1959 @hargrump @Veganella_ @jadeo09 @GodZo0 @SBakerMD… https://t.co/xesBkBtJR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @USMC 2/ Studies have been done...this is Expected behavior by outnumbered Prison Guards who have no prot… https://t.co/kQdBDlAEg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh summer bonfires how I miss thee. - Drinking a Bonfire Summer Stout by @mobcraftbeer at @mobcraftbeer  — https://t.co/bnbwQfOzQH]]></document></documents></author>