<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@titanium_neb1 over @Premier_VB Black in second 25-12. @nebhsvolleyball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima be that wife up at 2a dancing in the kitchen in my partners t shirt making cookies or something 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sa_Ni_Bo @bobbybonesshow Exactly! 😂😂😂 I’m gonna go ahead and assume it’s a myth! The carrot thing blew my mind! I’… https://t.co/oOhcNp71lH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your administration is slow walking thousands of asylum seekers who want to come into the USA.  Ne… https://t.co/h2YpAxydy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at North Garden at McNeely Conservatory https://t.co/hG7jwidx6v https://t.co/iDV76t31gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Mi Amor !!! @iamerikestrada  ❤️💯✌️🔥😉😘 @ Maryland https://t.co/wrqI2f5GqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicbygemeaux @_shananon This is me now 😭😭 but Uranus in Taurus is changing us forcefully 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inertiauk @FranzHistory @Franz_Ferdinand I didn’t even notice that, I’m way to focused on Alex’s gorgeousness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lc1and1 I had spinal lymphoma surgery. They cut my back open 11 inches to get into the spinal cava ties to get the… https://t.co/rfn7HiQPR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meggangreen Well, who knows if the writers would do it. But the thought made me blush!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trinity HS Basketball Sweet 16 Presser vs Ashland Blazer https://t.co/gaVPvNKpxD via @kysportstv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I want on TV before more startup football -  * Lacrosse * Women's hockey  * More softball * Handball * Crash… https://t.co/JLsl6v43ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Power106LA At first I thought "cute face. cute hair" then found out he was arrested for child abuse.  https://t.co/juLfIFOqNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does seem to care about the law but the outcome.   https://t.co/9W3opMA70T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxRickyC That’s funny.  My dog used to love Doritos and vanilla wafers.  But funyons?  I never tried.  🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out it’s #loveyourpetday2019 today - terribly missing our little guy Bentley that we lost in November 😢… https://t.co/7kDx3BYJOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @sxdoc @gatewaypundit Drop out of the Olympics! Let all Transgenders go at it!!! See how many show… https://t.co/ozXxZWJaFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flakey @dr_pete @ddale8 We all hear it. Who's gonna act on it? Certainly not the complicit GOP. Can't get rid of h… https://t.co/C9RkLi9LBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferFox13 Maybe not PLN per se but definitely “how do you work on developing as a teacher and a professional?”… https://t.co/kY8F0p3h3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Jane Rathburn (1922-1999) would bake up to 50 dozen "brownies" a day to bring to San Francisco hospitals to di… https://t.co/7uHKEhUb3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SterlingKBrown @skelechiwatson @NBCThisisUs Love you and Susan . Team Randal and Beth . So excited for show tonigh… https://t.co/30JtRXOMzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner is served... #crockpot #healthy #dinnertime #monday https://t.co/1VLtBqtgtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be another great morning of swimming for the Concord Swim Club!!! Go Mya Lynn and Poseidon Grey Kiddos!!!… https://t.co/bHXQivZrsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver Poor soul probably had sleep apnea and needed the C pap machine. What a waste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get into this cut ladies ! 😍  Closure quick weave done by yours truly!   #closuresewin #quickweaves… https://t.co/JHoF2ezLhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arguably the best one-two punch in the country 👊  Virginia Tech is the only team in the nation with two pitchers wh… https://t.co/Gaj2L0hAhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw commercial for Jimmy Dean breakfast sandwiches made with egg buns. I just happen to have a mini cast-iron. Br… https://t.co/mwAzfblvDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @POTUS I will not support you. Congress has failed at their job  Build the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skully_Westend Then you dress like this my dude. Don’t talk. You look like you fuck white bitches for a living how… https://t.co/QV1mY6YgeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland She chose the Navy for its linguist program. Kent had a passion for languages from a young age, even d… https://t.co/mLjh0DmKy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Carson is an amazing person🇺🇸❤️🇺🇸❤️  also, thank you for working with our public housing system.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I could go back in time. I’d go back and change everything so i woulda never met ya 😒😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you idea focused or answer focused??  @mfannie #WSMI https://t.co/efyQckm4b4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimesent That is horrific experience for a young boy. My son is 21. Sexually assisted at 7. Much less by someone… https://t.co/Jafle3r03X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flywithkamala Sharrod Brown isn't running, at least that is what I thought I heard this afternoon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beijingcoma @OTWTheater @ButlerEagle I forgot to tag you. Thank you so much for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherVoorhees @BreitbartNews Oh no. There r NO drugs coming across the border, just ask Nancy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_granata @kulsgrace @justinsplanet42 @Bizzlex8 @MichelleCaissi1 @296_cool @loveujustinjb5 @BhanuRajput33… https://t.co/4T6wqML1Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me the sparkle! This #DiamondNecklace from @kayjewelers is perfect for #ValentinesDay. https://t.co/6yQSgFKyhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I get sad I never got an official photo with @HillaryClinton. But  the memories keep coming of folx I got… https://t.co/whPCf0gG8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the rest of the country is getting smacked by snow, I’ll be enjoying the beach breeze🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAThrizzle @JackPosobiec @w_terrence He tagged them in one message, I believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit really changed when I decided to simply not allow myself to be bothered. #UnbotheredAF #OnAMission]]></document><document><![CDATA[@experianhelp_us How can ANYONE TRUST Experian with their credit security when your wacked out phone system has cra… https://t.co/tYNyxYSBV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the 6yo girl in the Dress Like a Hoya contest hit her bucket on her first shot! #HoyaSaxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for  @ambermilamlee to be on the cover of Jetset Magazine https://t.co/vo1vxt2ChU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @hunterpence is the kind of person you would want to be friends with. He seems like such a cool dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t care who u are, when it comes to the people I LOVE, I WILL hurt your feelings period]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @geekhard #stan @MaryBrowns Eating #tatersntaters FANtastic Friday! @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/OxrCCB6Zjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[How racist, bigoted, homophobic &amp; politically biased of the Chi police.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Photos: @DierksBentley at the TaxSlayer Center https://t.co/Dr1a8uNBIv via @dispatch_argus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denisehernand18 @Betzizzzle It’s not me and not Denise?? What’s going on here??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @443777 @jonz970 @nancyleeca @TraciIrving1 @QmagaMike @Mary251177 @Cheetarah69 @madawson74 @mark_covfefe… https://t.co/kpnWKxRBpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoveYourPetDay with my ball python &amp; my jack russell! https://t.co/EYIwLaKN1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bri_lynnx3 Ooo girl I cant stand high school ass drama from a grown ass women]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillyosul @RepSwalwell You must not follow the news very astutely. Millions of us are well aware of the ongoing wo… https://t.co/8buv6H8DxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As many solo Valentines I’ve had you would think I’ll be used to it.... fts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecutor Carol Siemon would not explain why, even in general terms, a first-degree sex assault case would be plea… https://t.co/ZSi2unLXdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SapphoPSJ @krassenstein But, dark black or medium brown black skin look gorgeous in any colour clothes. Especially… https://t.co/MmNReIzPsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw Where have you been since the #CrimeFamily #ClownCar blazed into the campaign trail in 2016? Fucking asle… https://t.co/g4O1PiApyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCSDmbb @CoachEricOlen @NCAA @goccaa @NCAADII @Division2Hoops Good luck Tritons!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyWetWet You tweeted this while you were working. IM TELLING HUNTER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about @abantemarketing at the LNK. @LincolnChamber Virtual C https://t.co/Saet5hXTKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sally__Thorne Shut up I read this book 2 weeks ago in 2 days and this is after I reread The Hating Game. I love bo… https://t.co/JnaRHj7Z03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eunicerea2 @marklevinshow I read an article about it.  She married her brother to commit immigration fraud.  She d… https://t.co/ACRsm5jwEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from Argyle! #brighterJax on a beautiful morning https://t.co/1akem2i2b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida regala los mejores momentos a quienes regalamos las mejores sonrisas. million_dress_cln  cl.makeupstudio… https://t.co/Wy1ylmOSyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bowie_joe Hey Joe, I hope you’re enjoying the Philippines. I’m trying to reach you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might not be a sexy #HenryCavill photo, but this totally melts my heart! Look at that smile! Look how good he is… https://t.co/aoLIsh3qbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/qsipyNGGYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrcrom1 @Merita_MK @owillis Ok, agreed.  These groups know how to navigate the system to be most helpful to people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaytonEWilliams @MoreLightPresby @wjkbooks Yaaassss!!!!!! This is amazing @LaytonEWilliams!!! Congrats! https://t.co/0W7Pa9qXd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alemgto @tunamex @politicomx @OphCourse @M_OlgaSCordero @JaimeRdzNL @CongresoNL @Jacquie_LHoist @kdartigues… https://t.co/rFp994YHnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some “friends” will take a knife out YOUR back and stab you with it...stay woke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgandthesoul @officialchevel That happens to me too 😂. Or when I’m tired @sgandthesoul @officialchevel]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you will notice - I’m the calm one of this group!  That’s saying something!  #daythreeofthehostagesituation #nsm… https://t.co/SPRgRyoZXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hasta el más Dark vio el homenaje que le hicieron a Daddy en los premios no me vengan con cosas, yo se que lo viero… https://t.co/9Egp1MYRMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @browndwbrown1 One of my great friends was a Muslim! I have lost her to Cancer. Finest human being… https://t.co/fgqTgQHPha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna fuck around and get my masters to spite my enemies and work at Planned Parenthood as an NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever try so hard to not laugh that it makes you wanna puke cuz same]]></document><document><![CDATA[why am I scared to go blonde but I could dye my hair blue today no issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would the market cap of YouTube be today if it was a standalone co?  AWS? (Easier because you get #s, though g… https://t.co/Q1h9hTYJLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows you sir are a stand up guy!  Was very proud of what you said and how you conducted yourself at Cohe… https://t.co/XlNAyWigAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIpatriotIZ @PhxGOP @KevinMKruse @BernardFarquart Take off your tin foil hat,  your tiny brain is overheating. #SHAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fast and Furious conviction: victim's family makes case for "The Wall" https://t.co/dhj58xJOc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home from my second job. Oh boii.... my body’s okay but my brain is exhausted as shit. 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonMartinCTV @AndrewScheer And while I m so distressed with my Liberals at the moment I would never vote for the C… https://t.co/mtuwNCTFkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The reason we do what we do is to make sure every child can be his or her best self”. Kenneth Ginsburg #SAHM19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas is hands down the very best  in college basketball commentary - can he just announce every game please… https://t.co/P0PUaa7ifA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holmes_middle #collaborativeart #bulldogartists #hmsproud Working on these interactive Louise Nevelson inspired sc… https://t.co/1UEroTBOFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧘🏼‍♀️🧘‍♂️🧘🏼‍♀️ Y O G A It’s so much more than poses (asana)! It’s our codes of conduct:  our ways of being + intera… https://t.co/frSqM3sTMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For the OT writers, it was virtually inconceivable that anything could happen independently of God’s will and work… https://t.co/6naw8MiWIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trouble was, I had been inadequate all along, I simply hadn’t thought about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aiken's Jakada Stone with two straight buckets and we now have had 10 lead changes. Falcons lead 43-42 with 2:08 le… https://t.co/nasdgTQNuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vacation needs to happen in my near future. Just me &amp; my man, a beach, and some cold drinks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Holmes is interesting and all, but keep your eyes on #2 here. Launches on Monday! @theskimm https://t.co/0qx5ZnB5HK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien It is an addiction which will only get better with access to treatment. We don't really offer that t… https://t.co/GujxdyTQ2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que me refiero cuando digo que tengo un vacío en el alma https://t.co/jJ4uSfZBtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although it was a short trip, but I had so much fun and much needed relaxation in the wintery weather in southern C… https://t.co/t5V6wF8giM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurameme @Apple @AppleSupport Sent. I finally got in touch with the third party company and there’s a note that i… https://t.co/xOyqUHhI17]]></document></documents></author>