<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ZTentertainment @whitneywrightx @IsiahMaxwell @seanmichaels42 @RobPiperXXX @yearofthericky #THESINSOFLA 🤘😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21BMJ I think the 10 teams that lost to the OSU should disband their programs. Wow BMJ wasn’t there a better game… https://t.co/6wmeppl0Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Greens will be going to the Kent City Council meeting on February 20th if you would like to join in to argue ag… https://t.co/aBUYg3Kd32]]></document><document><![CDATA[The types of nights I have continuously change for peculiar reasons. 😗💨💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone said “Bari it seems easy for you to change now, back then to take the leap was difficult for you”  I didn’t… https://t.co/EejHq3ooKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @Garr_ @penguins https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/hZEJ0f6Zg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photovoltaics are just getting more efficient and the cost getting better. Definitely. California's solar energy pu… https://t.co/w9EXzZXN6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Source material for history buffs looking to compare and argue with me: https://t.co/Vxnjz9aKMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ser feliz no quiere decir necesariamente estar disfrutando, sino vivir la serenidad que me da saber que estoy en e… https://t.co/FnxxSQZxmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGeiser @NFLonFOX I was there with my pa cuz! 2nd happiest day of my life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[About time these people are not special well they are but not the way you think that type of shit will bring this c… https://t.co/bclGEPofzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that doesn’t warrant a flagrant, I don’t know what is. Akenten could get a flagrant from two separate incidents on the same play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCAntifa @jaredlholt That Shapiro kid pisses your children off doesn't he.???  Almost as much as my Son Milo .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my room for some water and when I came back Luna passed gas and it is the most appalling smell I’ve ever inh… https://t.co/6tOTyiMoiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathormot @VFL2013 I had not heard she was one of the Republican Senators voting against. Her I can possibly under… https://t.co/Vf2WiFOEtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oh_Watup @SamsungMobileUS I need to look up these features. But the fact that it costs more than my damn gaming co… https://t.co/BiHZRdKpQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching @KristenAguirre all day at the @WorldDenver International Women’s Day event, she might just be my ne… https://t.co/iJtTOTweex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Disney fun at Magic Kingdom yesterday with some good friends from Birmingham @KimLawNoles https://t.co/U0fNn0LPSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buddy Boeheim keeps proving coach’s sons have an extra gear over every other player]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceMercsPro Keep those cheeks loose and just let it all out man you’ll feel better in no time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Allen is the dude who barley does any work in the group project but still gets an A.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoopStats I wished 1210 AM would be all sports and carry the Phillies games in addition to 94 WIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot damn, those crutches shots were legit! Go ahead with your bad self, @BeckyLynchWWE! #WWE #WWEChamber #TheMan https://t.co/Jf7Lc0DFOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most beautiful sunsets I’ve ever seen... Tampa Bay in Florida!  #ShotOniPhone https://t.co/IvGsUrV8Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@305miami6924 Yeessss multiple orgasm's in fact 😮 happy Valentine's day beautiful sexy lady enjoy from John in Manh… https://t.co/8dUMzmsxg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working class people being upset about a rise in the minimum wage shows how broken our system is. Why are you upset… https://t.co/tNikMDf9Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urdadssidepiece https://t.co/VE8ZHZ7EMy is a great search engine for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taker is back at #3 with his @WrestleMania 20 entrance #WWETop20LightsOutMoments]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said something which could be easily misconstrued as antisemetic. She apologized for the bad tweet (as she shou… https://t.co/MzlORQoe3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onlyyoontv @CNBCi @realDonaldTrump Didn’t the US fight a war against the COMMIES in Vietnam Nam. I seem to remembe… https://t.co/34DD3PJffH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait.....what?   Pentagon reviewing @elonmusk security clearance!  https://t.co/fRe2PmtcGE Hey Mom @mayemusk #Pravdah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeRusTerr @AOC Yes I would. In this case, it’s a no-brainer.  The far left, is more totalitarian then they want to admit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#40ballsundays @ #dolce #sundynight #drinks🍹 #bottles #vip #birthdaypartys #sections #goodvibesonly #weekendvibes… https://t.co/EONvdEff9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[When can I see @Tone_Troy here @Terminal5NYC ??? https://t.co/QbCXubgxi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commitment to indigenous languages powered by AI @janephilpott @TBS_Canada #AIDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShortPants12 @________AGA @pretti_brownn88 @JStoutmyre @LorenzoB76 @SarahJSG @MassRoots Apologize to those poor se… https://t.co/DLtGgG14i3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who bid on items tonight for the @Timberwolves broadcast auction.  Over $45k was raised for the… https://t.co/KUNfm5hI0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson i feel like my brain is abstracting better.  This massive stress has come of of me.  People often la… https://t.co/cwFgke8k5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Patriots have come out firing in this second half. They have a 41-37 lead with 13:28 left in regulation. #NDpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇸🇪👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN! Sweetheart!💝 Miss Anna Nystrom! annanystrom The White RACE Swedish BLONDES👑🇸🇪 Women Are The… https://t.co/Tkhvm6fwg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother goes through 3 times the amount of toilet paper I do. When i questioned her as to why this occurs she sim… https://t.co/Wgso1324gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjabrams @starwars @Twitter @Rey_Sistance @JohnBoyega @oscarisaacposts @JoinTheForce @SW_Celebration @SW_Insider e… https://t.co/0GGVY3SzVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[SXSW let’s live!! No rules  #sxsw2019 #rollinginstyle officialdannytrejo @ Downtown Austin, Texas https://t.co/vh8mB5DY2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @PageSix That's right turn and run you crook you got your 15 mins of racist talk. Wait for the next staged attack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBoulayJDM Il était déjà pas en forme à la pesée c’était écrit dans le ciel qu’ il allait en mangez une]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost there...'63 Lincoln Continental convertible.  #Lincoln #continental #convertible #workflow #work https://t.co/2ESjeWlDNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniAlvarez_16 @victorvmesa Lo que hace falta es que batee .. los comentarios DESPUÉS QUE juegue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Remember it was the Democrats that fought to keep slavery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hear anyone say “ fast lane” I automatically yell “baby”. Thanks @WrestleTalk_TV @OliDavis @ThisisLukeOwen @ElFakidor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReallyAwakenNow @Kirk405 @CillizzaCNN This just might be one tiny little problem here I’d say. https://t.co/OSGBWWgxNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NardaGraham @FastCompany Lol. There's a general tendency in Europe and North America to project that view onto dev… https://t.co/Nh1w8bPfma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Fahrenthold @MotherJones @realDonaldTrump @FBI @Trump So BIG... HE is eating the little alligators Like… https://t.co/weHFCi0R89]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try a day of not pissing anyone off, then god gets back at me with the weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuggetsBearsSox @TruuuuuIsMyQB Debatable? Its not even close. 3 rings and fmvp and was a way better defender by far than harden.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be the point in the sci fi movie where the kid realizes his dad has been replaced by an alien impostor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business @AOC Hmm Govt rep with NO say doesn't rule out....thanks Bloomberg , BTW I  dont rule it out either #Clickbait]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you.... from an American that has traveled in your country and been impressed with it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This team has mike reily, Jordie Benn and Brent kulak in there lineup on most nights , What more can we except from this team ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmeinke Finally, 7 Lions rooks from that year--including UDFA Cornelius Lucas--played at least 4 NFL seasons in th… https://t.co/U7cg2JK3x4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoopinsider Your 2019 bi-district champion Pflugerville Connally Cougars! https://t.co/1no7Ada9Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manzie Wilson bucket cuts Gonzaga lead to 57-55 with 7.9 to go. Timeout, Cadets. #DMVhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hero . . . #ASTROBOY #japan #love #anime #superhero #manga #japon en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/OqEhqF1qD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @Carolchapman192 Pence has always been a crook and a fraud racist bigot lying piece of shit just as… https://t.co/p9E4jsgP6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, fuck it. Here's some failed attempts from me trying to do squats, while holding a kettle bell, while balancin… https://t.co/TccJ2jnRb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast Guy takes his pet duck to movie theater that doesn't allow pets. Hides duck in his pants, sits next to… https://t.co/wFObeJA6jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dij_plz Fasho man. Maybe in a few months. I'm still stepping and dropping fat though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends They finally figured out you're a #DUMMY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidharsanyi I'm still warming up for the mental gymnastics required to address this question.  Give me more time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregLeding I’ll be there on Thursday to beg for more money for higher education and *equitable* funding 👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I might’ve been that person to come out my room complaining and shut this down]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are way too quick to antiquated money with happiness and not consider for a second the demons that some peop… https://t.co/NlnDvNX1HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TutuApp_vip you can’t download the configuration profile it says it’s revoked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy and Daughter Day @ Bixby Park, Long Beach https://t.co/3jThWLSTHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FosterCareAdopt @DrJamesMercer I Wrote A Poem About Adoption The Poem is Long So I Have To Split It Up In 2 Tweets… https://t.co/bX13SbbvI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelJkt2 @Grahamsaleh5 I think you may have misread what @Grahamsaleh5 was saying. He was saying that EVERYONE wi… https://t.co/7yHsk66Toq]]></document><document><![CDATA[La importancia del check and balance. Coordinamos las agendas y adiós separación de poderes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schiff has gone off the  deep end and is totally delusional. But upon further thinking is there a California Politi… https://t.co/H5ZOW4vFK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with Marcus (at @Swedish Medical Center - First Hill Campus in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/P7f8TjVqeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfailingly good boy 🍩🐲 #balumckeever @ Kensington, Brooklyn https://t.co/MRUcn2E4d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ojo que el tipo no esta satiafecho y quiere cuatro anos mas, Dios mio q apetito por el dinero!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunKelly @bethferguson748 XOXO. I'd love to get you, your brother, and his co-workers ribbons.  When you can,send… https://t.co/RRJ3BgIIHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jephjacques I have to object, 90% of bats species are super fine and also FLYING MAMMALS THAT’S AWESOME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karol @roddreher This excuse for a university should be deprived of the people’s money. And I should be ashamed fo… https://t.co/koTVCWX3rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Babblin_Brooke She's about to get everyone right in the feels, but in the best way humanly possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Analysis: Steelers look to get back to their ground-game roots https://t.co/DRg5zQGXrr via @pittsburghpg @EdBouchette #Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool spot #Seattle (at @FlatstickPub in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/H1Bo4ZpNJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PAUmaui @HoagClassic It's great with the @mauibrewingco Ginger Beer! #MauiMule]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedChasen Yeah the zekes and Barkley types. I’m cool with Jacobs outside the top 10-12 though]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are great, I love that they took years off to pursue their lives but they took too long to get back together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house for the Super Breakfast Session in Ballroom 20! #NGAshow19 https://t.co/JelMPgihPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have done RPG shows from various genres from superhero to horror, to mystery etc. Watching live is the best. M… https://t.co/j7VL9ijH7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravesAndBirds Agree on Betis. It’d be magic to see them challenge on home soil.   For RM, what are their options?… https://t.co/PrWDexaDP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deeper understanding of the cultural iceberg takes careful consideration of curriculum, threading interdisciplinary… https://t.co/T9QJwB7Dng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heidiaberi Partner up back to back, each person picks a body part, NO telling/conversing, 1,2,3, Jump Spin in hope… https://t.co/DPuE43t9Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[WH Briefing:: S. Sanders does not answer the question whether Trump believes Democrats hate Jewish people. MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to presenting on “Building a School Culture of #Mindfulness” at @LausanneLearn in Dallas/Fort Worth… https://t.co/fP537scF5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill He’s an idiot just like is overrated patriot team who play in the weakest division in football. If they we… https://t.co/HyD07L1giS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I’ll be hitting Costa Rica as well! Super fucken excited!! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't stress enough how having a relationship with God will benefit you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNBooger @geoffschwartz Let’s NOT turn this into rich VS poor .....this has NOTHING to do with coming from nothi… https://t.co/xrsDLMI6PJ]]></document></documents></author>