<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 54 of Stay in Touch is posted https://t.co/b3eKzmRPsG Decadent treats Th… https://t.co/X3RGU09EJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leyla_Years_Ed @_EmreTurkmen_ smile with your teeth, you look like you’re holding in a fart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys just posted this. I am going to apply it to my favs @BTS_twt because this IS their reality. Natural, or… https://t.co/8o5cstAjfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg... what is Cassie’s problem??? She waits till the fantasy suite night to tell him she’s not sure she can “get t… https://t.co/Q6lnhdAUjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump My Lord, they have gone completely bonkers, with all the stuff they are saying and want to do why… https://t.co/StyqLYo7dU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do so many sites say @brielarson is an extrovert instead of an introvert when it comes to the MBTI when Brie he… https://t.co/5EeKD26aek]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th grade parents: mark your calendars for the rising 6th grade parent meeting at Elkins Pointe on March 12 @ 6pm!… https://t.co/HKz4DvSWwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curse you #DaylightSavingTime! Why does it always fall on a weekends that I’m on the East Coast? 😫 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m with you guys, the movie never scared me. Elements of it did like the spider walk. Great film but not as scary… https://t.co/kZmVd6u2GS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support #ClimateAction. Be part of the solution and show support too, because #ItAffectsYou @MoCCaEUAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaBugle @michellemalkin Thank you for always standing up for what is true and right and never wavering. You always give me hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to dip out my life the door is wide open. Neither one of us is benefiting from pretending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you don’t gotta be perfect, you just gotta be worth it ✨ @ The Hotel Hershey https://t.co/CvrxtPB9GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No host is better than Kevin Hart as host👀Alrhough i’m interested in seeing how the presenters will make up for it… https://t.co/B6octBZnxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our AVID 7th &amp; 8th graders for researching 52 different HBCUs! 🎓@CreekValleyMS @AVID4College… https://t.co/H79LxVwY0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump   Mueller Investigation about a matter before the presidency wasted money for two years so what po… https://t.co/ZviUA74ne2]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: the dad sent his plate back because it wasn’t “medium rare ENOUGH”  My father has arrived and ordered a bottle thank GOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today has been super cold, super wet, super foggy.........and super foodie 😋😋 https://t.co/xAEtILQmWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RandPaul: Trump Won 'Big Victory' with Border Wall Deal https://t.co/Ki2GQdv12f via @BreitbartNews https://t.co/cQpJRyrKHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been this way for years and starting to get annoying and old. grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianf716 @KatieMorseNews @EdDrantch @kradwkbw @7FirstAlert @JoeBuscaglia @news4buffalo Good morning been tracking… https://t.co/4uQmf2SYYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DAdamWHIG Call when you return.  I have another IHSA bill for you, ha ha!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt these two loved snow days! I am missing them both a lot this week. #gonebutneverforgotten #ilovemydogs… https://t.co/jzz2nm7tLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB @YouTube That was great ❤️❤️@amandajane_24 did you see your fave NK, Griff in the video??]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCREAMING GOODLUCK to my bestfriend in the whole world! These next 5 weeks are going to be brutal for the both of u… https://t.co/KTs6hMEOgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HAWK57NYC1 Good morning, all we can do is pray for those who do unusual things who has major situation that accrue… https://t.co/vfEIkbNeFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kayschoy Joining a sorority is the best decision I made for myself, I 100% recommend giving it a chance. Having a… https://t.co/zSDPMe4OnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoolKerm Son asked Her Bae did I win???    Her: https://t.co/EcJe1SbNRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpinpe @realDonaldTrump Puerto Rico has no electoral votes &amp; officials there criticized the response from the administration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another night of beautiful talent on display. 🎶💙 @ Nazareth Academy https://t.co/pBfRT1pxo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn ya going harder for Venezuela than Puerto Rico https://t.co/4olSXSkCeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megan_kking one time freshman year i used evidence from The Onion because i thought it was a legit news source....… https://t.co/Bbnl1oRAR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three years ago today I moved to Vegas. I had no idea what was going to happen, but failure never entered my mind.… https://t.co/4MjkxeeV0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LD31Oficial saludos desde San Diego siempre agradecidos por darnos ese título, #14 nunca olvidarte Luis, que suspe… https://t.co/FS0wqssiku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #IT job in #Charlotte, NC? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Sr IT Su… https://t.co/FQnhOEOzvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all don’t know excitement and happiness until you get paid on your b-day]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is a roller derby team at this bar and they all keep staring at me LEAVE me ALONE]]></document><document><![CDATA[everything                    in  life          happens  for              A REASON ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dianafowles @LoriMoreno @sarahjeanfry @KnowSmallParts @AudreyDesisto @toolatetoboogie @Saun_Fischer @Cheryl_L_Hyde… https://t.co/M1B0dMrQGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/83n9rAyatQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you don't realize your own strength until you come face to face with your greatest weakness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OM GOSH! Grew up watching him! Mucho prayers to #AlexTrebek You GOT THIS! #FuckCancer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coolcam101 @realDonaldTrump But, don't expect change back from your dollar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffgargas @teachbetterteam Weird to see a face to a voice from the podcast! Glad you’re chatting ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenkurlyyy09 I made Pho last night and it turned out amazingly well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraxyD We are losing our homeland.  I just pray the measures being taken are not too late.  Yes, we can prosecute… https://t.co/lt9aSgFr8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of people who didn’t go to school today in texas because it’s cold i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm actively evolving, revolving and conceptualizing and this shit is RIVETING. Big brain energy all around tonight 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @Mattr_Murray, what do you and  @TODAYshow think of this cool video of @Nichols_College #basketball #coach Sco… https://t.co/pnnukQeGFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not always rainbows and butterflies It's compromise that moves us along, yeah My heart is full and my door's a… https://t.co/rz15Bm8N6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariacathleia Hehe I call it the day before chocolate is 50% off in stores 🙌🏽😂 the real holiday is the sale!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve probably asked my dad to spend time with us a million times since he’s been in town and he has declined them a… https://t.co/N9cYeagsAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the people brave enough to be out in the cold for the @OU_Softball game...you have some kinda super power or something. 🥶🥶🥶 @OUontheAir]]></document><document><![CDATA[more #fiction. stock up, rainy days ahead. open noonish to 6ish today. 371 cotton ave. #downtownmacon.  #books… https://t.co/nL6uuAgiNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nyaiosh Haha. I’m definitely NOT a camper... but these @HydroFlask in pink are cute!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t speak on anyone’s life when yours is just as bad or worse! I don’t know how many times I gotta stress this bu… https://t.co/t0e85uqh04]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 2 years since @KOlusola caused me to have a meltdown bc he said my name. My mom and I were so shocked and… https://t.co/uaSe0HVDzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1tomstraw @TwelfthPrecinct @gretchenyoung16 Would love to read more! They are all great fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who can you be intentional about caring for today?   #BeTheOne #buildingrelationships #culturize #JRErocks #KatyISD… https://t.co/BkZbPh26xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merrinish Like, wait at the back of the classroom for a stopping point! I have them frequently and you can explain then!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumptrump1234 @TeaPainUSA I feel better now.... I was having a total rant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I was watching “Bad Girls Club” and there was a girl from Compton that was arguing with another girl and Ma… https://t.co/08I2XGiPdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadBarbi @gatewaypundit The "F" word is now DEMOCRATS FAVORITE WORD!  Are you a "F" Democrat" ??? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlfSchmid @DavidBflower What an amazing couple. Hope they won, they sure should have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already one of the most stressful trips and I haven’t even checked into my hotel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannibals may seem nice but they're really just trying to butter you up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blairfan4life why??? I hope they arent giving her a new character to play she will be on her 3rd for GH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apollostowel @Karin12th I can. https://t.co/XyZN8Mezaw  😉  #DoctorWho #TheUniverseLovesPeterCapaldi https://t.co/b00bxorDVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherity1313 Haha omg, what an amazing reply!!! YEEEESSSSS, strong=less injuries + longevity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMcKew He’s not the type of grandfather you’d want your children around....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estaría cool que la tarjeta de vales se pudiera utilizar en el Starbucks 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marc Anthony tearing up the stage! @ American Airlines Center https://t.co/2Tol3dDTJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenmartino @BertlOsbornejr2 Perfect!!  It’s taken too priority now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilosParrots These! Come from my homestate of SD! https://t.co/MYJug390RP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferHorsle3 You have the 🙏🙏🙏. My favorite Christian comedian said “sitting in a church doesn’t make you a Chri… https://t.co/p5JWVWJa1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner and basketball! #beachpeeps 🌴😊 @ Dagwood's Deli &amp; Sports Bar https://t.co/fbRDeKfoR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow I can't wait for the clean up!  I hope people start to go to jail for treason.   Mostly Hillary, b… https://t.co/uAodoh6q2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to visit Chewy!!😍😍😍😍he is so smart and doing agility now! (Sorry my finger got in the video) look at that hap… https://t.co/OQuxjuHXTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this video because it went straight to where he changes his range.  He keeps going higher and higher to unbeli… https://t.co/a665P8INRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do that all the time ☺️❤️My Lucifer❤️ @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/Fgpjo4GvdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[lil sneezer. i’m grateful to be crawling back into my life after my insides were a phlegm-circus. 🧖🏻‍♂️… https://t.co/sik6y7Fudg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s why @Disney made @FastCompany’s top 50 most #innovative company’s and what we can all take away from it💡 https://t.co/sigvRz1YhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robert_coach @Abby24Coates @BeckerJosi Always great to have local players be the faces of our program! Each of the… https://t.co/cZWXYnxhTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aUSAFVeteran @BostonJimmy67 He cant. That would using extra brain cells he cant afford to lose. https://t.co/bQ6QkV0upj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used to do this before when I wrote. Maybe it’s time to start it again. Here is today’s word of the day. #wotd… https://t.co/TsbXYdfw7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[2.24 am no puedo dormir ... en VenezuelA pronto va a amanecer el 23 de Febrero ...será este el día  que estudiará m… https://t.co/Y4laQ0joV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good 2-track #TXlege effort on kids' mental health:  Thx @SenJaneNelson for work on psychiatric treatment in the co… https://t.co/AfqNKsChLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[homeboy really stalking my twitter😂bro go stalk the side chicks you had when you were my bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we know is that you are an idiot. #TrumpDerangementSyndrome #TrumpBrokeTheirBrains]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need a guy who will put his head literally up my ass I guess lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo dia nesse mesmo horário me bate um sono que eu não consigo administrar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Wow, did you just tweet a racist comment or what!!! Pos]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is the best at planning Valentine’s Day! He informed me that he took the day off...I hope he enjoys a ni… https://t.co/WP90e8VlA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stress level watching the bachelor #BachelorNation https://t.co/4hfLuQkwRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[TANZANIA DAY Lugha Ya Kiswahili!!! Chimbuko letu la Ubunifu https://t.co/HMoKhQsuyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao he was mad af that she had the audacity to cheat with a nigga named “Hubert”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Nauert has withdrawn from consideration to be the next U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, State Dept. s… https://t.co/HjVUky6mSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenozymandias just came across your DNA story.  For your family's piece of mind, you can let your dad and nana k… https://t.co/GuSvIpzvHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2About the only thing I can surmise is that Indiana doesn't give a rats ass about the air they breathe,the water… https://t.co/ObCyHNGCGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnll_dlcrz Thank you😭😭😭 LOVE &amp; MISS YOU!!!😢💙💙💙💙💙 hang out w/ us soon please]]></document></documents></author>