<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech Yes.  All they need is some independent corroboration.  Stone’s records have been seized.  AMI’s records… https://t.co/VxsMmSitXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cloudy_suit Happy, Happy, Happy Birthday! 🥳🎉 I‘m sure @ahouseingotham has some fun plans for your day. Enjoy! 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19 #JCS_RYS19… https://t.co/YviNHDpGII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxranchm @CAAARRLL89 don’t need to run out grounders when you hitting yombs babyyyyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Publier des faux jetons, il n'aurait qu'à publier la face à Charest #polqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Haracz @J0hnnyXm4s BRB realizing my dream of becoming a pizza scientist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmilstead @RubbingTheRock Already seen the officials not bail the team out at the end of games this season. Set… https://t.co/4W2MOUeDry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkass99 @PaulSzoldra @JamesWClark @TaskandPurpose Yeah, except they’d turn it into a Sitcom where they tried to re… https://t.co/cy1nwMX6s2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The congressman from FL represents his constituency well. If you’re going to commit a crime (witness tampering) try… https://t.co/wKk5J94obW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surgery day hopefully I’ll be cancer free in a few hours. @Jaboowins @kwon @Geraldini93 @LavonteDavid54 @Buccaneers… https://t.co/KBeuClWgjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[instead of Paisley Park being a flat rectangle in the background, it now has a steep perspective https://t.co/kGV0eTSMnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#selfie mood: brown-on-brown-on-camel. 😎 https://t.co/PfEaxGCssE https://t.co/eHSaxgL6FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llegando a la vejez con tremenda frente! Damn! Lol. #jacksonville #vejez #color #astral #lifestyle en Jacksonville,… https://t.co/4r5T3vnm7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Todos uds son hombres muertos. #noperdon ladrones, asesinos. https://t.co/83M2g4tzqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this weather to warm up so I can get in the groove of doing baseball,softball and track portraits. Spring, where are you??]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Original Buffalo Chicken Wings. #buffalochickenwings #theoriginal #anchorbar #anchorbarnyc #wings #nyc #nyceats… https://t.co/ZFo209kBiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phenomenal book and a different aspect looking at moments from a coaching view , which made it an interesting read… https://t.co/8dCnC9iEgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanjpeck @pnr9 @realDonaldTrump All I can say is China has used them very effectively to hurt our manufacturing w… https://t.co/wtiubcPaVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CulturalGutter And it must be accompanied by a grilled cheese sandwich. #CineJanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday is the final sermon in our series from First Peter. #firstpeter #thebookof1peter #bostonharbor #humility… https://t.co/R9X9f5jXtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 How many black liberals knows this? My guess is none...and so many Democrat plantation liberals ha… https://t.co/yq6qzbdNgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is good (in my option). “She has a problem with immigration”. There’s a horrible speech she made to Conference… https://t.co/FEbsuWxr7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeAKnee87 @RyanCovay Marvel... usually won’t see in theaters, but Guardians 1 imax 3d with edibles was the best… https://t.co/2IjSvsUvb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep calling my cat Garfield when she does something bad and i think she finally gets it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopherHole @Patrick_Reusse No point guard has hurt tremendously but I have been very disappointed in his offense.… https://t.co/r3nXfrGFe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Generally I’d agree, except that’s the wrong homonym.  🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOWT6News You know what England was growing 800 years ago ..... Grapes for wine .....  be human. Adapt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @DiamondMonrow @AnaFoxxx @CamilleAmore1 @SexxxyIvy @iluvchanell_ @IndigoVanityx10 @JezabelVisser @kendallwoodz_… https://t.co/RDCDNCvVnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 500 employees at the @NCAA’s Indianapolis headquarters.  And all of them should have gone pro in somethin… https://t.co/NfnQ33oCyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisaklenner43 @thomson_reece Fantastic high school basketball career! Wising you the best at the next level and chapter of your life! 🏀👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mooties and friends ⚖️📑🗣👯‍♂️ #easypeasy #moot #mootcourt #windsorlaw #law #counsel #friends #futurelawyers… https://t.co/0mcKBgh7jC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgressiveDe10 @fatedt0pretend @DFWAirport @KRLD Thanks for info. Ok if we use this photo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeronDemarco Ok did Jamie Fox say that with his crush on her? Did all of her other blk men she dated say that? No.… https://t.co/GJbUcNzFQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deelucks @AskRubenHow2Bet GGF is actually making an effort to their credit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davecraige @APompliano @Alexintosh @Victor928 @InstaDApp If you giveth to employees every hour or day you are crea… https://t.co/t6AAgUNQpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re gonna cut some corners, expect to be cut out of some corners 🤣 // #DontPlayMe #Facto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see how popular that will be in the near future given credibility to secure and NOT use data!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really happy @wku has done this. Mitchell was a special guy and I’m happy this will keep his memory alive! #WKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Ramsey score has me hype but then I remember he’s leaving at the end of the season. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s my Community Day Stats! Also shoutout to @nickatnyteYT for the random #ultraleague battle! What was up with… https://t.co/T0r7HTjixf]]></document><document><![CDATA[While my flight is delayed between 3 and 7 hours, I was able to watch the documentary about #DuPont and #PFOA.… https://t.co/DLCyiaxpxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccuRayno Mother Nature is in her full beauty in Mahwah, NJ. (permission to use) https://t.co/vFyt7Wypy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that the lead guitarist for my favorite band when I was in high school, Brian May of Queen, has a PhD in Astrophysics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDoyle76 @SoccerCooligans @SoccerCooligans when’s @MattDoyle76 coming on the show??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoshi_sudarso @PeterSAdrian Peter you rock as well, sorry I didn’t get to type it earlier got busy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrible consequences of racism, human rights violations and hypocrisy 😢 @UN  #TrumpCrimeSyndicate #UnitedNations… https://t.co/snEsZwjbxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just casually looking at my hair in the mirror:  Ugh whats a feminine hairstyle? This is, it’s just nothing looks f… https://t.co/haCbjCB7ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read all caps-lock sentences in Alex Jones’ voice bc people being excited about something is funnier when u hear… https://t.co/nSURjyF21Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killacraig22 @jimrome #.200 Lifetime but hitting bombs ⚾️💣 at a rate like my name is #DAVE KINGMAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveLaurence “Never compromise. Not even in the face of Armageddon.” Happy 10 Year Anniversary #Watchmen! https://t.co/iW74csU0ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligatory daily picture from #Mets #SpringTraining @ NY Mets Spring Training Complex https://t.co/nOzxJyWu5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeFrancesa Yes they have many holes to fill yet you pay a crappy qb almost 20 million. Cut him and save your sel… https://t.co/XPOGw6K26E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers @TheLeadCNN @JamalSimmons @CNN Good reporting on The Lead.  You should run for Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we the only dumbasses who call these Pineapples instead of Pina like the rest of the world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Light pole down due to high wind at the mall!! @ Beaver County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/DOxn56rQR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck tonight boys! Come show off your storm pride and support the boys tonight! #letsgouv #stormpride https://t.co/wqhTqKK28n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morterenatus @AshRatcliffe92 Anna has been shaking her polygon hoots for years lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foe_us We clearly have two fronts to fight. CO2 and Methane.  They are both important.  Would be nice to have UN I… https://t.co/PfJyeRZpY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼"I STOOD IN DA KITCHEN FOR WEEKS.. COOKING CRACK LIKE A BEAST " RICK GARLEY 2019 @ Northeast Houston, Hou… https://t.co/IGIGjQNnDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another big night at the windows at @TheMeadowlands . Total handle was $3.175 M, the second-highest of the year! Th… https://t.co/Drq5ANV9fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class field trip to @HolocaustMuseum. First visit was 1996. I bring my class every other year. Never fails to shock me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PunisherCoachOL @CoachRHiggins Lots of #TrumpCult members won't vote for Cruz because they haven't forgiven him fo… https://t.co/RIVf1ZehGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wanderley O técnico do time disse q foi certo o gol foi falha do goleiro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThosChamberlain Absolutely. They apparently got the green light from Mueller. The target list goes after the Inaug… https://t.co/OmWzsOPsUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamichat @Roberts_Ben_M @TexasTravelTalk Is that their Twitter account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4 - Jim Collins talks about technology being an accelerant to change but not the cause of change. I have used tech… https://t.co/qfeFLqpqZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool kids show up late to the party, right! @UBmenshoops looking good early! https://t.co/VJ2EXtpml6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallJenner What do you really know about that? Literally, seriously, but not to serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dais_julian @bporch3110 Been a fan for a long time. Julian used to watch games in the Astrodome after a long day at Astroworld.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikecavalier I remember you saying this. I am outraged that you brought this back with you from the otherside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 Do you not know that you are God’s temple and that God’s Spirit dwells in you? -1 Corinthians 3:16]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look to you... god bless !!! #👏🏽🙏🏾🙌🏾🇹🇹 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/EVNU5LQnCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road games at the Spectrum in Logan (USU) and the Marriott Center in Provo (BYU) can be mayhem! Nevada Wolf Pack wi… https://t.co/3QlJH9IDOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southerndwaal @tony_bicycle @BadAstronomer @AOC People are bitching about paying more in taxes and getting less ba… https://t.co/avos2yjGVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just did a tour for a bunch of 10 year olds from a South LA school.  Walking back to visitor control, one little gi… https://t.co/FTURI3xAGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athletic City Update:  These Morris-Sussex Wresters are heading to the Quarterfinals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moshik_temkin This article lays it out really well. It’s a pretty straight financial transaction, with Jared Kushn… https://t.co/a5ImBFtNkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid Cody Ware. Learn how to put idiot. There goes our good race figures #Ally48 #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews Eres un periodista con los pantalones bien puestos mis respetos para ti por tu trabajo tan profesional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zsmiller23 @SamTomasi13 How many of them National Championships ya got? I think we have twice as many and 3 more F… https://t.co/iv1H6uw8YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonPincince I don’t on VG specifically, although it’s more hybrid than what I mean. I’m mostly talking about the 0 site, all online stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Mitch appears to answer to a higher (wealthier) demographic, like all of today's modern republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but what does “ taki taki rumba” even mean ??? That song annoys me so much lol, it doesn’t even make sense in Spanish]]></document><document><![CDATA[This stuff scares me when it comes to children seeing candy not #canadacannabis . https://t.co/HfEaJS28pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demobizz Same, I will make noise, be disappointed, but I will not fight anybody, my people of ekiti who voted mass… https://t.co/vOITxenqSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[After rumors swirled about Andrew McCabe and Trump's fitness for office, the Prez's Clarence Darrows convened to ca… https://t.co/oYFaol5SLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooling of Climate sensitivity - Anthropogenic CO2 Global Warming Challe... https://t.co/FWzs8YcyeI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the gym and Talladega Nights is on. How am I supposed to concentrate on anything now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even going to hide it...I lost it when I saw this in theaters. It was so good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks until VA Beach Half Marathon Six mile run today in a damp and drizzly Fells Point @CharmCityRun… https://t.co/s9xSh0D7Ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texture study of Saturday . Wip. 100% Substance #madewithsubstance #substancedesigner @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/ditbTrM0IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Explicado así parece tan sencillo,  pero bueno, de cualquier forma no nos queda más que seguir intentándolo...Ánimo… https://t.co/bcuXYZCbXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trambolico24 If you buy a nonrefundable airline ticket and your plans change...expensive. Pay a little more for a… https://t.co/fj3eb7lMUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLakeErie @GrLakeMichigan @LakeSuperior @LakeHuron ... and currently having issues with algal blooms, hypoxic z… https://t.co/dbuchJyhtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[08MAR19 Celebrate and honor International Women's Day https://t.co/Xe4QEOpGPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrudWeiser @TotallyCasual_ Most points on a team that’s only relevant because of how their young goalie is playing… https://t.co/f2uxSDgrsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thvgcess Dont give up so soon its only been like 8 min since you tweetedr it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN are you going to let a panelist on your network compare @POTUS to Adolf Hitler who murdered over 6 million Jew… https://t.co/RdiFlldh27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick Run Around the  Back Home Park💥🔊🍻💸 🛹🤘🏽👽🙏🏽🛹 Happy New Years Eve ‼️🎉🎉🎉 📹 sirsquirtness 📽 I love you all and tha… https://t.co/MNLpyPnlQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wallfryd1 ..of monster of the week, investigation,Cthonian fantasy, horror, adventure and cosmic terrors with a ra… https://t.co/jYmLJg635Z]]></document></documents></author>