<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CitizenWonk Cheers to the patriots! #Trump #MAGA https://t.co/erQnKTkx6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterBardatsos @Aj_Arroyo_ That is great to hear Peter you have learned so much with Soc will be easier second time around!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/WVJ1QUJ7j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[But now faith, hope, love, abide these three; but the greatest of these is love. 1 Corinthians … https://t.co/TmRPDTwjfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtBusiek Lol. I was just thinking that very same thing the other day. I’m pretty open anytime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSCampbell The whole point of asylum is that there is no safety there. It is so dangerous that they risk life… https://t.co/VOhezrGt3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando la vida se pone difícil, aquellos que amamos son los que nos ayudan a salir adelante... @ Top of the Rock NYC https://t.co/Z2arvFt9AK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump President Trump.  You need to fire the people that are supposed to provide you with the facts... t… https://t.co/BsJntKUESk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealChillyPod We live in a world where this man has beaten Villanova... https://t.co/2VQq2k5Y2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dropping the next person who takes my Juul and asking questions later idc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has been a long and cold week in #Kansascity #tgif https://t.co/jX96LnBdNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson No the 25th amendment IS part of our constitution]]></document><document><![CDATA[By this time next week I’ll be yelling at someone in Fort Worth and life will be good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretStephensNYT @benshapiro Your progressive politicians at work. They looked a gift horse that had TRex teeth in… https://t.co/wcc2kJTEMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We learned this month that GM and Ford paid little to no federal tax in recent years thanks to generous tax breaks.… https://t.co/UWBjnhqNzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of all the hard work our @PGATSS fam put into our 2019 Spring campaign! Working with @DJohnsonPGA @JonRahmpga… https://t.co/QaHgqcvBXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov @GOP I wish they would. But Republicans continue to abdicate their responsibility to investigate crimes… https://t.co/aMfmzNfcV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que acabados se ven los @backstreetboys en #ViñadelMar #Viña19xFOX https://t.co/TMzMSvsMlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One unified morning service hbcbluesprings 10:45am. Building nothing but people, but building for eternity. Come me… https://t.co/meDvJjoea1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Harper marks 2-year anniversary of heart attack: 'I am so thankful to be here' https://t.co/HJa4PWPlkS via @TODAYshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the #Sabres struggle is worse than stubbing your pinkie toe on a chair. 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tessellation by @ConclaveBrewing @ Springfield, NJ — https://t.co/kS6OPRkG7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the socialist propaganda says: Household net worth falls by largest amount since the Great Recession, new Fed d… https://t.co/fQjMv8vvCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this amusing. 22 Jump Street Begins Production - Principal photography began September 28th, 2013 on Columbi… https://t.co/OULpBc8FAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady made sure last night’s  cruise was a safe, successful adventure. https://t.co/P37x1kijJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman The media will scream 24/7 about Democrats attacking the president’s family, and no one will point out that hypocrisy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think about that time nicki minaj went off on turkey bacon that doesn’t get crispy often]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really disappointed in the Miami home whites and their helmets. It’s just so... meh. There’s so much potential… https://t.co/9kW6ghsG2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: #LSU 17, Bryant 8  Tigers improve to 6-0 and were led by 6 RBI from Antoine Duplantis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamAtheistGirl It’s good that you read the Bible , keep it up , but hey tell me the context of that verse , becaus… https://t.co/LmXfnKw2b4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra The green new deal is necessary because Obama Care didn't quite destroy America financially.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHunterWildTV @MeUndies We match today!!! Been rocking then myself for 5 years now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplys30298497 @DaveSchreiber3 @Lindamu93790975 @JamesBo77952200 @JJPPATRIOT @Godsgirl158 @Dawn_DeMore1… https://t.co/PETy1Cxp2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #SportsBetting Twitterverse launch into to #Oscars2019 like Super Bowl pre-game is interesting. @Gambling @bookies #SportsGambling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shmidtBC @NBCNews This network hires known racist and has no problem with that https://t.co/UblzDwj6wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedNationRising Bam! I like be Attractive Hazard Rule. Now build the “Attractive Hazard Wall Now”!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schiff wants to investigate every rabbit hole! Maybe he can pull out a rabbit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@o2bmattsmom I believe that was in the context of his opponents in this race alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last team swim before synchro nationals ... the Rocky theme will be a winner every time!! #LetsGoWheat https://t.co/rMmM6Xxwua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mp3michael @Sharkyl Proof? And source for the inclusion of hidden costs (I disagree that a farm subsidy isn’t a hi… https://t.co/qu3B3cLOPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jqllc @myceeta @FightForNYCHA @NYCMayor @AliciaGlen @NYCHPD @hud @LynnePattonHUD @NYGovCuomo @NYCHA Yea the fundin… https://t.co/9UQ7wAFfzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawn illuminates the destruction @ Opelika, Alabama https://t.co/Eom2vtacds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@assissicourt @pst8367 @blueeyescooking @KTHopkins @sammymarks__187 Well when you have several kids and pay for all… https://t.co/JvATDc0Gw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fleetwood Mac with my Gold Dust Woman. @ Smoothie King Center https://t.co/lxwGzFTIO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winning for our clients in highly competitive situations. It’s what we do. #ProfessionalOne #realestate #PlymouthMI… https://t.co/7M47fr0eSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catschmuck @gailfinke @streetcitypub @fccincinnati @ShawnHeine @streetcitypub can’t wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickNeumannn I’ve never seen a team utterly collapse like that. Unbelievable. They didn’t even look to get shots off]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Predicciones Nuevas 🔮👈🏼 En Hoy #MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni Me Encanta Pero Me Gustaría Que Durará Mas Tiempo Su Se… https://t.co/AcPiv9NsPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re straightforward asf and really don’t care if that hurts your feelings, free spirited and doesn’t like feeling… https://t.co/iIc955B09P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bettycrackerfl House lizards (they're not geckoes) are always fun to watch - and they eat skeeters and other insec… https://t.co/0Jqkw9VPkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smash night at @LuckyLabPDX #nintendo #switch #ssbu @ Lucky Labrador Beer Hall https://t.co/Czli3gsBo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A deeper dive into why #Azure ADLS Gen2 is a game changer for #Cloud #Analytics: https://t.co/KrGKxXPLQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexsideris_ And in these really small startup ecosystems the vast minority of people actually making money are se… https://t.co/8scZBhOfPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This random. But @BrotherMob why is your album The Untouchable not on Apple Music or iTunes? I love that album]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chupacabra66 @Barracuda_Bella @MazurikL @RepCummings I agree and these Dirty Democrats will not stop. Even as thei… https://t.co/SaDp8pFrrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth and Mr Cohen are seldom in the same place. Nothing to see from this clown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME He is just so sad and negative all the time... Its sickening... People jeep trying to say he's a nice guy but… https://t.co/tyTsrv2bQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akidnamedmo Chocolate drop while I’m eating chocolate chip pancakes ???? Legendary]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a cool thread and it started with me asking WTH a “bolide” was. Fascinating. 👇🏻👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[We would like to thank @BeauPrice78 for his contribution of "donuts" to our staff breakfast this morning!!!! https://t.co/IlQ1RtNi9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Call them out when they've gone too far but be careful though so you don't get suspended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuerpos hablantes, eso pretende hacer de la sociedad con la ideología de género, adiós hombres y mujeres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday “Big Game “ James Worthy, All American, 3X NBA Champion, 7X All Star, NCAA National Champion, #52 Re… https://t.co/FBLgjsvkeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeyD1017 Bruh i been up since Saturday morning. I feel like when that sun hit the sky Ima die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom my deceased parents, must be turning in their grave right now to see their family’s name, reputation a… https://t.co/CO0N2yzYLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmeltzer non-goalies have no idea how frustrating those off-speed pitches are. it's one thing to expect and adj… https://t.co/EhlQlBIPBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s bad I’m all out of contacts and my glasses broken https://t.co/RJ9sh2UVjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StargateDaily He fell on hard times after saving the universe from Ming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its officially that time of year when the potholes in BW parkway will swallow an SUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment when Elle steps into the courtroom as a full fledged lawyer in full pink legal garb....she has fully joi… https://t.co/3lqFoq6tXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just chillin’ after a day of door knocking in Stittsville. https://t.co/15oOCbDo3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful Saturday gone to Ojai for the day got to hang with Grandma and Mom and went to go to see lil baby… https://t.co/kRRrRJKVgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRidener @matt_mccutcheon @SeanWTHR Maybe! My wife and I are both from Lebanon and our moms’ chilis look a lot lik… https://t.co/JiUDY46Yup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanOKana Thank you Sean! I'm honored. I would love to get together in the coming months to create some new headsh… https://t.co/GE1u8ppSEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesonn more info, leading to the inevitable “when is it Due to open?” https://t.co/sYmbYmOCxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shiiiii if my man was warmed up just believe it would’ve been a 50 across the board🤷🏽‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was also one of my clients when I was in Transportation as a National Account Executive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston, MA: at hotel140, Clarendon Street awaiting BIDMC medicine. Now 6 days delayed, due to a typo on the hospita… https://t.co/GE9IJ4kU2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMarshh Thank you your leadership on the field and off! True champion! My son was stoked to take this picture with… https://t.co/mN1e1fouk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥 Last 3 workouts! 🥵🥵 Finally Posted and Not Bad!!! 🥳🥳🥳 #anytimefitness #myzonemoves #yourgym #goals #motivation… https://t.co/X22zX6sHCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddymedina2115 BRO...YOU. ALREADY. KNOW. WHAT. THE. FUCK. IS. GOING. ON.😭🤯🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥❤️ OVO SOUND RADIO ⁶𓅓⁶𓅓⁶𓅓⁶𓅓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey ha, you claim to oppose one thing but then support it in a different context. i am very intelligent]]></document><document><![CDATA[For I command you today to love the Lord your God, to walk in obedience to him, and to keep his c… https://t.co/V1GKstBLce]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a HUGE congrats to an erstwhile kid actor acquaintance (and the 1st teenager to read the lead role of Halada in… https://t.co/F4LghjS2Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse me I am an old lady any start time past 9pm is NO GOOD 🙅🏼‍♀️🙅🏼‍♀️🙅🏼‍♀️🙅🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una bendición la Conferencia para Matrimonios de #cdrhouston  El Señor nos ha hablado de lo que sucede cuando Él es… https://t.co/b44fUJNSAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Poole is 26 but he is essentially Bobby McCain. No need to look here folks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarcasticluther @sxsw There used to be a great barbeque place on commonwealth about to blocks from a place that se… https://t.co/HIUwiIMPZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke to Ivan Baranchyk’s manager, David McWater:”We have adamantly told them we’re not in the tournament. Out of r… https://t.co/V8Tpbqx2pK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freedom_Funds @GameSetProfit Agreed. But, with all fights that end controversial, if he hadn’t allowed himself to… https://t.co/irGpYDrGma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Intolerance and hateful best describes today’s democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francoBamaBoi @cvpayne This is a violation of the Equal Credit Opportunity Act. No new law or partisan support for any law is required.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently at Cameron Indoor Stadium at Duke watching @DukeMBB get on the bus to play @UNC_Basketball tonight 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VendorPower @lvhernandez I’m not the bill sponsor, so I don’t schedule hearings on bills that aren’t mine until re… https://t.co/frF3dc9LdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyItsAngel_ Haha real funny quit playing with me on social media child lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dancing_dawson *record scratch*  *Freeze frame*  Yup, that's me. I bet you're wondering how I got here. https://t.co/rjG0c0ejdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs Nothing in the Constitution says a Supreme Court Justice has to be alive.  Sincerely MSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing a lil heat on a good day! Outtake from my recently published submission in the February issue of… https://t.co/0uH0hopJX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has come to my belief that potus is not so much a racist as he is an investigating opportunist. By this I mean i… https://t.co/InD6SmY6bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Steelers sending AB to the Raiders is the biggest trade in Pittsburgh sports history. Treat it as such.]]></document></documents></author>