<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Finding a great fitting plain tshirt to wear is actually a challenge. Or I should say "was" a challenge. One of the… https://t.co/sOwCxhI6QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to stay off torrids website!😩 I wanna buy new clothes but im actually losing weight so,  1. I dont kn… https://t.co/njFldwRldG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have just quit on #projects because that’s what their #majority firms do as if I have that same #privilege… https://t.co/syhGvFw2DZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theres always time for the important things🌱   Hitting the @mmlbarftw stage tonight at 10:30p!! Had to grab one las… https://t.co/lvmNvy1Z7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @RepMattGaetz It sounds exactly like Donald's words and Matthew is craven enough to say them for president treasonweasel]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only collusion was their prescious Obama and Hillary colluding with the Russians, they twist everything because… https://t.co/40tTJpFyhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InEveryCorner @realAliTweets @AnnMeganHurley @CNN Agreed Why have Michael Capputo on when u know he was accused of… https://t.co/A2jRCj2I9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg Devin you had a baby on me?! I can’t believe you 😭 I THOUGHT YOU LOVED ME. YOU WAS MY BABY. MY CINNAMON APPLE 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey FPU Students! I’m writing about people’s opinions on FPU’s rules/regulations for my journalism class. If you’re… https://t.co/L9wt7cad8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I had this much energy on a Monday but truthfully the time change messed me up 🤪  📸 : @exaltedhotmess @ Torrey… https://t.co/1OKOTf8Irm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Two top 10 LHW wins. 1 top 5 win, he doesn’t need to kill someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Saturday I had someone tell me “you’re my ideal body type” and it still hasn’t left my mind. It made me feel s… https://t.co/7tWwL60fOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tweeted that One Day At A Time is unwatchable and now I’m mad lmao. I would throw hands for that show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fire service is a very tight knit community and while the members of the Berwick Fire Department continue to mo… https://t.co/Qwv9v4WJCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathrynVSantos @DrDadabhoy @auctoritas A women in the audience specifically asked her about this, and she just dismiss her]]></document><document><![CDATA[AUBREY PLAZA - HOSTING THE 34TH FILM INDEPENDENT SPIRIT AWARDS TODAY FEBRUARY 23  _ plazadeaubrey #AubreyPlaza host… https://t.co/SyEi7VPzUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thriftycars never again.   Said my reservation was canceled. Gave agent confirmation. She said too bad, didn't hel… https://t.co/uYaH78N2Ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so lucky that I have the ability to act like someone I want to punch in the nose doesn’t exist while they are s… https://t.co/zayMruB81r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mg81992 @nypost Oliver wake up!! Or do you just watch what you want to hear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorahahaha OMG BABE! I remember!!!! We were selling in front of the UP chirch and u ordered tokneneng. Huehue 3rd… https://t.co/jW3FCcXXvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheryldhanna @KCDurling Does anybody know who the owner of this dog is and if he or she needs any help?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethCotlar @CharlesPPierce I've wondered about that also. But my husband would never survive an extinction of UNC football. ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re out of the nightlife game when all you care about is where the BATHROOMS DISAPPEARED TO!? https://t.co/WircSq2sBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigeonpieO_o @taystar8_gypsy @XylanneOfficial @lindsay_628 @SsssamanthaaMUA @beautylish Anyone doing that deserves an infection]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DedicatedEducators #KidsFirst #ConnectGrowServe #EdCampNKY2019 @NKCESKids1st]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being a professional photographer and being assigned to a group of fans and not any artists. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to this discussion with our colleagues from @RISD incl/ @justinwcook and the Center for C… https://t.co/wOqqxC3CLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigHoffman Also, Mike Shanahan has been gone for 5 years and very little talent has been added since then. Take… https://t.co/rWseDm70Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a Black Mathematician, What It’s Like to Be the ‘Only One’ https://t.co/A7x7wMmt7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibraryWoodview @WVEBeagles @SBISDLib @SBISD @BeckyHagan1 So excited for the work that you are doing with students… https://t.co/H5Ni1wk9BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me how moral UR ppl R again @BillSpadea U want jump all over Dems 4 made up shot they never said or did while… https://t.co/ncmJmJL0me]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if I like you you’re special af to me 😌 don’t take me for granted. Periodtttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pussybeaux @erikajayne Erica also says Nene doesn't lie give me a break and Vanderpump gets all the attention Nene… https://t.co/UULRdYnTDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schoolsocialite @Proud2BeAtPride @JoanneMillerHOH Please tell us how it works😀😍 Do all classes compete for this in the cafe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[me before donating blood: i’m a universal donor! i’m just doing my part! donate your blood!… https://t.co/Hbw2D3xMs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubycramer @TheObamanista He’s trying to gaslight folks by inserting “establishment.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I’m working on something major and I’m genuinely so excited to announce it once all of the legal stuff get… https://t.co/CynjUuKYYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and @sodastreamau in celebrating #internationalwomensday with their new SHE campaign and exclusive water bo… https://t.co/mNujG3rmVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope lol I’m stingy I don’t want none of my friends messing with anyone I messed with because I wouldn’t do it to t… https://t.co/Y98Ni8xFhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-pound puppy dies after ingesting nearly 50 short ribs, shelter says https://t.co/hmJ8NtEfx1 #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily reminder that this woman is trash as is the Premier that wouldn't denounce her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaFins @DeathByLipstik @LittlestFish @GhosthuntingCPI @AForce01 @uniqueflowers17 @WeightReed @VictoriaIdoni… https://t.co/vxzQYZWLkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I pretend Im gonna take a nap, then wake up and do homework, but then I just go to bed and wake up in the… https://t.co/sBY8kWyUfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AunqueClaro Este era de jaque mate fácil. No queda mucho rival digno en twitter 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSin_E @JeffreeStar DaVinci looks like DaVinci.  That's just so cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[writing starts with reading. then reading more. and learning what you’ve read, and conversing with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janice4Brexit Too bad it's not a couple hundred years ago when people rebelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiybro @Browns Lol no, I’d be really surprised because they don’t want him in the AFC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Happiness can be found even in the darkest times if one only remembers to turn on the light” Albus Dumbledore @ Wh… https://t.co/JccopPBb7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnAroundMom @healWRITEnow @Peace4Tarpon @marwilliamson The person in the pic is also wearing an assault rifle pin on his lapel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnchats I need to book this for my kids!!! And let’s be honest for me too! Perfect for any #Disneyphile 💗#DisneyKids]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else heat up the same cup of coffee like 5 times throughout the morning? #IsItJustMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun serving soup for Operation Soupline, a fundraiser for Doorstep Incorporated which helps the poor and und… https://t.co/TzaXCngeiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyEC98 @jonasbrothers I think it’s a sin that I forgot about him. How dare I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump OMG! You have gone over the line to craziness!! Where do you get those figures? Do you make them u… https://t.co/OCJ24jQuig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before and after... The after turned out brighter than what the box said but I was expecting that since I had blond… https://t.co/ebCT8BP3sZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cole02780343 @Indians @TribeHotDogs Oh it’s always real https://t.co/yaBJe8NgqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @instagram: what do I do if I have a bug that I cannot fix,  1.) your Help feature cannot help 2.) update, uni… https://t.co/2kmekg0or2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is BS. No valentine.  No heart-shaped trays. See why I don't celebrate?! #vd #sorryfortheinconvenience @ New Y… https://t.co/acns9pxER5]]></document><document><![CDATA[They knew we were coming! 😎 #methodistswag #GC2019 #GC2019EPA https://t.co/kPTajknd7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn escaping into the witness protection program https://t.co/ac3d4LqAnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedo creer que me quede menos de un mes para volver a CR. Que se detenga el tiempo please 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just want to draw Sailor Moon. Been over a year since I’ve actually drawn pencil to paper and I need… https://t.co/ulBafmKAVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was the Guadalupe County Bras for a Cause fundraiser. This event helps to raise money for those fighting… https://t.co/kBimqMFZ9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta Really, @peta? #SteveIrwin was an iconic hero to an entire generation of children. He taught those children a… https://t.co/77oLOiS6Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barack's marriage proposal to Michelle is one of the best stories I've ever read #becoming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump This man doesn’t care what anyone does unless it goes against him.  This terrorist is a trump supporter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@souljaboy turning this up now! Y’all give Big Draco credit  #BETSocialAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kellyw324 @DanRather Me too! Sick and tired of different laws for Republicans!😯😯]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s wrong with people why can’t anyone fulfill their words with actions anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to put congress on budget. No free plane rides and big expense. No pay or perks if running for president. D… https://t.co/NE8HvInKvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressive wing is offering #MedicareForAll  #FightForFifteen  #GunSense #EndTheWars #ERA #EndRacism  #TaxTheRich… https://t.co/c7estgYa4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjillian I agree. Ready for #got   Sad it’s coming to an end but excited to watch!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when the jonas brothers said “everybody bought our 7th album” that could actually be a thing 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracie_aby Drop the @ and ill fight! You don’t shave legs in the winter for nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seemaxoxo She’s wilding !!!! They should let her kid stay tho. He/she is innocent]]></document><document><![CDATA[analeahaaha is modeling the new “STRENGTH” Hoodie💪🏼 and looks amazing❤️.   Order yours today!  They are going fast🔥… https://t.co/ijZ552UAZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @AnsonEa23 , @eyagnew and @DJRTeacher to share seven of my favorite books - no explanatio… https://t.co/60qjM2kHv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrisonSmith85 @DeathHouseMovie @JasonMcFiggins @TriCoastEnt I have them, Guinness, and Jameson on speed dial!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is crazy he has to explain this. Americans should already know how “free” stuff works!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ExploreJapanWith KathNiel  #KathNielLovesJapan  #VoteKathrynBernardo #KCA @bernardokath https://t.co/vDHu6obLkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do this Wednesday!  I’m ready for you #AMNewser #GoodDayNWA #ItsGonnaBeaGoodDay #KNWA #lifestyle 💃🏾 https://t.co/Ve2AtJ7XiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGrossNewsday Where is a player supposed to go when he is being pushed from behind?  He was shoved right into him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darius_M4 He a “victim” for real. Everybody always doing him wrong type of nigga. This tweet should have been brou… https://t.co/fX3JQ3xUih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brisk NYC sunset 🌇  . #nyc #newyork #newyorkcity #datenightideas #wallstreet #travelcouple #travelblogger… https://t.co/Bp2RFUJbbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuthHHopkins Wth is Tim Cook even sitting in the same room with this man? Makes me want to throw my iPhone in the trash!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird seeing pictures of me from over a year ago because even though I feel like a fat cat I definitely lost w… https://t.co/ed10FxDKpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mathcounts Mathletes are getting ready for the Countdown Round! #mamslife #mathcounts #WFU https://t.co/AewBzOHyYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending my birthday nite with my sweetheart and the @SLU_Billikens noeeinning 13-12.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already know but the fact is still the same with Barack Obama's bloody campaign trail and what they did selling o… https://t.co/AaaBRk4DJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenMillerND @TQPurdon @barblarkin Anything shoveled from a scoop at a cafeteria...hard pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[im mad that wrangler only has the cute black jacket for guys☹️ i want one but I DONT FIT IN THE SMALL ONES. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to come to thebeautyandthebeeeefwpb tonight to try Shayna’s famous strawberry Monkey in Paradise mule?… https://t.co/u6AUkPwfMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can't explain what made your day good, then I don't think you had a good day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dmose got some new shoes, now he doesn’t know how to act LOL https://t.co/U7OXMffAea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to the bar with no money &amp; ended up Fucked up. It’s a good night to be pretty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder on this #InternationalWomansDay there are tests that can help save your life ladies!!!… https://t.co/PfLdsZ8p2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy cumple mamá y como me duele el no poder abrazarla y celebrar su día 😪😪.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSentenil @angelo_bottone @repeal_shield @CoraSherlock I am blocked, I don’t even know who this person is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newton and #PaulDouglasHale #DruidHills #Baptist #Church  Now Gay #ChurchOnPonce by #JimmyCarter #Carter's… https://t.co/u0TWBxTrR2]]></document></documents></author>