<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Plan envisions adapting roads, expanding trails for walkers and bikers countywide https://t.co/bslCcTiFDn via @lancasteronline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memphistigerjeb Vividly remember this game. Wasn’t if on CBS? I feel like Billy Packer or Al McGuire were on the c… https://t.co/4yUotBxyU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derosajoe51 Fun hang last night. It is nice to finally get to know you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching Supergirl and earning great rewards from #viggle #Supergirl @TheCWSupergirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @ChurchAndStateN WRGAS to what this old fart has to say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[«Je ne comprends pas que Kavis Reed s’autoproclame grand gagnant» - Bruno Heppell https://t.co/wLVA85Ev9q https://t.co/bCqvpTP7l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle @AllmnnaIdrotts1 It’s literally equivalent to calling a black person the N word. It’s disgusting and… https://t.co/bJBShMsynv]]></document><document><![CDATA[System is basically a humid wind tunnel, blowing moist air across test samples. Measure collection efficiency for d… https://t.co/Y6ir99tsHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael No se lo regalaron ustedes para embarrarlo? Digo, ese truco es viejo también]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us every Monday night for our Neighbors night prefix menu. @ Rosso Vino https://t.co/wd9ZNtZh6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was great meeting jon.blondell of sublime yesterday! Further proving my theory that trombonists are the best, most… https://t.co/2x9Hdp4JrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie now you see why i call my wife @SelirioJennie  "Jhennie By The Ocean"🇺🇸😍🇵🇭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemoe79 @NYorNothing Another Good player,  Can’t forget Sutter Brothers .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook boasted of buying Instagram to kill the competition: sources https://t.co/mt7w1WxjAz via @nypost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@co_rapunzel4 Bullying is an understatement. His ego is so fragile, he was offended by what Harry Reid said on CNN.… https://t.co/gnvbXf1ysW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why I had a dream where I pulled up to DT with:  - an old coworker  - a guy I hated from HS - my ex’s littl… https://t.co/XePXtpwj6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday Organ Concert. Always free. Always amazing. (@ Christ Church in Rochester, NY w/ @ugogrl2)… https://t.co/nio6oSzXnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyTurdsday @stormewarren @MCSiriusXM @TommySiriusXM Your #NatDaysR “Hospitalist” “Be Heard” “Crown Of Roast Por… https://t.co/4Gb06CZDI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, 4 #nationalnametagday here's the name tags I've collected in my 📻 career so far. https://t.co/PYJfc5E0fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirkgoldsberry Awesome! I'll follow up with more details as it gets closer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast Protected? By who(m)? The straight white males like me that both of these groups work toward abolishing on… https://t.co/4xVKImobJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2011 #dm to see the whole thing #push #sapphire #precious #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram… https://t.co/DCuP8plcTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jwayne9025 @DivaQBBQ Didn’t know there was a town named KC in the state of Texas...BBQ country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Dan...I wanted to share something with you. I had back surgery 4 weeks from a car accident. My Dr prescribed me… https://t.co/WXELjSUz4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess a 20-5 record gets trumped by 2 last second wins in a conference where no team is safe at any given point.… https://t.co/EdciIrI8hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drbanj @bane_newton @kennettjohn @dmellon2270 @AOC @RashidaTlaib No it’s not progress I hate. It’s young Swedish w… https://t.co/NsUe4vDXyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#calandersonpark #seattle #capitolhillseattle #birthday #3/10/1952 #haveanastycold @ Cal Anderson Park https://t.co/FdR2BgR9sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harden gets fined for speaking truth. Decides not to play against GSW in a nationally televised game. NBA ratings taking a spike. A king.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way downtown to train two new ARC Donor Ambassadors. Will you #BleedForTheThrone? https://t.co/oyyFjLtlkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoyalMerengue Completely lost at how a man of his frame is getting tossed around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the way @RHSVarsityHoops battled Selah (and the referees) tonight for a spot in the 2A State Final! Came u… https://t.co/iWxXNWZvXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud. #bass #bassrig #loud #tonefordays #ampeg #tech21 #VTbass #pedalboard @ 89th Street - OKC https://t.co/FSnboJL550]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck @thebradfordfile @RepAdamSchiff Total B.S. he’s the only one saying that.. they all got caught with… https://t.co/GkCb0TCYf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAAF @BleacherReport Just find them a paycheck. So we can keep enjoying ur league.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New song on #IGTV with my boy @KWalkerCountry one of my favorite songs he’s ever done... not including the songs we… https://t.co/A01k3FBeGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA_CR Only slightly late (= on time for @KeolisNA @MBTA_CR ) but what about the sewage leak on the first car? Be… https://t.co/viC5UG1gkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to coach @CoachMikeHelfer and @VSUBasketball on the #1 seed! Wish you the best in the tournament 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier @steph93065 @FoxNews @DNC Democrats will not be able to get the questions a head of time with FOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter , what would you have done differently . You are the only person who predicted he will win the election… https://t.co/7osklW3Y8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen was for sure one of the highlights from tonight!! https://t.co/s3qso7LTH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_well3 @Mastermind Dancehall reggae is different.  Riddims are made popular by multiple deejays and singers singi… https://t.co/jqOEfxaKpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Good morning, all you need is #love and a little #coffee. ...No matter how #goodorbad you have it, wake up ea… https://t.co/mbkBjIAN1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEEI And that should surprise, who? Only difference is those other purveyors of virtue haven’t been caught yet...]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: The Five Best Moments from CRSSD 2019: Five years on, San Diego’s electronic-heavy CRSSD Fest feel… https://t.co/Ha5aYRcYaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random guy: bro should I go hit on that super hot chick?? Me: Up to you dude we looks looks like she might be a pro… https://t.co/fAsXwDps9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Florida photographer, Doc Jon, captures a rare circle-of-life moment, an Osprey carrying a Shark carrying a Fish.… https://t.co/OXXdcn6JPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who claim to possess either a “manifesto” or a “repertoire” are hereby entitled to a large bowl of get the fuck over yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Towards the end I was really only getting high to try and band-aid my broken heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schemin’ on the low, the furthest thing from perfect like everyone I know]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the Democrats promoting attacks on Jews we can see why Evangelical Christians have supported Jews and Israel so strongly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@playbill @TheTonyAwards Dreamgirls being defeated 😕 by Nine as Best Musical in 1982.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ain’t the first time that someone has blown a @Nike shoe #LikeMike #ZionsShoe #dukevsunc #ZionWilliamson… https://t.co/UlAilnlKGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viking_hage @ThatEricAlper @AAMcLane I don’t know why I thought he won that, maybe I just thought he deserved it ! 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BismoFunyuns16 @JoeGiglioSports WINNING puts butts in the seats! This team will be legit, unlike last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blustery Saturday. Strong Records. @ Evansville, Vermont https://t.co/cWzcthJAEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Become the person you were always meant to be.  #TeamNoBoundaries #TeamSkysTheLimit #Entrepreneur #BeYourOwnBoss… https://t.co/NYF5Dw0uut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@middlebrooks @Phillies @CMBaseball41 @JimmyRollins11 @BobKellyAbreu Hahahah factual]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bishop Canevin leads Maplewood 61-34 at the 3:48 fourth quarter media timeout. @maplewoodtigers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackrepublican @DrOakley1689 @BarackObama Your “lily white” reference shows who the real racist is. Imagine someo… https://t.co/chWl6nTskz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majornelson Been a while since I have play DMC so I am just going to go with Dante because he is the main one I re… https://t.co/vSQEqWI0jS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #SanAntonio, TX? https://t.co/rqi3Dae4Fz #TopWorkplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickrizzo Rethinking this, I didn’t take into consideration PS 207 is the only polling place in the “New Howard” s… https://t.co/JCUdAimRBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatKidDeals Anything for a butane torch or a cheap office/gaming chair?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I feel too fat, I watch #my600lblife and then I feel better... 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día mis amigos y amigas que tengan un excelente día martes en New York, New York https://t.co/RpwQ6MTl6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrafficServices @TPSTrafficDC @TorontoPolice @TO_Transport @TPScott_baptist @CP24 @CityNews @TIRFCANADA… https://t.co/Q4dyPpYa9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my small town, there used to be a small health clinic. It’s gone now, but somebody twitter-labeled the location… https://t.co/PHLec11gVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stay Puft by @Ricketybeer @ Rickety Cricket Brewing — https://t.co/cL1W9ErAxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imillhiser @AOC &amp; she communicates her approach beautifully &amp; persuasively #BreathOfFreshHair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieWalton @Destado1 I feel like we do more for Rockstar games casually on twitter than the Russian bots on all s… https://t.co/WYo4Vyq9ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you want the best for whatever you cook I love too put some Urban Q Seasoning on it the taste buds go cray cra… https://t.co/0KNtloKyoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danawhite when Woodley finally lost 😂🍾🕺🕺✌ #UFC235 @ufc https://t.co/s5wfazck51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manfordou @ASPphysician No you are a perfect specimen of a human being]]></document><document><![CDATA[SENIOR CLASS PORTRAIT📸 Tuesday, March 12 8:15 a.m.  -  Gym Don’t be late! Any senior girl that would like to design… https://t.co/5Ryhi8iJuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gutterXcheese No lie I thought that was you in the gif 😂 go use some moth wash bruh 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning family: Move it, stretch it, nourish it, hydrate it, pay attention to it. The better our bodies feel,… https://t.co/6q0o03EUKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You should have stayed inside... Clown... Signing checks.. Lying your ass off... Most guilty people… https://t.co/pgxLuxzX9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc @Accenture And There Goes JOBS For AI Or Artificial Intelligence!? You See, This Earth Is One Big Experimen… https://t.co/mSLkr4R0Ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inaugura secretario de Economía, V Foro Voz Empresarial https://t.co/dW21SbyYL7 @kioscomayor @hanayagrafison… https://t.co/qDOLC9ETHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuagates so why couldn’t the Bhutanese gentleman show you on the map where the region was?  Maybe show the loca… https://t.co/8Uy8ctAEDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Before we leave we are going to win a National Championship”- Madi Williams #Sooners]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden and Sanders lead new poll of 2020 Democrats. But it’s still super early. https://t.co/cYSwoRT3KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathieRocks Never too late to figure it out. You could start with gratitude.. gratitude that you live in a country… https://t.co/PiraqrFlPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #StargateRewatch continues with Atlantis 5x07 “Whispers”... definitely one of the more horror inspired episodes.… https://t.co/nX797b2cE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nipomo had a real show that day. The parking where I work on frontage road was Buried in ice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @byzantineicon The woman who seemed to be flashing White Power gang signs was Zina Bash, a former Kav… https://t.co/Ezj0LxeU4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylie_diehl Such a sucker .... get it .... cause the song is .... yea you get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if any #CPAC attendees ever look around and say, “Man, that dude is fucked up. And that one and that one,… https://t.co/DLkEWSOVb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roar, a great hammered brass lion face ring handles footed cache pot 13x9x6.5H $78.00 #accessories #decor #design… https://t.co/d7RbxXi6P5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never really think about my age too much anymore. You can’t stop what’s coming, might as well attack it. @ Crunch F… https://t.co/lt67M9Eo1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @RandallCRP216 @yaf Spent time at the ranch while stationed out west in the mid 80's.. AWESOME place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI LeBron Stans.  You continue to look the other direction with evidence like this. This dude gives up. But yeah,… https://t.co/K1FGP7rGwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c0cainecourt  ONE OF THA HARDEST UNDERGROUND ARTISTS N HOUSTON 💪🏽 CHEC ME OUT 👀👂 🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥 https://t.co/5lXDge7pdq 🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥🚨🔥🧨💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to watch his show all the time as a kid. This has made me truly sad 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're back! @SupercrossLIVE returns to @MBStadium TOMORROW -- but I'm hanging with racers Kyle Swanson &amp;… https://t.co/mV8dV9uFlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @frozensooner @J_Dot_J God I admire you... https://t.co/h2l76hJGVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadGamerSwiss @VCU_Hoops @BostonChildrens @RobbyVCU @VCULitos @910TheFan Great work fellow Ram! I’ll take a season split]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Governor @RoyCooperNC I hope to see the @NHLCanes in the playoffs. Especially if you they knock out Montreal ;)… https://t.co/5H2z4Qx2MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chill Sunday • Hope everyone been having a great weekend! • • • Partners🎮 _____________________ limitedtimestruggle… https://t.co/6bpRZlgRV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @VP Reputation, faith, integrity and patriotism thrown away because of @realDonaldTrump . You betrayed your country]]></document></documents></author>