<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thanks @shay_1715 for getting us on TV! What a blast! @OU_Softball #homerunfest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow… https://t.co/FszA3ARQd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t necessarily want @RandallKingBand to get sick today, but considering I can’t be in two places at once, I wo… https://t.co/iL2ktfYe17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyBorn I’m pretty positive I’m the only one from my graduating class that isn’t engaged, married, or a mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Did  you actually say PRESIDENT OBAMA got away with murder? FOX FAKE NEWS SEEMS TO THINK SO? GUESS I am ho… https://t.co/CLcEL1mD8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein A cult reacts to truth, like a vampire shrieks at daylight!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khoggardGRT @CristinaDajero @ILBeachLMS @EALewis2016 @nmgarzia @MsHoioos @asdajero @MartinGrade3 @NataliShultz… https://t.co/FbHjnPo77G]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing the way jordan interacts with children literally melts my heart 😩🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btwb why isn’t this deadlift showing up in the overall list!’v https://t.co/g821FmzN4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Isaac sowed in that land and reaped in the same year a hundredfold. The LORD blessed him, https://t.co/4ZaUfstqdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a small disagreement with my mom and now she’s not feeding me lmao what 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TiffanyDCross makes sense! Basically said if you're still swinging between Trump and the Democrats are you really… https://t.co/08AnlY7E0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember you could go into any footlocker when I was in high school and get 2 pairs of high top reebok classics f… https://t.co/RWv3n3Mz38]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸This Offer Only For U.S.A👌 Get $1000 Visa Gift Card Now!👉 To get a  free $1000 click on the below given link and… https://t.co/gp7mvY0Lia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estas ocupado dudando de ti misma, mientras muchas personas se sienten intimidadas por tu potencial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman Democrat Rep. Ayanna Pressley Pushes for Impeachment https://t.co/gdqKeRDu1R via @BreitbartNews Crazy has… https://t.co/0cJSajZGGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chewie &amp; Princess Leia on the #binaryblanket from @thinkgeek 😊 @ Monterey Park, California https://t.co/ljWtIGH6Dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AusIndiMedia @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump It will be OK, if you want to trust somebody trust Donald Trump. Because… https://t.co/An7i1kbNDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfreewright  What , Trump betting on Buffalo Bob ? Boy Howdy, that is low .🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[More details on the @manifdart bus tour I mentioned on @CBCBreakaway : https://t.co/Hl8ofUANgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of sandpipers on the beach today. #SashaInPCB #VisitFlorida #travel #PanamaCityBeach #Florida https://t.co/pUM7TF7bp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least he committed to going to prom early. @ Men's Wearhouse https://t.co/8SWfGnCVVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo baby daddy favorite trapper ❤️ #pettigatez @ The Cheesecake Factory https://t.co/wlyLib5dw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I have accepted a challenge to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews- just the cover.… https://t.co/zdBrO45Hpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't amazing that our president is concerned about the security and safety of American citizens and uses "national… https://t.co/Vq8S21QBwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Volpe_Renard That is so amazingly special. You should tell him your gender is blood player. :P]]></document><document><![CDATA[All time high of 66 lay leaders this year!! @wnet brought four Friends board members, two @macaulayhonors students,… https://t.co/Oo44oHBTFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lady parked next to me.. and her car had a huge sign saying “ defund planned parenthood “ ad a whole bunch of cro… https://t.co/VOhwyXDyqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching this, Im literally going to return the makeup I bought today for ELF! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t have a little sister you’re really missing out, bc mine is my world 👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic #shaunmichaelphotos #nude #sexy #chicagomodel https://t.co/Zw0WA71XYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum I’ve worn one—a replica of course. I really don’t mind them; it does help remind your of your post… https://t.co/3AY1mNVs7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeroesToday I don’t know his context but it was inappropriate &amp; frightening on any level. John Cornyn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irianazavala Ugggh I could’ve been done with this assignment an hour ago but here I am on Twitter 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loudlearning Great perspective from the main character for us educators to really listen too.  Loved this book!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this to my friends every time they leave my house but do I ever hear it when I leave theirs? Absolutely not b… https://t.co/rpo1ss5EqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luOliveira30 This it's a little of what I love!... Reading, transport's me to far away places!.(love yours!). Hi L… https://t.co/8JoirihLsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly this is the most ridiculous justification I've seen and I remember the #Watergate hearings.  I swear I was… https://t.co/UmxNkADBVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smichaels1989 @Brandon47162193 @danacass61 @LTheresistance @AndreBreillatt Oh, justice  is going to be served, all… https://t.co/OfcF0NKPfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancykoppdw @JanineSneed She really is awesome and we need more leaders that think of the many not the only. Thx @JanineSneed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afterschool STEM building index card towers @MtHopeNanjemoy @melinda_mwright https://t.co/Qk88c4KZyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson They have gotten away with interfering with your Presidency for waaay to long! Put them ALL behind bars!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s only one sure way to ruin a night that was going this good and that is Perth by Bon Iver coming in shuffle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilMakhija @hollyotterbein Could it be because he already had a following and they started clicking to see his announcement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuddling with my beebs!  I feel like Landon SO looks like Rob when he was this age!  😭💙🧒🏻 #Landon #love #paraunting… https://t.co/sDgQGYKKrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arey nina vedini evariki aina chupinchandi ra Babu . Elane vadileste Andhra Pradesh lo prajalu bathakaleru.… https://t.co/8AAuNcyIL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[After @Boston_CM I started walking in the same direction as a woman who just finished up #UX studies at GA. Interes… https://t.co/StvpLD6Fil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldorco1 This is one of the most tragic days in American legal history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow Pop Comedy Show The Laugh Factory - Hollywood #losangeles #rainbow #comedy Discount Tickets:… https://t.co/u2zDZBVT4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Thursday! Poor Knox was wishing hard for a snow day lol! As I snuggle my littlest monkey, I cannot believe she… https://t.co/DFBRUdrq6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so easy to swim in the negativity and drown in it but being positive and spreading that positivity feels so mu… https://t.co/qcZmjiC9kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz Yes, pretty much every single day. I mean, look at these two. How is this even possible? https://t.co/J4EGncrhmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IRBroadshow @IngrahamAngle @JobCreatorsUSA @AOC Let them think we have no power. Stay surprising them with the power of community. 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case you think it is a lie: La Verdad-The True Network, un canal que transmitirá por cable e internet y que… https://t.co/G7y7Hq5AX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earn $10 in 10 Minutes by Completing These Free &amp; Easy Offers https://t.co/ybLWDhMBac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllisComms @boomboomtunes Organic sweet almond oil - I have an article coming out hopefully soon about all of this… https://t.co/mh5W8kErLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furtogo @cspanwj Pay $20K a year and you don't have to go to prison? Crime does pay...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heathercampbell Sending strength and ❤️ to you. One breast cancer survivor to another]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhssoccerweigh1 @BHSWomenSoccer @BashaSpiritline Well, look at them....of course they did!  Great job ladies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’d that shorty get so wicked??⠀ WTFYMT⠀ 🌬🌊⠀ *l I n k I n b I o* 🔊⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀ ⠀ #sf4l #anxietymusic… https://t.co/vj3DD4SKY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregpmiller "Addled, fixated on immigrants and racist" were known things about Sessions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who gave @BoomboxCartel permission to go so hard last night?! Without a doubt one of the best shows I’ve been to in… https://t.co/O6vi7uxFSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeggyBrava Things are going to drop everyday now https://t.co/xZiUkEyC4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[As @GUEnergyLabs likes to say, #EatingIsTraining. I sure hope this qualifies. Today’s @USMilitaryES ride was all a/… https://t.co/L1nF4m3mgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would just like to point out that a couple of Alder's recent CBC Athletes of the Month said they wished they had… https://t.co/tLpQYo47v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve finished studying for my last midterm and now I don’t know what to do with myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh why do only weird ass morherfuckers message me https://t.co/Ce7o790z8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m drunk at my best friends house and my gf is coming to pick me up, i could cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day drinking with the fam in Chicago! - Drinking a Resillience Butte County Proud by @empirebrew at @3floyds  — https://t.co/wDeIOIhtzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to learn all the words by Saturday night...thought all along @JonTLangston wanted to play spin the bottle (w… https://t.co/ybpojfVNMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜🥚🐇🥚 Ends 7/31/19 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilsimmons Not any more 40 50° tomorrow cannot wait perfect temp, not to hot ☀️🔥not to cold⛄☃️❄️⛄⛄☃️❄️❄️ yeah, Saturday!!!🐞🥀🌹💮🌻🌸🌱🏵️🌴🌲🌻🐝🌷🌼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t leave the gym until I finish this choreo. I woke up this morning and just knew I had to go if I was going t… https://t.co/GhQqNwWMzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supposed to be going out but I think ima sit tonight out I’m mfn tiedddd, ive been out every night since last Thursday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just hate when you pour that coffee you’ve been dying for, but put it down and promptly forget about it.  #needcoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davido222 Surely not me. My husband was at an airport somewhere in the world and that group was waiting for their… https://t.co/CJcZ9cgX0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Verizon -… https://t.co/L1yb8O6AeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[More positive news on Dad. Earlier this week, things looked bad, but doctors and nurses did an amazing job helping him turn around!]]></document><document><![CDATA[... and said to him, “Go throughout the city of Jerusalem and put a mark on the foreheads of those who grieve and l… https://t.co/LKoDrVlrvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profblake This is great. I’m going to NICAR in two weeks. You’ll be proud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janet this brilliant and  oh so clever! 👏👏👏👏👏👏  FB good lady. Thanks. 🌴😎🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[No time to have had a blessed day and then come home to my mom being mad... nope negativity out I’ll be in my room 🤷🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniJoyceTV @FOX29philly He will be flat broke again in no time at all.....Shame he won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Look at these wonderful Christians...Praise The Lord https://t.co/5gPJiKCg4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así o más fácil de leer??? Pareciera que eso es lo que se pregunta el director al palpar en sus manos el primer nue… https://t.co/1g4bDNpCmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to curl up with a blanket and take a nap...... but I guess someone has to make some money around here 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Happy!! Thank you so much @TinekeBrunfaut for your support and guidance!  #TIRF #LTRC2019  @LU_LanguageTest… https://t.co/V2aTkx1qmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stormthephoenix @BeautyAbounds4U @jeppsaddison @Dax_x98 @Tiffany61662071 @julesp__ @jenniferflynn @traceyecorder… https://t.co/QdomxQvyap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized homeless dogs don’t even know they are homeless and that’s why I’m gunna sleep better at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then at 6:30 when the alarm went off they lost their shit and tore up everything. I was awake just laying in bed li… https://t.co/IuP1ehqF0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the hamster wheel but it forces me to work on my endurance. My time would have been better, however there wa… https://t.co/6jy17lAifB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home on the #TTC 😎  Day 2 of #CapesForKids is almost done, but there’s still time to donate!… https://t.co/kRdPvq10Oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought HEAVYWEIGHTS on YouTube for $9.99 So I can watch it whenever I want and I feel so incredibly great about t… https://t.co/yvYlZNLQdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodBlessYou_YaH  @Esther188rod  THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH GOD BLESS ALL OF US IN THESE VIOLENT WORLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomMila @balbuen5 @goodenough_fu @HWolson @CMX9NujRcQvVVwW @Dzsozi22 @KandutschP @0_werewolf_0 @VixenVegas… https://t.co/iL7i1GtkyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last one to leave and first one to get here. Happy hump day! #2tensalon #aledo #humpday #bangs #oops #hairstyles @… https://t.co/0C7y3LHOFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RealCandaceO @BreitbartNews @JudgeJeanine @JudicialWatch @JudgeJeanine @kimguilfoyle… https://t.co/RP1iEtKK60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Wow. This president is so horrifying. Kim has hundreds of thousands in concentration camps, he tortures,… https://t.co/st7YDT6FUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr And who investigates the investigators who investigate the investigators?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingAlonah @GabrielaSpoken @xxhaley95lynnxx @marlenrey05 @PumpkinButt458 @grandegarza @JeffreeStar @claires And I… https://t.co/S9ru7Y0eOs]]></document></documents></author>