<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I rather go through it and do it until it gets right then give up that’s a sucka move]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broncos could do much worse.  https://t.co/349uH2UaXL https://t.co/k2XaXUwxJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #story at #instagram Gerardo_amparo #followme #fashion #fashiondesigner #sketchart #designer #artist… https://t.co/zfMm3IFKVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s fun when life constantly reminds you of the things you were forced to let go of..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheS_Squared Whenever we meet up for drinks will we be the Two Lucilles? https://t.co/uFtY0d9LeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s Sarah Davenport’s daughter and Kennedy is her aunt? I think? Girl it’s a huge family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRCAnews There's a red light burned out at the intersection of Highlands Ranch Pkwy and Foothills Canyon (by Westr… https://t.co/ZoE58KpfwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TulsiGabbard - The Establishment Is Desperate To Stop Anti-War Candidat... https://t.co/X0r0HhpyCn #elections #Election2020 #Syria #Assad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to “teeing” up a positive view... just 25 days to Spring! ⛳️ @ Blue Hill Country Club https://t.co/0Jucv9JBCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[therealbobbypinson is the truth.  Never did I ever think I'd be at a #nationalwildturkeyfederation event, ha.  Yall… https://t.co/AtVG5O49M0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelStudios @brielarson @phoebe_bridgers why does this look like you lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxyabrams Called it!!! much love for you two!!! Im just so happy to see you happy ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is a day that we should really show our love for the women in our lives, they really run the world! I can’t e… https://t.co/aSw7LxNLJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulldogs face tall task at No. 5 Tennessee https://t.co/jMOW1ptWVS via @DJournalnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[So to summarize. It’s cool to go all lumberjack on someone’s head, as long as you don’t do it twice. Then Player Sa… https://t.co/zjY3MZoBow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgement that something else is more important than fear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoonbowMusic @aerielist Not even just sharing, music in general. That shit is bigger and greater than any of us..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonLifthill @KP_Omaha New rule this year “player safety” doesn’t matter where the pitch is IF he is determined to… https://t.co/lKr9Cq5U2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy @OliverMcGee @TheAcademy @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulMiller1313 @RobertFeder @CumulusMedia @SteveDahlShow The podcast is still around and still great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secret shopping once again. Let’s see how we do. 🕵🏻‍♂️  Clean 👍 Quiet 👍 Pleasant welcome 👍 MyChart brochures 👍 Easy… https://t.co/W40xMezqcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m delirious but I feel so grateful; my life is okay right now.  I have a great job, I’m going to school for somet… https://t.co/Bdf4B9PENj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIPharmacists it was an honor to present ‘Food First’ today! Thank you for having us. More pics to come @GCFBGERRY… https://t.co/Mk8Mf0pmOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevinparisien @SeanNicholasJay @BillRatchet Yo lemme come try em all when the collection is finished lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEWS4_NICK @news4buffalo Both? Something happened to that ankle too (you’d think) https://t.co/R8z8Iy9Y7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megmyers  @ALT987fm #WomenWhoRock 🤟🏼 #IWD #MegMyers ❤️💚💙 https://t.co/YuHB9BrISk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I have a pretty good feeling about leaving @ValleyHoops in attendance for the third straight year next season… https://t.co/v01RvOWXDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TroySoccer hosts @rialtoathletics in the #CIFSoccer Final.  Saturday February 23 at La Habra High School Stadium.… https://t.co/u64sanHC35]]></document><document><![CDATA[The room ah be absolutely silent and I’ll just start screaming   IM FROM THE FYE MIDDLE FINGER ZONE 6 DIRTY LAND DIRTY STICKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailed on we’re going to get Millwall or Brighton if we do the business on Sunday.   #FACup #CPFC 🦅🔴🔵⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years off my spring was wasted on playing south Fayette baseball🤦🏾‍♂️🥶favoritism is real🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️#peace✌🏾✌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me for the @garcesfound #ThinkLocalGiveLocal benefit on Friday, 3/29 at the loewsphiladelphia. Use the… https://t.co/iQVPsXVqQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the takeaway. Zion is worth hundreds of millions as a pro. The knee injury is secondary to the fact that tho… https://t.co/ffCJA4KCQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AOC @RepAOC SANDY! You’re a fraud, a hypocrite &amp; a liar! @SenMarkey @SpeakerPelosi https://t.co/WXuS6eNMuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazSibley @orlandoderby @OrlandoCitySC I recorded the game.the assistant had “oily “ shinny sweat this is a sign o… https://t.co/jOMogDopZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TiUhUmf1T1  https://t.co/PdOZmNO1kj  https://t.co/BkE0vXzCCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blanca . . . #quintarealmonterrey #quintareal #fujixpro2 #23mmf2 #xphotographer #classicchrome #weddingsession en Q… https://t.co/txyRfMfp4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will rock my James Johnson or Tyler Johnson Heat Jersey but tell people it's actually Joe Johnson 👁️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man does not care about the truth and will misuse or misread anything to further his leftist agenda! The sades… https://t.co/duCd9IbXNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ronnie2K Pretty soon guards are gonna be extinct. Big men doing what guards are doing on top of being 6’9+ 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen “God's Not Dead: A Light in Darkness” on Netflix yet?  https://t.co/MhCJtAQYH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clover54Draves I enrolled inethe ACA.I kept my Dr.  No one ever suggested otherwise. Obama didn’t lie to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One or the otha? Which juan yall got? #boxingallday #boxing #juan? #whydidntyoujustputone #oneortheotha… https://t.co/D82Hgm78Pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taymarieluhv Idgaf what ya say, but this white boy is making bank...cuz been on every Kidz Bop song...]]></document><document><![CDATA[for real girl who said corp dick isn’t that good, if you’re reading this i have some ... personal testimony to support your cause]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOT ME! I DON'T BELIEVE PROVEN LIARS! AND COHEN IS PROVEN TO BE THE BIGGEST LIAR IN NEW YOUR! WELL MAYBE AOC, BUT S… https://t.co/4HVSoB5srr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you *can* do 24/96 output on the iPhone if you really feel like you need that in your life. https://t.co/ij5l7tL9ER]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think my mom tried to get me to move back in with her bc she lowkey misses this stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get why are approach to make people use less plastic bags was to make thicker bags and charge for them inst… https://t.co/YuKZssLvAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KOB4 @KaiPorterKOB That's why they eat TIDE poses snort condemns n play dead!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyRhodes I loved this gimmick although I assume that mask was uncomfortable. Great vest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Louis_Tomlinson do u still like one tree hill?? i rewatch it all the time bc its my all time favorite show so i need to know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up. @A_Train_92 story time. His height test and somehow Rex Ryan is part of the story. Next on @ESPN690Jax   https://t.co/KP6A34OU6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones @NYTmag @MeekMill Thank you @nhannahjones! Definitely using this today to facilitate conversation wit… https://t.co/Mp20RxrNsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockerTeacher @NomikiKonst Did she stand with Sarandon/Stein in their general election effort to elect Trump? That would be disqualifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fightoracle @Benaskren Don't think it'll be anyone on that list. He'll be offered to rematch Robbie and probably t… https://t.co/w1QCOo8Dhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmorris Ru gonna be the mortiis of dance music? Leskeddit my mans https://t.co/6DWPTe44Je]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bookstagram #bookworm #booklover #fairytales #bookgeek #bookstagrammer #bookseries #writersofinstagram… https://t.co/igvF6LlmRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see why my cousin left these 5 IPA’s here 🤢 still got the job done though 🕺🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodness gracious. A man of @RealJeffCobb’s size able to do a kip-up into an immediate standing moonsault... so muc… https://t.co/B2ALic1NJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intimidation, Pressure and Humiliation: Inside Trump’s Two-Year War on the Investigations Encircling Him https://t.co/LeGoxtcWbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find the strangest, but coolest things when I'm bored and tired late a night.  https://t.co/AIfSg9Uemw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If The United States completely stops using all types of pollution causing products it will make no differences in… https://t.co/3sFpCyorzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDr0bot At a certain point that won’t be the case. Hence why they want an hq2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAPellessier @NJTRANSIT @NYC_Patch @Amtrak Thanks so much - glad you made it. Was there any indication anyone was hurt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[is this girl ever gonna go to sleep? 🤦🏽‍♀️ why you gotta keep me up like this? https://t.co/iFJ9k6RQVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay. @ladygaga has her Oscar. I can sleep now. https://t.co/DETILcOX7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love in an elevator! Perfect for Valentines Day! . . . . . . . #love #sex #sexy #ménage à trois #threesome… https://t.co/T48J7FInyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's supposed to snow, and I didn't run out to buy milk. Whatever will I do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought this commentary on a passage I read in Isaiah yesterday was on point. https://t.co/yFxsDjdPur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just shared a nice #GoDeacs with Muggsy Bogues at CLT. One of my favorite Deacons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's all take a moment to remember we won't be able to eat this delicious concoction all week. #oatmeal #cinnamon… https://t.co/OVzLFeiV4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Academic Excellence!!! Proud of areyousurethisisrael for working hard at school! This kid is brilliant with a brigh… https://t.co/KMbSeDzPKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradford Lott crossed 5K. Time 00:32:51, pace 10:35 min/mile, est. finish 7:56 am https://t.co/GsK0HTG9PB #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAIFANESMEX Heridos Su Nuevo Sencillo Este Domingo 10 De Marzo En Mellow Rock De Radio Fabulosa 102.1 Fm En San Pe… https://t.co/oZH0hsCOKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[refreshing game cast every 5 seconds for @HokiesMBB game updates is not me living my best life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blayne_ferguson @medellinemil @RyanAFournier Agree that both parties are full of shit. But when you’re taking abou… https://t.co/JaB7DgCEp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllisGreggs @BizballMaury @TheRealP_O Probably TV.  the entire country is getting older and any mass reach sport l… https://t.co/OXEexQuT1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREP SOFTBALL (FINAL): Odessa High defeated Hereford, 11-0, to start Day 2 of the West Texas Classic in Midland. OH… https://t.co/4uqGEVIobc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You niggas get this through ya head nigga ion fwy you just here bc my partna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leeazareel @lcdo_raul @LuisRiveraMarin @SecEducacionPR Aquí hubo algo más que me da la impresión que no quieren revelar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Duke practice tomorrow. #BigBaller @bigballerbrand https://t.co/yhN63UHnVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought a few shares of $jnug! So now im invested in gold, Real estate, streaming, and cannibus. #StockMarket #stocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA @MBTA_CR  one of the readers stops working each day around 11am as it is no longer exposed to sunlight. https://t.co/wV3jA3myWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to chose a player who wasn’t ranked too too high either cause I thought that was mainstream, he was ranked 2… https://t.co/Cg9tyEAhO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preocupense en emigrar, luego cuando caiga el gobierno se regresan, pero no se puede seguir esperando por politicos… https://t.co/IEN8qfUwuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STONESXTHROW I watched him dominate a guy who could beat the shit out of me with one finger, he’s such a fucking m… https://t.co/PkfrCkZg7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nightislaw GIR to me is a golf term. Stands for Greens In Regulation.   You got your nerdy ass DDR lingo, I got my golf shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep thinking the same. The very ppl who keep Trump, McConnell, Grassley and crew in office are the ones who suff… https://t.co/2tvMiLqOfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@e_fletch9 @GaryBedore Lol... I forgot about this.   Wish i had been wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PigCakee @chrisramsay52 This isn’t the best answer, it’s the only answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @mkraju Sweet Irony. CNN wanders slightly back into journalism, and look what they get from CAIR's pit bull. Popcorn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaddenX You guys are just as bad as the Steelers with this drama and fighting like high school children. For s… https://t.co/nd19KnIMRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC Vs Marvel who wins outright, DC TV Series to me are much better than Marvel TV Series, but when it comes to Cine… https://t.co/PJOmTOtVGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Islam is not incompatible with free and open Western secular democracies.”  •Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, Ottawa,… https://t.co/7fkcTDse8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael Si tú sabías todo eso x qué lo candidatizaste y con fraude lo hiciste Presidente? Caretuco hdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheesecake’s mini baguette “brown bread” is now available... My life has changed 😭 #CheesecakeFactory 🍞 🥖 https://t.co/anRFBYbApr]]></document><document><![CDATA[sounds weird but i can’t wait till i am a husband and father, so as the father i can do things with my kids that i… https://t.co/B3tCVvdLCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlon_humphrey He didn’t deserve to be in the pro bowl. You know that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Don Jr posted on Instagram about how nobody cares about the Oscar's, but apparantly his dad does, so....]]></document></documents></author>