<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i never really understood dark skin jokes. like when people would make fun of someone in a picture cause they showe… https://t.co/4Ow6q5KZwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisDill @sstudieschic Sometimes it is not the Ss passion. Sometimes it is an activity that the parents require… https://t.co/gSxDbGNGa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW: Kamala Harris’ Father Goes PUBLIC With Shocking Family Secret That Could End Her 2020 Run https://t.co/C8tTx6jxJP via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finchfrii I bet he wishes he would’ve had judge Ellis - he might have gotten a commendation instead of a prison te… https://t.co/WNFUhw9tlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft and Ariana Grande have something in common. They both have 7 rings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was not prepared for Queen @Lupita_Nyongo entrance. I can't even tell you how I hope to one day raise #blackgirls… https://t.co/K68ZIOSUt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJDever @jkobopoli @elizabethkeefe @A4AOntario @MacLeodLisa @CBCQueensPark @randyhillier @Dean_French… https://t.co/Hk90RblIQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary Why, Trump's nominees all have conflicts of interest and your party votes them in anyway why bother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domojavobean Oh ya, well later in the night i May have tried to go into the bar and yell at a girl and Brett moved… https://t.co/8VywNWIyvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff Hey Traitor  We are watching you. You have to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i m  thaking  a word   I can't thak  abut  someing  i  need  to   cry  some    but  i   just  cape  it  in  i  just… https://t.co/m13Iefiz9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[blame it on the weatherrr, but I’m a mess, and this february darkness has me hating everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ann4252 @Iluvinspireu @karenslinn43 @MyEngland2016 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Collazo474 @ClockworkHamma @FRISEEMYRIAM… https://t.co/nzRCAupsRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManInTheHoody Maybe POTUS is giving out his version of an Oscar when he returns.  “Best performance in a congressional hearing”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @jaketapper @RickSantorum Well if he did not know about what was going on in his own dictator led country, he is a bad dictator!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahThyre Embarrassingly @dashboardmusic was the soundtrack of my teenage misunderstood years! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henthorne_chris @RedNationRising And Kevin Cramer. Scott and Cramer, ND were on their way to vote but did not get… https://t.co/Uljxaj8dyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsaSmith I won't question God but I will never understand why you let a 3, 5 and 6 year old go to the pool with… https://t.co/FBnK0rWsDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[yoooo the pants i bought the other day are perf for the pink long sleeve @thisisLANY cropped, i can see it now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimmyJoBrown @BuckeyeGirl_6 @teamwraith897 @JamieAllen121 @LostGirl08_LINZ @PinkFluff1888 @babygirl_0906… https://t.co/n4X8cP4591]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @ConradMbewe for ministering to our staff today at Children’s Hunger Fund! https://t.co/Iuc02H7YO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some high schooler at the gym just said “that Zac Efron guy” to his friend and the other kid looked at him like he… https://t.co/dgXwwuNk6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have the best AD ever... keeping us up to date on all the amazing accomplishments our Waterloo student athletes… https://t.co/sbPHcNgcTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the Lottery to win $30 tickets to #FreestyleLoveSupreme on @TodayTix! Enter here: https://t.co/cT4TbLKr65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaulaEvans @1Lavishone I have a joke that shocks people but I'll never stop doing it because i love it too much Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people are right in the white house every where enough is enough God is King of the heavens and earth everyon… https://t.co/0Kqzgi5Jge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selasa, tapi rasa capeknya kayak besok mau Jumat. Kalo dibayar hourly udah kaya nih gw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday from my #love My #officeview is so much more #beatiful now. #thankyoubaby #iloveyou 😍😍❤️❤️😘😘 @… https://t.co/dvO7DmYyXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chow downed some Chi Town Chinatown chinese. Try and wrap your egg roll around that 🥠 https://t.co/20Nijv1wwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean... I feel like the demons didn’t have her best interest. Why wouldn’t they recommend a BMW or Mercedes? 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 16, 2018: experienced an earthquake in Mexico City. That was a big one too. February 15, 2019: experienced… https://t.co/cAa5H53exZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered this for research for August! Already excited and we still have Sweden and Norway before! @ Washingt… https://t.co/gwpetXiPvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a @BenefitBeauty gimme brow +volumizing fiber gel sample in my February @birchbox and gotta day WOW 😮❤️❤️❤️#transformative]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavannahGuthrie @JennaBushHager @hodakotb @klgandhoda Congratulations Jenna!]]></document><document><![CDATA[shortys mixing corduroy and knit...where they do that at https://t.co/qldQYocrfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brant_spinks42 hey long time no talk  you have missed alot i just got out of prison and now i am in rehab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSalter55 @WhitfordBradley Say it again so those in the back can hear ya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @AmericanAir for this “exit row” seat three rows behind the actual exit row.  I guess Platinum status doesn’… https://t.co/o340sCbz4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[#REACTION Chick-fil-a has temporarily released a "Fish-fil-a" sandwich for lent! It's on sale now at select locatio… https://t.co/wEDSfVpdGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanorlean or did he even take it? perhaps he was just handed an acceptance. given his vocabulary list is merely… https://t.co/NepNLRJXk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will Shine ⭐️ #worlddayofsocialjustice • Listen now on all major music streaming platforms! #linkinbio . . . Pro… https://t.co/m1aJxMni3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolicOnion that's their problem and doubly so for whomever tries to make it mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the best thing about being back in AZ is riding the Bird scooters around campus...that literally what I get most excited about😂 🛴]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WorldBookDay   Don't miss this #Bestseller  "Lives up to the Hype!"  "The edge of your seat suspense at the end is… https://t.co/SUvHvGbrRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hroberson1Holly @Jenn_Garrick @LHSWildcatsLex1 Y’all are the cutest!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i care too much about people who don’t care about me and it always screws me over in the end]]></document><document><![CDATA[golden hour on the brooklyn bridge? YES PLS. 🤩🤩🤩 https://t.co/k6N3I7DKkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[♡Happy birthday, Kameron. These are some of my fave memories of the toddler days with you. Sweetest boy. And now, y… https://t.co/b4Xs3WHLNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeautybyLOVE #lashes   makeup @lmondayglam  3D mink Lashes @lmondayglam #dallasmua #atlanta #dallasmakeupartist… https://t.co/5lMCTs6zhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my last $4 to buy a stray dog a convenient store sandwich. Priorities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DNA test brings long lost sisters together https://t.co/OBMOO4c5VS via @YouTube My friend Jody found SIBLINGS!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just overhead @WaffleHouse “going to workout need to fuel up” Orders: scrambled eggs w/cheese, bacon, cheesy grits… https://t.co/C0PwyTW6wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickhealynyt In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Knees dictate health. Muscles reign supreme. Both government… https://t.co/1eR3Fne0uT]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦸🏼‍♀️DAY 3 Giveaway benefiting @bravegowns ! ... Enter to Win All 3 Days of Giveaways until 2/28... . Day 3 Prize P… https://t.co/bbg0YFK06h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LigaMexBeis Radio + Beisbol, me recuerda mucho a Jorge Vilches. Era un placer escuchar sus narraciones, cada atrap… https://t.co/y2o7ji7tze]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all fun &amp; games watching videos of girls drunk af acting a fool until it’s me lmaooo 😩😩😩😩😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surrounded by the people I love on this incredible night. From the bottom of my heart, thank you 🙏🏽 . . . . . . .… https://t.co/jx8qFLSH5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/khr6OUzzZF! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/pguNEf06Lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustineLavaworm I mean I don’t see how you can say that when Boston is still on this planet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freekurds1 @TamikaDMallory @IlhanMN Russia and Putin thank you for yours after Trump sold your ratty asses down the river]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @roads2 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Iluvinspireu @Peeperpea29 @MyEngland2016… https://t.co/8CtS8Tw33a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Love_Promise_S I cannot believe what we put in. I have to empty mine about every 2 weeks to see if there was somet… https://t.co/8Tkhcmo412]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemiCassiani @winewankers @amylieberfarb @_drazzari @pietrosd @LisaRivera2207 @SteveKubota @RoarLoudTravel… https://t.co/uBu5cSjqff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is she the only female but the only Pop Album! Whew 😭 she is WORKING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk They have been.  Told you 3 years ago, if they can't find a crime (And they won't) they will persis… https://t.co/d8O7kKDMGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachbue @CoachO2345 Sterling should have a 1-2-2 half court trap. They are allowing it. Widefield tried that agai… https://t.co/D7pCuxA1OO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoleoRafael Primero salida del usurpador , segundo gobierno de transición y tercero elecciones libres (después de elegir otro CNE ..)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember this @HouseGOP @SenateGOP what the @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems are doing, the hypocrisy of these people to… https://t.co/jT8edf9PcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Afraid not even they aren’t real news they are the trump news network and bs propaganda. Dems want to hea… https://t.co/td0VygvNVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite memorials. @greenwoodhf #greenwoodcemetery #aj_graveyards #graveyard_dead #grave_affair… https://t.co/3jdnLQHQ25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bedside is a bookcase full. I enjoy constantly refining my craft as a marketer. Just purchased  Content Inc by… https://t.co/IOVr8Pu0kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only wear makeup to work because I KNOW that no one cares enough to judge me or make fun of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaveyDaniel Me trying to stream #ColdinLA on every possible platform @whydontwemusic @corbynbesson @ImZachHerron… https://t.co/g0cjF3PuZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Smile Is The Prettiest Thing You Can Wear - Inspirational Quote for a girls, teen... https://t.co/Veyet2WiKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Look – the #WhiteHouse  Is Trying to  #Sneak Nuclear Tech to Saudi Arabia   #care2 https://t.co/F6VWEL0eyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happens so often! I've never seen a game get *worse* by cutting something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomOfAllCapes @8thBernardSS @icivics @BernardMiddle @MEHLVILLE1 My kids will be doing this Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also YES on positive portrayals of fathers and male faculty engaging in child care and supporting family balance. A… https://t.co/IkXOmaQuqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkline56 @rosered2020 @hoppinmama5 @trumpshappygirl @GeanineC @Jetsta812 @WandaWomanHere @Thom_Thom9 @mary_patriot… https://t.co/z6QA5haXxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recording it!! Watching @ufc right now and this Barberena v Luque fight is insane!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #EduGladiators Lisa. Assistant Principal in high school, from Georgia! #CoachAtHeart https://t.co/pFAVEOjXsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tobin Heath doing what she does best— attacking the line and slotting it in to Rapinoe to get the US their first go… https://t.co/YzzMgUAs6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenbholmes yes! for me the mrs. dalloway line i always go back to when i'm happy is "life; London; this moment i… https://t.co/efXXqWa76s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@That_gal_debbie @traytrayolay @shamichaa_ofwg Y’all KNOW I ain’t wrong tho 😭😭😂😂😂😂💀💀💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard Prime N Tender is being torn down. Remembering teen dance nights back in the day! PnT and Fields were the p… https://t.co/SeXFZiZJAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful, as always, to work with lawyers who let juniors do the fun stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimplecute06 @menggalurks @mainedcm Lourdes...y r u mad...??? If u dont buy  ...the product... dnt curse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send a valentine to a kid @ChildrensLA and help spread the love! $1 will be donated for every card sent, up to $25,… https://t.co/LtoemR2uLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole signing bibles thing is a pretty genius marketing tactic. If this fucker wins again...😡😤🙅🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#love #followback #instagramers #socialenvy #tweegram #photooftheday #20likes #amazing #smile #follow4follow… https://t.co/te6z5WA7qh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some would say my friends and I have a drinking problem https://t.co/0oTzfcy4RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[From: 40404 (1/3) @brandy1960: RT @coronilhartmann: #ServicioPúblico Se solicita con (2/3) carácter de URGENCIA Est… https://t.co/sgiK3kNTP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5SOSsafespace "Hold you tight straight through the day light, I'm right here, when you gonna realize That I'm your… https://t.co/czp8OAqVT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rehman_Callitri Okay, but the network and technology we offer is one of the best in the world though, so there’s t… https://t.co/5bomas7Lh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande I love you u r so fucking Cool and beautiful and sweet honest woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anas moms music just turned from Italian opera to bringing sexy back, we love diversity]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaracasVenezuela TONIGHT!! GOD help them!! Another tyrant who MUST be taken out!! 🙏😠💔😪😟🙏 #prayforvenezuela… https://t.co/FQvPGNfz3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkYuhnke Eh. He's last on my list... but if I'm wrong -- just put me on blast tomorrow.. I can take it 📢]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing I’m going to when I graduate, is take a nap. Probably on stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @redsteeze @xan_desanctis Over the weekend, I unfollowed Brian Cate because he made her tweet pop up o… https://t.co/aZvmoI9C9I]]></document></documents></author>