<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This illustration by yours truly comes to you from today's post in which you can read about at this link:… https://t.co/bqSnI9hYhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Women will crush you, you know? I suppose everybody hurts everybody, but women always seem to get back up, you eve… https://t.co/psmdPclYGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all starts this afternoon on @yesnetwork   1pm #bluejays #yankees #bethere @ George M. Steinbrenner Field https://t.co/fgEkD5yD1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just coming to this conclusion now???  Almost 3 years late!!! Descending the escalator like G-d. should have been a… https://t.co/VuNJrt9yUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProBootyLicker I did and shit got better but it’s a process brother I won’t be truly happy for a few years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMeister2013 @Storm_Nation @JBelmo You are entitled to your opinion. Two-handed bowlers are respected bowlers.… https://t.co/2HXRLrcBQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Makayla_Marie19 @LilRussianRook Omg it’s episode 17 and it’s the only one not on Hulu 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatWalkerWX @LRMarathon @GregYarbrough @WFLALeigh Thanks for the heads up!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating pedometers with #microbits @bbc .  #Makecode programs using variables allow the microbits to add up the “s… https://t.co/ixn46VobSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[✅Hair goals? 💇‍♀️ ✅Want to try MONAT?🙋‍♀️ ✅Be a Boss Babe💃💋 ✅Become a VIP! 👑🕶💖  One stop shop available now!… https://t.co/i5QPUSV3nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyred1956 @andrerucker51 @AlexLynn0096201 @CHHolte @cherokeesher2 @BarReNaples @girlsreallyrule @sunrainsunrain… https://t.co/VkZQQ0Gmat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is real powerful. How can “the team” be right when the “Team” is not right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to be scared to do a nigga how he did me ! Now I will FINISHHHHHH HIM💅🏽.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 10th 2019- I attended the the #Unicorn phresh off the runway fashion show looking for some diverse content… https://t.co/lVyXeKbDvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousNIK @maggieNYT Gives new possibility and definition to a parallel universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday  #womensday #women #nerd #geek #fandom #faith #faithandfandom #doctorwho #batman… https://t.co/cQnzlkTnuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @kwbmontessori to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Ea… https://t.co/ma8gOOBI1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueHenGaby Google Calendar and a notebook to jot stuff down when I’m not on my phone or laptop!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaFOXTV @Q_QSage @sqwigs @JimmyFalk5 @Chookchook8 @kimberlytoday @Timedabbler21 @DavidDMiller5 @DeltaTheBravo… https://t.co/J3Tg6GrnPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RODEOHOUSTON  had amazing experience  seing @lukecombs  for the first time in concert  sang my heart out and   cri… https://t.co/JL9bq32A6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOtherWoman__ If adults want this lifestyle, it’s their business, but I have a problem when they drag their chil… https://t.co/ZjFphuodMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwakenedAussie @JuliansRum Well at 4pm ET time you would tweet it at whatever time that coincides with 4Pm ET. For… https://t.co/jCU8eifcos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day! May we support each other’s crown daily with Love, empowerment, and respect. 3 yea… https://t.co/QRjVnIxHwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfox207 @JannardMarc McConnell,Graham,Gaetz,Jordan, Nunez Meadows have to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone swear they miss me now that i live out here all these old boo’s coming out like boy gone on this been ded]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_1Melanie1_ @flowerchild2017 @KathyDutton16 @brandiz2 @Mopor777 @GatorGirl675122 @Karrasamelia5 @WarriorAllways… https://t.co/FrIpUs4zyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been buying summer clothes since last summer ended. Ive got the fits]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning friends!!!! I’m back after a lovely long weekend away,  @JPaulWSOC9 and I are getting a breakdown of t… https://t.co/DwET1jE2YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of changing my page header picture.  Here's a poll so you can help me decide.  😀  (1 Of 2)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried out a new #MathAssessmentProject #FormativeAssessmentLesson thanks to my @MathforAmerica #PLT on representing… https://t.co/LIkM1mm19c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDeanCain Ah yes, I remember back in those days when I could jump also!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I regret going to sleep at 10 last night because it’s 5am and I’m wide awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[#C89robandmegan #mondayattheoffice Kitchen girls say hairnets r a must guys @ Crescent Park Lodge https://t.co/TAPdJpFZ9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeaChatham Sending you a #HIMSS19 Hug while experiencing FOMO. #HappyValentinesDay 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we use air horns more when they say nonsense? I might run for office if so...#reclaimingmytime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapiPeck @StephanieTC @CathyEKoehler @ElectTippi @Anointed08 @jdoyle916 @CityLittleRock @TriosLR Thanks Team Trio’… https://t.co/0CqhRKenSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cary_northrop @lauralucy2010 @mikepicone55 I just blocked him 🤷🏽‍♀️🤣 I didn’t even respond. Thanks for handling him for me 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bk502010Barb @RealSaavedra Nope she’s a complete moron; I’m Puertorican and I can’t stand her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @jonasbrothers I see you! I take back all the things I've said in the past, I get it now. What a way to mak… https://t.co/ZAEjVi9C3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaidegramer At this point it is 20 years later... and I don't know how to bring it up in any kind of conversation.… https://t.co/QtG2177AyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XplodingUnicorn I read the Adventures of Waffle to my recovery group. We all agreed that she could have a chair in… https://t.co/hbezpFFCmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th birthday to @P_russell11 I’ll still beat your ass no matter what age you are 😂😂😂 love you https://t.co/OcFmsGyJV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[the reality show of : Lorraine &amp; Camila &amp; Gabriella https://t.co/MX6rbcIx54]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for Friday it’s my favorite day of of the week I will take more pictures of me and chris this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solomon Ince completed the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! Time 02:26:19 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/72tkUh2Xbc #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just discovered @tylerperry’s #thehaveandhavenots. Nearly finished the 1st season. I like it, it’s addicting, BUT… https://t.co/vPHitdue19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love your tweets. I always rt as much as possible, you ladies are quite creative.  Best wishes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pnbrock literally tried to call you.. no answer lol I'm sad af😔  Add me on snap👻  @megan_faye12]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY happy happy 20TH birthday to my SMOKIN roomie @KaraPisczek 💕🔥I love you so much and I’m so blessed to have a… https://t.co/zopuKfljaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see someone using the pen you thought you loss https://t.co/SVjToocFjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! #breakfast @kindsnacks @GoodDayChoc https://t.co/OYMxsGhkAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having to cover my mouth laughing to avoid waking my roommate up 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[broooo i miss when servi was the move cause everybody se la pasaba aya ahora parecemos sardinas en botanero everyone and they momma here smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Stayed With A Man ThrouGh As MaNy Love SayiNg “His BS” You Don’t Then Get To Blame Him For That Choice! You… https://t.co/rF6PZT0x35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelleFletcher and @JRodgers11 YouTube channel is my new favorite thing. 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for waking me up Mother Earth. No more please, okay. #bluffdalequake19 https://t.co/vEkbhomVil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life Skill Class:  Quilting with Rosetta this Saturday, March 9th 10 am - 12 noon #quiltingclass #lifeskills… https://t.co/W8HBhuJofW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I smell your fear,  here in California. https://t.co/I6OfVua6A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeWhoWait1776WW @StormIsUponUs 😂 yes. Too wonderful. Grab them some Depends!]]></document><document><![CDATA[John THINKS he’s right but he is wrong this time. Go Big Blue! #Catscatscats https://t.co/SZ8JvkNM9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious snow prepping going on 😋. I made 👩🏽‍🍳 empanadas before the storm gets here 🌨❄️. We’ll be live on @FOX61News… https://t.co/IR7sAWA2sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t be Monday if I didn’t spill someone elses urine all over myself #nurselife #happymonday 😅🔫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swilkinsonbc And what you and so many others have been screaming is finally being heard...thank you @swilkinsonbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very Happy 42nd Birthday 🎂 to this awesome guy right here!!!!! STO LAT! I love you Radek! @ New Brunswick, New Je… https://t.co/2G5nqfGyHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duranduran Love the new setlist. Lucky me for getting to hear FOM live. Kill it again tomorrow night @SimonJCLeBON… https://t.co/mWnAkO6Swl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@londoncafe @ziamsvaIentine For real leave my babies alone gold diggers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bostoncitygirl @IvankaTrump The only people who follow gun laws are the already law abiding citizens. Do you reall… https://t.co/nuLHwuqJM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legallyfitt @bricesander @TeddiMellencamp @erikajayne @etnow All that proof she said she had was between her and him, not LVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @MorningsMaria @FoxBusiness @dagenmcdowell @WellsFargo Great Picture - #Fearless #WomenRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/l6lu4l7WW5. Please help the children with cancer and donate a few dollars for the Youth Cancer Basebal… https://t.co/64wxoGLoSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know what the world would look like if jamie lynn spears hadn’t gotten pregnant and ruined zoey 101]]></document><document><![CDATA[this dude really just said “alcohol causes rape!!”   and then in the thread goes onto say “i never said alcohol cau… https://t.co/2neFusJ19N]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #MKNaomi mindfuck was like a glove being turned inside out. The backup system that kicked in was beginning to f… https://t.co/qWVXRzGZkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTNHoller TN is a state of hate. The white men that inhabit those seats hate women,  the LGBTQ community, people… https://t.co/tIe9UWxvCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time we played Weslaco we lost 1-9. This time we came to play, but lost a tough game 6-7. Our  Lady Raiders ba… https://t.co/Gsmh0GwONK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m venting.  I have always believed that if you attend a game at another team’s arena you act respectful, cheering… https://t.co/c2t9N17xTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmigyanko @MatthewLillard Totally agreed! But Twin Peaks is a new legacy in itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made my first big adult purchase today, a 3,499$ mattress that I got for 949$ 😌❤️🛌💸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malucadua @BarbaraWatley @Jilliemary @robtropper @_____YO_____YO @guiller25136814 @khanhakim_k @reeves5150… https://t.co/LjbkLS20E2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dudes r really 6 ft or taller and I’m still chillin at 5’7.... how is that fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls Night Out was a success. Having fun and laughing with my best friend! 🍹 @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/UnzHLaT9TY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sukee_B @allisonceck @carlzimmer @DavidQuammen @Harvard such a small room! you're soo close 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your entree arrives and it's about equal parts friend tofu and crispy garlic, you KNOW it's going to be good.… https://t.co/JzCMTDx4S7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OurRevolution @AZguyTodd @BernieSanders He believes healthcare is a right to all people? Except newborn babies, Be… https://t.co/Q4UJLcNfAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BloqueadosS Ah de ser de tanto sedante que toma, no le veo otra explicación de porque habla así.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels Global warming my ass. It's March in Ohio and it's very cold. They call it climate change now]]></document><document><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY in effect until 9AM. We're bringing you live road conditions of the Triangle all morning on… https://t.co/OTytDBT725]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews No thanks we have had enough lies and attacks on our constitution. You are n… https://t.co/36hqbc2NvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefOfBcrk @EmonEconomist @kirasroth When you can't figure out that you're being abusive, sometimes you need to b… https://t.co/lRI6nrGWKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun show tonight thecomedyundergroundseattle 💚 I was excited to see my headshot on the wall, but way more ex… https://t.co/8O8Uwzu3Ml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I get asked “How do you stay motivated?!” “How are you so full of energy?!” The truth is, I’m not always.… https://t.co/sWvoCRdJaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wingsrme @TeaPainUSA I get that! But just saying it’s not worth it I don’t get unless she’s playing him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris Tonight's show is one the best I have seen you do. It was so special, informative. Wish 45 would wa… https://t.co/grHiCKmUGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day dispatcher comes in yesterday morning “what a morning! Friday’s, am I right?” Me “it’s Thursday”]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@houstonpolice are on the hunt this morning for the shooter who ‘ambushed’ a group of people fighting in the middl… https://t.co/PGzEYtjupR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all else fails, hug the dog.  Then read a book about a dog and come to our awesome book club! #Geneva304… https://t.co/byGHx4xJUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[just the bee's knees: My interview with a 3 year old. Great idea to do on... #humor #giggle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/eUAl6xaI4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Most people in Hollywood needs mental health help.  Need detox, counseling and need love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @FrGoyo Well, you could take a cake to him, or take him out for dinner or something!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow your dreams from wherever you are with whatever you’ve got. Gods got your back. #wednesdaywisdom #godsgotyou… https://t.co/0JvKhd4G2p]]></document></documents></author>