<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[¡Entre la recolección manual de semillas de #chilessecos y la elaboración de #chocolatemexicano, la #comidamexicana… https://t.co/8xLJXT6Cif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @PressSec @SecretaryCarson @RealBenCarson @NRA ¡Mentira! Solo menti… https://t.co/W7Z5NMmxrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtSAC_athletics El Camino College Warriors baseball team hosting Mt. SAC Mounties!#mountiesbaseball# https://t.co/zZGUsoTiOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love how twitter change it to a star when you like a tweet https://t.co/zTOT7qwb2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is honestly really funny when she sinks her teeth into the Presidential mushy dim-sum that is Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody can make this Shit up! Tucker are you Mentally Sane? Just wondering?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxyhedgehog @KennyCoble @bookmonger @danyakukafka @accidentaltheo 🖤 you Katie!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Negotiations aren’t going well; now, in addition to insisting that I pay for rides I never requested in countries I… https://t.co/brH5TB4BPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps the great negotiating  trumpy should go to Bombay.  Wait, he'll cause nuke war..  nevermind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting with Betty's son Buzz, our daughter-in-law Wendy, and grandchildren Jack, Olivia, &amp; Emma. https://t.co/gCRtcltKL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What radicalized you? For me i think it was sexual assault and the lack of response. Or maybe just poverty and bein… https://t.co/O5rHWmBlYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Dakich..who was playing? Purdue v Indiana?  Seemed like the Dakich show..the NCAA actually let's  this clown in… https://t.co/Uzu1jttO2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivanflowers34 @ABC7 I was dropping something on 23rd earlier and drove right past it as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJSnM @elonmusk @RocketTenor @NASA @SpaceX @Space_Station @Commercial_Crew If Dragon is their only option right no… https://t.co/YYXXLVW7Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN If you all are really serious to listen to a peacebuilder with a set of information theory designs that 15 mon… https://t.co/jD8VYfMVRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgreen you used my words, name, and likeness without my consent. Pay me for being in your advertising.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @stephencurry30  -  1992 to 2019. always repping the QC! #buzzcity #dcfor3     #nba #basketball #nfl… https://t.co/HWavQXpcXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we texted for a day or two and never talked again we never talked 💯 just had a friendly convo 😬😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJosephBurns @zerohedge I cannot remember the last time we saw a number that low. But, I am sure there will be som… https://t.co/vfMnIpFORk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a @FinalFour caliber team, USF HC Gregory about @UHCougarMBK @KPRC2 https://t.co/d5kardG9oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE DONT HAVE A PRESIDENT WE HAVE A MOB BOSS &amp; A LOWLIFE LOW IQ ASSHOLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[For UCLA to be this bad with all those built in recruiting advantages is just stunning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USWNT The game before THE GAME  #SheBelievesCup #SheBelieves #tricitiesunited #nissanstadium #USWNT https://t.co/MLc0Q30AvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayJunior!!! #HtownRush  @RussKHOU ⚓ @GreatDayDeborah 👠 @BrandiKHOU 🍷 @KHOUBlake11 🌤☀️ @KHOUStephanie 🚓🚗🚕… https://t.co/JxFRCaMgFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump The Clintons are the true Russian collusion who wrote the dossier just talk to inv… https://t.co/JFHuS1kLyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since @Dodgers released Matt Kemp and Yasiel Puig to afford a Bryce Harper/Manny Machado contract and failed to get… https://t.co/0MfwCVHhSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelgaVonAVick2 He said be easy Shelby you got this https://t.co/kHiQJMHLH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought 'Ruger Charger Takedown 22LR, 10" Threaded Barrel, SS Finish, Green Mtn Laminate' on Impact Guns https://t.co/YWNPdeI4Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - Edinburgh Old Town streets in traffic closure trial https://t.co/2PPZMtWtpj very sound city planning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargotParsons @pammoran We have been in this work for 3 years. We have had over 1,000 visits to our school to tour… https://t.co/y7J9reTcoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndbeingme I saw that you got Double or Nothing tickets! Would love to go. Happy for you! I'll be at WrestleCon bot… https://t.co/FDm6q1iFzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewzimmern Thank you soooo much for replying.  I love your shows and hope to one day meet you in person!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats and liberals, want to keep the borders open, for this crap, to come in!! Nope!! https://t.co/croMfwGptT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ailishlynch93 You betray them but glasses were always there for you, even when no one was]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trying to brag but I hit numerous 215 ft. Home runs with the CF4 @_boylingpoint]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bartman_john84 Lol some of the Michigan people were talking about making part of this a gif and use it every time… https://t.co/nGvGxDUPwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Democrats always standing in support of democracy and humanitarian relief in #Venezuela.  Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jess_Skel @SAPConcur @KimAlbrecht @fionaashley OMG. Four of my favorite people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnadilley @cvpayne here IS your #EnemyOfThePeople a #conman #Traitor we SALUTE .@FBI those who took their oath t… https://t.co/lM37vgfcIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day I wondered how New York state would be able to try Trump once he got out of office, based on evidence… https://t.co/1encgGc2Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright folks, this is it - the final countdown to #StMattysDay2019 - we are ONE WEEK away from rock, acapella, and… https://t.co/WVKUAHmXHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickMalambri just to be clear the 16 year old is not Faith (the girl in the stream), she is reading messages from… https://t.co/Rg4JExZ1UD]]></document><document><![CDATA[some people really be out here eating oyster on the half shell https://t.co/ewa4pMpLrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[and they wonder why we don’t listen 🤧 are any of these ever true ? Ever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicO_Suave03 Nah. Never would do that. Just joking about you talking about my drought. All good. Just playing, fam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like no one can hear me or just not interested in listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Yes as long as the  Trumps in the White House and Republicans control the U.S Senate and SCOTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great message that we educators need to remind our students of constantly! Persistence, Grit, Perseverance… https://t.co/GtXfAWAFom]]></document><document><![CDATA[more #powerful a #force for #good when we are  working together moving as one  more powerful together, as one servi… https://t.co/1CUZLDatlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key to #TimeTravel is being able to see patters, and drawing accurate conclusions. #Survivor #QuantumBreak… https://t.co/GVKjen7ZgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward to the day when a Democratic President declares a State of Emergency on gun violence and uses that p… https://t.co/wYJ7Q5vPUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my live stream: 'Garyvee Blockchain and Me' at https://t.co/txoAYiVxDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bred 4/11  Clay 350 v2  “Gucci” 4s Yzy bsktball   Just 2 of these this year and I’m good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A snowy ❄️ ⛄️ night in Vegas!! @ Enterprise, Nevada https://t.co/A9cGk4g2d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athletelogos @MetsMerized @mikemayerMMO This only would have happened if he played for the Brooklyn Dodgers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're an undercover cop on Staten Island , that's all cool and fine. Don't drive like a jerk off , make me beep… https://t.co/TEK6sRom0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turanchik repeats his plan to hire diversity +inslusion officer. The best way to handle “broad paella” that is Tampa, he says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That man Spade a problem 🤘🏾🤮  Section 8 video out now!!’  https://t.co/GcEitY6TQJ 💻💻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdb325 I don’t hate incubus by any means but 311 wins this one for me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertAWiseman @CanadensisMax I also recall Mulclair promised austerity and 2 double the anti on refugees and that… https://t.co/utOwICZg7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylynmarie27 You are honest about mental health. As a professor, it helps me better understand what my students go through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling @MikieSherrill But will it Pass the Senate in your opinion? (I don't care if Trump Vetoes it.  becaus… https://t.co/KAxFusOvF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakeRaMan @ColinCowherd Big facts! Goes a long way with the youngins around him definitely don't look connected an… https://t.co/fI47cGoVIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[صديقي الانتراوي انت الوحيد اللي ما يحتاج اترجملك https://t.co/2OYuSIx4Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just focused. New challenges, more motivation to achieve them. #WontStop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumanistReport @MyScarletFelony @SherrodBrown This is also, unfortunately, how the professional staff and "leaders… https://t.co/ejW2SEJ9kJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC We grew up poor, i continually worked hard and kept taking jobs that paid more, never went college, scraped en… https://t.co/fNKRslFdMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Privileged people say the dumbest things. Understand that all the stuff I have is because I earned it. I worked and… https://t.co/iJIC2vjD03]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful what you say. Just bc you not happy with your life doesn’t mean I’m not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a 29 year old guy doing sake bombs in his kitchen while his pregnant wife watches and laughs.  Happy Saturday.. Kanpai!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Cashman was asked about Bryce Harper/Manny Machado. He wouldn’t speak about them specifically but said: “I’m… https://t.co/x0KiQqzBmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be remiss if I didn’t acknowledge the Greatest wheelman of my generation. #forever3 https://t.co/lSCV1zOEEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, I think SuperButterBuns had the right idea.  I too am going to take a break from the Kingdom Hearts fando… https://t.co/7ThAj1IjUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottchaile @shaunking @BernieSanders Hillary has bern despised by a significant majority of the American people,… https://t.co/BNwpkpuM9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, there’s all my specific baggage from the fundygelical cult. But I also explained that there’s probably not… https://t.co/9Q8ofZYZsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love getting random messages asking me come play keeper tonight.  Of course I’m in, will be something different from playing over 30 co-Ed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brimstone. Bold statement, but a scent I'd associate more with work--torturing the sinners and pagans, haranguing t… https://t.co/TSFBVP0eYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my brother.  He keeps me in line.  Love you much bro.  Happy 22nd Birthday. bryancrhea @ Durham,… https://t.co/KHYGWdufL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon @CitizenK9s The wise person keeps the end in sight. In no case has this human body ever lasted. Why build a  house on a bridge?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Cibernéticos mis cojones  usan las tácticas cubanas para poner a la gente en miseria y hacerlos esclavos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking into the Nike store on Melrose in full Adidas gear to get FREE Nike merch from their Vending Machine is suc… https://t.co/YJRnvvsIBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times playing @PlayApex with @jsbodden tonight. Got my first three kills. Maybe next week we can get our first “W” buddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find the teams who are open and experimentative. Go to them and help them take their work even further.   Even as y… https://t.co/QeIEWuDu7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wildwood Flower by @TNBrewWorks at @HomegrownNash — https://t.co/QYnb2rAZCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaraSorrenti I’m venezuelan. I have friends that I will never see again because of Chavez, many of my friends hav… https://t.co/IXUyq3J2Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NelleNCCoops @LeadershipNC We missed having you with us and grateful to you for sharing @Lee_Ragsdale, Scott Saff,… https://t.co/cg8UtIjkAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[La función de Senadores y Diputados es pelear por mayor presupuesto para #Sonora, señaló el secretario del… https://t.co/QxE06uv1JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haley1Graves2 Just wanted to give you a quick  reminder of how many L’s y’all hold in November against LSU 🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssomers55 @halfie44 At this point it's really only battle rage imo, but that's an important one you can't replicat… https://t.co/RgVovDjmvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Buen_Miguel @Stru_Alexa @RaulBaduel Ella es venezolana hija de franceses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Sunday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍🌈☀️ https://t.co/dctxQt5NET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rememberruss I don’t think he imagines this at all. I think he was given a speech and forced to deliver it, but Eu… https://t.co/rJPHZNQTaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could watch gardening videos all day, I'm legit obsessed y'all  (Springtime in is almost here 😩👌)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moreover, when your fast from social media for Lent, do not be as the hypocrites who post they are giving up social… https://t.co/Y2RhUGImc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AholeBarbs @AOC @IlhanMN *Ilhan says racist things* gets called out by both sides... there, I fixed it for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even close to being a Marine.  The first day of Marine educator camp was incredible.  Words can’t describe what… https://t.co/xaNFtVrF8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to mentally train our mind like we physically train our body. Thoughts that keep you peaceful and happy sho… https://t.co/3QrTfDeQNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not love the world or the things of the world. If anyone loves the world, the love of the …… https://t.co/HQbc9DUIL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrwells82 I'm still trying to collect all the pieces for the Leprechaun village. In sure that will have one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiLHuvziVert Hate to do it to you, but tickets were only $20 more on average from last year. Both are top 10 teams… https://t.co/62ckJ7e1Cy]]></document></documents></author>