<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Thomas_comma_S @USFigureSkating @rockerskating @ISU_Figure Make @jasonbskates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherokeejmk @DonaldJTrumpJr @Kilgore_Trout2 I only apologize when I’m wrong 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10K23_  the energy my boyfriend gives me &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[...my daily routine is OFF, but I’m excited to get back to one with all of you at JAM tonight! 5:30pm!… https://t.co/WkZy6Ihr6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[L💓ving my daily @Natural_Life chirps! 💕🌈🐥 #SaturdayThoughts #dailymotivation https://t.co/oWLJBb5Xfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyBauer Who was follower #666? Maybe that’s who you should be scared of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinese deliverers be having stink ass attitudes nfs .. Now .. NO tip fuh yeu !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Social Work Appreciation Month to all of my fellow social workers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[MPA 2nd Grade living wax museum honoring Black History Month. Mr. Cooper was the 13th overall pick by the Boston Ce… https://t.co/GZImUTevpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You or someone you know living in Georgia and in a toxic relationship or are have you been feeling low about being… https://t.co/qY9avVpuxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rentonMagaUK @DontSalty No traveling make up artist? Money must be tight for the Clintons💰 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1 Kid's Earrings I have 2-Purple          2-Pink          2-Muti Color          4-Clear @ Mount Holly, North Carol… https://t.co/nC53wSJgZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[T o n i g h t  It’s Time to get “PUMPED” #hamburgermarysweho!  I’m so excited to be sharing the stage with such tal… https://t.co/XYwR9ea5fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my bby @robbxx2 ily the most ♥️💌 https://t.co/euinPM8p8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleismyna2 What? Death threats?? Are you serious 🤷🏻‍♀️ oh hell no!!! Not acceptable https://t.co/RRn7ZlMo4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zfree @MadisonSiriusXM Unfortunately we are losing freedom of speech on a daily basis and unfortunately they were… https://t.co/tAsDBPH9zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then NJ votes SHOULDN’T count towards the election. Ignorance at its best! The federal govt CONTROLS federal electi… https://t.co/Edt9V3gxAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made that bihh sit outside &amp; wait in the rain while the bro hittin’ the friend 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering where graduation is like... 🤷🏽‍♀️ #89days @ High Point, North Carolina https://t.co/1pKfuPfSb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherMirish @MsMollyRachael Chapin my dear, no L. Cat's in the Cradle, one of the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbcpersian #Iranian should remember the treatment of #afghans asylum in their country and expect the same from Tur… https://t.co/nKUT7YpIk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wigs are better lmao Just cause you “prefer” it natural don’t mean imma spend 7 days doing it 🥰🙃😂... “awww your hai… https://t.co/5HnJWXoe2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyzman @FelipeWWoHP ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ i thought the first one was funny too. Idk. I want to see it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Your such an idiot .. why would they want to come here... they want to stay there and get their count… https://t.co/8xIjfbsLrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got burnt in the tanning bed just to feel like I’m on vacation during SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[shawty fye for this lol getting niggas to pay u to b around them and it’s just acting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rothko lives❤️ #MarkRothko #Rothko👩‍🎨🎨☺️❤️#abstractexpressionism #artastherapy #art #abstractart #abstractpainting… https://t.co/ShClwIbl6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[ᴮᴿᴬᴷᴱ ᵁᴾ ᵂᴵᵀᴴ ᵞᴼᵁᴿ ᴳᴵᴿᴸᶠᴿᴵᴱᴺᴰ ᶜᴬᵁˢᴱ ᴵᴹ ᴮᴼᴿᴱᴰ @ North Pole Express https://t.co/XVkx25MXvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time ever making Guacamole and damn it is goooood!!! 😍😍😍 Thank you Eleanor!! #Fresh #Organic #SundayFunday… https://t.co/chAxHhWxQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neil Finn and Stevie Nicks singing Don't Dream it's Over from tonight's show at @bjcc. @fleetwoodmac. It was so so… https://t.co/wALie3n1cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have four words for you. A. Star. Is. Born. Simply amazing. @ladygaga #BradleyCooper #AStarIsBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristopheLloyd @RaysTrashServic i’ve been that guy...but in my garage...(door shut)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Wrong on so many levels. Surprised they didn't spontaneously combust.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The person in front of me paid for my Starbucks drink 😭 who ever you are thanks 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love is at the root of everything—all learning, all relationships—love, or the lack of it.” -Fred Rogers (now that… https://t.co/pUjVWQZ8b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cassaaye @Wolf_Holl Im gonna be honest.... watched the first episode and thought it was terrible. Does it get better? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[you shouldn’t have to remind a grown ass man on what he can and can’t do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennilouwho4 @valentinifrank @MichelleAltman1 @GeneralHospital @lldubs @MauriceBenard I cant wait. I'm sure Sonny… https://t.co/XQ0oWcl1CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanTheBeepMan See ya in a couple weeks beepman. https://t.co/mFgU5MXX6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goatmemaw @charliekirk11 Congress has to vote to stop these things! We have cowards in Congress!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put my birthday night outfit on and I can’t seem to take it off lmaooo I needed a reminder that I...am ... pretty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean if the new people at work are cute and my age I wouldn’t complain.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump I’m laughing my head off right now. Thanks 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring mindfulness in my #sciart - this is a pair I made in 2017 and YAY I’ve been commissioned to do a similar… https://t.co/ueDOtBXjPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Stop believing your own b. S.  Already.  You people need help.  Focus on that for yourselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gunner puppy... My ride or die.  #LoveYourPetDay is everyday in my world. ❤️🌎 But LOVE that this fun little holiday… https://t.co/j8D0pORUUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanareno14 @onilgaparat You bwords have fun!! 😘😘 #deandontgetcutoff #loveyouguyssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 started with the @intrepidmuseum. If you’ve never met my kid, he is the definition of an airplane enthusiast.… https://t.co/eW5rmHCxxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLineCo It already went through (by accident. I’m tired and can’t computer) so no worries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the improvement and husbanding of the soil; the regulation of prices...".  The British East India Company and the D… https://t.co/WFDaZXUA9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissyElliott The rough truth though is back then, it helped if male rappers and other male artists would actively… https://t.co/bOmnGeduRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG @HouseGOP @SenateGOP Trump is GONE unless RUSSIA helps him win again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How charming is this ANNABELLE top for Spring wardrobe?  #annabelle #misalosangeles #shopping #onlineshopping #… https://t.co/Z8eE7LFvFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy year for trade shows. Attending the @WWETTShow and @WorkTruckShow in #Indy then to @MandalayBay in #LasVegas for the @EASA Expo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlsFromMyrna On a scale of one to ten, interest in what you have to say ranks right up there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Who is silencing the media by threats????  Reporter has a press pass?  I assume he did.  He shouldn't troub… https://t.co/kDifj8h8yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally having such a rough week with just getting out of bed. I’ve been so tired and weak and I’m just ready to feel better 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[since it’s officially valentines day i just thought it was right to share this https://t.co/hukLGUkPKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@costellodaniel1 @AndrewScheer @fordnation @macleans @TorontoStar @CBC MAYBE, and just a suggestion, if you want th… https://t.co/YuHCq8XxQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @JamesBayMusic , if you ever wanna be in love, I’ll come around https://t.co/eCHaInBJJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President what good are drones flying up above when they see someone cross the border and you… https://t.co/2K7OZT1ZNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, this THREAD of sleeping babies, smiling in their sleep.....I needed this, TODAY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martingero @JaimieAlexander Ask and ye shall receive! Thanks @martingero ! Was hoping you were reading my tweets.… https://t.co/RZNLacjfUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to be back in New Orleans like yesterday. Crawfish $4.75/lb at Castnet. In Connecticut? $13. I saw these… https://t.co/LvQm1mwksW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week another #newprincipal asked me how I stay so calm with all the stress we face...  I strive for excellence… https://t.co/znYZQngRhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett charged with felony disorderly conduct  https://t.co/VPwyOs3XJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @LincolnDuncan8 Those ppl hugging on Trump are not woke to his taking from them He is a dictator nothing m… https://t.co/JUAzCK04wG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo #MAGA Bros, You were right. I am a #Snowflake.  #ThisIsMS #MSAwarenessMonth https://t.co/s4CQhHiDgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mention the help here at @Budget in Jackson, TN is laughable. No actual help at all. No guidance. They won’t… https://t.co/wecGUndrla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookAddict10 @DienamiteRedder @Jennie_Agent99 @justanurse25 @JoanneMason11 @AlaskanCourtney @LadyJessMacBeth… https://t.co/5KxnJXmaFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why, but every time I’m in a hotel and I have to sleep on the bottom bunk I always think the top’s goi… https://t.co/AEawyK0kBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I wanted something that clearly was not meant for me. God showed me that I had the courage to give it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody else HATE when your vacation comes to an end?! 😭  . I’ve been editing photos from our Kennebunkport ge… https://t.co/hAchFjNdPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent he afternoon decluttering my dresser. Next is he bookshelf. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/JeYNiCIGMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty excited to spend a whole day at Disneyland tomorrow and also attend 90s nite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cinnamon Roll Imperial Ale by @stbcbeer @ Brews 'N' Blues — https://t.co/VxUr2e5ca7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lean On Me by Kirk Franklin holds a very special place in my heart. But I can’t listen to it in public lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The start of today's #wnc #sunrise #wncwx @ Maggie Valley, North Carolina https://t.co/f9kU9enwCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi anyone want to report this account for harassment?? She harassed me and my friends :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Laura for supporting The Homer Fund @homedepot2771 #ISupportTHF #PathTo100 @MShurlow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGANuggets @DogsBCool @2cd3b826bffa4c7 @ShlomoIndiana @__CassidyRae__ @freddyrace14 @establishmentno… https://t.co/H7M7OrbjKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren He’s not a Governor for anyone but himself and a bad one at that! Total insanity the things he’s doing!… https://t.co/FqMhrR6SZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be filled with God's glory. Have a blessed day 😇🙏  Numbers 14:21 "Also, as I live, the entire world shall be filled… https://t.co/6Ilr4SqsYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Jon just bought me roses because he felt like it and that right there is a true gentleman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonlovett on @drunkhistory  is saving my shitty day!  With @freshmeximelt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryJacobo Yoestamañana. Llevo 24 HRS y muero por pan ¿A ti cómo te va?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cats looking around like “why’d we stop keep going we’re going to be late”]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question is did #MichaelCohen act in ways that go against #ABA guidelines in carrying out @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/5V2teiCYT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ufpearth Oh no! I haven’t seen this one yet. I’m falling behind!! Wait, is this the most recent one? Even after wa… https://t.co/e7vvpF5CBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take your time &amp; get to know someone before getting into a relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paduwon I was like wait a minute, had to go make sure I wasn’t imagining it LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte minimum wage: $7.25  $15,080/year based on a 40hr week  $1256 a month  Average one bedroom apartment: $1,… https://t.co/cXUtaZ0GsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smashed tf out some chili’s today can’t wait to smash tf out some more tomorrow💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my favorite museum founder in a hearty toast at last night’s @NerdNiteDC #pealedallaround #greatincognitum… https://t.co/AIgSKqZZxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NAACPPENSACOLA Can I join @NAACP? My husband and I wish to attend the event. https://t.co/amRW7V56ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally can’t afford my school books and I don’t have financial aid so wtf do I do drop my classes ? Ya girl tr… https://t.co/PuouFVgaTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLAmeredyth Thanks for the info on your traffic segment this morning on WFLA. I appreciate you &amp; your teams reporting each morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ความเห็นไม่ตรงกันเรื่องไปเที่ยว นี่ก็เลยแบบ เออแม่ แม่ไปกันเถอะ เนิสอยู่เมกาก็ได้ เอ้า สรุปโดนบังคับไปเฉย เอ้าาาาาา แม่5555555 ไม่ปั๊ยยยยยย]]></document><document><![CDATA[One huge takeaway for me from my #TeacherLeadership cohort family is knowing how to have the tough and meaningful c… https://t.co/sa3vI63FDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting comfortable on the couch in preparation for Michael Cohen to testify before the House Oversight Committee.… https://t.co/WrgQ2Nmtfg]]></document></documents></author>