<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Finesse_gawd7 Bro I literally don't sleep in my bedroom I sleep in my living room everynight FYI don't know why I need to share this 🤧😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicaalba @WSJ @VanessaOConnell @Lisa_Nova Looks great - re-standardize the world so everyone can feel comfortab… https://t.co/vSCePGlBrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i only had three fingers for three lines, two of them would be Ws with an o in the middle. little os! read between the lines- WoW! @IBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfpack_Cox @hester_chip Thanks BP! would be cool to come back for homecoming and see my boy playing football at old Barton!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magsawad @TOPolk Yeah I raised $ for politics at around $10 an hour when my car broke in 2009 for like 2-3 months?… https://t.co/1jUmua6Cwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏 Working on @coinbase Web everyday with @MelissaZhang13 is a joy and a privilage ✨ https://t.co/uf1aQaFuXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at SR 436 &amp; Hunt Club Blvd in Apopka, FL https://t.co/kcHz1g50bX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THINKiWONT @A_Loyal_Boss_ @Akkustomed Well im giving ya my perspective. I treated female with respect honesty loya… https://t.co/eaPBCthjcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #workwife and my #bestie. We SOOO enjoyed the Winter Drill Team’s 80s JAM by Technotronic!  LIVE UPDATE (a few h… https://t.co/WERoTwMOyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pesadilla de los asesinos @NicolasMaduro y @dcabellor https://t.co/IOwzHsXTdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PussyButthole I can’t tell you how excited I was for the reply. Didn’t disappoint]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super late to the punch on Creed 2 but man, nothing ruins a emotion driven movie like a heavy script. Let me feel f… https://t.co/34signy36C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattCapps55 Hey Matt, do you ever do appearances or signings? I would love to get you on my 2010 ASG jersey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a new kind of Twitter meetup. @tarynbray and I “know each other” but have never actually met in person. But… https://t.co/rNHlyDscqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Live with Passion...” https://t.co/R47HISdldN  Pierre Mouele https://t.co/8CPrd7IDSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERY democratic led state should do this immediately.  It would automatically lead to HAVING to release taxes ever… https://t.co/pWLFr3JdX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[me on slop days, wearing my target jeans and H&amp;M cardigan https://t.co/TqOwWdHtSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@bigdimsumdolly Thank you for the follow Selena... Have a great weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qkjrhwjdhjajahahahahahha el estos tipos como que trabajan para Donald Trump 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodyBezan There is a set number of questions every day, with an allotment to each party and provision for indepen… https://t.co/cEz8VpxolR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MysticalPP Nero, I need you to carry on without me, because...  My Sin DT is dummy thicc...  and Urizen can here m… https://t.co/LKFuRRbYpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Friday and yes, we’re on vacation. BUT there’s no where else I’d rather be to start my morning! 💪🏼🙌🏼  Shoutout… https://t.co/5Z8GvdWHun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephamodeo @PeteButtigieg @POTUS Most conservatives like me dont want to go his way. We want traditionalism, low… https://t.co/IUvCnS0flu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avoided the Avalanches on I -70 to watch the Avalanche downtown. https://t.co/P7M2Tm4GFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/TzMxkephEY! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/SWpawMwT4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to @lildjj0 on completing a great HS career. Glad I got to be there to witness a small part of it. Best of lu… https://t.co/clyhn7cVvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LGBToftwitter hi babes, just your friendly reminder. You will be okay and you are so worthy 💛☀️ https://t.co/UaoLIyrROp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones fights to win by playing it safe.  He will win by decision. @ufc #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_savoie can I catch bad guys with you any day? Your my police influence sir my role model my mentor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConorRobertDool How am I gonna fling poo without seeing the mime emote on a constant loop throughout the game... thanks Abigail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made bank at work and then I come to my cats loving me AND now each other my heart is happy tonight 😭❤️ https://t.co/lUnBUw2yHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTmBoyle @antoniogm @jamescham Oh no, we were Florida tongues-speaking, spirit-slaying, CD-burning, gay-bashing ev… https://t.co/6ER3lIiMff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night yo (@ Doc's Waiting Room in Brookfield, IL) https://t.co/tQx46unk1R https://t.co/6svr3k2n74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajplus Nice to build A future with one's natural talents...But first comes parents when it comes to birthing A chi… https://t.co/M5qAMalMPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 3240 ZANDER DRIVE #GrandIsland #FL  #realestate https://t.co/Ruz55PcwDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Featuring Atlanta’s #1 photographer per creativeloafing 📸 quanatl  casting spells 🔥 . forgotten city 100 feet below… https://t.co/notaupw5zJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/yomUwIpTnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESTHER ANAYA RELEASE PARTY NEW MUDIC VIDEO VIOLA IN SANTA MONICA TOMORROW NIGHT 7 pm to 10 pm DELILAH RESTAURANT. P… https://t.co/UlJj9KrP3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailers take 2-1 lead just after their PP expires. Kevin Spinozzi throws it off a Royals defender and in to extend… https://t.co/8jHAYVYcNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump when will u insist ur Order from 9/14/2018 to release Unredacted FISA docs and Emails betwe… https://t.co/cRZr7T15pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Military_Sup It takes a hearty soul to do what the military does for us- Thank you all!!! https://t.co/NgnoTucEEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @netflix: now that you have canceled Marvel shows on your service (#Daredevil, #JessicaJones, #ThePunisher,… https://t.co/KwBAgZyPXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevecripe57 @afterthecallMH @StationPride @BadgeLifeCanada @behindts911 @dma1096 @jkeirrr @FirewellHealth… https://t.co/1XmdmDUz76]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most George Costanza “The jerk store called” moment in @realDonaldTrump’s presidency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/yZHXpDXoCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azecho @ElvisCostello I have been trying to find out for a week now. Still no answers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Crime and border crossings at 40 yr lows, wall not supported by 2 yrs of a Republican controlled Con… https://t.co/78TIaegl7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure how smearing period blood on your face is supposed to somehow convince people that periods are "beautiful"........but ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Evans is great and I’m going to be a MESS when Cap dies in Endgame... but tonight is for RUTH E CARTER and HA… https://t.co/t99glIc53w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathiepham @jttrw @F6x I’ll take the first shift of combing. @F6x can start with the brushing. We’re gonna make it y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liljon kicks off a busy weekend! For guest list and bottle inquiries, text +1.702.677.1525 by 9:00PM  Provide a Fi… https://t.co/1ubOtDkn6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first part of my next novel, GODAN: QUEEN OF THE THIRD COAST, is now being #serialized in @SchlockWebzine ! Tun… https://t.co/tDzGx9CzG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait, im confused, so @facebook allows ads that say and call out the word "In Your Vagina", but I can't use the wor… https://t.co/vKoNPkTxxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrayHall6abc @6abc @chris_sowers @Christie_Ileto I’ll still watch u and sowers👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a classic Sunday this morning at motionchurchnc. A BIG thank you to the entire Motion Kids team for putting to… https://t.co/YZNUcAAfzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN A topic worthy of further discussion for sure. Tech co’s give u their services for free. If forced to pay user… https://t.co/xPew7DdQmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andraydomise I kind of translated it as oh look white people are better at crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once it does stop raining, be prepared for #rice #Plant19. Some helpful recs here in the AR rice update.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Herb&amp;Garlic cream cheese at Saturday morning year-round #Barrie #Ontario #farmersmarket @ Barrie Farmers' Market https://t.co/7a7zMZoHSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even begin to describe this level of humor but I love it so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackoni My block list of these scammers has gotten so full it’s insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @joestornaiuolo Democrats are privileged..they would of nailed a Conservative to the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frederickhiller @SocialPowerOne1 Dump is Putin’s puppet and a wannabe authoritarian dictator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenemos que mirar a lo alto y pedir al todo poderoso que le de sabiduria a los Generales de Venezuela y lleven a Ma… https://t.co/KgOXn1zxID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at work this week at work after talking to my boss... https://t.co/I5yQ5nVkrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Said the dolphin, "I don't have to have it, I just do it for the halibut."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @NickVizzoca https://t.co/SF55w9KVk3 @Dollar_Bank @WRIGHTAUTOGROUP https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/9ZUxniQkQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChargeGiveaways Me ive always wanted to win a giveaway and u new have I've entered in so many in the past 3 years… https://t.co/RCdeivjCd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bethlehempa #bethlehem #moravian #moravianchurch #church @ Bethlehem, Pennsylvania https://t.co/pzaNMTdlCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night now. A student in one of my illustration classes created an illustrated data chart illuminating various… https://t.co/BHSlBlPVRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assistant Chris Marve Excited About Opportunity at MSU https://t.co/WLOCb4Gajo via @247sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDeLuca1 What parents also don't understand is that college coaches watch their behavior and if it comes down… https://t.co/gcVW8yo5r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Because the republicans turn a blind eye, they are just as bad for letting him get away with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2 of cross country was a bit more challenging this morning. Thanks snowstorm 🤪 @ Mont-Tremblant, Quebec https://t.co/NQnFq6Pi3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOHN 3:16 T-shirts designed by Nicole M Boito Hayworth, printed @ForestPassage 5 left!  3 Medium size and 2 XL.  Th… https://t.co/RBLvcaDQHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomShady300 - Ryan and Bill Podcast, “NBA-holes”. Old name that @TheCousinSal called Bill, fits perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently @weberstate moved the student band RIGHT next to my season tickets. Great ... 👎😡 https://t.co/zdKyOADN1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the crazy sequence at the end of the first overtime.   After Chiawana made a go-ahead basket with 12 seconds… https://t.co/ReElwb7QkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. There are some friggin creeps in #distwitter, but @MagicCityMayhem has found the cake-taker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy win tonight for the boys! #sosteez #tat #detroitbasketball @ Little Caesars Arena https://t.co/vgIRTKD1zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[- Fine And Mellow - Ms Billie Holiday the Prez Lester Young , Coleman Hawkins and s young Ben Webster.   https://t.co/MRsQzjiz3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[So not just 2 monkeys, but do to a shift change, we got lucky enough to get 4 Fantastic, FANTASMIC monkeys!!! 🙌🏻👏🏻… https://t.co/cu7VEdZEzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a person who normally add 5 to 10lbs during the winter, I'm excited to see the little things. Hopefully I will… https://t.co/vy7Q8r9dDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taseenb @NicolasMaduro That’s an old Chavez rally video , why would you is that fake news]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes imagination is better than reality... sometimes it’s worse...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would seem that I am becoming the Queen for males with less than desirable peens. Bring me your garbage cock slave fucker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, wow right back at ya! So very glad you enjoyed and thanks for the high praise. Btw, some very cool podcasts r… https://t.co/DsvKzxMotr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claire_Millerr This is the reason I’m so close to deleting Twitter lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCT_mx material suelto una semana carr. Matamoros-Victoria, parabrisas dañados, que procede? Km213-240. https://t.co/Zbn3cACwrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@galow1 @ScrappyNoot1 @SeedsOfDoubt3 Tell that to her parents that seems like much her out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calhoun ties it at 4 with a bases loaded walk by Maise Ondreas in the top of the fourth]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my @NBCChicagoFire gets a season 8, you can’t help but play Life Is A Highway!  Driving to Chicago song!!… https://t.co/jrS1LUClwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dpblissit Oh, I’m calm because I know it’s wishful thinking.  Lowering expectations so that if it happens, I can go meteoric.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carat240 I love your pizza book on your table. Of course you would have that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Café Deth (2018) by @revbrewchicago at @jgreebs — https://t.co/stQOyIajQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Sit-down forklift - https://t.co/qjr90O3sfM #SupplyChain #Orlando, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simp947 @KhurtissPerry @JamesRobinsonn_ @Madhousefit @247Sports @ChadSimmons_ @JohnGarcia_Jr @Vol_Football Congrats on ur Tennessee offer ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTasker89 Hi Steve,  Will you be at Batavia Downs autographing on Sunday? My brother will be going on my behal… https://t.co/nPZJ0LCmLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sportstalkcrap @tlhalm @Cyclonepride Because that's not how humans work 😂  Would rather be woefully unprepared and ignorant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@regretandreward @dianedygert @hotterpop @lauriesaurus_rx @mondestereo @glenspen @Educ_in_Latvia @StephenKing Leave… https://t.co/f2YQ8Jwvae]]></document></documents></author>