<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ningún lugar como en casa... 💕 (@ Allende in Nuevo León) https://t.co/GYZLZHoYOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one to send this gem to so Happy Valentines Day Twitter 😘😊 https://t.co/VdTNzZBtG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melvin_only No my sister stay by the base and I’m always over there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definition: Carperimeter noun (car-perimeter). The minimum distance you can place an item beside my car. Typically… https://t.co/8E74MjN8pO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big questions: Does this challenge the commonly accepted implausibility of epigenetic inheritance? Will it apply to… https://t.co/nphOnkGUod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shadow135Simmi @HippieJohn55 @GordonA90 Good Morning and happy Sunday to you as well 💙💞💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BureauIndianEdu for coming to Rockville to meet with our @IHSgov team to discuss services for American I… https://t.co/2lrcSx2ZGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also huge congratulations to one of my best friends and I consider him an uncle. @PlymouthDawg on becoming a grandf… https://t.co/YpcnHFtMny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrific presentation on the association between starting ART wo a CD4 and early mortality in Zambia by @Kombatende… https://t.co/MYY5jx0x1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I have always been down with @CoachRomar because of acts like this. He has been a real one since I firs… https://t.co/OZ0mjG35gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever spell a word correctly, but you doubt yourself so much that you spell it again incorrectly just so it will… https://t.co/G0N4wY4GYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that nobody in this universe ever has their phone on silent gives me anxiety. #You]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help!!! I need a puppy name!!! I’ll post a pic of the puppy underneath this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going live. Check me out for a bit for free. Link is in my bio come show some love #twitch #twitchstreamer… https://t.co/V9ERupGg79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifebiomedguru The term "heresy" as was used by the Christian Inquisition, has now been replaced with "conspiracy… https://t.co/JjPgK79jow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora que van a quitarle a PR el dinero de la recuperación, recuerden quienes la gente que se supone le de frente a… https://t.co/Pt70lqNkyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronjmate What exactly is evil?  Putting people in jail for no reason, or for small offenses? We do that.  Divert… https://t.co/jshd9pQCF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just talked to a journalist and two twin sister YouTube sensations in Gaza City. Through May 22, @SharedStudios i… https://t.co/x04zlYJohm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see your Kanye MAGA hat and raise you a Cheadle CCCP jersey, and I call:  Happy 44 out of 45 Presidents Day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabrielCuellar_ Gabriel y a huevo te guste o no te guste ya llego tu president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@custerwork You make it sound like I’m personally affronted, instead of simply moving along my downward-sloping dem… https://t.co/KW7LCuH4xH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Scary. There should be oversight from congress @AdamSchiff @TeamPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The special effects on Tales from the Crypt still hold up. The zombie bride in ‘Til Death is incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫get well soon by Ariana Grande, from #SoundHound https://t.co/D63Pbin8yT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake55296094 @LupoZach @MikeGarafolo @RapSheet I think we get 2 mill more in cap hit from trading away OV and getting Zeitler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: @TUWBX hits a program record 18(!) 3-pointers and win the HCAC for the first time in 4 years with a 90-52 ro… https://t.co/0Pu8kjaqh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northern California Division II Championship! Campolindo beat Serra 59-38. @ Campolindo High School https://t.co/VwAkXPcbTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremymbarr @MollyJongFast things only kids who grew up when newt impeached the president will remember https://t.co/Enx6Am4FPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elitvasports @JiCLajoie  on dit que tout ce joue chez les enfants 0 a 5 ans. le CH c'est 0 a 5 min. Ils doivent sortir fort en 3ième.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez, Alex Rodriguez, Adriana Lima, Spike Lee, Kendall Jenner, Julianne Hough, Nina Dobrev, Halsey and Al… https://t.co/LaY7QzKd4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@movie_drone @MGnPpodcast @podernfamily @littlebirdcarr @flick_face LOL thanks you guys 😆 And yes, I died b/c I had… https://t.co/4UWaxMMP3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly honored to be around so many great women. Cheers to the women in my life on #internationalwomensday @ Ga… https://t.co/szglr951wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last Woolworth's lunch counter still in business in America. It's located in Bakersfield, #California #Travel https://t.co/7dMBrYv948]]></document><document><![CDATA[Topping off the gas tank today, I found a dime and a penny in the snow. That comes out to 6.5 oz of FREE gasoline. #KillingIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wave3news No. Law bidding citizens should have the right to conceal without being harrassed for a $70.00 class the… https://t.co/u5qfTZWOzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rural route sleeps while the city bleeds all over itself — Son Volt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain is so freaking handsome!! His smile gets me every time. @ K9s for Warriors Gold Family Campus https://t.co/wWOOtkgRlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder-ful news about the Wonder Award! !! Congrats to @HSDUnaVoz for this well deserved honor. @hillsboro_sd… https://t.co/Y6Xe8ZwEdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤦🏾‍♂️  New York Post : Bill Maher’s red-state hate will help get Trump re-elected. https://t.co/t1v4jFise5  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ahead start for tomorrow. Werk werk! Ain’t work if you love it! Plus Bey singing that song! Lol 💁🏻‍♂️🙌🏼❤️👸🏽… https://t.co/CPWsBjKawU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is glorious. Poor Josiah Didier being viciously RKO’d by Canes defenseman Brett Pesce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poeparty @Komatose22 @cowill1111 @tlrd Uh oh...that's not cool. https://t.co/3c5GCKIPPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was friends with some of your family for many years. like Mike and John. I remember sleeping over Mike's when we… https://t.co/OGNnDpEZ13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitivamente cuando se tiene la edad de Mike Smith el simple hecho de tener sus números ya es algo heroico, no p… https://t.co/EJHd3jahv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJovvs Can’t say no to wings. But if you cook it gotta be like a pasta mf, fully loaded]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gunna &amp; Set dropping on my bday. They knew it was holiday on the 22nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyBeanSunrise I think w/the further interview request-CPD is trying to cut to the chase. It took 2 days  of grill… https://t.co/1z008sNc0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikUribarra que nuestro Buen Jesús te siga concediendo abundantes bendiciones, feliz cumpleaños mi estimado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefyF168 @danteguerra98 @danteguerra98  sacas que @ana_cantu_30  me dice igual ;(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bflay I watch your show because you are cute. Your recipes suck! There is no sense in putting hot peppers and all… https://t.co/1yMNRklano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Bueno llama votar por el concejal Ydanis Rodríguez para a Defensor del Pueblo. Vote MaRTES 26 de Febrero en lo… https://t.co/wuO8cBaHab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knock it Down! k.tilley_8 to the limit! #c/o2023 #YoungKentuckyBallers #502comeup #ballislife  #grinding… https://t.co/o7B9kWcW60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning run on the beach 🏃🏼‍♀️🏝 @ North Palm Beach, Florida https://t.co/QxEINAy1SO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ever it takes for Spring Readiness!  Sometimes there’s some heavy lifting. Thank you Building Services… https://t.co/KUBMyNbUOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys: when the patriarchy is demolished we’re all going to be better off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t sleep as the anticipation of hearing her sweet voice overtook my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GSW_Baseball Good job all around last night, on the mound, with the glove, and at bat; (watch the back picks); sta… https://t.co/5ITWcWyvDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJBrea @realDonaldTrump Eat your own dick stupid. You’ve already got a dick in the White House]]></document><document><![CDATA[WKU spring break is the week of the Tops’ 2 bonus play home games. That’ll certainly hurt student attendance. And t… https://t.co/saiKaOGuCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so great... Another horrible liar, trying to scare a witness... @RepMattGaetz @mattgaetz go hang with Roger… https://t.co/L37zTGtxnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyLaDue1 @ben_stana @sabanfaux The only thing bigger than Derek Henry is that nose 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cal O'Reilly just tied it up for the #IAWild #mnwild 4-4 game late-ish 2nd period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunDoniB Fly by the seat of your pants - the new-age Sens philosophy.  But trust them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most dangerous people are not dangerous people, it’s them people trynna prove that they dangerous people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sogrady I had to book an appointment while on the East Coast, with someone there, before DST, for a time when I’ll… https://t.co/qVhmKxlqP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenrySaysKF Me after 10 minutes of not being able to make a left turn anywhere in the state https://t.co/oxLawBDLt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s breakthrough was standing still. Turns out. Pretty OP. Also reinforcing out of shield grabs.   Also uhhhh fuck Jigglypuff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EjiroOrherhe @sasen_eo @Nuru_a 4th term tinubu we avoiding . We vote out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@synredae @deelane @YeshuaLover1970 @Elinor27652146 @Mel_the_geek @Observer2541 @TheFinalDuke @Atheist_Dragon… https://t.co/5aK5R4gD4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @WWE... can we please get a double stunner one of these days? Stone Cold on Vince, and Becky on Steph. Then the… https://t.co/RIcSkzfbJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrachenJagd Same, I think doing a digital redistribution of AC4 &amp; Answer would be a good start]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna hear anymore music from The Weeknd until he starts making songs like Trilogy again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_Bruinsma @CoachReveno @GTMBB I think I lost a weeks salary feeding the parking meter that day.  #mobileoffice @LovejoyBakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickconfessore I am a serious chocaholic, but I like candy corn and circus peanuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutoffCrawf Still is! Recruits see videos like this and say why would I sit and learn two years at a small D1 or D… https://t.co/sMkCIDUoCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort please take a look at the plea agreement that Cohen signed , under #4 Additional Charges . Your answers are there !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte @marabutler67 @CAIRNational From a group of terrorist, calling you one, right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[House overwhelmingly approves resolution against anti-Semitism and other forms of hate - Jewish Telegraphic Agency… https://t.co/NWuK0PL7eE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JlJoshlane61 @joerexrode Memphis had a great road win , Jeremiah 37pt  @WichitaShocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[...you don't have to wait until the equinox on March 20th. Astronomical refraction, the bending of the sun's ray cl… https://t.co/SzVeMeFC2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP my Padres/UCSD cap. I lost it somewhere between the trolley and home :( cc: @TeeOhEmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradinGlendora @Vickigr81567276 @thisism28744900 @deezaintmypants @thehill Respectfully Brad, I won’t criticize yo… https://t.co/ybDqVUcyw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last frontier! What lies beyond? I imagine an image like this could also resemble our own minds. A great way to… https://t.co/p5o0FfObYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson That’s why when Trumpers accept and repeat Crooked Donald Trump‘s lies… https://t.co/hmEgCAjFrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unleash the POWER of your Heritage. - A Taino in New York City. - In a recent photoshoot with nichi_139 we set out… https://t.co/VpeCMXqVml]]></document><document><![CDATA[she talkin bout "I can have it" @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/ckCZnCnT33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! it is now 6:03 AM here. Have a fabulous day/night. https://t.co/nsV5VPhXza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pima coach Todd Holthaus doing his best defensive stance. https://t.co/3OvWWAmqVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t you be spending more time shredding incriminating documents and paying off co-conspirators?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidprusan14 @FrankieBorrelli @spittinchiclets “For the most part”? “Come playoff time”? Tune in on to… https://t.co/M7UPoI1zCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unions raise wages true. They also raise prices on goods and services which non union workers have to pay. Thus con… https://t.co/SvbHtpgzow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSkojec Bishop Schneider told the pope during his ad limina that his Abu Dhabi statement on the diversity of r… https://t.co/lthcYIamki]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how every president has this 1 thing we’ll always remember him for and almost defines his term:  Bill Clin… https://t.co/aLvVroPg38]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/...So important that teachers ensure that they have locked down their Social Media. Recently assisted a high scho… https://t.co/YSZIEEP2Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[We did it! Finally our first #podcast of 2019. 👊🏻  We would love for you to check it out. 🎧  @LoganPo77123443    https://t.co/YoLBnJQk2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4boysnanny @123RMAGA1 @Spring_Harbinge @KathaleenHarpe9 @libbster219 @JJasdam @RonnieStand3 @jhbentley… https://t.co/QlwflO4ZaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minhtngo @BySilent Haven’t we already established the fact that DT junior is a f’n idiot?  So why is this surprising?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissDollyLeigh @Twistys I want to say the same, but I had a ten year dry spell followed by a two-year dry spell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People not to sit next to at marvel movies  1)children  2)dudes with waste long hair wearing sweatpants and Spider-Man shirts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to knock out the next export trip!  Palau&gt;Saipan&gt;GUAM!  Looking to thaw out a little in the South Pacific!]]></document></documents></author>