<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My phone is super cracked stuck on the word L so if I send you anything lllllllllllllllllllll that’s why]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to get my car fixed so that road trips can proceed to be a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Car selfies on the way to church. Listen this spring forward took me out. But I am about to leap you hear me!  Have… https://t.co/6WsbgjUlT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just your typical gym obsessed lesbian 💋 #issaqueer https://t.co/Vk7kQ9qYkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom and friends that the fabulous @latoyajackson was under the #AlienMask on @MaskedSingerFOX.  Yes, I lo… https://t.co/quJzuP5GLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset at disneymagickingdoms #vacation @ Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/NYENF8or69]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 There’s a thought.......WHAT IF???  . . . #thankful #attitudeofgratitude #God #blessed #blessings… https://t.co/2G600T3YGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump Childish memes, but no facts from the left as usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @pewresearch my political views are closest to those of Country First Conservatives. See where you fit. https://t.co/BYEdlcLzF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many situations at work throughout the day that I want to say “that’s what she said,” but I’m scared n… https://t.co/GpMQua6KHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studying in the lib with sisters makes for the perfect escape from this cold weather!❄️📚 . . . #uicalphatau… https://t.co/tv2FlVavdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellynashville @netflix I have like a running list of things I need to watch on netflix. That is on there]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a pineapple print kimono this week and was going to save it for the spring, but it feels like spring (kind… https://t.co/OSATVIGQ0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrinidadTerror @WhoaDelco I read the caption and saw the first too seconds and I started crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY @KathleenRice  was disgraceful. It is unbelievably that Congress won't fix this problem, and are using @SecNielsen as a scapegoat,]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 years ago today, @xdreamisdead and I met each other on stage at STYG 😭💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'm out of touch today.  I can tell by tweets Trump is scared of something pretty bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and I’ve learned to laugh when you call me names like Fat Ass from the seat of your motor vehicle!  Have a great… https://t.co/NWpDtXJGUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️ 30% OFF ♥️ in my #Society6  shop today! New Unicorn with roses on pink on lots of home decor and accessories! ♥️… https://t.co/e0fhWbN4ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katie really has no room to judge anyone else’s relationship when her HUSBAND cheated on her last season and she ju… https://t.co/BUWeYUO137]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrlongisland @MTA @LIRR Literally, an unsolicited and unnecessary lecture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassSunstein I have data that I think would interest you from a new report that found consumers blame social media… https://t.co/GWwjnR7K4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the girl at express tries to convince me that the regular length jean will be long enough for me cause they ar… https://t.co/53pFS7grxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[All any parent wants for their kids is for them to be really, really, really, ridiculously good looking. Proud of t… https://t.co/t5C93zwjAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maso2k Oooo. I get what you’re saying. However why would they do that? Why would they just go ahead and do it. Why… https://t.co/EKuRS27XQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karmabieber01 @c9ddcee4369b4b0 Is that Justin Bieber? Wow if it is. He changed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateHipHopHead Had love for me ?? Sure. Lust for me definitely. But someone's full honest  love idk that I have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeeBear @DaveTownley2 Mime definitely 💕💕💕 have a great day! https://t.co/G0zKhcfKnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You will never be innocent..  You are a guilty man. You just keep running your mouth. You dont know how or when to shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abealarcon @RosaIsiah We don’t give up or stop trying to reach them, but sometimes our actions have consequences]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah we agree TDS has Hollywood and television stars bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobcesca_go @TRexstasy @fromthebunkerjr I'm listening to the show this a.m. and am at the #LeavingNeverland sectio… https://t.co/TFdQUNmWpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMCslipintoit @HoarseWisperer Former waitress here, and similar. People would FLAG me down to order when we were s… https://t.co/m6fRt6Q7sO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantCardone Get that bird &amp; Elena to fly to CT!  #MoheganSun https://t.co/wHuAPMs4A0]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone is freaking out around me and i’m just thinking about my chinese food]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE For the Wrestlemania nero coming up keep in mind Kofi Kingston vs Daniel Bryan main event headline Next Wrestl… https://t.co/Fe2XKDOJAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlBovisNature This would make an excellent reference for a drawing or pen and ink stipple! 🎨🖊]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mariel #Cuba/n #Fire @ The #Atlanta Penitentiary  Where #Union #Labor's #EugeneVDebs Jailed  Greer-Hale Home:… https://t.co/26CNapn0rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temptation island is the only television show my boyfriend and I agree on. He loves it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got the Feinstein incident all wrong. You would do well to read more, get more political experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s Same Page Broadcast with our Freight Team and Overnight MET Team @Thd2744 Everyone in this room donate… https://t.co/deBAW7DWtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a bad day at work and on my way home I saw a shooting star so I just cried the whole way back home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javieryanguas @HarvardHealth You’ll be interested in a study we will be publishing in a few weeks! Related.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice day ☀️, delicious breakfast 🍝☕, perfect girlfriend 😍   Happy 5.9 sunshine! Love u! @AngelesMtzMX 😘❤ en Fit Tru… https://t.co/eHNllRijca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Murkus Aurelius by Austin Brothers Beer Co @ Horrocks Tavern — https://t.co/sWclsSWMy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Keep up the great work! You’re the best and have made politics interesting again by keeping the old, boring wh… https://t.co/rwv3qh6gL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @KelliButlerAZ for being such a strong supporter of arizona women!! #ERAyesAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter @DiviResorts' 6-Night Caribbean Family Vacation #giveaway for a chance to win a magical stay to Divi Little B… https://t.co/G0cr5hXyp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Decided to start the week off with a legend-@johnlegend’s LVE Napa Red Blend🍷Have you tried this cele… https://t.co/xfomQD8OXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Royal Seafarer Unit 1003 priced at $729,000 is a 2 bed 2 bath beachfront condo. This unit has gorgeous views of the… https://t.co/jt0ek4qtKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “Ok so I’ll leave the office at noon to avoid the bad afternoon traffic”  Tampa Bay traffic: lol you thought https://t.co/WCUB5uBxHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ideal Sunday: Emceeing the Tacoma “Dancing Firefighters” Charity Auction at the #SoNorthWest Women’s Show!… https://t.co/unyawfH03g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missgreengrade1 @Seesaw @ncties So glad you could join us! Be in touch if we can help! #SeesawTechMate #ncties19 https://t.co/9uWeWBZLK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read my special Seuss pop up book of 7 stories to 12 classes, provided #seuss related activities, helped find the ‘… https://t.co/z4yioljPKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[growing up, my dad used to bring my elementary school class donuts EVERY SINGLE DAY to the point that he was asked… https://t.co/FAMNy1jAxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me this morning: I’m gonna quit smoking this is it I’m doing it Me 3 hours later: https://t.co/FaENUAnBtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deb_on_mars @30SECONDSTOMARS @JaredLeto @ShannonLeto @adventure Love this!! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are only 3 people holding the fort at work tn &amp; 2 of them are fighting while I’m in the middle of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jill Smith crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 07:16:47, pace 16:10 min/mile, est. finish 2:54 pm https://t.co/D8W3FHQdsJ #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Str8DonLemon @DanCovfefe1 @DarrenJBeattie @ColumbiaBugle Lemon are you nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @dc_tribune I disagree, Ivanka has created nothing for Americans. She has stolen the designs of other s… https://t.co/6B4Q3kmeYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don't see La Salle and UP in the Final Four this year. Not even contending for a spot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalLoveYourPetDay!!! I’d like to think my PRINCESS P is in good hands especially with her #dogmom being… https://t.co/HyPKWOS7NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am LOVING #UmbrellaAcademy but why hasn’t anyone shown @katewalsh how not to walk like Julia Roberts? It’s so dis… https://t.co/ApFpkALnOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orca will always be one of my favorite animals.  So glad I’ve seen them in the wild!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that as of 4:15 this morning, cuffing season has officially ended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA Thanks. Was 1684 on the outbound run that is scheduled to arrive at Centre/Eliot at 7:36? It's my understandi… https://t.co/duRqC0kl98]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will LITERALLY laugh the f*ck out loud ...  theplaythatgoeswrong @ Broadway In Detroit - The Fisher Theatre and… https://t.co/Ljs9DV0dXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OddNMacabre Tell it to get the out the way before I pissed all over it instead!!! 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Republicans are too incompetent to run a country. They are like fish taking a last gasping breath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp Since you know everything about this situation Teddi, the only thing I want to know is, did Dorito… https://t.co/Mrj6C68xqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelada time! - Drinking a Tecate by @cuamocmx at @mamboseafood  — https://t.co/Ig9X0mLAAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to live in the place where waterfalls freeze....#movetominnesota Several people have asked what is ha… https://t.co/PFmeNb2WbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[não sei se é possível morrer de dor de cabeça só sei que no momento to bem perto da morte]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, at the bar, deciding if he’s a snack or a meal that’s worth my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sleeping schedule is soo fuckd up bcaz I seriously have the hardest time falling asleep at night 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cease to exist if you hurt an animal abused it you deserve the same treatment bastards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE You should not Have touch Ronda Rousey she was just Standing there. She was not attack you!!! Your n… https://t.co/AgpK9Zcfc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Truck2161 @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump I hate trump because I love our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized, apparently i don’t like the jo bros but just them as individual performers. I think this means im old #jonasbrothers #SUCKER]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having a brain storm... families gathered, some kind of poultry baked for hours, something sweet with a flaky d… https://t.co/JnIJKS0ZgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finaly found a hospital. @ WellStar Kennestone Hospital https://t.co/Du3io2CFJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Humane Society of South Central Michigan in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/SlsDtmsMNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews very sad Mr Trump just takes his word like Kim Jon ung would tell him the truth 😡he needs to get to find out the truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ravenpug The prep hasn't been as bad as I psyched myself up for. It's not pleasant but could be worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[spending all of dinner hiding in the bathroom and drinking wine because all i’m hearing about is how beautiful and… https://t.co/66MFfin3o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t fw cheese on breakfast at all and i don’t eat pork. soooo she thought i was going to eat it? https://t.co/EIV7rZp551]]></document><document><![CDATA[My love! The one I hold dearest to my heart! You are amazing in so many way and I am blessed to have you!… https://t.co/7z7zxlRLUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photoshoot outfit deets: Leather Jacket: @topshop retail $200 Thrifted:$40 Top: $retail $25 Thrifted: $10 Jeans :… https://t.co/rzd8O0XbNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be praying for #JerryLee!  🙏🏻💙🎶🎹🔥 #thekiller #jerryleelewis  https://t.co/zXmHpouc79 https://t.co/CJIezrnLFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real news.  @AOC @Alyssa_Milano @maddow @nytimes @washingtonpost @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanMattingl5 Yeh yeh. I had them lined up before I got remarried. 😉🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly how I look trying to wash off my face mask after a long day https://t.co/fI5LUs8USi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #LucidDreams for #BESTCOVERSONG at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/HnVutU2ew6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bank Fraud by over valuing his assets, committed by Trump to get loans..the same crime of Manafort and Cohen.  They… https://t.co/lkSCPNh8hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have any Marriott points they want to lend me? 💁🏻‍♀️❤️☺️ @Marriott @MarriottBonvoy #marriott… https://t.co/cVuLt1IDIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[.....ago when I grew up in Africa, they took you from court to town square and either hang you or behead you. No pr… https://t.co/y1D0J8PzDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to get compliments every now and then!! #mademyday #itsallgravy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7anthea7 @ProudResister He was still the best.i know he was.HE WAS CARING REPUBLICAN.HE WAS NEVER SELFISH CORRUPTE… https://t.co/GNkh4GcbiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the goofiest, most kindhearted person I know. see u soon!! https://t.co/OoWJMymDT7]]></document></documents></author>