<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Another thing, remember the @nytimes denied the Holodomor holocaust for decades, siding with the Soviet propaganda.… https://t.co/EyJQmWc3er]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee is finished and I just drafted Jason Vargas in the 38th round, morning is deteriorating rather quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[H-  why am I not paid in full? C- you were funny H- and? C- you did not give me something physical that could help… https://t.co/AGzjdkMNbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @SheriffClarke  It looks like we are living in a different time in America. Not sure where or what w… https://t.co/OOFAgIJUQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dani_gooner @dbongino @EddieZipperer So you  bought into the insurance policy. https://t.co/f4Jk9L09zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay.. Look who's back again. #Robin   ❤ #Bird  Think it's the 3rd or 4th year in a row. 😁 @ Olathe, Kansas https://t.co/KBp3HZutUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FurzKathy @holachola @djthabitualliar @signorex3 @impinkestgirl @chunkled @Stop_Trump20 @JimCarrey @waltshaub… https://t.co/ea7Nd84wDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its USC VS UCLA at Dodger stadium on pac12LA good game going 4-3 middle of the fourth. UCLA jas two on with one out… https://t.co/rAiAlf8Rsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ArethaFranklin hwdwalkoffame SPONSORSHIP AND INVESTORS OPPORTUNITIES FOR SPORTS AND ENTERTAINMENT COMPANIES WITH O… https://t.co/0pWCD3ZRfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Musician Spotlight  February 19, 2019 SPC ECO  Suggested Albums: Silver Clouds  https://t.co/DilQla2PrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eres tú la parte más significativa de mi felicidad 🤞🏼🤞🏼 https://t.co/mlf96KPJyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m starting to think you may have success pleading insanity at your trial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JiveAhhRoshi @devon0 you act like travis porter came on the scene charting lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overoverunder @Gabrus We’re getting them for the draft: https://t.co/JnaM2vwQD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why we need discernment, which comes from the Holy Spirit, to follow after what is TRUE, and what is Good(o… https://t.co/b4AWs9FazL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neylandmafia Forgot all about rammstein. Used to be my jam! https://t.co/QMFEyNdWGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prjct92eh2 Since they’ve added voice, and Samsung is playing nice with iTunes and AirPlay, they should have some w… https://t.co/saGEKTQqfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hadn't really been following WWE for most of the last year,  but #FightingWithMyFamily has me back in and I'm so… https://t.co/PwjTjqYA8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not one of these changes do I sit here and think will make me want to watch a baseball game more. Stop 🛑 trying to… https://t.co/VFLuu6lrqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guarnaschelli Cracklin Oat Bran . What’s not to love about a bowl of oatmeal cookies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliiigeee @celtics @celticslife @NBCSCeltics And don’t forget #UntuckedKyrie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding pre-#daytona500 party Saturday night featuring the great sounds of danandshay @ Daytona Beach, Florida https://t.co/633a6ntkNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GratuitousSax @DigiRanger1994 Howard needs to enter the MCU... as a CGI Duck. Hey, it worked for Rocket Raccoon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@made4excellence @NBCNews Being female at Hef's is implied consent. Not true in the real world]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building Cool Dungeon Sets https://t.co/JNTnvgnVaz via @YouTube. How to collect and paint dungeon scenes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docshanep @FreedomDPC @UnbridledMd @drcrall @DirectMedicalPC @AspireHealth954 @schusterdpc @LiveLightClinic @risheetpatel Yessir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You demolished the cases we bought. Now it's on draft, $7. Unlike any NE IPA we've ever had. @ Fiume https://t.co/6BvrcKFH2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elliotsci @BBCTwo And I see why it wouldn’t work on a 64 bit OS: it’s a 16 bit program]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Author_Tyler @RAS20135887 @LondonBreed Not only identity but history as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tp-  what do you want? C- I want all of you to quit Tp-  we will not C- then face the mirror Tp-  we are the traito… https://t.co/l1me26armk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have big changes in our lives that are more or less a second chance. -Harrison Ford]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom gives birth, then claims she's actually father - WND https://t.co/jNrdlOazfA via @worldnetdaily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only time you’ll catch me buying anything other than sandals at Payless lmao they’re such a rip off for absolutely… https://t.co/2NSUWvKflL]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 @thearn14 you ever thought you’d get compared to @mckenziemills27 ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr If I recall ACA passed both houses of Congress and signed by President Obama. Not once was a state… https://t.co/LrtqEKGT4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retireburg96 @ulysses23 I respectfully disagree.  Making them go on record, even if they're lying has great value.… https://t.co/otRUdKMHIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artsycarol @gregolear Yeah, it’s freakin’ astonishing that Duncan Hunter was re-elected, and it shows that Republi… https://t.co/O7bj23hGBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi This is what open borders causes on  Mexican side... https://t.co/NNgvhWHZot]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/5vPi9PdOqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook branded 'digital gangsters' by UK lawmakers #CORRECT  https://t.co/36yxA6NKxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcrcat2 @Starchildx5 I keep hoping that he will consume one McRib too many!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResortTV1 @thewdwcouple Congrats!!!!  Even more reason the Cali trip will be more special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best LED Downlights on Sale These LED Downlights start instantly with no flickering and humming-providing you with… https://t.co/tiO6Fai6Yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren I think we can make demands about how it works, but the key thing is, we need to stop them selling your da… https://t.co/PWfsP9SBmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Miami, Florida! Thank you @MiamiFilmFest! Thank you Miami and surrounding area poets and poetry scene! Th… https://t.co/NwYTR5HDtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Ed, Ed, Ed, your party is almost over! These fools are going to prison! Adam S… https://t.co/PYKgJNZ8wX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We may be awkward and full of too much energy, but we had a great time today on KFDX 3 News Today on texomashomepag… https://t.co/zPEr9fQhOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlm2929 @marcorubio It's a question of morality not what kind of degree you have]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six straight @Hamady_Hawks points cut deficit to 20-19 and force a @byron_athletics timeout wit 2:00 left in the first half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this kind of hard-hitting criticism and indignation to be directed at everyone but the four people a… https://t.co/Gspf1JIFsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Ortega’s recent move to meet with opposition leaders is a step forward, but not enough. For far too long,… https://t.co/Etl6UmtydD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck They know they’re wrong they know they made a mistake he thinks the audience is going to go to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am SUPER PUMPED to see @coleswindell, @ScottyMcCreery, @TylerRichMusic @tasteofjoliet June 22nd in Joliet, IL! https://t.co/WwGkpFY4ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Boffin This could explain the progressive left’s hostility towards #AlitaBattleAngel even beyond that it was us… https://t.co/8uJRVHFxWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome It is just the beginning. Who wants to be associated with a party that murders babies. If you listen closel… https://t.co/c41LBu1rPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auburn trying to finish at the rim is laughable. It’s also the reason this team isn’t a threat to make a run in March]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolandMFA @HeikoMaas @PLPermRepEU @PLinMunich @PLinDeutschland Polish Parlament has to create law(uchwala,decret)… https://t.co/umvm2ZGt39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several people are now speaking in opposition to #SB250. https://t.co/jBbtjrgFhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[who’s looking for a roommate in LA ? (for my friend) (not me) (not carlo)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @Teresam46396557 @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump Take a hard look at your parties past. You voted aga… https://t.co/KXo1O91aw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power button probably accidentally held in, while in my pocket. The old Motorola was pretty temperamental. https://t.co/A2a1ZarrmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UnityOfPurpose RCHS Orchestra Feeder Festival. Wonderful performance from students at   @RockCanyonHS… https://t.co/Ugys1iWbhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planning a meeting in Maryland, Northern Virginia or DC? For all those planning their conferences, conventions, gal… https://t.co/MkPA9hRCxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[....PUSH PULL PEDAL PLANK ...get comfortable being uncomfortable!!. #worldgym #flpt #trxtraining  #trx #trxclass💪… https://t.co/vMSjjlXzAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @gtconway3d @shearm Trump adopts the policy of a traitor impersonating a legitimate president of the United States.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshIsenberg4 That’s like say Kia’s are the best cheapest cars in the world. No one cares about tag teams anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand This headline is rich considering Nancy Pelosi the head of your party attempted to use military flig… https://t.co/x7rqU3cHst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingdavidotw @LordCognito @IronLordPodcast @LordAddictILP @LordSovILP @Bl00di3knuckl3z @JayDubcity16 @BRAP_Podcast… https://t.co/UQNpy6Orw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonjcohen I also thought it entertaining. A lot going on in that movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find myself newly proud, as such, to be the SECOND Iranian-American faculty member at @TAMULawSchool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our daughter, a junior in high school is receiving mail from different college's.  @Yale @Princeton @JohnsHopkins s… https://t.co/2wSSdzZM3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Grand Central Terminal https://t.co/uRi0z98adB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealguise @Alyssa_Milano Russian bot...upgrade. You're a fucking idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmperorBigD @Rhymestyle @THEREALRTU @VampyBitme @YouTube @TeamYouTube Thanks, Dan. I'll try.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, he’s sing-songy now. How fun. And he’s counting on his loaded Supreme Court.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlannaMartella vs herself in #dreamselfboxingmatch🥊 #dingding🔔 #fight👊 #knockurselfout #youwin xoxo #wceveryyear💗 gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aikens_Josh My baby ate all the scrabble tiles... Now his excrement makes more sense than Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez @AOC 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was the loudest I have ever heard Koeppel. Unreal atmosphere. Truly amazing what happens when two schools sepa… https://t.co/YnzFcPI6yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[warn be still, and know that i AM mightiest, i will be lifted among the nations, i will be lifted in all the earth!… https://t.co/iB4TbRQZ9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WxShaw @BenAxelrod said he had to be on the roster and I was merely stating that league rules prohibit that from h… https://t.co/WqpwydeDcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman @DiegoMaradobbn Successful marketing shift. Well done! Kudos on the self-deprecating humor, too. Grown Ass Man, right there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know I will catch some heat from my fellow #Titans fans but I think it would be GREAT to sign Blake Bortles as a ba… https://t.co/Wis5Dqy8xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing someone warned me that the Granblue stream had no intention of showing anything related to a trailer until a bunch of hours in lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE!!! FREE!!! Clippers vs. Trailblazers tix for tomorrow night! Who wants them? 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[My weakness is that I am to kind and i am over that this year. Done holding my tongue back. It’s all about that action and asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could’ve been anywhere in the world tomorrow afternoon, but I’ll be here in San Francisco at @HamiltonMusical bec… https://t.co/sagZ1BuDy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx Bueno no vamos lejos Los del @PRI_Nacional tienen Muchos ejemplos]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact this is how you want to spend someone’s time, can southern women just be thick these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobClarick @delong @owillis Grant was a great general horrible  president. Turns out being drunk 24/7 doesn't work well at the white house]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 horses died at a single racetrack in the last 10 weeks. How did it happen?  https://t.co/m5pbNXktxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gates about to open @PigsMemberships pick up starts now #pigday #pigs #pig #tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J5iroDi5z5 Bro you’ve also said some dumb stuff in the past but this? To much. Aight fine ... ready?.... red dead is stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the last day of the columbuspetexpo2019 Come stop by and say hello.  We have been having a great time.… https://t.co/r9qotrpFri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Our ties helped prevent friction between armies, Netanyahu tells Putin in Moscow (Haaretz)// even all the whil… https://t.co/5CKzDeFNQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Self-Hypnosis Can Help You Reach Your Goals - Read more at https://t.co/bGIpcAxxGY https://t.co/GgRDcKJWw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of the @realDonaldTrump s attorneys mouth himself. Of course he's telling the truth. Even my grade school child… https://t.co/eJhAwY1l37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donovan smith got a HUGE contract today. I talk about some of the implications of it in this video! Go Bucs! Donova… https://t.co/80MOq0ntLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[46 errores no forzados en el derecho igual. Horriblemente impreciso cuando está en posición de control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBarasky .Here are 14 previous 1-minute challenges. https://t.co/gxlrUC55M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheoTypes @MaybornUNT @DentonRC @dallasnews Posts like these seem elitist. I landed journalism jobs while studying… https://t.co/gyyUUtRO7d]]></document></documents></author>