<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I just jumped into the shower with my socks on, I need to go back to bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenesisMako @jpmir Invitame a vivir a tu pueblo, y me ensenas a trabajar en el huachicol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally came across an Ab workout that is extremely difficult to do. In 2-3 months, I'm never wearing a shirt again in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerheimMgdSvcs @CloudPinnacle @awscloud Great article @DerheimMgdSvcs! Finding time to read is not easy, especiall… https://t.co/abcKP5vh4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robnucatola Where did this rain come from? Forecast didn’t call for any yesterday. #surprised]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all out of state mofos need to stay home, traffic jams out here getting crazy and I know it’s because of y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time you hear Usman interviewed or talk he seems like a fantastic guy. He’s not gonna be a fan favorite, but good like beating him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@korbindallaz @audilvrs7 @zdravkost @ren_119 @iceman7news @RaikkonenOficia @fokkerdude @PriUzun @uchuta_m… https://t.co/JorMN10Ecf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikHerzog Dosage time and the therapeutic index. Just in hypertension, many lives could be extended. CC @thebyrdlab @sarahkmels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalwareJake I was glad to see your account in there. The whole thing reeked of amateur hour “investigations”, but… https://t.co/RjGJIeo3oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiegoFuentesEC Es típico del Morenismo-Neoliberal salpicar lodo con ventilador a los ciudadanos de bien, y si lo p… https://t.co/6xg1dKkwPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @DeniseInNC Wow! Talk about a hater! You seem to be the worst kind! And, it will get you nowhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a rest day yesterday as I was feeling a bit beat up from my first interval session in forever and becasue the… https://t.co/mlkeQ0Ki2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraunStrowman when are they gonna give you the #universaltitle? I’ve waited too long for #thebeast to… https://t.co/TIfASx6Rk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RusevBUL You are a loser. Snowflake? ❄️Welcome to Brother Love’s world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slayAbides @Spewheb I agree with you. And have deleted my tweet because you’re likely not the only person who thin… https://t.co/RjMdNeOqAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comenzando una nueva aventura 😎🙌  #Honors2019 #🇸🇬 #familia 💪🏼😎😊🙌 en San Francisco International Airport (SFO) https://t.co/lOdfL0tUq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost andreworthphotos with get_repost ・・・ @thebrentloper Country singer/songwriter Brent Loper is living through… https://t.co/mPq8zmepSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Panther is a highly underrated film and Marvel character, easily one of my top 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[This afternoon was perfect for running and spotting rainbows over Washington DC! ☀️🌈 👟 https://t.co/EVWCiMxmkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bill Maher is right. When history looks back on you it will say, above all he was a whiney little bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating piece about a small part of what affects cost and quality in health care https://t.co/43tIvg2AUb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy Favorite John Candy movie???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#afirmación #afirmaciondeldia #afirmacionpositiva @ Doral, Florida https://t.co/I6dwydtdLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdeelRanaNYC @DSTWorldTravel @NYPDchaplains @NYPDMuslim Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ducks #floridaphotographer #florida #swfl #swflphotographer #waterbirds #birds #photography #wildlife… https://t.co/Z66i00qxMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to say up front "complexity" here is meant in the formal sense of complex systems, not just a term for somethin… https://t.co/NWMeWiPtNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s cold when the water you left if your car yesterday still feels like it just came out of the refrigerator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUB RUN ATTENDEES- enter the GLBC Tasting Room from the side door off of Carroll Avenue- you will see our sign 😊 https://t.co/dcgtkifbgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realamymholmes @amyklobuchar No more than trump had to answer too and avoided.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Club I love: Manchester United  Clubs I like: Borussia Dortmund, Real Madrid, Chon Buri FC, Orlando City FC  Clubs… https://t.co/gZICEwnvLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames member when we used to get awesome story dlc that everyone loved? I member.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Pelicans Day!!!!! Geaux @PelicansNBA!!!!!🏀 #Pelicans #PelicansGameday #DoItBig #NBA #NBATwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all mad bc he ripped that ugly ass flag up but y’all people still out here killing and accusing innocent BLACK ME… https://t.co/XwvXgGuzak]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Puck man is finally getting fixed and vaccinated thanks to the AZ Humane Society’s free spay/neuter weekend. I’… https://t.co/vd0yaq4cRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: Portland State 36, EWU 35.  Eagles erased a 22-8 deficit before taking a brief lead. Kim Aiken sparks com… https://t.co/AKL90k7R5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[15.27 minutes/mile. Went slow because I didn't take a day off between, and because it was my first no-walk day. Que… https://t.co/KkcA1Qrbsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tridentinus @AOC Oddly, it was just reported a couple of days ago the Amazon was paying $0 in taxes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll finish my rant here: this move by Facebook is not about privacy, it’s about commerce and that’s it. It’s findi… https://t.co/ldMLd7FsEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teenygozer @NotTooPCMom @bearded_raven @nikkiwentling https://t.co/GeFwe214jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgmcguire68 @ShaneGoldmacher The Supreme Court nullified the Reconstruction Amendments until the 1930’s, but they… https://t.co/9QHS0Nsl97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una partida al #RogueAgents, no sé si traiga video (hay muchas cosas que digo que voy a traer y al final no sé si l… https://t.co/GvSah3nltn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The smart man knows that everyday is international women’s day. #WordsOfWisdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for good, short #podcasts (20 mins tops) to listen to during walks from the train to the office. Drop some names, Twitter friends.👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got invited to a Filipino party in Stockton and while I enjoy eating lechon that drive ain’t worth it boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @OrangeGrove55 just saw you Toontown video... while I agree that the ride would work in Hollywood, I think it i… https://t.co/01XRXNDp0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pinkmustard21 @baldmanreacts Well that’s not the show but.... I didn’t say I don’t smile. But my natural default face looks like a smile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait lines for a bathroom at a concert Men: 0.5 seconds  Women: 7 hours 23 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gelliottmorris Special elections in KY haven't been all that indicative of anything recently.  Here's what the 201… https://t.co/qdhNhbwObu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rachael_Swindon She is a weasel, like Boris. A person of no straight lines, everything is an angle. That said, I w… https://t.co/BoVVL9Kr1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seannyd22 @Thomas_hook White Goodman makes it a conversation but prime Will Ferrell in any movie around that time… https://t.co/cZN95Mb37i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard mode activated, as United moves the tight connection from two gates over to the end of an entirely different wing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AM @MCO heading back to #LasVegas. Thank you #Lyft for all the rides and a great week @HIMSS where I had a FANTASTI… https://t.co/KyXDTVXuv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbrown107 Yeah that’s not good. Like you said, let players learn through experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IwriteOK Im glad you are doing your pods.  Honesty, dispatches from wars scare me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 As a Catholic, I am incensed by anyone, including Donnie Dumb Ass, to have t unmitigated gall to sign a… https://t.co/CYNOOZ0Z5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Stone may have turned into a whiny little beyotch .  Plea deal coming ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @PakStreams for giving me this jacket as my belated birthday present!! Thank you!!!!❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/xqkmte27Ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[On draft! - Drinking a Kentucky Bourbon Barrel Ale by @kentuckyale at @stillwatergrill  — https://t.co/fKUNyM0Wpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisMunnings What an honor it has been to get to serve you in FCA.  We’re not done yet!  Proud of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airwaysfoodie Lol I have had my current car for 11.5 years and I still get the buttons (half the amount here!) confused! #hotmess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind @UncleSamIsTheN1 Inciting to RIOT!!! This is what he’s doing. https://t.co/de1BQDqMmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @SteveDeaceShow @realDonaldTrump well that congress give him no other choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ballerina meets the waitress #slay #sagebrushcantina #sundayfunday #gayboy #pandaextraordinarie #legsfordays @… https://t.co/xppsFivCWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zeepees @Vol_Hoops Small school mentality. Not surprised. Enjoy your regular season wins and winning nothing of significance this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llivia07 @makaurel @CMonteroOficial Siempre hay una salida pacífica esperando ser descubierta. Nunca debemos perder la fe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least some justice. Officer found guilty of gunning down black man whose car broke down on interstate. Corey Jon… https://t.co/QGwUR4fS7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 1L year before my final oral argument, I parallel parked right outside of the Moot Court room in one attempt lik… https://t.co/9HoqXzM201]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait till the 2019 @houstondash season kicks off!!  Can these gates just open already?!  Asking for a frien… https://t.co/gqaJsWV8XY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAmberChandler @AMLE @cmt215il @Lkleinteach @ScholesE15 @Beyond_the_Desk @Larryferlazzo @nysutEVP @ritaplatt… https://t.co/oJ5qroFCTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The House Cleaning Podcast 🎙 Episode #58: What Is Branding and Why You Need It 🎙 . Now available 🎧 . Link in bio 👆🏼… https://t.co/PSWJ0uaTGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jpell915 @PressHerald @PPHSports @GlennJordanPPH @APSE_sportmedia Congratulations, Glenn. Excellent news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the hell is Trump tweeting about a wall, when he is about to meet with his lover Kim]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i am not John and Sallie's 2nd son .is an African-American child the daughter of Heidi (white Swedish) ex https://t.co/heZDB4uo72]]></document><document><![CDATA[the missions 2 outer space are legit, but not for publicized purposes. no conspiracies, just ‘alternative’ agendas. all bout optics 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously done with all the food service app like @DoorDash_Help and @SkipTheDishes....food didn't arrive due to in… https://t.co/af8SnJx87u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhizalHasan idk about you but my favorite play from the game night:  Some UCSB player smacks the floor on defense… https://t.co/PXmpqvtyjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition to the Soros comments, that nasty man is allied with many who want a global governing structure, not de… https://t.co/I1ZWOquriZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[*-15 degrees with windchill in Chicago*  Me: *a gay with iced coffee on the Belmont CTA platform* https://t.co/y2ZdT12VrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I been saying this! The A would've went stupid if the Saints was in the SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seek 1st the kingdom and these other things will be added to you. Happy birthday Mo! #havingtoomuchfun #BMR… https://t.co/ZiZMQYzE6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cabezas es un idiota, va siempre a buscar pelotas encima de sus compañeros y deja agujeros por todos lados. No hay… https://t.co/pvTITScf6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickSchellens @tribelaw donoot send me stuff like this it only encourages me-- i wanted to a very good poker playe… https://t.co/AWSjULwPgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sesom_ @EliseEldracher @NJDevils @Blockaid1 @DidiG18 She seems like a great person so yeah she’s probably fun to… https://t.co/fXT4SX9LDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PeteHegseth  #IllegalVote  The problem isn't just illegals voting.  Because of the DELIBERATE misapplication of t… https://t.co/r4tC7kMbRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning the TGD US tour is over and i just wanna say i love and miss the shit out of @PointNorthBand… https://t.co/3A9GeShoUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cardio ✅ #posing ✅ #letsgo .. 5yrs off and only 9wks back with 29wks to go before #tampa weighing 224lbs now and s… https://t.co/GuYraXBrSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHayesCFB @1010xljoec @searcy_leon I think there would absolutely be title IX issues due to the much greater ex… https://t.co/q3BteM7DGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: @NTSB says #atlasair 3591 cockpit voice recorder reveals "crew communications consistent with loss of co… https://t.co/k2efZGlXmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love to giggle. School Teacher Wears The Same Outfit For Yearbook Pictures for 40 Years | Bored Panda... https://t.co/RX5MbVrpwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but nothing beats this view! 😍 I'm covering @ASU_Baseball for @HouseOfSparky tonight. It's game two. ASU… https://t.co/qmPA0bUE1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sl62949428 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Well Scott—since you said Lori’s tweet is ‘absolutely true’, perhaps you ca… https://t.co/Pf5sCDAgoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChateauAmboise Thank You, loved touring Amboise...and creating this unique image from a work of art #leonardodavinci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @choesanghun Consequences do occur when you have Incompetent leadership. It must be that McCathyism. @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made it out to Bud Walton for a @RazorbackWBB game. @chelsea_dungee dominated, per usual, and some weirdo t… https://t.co/RsU0LCv7h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lateupload #ciaa #epicenter #spectrumcenter @ EPICENTRE NC https://t.co/Da2BjAcUKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[People wont care until the art you’re creating is tangible. When it’s at that point, they have no other choice than… https://t.co/AWQvofMgVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is almost here and that means FUN season! We insure all your FUN toys. Heck we can finance em too!… https://t.co/tZRDyUC75i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alinea might be the most ridiculous restaurant in America. No outside wine but 5x markups on their own wine list, c… https://t.co/QNbjTkgUY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Al_Weave @J_Merryman Need to work on your length. Hair looks great 👍. https://t.co/OdwZziueeF]]></document></documents></author>