<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cbouzy frankly, he deserves every last penny and more that he can get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time again... #coneyislandpolarbearclub #everysundaythisyear #brrr @ Coney Island https://t.co/hPkyOO95RI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need Promo for your business? Contact me.. #PROMO #nails #clothes #tattoos #hair #events #advertisement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally learned how to pronounce Sepulveda, Thanks #HotBenchTV Learning while sick in bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[no offense but this self-portrait by leonardo da vinci looks just like me https://t.co/Q1IEglJofv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello  😘😎😃March and everyone ☀️✨🌈🌷🌷🌷wish you all an amazing day #SamHeughan #LoveForSam  Credit to tanyatartaruga @… https://t.co/MqxFkAG0Bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomboyD What he called "policies" was nothing but a wish list, with no plan in sight for how to achieve them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7thgradeseason @Morgantay11 @StephenCurry30 #11 @girlsbasketball #fortheloveofthegame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for her do not let two opportunist cheating scumbags keep you at home! Work must go on and what a great messag… https://t.co/062Hw9cpGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You decided this for all the taxpayers? Because we pay their salaries, not you. Lady you are a little on the slippery slope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo who’s going to get me this for Valentine’s Day??? https://t.co/DoAgYwG15I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truer words have never been spoken 😂😂 @marasmith214 @aledalton @stuschaff @CKlawyerWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does no one mention his sexual entanglement that resulted in an expensive settlement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueeenVina @perdiodT @slavicshawty @HesAntiS0cial @Tyler_LaRue we all seen the kim k sex tape, she just laid there… https://t.co/THylmjdSMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine’s Day is being spent stuck inside with a sick baby while it’s pouring rain. Still better than all the… https://t.co/Zcr5BpUmJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“hey Tom, can take a picture of us?” @ University Heights, Ohio https://t.co/HLl9hqn6EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9Cx9ZPnT… https://t.co/iwrP7TfrZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @GeorgiaStateFB 2019 season is confirmed! Schedule is modified, printed and POSTED!! Mark your calendar....The… https://t.co/Cu7uwJCbdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geauxldn @SDJBeauty Yes, yes it is! So is the CoCo Cabana Cream!!!  🙌🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWCA75SH almost complete with Intern Juan picture! @TexasWCA https://t.co/7BKUJ1LdER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar You have WAY too much time on your hands (and a weird towel fetish).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome PE class today! 💚💙🐎💙💚 #theirpeisbetterthanyours https://t.co/3mvHtQE6jP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cancerhusband1 Thanks for the update.  I was hoping you would continue to keep in contact with us and keep up your… https://t.co/qNwTNDmBi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Carolina legislature attempted to stop Justice @Anita_Earls from being elected to NC Supreme Court. They fail… https://t.co/pniMxyXCDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still early evening my timezone, Ramis💙  but wish sweet, rejuvenating sleep to you😪🌛for wonderful day tomorrow🌞💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add pie. All pie. Pie of all shapes and sizes. Honestly a real look into the mind of a psychopath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When watching the Presidential speech yesterday, it made my day that they timed it perfectly to interrupt The View...🤣🇺🇸❤️ #BuildTheWallNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure someone's already done the analysis on Meat (™️) and toxic masculinity, not to mention rural White politic… https://t.co/VUKnUh1PE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THIS GORL!!!! Let’s have some {twenty} fun!!!!!🥂🍾🍻 https://t.co/dVER4FzB4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: No. 4 Woodville 59, No. 5 Franklin 38. Lady Lions’ season ends at 37-2. Woodville (38-1) will face the Wall/… https://t.co/iAKdJKDR6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Nice speech Ivanka.  How about paying your correct taxes.  You and your family are dis… https://t.co/12mli3vQqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman This woman is not well. Honestly. And why don’t you finish eating before blogging. How disgusting. No class whatsoever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 You are such a disgusting human being.  You are a frat boy who will never grow up and become a man.  Pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An excellent #podcast every #Christian should listen too. Why? Bc we’re asking hard questions that involve the live… https://t.co/lECFxziIL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriciomonero @marianoruiz_b @julioastillero @RadioCentro977 @LillyTellez @rturrent Y muy pero muyyyy merecida ..… https://t.co/K2UPekkGd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday isn’t until March 6 ... my birthday is always during lent which does not help me give up my vices  #catholicgirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exhibit with #Viking artifacts at #NordicMuseum. #Seattle #Ballard #history https://t.co/cYtWL5CmaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myfear Yup yup, in SF all week. I can’t decide yet if this better or worse for jet lag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sent my girl off to South Africa on her own tonight. 🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻 I need everyone to stop telling me how dangerous it is… https://t.co/iylp2ZiPaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se subió alrevez la anterior :( aquí de nuevo hahaha buen lunes! https://t.co/lFoUBV9YbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert30062 @James_rwnat Just so you know, I think you are a bot? Or maybe a very miserable individual consumed with hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rainahhh i want joooheons jacket 😍  and to be in his place next to shownu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexieeprayor @Rocioceja_  @hayleyyjay  if you could please share this it would mean so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Brian🙂 He drinks pure therapeutic ketones EVERY. SINGLE. DAY.   50 pounds of fat GONE and replaced with 💪   He… https://t.co/NIyByrNfHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Videos like this makes me so happy to know I’m not the only super goofy gal outchea😩😭😂💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to @NATO on both sides of the Atlantic for helping to arrange interviews with @CMC_NATO Air Chief Marsh… https://t.co/x5cGSNMTbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry but you gonna pay your cell bill or sum cause this is a cruel world and you gotta grow up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH YEAH AND YOU KNOW THIS... YEAH USE IT BIG DUMMY https://t.co/dnXPsm9YGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember one time in hs my dad kept calling me so I stepped out of class to answer it and he wanted to ask me if… https://t.co/lR6Bf9wUhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delzof1970 @naturalrights23 @RMConservative @KurtSchlichter @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr OMG!]]></document><document><![CDATA[that friday feeling #EatConservatory #harmonicait #WeHo https://t.co/1gzQLBHRfB https://t.co/ro32A2t3dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PandaExpress Super disappointed with the service I received today. Multiple items missing that I paid for and very rude customer service]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now rain and I can hear a few birds out my window. Looks like a few is us are awake now... #Sonoma #Earthquake]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more ☠🌌❤ #photography #canon en Torreon, Mexico https://t.co/ydf5YB7FXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of Keller Williams Family Reunion in #NOLA   ☎️ 📱  (316) 371-7282 📧 StephanieMcCurdy@kw.com 💻… https://t.co/Wej8MbBezY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing you Mom - Heather Jean Cumming - your bright light continues to shine in our hearts and memories 💕#mom… https://t.co/yiHaJPrysD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayGrape @LindseyGrahamSC @BenSasse They don't support anti gun violence against children either. Truthfully, I do… https://t.co/TaBaEOLqkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but why does every man I date waste his breath telling me how awesome and amazing I am if he is just gonna cheat on me....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoppe Satire – Humor for Photographers – Dealing with “Crop” https://t.co/zOPlYGMWmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #GalentinesDay to all my beautiful, poetic, land mermaids! https://t.co/8sGLxW9197]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Gee.  Dunno why that happened other than you weaponized your phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s a war zone, you pretty much need to pick who you want to go to war with .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Born 1929 Amanda Blake [Beverly Louise Neill], Miss Kitty on Gunsmoke 1967 Kurt Cobain, in full Kurt Donald Cobain #OTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[International womens day was invented by predatory chauvinist pigs so they can maintain plausible deniability by po… https://t.co/CXzi9zsewk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abortion has now been raised in today's debate on Minnesota HF 13.  It is a moot point. move on. #ERANOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dorothy7x Yes I agree! She just says and does whatever. It really is not nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ListMccarthy Again, I’m back to asking for specific examples of studies. And reference for this latest claim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to get my mom a Dr. Pepper from sonic when I was in town and you would’ve thought I did something awful to… https://t.co/eDeYlrWydv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m reading Rich People Problems, and I’m at a journal entry marked “March 1, 1943” just as we hit midnight on March 1st.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElainaMarie89 @DWImpalaOwner @Osospeical1 @Pathryn34 @thisroadsofar @Steph_W90 Lol I'll let it slide Elaina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanirN Que legal. Espero que a banda dê certo e possa se divertir bastante.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureanomar Lamentablemente pareciera que para el mundo, la vida de los venezolanos está tan devaluada como nuestra moneda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone make my day better and tweet me phots of wdw or one direction please ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reclaiming our time...  #BlackHistoryMonth #All2019 #Memphis #Heritage #BHM #PoorPeoplesCampaign #IAm… https://t.co/jNsCM1C47g]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet Madalynn got to be apart of our Ned Kindess assembly! She definitely shows kindess to others everyday!… https://t.co/CSeHZz1NRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the long term great relationship Dwayne!! Appreciate you! #takeyourshare23 #hdms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bishopk_ You sure won't be disappointed their both(@OldDominion @MorganCWallen) the bomb soo much fun and super hi… https://t.co/3uOb1UagZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite sport to watch boys play used to be baseball until i started watching my boys play basketball in high s… https://t.co/iJW8VrbIoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[but if I’m being honest the best thing you ever did for me (@alysegundo) was teach me to take my hair tie off of my… https://t.co/CqNaL1PEUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been telling ya!! And it's almost time! Take a moment to follow @WoundedBlueDoc  and @WoundedBlue for updates on… https://t.co/SsFk4dfilR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicely done justice! Great to see these positive and powerful messages featured on your latest fashions. #gogirl… https://t.co/7HLWjTEiCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andthisjustin Aww I thought it was a pre-order campaign! I want a pennant 😭💕  (also pre-ordered MONTHS ago IM SO EXCITED!!!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove @realDonaldTrump God does not speak that way. Hypocrite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner I pledge to support America by voting for all Democrats, especially the one chosen to run against the orange idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch face 😍 😘 #ingridrachelproject #everything #do #girlfriendzchatcorner #pinkhair #smile @ LouVino: Cincinnati… https://t.co/X2yj6bgmyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[29 degrees outside right now and I still have my fan on full blast in my room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stationary design planning swellpress this afternoon!  So excited for this fall wedding!  xx @ Swell Press https://t.co/o0RfxOnfrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a Hitler in the White House that is going to do everything to stay in there how sad and will do anything to… https://t.co/Tx2e06WD3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Protect kids, not guns” is what’s printed on the T-shirt I’m wearing today. #ProtectOurSchools]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst is kind of sorrow is the one you didn’t see coming. It’s like the ground has been snatched from underneat… https://t.co/BVmXoo5Qv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must see.  Absolutely brilliant documentary Apollo 11 directed and edited by Todd Douglas Miller.  #apollo11… https://t.co/0KCeS0KbxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super rare vintage New England Patriots Drew Bledsoe Starter jersey. From the Classic Team Collection. Clean condit… https://t.co/PAuiVZXN6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly @J_Sump's instagram should be a magazine https://t.co/jXwXETDXxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey cocacola, gphi wants to share a coke w/ you! @ Coca-Cola https://t.co/9aK805esCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJenSewell @FloSoftball Oh my gosh yes!  And stop talking through the WHOLE game.  They would be rambling abou… https://t.co/wC3houbuLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no way getting home or my moms job last night so glad @shaylee60218274 came to my rescue entirely grateful and thankful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 @Morning_Joe  Thought you might be interesting since this guy represents your old district..Any thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearlyDoug I hope to be! I was there 2 years ago when they won it all! My hubby was sick, I didn’t have a hotel ro… https://t.co/54uoTveKFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started this piece thinking of time. Intertwining like the fabric I used. As I went along creating I discovered t… https://t.co/S0e4DzIDI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to share spring break with dedicated educators expanding their toolboxes of writing skills! #HISDLIM… https://t.co/VAzFKfJfFQ]]></document></documents></author>