<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @AOC Absolutely agree with you! These low IQ freshman people are in need of History lessons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melisavdl Es esa persona que sacrifica su bienestar, digamos que se hace adicto a la dependencia de su pareja, o s… https://t.co/pmlbwPOnUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[During a gator game  Boss: Mark can you come in? We are slammed rn.  Me:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow didn't somebody say if you want to judge a society check out the prisons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySalads So CNN and MSNBC are either stupid or liars? @GiovanniGiorgio @RealJamesWoods @AnnCoulter]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NeverForget .......(next time someone in Flint Michigan complains that they still don't have clean drinking water.… https://t.co/kBnpiQpRTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datscoowitme @CNN So you pimp off your wife. What’s the difference?Same hustle different game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMDeMatteis @jamestucker Absolutely. Marvel needs a Bruce Timm. Some sort of defined art direction for their anima… https://t.co/qlX1E9FPUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[me voting for @jeddy24k twice for shortest senior https://t.co/SsEt6mJuOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[He even defeated the Monstars with a team consisting of Bugs Bunny, Bill Murray and Newman #GOAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMKSESPN @RealMichaelKay @DonLagreca @Rosenbergradio  The new rejoin still photos on @TMKSonYES remind me of the J… https://t.co/f15HtN2zah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our gas log fireplace has a glass front panel.   Kynadee asked "If our fireplace has that big glass on it, how does… https://t.co/JWQqHCzD1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Ronnie Howard is from Duncan okla down there that Jeff Duncan Dad Gary Duncan is his name now out there around… https://t.co/VpdwZC5DTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhxSaltyDog @dom_monte @t_creer54 @joshualovern87 The thing that is going to hurt UVU is that Pope was also called… https://t.co/6beieRAuWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump announces recovery of American hostage in Yemen @CNN https://t.co/zdYkLvLVuA. Santa Rosa boy Rob O’Brien reco… https://t.co/GkNnXAn0bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eagle1Wrestling boys take 2nd and girls take 3rd at Regionals! Several kids going to State next week! Great work i… https://t.co/4P5HD1huyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesserker @TPorter2 @JimCanto @ScottOntiveroz @joshmccormack @DreaVilleneuve @TheComicHunter @matageli… https://t.co/Sp0EpBXpYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rossladycom If they aren't healed they can't heal you, wait upon the LORD who is mighty to save... Don’t let all your efforts go wasted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigirules7 @WKatCrook @SeanMODonnell1 @clark_gasm @Acidic_Blonde @RoeGhost @PoloOrtiz9 @AlikaHope @JanGilson… https://t.co/5doDywuk9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrodriguezVen @realDonaldTrump 😺😺😺😺🎉Con la participación Del Grupo Tirame Algo ! 😸😸😸😸😸😸😸 Hasta la Luz se les fue en la tarima! 😸😸😸😸🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[The deeper, hallowed Halls of prayer involve deep petition, intercession, worship and praise. As our own heart is t… https://t.co/jYLAgSu1KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @mehdirhasan If sweatshop-mavens "create jobs," did the olden plantation masters similarly "create jobs"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UGA_WBB Head Coach Joni Taylor had a baby on Monday... She’s back on the bench tonight.  Incredible! https://t.co/aOgYxX7zif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse tRUMP face the facts your on your own. Not one of those countries trust you. You got a… https://t.co/I4b926JPV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start investing with @Stash today! Get $5 to invest when you use my link: https://t.co/5IP4Eymehj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #WestRaleigh on Hillsborough St and I 440 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fresh out of jail but I still hit a nigga with that glizzy. Back to stealing identity, back to credit card fraud”… https://t.co/5No8wniY1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe you missed my talk last week, but you want to get some #nerd talks in next month to make up for it. Or maybe… https://t.co/ogmueUvJnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The greatest among you will be your servant.” -Matthew 23:11  Lead people by serving them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yalitzaaparicio (@ Egyptian Theater and Courtyard in Los Angeles, CA, US, CA) https://t.co/t4s4JY3I1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmargolis @BlueBoxDave And it certainly doesn't look like the stereotype the left is pushing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilyflutterby @BostonGlobe Phones are a sort of prison.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HI… https://t.co/pgoXhCqpbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the gym to blow off steam is counterproductive when you just get angry at people using benches to scroll through Instagram.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandauDave @erockradio Starting at 36:45 Anthony starts the Dave Herman songs https://t.co/B7U9mL3Rob]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made my day. We work really hard to make sure we @kittyhawkio customers succeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Store within a store: Can Walmart CarSaver change how you buy a car? #CarSaver #walmart #auto  https://t.co/V25DnrpSpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one to many times had a bug with misspelling a string so now I have a MagicStrings.swift file that stores a… https://t.co/1wzeSsZ3Oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m over here dancing in front of the mirror to throwbacks like i don’t have an 8am tomorrow lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just one reason why Boone is not the answer...he is lost in managing personnel and a terrible tactical in g… https://t.co/hzlrRkYZn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster Should already be one.  This proves you’re recycling everything from the old show.  When is the Hindenburg hoax? 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[In November my A1C was 15.5 and I was hit with a wave of diabetic issues. Today my A1C is 6.8 and I feel wonderful.… https://t.co/gu9SkFtjSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep with gum in my mouth and I’ve been chewing it for over 24 hours don’t judge me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/OAvUPboSn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comando ejecuta a 14 personas dentro de un bar en Salamanca; tres más son ultimados en Silao https://t.co/eSlz336CdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher When you idolize any individual to the extent that you are willing to defend them no matter how unaccept… https://t.co/lDgX1LkNuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JReagan31 @ayy_train Lmao that’s where I’m at but also my heart breaks for her man.. that’s some FUCKED UP behavior...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a professional salesperson, there are only three activities that make you money. Prospecting, presenting… https://t.co/RlVqHuFh4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@falibey @JoeR42 @jodikantor Yes, because the government is so competent when it comes to solving big problems.  Duh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corruption Will Continue In NCAA College Basketball Until Schools Can Openly Pay Their Players via @forbes https://t.co/Vc1AJVyLUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaRadio @pepsi @CocaCola That’s where we differ, @CocaCola for me over @pepsi whenever there’s a choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios @TheRealStanLee @Marvel While I have not been a fan of the movie revi… https://t.co/8kAVKPJJv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 Shocking! I thought she would prefer one of her own kind. Reptilian. She’s kinda particular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A) Griffey is the best. B) Bagwell’s is also legendary. C) how is Sosa not on this list?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottishSun I dunno, my wife had a visit from Aunt Flo and she was not giving me the impression that it was “beautiful” 😬😳😲😂🤣😂🤣🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prototype for taking the @AccelTex "Everyman" to the next level!  #3DPrinted mount in the works https://t.co/ndjdH6BX5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how the troops will like Trump stealing their rainy day funds to pay for his unnecessary border wall?   Pe… https://t.co/EwwNryJD1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this thread. Admirable candor and a good look inside what actually goes on in the drug development business (o… https://t.co/jZGSFJLpV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[DON'T VISIT OUR ENEMIES : Word to the wise. IT IS Not safe for American citizens to visit IRAN, RUSSIA, OR NORTH KO… https://t.co/MvhvMWSD3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philliegirl5 ...or a steadily declining bust that will put their club into financial ruins for the foreseeable future. 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets call it the way it is. Jim Jordan looked like an idiot yesterday and even looks worse today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ella casi ni sale, la traicionó el amor Tiene par de amistade', pero no quiere relación 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has Anthony Carrigan received the due attention deserved for his character work as #Hank on #Barry ? He is incredib… https://t.co/2XjBruw73N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright so @krboards20 it’s been a few days, have you recovered from seeing @kelly_clarkson yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mimperia If you’re trying to recruit me to Marquette you have my attention. Are snow plows part of the startup package?]]></document><document><![CDATA[my teammate/best friend is doing 5 events at elite team cup tomorrow. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The founding Father's of this Nation, were intellegent, they were remarkable individuals whom all fought to create… https://t.co/z2fEDj6hJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then it was snacktime! #cupcakes @ Cute Cakes Escondido https://t.co/akTGtIMpBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilybradburyks @ks_press Hey! You and @thatelliotmetz! You two should meet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYRangerFanclub @NHL This is like what happened when they played in Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me for your ticket! I am selling the winner this year!! @BearDownHOCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I was a child, I used to speak like a child, think like a child, reason like a child; when I became a MAN, I… https://t.co/DFZw7AqDtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @chriswaslight @Truth2Dj @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/tAmLGPIfJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterAlexander And of course you’re salivating at this. But regarding the rogue liar McCabe, the White House doesn… https://t.co/nfZMRGEtQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the pile on mustafi. But his ass got caught up field. Which left sokrates on his own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goz_1911 @ROCKONOHIO @PatriotSmirk Because Dems are driven by feelings and fantasy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Amazing that they lay the Bernie love for Russia on @realDonaldTrump Like morphing protest in Cairo to #Benghazi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Album Spotlight March 8, 2019 Featured Albums For March 8, 2019  Mystic Crock - Seduced Sen… https://t.co/8GljmGxMKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Manny1Dream @AdventComics @thefootballgirl I'm glad you said that matters. He was sacked 171 times in only 69 gms… https://t.co/NGg3hbMzsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are demons that dress as angles and try to dim there light but there are also angles who walk with demons to… https://t.co/Y9MFEoMAuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Matthew Lair, the recipient of the Von and Jo Knight Scholarship! The award was presented to him… https://t.co/z6lHWXlGK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMichaelGibson The article (not your tweet)is a bit of a false narrative. There were specialists providing care vi… https://t.co/DFNsWVnswY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard The true power of the left is to make something up then on que everyone talks about it being true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ian_miller157 @zzsmiller @OHSAASports VA ? And I believe their tournament(s) are in small HS gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misguidedmommy Absolutely right. After 18 I’ll regroup to see if I’ve come down from that high... and then start again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACHockeyHistory @HockeyHallFame @Capitals That's great. Enjoy the moments!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl that truly care about you won’t have you repeating yourself to them all the time. They’ll either make the chang… https://t.co/4uKnCjgoPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation How is this going to end hallway medicine and help suicidal patients?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/oSpT7gMpmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aussiedutchman @Teamfrench23 @MichaelClayto15 @AmyOlsonGolf @jutanugarn @LPGAMedia Bull hockey. No rule broken, no… https://t.co/vPiQ1aD64Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tijuana Mexican Lager by Consorcio Cervecero de Baja California at @theredhot — https://t.co/vqKTuA94w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[apparently one of the ceiling fans in my living room wasn’t connected properly and i just hadn’t noticed. it just s… https://t.co/BBaIlD6G0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well said. This is about an overall problem of corruption. The @cwa_nj and @NJEA have not represented thier members… https://t.co/mOFIemWWtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_woke_yolk Went through the first Tour School there in fall of 1982. Balls would land in center of greens and c… https://t.co/Os3Twjqs4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drpichel totalmente de acuerdo con su opinion de @MarcoAmeglio. Me parece q es muy autoritario e imponente, y cier… https://t.co/D1CN4cDX8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some parents love showing off their kids but me I love showing off my dogs! 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so tired of seeing this on my timeline. We have men that ACTUALLY rape and don’t get jail time so shut the fuck… https://t.co/dCdkgDIG0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @AWorldOutOfMind Politics are broken, having a criminal get away with what he’s getting away with. W… https://t.co/PSx11JFGlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was one of the best professors I had @CSUPueblo. The whole @mccnm department was really fantastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you expecting something when someone you know gets on. You a bum. Go out and get your own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alita: Battle Angel”. Behind The Scenes. Eisa Salazar #alitabattleangel #austintexas #moviestills #ricotorresphoto… https://t.co/ckBwDdh1cV]]></document></documents></author>