<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My mom and her boyfriend (who happens to be a year younger than mine🤦🏻‍♀️), have been drunk singing Sam Smith songs… https://t.co/gesGBOXKHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ask for support for SB462, outdoor recreation helps diversify the state's economy, lifts up rural communities, a… https://t.co/ybyWZ1eq4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy due to the politics the luster of watching is gone.  Our family will not be watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate Still waiting for the Fed charges Sending yourself hate mail laced with Tylenol is not smart. Using USPS not good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel for the girl. 'I am not a racist': Student who wrote op-ed titled 'Should White Boys Still Be Allowed to Tal… https://t.co/PaRYV5tBsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elegant French Country Estate in Loudoun County available at $1,299,000. Contact Michele Cornejo at Hunt Country So… https://t.co/9qbjUshEIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicodinu1 @sami_dg89 @DimashifiedDear @DimashIfied @Lindsay07474358 @tweetingdears @pgrullion @dimash_best… https://t.co/aVYpNddjVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, Have a Great Week! #MyrtleBeach #MondayMotivation https://t.co/U337FA9Q2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 more days till I’m at Walt Disney World. Glad I haven’t been skipping leg day. https://t.co/7BbP9fmxjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[VICTORY IN THE HOUSE!!!!!!!! Now it’s go time @ the Senate. What can you do?  Call 1-866-368-5630 and tell your Sen… https://t.co/cfrsm9FBat]]></document><document><![CDATA[The UU World magazine with the problematic content arrived in mail yesterday, had to decide what to do with it. Dec… https://t.co/dwjMJPXqya]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Black History month! Bringing The black vanilla to the front boxiparklakenona #fashionstylist… https://t.co/eNhuwU5hsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a blessed day everyone @ The Auditorium at The Douglass https://t.co/t7IMc6awEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TYFofficial @summer0001 Congratulations! A #TYFOscars lucky winner happy dance for you! https://t.co/oaFfz3wFj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 🎁@tperez3826 #GIVEAWAY AT 1,000 FOLLOWERS🎁 . @BM_Cosmetics is now available at @ultabeauty. . -  . 💜 💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜… https://t.co/8AMEg2FSAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every paper I wrote in college would get a note about spell checking.  I carried that over to twitter.   #Delicate… https://t.co/CXi2WZpnSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a little late seeing these holiday ads, but, still fun times... obviously.😉 https://t.co/EimcFWLJxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfredSchulz @movingsideways Blind? Start here https://t.co/gH1hRIsSWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un New York prime en menos de $5, short rib prime en $6 y sencillo... toda la compra como en $43... luego me pregun… https://t.co/mx8LdK5JxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[house babes in LA!!!! ... who's down for a shuffle sesh all together ??? Blast some music and just dance away 💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah it's an effect it's a hate crime targeting and harassing yeah it's a chain effect with these women forcoverups]]></document><document><![CDATA[#badvibesforever #badvibes #streetart @ Melrose Avenue https://t.co/GShZA4mwPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my sons @ogscrappy @kameronblount4 Gonna miss them ballin out there under the Friday Night Lights! #SMAC… https://t.co/1vul7tUkRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only time Five has ever looked like the kid he physically is is when he sees his dead brother. #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.e.m, breathin, everytime, goodnight n go ☁️☁️☁️ Imagine, needy, nasa, bloodline, fake smile, bad idea, make up, i… https://t.co/KkeuTSXUtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bbq chicken, pork belly, and riblettes with white rice &amp; cucumber salad for dinner was so bomb 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @adambeam — welcome to Sacramento, from a former Bluegrass-er. Congrats on the new gig!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 12 days I’ll be in Boston for more of this at @conageddon 2 What a great time last year! And this year our… https://t.co/eM9JOEpasO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my friends and my family , please my God just bless  my love ones. Thank you jesus for your blessing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateSPEHA @JuliaNesheiwat How upset would you be if you found out that muscle knots can be removed immediately an… https://t.co/ASE0lCwUQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want it to be Thursday already I want my new bedroom set and mattress already]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to laugh it off. Buisness cards of famous people #mirth #snicker #grin #cute https://t.co/xQJBXenP5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think she missed her calling....she should of been a stand up comic 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsvu starts Now!!! RT if your watching! @Mariska @FINALLEVEL @KelliGiddish @PeterScanavino #SVU #Brothel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your resume 📝 is about selling why YOU are special! 🌟 It's not just a run-down list of your skills, but what YOU di… https://t.co/RXxN6HKpzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamen131 @charliekirk11 I think the people who showed up at his rally in El Paso made their views pretty clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sabres ⚔️@SabreKevin1639 @jimmyreu81 @SabresFunStats @lno09281978 @MsAFromBK @Crazy4OReilly90 @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/X4fb3mkyUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cumbriaoldrural @AdaireWillow @sprigwig @traceys294 Awe she blocked me too! Veruca Salt didn't get what she wanted… https://t.co/GuhRCILk9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrenPetel Interesting! I don’t think I’ve ever seen how it’s made, although I tried it once while skating around dows lake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coach gets absolved from blame cause they're RARELY hands on with that part. Guess who gets blamed and faces th… https://t.co/OrV4PTqd84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearing off the latest round of snow here in Minnesota be like.........  @PascoSheriff #MoveToPasco https://t.co/9eyo7keCMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@48hours @SLRice_76 In the first semester of Psychology our professor gave us the assignment to watch The Silence o… https://t.co/Hn9GSvqiTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we #fans are so very #excited. And Eric you had Doug's back all the way!  Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laraeparker on the flip side of this can we get tattoos that if we need a hysterectomy due to the severity of endo… https://t.co/3FHeGC1Bbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Mr. Levin, we've been so frustrated watching these people keep lying about this and the people on Fox nev… https://t.co/wyckE6i2OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodness .. bless all these wonderful young people! Making a positive difference. 😭❤️ WATCH: Emotional video shows… https://t.co/0Y1aY21EM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was just always losing the remote but I found out that my dog has a new game called “steal mom’s remote… https://t.co/GPYVPKuoiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright #planetshakers here's some behind the scenes shots on  location 💯 what a wonderful partnership @smartwater… https://t.co/RfQLIYANDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jujo28 @NicolleDWallace Meadow meltdown because he thought Rep Talib called him a Racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Real Housewives:  "Now these earrings are a bit more reasonable. They are only $80,000."  I need to get to… https://t.co/5msGn9PZ5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/VI1Y2yAHJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A grateful heart protects one from negative thinking.  Choose your emotions wisely.  #truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @DCTFTW @AOC Ooh your mistaken its TRUMP donating his salary....not AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they say they are black, and this is what I want them to look like https://t.co/Kazfjsbbhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley I gave this book to my sister in hopes I will get it back. Haha it was a present.]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% the womans fault.  I am #TeamJaguar on this one.  You can invade someone's personal space - their home - and e… https://t.co/CLpaIT7Y00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aye_kyn_ From 2013 LMFAO your dumb😂😂 go get into some shot with somebody else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuteness overload!!!!! @AmericanIdol @LukeBryanOnline #LukeBryan #AmericanIdol https://t.co/ggK4LmViqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved these jumpsuits on aclu and @kflay at ACLU concert at #SxSW @ Downtown Austin https://t.co/Q3u4YNJzTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport He's one of Trump's top henchmen, so he might think that it would be in his best interest to run to M… https://t.co/I4YC2X5uam]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of men leaving hyvee at 5:00 with a dozen roses is astounding/amazing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimisanauthor37 @cspan @ChuckGrassley I wouldn't expect less from a liberal who believes not knowing who comes and… https://t.co/rfmC2U2OZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wut? Somehow, I think even our Fastpass is going to take forever! https://t.co/fo1xGDQVXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monyb89 @interjet Thank youuuuu @monyb89 I haven’t really announced it yet but I was FORCED to since @interjet has… https://t.co/5FX97V8M99]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m happy it’s the weekend. I can do my chores, sleep and spend some time decompressing because it’s been intense]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know , at this point I’m tired of apologizing for my attitude . It’s just who I am , don’t take it personal. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashBackFriday #FBF #FridayFeeling #grateful #ff #selfie #appreciate #cheers https://t.co/xN8AXAGU38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who remembers the iMac G3? @mariodiaz gave me a red one for my birthday in 1998. He lugged the giant box to my birt… https://t.co/X3gmtKcphV]]></document><document><![CDATA[and then he goes “yeah i got lost in the waves” ... 💀 https://t.co/hN4AJXdULV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyThomasSco Awesome clip! I still miss the original main house, even though they made improvements on the current Newman home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGuyInOKC I do. All the time. I’m just a lot older than them and don’t know if they really understand how much i a… https://t.co/YzGW2P67JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodkingjon @thethimbleful Sansa after looking at Robin for one second: https://t.co/eBPj2DJlCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elected Officials from the state of Michigan attending a weekend filled with advanced education, including public p… https://t.co/7ZZbCgt0yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My throat is really going to start feeling scratchy, huh??? If I get sick, I'm gonna be so angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweaterbeats @Sum41 This is everything thank you for taking me back. Nostalgia at its finest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniiogarza21 Twitter should be easy!! I can’t believe they haven’t yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t that what pelosie said. We’d have time to pursue our passions, with no job.  These people are lunatics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marlene_241 Hopefully we’re able to go back sipping on some Mai Tais soon ):]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last shift with all graduating players on the ice. Why not finish with a goal. 🎉Well done @HeronHockey and congrats… https://t.co/YtEt4GHmUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have idolized these women since SNL and mean girls. They’re funny, smart, will kick your ass, and do it in a full… https://t.co/tMh0bBMNpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[people really drive their tractors around town &amp; i think it’s hilarious lmao if only they had a sport mode bc them shits slooooow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Huntingn @IlhanMN Truth about what please enlighten me. I am missing a big part of the truth I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[(- I Get To Love You It’s The Best Thing That I’ll Ever Do -)  #InItToBennett2019 #49days #IGetToLoveYou… https://t.co/hhNzreQ56g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it silly of me to stop enjoying a tv show due to the fact that the fandom is so toxic?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angrysatan6661 @docjkcardinal will tell ya I shouldn’t be near any type of darts 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so I went out on a limb and ordered @PapaJohns last night. Worst decision ever. I waited almost 2 hours from whe… https://t.co/EvhXxpH00O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithClaverie Spartan is way better than Snow. Ughhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhjh Jon Snow is so fucking emo and brooding and… https://t.co/lpPlxnLgZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Brighton, MI? View our latest opening: https://t.co/lAJaUgTTkd #HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eglane66 @ABCDEder123 @RidgewoodES Such a great 💡 ! I’d love to 👂🏻 more .]]></document><document><![CDATA[my babysitting job got canceled &amp; the mom still sent the money to my bank account 😩 blessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Staged: 1017 Shell Blvd #12, FOSTER CITY, CA 94404 | MLS# ML81737233 | Redfin - https://t.co/ByMlLd7E32… https://t.co/z9sUB72smP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I have to work why can't I just sit at home and watch the spoons in the microwave sparkkkk :((]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weights. Leg day! 4 sets of 10 with 25 lb weights on each side 🏋 #gym #gymrat #weights #lafitness… https://t.co/m31Ffcb4Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, at this point I feel like they’re just kink shaming Laura for enjoying some erotic asphyxiation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump SAD!! CHRISTIAN ARE NOT VOTING FOR ANYONE WHO IS WILLING TO COMMIT MURDER!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameKween @samsmith Yes! I was hoping you were a @samsmith fan! He and @Adele baby! My two favorites. Speak to my soul music]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distinct_Words It Sounds like she's crying over being black instead of proud! When you go around saying this happe… https://t.co/3UNrTlFgi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_leslian @CrispyHannah this reminds me of when we were at first Friday trying to eat and that girl was recording in the street lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabes que eres docente cuando escuchas más de 20 voces y sin mirar ya sabes exactamente a quien pertenece cada una]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been restless for countless nights. I can’t wait to put all these ideas I have in my mind into fruition. I hop… https://t.co/BVGuoNHpZs]]></document></documents></author>