<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Si se te acusa es por que vimos las consecuencias de tu período asecino narco corrupto tranza millones huimos de me… https://t.co/09ffoDwZye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonaevolentatis @Kate_Amara @aarostew @WanderNWoodsman @images_mc @udarnik @texbrodave1 @nailbomb3 @marymjoneil… https://t.co/pMtH95F8tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This a sacrilege AND Will NEVER EVEEERRRRRRRR.....EVER EVER EVER have a place in a traditional mexican home. No señ… https://t.co/yFfHLwPGl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright, let’s consider. the @FBI  showed their hand.and we may or may not have cleaned the vipersout of the nest.… https://t.co/Yq5EdlfA4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nataliew1020 This poor baby, thank God she has folks that love her! She looks happy as hell, God bless her and her family!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran How ironic that you call these “listening”. You somehow only listen to your GOP Senate colleagues. You… https://t.co/2nPxiBvQkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJordanRachel DEMORATS has nothing.  President @POTUS eventually will get tired and retired from White House.  But will be on:  2025]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Building a new home was the opportunity to get the kitchen we wanted’ https://t.co/38F1VvxvR1 via @IrishTimesHome… https://t.co/QKmSSerTJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra Lo mismo pasa con cuentas donde los pro-amlo insultan y saturan cuentas por ejemplo la de calderón.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danw8477 I wouldn't. I'd strip 'me down to their skivvies and drop them off in the woods and tell them they have t… https://t.co/u4ptvHtN46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTVLebanonNews كل أسبوع يطل علينا الجيش ببيان ك هذا لماذا لا يقوم الجيش بتدمير هذا الزورق عندما يدخل الماء الاقلمي… https://t.co/2euF1o36DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[T. Boone Pickens: My Advice On How To Jump Start Any Meeting.  @okstate @DougCarel @KandyceMitchell @mitchelltalks… https://t.co/4Xp7phGMV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RattusDaddus Also, has the actual FBI ever come out and said anything about the investigation? Seems limenit's alw… https://t.co/25pKVbUPUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect 9th inning for @Doliver05, getting swinging strike out to end it.  15-1 Alabama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanShilinsky @Americareform @Ken_Rosenthal Of course you cant say never but its certainly highly unlikely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my big bro @coachT10 and  @wrenhsbaseball on opening day at @NaturChemInv. #PRIDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcarmody Both Donna Reed and her TV daughter Shelley Fabares. I refuse to discuss this further.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenWNEP And then ALL the stars come to the team next year plus Bugs Bunny  - looks like we got ourselves a story..that’s all folks]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all never got lost for a full three days in Blackreach, you never played Skyrim https://t.co/fb9oPYNm7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BR_MLB @MLB Is it me or does anyone else think that Tebow is best suited as a DH on an AL team?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@49er_Frank Better than current, but we'd be back in this situation fifty years later IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst day of year ride. Ha Keith had a flat - Drinking a Ruby Zozzle by @hiwheelwines at @hiwheelwines  — https://t.co/iWlZuEuPn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinoReddit @kk_naval_94 @guardian @CNathan_Kwan I like it. All flash and no substance. Is this your big run up to… https://t.co/QZyob6LfiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the best nutrition bar on the market? #tunein to Sports Medicine Weekly @670TheScore and find out. Karen Mal… https://t.co/bDxcCGJHcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceSports Yeah I’m with you. I also know that coaches can have at least a little influence on conference schedul… https://t.co/c9IRB6Mfnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mileswhip @skuldyie @autoslash Thanks! I have a booking through AutoSlash already but will check this out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limbaugh: Immigration Is an Emergency — Our ‘Culture’ at Risk from ‘Parade of Illegal People Who Are Uneducated’ https://t.co/g1iJ2vkDAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must do and no else can do it for you. I ain’t being taken out by distractions! https://t.co/ioSmkETvay]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were minus one partner in shenanigans (and I’m sure we’ll all make up for it soon). Good times were had. Damage… https://t.co/ubznbalqxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX61News Well he better change his stance again .. gas tax grocery tax income tax inheritance tax .Now tolls!!! T… https://t.co/ncIqeYTpe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're never too young to save for #retirement. https://t.co/71NN4XgVXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maby80 Bello té va a quedar el traje naranja de presa en una carcel en La Haya, lastima que no podrás usar el IPhone capitalista]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #Millstone! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/IUFqa7o0sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin lugar a la más mínima duda @ReinaldoPared consolida y fortalece a cada minuto este formidable proyecto de nació… https://t.co/MVT6mGhWn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Trout stocking at its finest. You gotta wonder if the plane ride is more expensive than trucking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceonyc Thx for the reply, much appreciated. 👍👊🏼.  Sounds like 25k is the magic number for quality deals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #RelicsandRarities how soon after release will a video go to YouTube?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/vsFjjTaA5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ojalá la directiva hable con @AlonsoDT no puede darse el lujo de batallar con un equipo infinitamente inferior a es… https://t.co/HSzHsV4N3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacheryRhys @Spunked6 @lucasleonxxx It’s called “acting” haha it doesn’t happen often!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmerForFLSen @live4literacy @emceeleman Don’t keep showing ur ignorance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking around a pastor’s conference with a big beard gives me insight into the females who receive a lot of male attention. #ShepCon2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senjudiciary Eastern Kentucky Harlan County 3rdWorld Country in America! Monticello Bank Umbilical To Socialism! C… https://t.co/ljMqammUPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[w/ Jonathan, Colin, Corey...many others (@ Alamo Drafthouse One Loudoun - @alamodc in Ashburn, VA) https://t.co/CT1IKDG58y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention baby boomers: recent Harvard business school grads will soon be bidding for your plumbing and/or janitori… https://t.co/Dcxq8log4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @POTUS @NASA @SpaceX We need USS Enterprise &amp; Captain Kirk a reality.  If we police space the world will be a safer place for all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamaluna @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/LWfnJ7HB8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real fat loss equation... do you dig it?  #losefat #weightloss #eatrealfood #foodprep #fitnessgoals… https://t.co/up7Pa4MxdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Success is what you do before and after you do everything you’re supposed to do.” @Nely_Galan  _ #riseandgrind @TheSharkDaymond]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevormichigan Sure is! And Vasey got 3rd. Strable wasn’t in the bracket that year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenfinerman Check this out #Comcast likes 👉this #you should too #no contracts https://t.co/NqNOcnGffM #going… https://t.co/xVHEu1Ucbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for 2,000 subscribers reached today!  New rotor wash Phoenix FD 3Ds Max tutorial: https://t.co/IT4MEq0BI6… https://t.co/9PQWi6XLhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frefreddiehaut3 I never got on the thing growing up. I am afraid of heights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyapatiaLee Remember in high school learning about,  "His Excellency, President for Life, Field Marshal Al Hadji D… https://t.co/2Bx3mDIMVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think anyone needs to persuade anyone that teaching is tough. Trying to help 20+ students to grow and learn… https://t.co/k2m1c5LvWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Past nine games: 14.1 PPG, 7.2 RPG , 1.2 SPG , 2.4 BPG , 1.6 3PG in 28.8 minutes with a net rating of +18. Whew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveCoker_PFFG @VinnieMessina @1159leader @TruthRX Somewhere an independent thought alarm has gone off. They don’t like when that happens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 4 came out to Wolf of Wall Street, Infinity war , home alone and pulp fiction .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested to see if CNBC classifies a 0.2% down day as a sell off... perhaps another episode of markets in turmoil?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trafficAIRPORT @ANTONI3ROMERO @cperez1962 @carlaangola @jguaido @AsambleaVE @TAMARA_SUJU @NicolasMaduro No going Back!!! Awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HzqXykMiXa  hey you, yeah you!  go watch my friends on YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awolf14 I made the grave error of watching Hank and I started sobbing and Christa had to come hold me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sailing_LaVaga The plural is, all y’all.  I keep just missing meeting you - in Malta, in Abaco, in Florida, etc.… https://t.co/8Pf2BGTWPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling the @AnovaCulinary into action. 129F/90 minutes. Salt only. https://t.co/ebml6mEWzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am almost convinced that if the Church doesn't get on her knees, pray, and: 1. Repent for her Laodicean living 2.… https://t.co/IVnLs4IC7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexjager7 @RealKentMurphy It’s the contact bro, if your team had that balls to the wall guy that would bury the b… https://t.co/ScPNsnR4J1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jockedupgeek It is and maybe it shouldn’t be acceptable. And to some people it isn’t, I think it’s just kind of li… https://t.co/zoLtTNNEcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrepDigChris @1stAllianceVBC @DGNVolleyball Thank you for your perspective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettHolden4 Son, hard to argue your picks!! However, I would have to sub out Graham for Thomas Robinson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lookner Why anyone trust @Tesla is beyond me. Without govt subsidies they'd have imploded years ago ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salbed @soledadobrien 3.1 Billion dollar net worth from 515 businesses. If that’s failing as a business man, idk if I want to succeed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embid runs into Young, making to attempt to avoid him, as he is in the air going to the basket... not a flagrant at all? #Pacers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soulgoddess1111 I appreciate your positivity but I don't believe this includes me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stalk is OVER! The #Epic #FlyyGirl #Screenplay By #OmarTyree is HERE! @ https://t.co/mKoF5etmFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatifisaidit Me too Girly Girl. I thought AOC's questions and demeanor were on point, and well presented.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm almost done my rewatch and I don't think I've ever looked forward to a series more than this. Also, we stan Gendry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @01ravenking @GeanineC @AW95NJ @rkline56 @Libphobic @gator4kb18 @KevinMFerrara @trumpAngel45… https://t.co/kwpZsIb5q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my guy, you still small tho ‼️🤭 @Rocco_Dsouza_ https://t.co/HHam6ZjVY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @highbrow_nobrow That's not how any of this is supposed to work @LindseyGrahamSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReporterGarriss The ceiling is the roof. Now get up and seize the day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si te vi 🙊 . #Fortnite #Season8 #Temporada8 #FortniteBattleRoyal #Multiplayer #FortniteXbox #Gaming #Headshot… https://t.co/Zlwzm8OGTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys. I miss my classic. Movie. Review. Podcast. Pls donate. https://t.co/IQuTL5Fi1R @jackferry99 @mmitchelldaviss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marnues @Marlon_Boarnet @kimmaicutler Race relations in America are tricky things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougNelson16 @BaseballBros I’m surprised we finish a season before June in Western New York. I believe last year t… https://t.co/JBLljToaQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí llegando otros cuatro caballos: Sergio Robles, Salomé Barojas, Mario Mendoza y Ángel Moreno.   El gran Kalimán… https://t.co/wvKpcKJb8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connolly206 @langfordjazz @MLB @NFL Good point about Grant’s point excellence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakehparker Thanks man, it’s at 5:30 so we’ll see if I actually get up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#California California's high speed rail canceled  Ten BILLION wasted on the force Chu Chu train https://t.co/G3J7tTGhJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the US Congress is still giving Big Oil billions in annual taxpayer subsidies, and @realDonaldTrump is t… https://t.co/YQUtkiWkA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime @RuPaulsDragRace comes on, I’m gonna be checking out @Lesdoggg’s tweets EVERY time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw @captainmarvel !! Whooooo - what a great time! @brielarson is kicking ass and empowering women. Funny af.… https://t.co/foGqTz0P7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Babes @ANGELAWHITE @MarkusDupree I loved seeing this video of @ANGELAWHITE  😘😍❤️ You're a sweetheart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a 👀 at the 8 playoff teams in our division this weekend in #Indiana PA! #PAHL #FinalStandings #LetsGoWildcats https://t.co/OspZc6XXZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tom_Parkin_ It's good on principle, but it's bad optics for the NDP to work with a party that's chasing the bigot… https://t.co/zjIdLD3c51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few more weeks until MY pitchers report for their first high school season! https://t.co/vA3qAMKwgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealClancyBrown I met @bexmader &amp; @SamWitwer at two different comic cons in the same year in 2014 https://t.co/OtkfJWY9D8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvanpat @_ReaalAmerican_ Yeah but who the nominee ends up being is an entirely different story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentAxeMedia I believe it was you who in fact coined the phrase “free throws matter”. Now, FTs weren’t their only… https://t.co/pkNTIXoacR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Giltor26 My mom was like watch out Jess we’re getting to the point too 😭😭😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rory McIlroy DTL Iron - From a fairway bunker 3/9/19 @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/pRuqX3u6Me]]></document></documents></author>