<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hubs, watching the news: Seems like manhunts are always "massive." You never hear about a casual manhunt. #Philosopher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EroticMadSci hmmm.  If I keep it in my office at all times and use it as a photo prop I *might* get away with writ… https://t.co/JB70Jz0vUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregFieldsWX and I were jammin to the same songs in the 90’s :) we both got the songs within the first 2seconds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolDannhauser Loved catching up in sunny space of your spanking new Fairfield County Writing Lab by @MetroNorth… https://t.co/tH4t7AhQ6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lordstown’s Drive It Home campaign sends special Valentine’s treats to GM CEO Mary Barra and the GM Board of Direct… https://t.co/hg1qgd45QO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been a troublemaker so today was my first time convoked to the Principal’s Office. I’m grateful it was f… https://t.co/pS4VyPb9yS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys, i'm still pretty sure this whole "more cowbell thing" is based on the sound of a WOODBLOCK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Kiosk Attendant" at Match Marketing? Applicant tracking systems look for specific keywords… https://t.co/sG7kPIer4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little peekaboo blue/green for this beauty 🧜🏽‍♀️ 🧚‍♂️ ✨✨@thenamestamara  I miss the smell of being in a salon. I… https://t.co/DSKZLIkhIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Esto es un crimen. Señor Presidente, le suplicamos autorice una invasions militar para acabar con este rég… https://t.co/2konhS6VjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mastercheftang A couple of my favorite dishes is lo mein and beef with broccoli still have not been able to master… https://t.co/mXxQcAYZIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stronger, more organized storms more likely west of Chattanooga today, but we are still at risk for seeing severe s… https://t.co/9NRyZ6RQ61]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep.. Just like this.. #onesies #pajamas #nightvibes https://t.co/NzDcO1cAdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 2 wine nights planned with girlfriends then huge family party this weekend 2 totally different vibes but I’m ready 😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nate Anderson from @jfftweets days rate of change and occupational shifts massive and daily. Need intentional engag… https://t.co/qcUpxv3mmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone replied to me and said girls that are bad drivers have the biggest hearts.  I FELT THAT. 😂 what do y’all ex… https://t.co/YSnnGpewry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nation_myers @nyyrobinson @JeffGordonWeb @FS1 @NASCARONFOX I S3COND THAT 🤗🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[5.6.7.8. (three) legendary ladies keeping me up on a school night @ Antone's Nightclub https://t.co/7dyPlSBfya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RufusBlaq I should have consulted with God before I helped a lot of people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CincyChildrens can U please tell me the purpose of the registration kiosk on the desk in front of the human? I wou… https://t.co/syBtfK3NBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shazrinee @Big12Conference @KUTrack @KUAthletics Congratulations Sharon, we are so excited for you and we will con… https://t.co/OSoTDtSCuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanBenedict @PayyElizabeth But yes a lot warmer .. still come back !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[While farmers are a small share of the U.S. population today, the farm lobby is still strong. One reason is that fa… https://t.co/U3nGd9SFbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeAndAlexShow I go with money, but if you do something you love it's not really working... And I have the best of both worlds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[all y’all hatin on me for drinking nattys i bet these will be in your hands soon 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryndenBFish I am only a young girl and know little of such matters... I’m not even an official voice of the fando… https://t.co/yIrZxjzFTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The Parasitic Professions of Banking, Lawyering, and Accounting stereotypically belong to that ethnic group.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im off the clock &amp; having regan &amp; jill making me drinks &amp; LOL i love being on the other side of the bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s 30 degree weather but you refuse to stop wearing crop tops...  . . . . . #nashville #cantstopwontstop… https://t.co/GuD0PlRhlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can hear my ass now... “UM HELL NO! DONT YOU DARE THROW MY YOUNGIN LIKE THAT!” *grabs the kids and heads to the c… https://t.co/vXiOgCNwMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at @thehamiltondc, we’re opening for #RoomfulOfBlues at 8pm trio style with @VitarelloChris on guitar and n… https://t.co/QzW0Ng9FC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the @nyurbanleague @argyleyarnshop and the recipients of this year’s Champions of Diversity awar… https://t.co/YPyD8iQZ56]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re telling me in ONE weekend mir and kole met chris and marisa hung out in venice and jessie and troy met jake… https://t.co/mqRfAzAfo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Évaluations en santé mentale: les psychologues veulent contribuer à réduire l'attente #santémentale #psychologie… https://t.co/sKBgwGsDQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr what fruits of the spirit are exhibited by trump? Kindness? Love? Joy? Peace? Patience? Goodness? F… https://t.co/yx8WuUBsJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to cut down on the sweets. If any of y’all see me eat some sugary bullshit please give me a swift kick to the nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonInga @SGottliebFDA That meeting was a waste of time. Come on didn’t everyone know that. Time to stop begging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhh game-changer...printed on #stickynotes so I can add them to my new product lists for all of my customer mail… https://t.co/AYPNMBwTvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe she will be charged before that.  The UN would laugh her out of there anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNCBank_Help I DMed you about some issues on my account- hope to hear from you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmeeagles Using models really help with scientific understanding of large concepts. https://t.co/1z4dD3jszm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Don't know if he's guilty of rape but he sure is guilty of being an ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliies I’m thinking about then when I wake up late I can do my homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[#faithandaktion https://t.co/kVPOazlana #TrustingGod #TrustTheProcess #TrustYourDopeness #TerriMonique #tbi… https://t.co/km54vGbkaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jocelyn_Vilter @AddisonBrothers Probably a lot? Can I wrap my legs in Saran wrap for waterproofing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crying during first period has set my mood for the rest of the day, I'm such a sensitive dumb bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Protect_Wldlife @rickygervais It is their right to not be killed by cowards like you two assholes!  Hope you rot in hell!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hatschebutz @wurzel260654 @Kuma_the_Cat @honkatt @KatersWelt @MauSupercat @TribeOfMa @fluffybasil @FFlauschkatze… https://t.co/AWh4ldOMsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopherSpiro Among GND, expanding SS etc - I worked in primary care - it’s not sinusitis and rashes - our pts are s… https://t.co/ZlwX8feXKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit! I’m so sore it’s not okay. I can’t even get myself out of bed this morning 🥴 I need to be a person and make… https://t.co/PJoUipgdEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[ima be mad if the outfit i’m thinking of in my head don’t look good for tonight😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at all these #FakeMelania pictures like https://t.co/IQQY7wdIWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did @photojimmy have our daughter watching this?? She done dang near watched his whole channel 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otherwise, was the additional money for more “catch and kills” you may know about. cc: @arimelber @mayawiley… https://t.co/Ioouja0zHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashBO4yuh I know, believe me! But you are doing great. At this point it's just like one day at a time]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fantasticfriday #horsesinmyheart #bubbles #horses #horsesinmybackyard #boysjustwanttohavefun #friendships… https://t.co/q9Wnj6HkVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time trying @AviationGin in my dirty martini... how have I lived before? 👏🍸 https://t.co/TUGkCT9Z2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50kft_K @wydmindfeersart @Arthur59611540 @splcenter @Dangchick1 @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems @IntlCrimCourt… https://t.co/OqTLohLFSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@late2game I think it is tougher for men to make deep friendships. I note that the older men I know, have one frien… https://t.co/O1IxNwNrqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent start for SPICE in round 1 in St Louis https://t.co/7CkVws9p7s @FIDE_chess @EuropeEchecs @WOMChess https://t.co/GSJTWVvlvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BibleBeltDarlin Obstruct our President and that's about it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coastalent1 @1SteveBurton Me too love this gorgeous photo of @1SteveBurton!! So excited 4 new cities hoping the Ca… https://t.co/qXRZTzzbV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS @HelpStopHate @gatewaypundit Agree. Stop voting for these crazies]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband just called and said he’s coming home early today, rn. I don’t have nearly enough time to get out of bed… https://t.co/Kt9CF25Cpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmay658 Man I’m so glad Captain Marvel is the last Jedi what a plot twist I never saw it coming am I right]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IAmShook around midnight my car alarm went off. My car was ok. The other car in our driveway had the drivers side… https://t.co/ueHGtkHkWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eekamouse13 I am right! lol I laugh at people who brag abut their wealth.Showing off their cars etc... I think, th… https://t.co/SLZOXthGS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am declaring myself a holy woman. Because we can do that now. https://t.co/5AwEc5yGXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @gatewaypundit Can’t she be aborted or at least deported??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@07reddevilz @SportsHackCA @DominicSeifert @TH3_GOAT_ Curry could not lead a team by himself he’s a great shooter a… https://t.co/tSXEZLVeL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am doing me. The way God intended. I'm resourceful, intelligent and very giving. 💯 For years and years I lent my… https://t.co/hf4BGrnVue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmpireFOX you need to fire @JussieSmollett the guy is a lying attention seeking fool. I am a @realDonaldTrump SUPP… https://t.co/H3C0Rm0XbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary I just love how he grabbs my penis https://t.co/JvinLLApSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The B.C. Court of Appeal has sent the Vancouver Aquarium back to court over its attempt to quash a park board bylaw… https://t.co/HOtVYNg306]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Affirmatively @Kybelle1957Liz @cspanwj Pay for it, and start building to your hearts content...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @IvankaTrump: Did your father, over the objections of national security personnel, order Don McGahn to grant y… https://t.co/lBJBRoeZXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @TXNativePatriot We tolerate Juan to get our @greggutfeld fix 😉  🎶 Animals Are Great 🎤🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before it started to rain, I got a glimpse of a beautiful rainbow. @ Sam's Club https://t.co/4VV3QRxNHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjhollis93 @tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @NGDAverk… https://t.co/LjDgK6pjrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Do Beyonce’ live in South Africa because that’s silly to spend 60,000 to go see someone that lives i… https://t.co/3ISQ7xfQTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[To know that you can possibly have great warriors and Queens and kings, in your family lineage is amazing to me. I… https://t.co/XH7aoCWgEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyMua733 just wanted to say I love you and I’m so proud of how far you have come. Can you pls come to San Diego soon so I can hug you 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[roses are red, violets are blue, i work on valentine’s day, money is my boo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically... Chilly this morning! Grab a coat, today. https://t.co/yQva8UzHE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX5Sports @keselowski @amsupdates @KCOURSEY6 Wow. That was so heartfelt. Great story]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Essential Oil Day! 2PM in the haus is our intro to essential oil workshop!  The sun is FINALLY shining in And… https://t.co/CODsGlJQN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theresa Turetzky Charged With DUI, More https://t.co/UQlO6YvVwj via @BocaNews1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @BachelorABC Monday 2 night live finale 🌹 @colton yessssss #TheBachelorFinale #BachelorNation https://t.co/hMg2EA2I5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NADOHE19 Reflects on discrimination as a catalyst to be stronger and act with resolve. https://t.co/IGZFkJRZ08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayeHawke @jstol3 @JacobAWohl Hahahaha! California—once GREAT STATE now giant disease-ridden cesspool...you can ha… https://t.co/2H4Dh67deX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFTutko @JaneenGordon Haha we try! I keep laughing every time I hear Janeen talk about the hay in the road. Where are we again? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efergie13 @demi_burnett Well she needs to find her clarity first... JS 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[bad bitches in the club  #evitaparty #evita #Nightingale_LA #andresrigal #munecamanosa https://t.co/asG95LoFtY https://t.co/b6L6FsFxst]]></document><document><![CDATA[takes drug prices "very seriously" and strives for the right balance between ensuring patient access to important m… https://t.co/YJtqxbgK0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Bryant at West Ouachita #models the #STEAL strategy with her students and #FormativelyAssesses their independe… https://t.co/ysYTlpaq2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@duciswild this Bryce Harper situation is taking too long!!!! C'MON #BryceHarper https://t.co/Ein4Bi2x6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the Monsta X tour being at the same I won’t be able to attend VidCon. I really wanted to go but this tour is… https://t.co/nlWxSsWqnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaturalEmblem @yvrshoots @lordvonpunx @Variety Or worse, he was in coma and wanting to wait so he could pass. My heart hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay today I will be fully productive at work &amp; not leave my purse at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was nominated by @Mr_Psyken to post a cover of a book that i love. major shoutout to my 4th grade teacher Mrs. G… https://t.co/jcEC2T1SEr]]></document></documents></author>