<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Got burned twice by @amazon in two days. One day they’ll get it right…. hopefully]]></document><document><![CDATA[would rather have found myself in unrequited lust than to fall in love. because then the good would never happen an… https://t.co/W47cXA1oAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new term for a massive quantity of falsehood is a "Smollett" as in "don't try to snow me with an obvious smolle… https://t.co/GL9wSicf7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleck1022 did you not see the Fountain of Youth was renamed  ?   follow @ThruTheBridle for all the exclusives  #TheKentucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexanderWCole I'd rather get paired with a pre-cum child like that guy from FE or like that tool Loic for a unive… https://t.co/vl0R8sv8Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: why do you feel the need to show off your ass and titties to these random dudes on social media.… https://t.co/XfepQtfhQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildshutterbabe @mnwild Not sure, I'm just glad that when the snow banks melt there won't be a substantial penalty for early withdrawal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side Cabinet with faux  drawers  on 1 door. Restyled  and  a great cabinet  to use  for storage,  open area behind… https://t.co/GaYdccFAf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot Property Newsletter: That’s not a mirage: In honor of the Midcentury architecture celebration known as Modernis… https://t.co/SFwyEjSTns]]></document><document><![CDATA[In for relief Jimmy Christian and making his season debut #17 Brandon Hickey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightsPress I enjoyed it. I am done. I have emailed you. Holy crap. Five seasons building a mythology. Two seasons… https://t.co/FjhuzLxo4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCFPresident @rolandsmartin Ya, you can watch today and notice the select type of black people that will be there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday March 11 - Balance of Power:     Donald Trump isn’t giving up pushing Congress to fund his wall     Via… https://t.co/aMHA87gQja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadLionGold 🤦🏻‍♂️ok. I’m jumping in, I can’t resist. https://t.co/n4e0llZsJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loudmouthjulia older videos are probably gaining views too as he gains steam...would be funny to see if his older,… https://t.co/w5HxVLizg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am just hearing about this and now am terrified about what my kids are seeing ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarcadosParaConquistar #YoFuiMarcadoPorSuSangre  ©️Ministerio Marcados para Conquistar Inc. https://t.co/IhZ02eqmIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrelldeer @drjamesmerritt @AdrianRogers NO😇😇😇😇he had that Funny little laugh after some of his quotes!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCannon Hey @NickCannon you should add my lil sis @karissanevaeh11 to this project she's an amazing dancer / ac… https://t.co/orzLKGWvfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mealprep roast turkey breast, sweet potatoes, and balsamic vinaigrette brussel sprouts. @ Cascade Heights, Georgia https://t.co/8EiiTUsJ9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xdanikrickl It’s certainly always this eclectic and each days lineup is always super diverse. Its kind of their ca… https://t.co/rGIBUMzbji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TomCross_ Nice photo! Its really toasty from this side. I wonder if they will use it just like that (the painting… https://t.co/v7Flqrz2Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benschrank @drozzie99 @chris___miller Dang it, Ben - you beat me to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tasters after the stonebrewingrva brewery tour! #rva @ Stone Brewing Richmond https://t.co/RID0tkgtJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revbethanncook I just sent you a link to my favorite artists on facebook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is every movie from the 70s all the way up to the mid 90s... it’s called statutory rape... commonly known as a… https://t.co/L23wk5wNhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish Tom Brokaw was back at NBC, it’s a shame it has turned to such tabloid news, hell even the National Enquirer g… https://t.co/NeqlGweXqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travel_danielle @KDBarbosa @Djxyz0 What happened here I don't remember this in stream lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bird by the bay in #SanFrancisco @ The Embarcadero/Harrison St, SF https://t.co/c6j5w4cUIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @UTHornsRawk She's just another anti-gun Kook... Ban all anti-gun politicians... No rifle bans...… https://t.co/1Fo1K2ubr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to porcelain fillings, because most of the foods I eat now make an unbearable squeaking sensation as if I was chewing on styrofoam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Wade should just pay for a non athlete to go to LSU and its all good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farmerbobnwmo Happy for ya man. Also... that hat isn’t jiving with the rest of the get up. #GoCubsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting hoops with my kid once he shows an interest in Basketball&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[#venezuelsaidlive #venezuela #vamosbien #ayudahumanitaria Thank you @richardbranson ...... Gracias @ Boca Raton, Fl… https://t.co/0RmoilpQiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRCA center of New York helps reduce her risk of breast cancer | Northwell Health @lenoxhill https://t.co/CWx7Q7EjsT https://t.co/iKZUE4vA1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra @Desde_Izquierda Contrapeso !!! Por el amor a la patria andan como cucarachas en quemazón el puebl… https://t.co/lhL82KvH1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hard truth is that all EV are overpriced and see 75% depreciation in 3 years. Tesla makes smartcars that buck t… https://t.co/nN1xiMNH4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Transgender is made up Crap from the left. If your born with a vagina, Your A Woman! If your born w… https://t.co/JBkY8Psqci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope all my friends are having a good time watching a band I love play one of my favorite albums of all time while I get sleep for work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAN’T TAKE US ANYWHERE🤣 Just another regular night at the club🤷🏻‍♀️ Who took this vid??? #ThrowbackThursday @ Rosie… https://t.co/oB4HUFuLlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amusing that people are upset that the tech on Discovery looks more advanced than TOS Enterprise. I watched Th… https://t.co/xMKqcLe1ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Oil of Gladness (2017) by @DarkHorseBrewCo/@3floyds at @jgreebs — https://t.co/dxI2xOobd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StraightOuttaCompton  #InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/L6NMPExHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConcentricSky Very excited about this ... we also need to help employers articulate their culture, work environmen… https://t.co/BrhF8FYczF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BebeNeuwirth And look, Bebe, he has matching shoes! You better have made that purchase.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt - Hiking the Syncline Loop in Canyonlands National Park, UT w/ fly_fishing_realtor.  This was a hell of an exp… https://t.co/3mDfLsKt74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mugtang @johncoonsports Insanely unacceptable if that happened. Haven’t seen video of it yet but I’m guessing it exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Kids, the sky is blue and snow is white, except during winter alpenglow it all turns purple and orange.” @ Rocky M… https://t.co/NdbxgWXGyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBeauregard12 @katepurchase @gmbutts You have to be kidding. The country has never been so divided and the list of… https://t.co/47oxkGecIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pastacreamcheez If you are trying to say that abuse of power or government overreach can only be attributed to Dem… https://t.co/qnxkNoN6Ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdyword @WSJ There are so many white families where one kid looks nothing like the other. To be honest. Like a b… https://t.co/0XzmDNhHCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@contralinea “Va a estar operado por la Sedena; va a dar servicio a empresas aéreas civiles. Será un aeropuerto civ… https://t.co/GPYP3oq8pE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect way to top off a morning run! Love my cinnamon toast and @HoneyStinger peanut butta bar. #hshive https://t.co/VzfUmx0i53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHODesusAndMero @AOC @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib That side eye AOC gives when asked if there are a lot of double standards around here. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Not related to Russia because there is no collusion! You obnoxious 😂 liberals see wh… https://t.co/LhXdHjK7Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[working on this lab report and my math says there’s 1.5 pounds of protein per serving of 2% milk. that gives me an… https://t.co/PSc9uoj5tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its starting to hit me that I’m gonna be away from her for a whole week ): ): probably gonna ugly cry at the airpor… https://t.co/NFtUIFiJtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for St. Patrick’s Day? Time to upgrade to a high quality organic mattress from Treasure Barn Organic Mattress… https://t.co/NM5XVaaCqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_El_Choco it is. he knew what he was doing was wrong, and he knew what was coming which makes him what he was doin… https://t.co/4MqwSAyW7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simply_gary @schuelkecorn @BirnamPork @thisfarmwife And of coarse horseradish]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big run by Blue Ridge gives the Jackets a 23-20 lead on Pusch Ridge, forcing Erik Michaud to call a timeout. Nothin… https://t.co/wHFL1SYFYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Lou Dobbs is a freaking moron. He is clearly out of touch with mainstream America. He supports traitors and liars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@featkingjisoo She's beautiful girl when she is smile I love her ❤️ like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a game! @MCKLADYSCOTS 18, @McNaryGirlHoops 23 ... McKay is hanging there - halftime. @scotsmandaily… https://t.co/xwfMKdqUQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help but like guys who wear jewelry and have tattoos THEY ARE TOO POWERFUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Chorus 2x) so long, bitch you did me so wrong I don't wanna go on living in this world without you You really fuck… https://t.co/XSJVU2OPDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The HARD produces perseverance! Not the easy. 😎 https://t.co/SZi2NPTiXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSGNetworks @alanhahn They aren't on the same level.  Fox is soooo much better it's laughable]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best kind of Uber driver ...is The one Who stfu and doesn’t bother you with idiotic questions and stories of their life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawryluk_Hive @ToxicNobody_ @itsvivsxoxo @mellii_xo https://t.co/0qSZLTcwyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost unity_sign_zodiaccouples with get_repost ・・・ Hey  You have to pick one! Which one will it be?! 🔅Dm to 12 fr… https://t.co/sxFZKGtJvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't the first time she's shown her feelings and then gave a slight apology]]></document><document><![CDATA[Markieff Morris makes his first start with the Thunder in just his fourth game with the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book #15, Within The Woods by Tony Urban. Oof...Stranger Things meets It, but without the quality evil or plot deve… https://t.co/HBDRWXMnKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Ones Bitch  . . Model @roxell_photos  . . Tee @REBELSOULCO  . . Photographer @MikeValen  . . mikevalenzangels… https://t.co/m49nSg1XD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @WLOS_13 for shining the spotlight on some of our great students! #Proud2BAMountaineer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberen a Jormanth Linares Desde la casa balanca #whitehouse  Alzó la voz por mi hermano Venezolano quien hoy se… https://t.co/cBM0sM2jdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jajuvera @dalcz Vende puras plantas tornasol, pasan de verdes a amarillas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysbob33 @ndrew_lawrence @daveweigel Mainstream cable news has devolved into an entertainment product. If anyon… https://t.co/sMaKyOBNkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Big night at the Ridler Ball. Cool new experience.  @TeamNutz maxmotivepgh #teamnutz #teamnutzpgh #maxmotive… https://t.co/uPODu9jpKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Through the nighhhht when it be stormin, hoping everything clear up by the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeverlyBlueWave @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @VDHanson A philosopher telling a dentist how to look smarter!  😆😆😆😆 https://t.co/Q9XZU12eb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachsaunders @JRHEAD1 What do you know, the Doublemint Twins hating again]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡 OPEN HOUSE🏠       Feb 24   1:00-4:00 PM 24074 SW 113th Path Call/Text 786-554-0161 #Miami #miamifl #miamifla… https://t.co/N72Jkf590K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caanmichelena @Lenin @jguaido Par d enfermos me cago en sus trompas hjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beloit College Baseball comeback falls short in 9-7 Game #4 loss vs Greenville University (IL) at the RussMatt Cent… https://t.co/BpMn8shpxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestleMania @WWE @WWEUniverse Can you SMELLLLLLLLLLLLLLLL it? https://t.co/U7ZEDsstHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes them think I can stand for more then one hour when I get twice a week lidocaine injections and spinal ad… https://t.co/Kux9bHKm10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfox9611 @BinningtonsNose @leahck55 Fuck no....im saying he should be playing today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thr Trump show has jumped the shark. Now for the recap show. "Trump - after the resignation "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primera tienda visitada: intenté resistirme, pero el consumismo me venció (todo por 7 dólares) https://t.co/QRnJxJjuQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToonamiNews @MattShipmanVO  I got to hear @MattShipmanVO voicing Floch on #AttackOnTitan early this morning on #Toonami! ^_^]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why but I would love to see the @Padres succeed for the city of #SanDiego]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks elonrmuskk!  154 was so last month 😁  teslamotors  #rickybobby #merica🇺🇸 @ Monroe, Louisiana https://t.co/kRNZnRpFeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY IF DICTATOR TRUMP BUILDS WALL WE CAN CUT THE WALL UP AND MAKE CRAFTS. YEAH. THATS IT WIND CHIMES.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are so pretty 😍❤🌹 #valentines2019 @ Melrose Park, Illinois https://t.co/mNaRPCIxl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally, we have a President  protecting both life and our tax dollars . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've gotten everyone hooked on GoT but my dad so far and he is not tryna budge 🤔 even my Grammy with the shits 🤣🤣🤣🤣… https://t.co/OTqVS2Qjag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump hasn’t said a word about the white extremists terrorist who was planning to attact our nations lea… https://t.co/iojNWSIGcK]]></document></documents></author>