<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EmilyRafi2020 @LeftwardSwing Needed: many more Dem primary challenges from the left like @AOC did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was looking through some old scrap books and found a few articles of when I played baseball at Burroughs and late… https://t.co/UUj0IVAI9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Drew After Dark Episode 2 you guys should check it out @tomsegura @ChristinaP and #drdrew are amazing....… https://t.co/7rSqyWJqMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vegan_Earper_ @earperfreak Lol. Actually, neither... two dudes, one girl... and the most epic soundtrack ever...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phenomenal production, beautiful songs and a brilliant cast. @DearEvanHansen was perfection in Toronto👌🏻 https://t.co/OflzEyiXW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Divine Act Three @ The Greyhound Bar &amp; Grill https://t.co/FGwqGwVX2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nsrm19 @zoll_p @OfficialSPGB @DavidAFrench @AOC You keep telling yourself that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People... what did you THINK was underneath @CodyJinksMusic  beard? Calm yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is like a total mix of a sea of candy kissesinside the giant candy kiss.. i must open one little candy kiss /..............ill be back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilkowMajority @justlikethat67 @AOC @AOC says landlords because she doesn’t know what Kuloks are, yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hindsight is the 20/20 year!  When you’re successful they’ll try to garner credit in someway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the beautiful and talented @gates_mcfadden thanks for all the joy you've brought me! Love Dr. Cru… https://t.co/8ivhyVNGAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[GoT been gone so long people have forgotten that there is a ZERO percent chance this ends happy 😂 #GameOfThrones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to decide if I need cold medicine or headache meds https://t.co/UrJ4QPO3v7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 She reforms real fast, now women learn something from this, if husband says he is reformed you got to believe him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky29893 @ladega1957 @2booty2muscle @SoloPHombres @book_of_life2 @unttalhanckoc @002_smith @spiritpowerone… https://t.co/eWDTqD38Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cIEefbhd5Q #etsy #dichroic #fusedglassjewelry #landscape #colorful #pendant @ Garfield, New Jersey https://t.co/GymUIn8PLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[La clasica en eventos donde hay Gobernadores PRI  y luego el sale como conciliador !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother hasn’t been to school for like 12 fekkin years.  And no, he is not a high school dropout. Just very very… https://t.co/RlxXnavBPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#healthy #personaltrainer #gymlife #healthylifestyle #enjoyinglife #gettinghealthyandfit #gettingstronger… https://t.co/DVfvhoKSO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Safe to say it was an incredible couple days down here in Vero Beach at dodger town. Went 6-0, scored a ton of runs… https://t.co/0prmrMAqq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta say, ATP, I can’t think of a worse use of resources than cracking down on fans/journalists who post clips/G… https://t.co/2m68Kz9OzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose Britain has serious problems caused by the radical left. in the same way the Americans do. In Brit… https://t.co/r8YhtYEQi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alelouress @LucasCollar Não é o único amigo...a vida não tá fácil pra nós...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marissaKlane @PavlikScotty As you should be Marissa, we look forward to making you proud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know who Gio is. Heyward is not Bryce Harper. A-Rod does not prove the point you think it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only if Repub lawmakers cant articulate the good this indicates and thwart your leftwing propaganda. Cant be deer i… https://t.co/LwmPK32i8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vermontgmg He’s still a bad guy no matter what. He’s only being humble because he has no choice left. Don’t feel b… https://t.co/dDnStsV6qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellycanes @CutlerRidgeLAZ @homerun0620 @lockhart_jesse @HeavySmoke239 @SportyMama @kelly_deezcanes @RobertPerera5… https://t.co/LbXqgnSzbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that pain and disappointment are never excuses to settle. Pray more. Trust more. Love more. Believe more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VooPoo Drag Mini Kit Prussian Blue 117 watt Uforce T2 tank @ Barnyard Vapes https://t.co/9pitBGplow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyanneHawkins @sengineland Smh. They continue to force a pay to play model.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all in for an inclusive church but if DJT wants in to sign Bibles, I’m barring the door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leannrimes I will tell you every story that there is.. but it has to be in the form of a parable.. OK?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fans of @NYIslanders : Toronto would like to thank you for @91Tavares. Enjoy watching our all-star skate on your ice tonight! #goleafsgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSeacrest  Ryan and team! Why don’t you have a small switchback ramp instead of those stairs for the stars to w… https://t.co/oedWPKNUFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are inpatient hospital treatment protocals and patient centered care in opposition? Feeling that in the hospital I… https://t.co/PYE9sVHkqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StMillerFan @ProfKFH Like we have photographic evidence of the swastika, it’s not a huge leap from that to anti Semitic bullying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplySylvan @bexchangewords The only thing that makes me frustrated is that damn weapon system. Everything else i… https://t.co/IxXTWTa2kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might have to come out of retirement and race arizona open this year!!🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to other half of the 2010 St Mary water balloon toss champions😤 hope it’s a good one bub:) https://t.co/ZJ1OzKqW3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllEliteTiffany @CodyRhodes @theAdamPage @AndyNemmity @Phoenixnjpw @couple_cosplay @TheBrandiRhodes @ATElitePod https://t.co/RcTnEq98Ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we defending a horrible dictator? What could possibly be gained?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teresalorraine_ That’s my only shot at redemption so I’m gonna starting training]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is certainly something that needs to be resolved quickly. Let’s hope that the reason for the delay in respondi… https://t.co/Xt9XB23gQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolaMurder Should be a poster child for everything Monday!!! Good morning Lola]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyWGR Why would Buffalo not want to get these two guys? if you want to win in any League don't you want the be… https://t.co/fdf37WzcPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sully1921 @BBsBigHouse1 @rivalsmike @Brodell_Haggins I don’t write the mock drafts clown. Get your shit together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third-graders spend 56 percent of their time on literacy activities but 6 percent each on science and social studie… https://t.co/n7i7Yrolae]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if I needed to be any gayer, I just watched Troy Tulowitzki hit a home run in spring training and yelled out “Ya… https://t.co/yWD5gQM5tA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Can I get fries with that?” #NationalEmergency https://t.co/5kuTvSFlnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[STILL REMEMBER WHEN I GOT HIT LAST WEEK AND WAS IN THE MIDDLE OF CALLING MY INSURANCE AND HOMIE TELLS ME “ima go ge… https://t.co/ohMJGMTbut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidneyHunsecker @marklevinshow @PoliticalShort Brainwashed Obama hypocrite.   He did way more by edict than any recent President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GurlPower72 I should try that but eardrums are shot from too many 10's on the volume on the Amps]]></document><document><![CDATA[WRESTLING: River Shettler with the pin, giving Brighton an insurmountable 37-15 lead over Holt with 3 matches left… https://t.co/AtEYKcJRIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article! Stresses the importance of proper and thorough documentation! @FFBehavior]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyeMartinNBC @nbcchicago 34 minutes to MDW from Frankfort so happy to miss all the traffic but that’s the case whe… https://t.co/nVnXMZ8n5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I only fuck with Alonso and like two other people everyone else gets them fake smiles and hi s because som… https://t.co/yRR6G8lmdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm searching for some answers I'll probably never find. I'm barking up a tree that I'll probably never climb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Reunion Kitchen + Drink - @reunionanaheim in Anaheim Hills, CA https://t.co/Jtx1QAI2R9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoMitchJones @SportsCenter Only fucking with ya bud haha. You’re not wrong he wanted to be the man tho so this is what happens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ali @LLinWood @culttture Go get these lowlifes, Lin. Get ALL of them!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren dodging this issue makes her a de facto apologist for colonialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest In Peace #DonNewcombe.  You and Jackie Robinson belong to the ages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literal conversation between Kelly and I today lol https://t.co/VfvkUcE88W]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a disingenuous piece of shit. And who the hell names their baby Zerlina?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla The “Manual seat, cloth seats and basic audio... ” though https://t.co/fhPcrxlx12]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nasa's newest Mars lander has started digging into red planet - New Zealand Herald https://t.co/kdXgqAJZmT https://t.co/MD8cJ9jtF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonrakerkih @andrewjskatz @mikedav57 @janfromdevon @margarethodge @JoRichardsKent @thetimes Ok, so what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not sure if I know how to say this the right way.. but I will try.. There has NEVER been a better American tha… https://t.co/xe6R597Bqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kimt50 #happybirthday #kimthiboldeaux #presidentsweekend #philadelphia #cityofbrotherlylove #benfranklin #kim canc… https://t.co/s8Uk84LY5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lamb-harissa meatballs from the #COOK90 book, with salted yogurt but without the tomato sauce. (I marinated a s… https://t.co/BSbo44CgPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[While EU Rejects US Intervention In Venezuela, Rubio Tweets Threat To Ma... https://t.co/Ttvj53nqS5 via @YouTube We… https://t.co/E9hzgFRs7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonsherred @2019fortheERA @JoyceCarolOates @democracynow Just because your wool is unusual don’t assume you won’t be shorn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LannyDavis @MichaelCohen212 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS I’m going to mark this on my calendar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnonByz @Goodtweet_man The point that animal agriculture has a huge environmental impact relative to its caloric v… https://t.co/5BwbFSvL5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another peek at a #modernfarmhouse #brightwhitekitchen we designed and built for a busy family that loves to cook t… https://t.co/aHt6Kys6fA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zakarpatczg Please provide protection to International Women’s Day marchers in Uzhgorod.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tryingtimes3 @DerekCressman So far it's reported 16000 farmers in Texas have applied for bailout money I didn't kn… https://t.co/t0fx03zyu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SOLD! 💫 66 Walby Drive, Oakville Congratulations to our clients!! 😊👏🏻 #alexirish #oakvillerealestate https://t.co/7Q0aFshSwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see us in a house next year You'll be making your mind up You can figure out what goes where You'll be keepin… https://t.co/AcZQNC3Ofx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@68shaubooker @GWF_1987 @PauQuilez @THR Uh, it’s not a secret that this movie has the trolls multiplying like cockr… https://t.co/SQIYh1CXNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focus on the execution, not the outcome. Let everything else fall away- @AndyStumpf77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdillonkidd Do you have to go to Russia to do that or...? #Putinhasthepisstape]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately I’ve been in such a rut mentally, but I’m on the come up. Watch for all the big things you’ll see from me. Guarantee it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[24.4 ppg and 13.2 rpg over the past 10 games. 🤫🤫🤫 https://t.co/Beqp89GYho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving 5 hours to eat donuts with my boy tomorrow...oh yeah and it’s a camp weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan The #Mexican Army could put a stop to this nonsense in a heartbeat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How these jackasses want people to invest in a wall when they dusty asses can’t invest in a proper sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, they do! Thank you Chef for your high level of expectation. We want nothing but the best for our Seguin ISD ki… https://t.co/Tt1KAaabN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenToomey This is far from true Pat, many middle class Americans are hurting deeply from your tax scam. It's time… https://t.co/kOjHwS01IF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaden Dillon |  0-0 at the end of the first period. @EldonWrestling @EldonMustang @LakeSunSports @LakeNewsOnline https://t.co/HxXrBxUWEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no!! Fuck Price is right! I couldn’t wait to get home to watch jeopardy 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pistol more percise than Lazer guided missiles  https://t.co/3EFbDe1I0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazC318 U really believe he staged it bro... my wife still believe him 🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rampa19 @Angels How is it a bad take? I’m speculating. Everything in my tweet could be true ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Age has smoothed it out but still good - Drinking a Bishop’s Barrel No. 6 by @saintarnold at @barmvsc  — https://t.co/iQmiNzvgxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fun Marvel film. Really enjoyed Captain Marvel! Looking forward to Avengers: Endgame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you missed it yesterday, take a moment to watch our wonderfully-produced #BlckHistoryMonth special; Hidden… https://t.co/HPaMFb2ruS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton Collusion 101. It happens right before our eyes, plain as day to recognize...and yet not a smidgen of co… https://t.co/TGTE5pR1Dc]]></document></documents></author>