<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm just wondering why all the coverups Obama???? @JudicialWatch @TheJusticeDept ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD @FLOTUS They are not partisan issues, but her husband is the biggest bully out there. Don’t you think it’s hypocritical?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ricee66512966 @lmdreamfree @MavenRn @amber_athey Their lives. Was it easy no. My husband and I at one point was wo… https://t.co/4mJ0bJdayn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight Mother and Sons Date Night with __jmarsh__ and j_g.o.a.t_ #qualitytime #lovemyboys Thanks to the Hu… https://t.co/8KMtkLjFb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TokisMom73 @realDonaldTrump GO AWAY. YOUR NOT WANTED ON PRESIDENT TRUMPS SITE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying In Perpetuity on the beach in SC. Thanks @TreeHouseBrewCo https://t.co/N5ahnXKBHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA i think @GStephanopoulos misspoke and said .."this hasn't happened since ...with President Trump in 1973." #what did you mean to say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarahstaytrue I need to find one ASAP for Eric, I hope I come across a Good Samaritan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who is they? You live in an alternate universe, 45. Seems like you're the one who needs to do some ”splaining”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosedixontx @steverino1997 IRS will tell them to  ... No. .. it's against the law .!!  IRS if they do.that  they w… https://t.co/e3ePJ8o9c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandyincanada @valerie_305 I checked on her Friday. I didn't realize she was getting close! I tried the Taj cam bu… https://t.co/Sk7At74GAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@takiyahwill01 You mentioned 2 projects but I only saw 1. Is there another? Post that link too😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone have $770 they can loan me real quick so I can pay for my last class I need to graduate lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Butterfield Park District in Lombard, IL https://t.co/cKvguvkbPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Technori @johnpletz @BookCameo I think Cameo’s going to win - as a Chicago company - bc they realized selfies are… https://t.co/pbxrhQPg2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[ETIQUETEN SINO  TIENEN UNA  AMIGA ASÍ POR FAVOR !!!! en Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/6SKJjKEH8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delerium65 @LaughRaindrops @GreyCaitlin @BarbLovesmusic @jamesbaconx @ghostlybeard @Dandelion_Charm @DuffyandBird… https://t.co/6RKgy0lpkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAGA IS QUEEN !!! She can win my heart so quick over a Oscar 🤧 @ladygaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macjamesward honestly nothing tops crying at mainstage and having your rave dreams come true :,) #plur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weddlesbeard Thank you for always stopping to chat with your fans! You are a class act on and off the field and yo… https://t.co/yBFLuJ2Uvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sappermartin @briantopping66 @IceMule__Nation @LisaTomaino @RebelAngelMike @lac919 @john_double_u @Raging_Todd… https://t.co/2xzc4gAPvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Sorry there is a real crisis at our borders! Wish you wanted to protect Americans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Jakob Poeltl standing right beside Demar for his big recognition vid, living in all the glory, just patting Demar on the back 👌🏽😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free event 2/27, featuring @EFillerCorn @C_Herring @KenPlum1  @RepWexton Sign up @eventbrite. @VAratifyERA https://t.co/YnzupaZyG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pixar made a short about my rescue babies 😭#kitbull Watch here: https://t.co/KEysjGjvZw https://t.co/dgsG6UYzIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is certainly lying when saying this morning that she would still be Justice Minister if Scott Brison hadn’t resi… https://t.co/tWRHcP6qby]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Monday to be precise. @ACLU @acluohio @AloraThomas @tleeeeee @emilyrongzhang are off to trial next week to bri… https://t.co/UuKQTfhv6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now my options are to hang out in the airport on standby ALL DAY to see if I can’t get on a flight only to be on st… https://t.co/hJoRwvz5bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMEN‼️ @realDonaldTrump is MY PRESIDENT and I am THANKFUL‼️#maga #WinningintheWH #ThankGodforDJT @POTUS ❤️🇺🇸❤️🇺🇸❤️… https://t.co/avCvrwQq40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMeece92 There are females out there that don’t care to entertain more than one guy. It’s rare but they are out there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Because you have yet to follow through THIS American Genocide is NOT gonna end well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voting has officially opened on BisonWeb! Cast your ballots for Abigail Hall! Let’s #ReviveHUSASenate! https://t.co/D6S8BZUzuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Ripley High School Winter Guard - 1st Place at the Connor High TriState Marching Arts Compet… https://t.co/l80Kj8dyNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many, including myself question this daily? Like, how in the hell did this happen? Is this a damn nightmare? Surely… https://t.co/jcK2Wg1NUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBKinTN @staccceee1 @sewaitman They are  noticing that you clearly haven’t packed enough tuna.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first few pages and description of the devotional I wrote are on https://t.co/o9FKG7TQwo.  Here is the link . .… https://t.co/ELG3500VhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 What the heck happened to Dershowitz? He’s drank from Lindsey Graham’s brew!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Oh, look. An old man pining for the old days when he sexually assaulted women without getting caught a… https://t.co/0EeKWCcSOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetupmeetups @KristalSchnei10 @mrsakopp @ash_vallecilla We had a blast! Thank y’all for organizing this event. W… https://t.co/5iIZ1ngoyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to try our 21 day program!!! You can get a free gift + free shipping and a discount % also one on one coaching… https://t.co/FisJUt5HF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @angeIictears @jordynwoods damn kris jenner really sold her kids souls to the devil when she got OJ loose huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Cert/Reg Medical Assistant… https://t.co/gMi3YJj31b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamster1212 @realDonaldTrump Or bring up another mass shooting. Definitely goes against those so called Christian… https://t.co/5uw3Rym2He]]></document><document><![CDATA[What changed is that finally we have a President that fights for us, fights against corruption, fights for our free… https://t.co/xBxfpGbAXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLESS IT I am so sick of studying... + I have 10 exams in the next 2 weeks 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the greatest honors for me is to be the person students trust with their future by asking me to recommend th… https://t.co/88iDl1Pvc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never let lack of education hold you back or compare your educational training with others. #education #lifeschool… https://t.co/3WFtC0fAWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gilead said its pricing is based on countries' economic and health backgrounds, and negotiations with most governme… https://t.co/VwopUW60qF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Go963MN @tornadojally Yooooooo this is so very @MagiciansSYFY of you... and I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tweeted this from the dunkin drive through so at least I’m alive enough to tell the story 🌩☕️ #goodmorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta cadena estuvo circulando en las últimas horas e intranquilizó mucho a la ciudadanía... como dije antes, el alz… https://t.co/U1A7P2v5e7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RepMarkMeadows  4 taking high road while representing NC. We are proud of you every day 4 protecting USA https://t.co/Ifw9Pkp8S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traependergrast Last week I went to a really bad yoga class, and I left feeling worse than when I went in 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏾‍♀️🤦🏾‍♀️why are y’all like this? that whole attitude gotta go. Swear I hate confronting a man about something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @DNC WHY IS BERNIE BEING ALLOWED TO RUN AS A DEM?  Bernie should not be allowed in the debate stage. He… https://t.co/IvC1P2hYUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mon_Commentaire Moi aussi c'est ce que j'me disais....pi??? https://t.co/f7wxOTRWah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GBemboom and I Finally making it out of the Minnesota snowmagedden to Florida for Spring Training. Can’t wait to s… https://t.co/zNjpokW4sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Bitter and hateful. Heavy burden to tote! God bless you! 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do kids these days realize that the Champion brand used to be at Kmart and Payless shoe stores? Lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally made it home to Ohio. Can’t wait to pack up my car again to head out to another race. 45 days till I head out to Bristol. @NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[sry again I’m delirious and half asleep ok bye let’s vote regardless #BestSoloBreakout #TiffanyYoung #iHeartAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/XxhfmvWu4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect!   Good beer and pizza.  Just raised the Walk Score of my apartment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump I do not understand this compulsion by Dem politicians to keep retweeting his tweets.   B… https://t.co/WvAlyH684L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t ruin my eyelashes but I want to cry. 😭 RIP Luke Perry. Such a heartthrob even as he aged into an attractive… https://t.co/4l8OWeCOYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such cute Easter things have starting arriving in stores - spring is almost here!  🐰🐥🌷 #springisalmosthere… https://t.co/y6F7K8veaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to watch #AStarIsBorn awesome movie! @ladygaga amazing as always! @iBradlycooper wow! Bravo!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daryl why in the bloody hell are you gonna look for Henry? I were you I would of left that kid. He doesn't listen for sh*t. #TWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @RashidaTlaib on @WWJ950 just now gives me hope for all of US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guildhall is the cats meow ;-) @selinaruthe @TheGuildhallBar https://t.co/XwWRtr4DwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Final - Lilly Goodman https://t.co/B8j1kOt3nn vía @YouTube. Amo esta canción con todo mi corazón ❣  Desde el pri… https://t.co/DlXyHUuJPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[when tx winters are starting to feel a lot like nash winters and I came home wearing a T-shirt     alt caption: doe… https://t.co/68VU2HsZuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Jordyn Woods Story”, anyone? I’m not tearing down another Black Woman, nope, not today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patyache @DiegoMalo25 Me caen súper bien, aunque solo los conocí de pasada 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WAS AMAZING!! I am so excited for and proud of this team! Down by double digits and NEVER gave up!! Keep grind… https://t.co/7KQctN1lrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JChambersOnline @7JustinChambers @GreysABC Chief Karev https://t.co/VAedj037W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 🖐🏻 time seeing @state_champs live. Easily the best live band I’ve ever seen. Their songs and how they perform t… https://t.co/NM0pMVUatB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stclairashley @ShinGokaiRed Yeah, I had the same after I said men weren't negawomen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside this morning but still getting work done! https://t.co/6SVzEANsi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spotted at the @LeadersBiz Women in Sport event in honor of #InternationalWomensDay2019 #leadersmeet… https://t.co/2shR8vvGvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy Friday!! #adventuresofmaxoliandwes #littlepiggydowninfront @ Bright Horizons at Legacy https://t.co/46O6O4zXCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Follett Corporation team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/aJy5NNq8AW #CustomerService #Escanaba, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look at all of our clocks go from 2 am to 2:01 am and sigh and realize I have to change every one manually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got in some extra snuggles, conversation, and (of course) ice cream with this cutie before heading off on vacation!… https://t.co/XieNTOvJZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Supervisor Logistics - https://t.co/PTEtXersi6 #logistics #Gainesville, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoboSlim24 @NASA @SpaceX @Space_Station @UCF That's all I can say at the moment too,  WOW!!!  Look what we have ac… https://t.co/cBNte1j2J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[trumps position on shutdown was placated,by a billion and change,it's all falling apart, despite Putin's heavy hand… https://t.co/4FZhnB2YDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so, so disgusted with the Liberals today - they never deserved her #JodyWilsonRaybould]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introduction to STEM students enjoyed creating an edible FFA emblem!  #McConnellsburgHighSchool… https://t.co/Hbj13y42jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHAHHA you’ll be in there for a hot minute too cuz you couldn’t even come up with your bail money 💀💀 @rkelly  stup… https://t.co/RC52eNvpUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how Bill Daley's platform is basically just 'This is Chicago and it's my turn.']]></document><document><![CDATA[@StamAdvocate What a nightmare for CT! Talk about traffic and increased stress for people. Way more negatives to this plan!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[region and were later declared "missing" by the government.  Kidnappings have become rampant in the two troubled An… https://t.co/QEzDojz3bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anything this season has clarified for me that LVP is everything and all the other ladies (with the exception of… https://t.co/mqiBJkmjnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay to @SpaceX’s COO, #GwynneShotwell!    ✨👩‍🏫💪🔥🚀🇺🇸✨  SpaceX's plan to fly you across the… https://t.co/EVhMMTY8Za]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Dianna Gobbi and Mr.    Jefferson for being our guest readers today! #ReadAcrossAmerica #huskychat https://t.co/uBNGiyMjUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComSciCon I have flashbacks of the bomb timer for the pep talks from last summer 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[enjoy this picture of me seeing him in concert for the first time 7 yrs ago.. Happy 25th birthday @justinbieber💜 https://t.co/PoQe1oOYPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahBear78 @marcusedelstein I’m in Central OH, I feel ya on this yo-yo weather!! ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC The party's over. Looks like Ken and Barbie won't be living an extravagant life on Tax Payer money.]]></document></documents></author>