<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DaRealGrizzle That's what I'm talking about.Thank God a story where someone isn't getting walked all over!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jasper is excited for the last quail hunt of the season https://t.co/ZeliOQHiO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please step up your Organic game @acmemarkets!  Nearly every time I go to the organic section this is what I find ­ЪўЮ https://t.co/g5Np1rMEvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Every Mexican parent*  Ya me voy a dormir ..... deja me tomo un caf├Е РўЋ№ИЈ ­Ъцд­ЪЈйРђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The life of a New Orleans child!  ­Ъњю­Ъњџ­ЪњЏ #nolakids #mardigras https://t.co/TGj2UU7Sy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RekedFantasy @DBro_FFB @TheFFRealist @FFfaceoff ­ЪЉЄ https://t.co/hI9tyrcQ6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Southern_Direct @kentonh @AtlasMD Like itРђЎs not bad enough that the information presented in its most readable forРђд https://t.co/Ga24XFyOUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANTIFAldo Wonder how heРђЎs feeling, weРђЎre well into day three of the Disney World bender]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizardkingfish @M_J_Fishing @HuntressMonster @mandy_leahey @1MonsterMission @JacksLures @Bucktailes @rgbassinРђд https://t.co/kbViSjXct0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it. This oneРђЎs moving fast since IРђЎm not doing it alone like the Yellowstone jigsaw puzzle. I did borders aРђд https://t.co/5ERbUysavx]]></document><document><![CDATA[NXS final practice coming up at 5:05 p.m. ET. @ISMRaceway. It'll air live on FS1 #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassiecollins37 I love ponds dry face cream or the clean and clear moisturizer !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoshiFCIM @FThooligan @SiavoushF Gives Beppe a change to talk about Jovic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emily_graceffa ­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­Ъца­ЪљД]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cleaned out all the shady non followers. Feel like I just showered after shiting my pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossSeverson @TheLoftGF They Рђўre lucky IРђЎm on the 15 day DL with my arthritis In my pinky]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come it's easy to fall asleep on the couch with the TV on but not when in bed? Or be passing out on the couch bРђд https://t.co/jaMZiDvx5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itswayneee Nah I just saw it so fast brah. Dude you have to be reaching to use that. Every person with a basic senРђд https://t.co/iECaMkkqXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #NetflixTedBundy on @TyltEntРђћ'The Ted Bundy Tapes' is eye-opening and scary https://t.co/qQw7Ie3p9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the better hazy IPAs I have had. - Drinking a Squeeze the Juice by @hopnutsbrewing @ ChiChi's Den Of MajestiРђд https://t.co/Y7SsMxvAX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #RangerJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i having a physical reaction to green book winning? #OSCARS   my skin is literally trying to jump off my body. https://t.co/cWQNXIgDz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drrobertdillon @Andrea_Trudeau @DPS109 Looking forward to having you! #engage109]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSigal @WSJ Nah the fleece vest isnРђЎt as cool here as it is on the west coast. All about the @canadagoose jacРђд https://t.co/DynI2eI6TR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando estornudan a todos les digo Рђюbless youРђЮ, y cuando yo estornudo nadie dice nada ­ЪЦ║]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add some packing peanuts and pink unicorns to YOUR mix!  #songwriterlife #songwriting #producer #newmusic @ Butler,Рђд https://t.co/MJhKPJ5qNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr president why don't you keep your mouth shut some time Rod Rosenstein was not hired by S essionРђд https://t.co/3FsmD7qXBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValeriaLya @enero26del86 @MilagritosMend7 @LillyCruzCR1 @Odioxa27 @SoyMimi9 @Jhziqita @lizmucinotellezРђд https://t.co/u2pemw05ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusMartinMx Es este pejete y sus gentes por los que tristemente ha votado Mexico, ahora a pagar las cosecuenciasРђд https://t.co/HXN9PbfP6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They're gonna be on you for the next 6 years. https://t.co/l62ZNdNG8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcrosss Enjoy your meal, Paul. Hope you like that special glaze. https://t.co/ySGyG7PTVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago. My caption was РђюIРђЎm their professor, and theyРђЎre district champs!РђЮ   Good times! Oh, andРђд https://t.co/DJQymEeE0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @BarbaraHenley3 1 why do Democrats insist on doing stupid videos? Just talking and making dinner­ЪЎё  2Рђд https://t.co/A6cYfuLPqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoxNerd I love ya @SoxNerd but no !!!! for a March win in Arizona against Milwaukee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюРђд positive, collaborative relationships Рђд supportive over the long term.РђЮ  In other words, we expect public money,Рђд https://t.co/XGkBLKsO34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last reporter out of #ArchMadness tonight (actually, this morning) at 12:40 a.m. but pretty sure @Kern0827 was stilРђд https://t.co/ZBxqPtYnY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Citizens pay all year and get rip off in April who is the fool?  owe how much? Americans shocked by impact of new tРђд https://t.co/tUGFyqtnaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanthurmond Time to do some more recruiting if the public schools are still winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bader_diedrich @RealKevinConroy I like both of you guys for different reasons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VikingGuitar also mastered a few @chiptune4autism releases including: https://t.co/FX5U26N6sm and https://t.co/1N2fVYsBor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nagyberryyy I donРђЎt thatРђЎs the safest thing to do... sit yo ass down somewhere. ­ЪЎё]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceJEmswiler Yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Even the Chester Charter cheerleaders put on a show @ East Pennsboro Saturday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did anybody ever figure out why Nicki Minaj was talking bout putting pussy on niggas sideburns?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two new @AHSAAUpdates Wrestling State Champions from Clay- Chalkville crowned today! AJ Talton is your 195 Pound chРђд https://t.co/MwG1NyaMP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day Everyone! Sending love РЮц№ИЈ to all from Brooklyn, NY. Photo credit goes toРђд https://t.co/JIW6ABRTjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikey_Delgado @AlCharlie75 @SenWarren More guns = more deaths.. So there are more guns in those cities, so of courРђд https://t.co/tQJwE0I4Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[I donРђЎt think itРђЎs a coincidence that North Korea started rebuilding a nuclear test site less than 48 hours after TРђд https://t.co/Rc9AWusq9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megamanex @SethMacFarlane @MattMcClurg2 @TheOrville @TomCostantino @Brooki_eh Brandon looks like fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many people talk about the РђюProcess Рђю. Here is some advice from Nick Saban @AlabamaFTBL . DonРђЎt just talk the taРђд https://t.co/n8gpAtzTrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish more people realized what an insane season the @TBLightning are having.  Geeeesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a trap tweet so that LouieРђЎs follow up tweet can be about his philosophy on whatever. Be aware of trap tweeРђд https://t.co/mTBDW3UTj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris It is not presidential to lie.   Refunds are based on tax - withholding.   Tax is different.   ExtraРђд https://t.co/ptrivEGuic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlarcomTom @politvidchannel And this is exactly what is wrong with America. ­Ъцд­ЪЈйРђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidblair If they did not have any evidence he was a drug dealer; the man and his wife were murdered. And everyoneРђд https://t.co/0V76wyz1Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwest *Happy Saturday* Hudson! #ActorBuddy ­Ъўј­ЪЉЇ https://t.co/F6iQbRDJ5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao @BrentMarks with the pink wig and the house curtain dress. Good job, champ. You did good that day.  #LohanBeachClub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN DidnРђЎt CNN falsely claim refunds were down a few weeks ago?  This must be killing you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller please tell me there is a Maller Monologue coming to absolutely destroy the Chiefs for thisРђд https://t.co/x4xXeGBlK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hub for grub ­ЪЦў (@ The Eating Establishment in Park City, UT) https://t.co/rqZyIMqoU1 https://t.co/nEG1lvaek5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport @EdRedstateblues She might be running a scam on the crackers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's another coon up here taking and reposting my tweets of my private thoughts to try and use as ammunition agaiРђд https://t.co/wUF5j1thDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidjrainey @SannaPrintezi FYI: weРђЎll be in Japan mid-May, so a bit closer ­ЪўЅ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a roommate with Dr. RogersРђЎ nephew, and meeting his son @nrcokey11 , this hit home to me. I know what you guyРђд https://t.co/JEAP8gOvR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was basically me this morning trying to run my 400's in  wind chills of minus 15 and gusts upto 90km #mylifeРђд https://t.co/VSYJQ6rLAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olfran1999 @PaulMaxit @Delphine_D Si, absolument. Mais ne comptez pas sur le faux chercheur @PaulMaxit pour lРђЎadmettre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2x champ with the spurs and all time great role player Malik Rose is getting inducted into the San Antonio Sports HРђд https://t.co/mlnChQ5AmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly sunny, 74┬░... ­Ъўј #HighlandPark #Texas #TGIF ­ЪЄе­ЪЄ▒ @ Flippen Park https://t.co/DqdWr0cpek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_richjohnson @FordhamNYC @SEC_News If I was home id take you out to Arthur avenue for good Italian food]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving with like 3 inches of snow on my windshield. I donРђЎt even care anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because everything they do is fr and not a joke *Message* Meanwhile our scenarios are jokes to be turned real]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont blame him he swung it for that weak side 3 enough times to watch them fools miss or over dribble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaganCrowe @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Generally law enforcement start investigations when a crime is known toРђд https://t.co/UCztqxHaUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieingalls thank u for being u­ЪњЋ @ Old Rock House https://t.co/1gqMCbZiQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously this life hack works for most other employees/staff in retail and medical - feel free to try it at your lРђд https://t.co/BVN3HFbEfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#neverbenormal you wonРђЎt be worshipped long if you are projecting a false image of yourself.   #theshitjoesaysРђд https://t.co/rLvRZM01Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski Au contraire... Sarah Sanders: "Contrary to the leftist media narrative, President Trump is very conРђд https://t.co/4IPr6h4pv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drabarnes @MPD_PAL I support you and the PAL program, so don't forget to add me to your notification list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pattern is clear. If they like your politics, you're given a free pass. But if you oppose their favorites: aborРђд https://t.co/DtNrJWW011]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn guess ima drink this tequila and eat this pizza I bought by my myself ­Ъўћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roundhoward Wow, that would have been the best intro since "Tarzan?? I"m TroyZan! "]]></document><document><![CDATA[s /0  .@GroceryOutlet  their support #Veterans and #family  remember the #goldenRule https://t.co/YnfHHiPSQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisxndraxe @lildoinkymane @tylergrosso I donРђЎt see how yРђЎall hate on this @tylergrosso, heРђЎs out here putting foРђд https://t.co/kzo2sbomxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[You canРђЎt have enough Morphe. #morphe #morphexjamescharles @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/s63pt0EWaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJBoyles @CougarHardball @EthanGa90708779 Appreciate it Mr. Boyles]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so hard to find therapists in la cause everyone needs them. It can be really frustrating. I'm glad to have oneРђд https://t.co/rm4j0ajGsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latilleon @ghettoOPRAH_ @Mr_HappyTBH Of course not. Cept a spicy leg. A spicy leg from churches can get eaten]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstalica78 @DavidGPuppet @roccomiller8 If you aren't watching the NoCoEWU Cup...you are probably watching something else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sorryimvannah Sexually assaulted one of my friends &amp; other victims]]></document><document><![CDATA[The official pants of not knowing how to use photoshopРђЎs lasso tool https://t.co/XgNN3RQJXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrchrisadams For companies trying to internally price carbon, using AWS is an unknown quantity in their budget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was going to give you some respect but straight up YOU ARE A FUCKING IDIOT! If you do have trump in your back pockeРђд https://t.co/xv4m9OGZlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinecrest HS Conference Playoff Basketball. Patriot Girls defeat Purcell Swett &amp; Boys defeat Scotland. https://t.co/qvVc7iqyyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeafsLunch1050 @TSN1050Radio @AndiPetrillo @dfeschuk DonРђЎt think thereРђЎs a need to do anything significant. No rentals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas Pretty good chances overall. Just didn't connect on the PP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayla_lov3 @LouieAsadaFries He already has a valentine.... better luck next time @kayla_lov3 !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika @Morning_Joe Split in Labor Party should fill a significant segment this morning.  Hugh internationalРђд https://t.co/DipW5uuHn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lea is sick and seems to understand on some instinctive level, through her haze of light fever and ChildrenРђЎs TylenРђд https://t.co/1ytMQLLxxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurpleHeartsOff ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ damn man that fucking sucks!! I know how it is though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another epic NETFLIX ORIGINAL !!­ЪЊ║ MANIAC has a really unpredictable and wacky storyline.­ЪЎЃ lol  Also, it really showРђд https://t.co/RZX2hKmca4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kuya Teongski!­Ъўі­Ъўі­Ъўі #100thdayofschool #EMC23 #MatteoCalix #teongski #kuya @ North Bethesda, Maryland https://t.co/Kjd6f7d4EA]]></document></documents></author>