<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jyllhbrick @meetmissjoness Benghazi, uranium1, 30,000 missing emails, fake dossier, I could site more but text is limited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stroz9 @NHL @NYIslanders @NHLdotcom Yeah I get it unfortunately the right people get chosen for these things because of biases]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HackswithHaggs So cry baby and instigator? He had what was coming and he provoke it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation just saw Sticks on The First 48 Hours. A murder in Tulsa OK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_H Dan i used to really like you. There’s a time and a place but BEST?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats - a former @Build_ADream #keynotespeaker.  You were very inspiring #GirlsInSTEM #yqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a happy ass personality with a sad ass soul , sorry if I be acting weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[DO NOT MISS THIS SALE!!!!! 🗣🗣 My $80 lash special ends this Thursday. Any style $80 regular prices are  Classic $10… https://t.co/gyRCYjSxE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR Beyond thrilled for you...Genoa City needs someone to help us solve the JT storyline and move on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go more Russian collusion more stealing votes please Congress don't let this happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoTaco1234567 @TwoInTheBushes @rfragan @ffoxxface @ProudResister @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump I'm not a democ… https://t.co/8cbThHGi0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarnoRealestate @stlpcs @Dvscott81Scott @bbusa617 @robyn_lance @KamyMAGA @BundyGP @krunalley @MattKnez1961… https://t.co/Qc5LUeZ5VG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJDuboisL7444 @realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner She got around..there is a pic of her with everybody..reminds me of the redhead NRA gal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sparkle_Lynn Girl, same 😫 Sending out this last email and I’m taking my ass to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a long day, trying to keep up with news and spending 5 hrs at dr office for tests. Another dr tomorrow. T… https://t.co/NNX5D9Ao0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeT0wn You need to check your data THE Ohio State #13 after Penn State 🤔#collegetownneedsglasses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyDublyu LOL I gave up on Pocket Camp. I need a REAL animal crossing game. I miss my villagers]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truth #abetterme #stillirise #growingoldgracefully #beautifuldisaster @ Stow, Ohio https://t.co/MHFbHfRyLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebellieing Melto bena, great post followed up with a great reply. I love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing my big bro Marcus a very happy birthday! Thank you for all you do and for always having my back 👊🏽 love you… https://t.co/VlDBmDoCAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[☔️ RIGHT NOW: @ebonideonWSB is tracking rain, possible isolated storms that could affect our Sunday plans! Her full… https://t.co/VEBq5rpMHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems.  Do you want a winning ticket??  Amy Klobuchar,age 58, Cory Booker, 49. Mid-west/New Jersey, blk/white, femal… https://t.co/9KajJPW3TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredouellet0 @ManonSavard4 @Bourmu https://t.co/ayXTzWfDRO Super conférence en EdTech 👍👍 On présente sur la mental… https://t.co/8aN4RS20ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. Left the bar to go home alone and eat a cheeseburger the size of my face. Living my best life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[plucking one wrong hair makes me feel like I fucked up my whole eyebrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisdiegolopez @mikeabrusci can we just try to get Mike Myers to make at least one more first]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now know why my parents were such fun haters when it comes to Play-Doh. And also why they both smirked the first… https://t.co/SmjZ0WSpb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister You don’t see it in the PNW....Wa State....socks and sandals....that’s us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iliza, thank you for reminding me not to stress the wedding planning (and that not all traditions should be contin… https://t.co/27KsSLzvJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[true @michaeljackson @thejacksons @janetjackson @princejackson @parisjackson @tajjackson @tjjackson @mjjrepository… https://t.co/Ma37xIeIIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSchmidtRogers @nekesastraker That or commencement practices &amp; how "student success" is measured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at City of Monterey Park - @cityofmpk in CA https://t.co/FT9BMKNVZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time Andrew Deluca speaks in Italian, my heart skips a beat! ♥️ #GreysAnatomy #innamorato https://t.co/ocIZoCSzkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a conversation with someone who doesn’t see the world the same way as you. Even if you don’t believe the same… https://t.co/DG2DQy9jhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time I tried Salvadoran food, I comatosed myself into Pupusa heaven! So many types of pupusa (translated… https://t.co/J891oNxp4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so beautiful and heartbreaking and I was mesmerized by their story 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austinnreeed Yes and I’m stupid don’t be jelly. Also, I’m all alone for the night so this should be interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost think he's trying to do a little Irish dance in this gif.🤣🤣🤣☘☘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You think teachers are losers.  You need to stop tweeting. You make yourself look immature and stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine actually thinking racism isn’t real bc of one fake report. That’s like saying rape isn’t real bc there was… https://t.co/YftbG4EImz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitCza @Joeybird @sharon_cantley @SassyCassyCat @ToughGuyMankas @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil… https://t.co/sn0JNQ57j0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EggerHaley @Zomboy And Friday is Rezz but I can't make that one cause I workkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@younggotti8 @clarke_kirk That is do hot.  I just want to stop his hand and start sucking on it until I reach the creamy delight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe we get having love for someone confused with being in love with someone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[twitter makes me feel like a hopeless romantic because no one will ever like me this much🤓🤓🤓🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get my shit together so I cleaned my whole room, just so I can’t sit on my bed and eat a whole bag of peanut m&amp;ms. Baby steps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow total at 5am in Eastford, CT. Over 9”! @ryanhanrahan https://t.co/lNtildi2Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simmi Never give up. Baby steps till you take off running. And if ya trip and fall. Get up shake it off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day on the water #capecoral #florida #sunset #boating #selfie #smiles😊 @ Cape Coral, Florida https://t.co/nrZJ4Toa8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brett_McMurphy @CFBPlayoff @Stadium WTF!? You're not even looking at returning players or schedules! Nothing but guesses here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, when an adult tells me they don’t drink coffee: https://t.co/3ul5oMBYgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryykilleen Mary, you have outdone yourself once again 😂 I’m cuttin up rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a real estate agent is so rewarding.   We are looking for agents who want to be mentored abs trained. Message… https://t.co/s5SZdz5Do1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think those clouds look like a Pig? I do. 🐷🌏⛩ #happyyearofthepig #clouds #animalclouds #drawings… https://t.co/fniIAG714R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davelackie @moominmania Congratulations!! God Bless &amp; the Love of Christ to you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamRomany @heydjnash He certainly is! Congratulations and thank you @AMillionABC for always tugging at the heart… https://t.co/2LVxw0EYCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Dick Cheney could enter the ring, water boarding the dems might straighten them out. Yikes 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnyaDobson @JudicialWatch You believe in trash! JD is an amazing group who strives for the truth and uncovers demo… https://t.co/cMLrwy1VRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnightsofBlue @ellievan65 @BarackObama Maybe he could run for vice president. It would be a brilliant move to put him on any ticket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffSteblea I need to do something. I’ve allowed chaos to rule. No more, chaos, no more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon Soft Cell, Tainted love. My friend Missy always thought it was “Don’t touch me please, I cannot stand… https://t.co/XT4MbzBAig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toadtomtoad @MomsDemand @GingerForst @Juniper78 Love you @toadtomtoad 😘 This means so much to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is your #bikejoy?! asks some of the charistmatic hosts of @BikeTalk881, a public radio program out of Cambridge, MA. #bikesummit19]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg techno song I just heard at the midway with the repeated lyric “techno is mysoginistic” - anyone know the ID??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started @GreysABC from the very beginning on @netflix    It’s been about 24 hours, and I’m almost on Season 2.   Lo… https://t.co/gicRtMFZFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t laughed this hard in a long time...highly recommend this for everyone! #goatyoga 🐐🧘‍♀️ https://t.co/SxhhSeFKS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Pom team’s whole dance routine was to a mixed up version of No Roots by Alice Murton... that was strange...]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has Facebook now, there’s no excuse for him to still bully me 5 years later. https://t.co/7Gzqevebw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food trucks line up right across the street from my apartment M-F!!! @ New York City - Manhattan - Nyc https://t.co/0m4gLHXkmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JakeRobertson_ No one:  Jake: *constanly points out the stupid things people most on social media*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I believe that many who are like you are actually Pro Birth. It seems that once a baby is born you do… https://t.co/UqMJWWWCZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanHenry Ryan can you please read the email i sent to Gina. You will be in Atlanta next week, I’m upset that i… https://t.co/xJyWMuyAxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I call a year ago when someone out and left the cat and he just sat out crying i called this morning and then when… https://t.co/WI9nzGHsQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[but i cannot keep wondering about something that is not in my life those thoughts the things i think of  that’s the… https://t.co/EUPJE6YnRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[a qué edad se le deja de tener miedo el ver cuanto se le debe a la tarjeta de crédito? 🤯🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[So so so happy #PeriodEndOfSentence won!!! #MenstrualEquality #EndTheStigma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teen Dating and Violence Awareness Open Mic 🎤... This kid can rock the 80s!! It’s a cool thing to attend these even… https://t.co/zCiGTXIphf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski I’m happy to follow you, even if your taste in candy is questionable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden YOU KNOW, that you and Obama separated children at border AND caged them!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsletter (my.openhaus ) coming out tonight. Make sure to sign up! 📝 All about community and why it’s essential fo… https://t.co/Qs81fXXCu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @supremekimun @XiJingpingReal @narendramodi @SirDougunefheir #Witness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKeithBritt @delictum @TerBer12 @FPE66 @sharpe115 @USxCONSERVATIVE @SherrieRogge1 @KaliS_18 @PreacherKeith1… https://t.co/D3PXDjmsly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no sympathy for the woman who jumped over the barrier at Arizona Zoo and was attacked by a Jaguar. She did i… https://t.co/SXHJN05CyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LebellNY @NYDailyNews @DNC Says you, House of Reps not thrilled with her or her antics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had another educational and engaging experience courtesy of 518Talks @ Proctor's Theater https://t.co/NMLpL3ByWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeMSNBC , There is nobody sleazier than Joe and Mika on MSNBC, for him to call out President Trump.  Joe and Mika… https://t.co/ToXbW0gqyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos y fríos días ☕️   Los esperamos en @_LASNOTICIASMTY . https://t.co/5u2c4aUqIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmahlandt @mfriedmanPGH @codeorg It was my pleasure!! Good luck in your new adventure!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nutrition #motivation #health #healthy #lifestyle #eatclean #healthyfood #exercise #food #cleaneating #goals… https://t.co/EuSOSOF1YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZB42 Heavy rain is not a good omen if the grounds still froze, I’m thinking. 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, today is a special day!!!!! It’s @anicole400 birthday!!!!! She is the big 19! I’m gonna make a thread of my fav… https://t.co/W5SQy3XrOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[No les pasa que tienen un amigo y ya no sienten la misma conexión que antes porque literal se nota que no le import… https://t.co/NxZlNRwTkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @lukebryan with @get_repost ・・・ @americanidol is live. Y’all watching? What do you think so far?… https://t.co/KYWzoSWiU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_classified_0 @danidonovan Whatever....  “If you’re not part of the solution, then you are part of the problem”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never even met her before.. she won’t even look at me if we’re outside at the same time, but ok. I get it. Tha… https://t.co/EdJLM9BJUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old45toter It’s not a regional thing… They’re everywhere... i’d rather have pierogies 😂😂😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Questions for Bob Gessler President Irish Memorial Board of Directors — Irish Memorial Will Move –… https://t.co/ocKZQ69ogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[every woman has been a dumb ass over a nigga at least once in her life. but i don’t want yall to be 45 and still go… https://t.co/Srl92kwsiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mqjiFDbd0n CHATTERBOX - March 2019 https://t.co/3atAkUvTxR https://t.co/RmvQ9LZYdB… https://t.co/KwCJjFHUmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #SpringFirefighterChallenge Day! Join us at 10 am at Station 78, 1225 Booker road just off I-45 to cheer on YO… https://t.co/olh36xISdK]]></document></documents></author>