<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kandi I always liked you, but after watching @CBSBigBrother  and the live feeds, you are loved!  Swanky game-play,… https://t.co/v4KbJ6BxBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we Say “HOY SE BEBE” After a Long work week, We’re NOT Kidding !! #FridayGuysNightOut #IguanaNYC #TheFellas… https://t.co/4A0XwFzQdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBS shareholders allege insider stock sales by executives in new complaint: The legal fallout from the Les Moonves… https://t.co/Zgi421qJGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norman is still the blue collar defense and rebounding guy.  Hansen is a rolling container of gasoline looking for… https://t.co/NFTLc0cctY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felonious_munk nigggggggaaaaa!!! This thread though! I know your dm’s have flooded with new compliments now. Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is your group, organization or team looking to raise money 💴 in 2019?? If you are, #TheGuyInTheTie and @DigmiNation… https://t.co/WloQAlkbPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[As annoying as the rematches are, there should be big crowds next Saturday.   LaBahn and Ridder will be full. Clark… https://t.co/2GNWtScXf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also did more research on former owners of the old house. Found their death certificates, wills, and photographs of… https://t.co/Ixw7RuFeXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re wrong. Trump got a lot of “fed up, anything is better” voters. All the key metrics for them were stagnating… https://t.co/PTs5BuhOOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BuenosDías #nuevolaredo #tam #Enriquegarzaflores Asamblea Cívica 11 de Marzo 2019. #Tiempodetodos #Anticorrupción… https://t.co/HeqhlECn9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NYCevents #NewYorkevent #BenviolaKreyòl #AyitiNanLakouA #ClassicalMusic #newyorkcity #newyorkart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if we knew it was historically stable, the only important question would be whether that will continue in the… https://t.co/SZggtP5yyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @TVAnews Lol you are so right. That ocasco Cortez representitive from New York thinks is… https://t.co/8UBtOEjk3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee now (@ Hurts Donuts - Little Rock in Little Rock, AR) https://t.co/bjFgEj9utD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might have to pass on this UM/Maryland game. The number seems to be dead on balls accurate with Charles Matthews si… https://t.co/09vMgGYvgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kornwithakay @NoahRFeldman Shameless plug for my first book, which includes analysis of Barak’s musings on the mea… https://t.co/2J0sSHFSLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossGraham555 @brucegreene Can we get her to sit on top of the needle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0Bonekun0 My biggest fear is that another country will both develop it and use it on us to substitute their own so… https://t.co/th9Hu6sL25]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story teller is looking for popcorn headlines is all. Hate crime my ass!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepliCel @chrisosaki @PeterAttiaMD @ShiseidoUSA @leebuckler If you’re working on hair growth treatments... we are listening! 🗣👂🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imthepk @nlycskn @flutterio Hooray! Glad you got it! Well earned, Pawan :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn.  I was looking for this exact job a little more than a great ago.  Of course, I'm pretty happy with the one I… https://t.co/YgA7lhyhjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy my new follower is about to start seing some shit on his timeline https://t.co/QIOPPBPp4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassFromAshley I know that she wanted that blender, but didn’t know it was all like that!! https://t.co/FRT7h1vgRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LOBOLOGAN9850 @estarc62 Pues como que no escucha muy bien, checa el tema con menor porcentaje de aprobación en su… https://t.co/W80m8yeKuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[En vez de tanta mamada sin sentido prefiero publicar historias de verdaderas mujeres que tienen un gran ejemplo a s… https://t.co/pk23B6QXm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @MyRedBeetle Those two are too stupid to get that Fox has them on to appear less white.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes #MichelleMalkin can’t actually be as stupid as she sounds.  Must have found out how to make a buck from those even dumber.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s as if City have been awarded penalties left and right this season... sheesh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyMilone29 @LukeBecker_YN26 If anything NYY buy out his arbitration yrs which would take him to his age 30 seas… https://t.co/A8eTfmKoDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieSMiller @SMAofHou @RebCouncill @tweetingtalya Me to @RebCouncill about a month ago: https://t.co/YMmySJgEQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[However, voting for the #Libertarian candidates doesn’t help the nation as a whole, it just waters down the votes t… https://t.co/81tErid00W]]></document><document><![CDATA[FML, I don't think my live session is going to stay posted so I'll probably have to do another one but edited version.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time out for these for our group tonight. #jordanix #jordan9 @diddy know about it. #snkrs @ O.P. Rockwell https://t.co/64GitRcV8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanfoxy @BostonConnr @VivalaZito @ThePubHeartland @PatMcAfeeShow pumped to finally get my membership!!!… https://t.co/zDkg0vviX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anuoa @HermosilloGob @Policia_HMO @CelidaLopezc @CampaLastra *crikets*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah! They're disrespecting Alisha and women empowerment that they shouldn't wrestle they should be at home doing t… https://t.co/iBePF8MQe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some laughter. friends tv show pictures and quotes - Google Search https://t.co/K0CZsGt5T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it wrong to love bot roth and sammy van halens ? LOL https://t.co/QK4QPY4vXr https://t.co/J7U73UlR7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Observing some stormy skies this afternoon around the Central Valley. At the same time, heavenly sun rays shine dow… https://t.co/XUQH0gqHip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Griffen Coincidental to see your Tweet just after I'd Tweeted this link: https://t.co/mIMMI3Eqp5 To understand wha… https://t.co/l2jljMpt8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonC1994 @wvfan789 @JustinThomas34 @USGA Well my 14 handicap keeps me out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinewithak1 @wahoopublic @WHSdance17 @wahoocheer You got this girls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Break with the kiddos begins!  Can you spot @JordanBWLake? 😎🤔 https://t.co/yNp4yFfuSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where does this impulse come from? The impulse, when you don’t know what you’re talking about, to try to correct pe… https://t.co/8bJyhfmzXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millwork design for a universal banker pod for a small grocery in-store branch in Arizona. - #millwork… https://t.co/aLXcKt0Thk]]></document><document><![CDATA[GARY REGIONAL,IN (GYY) ASOS reports gust of 51 knots (58.7 mph) from W @ 2045Z -- KGYY 242045Z 27035G51KT 10SM BKN031 M01/M08 A2982 RMK PRRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little appetizer before the #NASCAR race today... #RIPcity https://t.co/41zyHa2mrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE IN @spondivitsbest KILLING THE SEAFOOD!!! #PESCATARIAN LIFE!!! #ATLANTA WE HERE!! NEW CHEDDA CHIXS THOTIANA REMI… https://t.co/1J4pC9LAHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[bra blazer bikershorts #battlestargalactica #cafeza #sing #latinjazz #sidehustle https://t.co/9AIJRoCCU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot it was Valentine’s Day. Prolly gonna stay off social media so I don’t get depressed. #foreveralone… https://t.co/6yVFkLsJr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlandotheCooke @nickylep @MadeleinaKay @manbearpig9282 @WeNeedEU WTO just setts the basic laws for us to trade, t… https://t.co/ET1FJ3ZVmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLongerIgnored We need more Patriots that are not afraid to be active on the issues, an in MARCHING on Washington DC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When preparing to dress for the @dcunited home opener, one has to consider:  -wear clothes that show your support t… https://t.co/DkMjua9EEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any of my beloved followers know anyone who works in the hotel hospitality industry?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it was founded in 1642, Dutch Kills was a swampy area that had scattered farms and a mill. The Dutch Kills far… https://t.co/gmygKgwf2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rureadyshuot students- check out the #mycareerpath thread. Post your journeys that lead you into OT school and beyond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toma pues...🍔 . #Foodgasm #Food #FoodPorn #Foodie #Yum #BurgerLover #Hamburger #LoveFood #FoodPics #Yummy… https://t.co/AvexwtzTCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done @CP0031 Habs' Carey Price grants Ont. mother's dying wish, meets with son https://t.co/CTHDNQAjrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien sabe donde puedo conseguir ese gorro aquí cerca de Los Angeles??  El frío está sabroso y necesito ese gorro… https://t.co/y39EjMFG2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom how much did they bay you @WalshFreedom to attack @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[some UT sig delts tried flexing real hard at my job today, and one of their cards’ declined.. SIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Trebek is a national treasure and I can’t imagine anyone else hosting this game show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a Lions, Red Wings and Tigers fan, all I can say is  the Pistons are going to make the playoffs. Yay...love ya.… https://t.co/BInAbHtrfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Please Joe Biden is the only one that can take down this criminal!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updates on both Bryce and Manny. They’re joining @TheAthletic https://t.co/VFNfXnZU1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton I understand your argument but I make a very good liv… https://t.co/pIhJVaStLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[They leave out the fact that she first massaged the salad into her scalp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey OMG PREACH!!!! @halsey is dropping truth bombs right now and it is everything!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five years from now when James is about to host the Oscars, they gonna bring up this screen shot. Then he’ll be hav… https://t.co/KVzLdxl4xI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Bishop Talbert swan why don't you shut the hell up... Racist ass hole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny Williams should get flop shamed just like Brad Davison. That guy is on the floor every time his defender has the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryalcurtis Nope... But, my friends at @LayriteOfficial send me products from time to time so I'm good there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final in Unified basketball Greely 51 Brunswick 46 @GreelyRangers #GODRAGONS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cut from tamethemane_barbershop can make it all better @ TAME the MANE Barbershop https://t.co/jgLATCYR9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[My god.  Its a deeply inequitable tax break that privileges new owners over existing.  Where do they find these peo… https://t.co/2Kpj2o79QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @CarolynSlaskiEY for her great leadership of our Americas Talent with insights on what shes proud of a… https://t.co/3BKZL9cjqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp, clean, slightly hoppy lager with touches of fruit. - Drinking a People On Streets by @OldOxBrewery/… https://t.co/gsqVqJvqqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EliminationChamber2019 highlights: Becky decimating Charlotte and Ronda with crutches  lowlight: Amy time Renee Young talks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311Toronto Hi there has anyone responded back regarding when lights on Steeles &amp; Mountcastle will be functional ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgauthi @Yayonne11 je ne sais pas si un jour je vais me servir de cette information mais j'aime apprendre]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may look like a standard strat, but it's THE strat that was used to play the lead on Sweet Home Alabama.… https://t.co/MOWF38rHiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Stephen Miller tell you to say that. Or did he write this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FMzeke Fair, let me put it this way: RJ is going to be a better NBA player than Zion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym, REMEMBER, liars go to hell, so do sexual abuse enablers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @marcorubio Hola señor es preso que hay que traerlo a todos presos para EU 🇺🇸 https://t.co/OZWVW41WV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliRN619 @OnlyTruthReign @dunbdav @MelchioriTech @Larrybarnett777 @TheyStoleMyID @SealeyGerald @Stevegaston18… https://t.co/2jsm4oSbaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GladysMarinaGo1 @DrodriguezVen @ViceVenezuela @realDonaldTrump @SMoncada_VEN Y el Chapo era bueno? Lo gano honrada… https://t.co/7aFFvNT8oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVajpayaee @larry_leadford @KarenBarryDavi1 @silvisol24 @bluemeuninck @Sylpete @Samanpriyankar6 @EByzio @shinunao2… https://t.co/IYzorlDbDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm listening to @espn1000 with @TuneInSports. #NowPlaying https://t.co/SOZPiNHkeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevUnknown And Ryan Reynolds voicing him doesn’t help that at all 😭 Pikachu really going through some SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBarreiroKFAN 12 oz. Beer for $5 = 41.66 cents per ounce. 20 oz. Beer for $9 = 45 cents per ounce. Not a great savings]]></document><document><![CDATA[people manipulate you just to get what they want once they get it... ,it’s wraps lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_lyons47 @SusieS34 I dont think it will happen but I would love it if #Cersei was killed by #JamieLannister b… https://t.co/tigQ3r0O0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck @ChelseaClinton You’re wrong. Yes, he had a conviction. But he “legally” purchased his gun and later… https://t.co/jamUz7oQxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMankiewicz I have a feeling after 2 hours this isn’t gonna end well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annamaria1word @AOC 1,000,000 fewer people@in poverty. 1,500,000 less people on welfare,  over 5,000,000 new jobs… https://t.co/gLEytMtfuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManvsAle @TuppsBrewery @cellmavin @zappafaye @almostablaze @ephoustonbill @RedStripeRocco @cedarflats @sake_tasty… https://t.co/6tUBHA0EVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[There just isn’t really an argument. One destroyed a football stadium and the other killed half the universe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rebuilds take time and are so much fun to be apart of. Best formula I know. “Get old and stay old.” Great times are… https://t.co/5igGRfVslC]]></document></documents></author>