<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BleacherDenizen @RichardOtte5 That’s true. The girls game is more of a finesse game like the European game because… https://t.co/ZWPaPxA827]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump rips into Mueller probe at CPAC during lengthy speech  https://t.co/hyAaxuwLwg If this were OBAMA these Chump… https://t.co/ypKb594XKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[on the way to a Palm Springs getaway a surprise #sterlingruby sculpture as part of #DesertX https://t.co/pV8WFzYJ41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gettv The bunny ears and the phone! We had lamps with large figures too - but we had an elephant and a tiger! The… https://t.co/mypmBedfAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still by your side GoldenKnights!! #vgk @ Great Lakes https://t.co/7uZ8EOL1g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Kinda blows up Chris Christie’s arguments from a few minutes ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting new from @swbts and @AdamGreenway. Please pray for our trustees. Please pray for this fervent evangelist a… https://t.co/GCOl04fU3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buena suerte a @JuanPabloMusic1 on #AmericanIdol tonight! He creido en ti desde el principio ❤ https://t.co/dyltN7spJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyythevegan He didn't say we were all annoying and militant he said some of us were. And yeah that doesn't make m… https://t.co/B1kQSGXbIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff: Erik Prince Lied When He Said He Told Congress About Trump Tower Meeting  https://t.co/RP8Tw0PHNs via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. If you blow your money on addiction, that's a bigger waste 2. Maybe don't spend your money on drugs??🤷‍♂️ 3. I'd… https://t.co/WwdkBp5oPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A MATCH MADE IN HEAVEN.  🎥🎤🎬 #StandUpComedy .  #HappyValentinesDay #Love #StandUp https://t.co/n5QOau0WFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PsychologyDoc I think it was the switch from sugar to high-fructose corn syrup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterboykin She just keeps saying stupid shit unbelievable this is the Democrat party]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost via from @MauricePKerry Another day down, what did you o with yours? --------------------------------------… https://t.co/ifbb41MnT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorKimberley Repukes do that (I mean what Geraldo, Trump etc do). They tend to use themselves as the standard i… https://t.co/Bl2PbdNV7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York been fucking with @streetwearvntg. The last three things I’ve shipped been going out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrbacon50 @MhawkRetland To be clear, by "get out of their own way," I simply mean that the party and it's media ar… https://t.co/VEQJQSMmE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[sonofavet_reality_show SPECIALIZING IN ENTIRE ESTATE CLEAR-OUTS, BUY-OUTS, AND ESTATE LIQUIDATIONS!!. @ Beverly Hil… https://t.co/EvvL6771Xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[i almost did not pay my phone bill on time!! thanks verizon for not sending me a text]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say, I really love these profile stories.  It's not just about showing up and playing ball.  Takes an ama… https://t.co/jvItwxLvqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CtrPubSafExc Congratulations Chief Clouston from your friends @scfirefighters!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I’m trynna be a step dad to one of y’all kids.. and going traveling and bomb ass you know 😉 for real tho. I’m ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustaRhymes That album, along with many of your others, are still in rotation...I still have the cd in my big ass cd case. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallSFears @lovetanner @JackPiperx @mackgibson2 @MichaelFischer_ @AustinDaMan08 too many bro hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is either a young #woodpecker or   cavorting is going on between them and the #finches. #ornithology… https://t.co/Jc9EFKo97E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregpak @sxsw @leinilyu @sunnygho I just saw this and am crying tears of joy. I never thought they would create a… https://t.co/tQW6GiyCwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturdayshoot  Time to get back to WORK!!  📷: @seanmurphyphoto  #bts #behindthescenes @ Destin, Florida https://t.co/dOc0bkEZnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bivol_d what a great display of boxing skillz Congratulations Champ!👊 @premierboxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rtreatwilliams I think this is far more dangerous situation that the President in Vietnam. Two nuclear powers on t… https://t.co/xR3P1piUip]]></document><document><![CDATA[This might be an addiction now?!? #peanutbuttersmootie (at @PressedCafe in Nashua, NH) https://t.co/Tk8ZubaiIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc America’s grandest lie. Go to college they said. Go take out loans they said. Go get a great job that pays the loans back they said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your an  idiot, nuclear weapons are not holding n Korea's economy back, you really know nothing ab… https://t.co/H789RNoXBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacenLee @d_yaddow Just subtract 12 from the big number and you get the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love following great people follow @Bob_Lazzari @larrystevensS3 @LarryBaseball @LisaLongball @mlogan31… https://t.co/MUnd1h9ScO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pulling hard for Julio. Dude is a lifetime @Braves player (to this point) and seems to have worked hard the who… https://t.co/wVAWLBJ51Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/X6Ur3Cdo14. There has been at least 58 states of emergency s declare by different presidents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beginning watercolor sketch for the mural #mlkjr #mlk #martinlutherkingjr #art #sketch #unity https://t.co/lL628OBYlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau "tuberculosis epidemics – families were separated"  That's the treatment since TB is contagious and… https://t.co/stOuh8pnWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinaLikesBooks Hey, that's a big deal, congrats! Is your grill out there :)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may not be where you need/want to be today, and you probably won’t get there by tomorrow, next week or next mon… https://t.co/updYxccJxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@design2research @Flipgrid @iste Thank you, @design2research! I really appreciate that. Looking forward to #iste19. #FlipgridFever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeedyariana , goodnight Butera dream of your ones gone but not forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptMarvelNews Rewatching The Last  Dragon 🐉 this weekend to celebrate. #YouveGotThis https://t.co/Fix9oolQDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day to all my gfs out there @marceyshehata @princessafaaf https://t.co/K26NV9BWb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came very close to vomitting today. #thankyoucrossfit #crossfit #truenorthfitness #ihatepullups]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin no other presidency, has made more progress with north korea than trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca na Historia do Brasil, uma Defunta De Nome Marielle, Fez os Esquerdista ganhar tanto dinheiro, ela leva Wagne… https://t.co/MXhUD444xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh1Rivera @doliver8 consider yourself uninvited to the brainstorm ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @trashtvaddict @pitsagainst @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/7yK6N67e2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsiren Congrats on the well deserved Jake Wade award...proving once again that good things happen to good people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Colton hop the fence or lose his virginity first on #TheBachelor ? @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Deporteando ⚽️ que bien @maldoga que estás con el maestro @Carlos8Reinoso en el Corre, éxitos y que sea buena gestión,saludos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraditionFlags @kiawahresort My favorite course I have ever played and that’s out of over 330 played to date. Spec… https://t.co/B7z0XYE9hK]]></document><document><![CDATA[*continuously checks email hoping classes will be cancelled knowing damn well they won’t be*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us make prayer and studying God’s Word a priority so we can be aware of the wonderful promises and treasure wit… https://t.co/ejYTfptJ9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @rail581 Pardon me JR ! #DemocraticParty Told illegals to vote, look what you got for breaking the… https://t.co/zKbcOQmc5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Florida Aquarium @ Florida Aquarium Caricature Stand https://t.co/mY7kDCcIzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines to the extraordinary, smart, funny, beautiful and one of a kind @Class_w_History. You are my pride… https://t.co/mK1mgcyxHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're long-time @Padres season ticket holders. We often wish for more hits, more runs, more excitement. But we alwa… https://t.co/Trf9oJ8ghr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_McLane Smart move clear money off the books and open up spot for much younger players]]></document><document><![CDATA[He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty.… https://t.co/h5tKsN83zJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we’re at this fresa club and they have karaoke night, everyone is signing fresa pop .. I’m about to kill the moo… https://t.co/Ht7tFRRw5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[New gang who dis? #fartbarf #continental @ The Continental Room https://t.co/8FzW5jFC1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goddess_R6 Phew. I mean maybe all the alcohol killed the flu. So you’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going down in less than 30 minutes!! If you aren’t at the Santander Arena , you better be tuned in @830amWEEU!… https://t.co/jP5pZs3LR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back_ttys “Why can’t y’all stop talking about the chick we won’t shut up about?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @IlhanMN Check out @RealJamesWoods’s Tweet: https://t.co/IK8Ro2Qlgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TooGooden16 Do all the older folks who live in Florida also have to fly back to NY when they ache?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people cheat? You have to be a real slimeball to go behind somebody you “care” about and lie to them over and over again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Methodist Filipinos Urged to Back Traditional Standards   https://t.co/ftrhD5hnJW via @TheIRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dude calls cops on someone, the ask for his license and turns out he has a warrant and he gets arrested. https://t.co/CnlWNUQrAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've just entered for a chance to win an XPS 13 9380 laptop from Windows Central! https://t.co/T6HNJCKQCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right out of the organized crime section laybook - page 4: Protection/extortion]]></document><document><![CDATA[You get a 💉 of adrenaline when you know good players are on your campus. Looking to continue the momentum for the class of #20TheHardWay]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Michelle blows up and is big time ESPN reporter I’m defiantly going to miss her Utes tweets. This is exactly w… https://t.co/7kKiRE3tgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest #photoshoot The Moves Collective #photography #bands #Concerts #band #jamsession #music #nikon #rocknroll… https://t.co/qSAMVu79SJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I married a Ho...I can say anything and it is legal. @kenjeong 😂👏🏽 #FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSTRodB @VintageBrowns @RageRhino1241 @NickKorora Now this fella sure could tote that pigskin. https://t.co/t7K06a0kas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@max_bronstein The wrench here is that risks of lending and staking are very different, so borrowing rate is actual… https://t.co/6FsnDzHRfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Remind me who supported white supremacist. Good people on both sides? Hmmmm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTOAdvisor @homelaber @Camtasia @NScuola @JessieO_Donnell Indeed it is, also includes SnagIT. I’m sure @Camtasia a… https://t.co/ND2MroCfdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing push day, hit chest. Shoulders, triceps with all my might then finish up with burning 400 calories on the s… https://t.co/ZR7s4F7Mwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to be the coldest IVE EVER EXPERIENCESd this weekend and going into next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewFitz_1 I posted about the same thing at the same time. Are the book title initials AGM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at me in the back.. Wow, I remember this day so vivid.. This was the first time Karl Lagerfeld showed in NYC a… https://t.co/KfxeeYIpWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glen Burnie MD Sun Mar 3rd AM Forecast: TODAY Rain/Snow Hi 39 TONIGHT Rain/Snow Lo 31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder tomorrow we continue Read Across America Week as it will be “Wacky Wednesday.” Wear your clothes backwards… https://t.co/w8RiqCkcNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinaRenee4 Then tell him to change his LinkedIn and stop misrepresenting himself. Sheesh, are you a fucking on… https://t.co/i92vSgbQVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiniMe_F3 @Doug_Siegfried @f3granite @F3PhoenixAZ @F3_TRUEbadours @F3MustardSeeds Great job Mini representin !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDSSband Do we get banned from listening if we check this out and don’t like it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t @RepJerryNadler bringing Bill of Attainder back to life? SHAME SHAME SHAME @realDonaldTrump @ScottAdamsSays… https://t.co/ehOSZH3G6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Charlotte #NC  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/rNYhYwILSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought this was weird until I realized Americans say chick, a baby bird]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisvo2019 @conniestitution @trevwitham @thesoydivision @ArturoTrapagaCA @livvsparks @jessboughton_ https://t.co/rqQvHRlmxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pierce County's Todd Carter ... Wrestling State Champion! https://t.co/SE5RUSdPRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightsCameraPod ┳┻|  ┳┻|  ┻┳| ┻┳|  ┳┻|  ┳┻|  ┻┳|  ┻┳|  ┳┻|  ┳┻|  ┻┳|  ┳┻|  ┻┳|  ┳┻| _  ┻┳| •.•)    I think this looks fine. ┳┻|⊂ﾉ      ┻┳|]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina It’s this and the Eli tirade that is literally forcing me to turn my back on this game I have love… https://t.co/YThKbdCDMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night convos with @Infiniteris will always be the funniest thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shiner Lemon Pils by @ShinerBeer at @rudysbbq — https://t.co/FowDZN9e3K]]></document></documents></author>