<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The Democratic National Committee has voted down a ban on corporate PAC donations!!! This is WHY we #DemExited the… https://t.co/ZyBMlpnWno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amoslee with strep throat is better than most artists on their best night. Tonight’s theryman show saw him leaning… https://t.co/xAtyU0QHPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharriseLane @DonnaHerndon39 I’m white and I’m perfectly fine with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife and I watching the bachelor with my mom and dad..."they haven't shown the ring guy" me: "Neil lane? " My wi… https://t.co/cGzZBN1mgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMViviano They didn’t allow him to play on Saturday. They don’t call that a suspension? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Queen of Africa: AMPLIFIED! https://t.co/WMykn8hPLF https://t.co/Vcqp9CkN25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously free speech is only for the lefty’s in their opinion! Don’t act like it’s OK to use your constitutional r… https://t.co/6Pz1CEwzPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[why were they filming tho? lol y’all are gullible as fuck, this is obviously fake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Staples I don't think attention is being paid to the naming here. While the BBQ combo is Mayocue, the mustard… https://t.co/mLyG8cTG5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump No he doesn’t it’s your TDS flaring up again it does that I’m sure your aware if it… https://t.co/xp8OyImub1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina You didn't deserve that! Chill about a QB! It will happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was going to check this out but waited to finish some things first. It was gone by time I arrived.  Lesson learned:… https://t.co/vhBdBuwG0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally took an extra flinstone vitamin today. Im fuckin zooted 😤🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@korynnoc Look 4 a prospective sponsor of your choice to help promote yourself n an exclusive sponsor $, u shouldn'… https://t.co/BSNv3GqPEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[BitcoinHEX: Claim free BHX by signing statement given by the claim tool from Bitcoin wallet containing BTC… https://t.co/LETzvxDgyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorChase is SPOT ON with his comments at the Lorain Board Meeting right now. Thank you, Mr. Mayor.… https://t.co/i1I1KxqFOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @MeTV @AntennaTV  @Airwolf4Life https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/iSXgNC5aue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @michellemalkin Can we just tell Twitter to stick that law up where the sharia don't shine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say no matter what if she get to come back she goes to prison for life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morningside College to present winter choral concert on March 7 at 7:30 pm in Eppley Auditorium.… https://t.co/r2DkLp1s0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima go pay my lawyer tomorrow fuck it give him a stack and let him get to work. Make sure we finish the case before… https://t.co/E588tibHgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wiscobeergeek We found half a bottle of Christian Brothers blackberry brandy in our apartment at an age where you… https://t.co/p3hd3LwTbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGPuppet @ASUNMBB @HoopsHD @jstalica78 This may be the biggest sporting event in the history of the City of Atlanta!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pasamos chingon en nuestro baile privado con uliceschaidezoficial!! Gracias a todos los que nos acompañaron!! @… https://t.co/dNY2wKpUvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wifey left me alone on a Sat, guess Ill get into some shit. #SaturdayThoughts https://t.co/PnPDtfOrwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neville_park That's why its nice Youtube livestreams let you scrub through the past footage and find the more inte… https://t.co/0JWcnVIXfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSuperHen you are very welcome my man!! I am beyond blessed to know you and your family!! All of the guys were s… https://t.co/CvRlcSyy9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone wants to take one for the team and tell me they have a crush on me that’d be tight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDBerryMD The Best Tofurkey recipe EVER!!! Just in time for thanksgiving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithCampbellJ1 @tweetmommybop Dammit I thought you were into Sadomasochism!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 Few people today remember that Richard Nixon had the CIA MURDER elected Chilean Socialist President Al… https://t.co/Y69uxSYEoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @benshapiro  Michael Cohen’s powerhouse lawyer Lanny Davis, under fire after he “unintentionally m… https://t.co/rpInKVLaVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_4_Nine @RuffinTwyla I was sitting among Grenada fans and they were very frustrated their team couldn’t stop… https://t.co/7YptaiabLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little DMB fix with the “She” intro on the Buckeye Show! @TimHall971 thanks buddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! @AnnikaLangvad! 2nd at #Stradebianche   Will she be returning to the mtn bike or not this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decent night cashing 4 of 8 lineups led by 41 points from my @Capitals stack in the @NHL and 325 from a… https://t.co/7j4nga5WCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got done visiting with the @montereyhs wrestling team! 4 of the Plainsmen are gearing up for State and we will… https://t.co/3xuBZ2uxE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[a rouge A319 with an air canada arrival on the parallel approach. #aviation #photography #avgeek https://t.co/0RMSeGFBWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinPWinter For the record you were the only one to answer. So thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Ways to Strike Up a Conversation at a Networking Event https://t.co/KnSnMw0hMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Michigan, MSU Chasing B1G Foe for 3-star 2020 Southfield (Mich.) DT Bryce Austin - https://t.co/dyZ1TZmQSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united PS: It’s sunny and 35F at @EWRairport Do you need it to be spring to fly in and out of that broken down heap of an airport?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfergus I loved The Ascent of Money! I'll have to give The Square and The Tower a try. 📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I said, habs praying for  2 pts on bottom feeders, problem is 4 goals on 17 shots. You don’t go far with this… https://t.co/rogltf7bA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CobraShadowJoes I WISH I could wait for Netflix. I'm just too "online" to pull that off. I love the interconnected… https://t.co/An0tTOQqtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you won the lottery. Can go anywhere in the world for dinner. Where will you go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Yucha’s husband wins. She received a prep-time Valentine surprise from JJ, the field dog at @uspbl Jimmy John’… https://t.co/f8HtPi6X5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the fuck they be so stingy with the cashews in trail mix https://t.co/IcOqSsK8C9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll stipulate that Tina was wherever you say she was the morning of July 16.  “I’ll talk to my client.” - Opposing… https://t.co/T8u7qMRc2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[😅 ya a real crazy clown Race to the extreme left to see who can get there first Contest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who's back, back again #Avs are back, tell a friend #GoAvsGo https://t.co/u2zsLUOG5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of @theofficenbc when @jennafischer (Beesly) told everyone she seen it, but no one believed her until th… https://t.co/3dAl8RmuhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resurfacing several of our Har Tru and Hard Courts at the USTA National Campus working with the excellent team from… https://t.co/u8Ms1XW6oU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ServantOnIce Ha!  I will always prefer tacos. But maybe they are a little overrated]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to make sure that I don't have sex with any of Buddhist monks or amschel Mayer Rothschild friends including… https://t.co/O6sEiVC9Tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this game @doctajordan told me they weren’t losing another game all year and he was RIGHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richmossman Mossman! Good to hear from you, man. Random as the world is, my wife works with Joe Haubenhofer these… https://t.co/3VdbdX2yok]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇹👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Anna Nas! growing.annanas The White RACE Austrian BLONDES👑🇦🇹 Women Are Th… https://t.co/9EtUGTLSVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really kill me , I ain’t looking to take nobody on a date anymore 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Oh please run...the clown show the democrats are running could use you...this will be a super fun election]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotink305 wants to a portfolio piece horror portrait special half off  to the first  10 people to HMU with your ide… https://t.co/tTnCX0AG51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickTimiraos Black % bouncing around at bottom. Uptick is not statistically significant yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I eat these for lunch and dinner.  For breakfast I have a meal replacement shake.  By equate.  Creamy milk chocolat… https://t.co/HsFx7mVzau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babes In Loboland 🐺 #chavezhighschool #classof2005 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/faD4M8nPSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great interview. Check it out, rasslin' friends 🤘  #VictoriaForHallOfFame]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @Taylors_Bar if classes are cancelled tomorrow will you do dollars all day until you run out of beer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start of second week of running, hips are tight and sore, cardio needs lots of work, but it was fun out at tge katy… https://t.co/gxfl1K7mcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a mini road trip soon with my family to cheer on the best team in Orlando. Can’t wait for the home opener.… https://t.co/Gq1eCNpOtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWW_ATC @ColumbusCrewSC @ChicagoFire @fccincinnati @Chas_Battery Thank you @BWW_ATC for 10 years supporting the black and yellow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidalangrier Even Uncle Phil would have been jealous of that luxurious beard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voy en tren camino a Nueva York y ya me conseguí con dos amigos que venían borrachos de algún bailongo.   De paso t… https://t.co/OhYq5dK6xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @GRHSLonghornsBB and me at 240 pm today for our LIVE coverage of @GRHS_BBall in the UIL Regional Finals from… https://t.co/4Iy4tJoBRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russwest44 They expect you to be quiet when people coming for your manhood. These people be doing anything just to… https://t.co/FvBweYxZ0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello can someone in Orlando get me an adderall pls why is this so hard to find lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some solid advice here when considering baby names. https://t.co/K3d2li7Dvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirkchatelain @HuskerHistory @OWHbigred Game changer in run pass and return game]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so cold literally when i got gas i had to run into my truck so i wouldn’t freeze my nuts off]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a Celtics fan? Lol. The fan(s) involved tonight shouldn't be allowed back in the arena but you're clearly just… https://t.co/lpdSaa8450]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thoroughly enjoy what the @NHLCanes are doing, and appreciate how they're handling the hate from older fans. They… https://t.co/RrnUTnAgA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Oh really? If everyone tells HER to jump off a balcony will she do it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[El que madruga dios le ayuda, enfocado en alcazar la meta! https://t.co/MzqlcZQkHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[La catedral de San Patricio es una catedral católica de estilo neogótico decorado ubicada en Nueva York. En su esti… https://t.co/ApOrfawzhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EasternSierra Tioga Pass will be plowed to the top on the east side within 5 days of the goshawks occupying the ne… https://t.co/v7gEQKg5on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarceloRdzA @FNxFamilia @DiputadosPANNL @MtyFollow Gracias Marcelo por expresar lo que piensas pero debemos entend… https://t.co/rUkMzOaEHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChapmanFamilyYT Can’t wait! Only thing getting me through my work day today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel bad that Bryce Harper has to live in Philly for the next 13 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops I’ve fallen so deeply down into another niche music hole.  Norwegian dance 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoTechBen Let them talk, we know how good the Bucks are and they will deliver when the playoffs come around. Let’s… https://t.co/y1C8gWrkOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuplaMaria @GirautaOficial Y el q no lo quiera entender....sonotone....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta Wey saco a toda su familia a relucir.... Jajaja eres grande morena]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @pdx_softlips @littlesexbuddha @NinaDolciXXX @elenakoshkaxoxo @_Rush187_ @xaidrafox @Kinsley_Edenxxx… https://t.co/9KxnxMYTpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodjobliz He’s my neighbor! Welcome to come sit on my block and thirst in the general direction of his apartment whenever you like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn it’s 2:50 and I’m bout to get up and make me some cookies and cream ice cream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a beautiful sun rise to start a new day! @ Farmington, Arkansas https://t.co/UHMLAWDU2E]]></document><document><![CDATA['I think Kim knew what happened' to Otto Warmbier: House GOP Leader Kevin McCarthy - ABC News https://t.co/qVCApX3PXk (via @ABC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imperial Imports 👑   Squad rolled in about 15-20 cars deep! https://t.co/ZYsOlWmjUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkulFred @ThatDaveBrown Isnt Goldn Person older than anyone on the roster?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gillette your razors are literally trash I am never buying one of your products ever again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoo @arminvanbuuren pls drop Road to Dublin @BeyondWland hahaha I’ll lose my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbel27931214 @LoganOfOrkney @iamIqraKhalid If their caught I betcha they won't say their names Kinda think we know who did it!]]></document></documents></author>