<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[For all my gamers out there watch this video it’s my favorite from nakey jakey next to his halo ones https://t.co/jztSpRp3kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samanxhamarie We only have to make up 2-3 at this point THANK THE LORD. but if we keep getting more it may just cu… https://t.co/BHdJvw5iGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoxybooMagic @LegatoTia @KLaurieks @DediShannon @marythemedium @TewsTinamarie @CmreddingDoodle @Haifisch_Von… https://t.co/MgHMj8tvd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian sooo who’s gonna tell @khloekardashian that her little family been broken 5 women and a baby ago ?… https://t.co/mkOtZUcsKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySimonds1 @GinaPustor123 @brittafahl70 @birgit_gerach @gandusio @wrightPG23 @SonjaNi41294318 @fulvia14130533… https://t.co/5zzn54AxBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13WHAM We were out no more than an hour @RGandE great job preparing and reacting to outages. You need to get credit for a job well done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewschmitz @IngrahamAngle @EllenPage @EllenPage is young, idealistic and Stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oficina del Alto Comisionado de las Naciones Unidas para los Derechos Humanos: Visita de Michelle Bachelet a Venezu… https://t.co/l15WhudRdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[pls he’s like a kid in a candy store im so ready 🥺 https://t.co/2REjnZzxfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MosaicPrep @KenyatteReid @PaulForbesNYC @NYCSchoolsOSYD @LRobinsonNYC @jmarifernandez @MorningsideCtr… https://t.co/eh3AyQb1cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can we not get Demi for bachelorette @ABCNetwork ?!? Please make it happen!! 🙏🙏 #TheBatchelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevieshew @jonasbrothers I feel that Stevie. I just gave my fiancé all the JoBro knowledge I have today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddinoble666 I mean I could understand why he says that tho. Bunch of college kids and people who just go bc of t… https://t.co/BnzAvHtwFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CKerns I was gonna follow up and I totally forgot and then I got a like and it jolted the shit out of my memory!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamdeVry1 All State/Fed Courts need to refine their statutes. Now he needs a victim he targeted. He was the pe… https://t.co/zJyeEFIe3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandarina65 @krassenstein He should never have had them with him. Family is family and #NepotismSucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be here! Great to reunite with partners and friends across the State working to be the best emergency mana… https://t.co/swqhEFB5yB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericarhodes Talk with us #4pawspantry! You won’t be sorry, over 1.3 million meals provided since 2012! Over 4K… https://t.co/o7EI4YZxvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[flyin back to england in four weeks solely to see my mum get pissed n buy a fish . hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulapessoabr @AVENAoficial @mARIACasadevaLL Ficar nua è o argumento desses lixos! Acefalas  so tem muchibas p apresentar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAM3R0NPH1L1P 1. reading fanfics  2. dubbed 3. behind the scene of dubbed   but all of your vids are great keep going sweetie🤪🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #science experiment that was supposed to end by 9:00 pm last night turned into an overnight relay race! Receiving… https://t.co/67T2dD4Q00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views from the 6... 6th floor  #WorkViews #NurseLife https://t.co/3wsq9LU40C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprintcare @MichelCombes Then why did someone go through my kid to get my husband's number to then tell us that we… https://t.co/dUfBh3knrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you're with me, but I wish I could hear your voice for real. I wish I could tell you about all the crazy buc… https://t.co/tu7VIG3Y6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworkers are talking game of thrones and I’m only on season 5, plz stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I throw all my cares before You. My doubts and fears don't scare You. You're bigger than I thought You were, You… https://t.co/FU3ljEsLNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reasons behind varying policies: fears (sometimes valid) of bathroom misbehavior, lack of resources to monitor bath… https://t.co/KSDDfe3dwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing hard outside, but I am craving for Jollibee and I want to see my cousin!! 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badenchalmers There’s enough spin going on in the world, don’t need it here. I said studied it. Not a career. What… https://t.co/MzhCuRQ3ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us Wednesday for our annual Spring Break Festival from 1:00-3:00 pm. Art activities, animals and more- FREE fu… https://t.co/es5FgSDXWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that weird? Does everyone just make their kids the same stuff they liked when they were young? Grilled cheese sa… https://t.co/DTjYNEjxtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous morning✨ Happy International Women’s Day! Thank you @katiemehnert from @PinkPetro and @randizuckerberg for… https://t.co/rtgE2CHRWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me last week: i'm saving my bonus this month.  Me today: spends $100+ in less than 25 minutes... 🤦‍♀️🙄😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ep 6 of the @WJCTJax "What it's Like" storytelling podcast: https://t.co/NjF9PEpr2H. Although it's been Claire's jo… https://t.co/b2yZBMTUXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my "first week" tasks at @MNBWSR include reviewing drafted @Articulate water quality training modules and p… https://t.co/57NN8WynPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Society has instilled racism so deep into some ppl and they’re so ignorant n blind to it it’s FUCKING WILD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J9DC Yasss hahaha I feel like @KitsieDuncan should be a part of this thread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDan039 @nancyandmj @DarrenJMeenan Don’t worry Dan, I would never boo ya!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happily ever after is right now!  Quit waiting for some future date to start asking for what you want in life and l… https://t.co/z3C9XSE7Hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonp1968 @AFP I was not there to see a crime take place. You weren’t either. Unfortunately his parents weren’t e… https://t.co/hWf0WiaHwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder when beeeezos is gonna stop playing coy and just acquire buzzfeed https://t.co/WjCrjk9b3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drnptk lol I went to visit family in Louisiana once as a little kid and remember them telling me “don’t fall in th… https://t.co/CANgnf0EXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watched Flatbush the movie last night now we watching da trap movie. Y’all got any other suggestions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isnt it funny how when ACTUAL racist hate crimes occur Republicans didnt acknowledge them but all of sudden they gi… https://t.co/z7pZ9qnPp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw someone talk about the app called Gemini that helps you delete photos you don’t need off your phone! I have o… https://t.co/nOeT9r2ZVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PinkShirtDay2019 is Wednesday, February 27.  It is a day to stand up for kindness and against bullying of all kind… https://t.co/VTOhb2VBnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Banda MS at the Smart Financial Center https://t.co/iASSgsxsXi via @YouTube interview with Rucker Express]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day #love #perfect #musiclyrics #BryanAdams #alwaysandforever #HappyValentinesDay… https://t.co/vhTJbdO3kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NataTheScribe @BrianBrackeen @jentrification @iRunWithLula @alf_y_jackson @deongordon I see this is going to be a… https://t.co/t5PYGEaPbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks barista on Broad River/Irmo - you rock! Holding my coffee out the drive-thru window with some early morning enthusiasm! 🤣☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincentdonofrio As a 5th grade teacher, I spend my whole day acting and entertaining. Inspiring students to learn… https://t.co/dw8mDoeTM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endorsed by #kingofpops #TheRealDonnaJTrump is the greatest pop taster ever. "We always get @TheRealDonnaJT to be a… https://t.co/a0g380N4R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWIT THOUGHT PO-PO: SEE THIS IN MY FEED. THEY SAID I ASKED NOT TO SEE. I RE-TWEETED, FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD! INSANITY… https://t.co/I1phbVXDrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dinolich It was just a couple sneezes but now he’s wheezing bad, pretty significantly compared to his brother. I’m… https://t.co/hUCswefja7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would never sit and watch a bunch of self-absorbed people who idolize themselves and think they are elitist. They… https://t.co/8lkbclper4]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who care about money more than anything else are all security risks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelagunder @jlknott @MaddieShellgren @gravesle @Caitlin__Barlow @min_susan @daniellefowler @hannahmbullion https://t.co/0YWIAxV4PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Ceni @peac4love for retweeting my poem! Happy day friend!💙💚💜💦 https://t.co/amVIDQb8UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey52389335 @washingtonpost Hardly! If Inslee’s campaign excels, he’d have no problem winning Wisconsin and Pe… https://t.co/dNk7hl01IH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #IStandWithThePresident Donald J Trump, soooo very proud of u Sir. TRUMP2020, if we could have u l… https://t.co/mb4WSUqu0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suggest move Bennie Thompson down to the border with the people who have to live in fear every day.  BUILD THE WA… https://t.co/cy9P6S2dNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I called the #JussieHoax since it happened...there’s a reason there was no video footage, also he was getting cut f… https://t.co/iNpQaIPhda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hopmar3 @IndivisibleNet my cousin home schooled her kids, and I've been told that home schooling has higher testin… https://t.co/V1m6zeXekj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Maher is garbage and completely out of touch with Americans..give a man a mic and suddenly he feels powerful..… https://t.co/GNGXtOEBv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome. ❤ #WillSmith #jadapinkettsmith must be so proud! Jaden Smith's Foundation Created A Water Filtrati… https://t.co/eugcW7oAsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when we used to have battles to see who can “ pop , lock , and drop it “ the best.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrTexIT Then we can honor the person who invented the gaff gun. https://t.co/8YumX58lN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Negative space alternate. #52frames #52framesphotographers #52frames_alternate #weeklyphotochallenge #cloudysky☁️… https://t.co/QQFOyihEdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache I'm an afro indigenous woman, best friend, aunt, sister, domestic violence survivor, #MeToo ,mental hea… https://t.co/9dwARCsdMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents conversation while my dad is half asleep:  dad: “when you go downstairs can you put the kettle on”  my m… https://t.co/BoMTchWkEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jylianfaith @_haleewilliams @geisler_shelbi okay this is childish. so wassup, y’all dry ass arguing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[every day to #pressforprogress. I celebrate the contributions each of us makes to make our worlds a better place fo… https://t.co/sjjpVyDkkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston Mayor @marty_walsh It’s time for infrastructure now. It’s what city leaders are focused on. Not a partisan i… https://t.co/lVFAA08byh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When girls post a new boyfriend every month, it’s the craziest thing to me. Like do you girlfriend but take a breathing break, damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Leach completed the Ultramarathon! Time 08:13:38 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/pvg8ZsgFgJ #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit, I would die if I got to see my inspiration and the woman who makes me wanna fight anyone who crosses my… https://t.co/M4pJnisBX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh please....he had sex with a sex slave ...twice!!...geeeeeeeze...you are unwatchable...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tunrip Ha! I have a wok I don’t use and millions of socks.  Now thinking what I can store in the crock pot, mussel pot, fish kettle...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is just one vicious cycle of buying stuff from Primark, going back to return some things and buying more stuff while I’m there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump just spat on the family of Otto Warmbier by saying he believes Kim Jong Un’s denials of involvement in Otto’s… https://t.co/gkCV9jemaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @amyklobuchar @donlemon It will never happen. NAP voters want Schultz. Hope he runs. Sick of the democrats and… https://t.co/gI1ThJKmw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now learning about how well 2015 Healthy Eating Index scores associate with incident cardiovascular disease, cardio… https://t.co/icTryZA9uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boodreaux1Pryor @alllibertynews @justinamash @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Has Trump spent the money that was allocated… https://t.co/tD3wPf3MIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like, the version I’m watching is commercial free but the Republicans were running their own advertisement rig… https://t.co/qlRLYHPdPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 19 year old nephew Teamont is in the hospital as well. On Thursday, he attempted suicide ❤️🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Boho Betty” dress. {$30} Only Small and Medium left. Grab your’s before it’s gone! Fits TTS.… https://t.co/CsSm6tomN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pherdtner @THEKIDMERO You must!! If only for Black Monday and Homeland!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Praying       For           Our                President .. Donald J Trump     Leader of Korea / Kim]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ride my bike. There’s evidence- always. wahoofitnessofficial @cycliq @ Birmingham, Alabama https://t.co/Duv6HULlCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so sorry and sad about this. How can people be so mean and cruel?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsareNazis @bknight53 We want to see Trumps. Along with DNA analysis of his heritage.  His tax returns would be nice too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IliveinDanyland @Laucijay @Susannen @JKidd_Nie @Msidreamof @ElcoRaiderMom @shelby_Nickell2 @MicheleLynd… https://t.co/yvNopuRFMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[dude I just posted something on my regular ig which was meant to be on my finsta 😭😭😭 fuckkkkkkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll always need my son no matter what age I am. My son has made me laugh..made me proud..made me cry..hugged me ti… https://t.co/QQaSfWrvxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 IDA  Austin Conference: Navigating Dyslexia. Keynote Speaker David A. Kilpatrick, PHD. and great breakout sess… https://t.co/t9URVS2cO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claro que si. Senti igual que si abrazara a mi hijo. Si ellos sintieron esa emocion con solo unos dias separados, i… https://t.co/FHZTj3WI9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_eitniear @BrookeEitniear 🤔🤔🤔I may resemble that yes!!! https://t.co/3sqVbIXlpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally get yelled at because I can’t walk down the stairs in the dark and it disturbs the tv watchers like calm the fuck down]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people make life so much easier. 🌻 #appalachia #mountainlife #relativelyeasy #canimovedownhereplease @ Downto… https://t.co/PzhncHYelq]]></document></documents></author>