<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cdotharrison @SportsFandom22 @RealMNchiefsfan @RonnieHSHOW @BKSportsTalk Is there a particular season you prefer? Benson, not Watkins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/i1wG9lKWuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S👏BACK👏IT'S👏BACK👏 IT'S👏BACK👏  Transatlantic APA returns after a brief-ish hiatus and brings with it that big, ju… https://t.co/QmR99SAqic]]></document><document><![CDATA[APPLE MARTINI #HappyHour #AppleMartini #IMakeDrinks @ Downtown Oakland, Oakland, California https://t.co/Ti8ydQiCPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@generalzuo I don't think anyone is saying it's a perfect system, it's a process that's changed and will continue t… https://t.co/uxkcEUmztc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you got an indoor soccer game at 8 but it’s ladies free before 10.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panarin pooped his pants. That’s a hard one to come back from...sometimes the turtle head reallly wants out I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro i just bought these shoes n they said it’s gone take 3 to 4 weeks 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonMutala @TrekFanLV @mooreonzach I don’t hate any Terminator movie.  I did not like the twist of GENISYS that… https://t.co/2ZrbiACnVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAROLINA MEJÍA UNA MUJER CON VISIÓN DE FUTURO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/BcnpZF0Ucz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah just realized The Mountain killed Oberyn's sister and her children, so the team chemistry will be a disaste… https://t.co/2XjMi4FJuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone in my building has a white Rolls Royce truck on aftermarket wheels... Shit is dumb clean i need one in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialceenote RETWEET❗️RETWEET❗️RETWEET  🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨 https://t.co/fXuFuS4NzD 🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next on the race schedule, unless I decide to run one between now and then. @reds @ Monfort Heights South, Ohio https://t.co/PZemfN0juy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldboxATL @ATLairport I can’t make out the airline? Looks like cargo though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Two years ago we expected that GOP members such as yourself would uphold your oath of office to protect… https://t.co/BYXjx9k6rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEMIvik Taking my youngest son to an escape house. Not sure what that means for me! 😂😳☕️☕️♥️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodieSimmons24 @noahcummingsoru And sure elite defender. But he’s missing that one HUGE asset to be dominant and t… https://t.co/008WauYbGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @realDonaldTrump Not at all. It makes Pelosi and her crew look like a bunch of desperate sore losers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks Let’s contemplate the devotion some young conservative men show this miscreant old lawless overgrown… https://t.co/QTRWGxiZg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harry_Moir he’s an unnecessary distraction that changes very little I hope he’s good for us but I also hope he’s n… https://t.co/CYqcJNmWEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internacional ??? vergas lo mas internacional que conocen es a su jugador 🇫🇷😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity You know what you pick a fight now fight back with what you know and stop playing pla… https://t.co/7BD3psJ333]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJPGunter @ECUPiratesFB Check out this video! https://t.co/2a5JNNokhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some pretty cool things happening in the next couple weeks.  This may be the coolest.  I was invited to tour this p… https://t.co/Vo0tOZaZ1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constantly contemplating what i'm willing to give up in life to achieve my goals, because the reality of sacrificin… https://t.co/l1tYNdVpr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy @Reddsaidit album today! He’s the real deal as a person &amp; entertainer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarissaLingen @alexandraerin Aye I imagine. Scary people with shops and houses and ..*checks notes* foreign games like soccer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josesal40288623 @PatricioMasmelo @HassNassar @PalomaValenciaL @RTVCco @rcnradio Señor, Hassam es el que necesitamo… https://t.co/LQIIvP0mD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@House_Feminist My grandma used to say she better get to bed or she’ll turn into a pumpkin. She was born in 1928 so… https://t.co/qUNHqzFblf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a couple boys basketball players at #CampCFalls https://t.co/sanRfVMytu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomGerend When Capital Transit ended streetcar service in 1962 until the begin of rail operations by @wmata in 197… https://t.co/kWu8PueEtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jalen Harris! The point guard scoops it in to give Arkansas a 74-73 lead with 5.9 seconds left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did we all just go along with “Little Drummer Boy” when it said “Pa rum pum pum pum”? That is definitely not how a drum sounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being in bed early. Even though this isn’t really early and it’s my normal bed time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's going to coachella weekend 1 this year? 😎🔥🌴☀️   -------  #coachella  #coachellaoutfit #coachella2019… https://t.co/gyhqQlNJHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Figured it’d be easier to make a new Facebook than going through the hassle of purging every thing and removing people one by one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hollywood. Sunny but cold. #california #losangeles #winter @ Hollywood Walk of Fame https://t.co/1PmpkHb6KZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos estoy viviendo un Deja Vu muy cabrón en estos momentos 😱😱😱 hasta este tweet es un Deja Vu.  OMG ¿les ha pasado?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthAmin red eye back to Miami?! Weren’t you just there? I’m not complaining, love having you on the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survival &amp; Recovery Kit for Endurance Athletes Giveaway - $7k in prizes* - Are YOU ready for your next race?… https://t.co/Ig2is86Mj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious Q: I just learned you can rent a monkey for a party. What’s something unusual that you’d like to rent if you could?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albion City Vehicle @mikayxox former St. John Church, Albion MI 1412 hours... @ Albion College https://t.co/dlOBpivJxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[BACK IN THE DAY IF YOU WANTED SOME BEEF WITH A NIGGA THEN YOU COULD GO MEET WITH THE NIGGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always wanted to meet @alroker and on another morning walk in NYC, I had the opportunity of an impromptu handshake!… https://t.co/VXXMs8KWJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoover_dam @gabpdx I felt a disturbance in the force.  https://t.co/oM2BBDC9AV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston's 17-game point streak is now tied for the 3rd longest run in franchise history: 23 games in 1940-41, 18 gam… https://t.co/ihW9v2AeUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @msdolann to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews, just the co… https://t.co/OAjbWQofqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[J. Eduardo Grajales Ma... crossed 2.5km. Time 00:16:43, pace 06:42 min/km, est. finish 8:57 am https://t.co/MchLx9zgJc #RNRMERIDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the 90s every kid was obsessed with #Slime but why? what did #Slime even do? what was the point https://t.co/1WXfjTttwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@queenelizabeth⁩ My ongoing convo with one of yours dear, he says he’s Canadian, or some sort, haven’t discerned w… https://t.co/3oykLZH67c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sues3jewels @krazy4ujc @Hetz20 @KSchottPhD @yeshua_porvida @CaptainJeff7 @IIIDeaton @BlessedLiibaan https://t.co/dmGRD7rifM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_2moov3 @Sethymoe Lol well if your team commits a Flagrant 2 the first matchup by punching a player in the stomac… https://t.co/mQk6G9TLTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[wasn’t til I was sitting on this bus that I realized how fucked up it is that I can’t listen to music and charge my phone at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shewrick @ShatterverseEnt Not the artwork but the idea of Hammer in the role]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think you’re going to be late for work, the train runs express. #happy #friday #CTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLeman47 Philippians 1:6 and Philippians 2:13  God at work in you/me! Faith is what we do, grace is what God does! We need more grace!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAmberlyMarie @realDonaldTrump How do you know that for sure if you’re that smart why are you not on  the Presid… https://t.co/YMZGlonTBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Marketing Manager (Bauer, MBA) - (STA001590)" at University of Houston… https://t.co/xCmzmvGCCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity What about White Nationalist Supremacist @realDonaldTrump suppporter #ChristopherPaulHasson plotting t… https://t.co/p0x3KDR0Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaBraxtonWWE Or a really tiny economy car hidden between two monster trucks/SUVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jock176 @UTChargerTom @natureboyfan100 @libertyhillpd @BeaumontCA_PD @sbcountysheriff @sbsheriff Haha! I couldn’t afford it]]></document><document><![CDATA[After leaving the club last night, got some Apex in with @Prustijimi and Enzo. Ended up getting 3 wins in a row! Good times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @DobesGurl THIS IS WHAT LEADS THE DEMOCRATIC HOUSE...……….]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s been talk about Arizona moving on from QB Josh Rosen. I believe that would be a mistake, and that Rosen and… https://t.co/FxR72rQuv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a little time to practice myself… Maybe I’ll fix where I’m breathing LOL . . . . .  #voicelessons… https://t.co/8GJ5Pabisb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoy this flavor combination entirely too much.. Way better than I expected!@LiveOakBrewing   #SomeLikeitHot https://t.co/QtkMUAvYPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of curiosity, did SNL do anything on #JussieSmollet ?  It seems a natural for comedy, and they probably don't w… https://t.co/i54lKVUNnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan I will recuse myself. I've done similar pushing the envelope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we just going to forget that time short time when snoop dogg changed his name to snoop lion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me realizing that ELVIRA witnessed my LA stage debut, in four emojis: 😱🤯💀👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OR_CTR_NRS We know the Counties are large so we are making our per diem positions very flexible so our geriatric m… https://t.co/N0RIjk69km]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme Court appears inclined to let 40-foot ‘Peace Cross’ stand on public land  https://t.co/EBdIGbCfAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaiderrr I hope no one close to you ever suffers from any form of mental illness because their lives will be in da… https://t.co/CWHNJT6rzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air out the whole ugly mess so that no victimized children will be so easily ignored again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure @bonniemcfarlane or @RichVos can give props. Get this bitch on the radio. @BenningtonShow @JimNorton @notsam]]></document><document><![CDATA[AM Data (2 of 2): This dynamic underscores just how difficult it is for Beijing to demonstrate accelerating growth… https://t.co/JENXeRrSLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made the connection between “Stan” that I’ve been seeing all over Twitter and Eminem’s Stan. Cool except fo… https://t.co/DPEl5DifLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i saw an 11 AM showing of “i am love” at the sunshine cinema on houston street. i walked out of the theater in a da… https://t.co/UKRLCHITgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a quick reminder:  The Broncos traded away Aqib Talib and traded for Joe Flacco.  And y’all wonder why we got… https://t.co/zQKxhYiHNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Mr. Brownstone by @gunsnroses on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/ygJOXG0HXN https://t.co/n2q5QB1X6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump overruled security officials to demand Jared Kushner get top-secret clearance, report says… https://t.co/qeFPqreAV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grimbwoy i got game pass so i'm just playing the games i missed and apex legends. mostly halo and i'll probably get gears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahCville Had to back out due to injury but it’s an awesome race!  Long range forecast has us damp but warmer. No… https://t.co/jxYDHjlzmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News_8 The first smart thing that has been determined in a long time. #Finally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hragv I identify with both my names, so in American circles (where it's the majority), to make things simpler I us… https://t.co/absJwS6Hlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I was given $50 credit on the sg app, as well as an apology.   I do wish the company paid real money to tho… https://t.co/vpxMqFYtsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisoliveros13 Si no s x esos radikls,ni Guaido fuese Prsidnt(e) ni habria ayuda humanitaria.Mucha prsion c hizo s… https://t.co/K1lMDXnBwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for a buyer on 237 43rd Street Avalon, NJ 08202 #Avalon #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/I9oGZ5OjAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PublicTheaterNY Sparkles in the Parkles! Such a gorgeous summer that was!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rotobahn Paranoid shit heels like Snyder prioritize “loyalty” and willingness to be the public face that takes all… https://t.co/0Mc6PAzhDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best episodes of all time. That was non alcoholic champagne.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado The summer is so much better when the Phillies are good!  You have something to watch virtually every night. 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danthd3848 Thank you Austin for your commitment to excellence!!  We appreciate all that you do making your store and our company better!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaySueMe the new single is so good. Can't wait for the official release 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the former Sears store at the Cambridge Centre mall. I have an odd relationship with this (former) store. 1… https://t.co/suEKQnEsfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweakBoxApp wont let me download any games from your app says unable to download please retry later and have waited awhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Tan crossed 5K. Time 00:24:02, pace 07:44 min/mile, est. finish 8:41 am https://t.co/tg6K0pC897 #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[The walk of a true competitor. Gives me hope for kids still loving to play and not just chasing the pay check]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SternabR6 @CloudStrucKTV @AffectedR6 @FilthyR6S @goanysucks @Malakai___ Thanks SternGOAT]]></document></documents></author>