<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ryanlawrence21 @WOLF_Rescue @GetLouieHome Oh man....I have had a lost dog before, it’s so hard!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing the turn west, my gut is saying there is a good chance they are planning to shelter off the coast of C… https://t.co/4FDPA0SQaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think our Engineers should have a month long celebration not just a week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOSullivan36 @nosheepfollower @Bitey_Bolger @ThorntonNiwot @JSapp_AR @tomwatson @KamalaHarris @BetoORourke… https://t.co/TKEMkKXQFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apaplayer69 @Stephie_Lark I’m pretty sure there is at least 1, but I love almost all of them. 💃🏻💃🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There are many features of climate change—its size, its scope, its brutality—that, alone, satisfy this definition;… https://t.co/KUy37cPsh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreeseWorks I’m so glad!!! And of course! Thank you for asking! So many people were having a bit of trouble and I… https://t.co/XFHXZw0RXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fionasoul @marienassar_ Beautiful quote also,that I had forgot to mention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the DEM’s added funds in their bill for the census bureau to help that objective of gaining more congress… https://t.co/MMNAgiBzFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting for @OneRepublic to announce a NYC show and then they do but it’s the day of @FLAGALine 😶🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ask learners: If you have a problem, who is an adult you can tell? #NotInOurSchool https://t.co/iiUUo7z7rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doggo-endorsed #sneckdown at 68th and 12th in Roosevelt https://t.co/oSPiRqDOB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/GJfoGFHhJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idoit_cvoice72 Lol, I just love it! We’re always saying, if only other people could hear the things we talk about.… https://t.co/1CY7FSxiQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gente tem lido e falado tanto sobre masculinidade tóxica, mas mesmo assim vocês precisam compartilhar um “cadê o… https://t.co/pMGl8RkVFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ApraxiaReaLynn @newzgirl @LaraMoritzKMBC @SanglesonFrench Busy! How are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SideHustleWino @DivaVinophile @SteveKubota @MacrinaBakery @BainbridgeIsl @nofussgourmet @SashaEats @GrnLakeGirl… https://t.co/08XEjIoqnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valuing these friendships extra hard today @Daniel_Lung and jsmartnick ♥️ @ Duke's Murray Hill https://t.co/HK8PY1ZRmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikequasar You know who the decent agents  are. If girls cant get one of those shes better off self booking and ga… https://t.co/JSrYK1PFjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nayalla334nd Good Morning on this Thursday @Nayalla334nd Blessings 👠👠🌻🌻❄️☕️🕊🎼🌟🍀💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @jonasbrothers better announce a tour before this #LateLateJonas is over is all I’m saying... please and thank you. @latelateshow 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother acts like prince is her first kid she doesn’t even know how to take of him I never had a kid why am I sup… https://t.co/nBhvwIFbHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hooked: How So Many Vermonters Got Addicted to Opioids https://t.co/UTI5340vnS @bunkybun @KittyBhagat @renemjclarke… https://t.co/7AmA61MR4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[#silkpress #blowout #naturalhair #stylist #naturalhairstylist #blackhairmag #silkpressmaster #healthy_hair_journey… https://t.co/ssEOYHW84r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasillasJill Happy Birthday sweet girl!! Hope you had an amazing day ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N7IRL @kashthefuturist Apparently by poor he means "teenager with rich parents". And by rich he means "nonsensical "]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellenhagan @mobrowne @biancalynne @freedewi @BlkLibraryGirl @JackieWoodson @jamilawoods @KAMoonshine… https://t.co/UN0dsPapPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @AOC Has your account been taken over, perhaps by the "justice democrats"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaziaYashae Girl they tryna be lit my momma gonna say i can smell the brokenness through the phone 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dobsleypromise The people who being mean to Nina, need to back off.  She deserves respect and divinity, if you can… https://t.co/ArGv1EMimM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to McMaster Marauders Women's Basketball team who are now on their way to the Nationals!...Convinci… https://t.co/v2LHiPlNlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the rockets should stop fouling them then. I mean that’s what rockets fans always say right??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having more that one hashtag for General Conference should be unconstitutional. #gc2019 #umcgc #umcgc2019 #umcgc19 #LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavenElyseTV It’s called “YouTube Kids” !! Highly recommend so that there’s no way this will appear !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off @PHXStartupWeek this morning with frankness Are We All Crazy? Robert Maynard, Founder @SurchX, "Lead p… https://t.co/qglgBuuU6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[71 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/jNgki7OYsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling the love today thanks to my Valentine😍💘 @ Gulf Coast Beach. Gulfport, MS https://t.co/a4fdfDdJ9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynashleyx I don’t understand why you people don’t like to drive with me?  🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPlotnitskiy Thanks Jenn! I’m going to start asking my family for travel vouchers on  holidays so I can go to NY and visit TC! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey #epitwitter, what are some good conferences for influenza and infectious diseases?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vancouver Island's Jesse Roper lands song on American Idol https://t.co/0HJZTFKech]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve just come home from the Staples Center. This was such a gorgeous moment. Truly beautiful. #DirkNowitzki… https://t.co/A5Tq4ksDHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jazz get a big defensive stop and Kyle Korver with a huge dunk! (Speak it into existence)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigboss72633155 @Hollyh82663398 @BaichwalABC7 @ABC7Chicago I see you’re clearly a troll. He deserves a far more ha… https://t.co/YT8wgDYEBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to retweet and like so many tweets about the Jonas brothers, idc]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m the #midget between my two #lovelycarribean nieces #suzannemendoza and her sister Maryann, with my nephew… https://t.co/tKDkGdwgnq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thundrspirit @NateSilver538 He did it last time and then dropped out again after the election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #CoffeeCrew Lots of org today and jax book fest tomorrow. You? @DoctorJAuthor @dbmoone @msymtucker… https://t.co/I45dliYZ4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VelshiRuhle I call BS on Cohen asking #Thug45 for a pardon. People accused Cohen of flipping because he wanted a p… https://t.co/3TZnmwAzEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children and youth suffer great losses in times of natural disasters. Their emotional well being is important to pr… https://t.co/9sDqSZgrZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! One busy week down, now time for another. 💪  Last week I worked 40hrs at GW, 6hrs of grad school, nan… https://t.co/DToNb4uFyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carson: for those unable to contact family, go to the Lee County EMA website, there is a form for you to fill out.… https://t.co/ZfNkb84SKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A hand extended to us I will lead the way Just put your faith in me and don't reserve any judgement I will show you… https://t.co/02wEubo4eC]]></document><document><![CDATA[All we gotta say is the bandwagon will come around and pick y’all up eventually. 🤷‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamontagneKara Get ready for an #edventure #sau46bookchat is going to be a blast! https://t.co/HfpNm3MjLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first of my insomnia-induced tweets: Who else wants to hear a Dolly Parton/Lady Gaga duet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really crazy to me to think that most parents room share for the first 6 months.. which lincoln is now 6 month… https://t.co/dqTmleUfBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjczunie my mom made me some comfort food! 😊🤗❤️ https://t.co/KFse3NwhLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElRigel_ @SonorasinPRI @SaraDessens @SantiagoLunaG @Yadiracotalugo @tibosanchez @1Agustn @mikeleyva75… https://t.co/RL9NqFPPVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser Your shameless individual all you care about is white people you have enriching yourself over the you cared… https://t.co/Cxee0hluaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder He's weak and owned by Putin.  No Trumpsters Russia is not our "friend" as so many have told me smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the snow wanted to stop so I could work on my tan again that would be great☀️ https://t.co/d3BoqQPICE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stolen last night Kingwood TX area plate number 267880K Please call Montgomery County Texas Sheriffs department if… https://t.co/nq8ex7V8AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #IWD2109, what’s more fitting than highlighting getting more female/minority students in the pipeline of basebal… https://t.co/xEM8tFeBk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I look younger than I am but at the same time, mid 30s doesn't usually look "old" on most people...at least, I don't think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to come with a complete show presented all boxed up with a bow. Someone attached to the shoe and with a pr… https://t.co/zPtjIGLhUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrixieTricking @InspiringU2 Great joke!! As someone that has battled PTSD due sexual violence and narcassitic abus… https://t.co/6g59LBQrJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shouldn't be thinking about this rn bc I'm p sure someone is walking back and forth outside my door but hey jokes… https://t.co/Hxcu2vK2r9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are still waiting for Sheriff Jones. The press conference was scheduled to begin at 5 a.m.   Recovery teams are… https://t.co/DoJneFwRzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babyhttps://www.pscp.tv/w/b0uTtTFtTUVQT0pWUGRlakd8MU9kSnJSV2tQellKWGZSapyeTy-6F6o7pSboXIE_jD_x6QULaMx2fjautiln?t=1m52s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing Well, I've blocked another troll. No wonder I have so many blocked trolls. The suckers are everywhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my first time here at Mackey. Couldn't be more excited. #Purdue #BoilerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catie_burnette HA! Totally missed this anyways so, I’m seeing both tweets at the same time 🤣 SO interested in this. Let’s do it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TotalWireless wants to send Me to the @iHeartRadio Music Awards! Enter daily for your chance to #win!… https://t.co/cIHd9ASMwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Run don’t walk to get your tickets to our annual Mardi Gras Gala only 6 days left until the big event. There will b… https://t.co/y0nGeWzHuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNITEDA1RLINES flight from Ft Myers to Chicago 80% of the seats in the middle are open, and “Group 5” is completel… https://t.co/XOQ9EtjWrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 um... 👋 quick question. If a guy "loves his family" one would think one would not be sleeping with… https://t.co/L9nfNZkbbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want some T-Pain with no auto-tune. IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK FOR!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javy23baez BABY &amp; WIFE R BOTH 2 CUTE 4 WORDS!! BE A GOOD FATHER/HUSBAND!! HA HA 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukelukeluke121 @toto99com Hiro were they asking about DavidP in the beginning of you clip? ❤🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently there is a doggy stomach bug going around. Unfortunately, Ollie got it and he wasn’t the only dog at the… https://t.co/QOt1EAfrON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynda3035 @sandyincanada @BloomNight2 @vroberts9 @PeachesPomPom1 @cobalttash @Axolotl_2019 @2kewlabs… https://t.co/z3PMKe10jf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshturnermusic Thank you for retweeting him singing!! He’s so excited! He loves this song and said he just wants to go viral 😁🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY_StudioSchool. Here's a pixel drawing of a Casade Badge (Pokemon) I've made by using colored pencils!… https://t.co/P3lJzf5Tz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[10pm to 6am Tonight on https://t.co/IKsW0B65JU, And Saturday 8-10am #aTributeToSkyLab2000 #unclenoah #pinartoprak… https://t.co/ZpOH99R4hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do know 40% + Americans divorce yearly right ? Also,most people can’t afford college which could help them get… https://t.co/n0gaVAKw9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna miss sleeping next to my boo tonight cause of work ): https://t.co/wwKHQB7Uwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like waking up out of dead sleep at 4am to a stressed induced cold sweat soaked tshirt... real sexy. 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@probableroller @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @Beylotte No we have not. You are fired though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*on ft with Karenna*  Me: why did you take them  Karenna: bc I didn’t have any earphones with the LEASH on it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have ever worked as higher-up at a manufacturing company that produces products that have the label “batteri… https://t.co/zlaYbOoWBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[vegan essen gehen mit @ruehrspiegelei @Kmpkthtsstz und @BananaGun1337 ist alles was ich nächste Woche brauchen werde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broke down and ran on a treadmill because of all the rain. Luckily I have @classpass so I could quickly book… https://t.co/9NvEa45BRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarilynLouise5 they are beautiful creatures who are also known for scavenging.  I think it funny and maybe appropr… https://t.co/uIRKvf4O9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[These would be the landmarks that would tell me to go back home. @UberFacts]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have an Hispanic/Latinx resident population living in Lawrence Kansas whose voices matter. Come out and be heard… https://t.co/cMHX4GtMih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the #jamminshow last night colonelandthemermaids https://t.co/jx2FUE0Xm1 ! #grateful for the #newmusic ✨… https://t.co/4AsJ7lDwBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work up out of a bad dream about an hr ago &amp; now I can’t sleep. I’m so mf sleepy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved doing this interview with @rainbennett of @storylabpodcast. There is a lot of actionable content about storyt… https://t.co/AmBts4r4gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoVohn_Morrow7 I gotchu, I just don’t have free time w basketball season :(]]></document></documents></author>