<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[New York: No Charges For Man Who Stabbed Unborn Baby To Death https://t.co/QkuVW4BVd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The camera at my bar picked up an irregular motion when I was closing the other night. This is me delivering a very… https://t.co/JJv9q3nRFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punkindrublik68 @HectorMariscal7 @ljreilly754 Hector DM me asking to be nice.Said he didn’t get his favorite donut… https://t.co/MKO5U7DJAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna miss ya Big Homie!!!  Thank you for everything in Baltimore!!!  I see you're going home tho!!!… https://t.co/Eczr69s7Pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedFlash on 13-3 run to start the second half. Lead 43-27 over LIU Brooklyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #txlege office is only as good as the staff supporting the elected representative. Very dedicated men and women i… https://t.co/fuAErTLugy]]></document><document><![CDATA[AW YISS all commuter rail infill stations are excellent but a Sunnyside LIRR station would be most excellent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump According to NM that's replacement fencing authorized in 2017. 'LIAR-IN-CHIEF']]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for a fill up? ☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️☕️♥️ Good morning everyone! Have a great Saturday. ☺️ https://t.co/VvDkNB1Rym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimmie will never admit it, but his success in #NASCAR is over. He just doesn’t have it anymore. He can say whateve… https://t.co/A2tBr5hREz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illustrations by Nicola Formichetti, exclusively for Google Store. @ Empire State Building https://t.co/fvhoaSutpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/Gc9V0ljZeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bamzis69 ur missing my point completely, what im saying is that it can come off as obnoxious when someone gives us… https://t.co/Q7h3wQxx6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not see how Democrats can win an elections. Writing bills to protect sex offenders who attract child, to kill… https://t.co/zBaupjQ4L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay cosas que jamás podré entender de algunos seres humanos. Estamos a años luz de ser una raza civilizada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Physicians, #teachers, public safety professionals, and people in other high-stress jobs, have hotlines to call to… https://t.co/P77bF2gscp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaivanShroff Never had a middle school dance or a middle school for that matter. Grades 1 through 6 in one buildin… https://t.co/mHQeLsxzQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, the guys swing has really slowed down. It’s hard to see guys age like this. Nothing left in the tank to give… https://t.co/hHGu8BLirI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all swear y’all the baddest bitches and best girlfriends but be dead ass single]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnahita @millanpatterson Again, you made it the issue, not me. Your assumptions about the coincidence of their… https://t.co/BfbjJnGRfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyHoverman @MitchellSmilie @jeremyminton9 @NealMcCready @AUGoldMine It’s America in 2019.  *Everything* is inflammatory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earlflynn @TalbertSwan Lying doesn’t have a race unless you misunderstand lying. Looks like I’m full cirlcle back… https://t.co/KNfVdpYB4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a honor to be able to share my birthday with this man who is also one of my idols! RIP @ Fountain Run, Kentuc… https://t.co/hAejVzJbPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you see this buzzer-beater from Thursday night? @FEAS_Panthers @upnorthlive @LourinOnTV @CumlerHannah]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are times where I sit and wait for a text, and then there are moments when I clean a mother fucking bathroom… https://t.co/HmdQL0B7rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CliffordAsness Yeah, that's *just* what we're going to do... https://t.co/KdW03GVEzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb not as warm as 2017, 2018. Feb19 was above avg and 3rd warmest on my records. Avg for Feb is, high 65.7°, low 4… https://t.co/gcjFSQDDuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I list this under one of the curses of being tall:  Impossible to “blend in.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holt’s Esther Han (28-0) defeats Lebanon’s Antionna Cunningham by a 19-4 technical fall.  Big congrats to Han.  Thi… https://t.co/iwWvBnpfbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @OldDominion show and the pre-concert music in the arena is @brothersosborne ... not sure if coincidence or trolling haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porsche Power! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides! @porsche @IMSA @disupdates - - - -… https://t.co/YJep85kuZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@platanitoshow platanito. Cómo se llama la banda que toca en tu programa. Felicidades]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigJDubz @Melchievous We kindly axe you out of the building mr chemicals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterBarendreg2 @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @MariaBartiromo @JudicialWatch @FoxNews It's awesome. You even tweet w… https://t.co/D1L9PmEXrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaneCook See you in Hackensack looking forward to it. You don’t disappoint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debelbot @codehitchhiker Your tweet would only make sense in a magical world where everything was already even and… https://t.co/iSR3tErIIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing when the love of your life ruined your bachelor party whiles she’s at a sex party getting drunk spending your money]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ReDespiertos  Hoy salió Asado con amigos y familia..., saludos desde Orange, CA. 👋👋😋😋 https://t.co/LXkPtfnPTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeSalk If he keeps up his temper tantrum, he will get released and the Mariners will just swallow the cost.… https://t.co/vavdwTlpnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a little of my #awardwinning #wines w #friends on this #Friday evening after a great week of #filming… https://t.co/F3Yfh41s4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[somehow all of my clothes are faintly covered in fine gold glitter and I don’t really mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makin’ it do What it do! #itsyaboi #djoj #PME #phatmusic #Serato #pioneer #Detroit #goodvibes @ The Library at the… https://t.co/358CnT2noM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichalskiAlpha @vanitystreaming @Xbox @MissAliCatt @MexyHandGrenade @SGH_RTs @RSG_Retweet It's aight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riverwilliams6 I feel like it’ll be the same one, he seems like a straightforward kinda guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulioDrones @RonnyTorresSS Nope 🤦🏾‍♂️ and my dad💪🏾went there 💯I was born Nole🍢blooded💉]]></document><document><![CDATA[فلمن أبوح بصبوتي ياقاتلي ياخيبة الشاكي إذا فقد الوفا و يزيد وجدي بهواك تلهفا فمتى وعدتني ولا رأيتني مخلصا أيحل في ش… https://t.co/okG5mwaSRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything a good bowl of stew and a pint of Guinness can’t solve?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @EASPORTSFIFA the @MLS season begins today. Why don’t you update the kits as appropriate? I understand YOUR rel… https://t.co/5wNiQqGbp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In some need of some acoustic guitar melodies for some new beats. Sending out for placement. 👏💪💯  Email them to the… https://t.co/XzVNfba2Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jubilee. I don’t contribute much in a group setting nor have a ton of useful qualities but I’m always there if/when someone needs me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgrego_21 Happy birthday bro! Gonna miss baseball with all the homies😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews Wouldn't trust a thing this clown has to say. Wait, not a clown, sorry clowns. #CohenTestimony he's a RAT!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[when someone going 35 in a 35 and have no intentions of letting me pass the@ https://t.co/W00VccyYP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winning : Federal Judge Hands President Trump &amp; Americans A Huge Win https://t.co/eddcBgnZN3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realJediMan1 @RubyRockstar333 @RepJerryNadler The majority of the Democrats are running scared , therefore they’re… https://t.co/T0tAMmhZsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FdeBoerofficial No reason we should be in this position. I blame you Frank. Learn to manage these games. We are no… https://t.co/5mMw0YBjPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpFrederick @ActualEPAFacts Hey dumb ass, Can you name a nation on the planet with no taxes, that the free mark… https://t.co/FugSRFjXjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Siberian Black Magic Panther (Rum Barrel-Aged) by @westbrookbeer at @thesaltedpig — https://t.co/KuCibYKKz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA’LL READY OR WHAT?!?! My next new single “COLD” drops at MIDNIGHT!!! KEEP A LOOKOUT ON SOUNDCLOUD LINK WILL BE IN… https://t.co/Hxdm4VtpA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMizwicki If we could do something weekly it would be awesome!!  I truly think you are genius when it come to teaching hockey!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalmartCanada very dissatisfied as a customer to know your are charging me full price on clearance items at Walmar… https://t.co/Ng2QmOjd9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @chrislhayes Drunk you said to be if words were said and words were said and now drink happened where’s my phone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @hannahjefcoat_ and Kim on an outstanding #SECITF19 and Indoor season 👏👏👏 #PoleVault]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Economic cooperation and competition is infinitely more peaceful than war and threats of war. Open up pea… https://t.co/d5MDydtgXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinaEllithorpe I’m calling on Mike Pence to withdraw his head from Donald’s ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKidCriley Tacos and escitalopram go together like peas and carrots brother JL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @IvanDuque @Almagro_OEA2015 Hoy murieron varios venezolanos de manera injusta y terrible. Las condolencias… https://t.co/g8sDzlCCln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please. Allow us some time. 😂😳☕️♥️😍 Good morning Twitterville! Have a wonderful Thursday. https://t.co/dWcaHtns2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#waterfront#oceanfront#beachfront#obx#outerbanks#obxlocals#realestate#beach#bulldog#bulldogsofinstagram#pitbulls#pi… https://t.co/EqpTKXcrSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[CUBAN CIGARS were always available to the "priviledged" - not to  "normal'  Americans.  Working at the home of Edga… https://t.co/4Q5rc9Uo5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Clausthaler Original / Premium by Radeberger Gruppe at @winkinglizard — https://t.co/LvFsoZdilq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock N Roll Ain’t Noise Pollution.  📸: @zakkiblakk #BeSuspicious #ElectricElvis @ Grant Central Station https://t.co/lrMMXkFa6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribranchvo it’s called evening shadow! I took your suggestion and used the office color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone who loves college baseball it’s an absolute blast to live in a state where @ClemsonBaseball and… https://t.co/RGo5mumRnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielgansle @TODAYshow @NBCNews @SavannahGuthrie @realDonaldTrump Don’t be an idiot in public. 🤦🏻‍♂️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @Rbigzs @sappermartin @QmagaMike @JulieReichwein1 @CuriousHobbyist @sianetta @heyitsCarolyn @janasea21… https://t.co/VqLvqadIMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HipHopDX He was never in a gang, he will never be in a gang, and he will be dropping his next album “life after hard time” in April.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m gonna do something productive today and not take a nap  My brain: https://t.co/a7DiEAlTPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[There it is...#seeitbelieveitachieveit @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/XnTUuZzLnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST A LITTLE MORE TIME LEFT to register for the @BGCOPreachConf. Registration closes tomorrow at midnight. Go to… https://t.co/QpwZkKcyQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, trying to schedule hangout times with friends at GDC while navigating my work schedule that week https://t.co/Y0Cxl0FHde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait a second... you’ve got a point @RandomMnky ... wasn’t #captainamerica the first avenger? In the 1940s along wi… https://t.co/pwUeLX0pjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arnakploverson Dawg if she’s ready to go a fourth round with you she’s gotta like what you’re bringing to the table big fella]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealredman We need to change the game! We have been on the Defense long enough. It's to go on the offense! Who… https://t.co/sUQ2S5qpFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUNIORS This is a reminder to complete your registration for the ACT by Wednesday, March 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCoachRentz @rocco_barletta That’s cool!  @Jennifer_Manly has all the resources you need for that. I have thought… https://t.co/WXS6C99ydX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 Putin must be what they are both looking and smiling at...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahthepope666 @pfeifer_sandra @woody2237 @KamalaHarris Sounds fair. And I’ll stop paying for welfare and insuran… https://t.co/xxGduVKlLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Why its domestic influence via you and your clonies, that is the real threat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intelligent50 @johnfel202 @Ltdsoltd @Birdseye1 @SSG_Davis_Ret @TresaBridges @CarolGarofolo @Whichsideareuon… https://t.co/3Bz0vcJ8Cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach calls your number you gotta leave the field.. that was a disgrace.. he couldn’t play again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kodeinekowboi Yeah that song was about his other friend that died in 2017]]></document><document><![CDATA[BCLUW leads GMG 29-19 after 1Q, but Comets are down Mason Yantis to an ankle sprain and Jack Garber to 3 fouls alre… https://t.co/JdzxtqjsiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was the highest honor of my career working with this team on #GodofWar. Proud to have made cool stuff with these… https://t.co/giJmIUzxOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey God.. God.. if you’re there, please tell me what to do or what choices I have to make to make things better..… https://t.co/sKEIzWli0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly why he left. Classless pieces of shit. After all he did for that garbage organization smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eso de que en el nuevo Código Civil si hay un divorcio por adulterio la pareja tiene que esperar 5 años para casars… https://t.co/fnmTM2N4JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionelMedia @mikey1701 She’s just another liberal that believed him The whole shows liberals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that noise! #koh2019 #schultzrclab @ King of The Hammers https://t.co/9z9fuf1aqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie I lowkey feel bad for Jordyn woods like Tristan is lowkey gonna get away with it and her life will ne… https://t.co/hUs6NIKyXn]]></document></documents></author>