<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CNN The mother who left the baby with an 11 year old should be charged too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to answer questions over DM, but please read the job description first; many questions are probably already answered there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffy1939 @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump And what parents are killing HEALTHY babies on a whim? Where do you go to get… https://t.co/9PAPAz5UgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Happy. Enjoy life. Smile! You can’t always control the things happening around you, but you can 💯 control  how y… https://t.co/mZ8OvLOuev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigHenra @brielyyn @niccochuidian hey don’t call brie trash you’re trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been sorta maybe thinkin you could be the one ☁️ https://t.co/hl1TMMHZ1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Female Pilots Broke Down Barriers in Aviation https://t.co/D06oSjps6F via @NatGeoTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you like the wall color in your bedroom to be dark like this or would you rather have something lighter? @ San A… https://t.co/17jthGwSOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m staying at a hotel in Minneapolis, Minnesota and the cleaning lady threw away my unused makeup wipe I left on t… https://t.co/rMCqcxgJJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Seuss Week, long celebration with our wonderful librarian Ms. Aguerro!#ReadersAreLeaders @moseley_school… https://t.co/kfIRkVBIgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can we do to raise Achievement?  Challenge, stimulate &amp; engage our kids. #championsofliteracy #SAISD… https://t.co/JuXsfvCm4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2019ATOY Check out Tweetdeck on your laptop. You can follow the hashtags and it eliminates the scavenger hunt of f… https://t.co/xo0fcKCv9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come over and follow me on Instagram https://t.co/s4Z09Me1Ur https://t.co/IQ08C6hWq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Urgent care.... third time in two months sucks again!! I’m over this shit! #sick #overit #allergies #pollen #florida #sarasota #boogers]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s easy for people to reassure you when things are good and make you feel better when you’re sad. It’s what they… https://t.co/z7LhnamnFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[when guys take advantage of your kidness and empathy, and use both of them to manipulate tf outta you but claim it… https://t.co/tOQMquAaVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you know what’s SUPER COOL? Being 24 and unable to open jars or containers because you have psoriatic arthritis… https://t.co/fcng3LivAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are scared because they won’t have a human manager to go to when their expired coupons don’t work at a store… https://t.co/cmB4eMzg5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human right for one, human rights for all; no matter how ethically devoid they are: #FREEJORGERAMOS #FREEJORGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbq_ If you've already been nominated five times or more without winning, you automatically get an Oscar. Next yea… https://t.co/UeiCzTfX0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another successful Family Lunch and Learn this week @WatsonLane069! @MorrisonsClass @WleRussell https://t.co/GlPP3kgMpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor Kenney’s Budget Proposes Historic Investments in Streets https://t.co/54BSAdYZqv #PHLBudget]]></document><document><![CDATA[So easy to drink. And delicious - Drinking a Purple OG by Froth Brewing @ Tiki Bar  — https://t.co/hVrethd82T]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ The only reason I live in Texas is for the honey butter chicken biscuits  “ -@JosueVasquezzz @Whataburger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Please declare a national emergency.  Nothing left to say but Dims are a JOKE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brunabosz kkadjfkgkjf eu entao? nossa me acho “entao fulana vc sabia que eu tenho uma amiga que é PROFISSIONAL em editar fotinha???”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on my neck pain: Just got done at the primary care doctor.  She thinks my neck pain is really bad spasms. Sh… https://t.co/qSpThrx0ic]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can be so lowkey with someone and people still have the nerve to try and be in your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJaysonJones @KellKelley2 @q_crews @AlabamaFTBL ROLL TIDE ROLL!!!!!   🅰️🐘🅰️🐘🅰️🐘🅰️🐘🅰️🐘🅰️💥💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvgraz @HillaryClinton She IS a neolib. WallSt loves her. DNC's golden queen. Bernie will not take her threats lig… https://t.co/m4B8PFYPFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margssister @acoyne She’s a political newbie. Missed a few classes on how politics is done and how cabinet works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[pessoas comemorando a morte de um menino de 7 anos, e outros tentando justificar, essas pessoas estão mortas, só não sabem disto ainda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Heritage has (since at least 1999) worked to eliminate #VAWA. Heritage Action for America considers a "no" on VAW… https://t.co/MwXCrI2MHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tallicamike @goiowa We will be there too!!!  We would not miss it for the world!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendship Day complete with giant slide and costumes #friendshipday #algierspoint @ Old Point Bar https://t.co/7qGsDLomDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addiemoreno @ghdezf21 @javierdecanini @Vickyasp @Piedrulces Pero la mayoría de las personas no tienen acceso a est… https://t.co/3C1dUsFtgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Have you ever heard if you choose the behavior you have chosen the consequences?? Live with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCUBasketball thank you student athletes and coach Dixon for an exciting, fun home game season. I am proud of everyone of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t stop laughing bc of how absolutely horrifying this would be lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMalachai__ @unlikeganamede @mellokittyhello @Titties4Sale @5BlindSense @emg_99 @averellgibby @lilnofriends righ… https://t.co/Lsf5RAb06W]]></document><document><![CDATA[It definitely wasn’t 75 &amp; sunny but these gals knew how to lighten up the mood ☀️ @ South Padre Island, Texas https://t.co/Xl8MyF1GRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RustyNa56941001 @MaximeBernier Could be ... I've seen some strange thing the last few days ... some of my tweets j… https://t.co/GurtsPaVUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICYMI coliseum talk is happening again as a need for major tax growth starts to hit the scene b/c the Mayor report… https://t.co/6tWsxGQYfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoot, one of my kids will be born at an airport, the other at a bank 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIPLuke Perry! #BeverlyHills90210 #Riverdale #RIPLukePerry #GoneTooSoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is adorable but if it was one of my jerks that wine would be on the floor]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “influencers” are out and about in Beacon Hill today....#Getthatcontent #doitforthegram]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RepSwalwell to be a champion to prevent gun violence and support #HR8!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh #SarahSanders, your eyes are browner every day. All that swamp stuff is leaking out. You are not there for we th… https://t.co/qtl8aQ2Km2]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTH... I love when my 18 yr old comes home on break from Uni.....Until I lose all rights to my bathroom:( Girl i love you...GET OUT!!!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My damm neighbor thinks its okay to have his loud ass music at 1:33 am go to fucking sleep 😒 i have to get my ass u… https://t.co/g8rwSxbtY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbchamberlain A5: #BikeSchool My hand knit mittens. I wear cheap dollar store finger gloves with my mittens over… https://t.co/FIM3Gj4R77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Gatto saw you were starting #TrafficCam when I was school, got super excited and started singing the song. May… https://t.co/k8MXdYrMYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that it's over I'm just sitting on my couch like... https://t.co/zGGi0JNBG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Displaced Rohingyas would be a big drain on the Indian economy. The popular notion that the West is the favourite d… https://t.co/OevMbC3XHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[*he’s not good for you, he’s not good for you, he’s not good for you, he’s not good for you, he’s not good for you, he’s not good for you*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer Thanks Charlotte. I'm getting close to 60 and I think I'm better now than I've ever been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcpr The arrogance of anyone signing their own name to a Bible stuns me. Shows both a lack of respect (I'm a b… https://t.co/DA2p7NH0fE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like Marisa Tomei in My Cousin Vinny 🐾 dress from #fashionnova https://t.co/HF11c0hhFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kacey Musgraves was really like I’m going to make a country disco track and idgaf. Iconic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Zechariah Cartledge such an articulate young man with a big heart! Great story. 💙 https://t.co/WNRGR5QdtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are among the smallest of the smug and self serving— cast the first stone Jim for your day will come. What you… https://t.co/tHcGwX5VaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post red eye nap. 😴 #catsofinstagram #ohthathenri #sexybadasskitty #dogsofinstagram #echodogadaline @ West Village https://t.co/Pb8QBfixB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to know, I haven’t had coffee in over 3 weeks.. I don’t know why I just decided to stop. But I’m doing okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mktgsifu @KMart2180 @BernieSanders Meaning you won’t vote at all?  Who is this hurting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Oh How I Love Jesus (Reprise) by Rev. James Moore on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/2RwqYVG9Oh https://t.co/hJ0uGL2k1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athletic trainers don’t do it for money (lord knows we don’t make any) We do it for this right here.  #NATAM2019… https://t.co/stmgDVn2OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl power soundtrack for the drive today: @JanelleMonae @halsey @thatgirlbishop @lorde]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, who casted her in The Lottery? I believe that’s Eisner, Michael for the win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[En qué chucha están??? 🤪 Quién se pone a remover nieve a las 2 de la mañana? 😴  ¡En frente de mi ventana! 😓 https://t.co/yCFmG5KaoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew @landryshamet was better than Malik Newman when he game Mo Williams elite 30 in high school]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm tired of meeting guys that are only into sports like can I meet someone that's an artist, writer, photographer ANYTHING else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[honorable mention to the things i’ve had to holler at dudes for various reasons in public places because attracting… https://t.co/gM2xtTNJZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[:: Happy Birthday to one of my favorite people!! @jacqbrush Hope you have a Swervin' Irvan kind of day!! 🏁🏁😉😉 :: https://t.co/q53Yw8dmaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because it says “nontoxic” doesnt mean you can put it on your pet. Just bc something isn’t toxic to humans doe… https://t.co/vT4mXS1kCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dega_boy_87 @LibertyUAlum @Jbriggsy_14 @DannyLeBlanc24 @4judyblue @rottzillasgirl @ToddShe72716015 @CMANGO… https://t.co/lpUjosnrmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to be tan again and walk around in shorts and flip flops ☀️ @ Fort Collins, Colorado https://t.co/chiTuI1XuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited my best friend is having another baby!!! 😬😬😬😬😬😬 can’t wait to love on him just like we do Lays! (Yes I t… https://t.co/JWwnb2fYme]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have a good job , the greatest mom &amp; the sweetest man in my life i don’t think it gets much better 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamisyn is so pumped for her sisters big game tonight...she can’t contain her excitement 😂 @traci_stinson https://t.co/fdUdCWjXFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegalMovies Why are my Captain Marvel tickets not showing up in the My Tickets section of the app? I bought them in January.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVERS of SENIOR DOGS: SOUR PATCH, 8, is actually all SWEETNESS(except w/🐯💕)! But she is AT RISK, #nycacc! GOOD w/k… https://t.co/0tfX6w5Qk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[youth ministry room ideas | You have heard of the game Hungry Hungry Hippos – Right?... https://t.co/XBoHYQT9dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicollyStephane @Mikeyevoo @pedrocass__ Don’t worry Nicolly we will make it through the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechrisbarron @Grr_George The best!! Here is my furbaby. She's no longer with us but we think about her everyday. https://t.co/am3Bp3MiRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music alert 🚨🎶🔥 Single Climb That Pole out now available on all platforms. #iTunes, #applemusic #spotify… https://t.co/QZp9T7TKxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I, Vicki Anne, pledge to take a damn vacation in 2019” #BeachBreakSweepstakes Please take me away. @LandSharkLager https://t.co/BQg36JxlxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Luna-bug! Five years have just flown by! &lt;3 @ Norman, Oklahoma https://t.co/nlcQxNLosS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me - caring for my Mom. Thank you for this. It is a rough road, with some tears, but many joys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonSawatsky @JamesIntrocaso @mercyfuldm @wildrosemage ‘Time warp’  A invisible pocket of time distortion appears,… https://t.co/XgDI7ZEl59]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only picture I got from @LiquidStranger last night and I ain’t even mad.... 🤷🏼‍♀️ come back to Milwaukee soon w… https://t.co/1N1cX4vK5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shareclt @LevineMuseum @QueenCityUnity @AmericanCancer @running_works @ElonHomes @CopsandBarbers1 @cltiscreative… https://t.co/Lnxgiu3IKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[connecting over music with someone that has the same taste in it as you is a whole other level of happiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the spotlight!  Thanks to UMass for their awesome support! 😎 #sleepscience #somneuro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, #Oscars! . . . #OscarsBrunch #Equity #BritishEquity #OscarsWeekend #OscarsWeekend2019 #actresslife… https://t.co/6PlFA6GTg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[After everything I’ve been put through. Being this damn happy with someone.. it feels weird but so right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyMason217 Just buy the CD and an old portable CD player and carry that around with you at work. PLEASE do that. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who came out to prep fields for start of spring season. #cherryhillfc #cherryhill https://t.co/Ooj6vN66IR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SamAliSports gave me today and tomorrow off due to scheduling for the rest of the week, but I’m pretty sure it’s… https://t.co/6TaHB4poIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Matt Schlapp.  He thinks @realDonaldTrump is clean as a whistle and bows down to believe every word he says.… https://t.co/hHZDSv318f]]></document></documents></author>