<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Hey Nancy, I love you. We can makeout later if you want https://t.co/Zq3OZpw9yU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh please!  You make insulting, racist and dangerous comments every day.  If you really want to… https://t.co/Hpl6Flx2p8]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump is the most popular President in spite of fake news !!!!👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍🏼👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickocchipinti There*. 4 ppl that argue that their scholarship is covering that. The reality is 1. (Especially in… https://t.co/YfVgDnGyKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLHay @OkieLibSherry @Jim_Jordan I will refrain from calling u nuts,as u did to me,because I don’t have knowledge… https://t.co/n1MwkYBLNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[will it go round in circles #colorwheel #FlowerShow #FlowerPower @ The Philadelphia Flower Show https://t.co/kGxQZA56Eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DM_Nading @dmribich How come you are not racing? I thought you were a Senior? If your injured, hope you recover so… https://t.co/AOPbakPc7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonpsmith0 @Fuerstenberg15 @SherryBerry1409 @samantha_giese @tshearer75 @RayKittle @JodieLuneau1409 Congratulati… https://t.co/l5Ct5jhKU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Santucci @ABC @AllisonMPecorin If it was done in a hearing, that would be witness testing. Warning him off of his… https://t.co/XuZPgyq480]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latsondheimer That school is everything that is wrong about athletics in high school.  Actually a joke. Bought everyone of those titles!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron can give you 40 12 and 12 and that’s still not good enough for you lame ass haters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStalwart @rohangrey I've got the Desan book...now just need to read it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paolucci40 @rauljulialevy que miserabla hdp, perdon ? para nada que se joda por hdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir $200 EACH WAY seems like a lot of money for musicians to swallow. Would you not agree? @united airline… https://t.co/dRdI89W5AF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshsojoshy Damn i just wanna swallow every inch of your dick till u bust in the back of my throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlaf01 At the end of the day, you have to do what makes you happy. You are not obligated to make anyone else feel… https://t.co/FQYgpLMaMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[National High School Award winners at @MaxwellFootball Gala. https://t.co/G4NBB62gwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot! I am beyond excited to join tonight's #factVSfiction chat. I'm stamping out ignorance as the library technica… https://t.co/WPO1HWUPr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the ResCare Residential Services team! See our latest #Nursing job openings, including "LVN - Residential Serv… https://t.co/hYLpnUx9LI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go with the BSHS exposed BULLSHIT again. Do me a favor, don’t follow me with that shit. I reported you twice 👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayJunior!!! #HtownRush  @RussKHOU ⚓ @LisaKHOU 👠 @BrandiKHOU 🍷 @KHOUBlake11 🌤☀️ @KHOUStephanie 🚓🚗🚕… https://t.co/jpf0xWQwII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eric_wheeler @AMNH @colgateuniv Its open to conjecture, but I’d say indications are strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannonball Shoulder Sesh! Get up &amp; do something! #itpaystobeawinner #feelthepump💪🏾 #cannonballshoulders… https://t.co/KUzwsoCGgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingcfb I think her answer would be, “Say it ain’t so, Joe”. For a 109 year old card that is as pristine as it gets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 1st is when my 2019 officially starts!! Jan and Feb were bonus 2018 months! @Jstlivinbbyy 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wind4me They’re able to sell in 60 countries. FDA is just a small hurdle here in the states. You’re missing the bi… https://t.co/Q4FOgQXRZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grievesmith @LIRR @Amtrak @SenGianaris @Barnwell30 That is dangerous and unacceptable. Thank you for bringing it t… https://t.co/lr6mhmmVSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umjeremy What I’m learning from this thread is that we need more copes in The UMC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching LOOPER for the first time and how in the sam hell have I not seen this movie? Everything about this th… https://t.co/d0H1cIPgpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[ayer fui una fiesta como de 100 almas y solo conocía como a 10...todos sabemos que eso significa perreo hasta el su… https://t.co/odzE8d40ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is going to mistake this racist POS for the multi talented Prince]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers You know he’s dancing around this because he wants to downplay the fact he had an MOU with his towe… https://t.co/MHMBFQBscr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Trump is so obvious... just like... when the tyrant shows up, he'll be draped in the flag... Trump... w… https://t.co/aOeJSVCQ8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonah just FaceTimed me and had nothing but positive energy, you can only keep a real one down for a min or two.. t… https://t.co/sYySVbgb7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @realDonaldTrump @WSJopinion Was of state and US taxpayer money. If they look, they will find many pol… https://t.co/cBXr1Nm14A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OC_Scanner Wondering if Newport will get involved as it's now stopped in Newport. Let's get everyone involved right 😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worked out to Red Hot Chili Peppers, “My Friends”. (@ Metropolitan Place Fitness Center in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/pjdbhCrBaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday morning ✔in❗60min treadmill work #WMSFITFAM #ForcedObedience #SuperEights @MsNardosG @austin_carla @Mr_Chapp… https://t.co/l4Xu9Slyzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brahmresnik Will Sheridan be using @chadwillems as his campaign consultant?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NObsrvr3 @huw_alistair @kshaheen You need to change your name. You are clearly not a neutral observer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graceslick77 It's a #NeverTrump Wednesday !!!!!! (#AllySheedy still rocks !) https://t.co/GIz8ItOP1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Specializing on 1 sport isn’t showing up to tournaments and playing. Sorry, that’s the wrong mindset and lazy. What… https://t.co/5hUrhTJoZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @foxandfriends Thanks for your hard work supporting @parscale… https://t.co/csGlNhiLIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found Ring (Arapahoe Crossing): Ring found around 2/13 in Arapahoe Crossing parking lot. If yours, please reply wit… https://t.co/v7gcdKwoDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith How is @mookiebetts not #boxoffice but Judge and Harper are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇🏼 esto! Exactamente lo q hace Estados Unidos, te dan una deducción de impuestos para cuidado infantil que ni de pe… https://t.co/WBWRqw9oDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s a comedy program, really?  Did you fall and bump your head?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMasino @PtreeCorners @PartnershipGw Great step forward in propelling our region’s IoT leadership in smart citi… https://t.co/2jIS3jGu8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer Antonio/ fredericks is a dangerous combo. Love Fred coming in at half if it’s tied or we’re down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covering the arraignment of two who face human trafficking charges in Norwell https://t.co/BYoRV1xaoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Dextra 😡🧞‍♀️😡lets start charging them and let the courts sort it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[The late pick-4 ticket I was working on for this piece: GP Race 11 50¢ pick-4: 1,2,4,7,9,10 with 1 with 4,5,7,8 wit… https://t.co/vun4tyxMkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babyyyyyyyy...  shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo  I’m sorry...because now you’re singing that in your head. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nine of Cups also represents having high self-esteem and self-confidence. It is a card of celebrations and parties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez denies dark-money allegations in FEC complaint: ‘There is no violation’  https://t.co/FJHgJsmZqo lets… https://t.co/xrEvKpX4y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinemiaSupport my gf app looks like this since Wednesday already dm'd you her info please help https://t.co/X0y4Naxi3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[A well deserved honor in the midst of a historic season. @CoachGodlevske has high praise for his assistant coaching… https://t.co/NMHtKrhiGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolderStephen I've been trying to look at players like u have said that fits the autry/hunt/sheard model]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath @ryangrim This is the smart strategic take. Its triage—thank you for writing this out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRunnebaum @BiophysicalFrog I’m a huge advocate of this, and I think sometimes academics are seen as cold ivory to… https://t.co/hn6dPaKS6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK as of now I’m not watching the season finale of #HTGAWM until a week till the Season Premiere.  My heart can’t t… https://t.co/5I3z4QlGsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garymintchell Good insight, Gary. I’m confident @Microsoft knows what they are doing here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicj9311 @CBSThisMorning CTM is live in the east and then tape delayed - so it airs at 7am wherever you live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriterLarry Perhaps, since you owned a hamster (or gerbil) you can help her. Didn't you and Vernon cry when the babies were killed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony Ferguson is the type of guy to go through a Burger King drive thru and ask for McNuggets! @TonyFergusonXT @ChaelSonnen #ufc #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjlive @phontigallo it's Outkast, De La Soul or Ice Cube if we're keeping it funky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy day drinking.  Also first stop at this restaurant. - Drinking a Mr. Hanks by @bonesawbrewing @ Italian Affair… https://t.co/MGvsyfUsTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Questioning Lebron so much right now, saying passive aggressive comments towards teammates in post game interviews.… https://t.co/fumNyO25Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PankajK14313353 @_basdijkstra @StickyMinds @elastic @PankajK14313353 , have you seen this Podcast yet… https://t.co/HYbPh8Q1aJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2018, the average density in Cootes was 0.08 stems per m2 and in Grindstone 0.24 stems per m2. (includes stands… https://t.co/QlFPfPAi72]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 yrs? Now did you determine my sentence beforei was arrested? So in other wordsi had no chance from day 1...Set-up @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan I feel like the 25th amendment is the actual law .... and if wearing a wire is against the law there ar… https://t.co/eKjp030pVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get weird. @ryanmatheny16 is 100 miles from home and is just starting a game on KMA-FM 99.1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auh , Grant , yourself and your neighbor , have some concerning reviews , , Alright , the strength of 1776 has some… https://t.co/jrUGqXWiXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweatNP_ I didnt say you couldnt defend him, also didnt say you couldnt respond if someone said something incorrec… https://t.co/RcrkzCrnt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orange__White  is amazing how shitting lucky Blaney has had since he left the wood brothers. I get snake bitten every time I pick him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackbandicoot @pourya921 Please don't ... Mention... Cyberpunk 2077 with #Crackdown3 🤣  that being said, it's pretty damned fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't need no ISIS brides coming home and breeding their terror babies. We have enough problems!  #isisbride… https://t.co/QXLawLUlwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnimeEyedGirl But also, family, friendship, fighting to protect the ones we love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnG_Reacts @ToddLaTorre OMG I know, right??!!  It gives me hope for the future bro!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tf I get suspend on Xbox live 🤦🏽‍♂️ all I did was tell that scrub ass nigga his mamma suck dick for a half gram of reggie]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful winter view from my office this morning at @SBTS. https://t.co/RHwjVfJ4CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today probably one of the hardest day of my life having to pass my crown of being the snowbunny king to someone els… https://t.co/IZyVQGOWWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OVCSports @TheFordCenter If the OVC b-ball Championships stay in Eville permanently, we should adopt a # like some… https://t.co/KXhPRPmkXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Plum Island Belgian White by @nbptbrewing @ North Hampton, NH — https://t.co/zxfx7nh7Mr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all the great UW women for the thoughtful and inspiring conversation. I just wish I had Wonder Woman’s go… https://t.co/ojJ7i1Pvyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmilDamarcus Falseeeeee when the lebron was younger he was definitely windmilling. Your think of Lebron now Im talking before before age 27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr Adding a meteorology section on the Dale Jr download?? https://t.co/4U4T0PpeKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do we do? We call thanos , let that fucker snap them fingers and we will have the space , fucking humans, some… https://t.co/DobcSACLR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the High Schooler Shaking Up Artificial Intelligence #AI  https://t.co/wshsqXqQ4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANT PEOPLE  SAVED YO   HOPI INDIAN TRIBAL MEMBER'S @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/yLYXaGUHmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I have filled my body with chicken and alcohol. There is enough hate running thru me to fill a stadium. But… https://t.co/dKs20ptrXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ProTip: Refrain from discussing work related disputes and disagreements outside of the workplace. You never knows… https://t.co/GemZdzfiZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C0smicRadiation I didn't forget you! So it looks like April/May for Part 1! Here's the box art. #SailorStars https://t.co/dTPMD2LeQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into broski slim400blk he is a bool individual. Looking forward to linking on the West Coast! #Bompton was in t… https://t.co/aAkBgiZTXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS hottest girls in LasVegas are waiting for you at the CAN CAN ROOM...DISCOUNT Private Bed Rooms shows 10 dollar… https://t.co/4LfEtB4W8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PugsleyDani @MHPS4SQ @Strengths4U @Dr_JakeLong @BombersMh Love to see this! Keep on! 😀👏🏾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firenicefly @MattHancock @DavidRamCFT @cftrust @IanAustinMP @lbeswickcft Good news is I bet your constituents get access soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rush was my first hope,Fox my second,now through this platform,still waiting to see justice served.Patriots are not… https://t.co/tB0el22sTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1b) Here’s a look at our #KindnessWeek #VAPrinciPALS  #VAESPChat https://t.co/l5jopkg6bm]]></document></documents></author>