<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[my mom almost ran over canela bro... she slammed the breaks so hard i almost flew out the window 🥺 @BrotherNature]]></document><document><![CDATA[الشعوب العربية بصراحة لا تملك قرارها بل دائما هي مرتهنة لقوى إما أجنبية أو داخلية خاضعة لإملاءات الخارج. ولا يمكن ا… https://t.co/31JmbkbZqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrArticaina @KeniaLopezUrias pa que te den mas ganas de ir al dentista (8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauramarano You're a role model that teaches people to stay positive, keep fighting remain brave, stay ambitious s… https://t.co/8jVXEHvA3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking home from work the other day along the Colorado.  #commutehome #gorgeousday #bridge #river #shadow #shade… https://t.co/YGH8MEQeku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I didn't sleep with my fan on last night, so we're going to assume that's why I am exhausted today.  It'… https://t.co/59scXYdV4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's talk about temptation and how it relates to purity. Are there things you can do to make it easier for you to… https://t.co/ytWgaXP3gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body is so tired idk how I’m going to make it through another 12 hour shift today 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bocavista2016 Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE… https://t.co/vlRtpMRmuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im too nice man. My one free day and i decided to cover someone’s shift when all i wanna do rn is nap :-///]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethanyParkhil2 @tmulvey5 @lcreswell5 @paul_slovik @WP5Duncan @BarbaraUssary Love seeing this AIG curriculum class… https://t.co/r74WJm0MxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/fBoS06n9wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Corinthos is the only ceo that never works #GeneralHospital @ChadDuell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember I said I emailed my boss about a raise? I also asked about our company paying for me to get my master’s in… https://t.co/OpneCdi2r2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josetorohardy, han demostrado que no les importa que el mundo entero los observe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet They truly are clueless.  They don't believe a word they say, so it's coming out more delusional/co… https://t.co/eZyoVJPd4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr We should have kicked her out of congress when she called our president a mf.  We should not have t… https://t.co/T4P6S1QXZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chickfila breakfast ends at 10:30 and I came in at 10:27 and got my breakfast 🕺🏽🕺🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[u can call me your maliboo 🌼 @ Malibu, California https://t.co/CJMGgFwKAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden This is unacceptable and horrifying: kids in schoool taught how to get prepared to die! #AmericaExceptionalism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isa54v5 @Sacraestvita @testisfidelis @_BLACKCATHOLIC @StevenErtelt @CatholicVegSis Break out your bible. Start rea… https://t.co/FBvrDXhiop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting spot for the evening. Let’s see if lightning strikes twice for this place. #ufc235 #vegasnightlife… https://t.co/79dawxlL5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would anyone get it if Ducky’s registered name was Charlie Conway? 😂 #themightyducks #aqhaproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelenMcCready Haha... good one. Feb 29th to Feb 31st doesn't exist. Here is a good for the last 3 digits of your p… https://t.co/2DC9aP0QAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump tRump is the Russian traitor.  Please lock 45 up quickly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to chase down a kitty outside of my house and I didn’t get her :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Approximately two-thirds of the state's highways are listed as Travel Not Advised or Impassable. Winter 2019, I qui… https://t.co/niCaQ48PPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep in the waiting room while my dad was in surgery and the sweet angel front desk receptionist covered me with a warm blanket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyrone345345 @uBattleGround @CNN @SafetyPinDaily @NBCNews @FrontStream @democracynow @ABC @blackvoices @RawStory]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's an awesome feeling to be among "like minded" people who are striving to become the best educators for our stud… https://t.co/tLocluzI6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iHeartAwards  #BestCoverSong  #StillTheOne  @KaceyMusgraves  @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooooh chile one of my outta town flexes got him an in-town flex and ugh TRAGIC. I miss the one he had before, thi… https://t.co/Zz9iqtxVbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Far Gone never left my rotation but something about having it on Apple Music playing by itself and not on YouTube 😂🙌🏾 #Blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[i used to go to a water park in germany called “Schweiß” which means “sweat” lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The language of digitalization is computer science”Jamie Casap: Google Education: We need to create more opportuni… https://t.co/055h3Q4uMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just lost a company shuffleboard game in devastating fashion and honestly I feel like I lost the super bowl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current situation! #NCAAgym 🤸🏻‍♀️ @FloridaGators @TerpsGymnastics @GW_Gymnastics @Towson_GYM @FloGymnastics… https://t.co/Eoavu74wJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHorrorGuru Am I evil for hoping you &amp; @Count_Jackula do a vlog on this when it comes out? https://t.co/cbczwTpNJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarR49721088 @charliekirk11 @AllTrump2020 You don't need to be disrespectful. Of COURSE the repubs would. Just… https://t.co/ekiO9naCFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#miamiheat #miami #celtics #easternconferencefinals @ The Polo Club of Boca Raton https://t.co/zE6CoODQbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is sooooo damn cold! I didn’t want to get out of bed but I’m here. Have to get summer bod ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdracing You did a great job !!  I feel a win is in you near future !!!👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old dogs Jack and Diane are inseparable, so their shelter married them https://t.co/bdVzXe0jSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our after dinner festivities last night.  #nofilter #boymom #3boysunder5 #momofteenboys #sahmomlife… https://t.co/IcKewNGPCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatironSchool @Career_Karma @Abdul_Qadir41 @AshleyS89102847 @AlvinSm86801437 @LambdaSchool @FlyTy_world… https://t.co/DfyXGUVa7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember in my 20’s my gynecologist commented on how nice I groomed my pubic hair. I didn’t know enough then to b… https://t.co/1oZVHBRuxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls post those question things to be hella rude 😭😭 j ignore the question sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ontem dormi enquanto assistia #TheMarvelousMrsMaisel mas vi que Amorzinho adorou o episódio. Ele tava gargalhando e… https://t.co/X9qc9S6QUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom No skin? Except like getting murdered in their classrooms?]]></document><document><![CDATA[could the #lion b  Kelly Clarkson?@MaskedSingerFOX    Whoever it is we have a real ?on our hands #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiHerald Omg! Here we go again with MSM fake news biases.🙄🙄 He, CLEARLY, has no idea who these people are. Trum… https://t.co/8th0IIeLF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s gonna help my little buddy exceed his goal?!? Can I at least get a retweet?@MarkDParrish @Chris_Hawkey… https://t.co/oC29tCoxXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m two @Twitter.  Can I get my Twitter account verified? @TwitterSupport]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would wear boots w/ cow shit on them at all times that way I never have to worry about farting in public - @M_Negangard   #mitchlogic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldLovell Also she has so many good fucking songs.... her recent work is 💯💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think? #opinion  @Airbnb host charges a $60 cleaning fee then asks guests to clean the house before che… https://t.co/8Dw2HhnjWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaVanZee @Twither407 @krassenstein @GOP @AnnaVanZee thank you.  We have a farm too. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaneorti_z They taste just like they did when we were kids they’re just smaller than before but still amazing 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us in the Texas Capitol in Austin, Texas at 2 PM in room E2.026  If you would like to testify or send a letter… https://t.co/pysEfFB8uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyssaaBear Shit, I didn't ever mind giving her a ride bc I knew she was gonna pull that shit out 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mikey lovingly greeted me as “egg” when he got home from work. I’m not kidding. It made me feel so special. I never… https://t.co/HLLXM7caEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeberWeberk So very proud of you Riya!   Congratulations!  Hard work pays off! 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 53 of 365: I just turned 20 unbelievable. It’s the first birthday without my great grandmother by my side. I ha… https://t.co/IJRgmf4aPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannclelia @Truckee530 I became a big fan of plow service. That said, there’s almost no where left to put plowed snow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jabrtb Yep. They are here we let them come in. Hitler said that there was no rush America would Fall from within.… https://t.co/gvZuylRJM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suddenly I am..... back to myself... going back to selfies and loving myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[undefined https://t.co/0xuopxBfgE #biblestudytools #bst #bible What can we learn through the life of trees? How doe… https://t.co/WvwE9AxKuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Memories are a doorway to the past. And the more one treasures the memories, the wider the door will open.’… https://t.co/vtYK7ZoBah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsteeze @lyndseyfifield @RepSwalwell I wouldn’t doubt if he put the snow in his hair and on his jacket for more effect!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@neemaguliani discusses rise of “public-private surveillance partnerships” #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student researching the college that Dr. Seuss attended. #vvreads @Columbia_VVUSD https://t.co/MF8Gg4Jj1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though Galaxy started the Icon X a long time ago. Apple did not create the EarPods.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to come and visit! See you guys next month! 🐶 🐾 🔔 #HailState #chooseMSU #whereinfloridaisjoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was 17 (only diagnosed at 17, but I probably had it a lot longer due to old lesions on my brain being found at th… https://t.co/8z156Rw9rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is my Schedule at @ChickenRanchNV for the next 6 Months:   March 5th - 16th  April 5th - 14th  April 26th - Ma… https://t.co/tGVZcJQQxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCF_Knightline @aafAPOLLOS @RealRadio1041 @reneingoglia @jerryosports Thank you guys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had chocolate pudding in like a week and I’m not okay with this #myfav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot @1loriking That's because until now it was under umbrella of State but Sec of State spent first year slash… https://t.co/AJDLHWx2qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpicyFiles @TrueFactsStated @lauferlaw @911CORLEBRA777 @ericgarland Can you threaten a federal judge and take it back just like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Smollett should not be compared to greats like Jackie Robinson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UPDATE on this morning’s shooting in Cabell County: We can confirm that one man is dead. https://t.co/DU0CmoKWeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz No self respecting woman would want your little wiener inside them. Yuck 🤮🤮🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of traffic at the Ranch this morning. Two herds, elk and turkeys @ Bassett Ranch Carbondale Co https://t.co/64dtu7e6vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garrard County Schools closing Monday Feb. 25 to curb the spread of illness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Girls Just Want To Have Fun by @cyndilauper on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/04W36ycQVo https://t.co/MunRs8QG74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump America has always been great. It is less so with you at the helm. You are a huge disaster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino He can try!  Most  kids, teenagers, adults have made forgivable mistakes.  His kid chose ISIS!!  That's insane!!!!! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonallendc Can you name the quality journalist at Fox that haven't capitulated to the Fox State TV agenda...]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao yea if u believe literally anything Jordyn said during her red table talk.... SHEEEESH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! Starting the day on a positive note is noticeable by our patients. They know when we’re invested in the… https://t.co/oDaGhmoN20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patla_rina @ramonaa1yahooco @isabenfica51 @alisonblamer @1Urban_Wolf @JakeBellalove1 @WolfVivienne007 @LisaBrabson… https://t.co/lngP8VEZ77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Then lock crooked, criminal, collusionist Hillary Clinton up.. or be a Hypicrite.. #blueboofwawaclub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MishLGee_xoxo We have a gastroenterologist appt today and hope to get a few more answers. He's had one bout of pai… https://t.co/AqNesrJnkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The FedEx guy makes his deliveries to my office...why?   He has to by-pass the receptionist, and another office BEF… https://t.co/SmcTQFsPqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAYJURRENS @Krissy_Anderson @Room209Literacy @KristinaManson @JeanniePfaffle @kkayserkemp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cw_mills @Soul_of_Nowhere The review referred to lots of “tea and bun shops”!  That means cake???  YUM!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normally I try to space my posts out so they aren’t back to back. Last few weeks have been crazy busy. My car was t… https://t.co/HlACbHnsJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancoCNac @CJLeBlanc The tyears have been good to you. I like Good Mikey, but you made a great Evil Michael. ❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @AsambleaVE hola Juan necesitamos una intervención militar ya no guantamos mas https://t.co/ipVzdGD549]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buying #art supports #artists directly, allowing them to continue with their creative process, which in turn improv… https://t.co/cl3cKqvaAP]]></document></documents></author>