<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Off on a quick trip across the pond! Traveling light so the samples I’ll bring bag can travel heavy. #postdoclife… https://t.co/5eOYgjxPvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me think of the conversation @MatthewDaddario, @HarryShumJr, and @isaiahmustafa had during last Year’s l… https://t.co/exBy2WNOzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a Terri-fic Tuesday!!! The sun is shining and it’s not snowing! Enjoy while you can!  More snow headed our way… https://t.co/1ZhoVs8eDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPiccini @KingaSurmaMPP @CommCareNland @OntarioNewsNow @fordnation @JeffYurekMPP @trulylocal897 @north_news… https://t.co/uGsKYBku7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Aramark team! See our latest #CustomerService job openings, including "Food Service Worker - UPMC Susqueha… https://t.co/Wky16Qyznu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @UNC made this image into action figures and sold them I’d never get another fundraising appeal #GDTBATH… https://t.co/o4rb5US7n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes we did! Before Tupelo invests a lot of time, money, and investment of teachers and students, I would think twic… https://t.co/cuWJVZeTfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offsetting technicals?!?! Are you kidding me??? We should be getting a foul shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you lend someone $20, and never see that person again; it was probably worth it.  #MoneyTalks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to win tickets to @LiveAtFirefly! @MalibuRumUS #MalibuRum https://t.co/FHrpDumTAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the @JosephMaleyJMF for a great disABILITY program last week! @MapleGroveElem kinders learned about he… https://t.co/huhfS2rsz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1893 Patricia was one of the bridesmaids for the Duke and Duchess of York. Here seated lower right. https://t.co/WzRSt174y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uterus free to a good home. Slightly used. You can repurpose it to a lampshade or a handbag. Whatever you like. Jus… https://t.co/Q2ALugC5Tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carpenter's Bluff Bridge spans the Red River between OK and TX near Durant, OK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February walk in the Bobolink Meadow.   Various types of animal tracks across the frozen lagoons in Jackson Park. A… https://t.co/FwYD43ddEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#justtoysproductions is in rehearsals with #thedogthenightandtheknife and we open in 3 weeks at @irondalecenter Iro… https://t.co/4sg231gxqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorBennet @SenCoryGardner @RepKenBuck  I guess we can all agree that there is no emergency since @POTUS is chi… https://t.co/x6wR7LHBXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayjamescarter @icpetrie I want to believe.  Except I can’t since I co-wrote a National Historic Landmark on Clive… https://t.co/xjIN1o8oE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Holly Springs, NC - @tohollysprings in NC https://t.co/OEYqBEqAWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am a pisces and that’s why i is a good game to be okay but it’s so hard omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You finally learning how to take pictures and I’m so proud! @kartierbaby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice cover @clickpolo #worldpololeague #newbreed #newera #26powerseverything @GrandChampions_ #polo https://t.co/lN3rESFXGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live from Mickys Weho W/ DJ SRO #MickysWeHo WATCH: https://t.co/Ehvzt5ET0k https://t.co/pVLO3mCEVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biraskikihayat @ayyapim @medyapimresmi Neydi en büyük korkumuz, sevdiklerimizi kaybetmek mi, yoksa hiç sevilmemek… https://t.co/emy0Btx2Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Historic Bridge in Prestonsburg @MarcWeinbergWX @Kentuckyweather https://t.co/yryqbhiUZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity at it's best. Quiz: What Would Be Your Fate In The Hunger Games? I lived, but here's why: Because...… https://t.co/jpkYgfmDY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW GOOD IT FEELS 48x48in acrylic on canvas #abstractart #contemporaryexpressionist #art #corporateart #publicart i… https://t.co/FmT4BWIBx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PucciaPatrizia @consuiglesias @Jose93571656 @Viviane6677 @AnaAndrade305 @eiteamokarina @carolina_smal… https://t.co/P1uggGrZ25]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Harley's Country Store &amp; Beer Garden in Bayview, TX https://t.co/N1URZY4U3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyRingwald i love all of your movies pretty in pink and sixteen candles and the breakfast club]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being home in bed sick results in unnecessary online shopping. #justified]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u think my resting bitch face is bad u should see my Resting Thinking Face https://t.co/8MIzjqEDeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Just lip service to keep their jobs. Next election vote the Socialist former Democrat Party OUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue mmmmm, I think, if we collect more in taxes from the 1% for example, we could pay for the Green New… https://t.co/YEYblslFxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[i remember when i saw mayday parade and i facetimed @KaylinDodd bc she loved them 🥺❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trnrtips done made international news. I'm glad you have your channel back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDaware How can we expect any truly ill or compromised patient to successfully navigate heath care ? I take that b… https://t.co/XBbYzummF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both are too expensive.. An *extra* $20? You mean to tell me you’d spend even $20 on ONE pair of leggings? LMAOO I’… https://t.co/zB39jCEylh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliveaaMarriie I was so ascared it was gonna blow away.. yes I realize we work inside but I thought with all the c… https://t.co/gSR4MBGSl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk can do whatever the fuck he wants when he wants to do it  without hesitation or apology. This fucking wor… https://t.co/NEzsmbnVyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReapSow111 @persianstranger @Sproprietors @Barbara98753838 @jeremyboswrth TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read the lyrics to 21 Slaughters’ ‘Slaughter Your Daughter’ and tell me how that is contribution to art and society… https://t.co/37M1ku6ojJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill can you relate? My daughter has a gorgeous makeup room, yet she gets ready in the living room while sit… https://t.co/995vjmspTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgriffith59 Keep this beautiful couple together  on the show. #Lane is a couple of "True Love" and "Soulmates".… https://t.co/F4n9lGgBCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the incredibly talented @KRThomasPhD who won a Student Liaison Committee (SLC) research award tonight… https://t.co/tYnoVUQhxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@countryfestwi @AshleyMcBryde They are all my favorites!! But if I had to pick 1 it would be..... darn, I can’t do… https://t.co/RUAaJRKu81]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s a different type of hurt when you want someone who doesn’t want you back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skiinnimiinni that shit like a mini amusement park swear lol I’m just astounded by the creations of the house like… https://t.co/FvTWohiBeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[conspiratorial purposes.  "The constitutional government of the Bolivarian Republic of Venezuela will not allow r… https://t.co/zrfw26oa9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to start painting again......that always helped me express myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carola2hope Tienes razón pero nadie reclama la ayuda humanitaria. No hay conciencia de clase.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stemceo That’s the essence of my job! I’m a middle school STEM educator, always advocating for minorities and fema… https://t.co/upoBsXg4rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Nextdoor is local, am I right @JasonHannaman ? https://t.co/yUrowqwvmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@B1047 What better way to start off #TMarvTuesday than to play .@TravisMarvin today? #TMarv #fangirl #Untied #NeverHadAFirstTime #Simple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theracheltucker @morgankmoody How did I get two amazing best friends wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scout_Finch @joncoopertweets But this guy didn't come across the southern border or from some "shithole" country d… https://t.co/pUZyJpKhSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter tried to turn me and my ex against each other for her benefit. She forgot that we co parent as one mind. https://t.co/Ips7SiUNxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[disembarked from the cruise at like 8 ish, went straight home then straight to work. im about to go home and prolly hit the pillow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! This is just a sampling of the amazing women in my life who inspire me every day.… https://t.co/kNQtWLabqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainMabel We need comedy in our life and almost every time she opens her mouth, funny falls out of it., Here’s… https://t.co/mWiDqDpTQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jko410 @smalltownandrew Can’t stand her! What a narcissist ! She needs to hook up with Smollett! 😖😖😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @thinkcollegeICI in a tribute to @hgse’s @TomHehir :  “Inclusion is more than an educational concept. It is a… https://t.co/iF0YPrkRYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family that reads together, stays together 📖 #DHE #LiteracyNight https://t.co/gNpUgKLYUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con Sue Photography and Design  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/8sbgQze2Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg listening to my students workshop their tribute speeches. ALL. THE. FEELS. They are so good, y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels like a Friday, probably bc @missfabela &amp; I are ready to drink https://t.co/4KJGlgWEpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can’t tell me they aren’t in love with each other look at how they sing together towards the end, I’m calling i… https://t.co/Sb8QEchGv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂 I cannot deal. Should I ask him to cash app me 1,000? https://t.co/oBT9wLVqTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump Wow! Do you kiss your dog with that mouth? Why do y’all always have to resort to name… https://t.co/wGi4ryTEs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhonnybay Oh my. Had to look a couple of times before I could see him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an important one too.  Thank you to @courtneyfriel for sharing your mantra. It’s made me look at each day w… https://t.co/IPicndLyPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t get over the fucking all stars 4 outcome 😂 I’m just so dissatisfied]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you work in tech you’re legally obligated to tweet every time you fly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyssaaaahh She wins!! She said "I made her p***y wet she need a MOPiana "... done it's done...She wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trynna complain but I wish I didn’t have anxiety 24/7 and panic attacks 23/7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm actually ok with season 7 being the last season of AOS as long as they give it a solid ending. Its longer than… https://t.co/KisI5HWvde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let it snow  . . . #snowing #snowstorm2019 #eastorangenj @eocityhall eastorangemacfest #becareful @abc7ny @ East Or… https://t.co/CfauXoZGiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmergingCitizen @seaghost78 @WSM_97 @911CORLEBRA777 @mopeng @thespybrief @JamesFourM @LouiseMensch Hello. It's 2019, not 1995.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everyone would please take a quick 2 seconds and sign this!!   All my hair stylist and I aren’t and did pay the… https://t.co/JqVc3PgDvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the 5th generation in my family raised in the Capay Valley.  Proud Daughter of the Golden West and don’t forget… https://t.co/xCzr7dcFDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: A Good Presbyterian???  https://t.co/K9p815Kgnc via @amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Grocery Store  Old Man: Can you count for me how much 3/5$ means for each?   In my head: *Do I fucking look… https://t.co/iKLysIYTia]]></document><document><![CDATA[We killed our workout! I did chest, abs, and cardio today! #workoutbuddy #schweatyselfie #chestabscardio @ Planet F… https://t.co/lFxe7Ggj4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyMountViews @MollyJongFast Nope...blame Viagra and Cialis. Now all these old goats can get wood even if the re… https://t.co/UomevjhctO]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being so bitter that you force your negativity onto people who are just minding their business https://t.co/q1039k7c5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @Kaepernick7 He gets a settlement for his own stupidity! Taking a knee, now the police is under attack!… https://t.co/Mckbnh1yeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #BuildTheWall #NationalEmergency #YouGo I’m so proud of your persistence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be so busy improving yourself, you have no time to criticize others.🗝🖤 Dress: @rainbowshops https://t.co/Pd4MRPjWRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump Peace with N. Korea would be great. Peace with Kim Jong-Un would be skeptical, at b… https://t.co/qJkuXMqZ27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardioIAN @AmHeartAdvocacy @cathymcmorris LOLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #LoveToHonk because who carries around change anymore? 🤷🏻‍♀️ @HonkMobile Happy V Day 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyGeorge really like song and love the simplicity of video. Ok I'm a filmmaker.. the graphics are definitely 80s… https://t.co/fOOs2VPgwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Hello. These are not journalists. They are just suck up hateful idiots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmarx If you spend time referring to someone else as irrelevant, you are probably infinitely more irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods These people are very, very confused about their gender. Not right people to raise a child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A gente foi atender um cavalo hoje, e aí os donos dele eram sei lá mexicanos eu acho, e eu falei que era do Brasil… https://t.co/oq7XFKBmL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never experienced pain like I have this past week and I’m just so fed up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ubazxo @EmmaVerkuilen You know why they call it almond milk? Cause no one could call it  nut juice with a straight face. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martibatres @senadomexicano @jenarovillamil Para cuándo la creación de la Guardia Nacional y la abrogación de la m… https://t.co/n02KOB2Lc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Alec Baldwin the Domestic Violent King is flapping his old has been gums again! What an idiot]]></document></documents></author>