<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[After Spending 4 Years in a #Box,   This Young #Orangutan is Finally Free   #care2 https://t.co/diyFi0ekyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chloefashion Last picture on the right, fully covered turtle neck all the way down to those tan boots. I love the military side buttons. 👄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway Casually Drops Mueller Bombshell In Wild Chris Cuomo Debate https://t.co/Ko1EL5xCmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want tasers to be a legal tool for wheelchair riders to use.  Zzzzzztt! That’ll move his boney butt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScruggleBus I think all forms of sweatshirts have a their pros and cons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton reminds me of my high school freshmen year boyfriend..... #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenBasmin @Bakari_Sellers “opporcoonist” is a great descriptive word!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan maybe you should just sit back and learn your job the first year. Your tweets and interviews are getting to… https://t.co/TyLzusYN3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brains_brawn_MD @tammyeaton17 Glad to finally meet you and your colleagues today!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenneth67293665 I keep unfollowing and refollowing bc I cant decide if I believe it or not 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreaneubauer5 @MisterMinor He is definitely in his zone and loving it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww, you know you’ve found true marital bliss when you can bring your wife on a stake out.  #TiffThursday  #STiff… https://t.co/q5aafVzpLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[my brain hoed tf out of me and brought my biggest fear to life in nightmare form lol it be ya DAMN SELF!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes What the hell I'm in Texas, I'm not his stupid base racist follower, What nobody else in Texas cares enough to stop this MADMAN?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wrote a review on Tec The Tractor Plush Toy https://t.co/t7Bvj3AVXS via @yotpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Part-time Evening Associate" at Crew Carwash, then look for people you… https://t.co/tw0gGZsljQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't understand how people get filthy rich and aren't constantly giving back to their communities/the lower clas… https://t.co/0RMY8d8NbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok... have someone else bring you your food and serve you alcohol. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Additional photos by Renee- the official photographer of #jbjbday2019  ❤️⭐️🎵🎂🎈 #jonbonjovi #birthday #party #food… https://t.co/P5OrGAgb5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jared_hallman13 Because the school is making money off of them and the players get zero of it. What is different a… https://t.co/AidUbjqafp]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do Travis and Kanye get all these extravagant flower displays into the houses without them hearing or knowing someone is in the house???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @Jim_Jordan Gym Jordan? #JimJordanKnew #JimJordanMustResign]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your kids get your Elton John tickets for your birthday cause they know you love him and it’s his farewell tou… https://t.co/jilVwbnGxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I go right for the cake or should I eat a meal first?!? #whatveganseat #vegan #veganfoodshare #veganfoodporn… https://t.co/y68NzEdR6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fayeluc97 @brittanydugann i think about this all the time, also the time she asked if you’ll glow if you get struck by lightning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darcysteels @RJellyman @cellmavin @badhopper @JonMontag @lhtetrick @JohanBBT @Stef_Pellerin @brew_dude @dzyngrl… https://t.co/UAOtR3T06J]]></document><document><![CDATA[S3 BUNDLE.   A combination of our services with an additional discount. https://t.co/NilfUjBb5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Djglo15 @BurketLS Good morning!  So excited about the upcoming @CarmillaCon announcement today. https://t.co/yoArIIhHVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankLuntz @MaeveReston is not a journalist. Just a suck up democrat who reports fake news just like all the Trump… https://t.co/CuMgFL4hKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonmarcantel I didn’t misconstrue your first tweet.  You insulted me by comparing me to tRump and his cult. I am a… https://t.co/GwdkBkzVhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Myraceisamerica @drawandstrike @realDonaldTrump How many times before it’s mathematically impossible 🇺🇸💃… https://t.co/FjMV4aHLVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your smarter and wiser than the average bear but play a little slow because you like mind games sometimes 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I didn’t know what it hurt like to be broken, then how would I know what it feels like to be whole:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[my father: *yelling*  me: dad can you stop yelling my father: *yelling* i’m not yelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naztradamix - I will give $100 to the Patreon if it will get us a proper J4/J.O.B with the original cast https://t.co/BY8XixRMJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie thinks he can win. He hadn’t looked around. There is a of choices this time. And all those women Senators??… https://t.co/2FCVZPF6NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in my opinion.... if it isn’t your kid, you should mind your own business, hunni 🤪😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our Pioneer Swim Team as they travel to Bowling Green for the district meet!  Hit the burners🔥… https://t.co/pqTnLOu00q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, yeah, retail employees don’t owe you shit :))) if you want someone to ask how your day is, get a therapist]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you love what you do, you do it right! Thanks Rookmin and Lauren for saving the day! When your life is on your… https://t.co/aRfzyplAGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is full again❤️ @ Greeneville, Tennessee https://t.co/xs5nhleXTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cripps_carmen @SupportEduc @DStaehrFenner @amy_r_whitehead @VongmanyE @KenyaLMcCoy @MrsCannonESL Yay! I’m so glad… https://t.co/tmd2MIqeiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[who the fuck don’t want their woman be to twerking cardi makes money twerkn like duh get it girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fr fr I feel like I took something. I wonder if jay gave me a contact high. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway through the semester and my professor STILL doesn’t know our names...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannaRoze I agree , but also he really keeps it very clean.  He doesn't swear or vulger . His kind heart and inte… https://t.co/5M0dTHvWe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fucking tired &amp; upset of these bitches doing this to me and leaving me out . Bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizarrogirl @abbycohenwl I’ve told my people casually to do this, bc here they are almost always tied to a tragic… https://t.co/5z2s92wr3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carey Price sera devant le filet du #CH ce soir face au Lightning. Aucune surprise ici! 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarchisReading month! Ready for a story? Join me! @HillcrestElem @MichKiwanis @CSDSchools https://t.co/QMTNCjeaGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[tb to the first day of my vacation when i was feeling good. + vlog is rendering https://t.co/6Uhbik6W4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leroy Johnson, Executive Director of Southern Echo making it plain at the Census 2020: Counting Heads, Counting Vot… https://t.co/4PFztOqIEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delevrything @SpitefulDoll I remember coming down from a trip and thinking how I had some how accumulated a shit t… https://t.co/wuHaMGc5JI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimiaess @WVTM13 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS This is just a small clip of what he did in Puerto Rico, maybe you should… https://t.co/MSGlP3hypE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy, huh? How I put like 10 alarms and still manage to snooze every single one 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[middle-income nations in the Middle East, Asia and Africa bear the biggest burden for their upkeep.  Amnesty Intern… https://t.co/r7hX8L1Feq]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:00pm &amp; 6:00pm Ashes only ; 7:00pm Mass after ashes again 🙏🏼 Don’t forget Ash Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will, frankly, take any and all of these candidates but also  Betoooooo catch up!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched the Sopranos from beginning to end. Anyone want to talk me through this?? https://t.co/c1nwFLME4B.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my mom tells me to just go buy food from town bc then I don’t feel guilty for spending money instead of cooking myself  🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to teaming up with #NYEdChat for March #WonderChat. Stellar lineup! #MakerEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Ah... Mad Maxine is scared her peeps are about to be exposed! 🍿 https://t.co/G95F0foF3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently, we are supposed to get 2-4" of snow... doesn't sound that bad but it will literally shut the city do… https://t.co/qyNLRfffPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/db90RoeNKT  @lisheyjohnson  https://t.co/ZrqrsOxUjQ TEXT CHECK TO 644-33  What happens in Vegas stays… https://t.co/QKJLbGcd9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[The net worth in this video .. yasss https://t.co/LJnqo4dUvE #JonasBrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't  you question the IG's conclusions.   Maybe he needs to be investigated.😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have Laryngeal Schwannoma.  Tumor in left Larynx. Only 1% of the country has disease. Just lost my left Larynx, c… https://t.co/gHZrCoxBUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bananas89Is @FRONZ1LLA stop acting like i won’t eat her pussy too gtfo bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpinionsMagee @AnonOpinion411 @teenmom2central That’s all she wanted anyway was a ring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman They offend me with their anti-Semitic insults. Heaven knows how they got voted into office. I know they don’t belong there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tax #client income went up 20k, their #taxrefund went down 2k but their TAX decreased 5k - wonder how @MSNBC, @CNN… https://t.co/zycBdRa9hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madelicate @noahlevy13 @noahlevy13 - the bridge between rep and TS7 that we didn’t know we needed 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently playing the 7th Player on https://t.co/nSHi44i2Tj. Come and join me! https://t.co/RZdAUBTJvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS #TmobileTuesdays+contest https://t.co/geWGWaTuGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonblack995 @BTS_twt @bts_bighit My daughter is on it! We wait for tour dates so I can drain my bank account! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to our friends at Hot Spot Nashville for this 🎤🎤🎤 interview w/ John Schneider. Love his commitment to CM… https://t.co/Hcsb07lwTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liacallahan4 @ultabeauty @NyxCosmetics @Vahalia241 @arcadiarose_ @alleykatt74 @influensterjen1 @Naddez @PanRose30… https://t.co/two6kJl6ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Ellis, showing sympathy for a criminal like Manafort, sends the wrong message to white collar criminals every… https://t.co/P0FQ8O0Bcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliane_luz @fmaier50 @Al_jazeeraT O seu nariz, sua anta. Não me meça com a sua régua.  Neste caso aí da foto a sen… https://t.co/0W1NfG3Nh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sue Sorenson @ortnercenter women are 2.5 times more likely to be killed by an IP as opposed to a stranger #ortnerexec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4kingandcountry Was phenomenal last night!!  They are a must to see live! https://t.co/sO0zO38owy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re in the executive lounge dressed in shorts while you’re coworkers are ready for the day with their laptops open...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#worship #godswarriorprincess @ Bayside Church Granite Bay https://t.co/5biGwCeoCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crux @eharris_it Solution for all problems facing the Church, withhold the money. They will then find a way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorswift13 is coming out with a new album soon!!! Look at the difference in her instagram lately! #cantwait https://t.co/0wWhtyzgWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t seat at the meetings, around the table. Imagine: I seat around the table. My eyes get big I feel urge to hi… https://t.co/d1uZolRtCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey want to help me survive spring break? $AudreyTighe  https://t.co/PRNbMylL6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell no. @OrrinHatch, raise your own money. I’m not paying for you to inflate your ego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[aksksks i remember when zayn left 1d and i was still in cheer at the time, and i had a practice that same night and… https://t.co/zsnQCm9naH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching a show on Netflix but it required me to actually pay attention so I turned it off]]></document><document><![CDATA[DPAC  Charlie &amp; The Chocolate Factory On Broadway https://t.co/YeqdXujsoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanT63511450 Alyx Vance fawning over Gordon Freeman didn't enhance the game for me at all. It was creepy and unco… https://t.co/Y1JRM7BTlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie @ja2cook @Jay_Rombach @jflorez… https://t.co/kBMDl2jlT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,Hey,Hey its #FatTuesday 🤹‍♀️ It fills our hearts when you fill your belly with #delight 😋 #mardigras2019  📷:… https://t.co/WGHVfM8r7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sunburnt I’m sun kissed ☀️ 😘 💋 (all lies I’m very sunburnt send help pls) #baylaketower #disneyworld… https://t.co/GzAVnx0CqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepRose @StacyA11 dmp @ alabravo,I don't watch the news and haven't since 1954lol, seriously ,I do not watch the news, anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past few weeks have been busy, so I have not been very creative with meals.  It's just been about getting some… https://t.co/PMO8ZAZLmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @fan_of_racing @bkent136 @macodiseas @katlinegrey Good Luck today 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebassprod #depressionwarrior #keepfuckinggoing #everyday #nottodayDarkDemon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ea6bbe086025482 Wrong because the original contact put him out of position. It was actually a very smart call no m… https://t.co/g2G9NvN8cQ]]></document></documents></author>