<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for him to go. For all of his arrogance he’ll be crying like a baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always cook a little more than i can eat for dinner and leave leftovers so that when i inevitably become hungry at… https://t.co/GZo1gFgyKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmlexxx @ttaattyyaannaa_ Y’all agree? @laurataase @lesrivera_ @hernanVVX ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 Graham has crossed over and is permanently stuck in Stupidville, USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to personal reasons every time I see a tweet about the Jonas brothers that disregards Kevin I’m taking a shot of tequilla.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungBarkley34 Almost every time the Suns lost in the playoffs it was just painful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klsmd12 @bigmouth Oh fuck.  No comeback. I just woke up smiling and laughing today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixing up a little this morning! #fatherdaughtertime @ Bojangles' https://t.co/Qdl9DMAUwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Year 3 for Chapman, Olson, and Pinder  Year 2 for Profar (as a regular), Laureano, Trivino, Cotton, and Fowler  Yea… https://t.co/AeXfs0mnuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinCassien Just the lead singer in Talk Talk. They did one of the best songs in the 80s, and one of my all-time… https://t.co/7udZh15Szl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlairKing_ca @keithbaldrey Before I was an MLA I sat on the original committee advising Government on Alt energy o… https://t.co/IRiL3sgr56]]></document><document><![CDATA[It still blows my mind that people actually spend time arguing with strangers on the internet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapped an “in-progress” shot of this guy making sand art today. Not mad about being at the ocean mid-winter with h… https://t.co/yvZWd6B6Lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCMurdoch Glad you said "one of", because I couldn't pick one! That being said, One of my favorites was the vampi… https://t.co/CmjlLvxszO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to forget all my feels for you, but I can’t help and think about all that we could of conquer together. How… https://t.co/9ZjiVts8y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BULLDOGcatchingCORPS in 11 days!  @JOSHUAKEHL2020 @BsblHeinz @Mitchelldzienis @ProeschelJack @CRJ17Canes… https://t.co/W0GJLNnsdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously think that KState is an “Above Average” Big Man away from being a Final 4 Team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is for everyone putting in the hard work. The blood, sweat, and tears. The key word in all of this is YET. Kee… https://t.co/DAdSlB8pRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nunya_bzznass @shannoncoulter @MeredthSalenger @Twitter It's far more insidious than that, sadly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell @lbthehype you don’t need lotion when you have drip for sale 🙄🤣 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/QhZP3tsSUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to save you guys some time. This is a garbage article that promotes reverse racism.  You’re welcome.  How… https://t.co/SZos76FVMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellehall_az @emilyygraaace Me chase Austin And Emily can’t do much damage ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assigned to G leauge 17x is hilarious to me. Still looks like a harder worker than most NBA players but I cant figu… https://t.co/yzSZ5NexK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! I woke up out  my sleep and this sharp ass pin his still on my back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylynch44 great man who has brought so much to the area! It's been a pleasure to get to know you over the years… https://t.co/eK5KwTmzjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaactregzz Aguaaas la finales se juegan miercoles y sabado ... o jueves y domingo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janilovesyou2 Research Directory: [ https://t.co/oBlviLa18k ] --- open to find the truth.  SiteAdvisor Cleared Safe To Browse]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here is another example of why Dems shouldn't rush to hold a debate on Fox News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greenbush Brother Benjamin on tap now. https://t.co/otuIrGMPS6 @Greenbush_Brew #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching old episodes of @QueerEye before the new season. My favorite is the one with @hjj122 and the boys from Cov… https://t.co/blTbFJAhj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers She is absolutely 100% right. Thank you Senator Flowers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The walls are crumbling. You’re now being held accountable. Boom 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing piece of theatre. Run, don’t walk, to a production near you!!  #comefromaway @ The Smith Center https://t.co/CIlwOGmLLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteforWoodward @ImmoralReport @federalreserve Correct.  We should have stayed with gold backing.  Looks like ther… https://t.co/0b7TcrOkYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[my instagram story:  ______________ ______________  jessica's story when it's her bff rachel's birthday from kappa… https://t.co/lBBy92XVbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifeboy @homelaber @myinthtayaung92 @porterdeleon You got this Rohan! #vCommunity  and @DCVMUG supporter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning.. Breakfast at The Oakkroom from 10 am .... Follow up with Lunch.. #oakkroom @ The Oakk Room https://t.co/s60S29rz2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Skonie Skoop   Police Officer Charged With Illegally Making, Selling Guns https://t.co/Lvh3nyCpCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mabey its better for me to go back to Desoto  or Juárez to find myself again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it difficult to believe that it is only one party I believe it’s both parties paying off with Our Monies. We… https://t.co/klFo3fP0Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snickersmarathon2019 @Runnergirl1972 @ Albany, Georgia https://t.co/9AHeWqvJYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@archinect I can't imagine any #architect NOT working more than 40 hours a week! #BoomOrBust, we're either overload… https://t.co/tkCfDcV2an]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherhobbyist @thisisalabama @spann @ObjectivityRach @perkinsphotos1 @MaggieWZDX @sbowerswx @simpsonwhnt Great pics 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHippieFarmer @principal I get it when you're cold you're grumpy. Makes sense now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregorCraigie @CBContheisland Canadians should simply stop filling in forms that cater only to U.S. residents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2006 Boys - Today's practice has been moved Monday March 11th @ 6:05 pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me in room 9ABC at 12:30pm to hear about the #EndOfKilling ! #SXSW2019 https://t.co/78w6koqFkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que bonito sería que alguien te dedique el cielo en su atardecer en lugar de canciones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 ain’t slowed down yet for me and I’m not about to lose this momentum....]]></document><document><![CDATA[#professormikey  007  #life #work #happiness #DIY #philosophy @ Coffey Park https://t.co/XlFld1eAp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRHLofficial When you have something of value to say, let me know. #MAGA SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man responsible for my new JFK Harvard Red pen — and the woman who created him! @ OMNIA Nightclub https://t.co/ybbSVvWfk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koinosuke @renfamous That’s logical. Though I can’t help but think why one would need to be informed about anythin… https://t.co/A3xYPGwJAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realized those results weren’t in order after 5th. Official ones 👇🏽 https://t.co/jLuUyQS8k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InvestSportsIRA @michael162002 @GamblingCleanUp Yes...better question is why are u paying a tout....follow… https://t.co/VJ0jrtRsBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who thinks trumps wall is a bad idea, I bet I can change your mind, hit the dm’s or if your brave hit that reply]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day in Horseshoe Bay, TX at Summit Rock Golf Club! Thanks so much for the hospitality! #SwordsUp ⚔️⚔️ https://t.co/8UYeoHbZPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A throwback for #greengoddess #dressing &amp; fried #portabella   #cookingphoto @ The Waters https://t.co/MHwjFDBJ1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEliza2 @gypsyglutton @CynChamplin @MikeroHonky @HamLibertarian @bigolfoot @Merica_Media 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentTrumpSuggestionBox  Quit now! The longer you stay in office,  the more prison time you'll get and the more you'll lose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As More Electric Cars Arrive, What's The Future For Gas-Powered Engines? https://t.co/uXqzIISuUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going down tonight @GramercySm at 830pm as I takeover hosting #AntiheroTrivia for @Decker6. COME ON OUT AND… https://t.co/7N1iZvRIft]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THE LITTLE BRO! Haha here’s a few tbts love you bro. Keep grinding and working hard!! @J_Smitty31 https://t.co/gAqk6ZBuny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Dump Trump!  Or Trump dump? 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🙂🙂🙂 https://t.co/lbRelPn57F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great local breakfast spot.  #LatePost #LateShare  #Pixel2XL #TeamPixel #TeamAndroid #PhoneByGoogle #MadeByGoogle… https://t.co/3XDDJdr61G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel sorry for this pathetic human being EMBARRASSMENT IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE WORLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hels *extreme podcaster voice* so they're a sponsor, but I have to say, I got a pair of Bombas for Christmas and t… https://t.co/EjdfyeC29U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin @HebertEnergy   Nobody is better than you. Get Amazon here and bring our children home❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaComtesseJamie I love iceberg lettuce but only for wedge salads. I used green leaf lettuce (a wholly unhelpful na… https://t.co/e9m4z4Xcel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdmomglitter @YoniFreedhoff @Medscape @Medscape should #RetractWeightBias now. Editor-in-Chief @EricTopol can ch… https://t.co/NUlKwdELAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipcoffey i’m glad i live in california close to the queen mary nothing like that here not saying we have our sha… https://t.co/7xWt2BzHWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepting the challenge by @jetzfan34 , @nphs_tech , and @hermannteaches2 to post covers of 7 books that I love. No… https://t.co/5YwouE6IMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick af right. Made a ridiculously large pot of chicken stew. This warmed my heart. #servant #periodt @ Koreato… https://t.co/WOoGAJnSKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curtis is ready to represent the @MCCmagi  at state Poetry Out Loud! #pol19 https://t.co/7ALBL59hVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @CNN I stopped a long time ago.  They continue to give all the wrong people air time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/wjGxFgXalL]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Forsyth (4A) is looking for an assistant football coach. Have possible openings in all areas except PE. Specif… https://t.co/hlTxbL7aY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come by GamePlay Space to get an early look at our game #OnTheFlipSide this Thursday! Looking for all feedback :) https://t.co/ZkcKndJV0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are here! Work as Worship Retreat @ Preston Trail Community Church https://t.co/aqSHY4MC92]]></document><document><![CDATA[People here meeting you for the first time will always be like “Matt who?” like they’re trying to get your family h… https://t.co/I2CnoLGKd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinstonKelley Now don’t sell yourself short like that - @AllWaltrip tells me weekly how lucky I am to WORK FOR YOU! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! Our educational strategies MUST adapt to reach the current generation of students. Anything that is not… https://t.co/jMeCXFmPco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blueberry Maple Pancake by @EBCwny at @EBCwny — https://t.co/wvGZhQxl5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recomiendo mucho #los43 en @netflix ! No entendía bien todo lo de #Ayotzinapa hasta que vi el documental. Da miedo… https://t.co/HA3m42lTZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniiiella Ha surtout quand ton coeur est comme ce qui est dans ton dos là]]></document><document><![CDATA[All them Baw in the group wanna talk about is how they gon cut up at the Cro parade...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son drew me a picture of 1 of our favorite players. Haven’t heard his name in the news lately. Here’s to hoping… https://t.co/5efadiBu6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot wait until ours comes in 😍 Ready to get to work w/ BOTH the hitting Rapsodo and the pitching Rapsodo to help… https://t.co/h9oxxNLX4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Checks and balances. It is time that the Palestinians had a voice in this country. Netanyahu essentia… https://t.co/2psP6tJdS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on this Memoir’s been kicking my butt.   Writing isn’t as cathartic as people think.   When I’m putting thi… https://t.co/HRWKcZjBXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta bandida #PatriciaLinares es parte de la justicia transiciónal impuesta por los terroristas Cubanos, Venezolano… https://t.co/whH9o7yWzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memo to @ESSVote where is this crook employee of yours and where are the hacked voting machines?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuallyYours6 @ActionCapNCrunc @baseballchickie Sorry to hear that. I hope you find one. I'm an animal lover too… https://t.co/2JzPTecO94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chulaconcntida Buenos días Gaby Chula, que tengas un excelente miércoles 😀🌷🌹🌺. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when you thought I was average, now I wake up and  I fuck on a bad bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martin Tyler, Alan Smith, #MUFC #UefaChampionsLeague come on @ManUtd @ManUtdUSA Ole!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DMVelite Nations Classic All-Star Event https://t.co/nF5WAvIDUY #DMVhoops https://t.co/6RPXUkxZ1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I about to run a 70ft Ethernet cable from my Xbox to my router? Bet your ass I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great week for the #LesWaldenRealEstateTeam #CallOurTownHome https://t.co/ZtEK1lDqc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can get better of you don't keep trying. #TeamNoBoundaries #TeamSkysTheLimit #Entrepreneur #BeYourOwnBoss… https://t.co/4DmjDa2gy1]]></document></documents></author>