<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If I were I--Wind  If I were I I would trust my instincts and move like the wind With excitement and wonder  Foll… https://t.co/j05vOzdvRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@InDTaleMagazine Think you know me? https://t.co/PAwmWBKHat via @peggy_jaeger #amblogging #romancewriter… https://t.co/4VreC2PCCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got into an argument with the town loser on BC fb page so hows your day 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @LAustyanJulian @IvankaTrump Happy to serve, sir. Tweeted a few minutes ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up and never knew my dad good/but still blew up to become a big bag 💼 wolf 🐺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAllGrady @CBS_42 Thank you for this! Glad to hear you’re liking/utilizing that new ramp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demon_EmeraldN @LaNoireDe @ahn_dray_uh @DrewskieC where did the fbi say cpd made anything up? all the fbi said was… https://t.co/bhiUuLBVBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's do this, @HooverLadyBucs!  🧡🖤 #RoadtoRedemption  #StateFinals https://t.co/1zkKvTrgvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to make an amendment and I’m a bit embarrassed that I left my bestie off the list. She gave me the chance to… https://t.co/YVF7B3fAK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amanda is coming over so we can go workout and we’re actually going to be those girls at the gym with matching gyms… https://t.co/l2x6ek3Npw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update didn’t forget about my life BUT I’ve been playing Sims 4 since I got home at 9:15. Good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linda Coopman is moving back to UTS Bloor to rejoin the Finance Dept. We will  miss you at Humbert!  Please visit. https://t.co/wqr41OS8yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[uppercrustsantafe TONIGHT, 6-9pm! #SantaFe @ Upper Crust Pizza https://t.co/H9kulH1aPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CUWcommission @ClemsonUniv @FacultySenateCU @CUStaffSenate @InsideClemson @ClemsonPrez I’ll be there! Can’t wait - I love a GNO! 💃🐯💃🐯]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy womens day if any man talks to me today besides my bf they will be fined $500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle yesterday was Rare Disease day where was those black and white stripes? https://t.co/mF3RBalFvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTKNet Geez AOC the American people are sick of you Dems/libs wasting our hard earned money on games like "where's… https://t.co/biptgtuJLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was driving, listening to the Jonas Brothers, and crying when Ryan calls. He hears I’m crying and is like “WHAT”… https://t.co/HTAtSwcfUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same people who are condemning @IlhanMN are the same people who’ve stayed quiet when Trump is OPENLY racist☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivianethewitch @miracletbs To quote Ron Reagan, "...not afraid to burn in hell!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InnerCircleGod1 @SBassettjr I just saw them that’s why and now I don’t care and I’m over it. You don’t have to see… https://t.co/YOUnNeTViO]]></document><document><![CDATA[😁❤️ Reminds me of our @SpheroEdu hallway maze that became a STUDENT maze at @SandburgD205 in the basement hallway,… https://t.co/JNiPNUrAYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[kicked the weekend off with completing my solo flight time!!! can’t wait for a sick photoshoot, going out w my girls &amp; skiing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beautiful @NatalieMNBC @NatalieMNBC with me, our amazing Board Member Sarah and Development Director Alexa. Nat… https://t.co/v153AWZlfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @blakeshelton for an awesome concert! You rocked Tampa#country#redneck#evertimeihearthatsong @ Amalie Arena https://t.co/mCIUhB81ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you go to your aunts house to visit, and she disappears. Awkward lmao someone pissed her off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your wall isn't being built!!!  Repairs are being done to fences already up... You open your mouth… https://t.co/cVLY3Qlc6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[What student group is most in need of physical security on American college campuses simply for speaking?   ⚪️ Wome… https://t.co/DaZH9wcOiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran out of binder gifs that didn’t include Mitt Romney. https://t.co/7Krqqz09oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are indecisive AF and make all the snacks you've wanted for a week as dinner.    #egghole #jalapenopoppers… https://t.co/9kG4GnfqoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrayHealourland @LarrySchweikart There are a lot of Democratic”voters”who manage to cast ballots post mortum]]></document><document><![CDATA[AL BORDE DE LA LOCURA y EL DIARIO DE UN FRACASADO, de José Losada @joselosada86 https://t.co/w1EORN4BIW… https://t.co/IK1lc2jqrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadiesLoves_ @marlenrey05 @PumpkinButt458 @grandegarza @JeffreeStar @claires It doesn’t bother me that the second… https://t.co/JSsSH72SL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ePatientDave @JoeBabaian @jhoronjeff @GraceCordovano @Colin_Hung @nickisnpdx @RasuShrestha @IrmaRaste… https://t.co/J7v1kyVwYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexa, play Glamorous by Fergie. 💜🖤 📷 bycristiancarranza @southerncity  #SCFF19 #SouthernCityFilmFestival… https://t.co/cS1jGDrD9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Krm Hussein @KrmHussein  for retweeting my poem! Happy day friend!💙💓💚 https://t.co/vvoMukRwR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling celebratory today! #pizzaartista #swampdaddy #yumyum @ Pizza Artista https://t.co/VbyRiM9iA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dickdbodine @gclarktweets2 @StonedHelton I read mikes comments and he handled it better than me would have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi friends! I’ve decided to go vegan and I know it’s going to be difficult but I want to really go through with thi… https://t.co/b8ny3OCM45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canibud @The_White_Moss @walkawaylib @JimmyDriscoll @BettyBowers @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Go smoke a… https://t.co/0N99jkwwsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious @KingHeadChester brunch! #latergram #SantaMonica #British @ Ye Olde Kings Head https://t.co/MncvxIXBW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KamalaHarris Still no apology to @POTUS nor to his supporters, no ownership of her "modern day lynching" comment,… https://t.co/w5LsR8D3h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it reasonable to make a 31 year old diva the highest paid WR in the NFL?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending this special day with these lovely fellas! Don’t mind the photo bomb 😂 #MidAtlanticNR #winninginwalmart… https://t.co/ltBBJbLMb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomOnWarpath @richeisen @UnderArmour #RunRichRun is my favorite addition to the #NFLCombine, such a great cause, e… https://t.co/ZbWnAlbQTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A note on finding light and love - - and of giving both to yourself in these winter months. Coming up on the final… https://t.co/MiQUYKcP0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am also a film 🎞 producer and executive producer and executive director. 75% of my job is raising money for my nonprofit @HerStoryChicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyaDevilleWWE @itsBayleyWWE @SashaBanksWWE @WWE_MandyRose Im happy for them but you guys were robbed deff need re match]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rented and watched  A Simple Favor,   #aviationgin needs to come to Columbus, Ohio ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoutherngyrlRhi I loooooove me some priyanka. I had to check someone for calling her paprika https://t.co/Z2kl305Ikr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cuz you haven’t moved on.. I mean I get the point but still.. move on.. cuz you’re never going to connect with… https://t.co/6lETiOOkPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impromptu haircut. #100daysinthelifeofanactor #saltandpepper 💇 Off to @pollysfollies @ New York, New York https://t.co/Nmuw6OwrUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babyhotsauce @EllzBelz12 Love love love @babyhotsauce ! Perfect addition to @ElvisDuranShow ! Completely agree wit… https://t.co/iCN0v987OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Will The New AG Protect Donald, as he believes the AG should serve the President, and be loyal to only him… https://t.co/remqFsb5uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleDula @ashtonpittman Interesting. “The small group of accounts that troll the duchess often retweet news arti… https://t.co/XbBr94MmEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok lady who brought her own PORTABLE SPEAKERS to the gym to play terrible music... who tf do you think you are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LinkedIn for featuring my resume writing course as part of the. #LinkedInLearning campaign. To those of… https://t.co/asq5twrAvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Malakoff Tigers defeat Johnson City 4-3 in the Blanco Tournament this past weekend! @BNations313 @MalakoffHS… https://t.co/zUFSQrtn8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarangVipin I’ve been wondering: shouldn’t have Trump known going into this that NK was going to make demands that… https://t.co/9trTjPW9O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I think my manager thinks that I don’t have a life or go to school outside of work and just thinks that I… https://t.co/jlUB2neWHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@visit_temecula Where is that chocolate confection from in Temecula??? I need that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So 7:30 this morning I sat in traffic for an hour and a half to get to work instead of the 15 minutes that it usual… https://t.co/C829CG9tiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox We landed in Los Angeles from Heathrow on Tuesday and the situation was the exact same here....border… https://t.co/NZn1nNarMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[H/T to da @chicagotribune and whoever names their classes. 😂 Chicago through and through. https://t.co/52cm8KxYP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoSunDevils @ASCDconf Bummer! I’m looking forward to it as I’ve never been to this national conference. It will be… https://t.co/QSVDMzGslX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews Someone better tell the Patriots and Kraft that they probably have tapes ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m conscious that it’s a very charged and very emotional time and it’s a time that is volatile. I think that thea… https://t.co/laUpbY8kIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone ever drank their parents alcohol as kids and then had to water it down so they wouldn’t notice it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ruins of Gorlan by John https://t.co/SoyP4SSoce via @wordpressdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[eu não to olhando mais quanto de dinheiro q eu tenho na conta p eu não me desesperar rsrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever look at someone and want to cry thinking they were ever heartbroken at one point? bc same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my feelings... blame it on #MJLive  #valentine #weekendbliss #lasvegas #thankyou @ Top of the World Restaurant https://t.co/NXdgxadsg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Price_Morgan @JayLColwell Maybe she will actually throw flowers at your wedding..... 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Spike Lee never mentioned you.  Did the message get under your skin?  🍼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naturechronicle Lovely, Julie! You could focus that first line on the voice by leaving off "the" (haiku usually es… https://t.co/i2trI0KeXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels Thank you for your Daily Words of Wisdom and Blessing! God Bless and Keep You!]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey are you really this good, damn are you really this good - baby, you’re just like a drug, I’d bottle you up if I could]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current mood: Toasty warm toes. mysavinggraceboutique your booties go with *everything*  Also: resisting temptation… https://t.co/EKJE4AhQ1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepSouthAly We used to move a friend’s car during the night in college. Totally messed with his mind. Suggestion:… https://t.co/NOPLeIT1zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably one of the tastiest shrimp cocktails I have had https://t.co/cXaS0F6qpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A relatively simple fix could allow us to return to requiring disclosure from groups that primarily exist to influe… https://t.co/T9artFm3yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to get something off my chest. I actually LOVE Mondays. The fresh start, the productivity, all around… https://t.co/o3YLG0JMhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the second time I have accurately guess someone’s moon/rising in the past week. i am so powerful]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Winter is on my head, but eternal spring is in my heart.” ~ #victorhugo #latergram from #yesterday in #dc… https://t.co/Ifv2g1b8Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the days are starting to stay lighter a little longer! Perfect end to a really fun day....more on that real so… https://t.co/c2fOmZ6QoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tony_sabol @MysteryCr8tve You keep on insisting you’re so smart. You wouldn’t have to insist so much if it were tr… https://t.co/o0Yr9lTxwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear people who don’t wear headphones while blasting terrible music in public places: STOP.  Sincerely, Everyone else on the planet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram stays making me shook at the fact that 17 yr olds nowadays are prettier than I’ll ever be 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been to Prague and would love to go back. It’s so pretty and an interesting place to visit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evawut @DearAuntCrabby @SusanCJenkins @funder @RepMattGaetz @mattgaetz @BillClinton This is sex trafficking. A little different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She should be impeached.  How dare the Dem whip say Omars experience is worse and more painful than the holocaust.… https://t.co/pFpnZi3BvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica In some, alternative, #EarthTwo, Lil', @MeghanMcCain, was "supposed-to-be", #FirstDaughter? If the… https://t.co/KMVfX7frip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyGreenMC  hey DEP, Spring is 2 weeks away. How about some tweets about safer, organic lawn care? like a daily twe… https://t.co/LnB7fk9XI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh great. Now Owen’s going at Amelia like this is her fault. Which it’s not. It’s the mother’s fault for being a be… https://t.co/9Jc9vq2oSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainbow bright in a slip dress 🌈 @ The Hoxton, Portland https://t.co/yXdKwY1Ux0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eileenjforrest @sophyish @bonappetit Holy shit thank you for bringing this into my life. I LOVE tuna melts. https://t.co/ALVCmNZNlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWB_Steve666 Hi! It won’t be, but it is available online with worldwide shipping! :) https://t.co/Y0nGLd7LVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krissymaecagney i wouldn’t say this is your tough side. just your honesty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rejuvenating delight and honor to listen to @SoundOfLifeMedi, @WSMV_Forrest, and Michael DelGiudice, to speak wit… https://t.co/jMioGqoWaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[first of all it takes me hours to actually get up and prepare (bc i don’t wana go anyways) then when i actually do… https://t.co/P7o0pCIC23]]></document></documents></author>