<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Proud of being married to an amazing woman, Temis Coral (@DukeEnvironment MEM ‘19) recognized as an Emerging Leader… https://t.co/GG2f9GWhKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN REMEMBER WHEN CNN FAKED A WAR REPORT TO HELP BUSH ATTACK IRAQ? https://t.co/QyvbzAq1Rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole country wants justice. We all want the most severe punishment—sentence for Paul Manafort. He betrayed our Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing my pianist hat today! Accompanying the Bruch Violin Concerto in g minor today at the Beckett School… https://t.co/CBFYAKDPO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a good talk with @DKMcDonald1 I am beyond EXCITED to announce I have received my fourth Division I football O… https://t.co/SiVY0vAs57]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Marathon Continues 🏁 @ Crenshaw and Slauson https://t.co/5N83Os0Q4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dude at the bar tonight was in the way so the bouncer pointed the flashlight on him to move him.... homie thou… https://t.co/N9v1gYPBf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your natural waves/curls fly!!! . . . . . . . #alexszoenyi #hair #wavyhair #curlyhair #2ahair #pelo #selfie… https://t.co/diaDMsFeb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jibril_SenpaiVR @IshimaruVR @Teckiies "THIS SUMMER, ISHIMARU IS...  PRECINCT OF PAIN.  STOP RESISTING."]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to protect our children:  Republicans: we shouldn't murder unborn babies, but we can at least agree we shouldn'… https://t.co/1WKM4TLaUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randykjo @RealMattCouch Probably will happen that way but that doesn't put them in jail and if they don't go goodbye America?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel Poor Pathetic Trumpublicult Followers. Your Cult Leader takes a Shit and You Brainles… https://t.co/OuiAL1bPDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud @theblaze @glennbeck @WorldOfStu Well, you are a no good, POS ... ;) I enjoyed listening to your interview yesterday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@descendants Do hope the hair is fiery and fierce hahahaha 😈 #hades #D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is so kind of you to say, Elizabeth. I hope it answered some lingering questions.  https://t.co/WzHbU4X948]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its almost Friday gente!!!! Hope all of you had a great day but most importantly, an awesome week! #tbt #2011… https://t.co/zweWenn7rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Meat Plant job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Gold Canyon Meat Sh… https://t.co/cQdfgqMkrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey i hate girls i’m neither gay nor straight nor asexual i’m literally just a human that is all goodbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo John McClane #BruceWillis #DieHard #YipeeKiYayMotherF*cker]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sooo fucked up lastnight. Fucking with cartier, know we had like 6 or 7 henny drinks last night🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to see @_Youngbull23 in as a Gator on Saturday’s. This man is gonna be a problem.   #GoGators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Friday my old friend, this fricking week’s ‘bout to end. Time for the sound of silence!  🎉🎈🎊 Just kidding....… https://t.co/yftK7Nufic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illplayit @MaggiBot @G2Summit Of Forum, I mean. Lou, we played Carpe Diem at Diversions at Kimberly's New Years thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetChizone @Nicole_Cliffe I was so lucky to have these bookstores availavle when I came. I made a similar call,… https://t.co/v6rQ5u0lAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Steel Beach Picnic by Crossed Cannons Brewery at @mcnellies_okc — https://t.co/sMUH8wS3xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone care? Go back to your gaudy tower and stay there fake first lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same for me, only 1992 for Dactyl Nightmare instead of ‘91. It was scary having someone running at you shootings at… https://t.co/SzFA3sEurd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @CConcern @AntisemitismEye So Christians aren’t allowed in England anymore! Ain’t that something, Screw… https://t.co/OhTegHeeel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByMHarrington There is so much wrong, we just have got to the goalies just yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pt https://t.co/eO4A7aK2PH by @br (though Brenda might have a better answer for specifically 9-11 year olds!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I turn around when these high schoolers back talk to me.. https://t.co/xm38RzFLXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's In For 2020: Bernie Sanders Is Running For President Again https://t.co/Y28tQPWcnd @vprnet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frozenflamekid It’s not flattering but I thought he came across as incredibly human. It felt realistic to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 years ago #HouseRepublicans deemed #BillClinton’s lying about an affair constituted “high crimes and misdemeanor… https://t.co/6zIEIMGYiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I feel like you are a wild woman.  I think that you need to use less ten dollar words.  If you don't… https://t.co/Y7B3FJcFro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport For the ungodly amount of $$$ you charge for your phones. You think you cheapskates can build a bette… https://t.co/YMYzhbNz1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kupcake_189 @utahjazz @spidadmitchell Nah, we sat by his mom and sister, and he gave them to his sister tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took my Twitter ignorance to Instagram y’all think that’s the place for that or nah? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when the ball gets stuck between the rim and backboard... Call on Coach McNight to sprint in from the… https://t.co/iTXSmqGiae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blake0986 @nowthisnews Yeah, this kid is sure to get into Hillbilly U.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbird765 That's RIDICULOUS! It should never take that long to execute a convicted killer! 🤬These lawmakers need to… https://t.co/QswNYS4vcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connect with us by dialing our #GmailHelplineNumber and get quick access  to #GmailHelp where our highly skilled ex… https://t.co/xCBgDPar1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[An American without papers, you dumb desgusting bastereds, DACA are Americans, deport a person for 1 DUI, thousands… https://t.co/3USrO17feY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiaJaxWWE Real talk Nia,  I don't think @brielarson wants that smoke with you at #Wrestlemania .  #CaptainMarvel c… https://t.co/h2B59RB9PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone looked into why it’s called Canadian bacon when it’s clearly Ham??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartCollector @markboone219 @MapoTofuAddict @peterjhasson @MeghanMcCain So they’re ok with other hateful rhetoric is what you’re saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanJory @DollarShaveClub Cancel now and buy the blades direct from @razorsbydorco   You’re welcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddUnzicker @RichardsJim @shane_pruitt78 @_SBTC @whosyour1_ Wish you were here bro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5chw4r7z I think the feeling is more reflective and pensive than sudden and abrupt, if that makes sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WingfieldNFL Schedule is already tough next year. Have drafted well last few. Established a young core of solid pl… https://t.co/DjoHuYnenz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaybirdsound @OldWarrior1950 @Jamierodr10 @JudicialWatch @MelGibsonFilms @USSFSupplyMole @DefconDefense @Pontifex… https://t.co/2K3XjRYCD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the money her family has she needs to get them teeth fixed ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocBees @WayneEstopinal If that comes it would be a patch and not part of the rendering on a board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLaraki @IngrahamAngle @CraigSBPA FYI "Dr" Laura: #Cruz not only lost the Presidency but the GOP nomination with… https://t.co/9jR4YzOc8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARQUINNBOOKER I’ve seen like three pictures/videos of you tonight from Hump Night]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@YubaSheriff is recruiting volunteers to work in key departments. Use your spare time to help build a safer commun… https://t.co/AYCNEf9OxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just went to the xbox store thinking i would buy ANTHEM because you KNOW i am gonna have stuff to say about it. w… https://t.co/8A2msmCMZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyPuente I’m not happy at all cause I’m a groundhog guy and my groundhog lied about early spring 😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanPreece_ @NASCAR @MonsterEnergy That was actually 11 years ago, but we didn’t train you to be a mathematician.… https://t.co/aynWme6CJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bye bye #AirbusA380 this was unfortunately predicted. #endof380 @Airbus #a380]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZiadFazel @ClarineMacaraig @dmrider Those are so good. We need some Toronto film talent to make something similar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLinda63 @sgtjanedoe @missheidi I'd like to see States take the lead on this issue. But that's good to know - app… https://t.co/DPVRzaLGOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate rooting, flashing, installing apps and updating Android devices just to find out the ROM sucks. It's so tedious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My second co-host on #Daybreak is sleeping. Am I putting him to sleep?? Hahaha. #kmas #ifiberonenews #shelton… https://t.co/iyUy1fKn5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas can’t really be mad frfr😂we ain’t gettin no hoes or scholarship off this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I’m going to have to take one of Jackson’s in.This is especially bothersome since this is my workhorse instru… https://t.co/WwBvWkAyi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hella cuties gunna be showing up here in an hour. Can’t wait to meet them 😍😍😝😘🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Lies, bullshit and censorship.. The same thing I’ve always expected and why I do not use that platform at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel really bad, I truly do! But to solve any problem you have to fix the root cause and that’s the greedy social… https://t.co/1MO6P17Qug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriqtscott @Boyd_2650 If you are white and a Democrat, what are you thinking? That party doesn't like you, doesn… https://t.co/FpelgAPbH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is becoming way too common. #hospital #appendectomy #surgery 🏥💉💊 @ Kaiser Sunset Hollywood https://t.co/xvhhutADl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 400 members at my club and we get questions everyday. It’s not about the rule but the penalty. My member vio… https://t.co/G75RvZgeXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I change my mind @KenWebsterJrSho. I will not sell my life blood to the highest bidder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good lord, @Interscope is absolutely shameless about product placement in their music videos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrecianFormula Anyone who claims to have predicted “no deal,” would have to pretend they anticipated Trump’s irrit… https://t.co/XkOBVt6AA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL - adding the concept of unsecured bank debt ($1k loan, $100 vig per turn) significantly increases the fun (and… https://t.co/e2TgR49MkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnniesPride @Men2Red @bvan0912 @NYPost_Brazille @Chris_J_Rod @nyfanin2ndcity @dfends_com I mean there are absolu… https://t.co/MZnY1NqQW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to add this one the other night. GOODBYE, MR. CHIPS https://t.co/GPTifaJ0Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀(7) Batavia vs (2) Newark - Class B1 Semifinal - @SecVBBasketball   •Batavia 34 Newark 29 - 4:38 3Q  •Blue Devils… https://t.co/4wMKC2iTpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staging the crime scene. Staging the crime scene. Don’t think his jury will buy that bull.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining in with the rachetivities #AODMondays #ReleaseYourInnerRatchet (@ Ace of Diamonds LA | AOD in West Hollywoo… https://t.co/pCPKbXhErP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Weeks asked a question, "when was your last time before a judge, and what happened?"  I had no idea when I star… https://t.co/ZD77ohXezc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concierto  #DevotionalDave  Depeche Mode experience  1 de marzo de 2019 Little Rock    #LuisFelipeGaspar #Concierto… https://t.co/lzOznlmE9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Cohen is trying to prevent himself from becoming someone's wife in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been busy = I don’t want to talk to you but I’m being nice and lettting you know that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A Free press is NOT the enemy. Those who oppose it are. Stalin,Hitler, Mao, Pol Pot, Putin, your b… https://t.co/hh8xz3Pg7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanamendoza10 @chihuastequiero @ComalesLaVillit Josephine trupiano is the one useing the main frame stolen fron… https://t.co/ibki5zUekB]]></document><document><![CDATA[💃🏻🕺🏻 Danny Jr. is giving very informative, step by step, dance lessons to his Aunt @katcontii right now!… https://t.co/TYtCVJ3RXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[More pics at napoleon444 's battle at crossroads @ Cambridge Armory https://t.co/TI7GDcXpmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CambridgeHS1 well done this year bears , tough loss , but what a game! And what a great group of young men to watc… https://t.co/N5NcwRbEAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMutisi If anything else, the enemy of Zimbabwe is ZANU-PF. They have presided over incompetence, corruption, scan… https://t.co/Q7Dr2HmO14]]></document><document><![CDATA[This night was astronomical! @trvisXX 🚀 #traviscott #AstroworldTour #ASTROWORLD https://t.co/UX3g1wA4Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if people actually like my snaps lmaooo like they’re dumb af 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Let them and their sorry illegal alien parents go home and stay there‼️‼️‼️😤😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tysonpara @williamlegate @EastTillman @gaywonk @TuckerCarlson These are the Hillary Clinton crybabies, The double… https://t.co/WNxg8OPCEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️… https://t.co/fvQf8t0ziR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnkleSilk I do that after work and have been for years. Almost as if I’m separating work from home...sometimes I s… https://t.co/2z6xYHkT1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last 2 times I try to search for an opponent. 🤦‍♂️ https://t.co/gwuYbe27vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet You don’t know much about how SS actually works, do you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working late on a Saturday night. #8 sold. Onto #9. #artcollector #artcollection #printsavailable #interiordesign… https://t.co/XNmsdJD5uP]]></document></documents></author>