<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @EdHarrisMusic @ccassiypaige @KorieAnne1 @franniesings2 @muz4now @Thornebow @MattBoydston… https://t.co/eXpAU9QKLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good idea to relate the #SDGs with popular culture like #StarTrek. Nice read on #sustainable #development #goals.… https://t.co/2BSrxhIIDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judicial Watch: Senate Ethics Committee Gives Sen. Cory Booker a Pass for Purposely Violating Rules to Try to Torpe… https://t.co/Q9HTNdrj3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEBigE You are a star ⭐️ and don’t you ever forget it I’m very disappointed but if they listening to us… https://t.co/i3W5q8lUYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDanielFirst Love that you let Ss set their own goals and monitor their progresss!!! You are so wonderful for the… https://t.co/tZIflgitf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pangolins are the world's most trafficked mammal because consumers believe that their scales possess healing prope… https://t.co/8qUK6iTx3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pollackpelzner Did you really accuse "Mary Poppins" of racism? If you did, you are an idiot, insane, and should be… https://t.co/47QkKbuehT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grizzlies @GTGrizzlyBears Jumped their ❤️❤️out  this morning at Jump Rope Contest. Way to gooo...  #3rdgraderocks… https://t.co/BWQdUaVrbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I don’t have to be the bad guy today because they made the call to cancel things last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriMoreno @DivaVinophile @VisitSeattle @_drazzari @GailBenzler @jflorez @GrnLakeGirl @SeattleBlgrs @wawinereport… https://t.co/15W1OggXqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna pic with @_delconte tonight at the game 🏀🤟🏼 https://t.co/Il1txJW5eE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuigalLodi @PPersnickety @SamJonesFBR @peaceinlife @diva_rebel @Cdubey_Texas @icrackedthesafe @Craigrm5… https://t.co/bFu4kyFWyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leigh_lmd @RealJamesWoods I would agree but unfortunately with the liberal left there may be no low.  Their slogan… https://t.co/AYME7ED2FS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RighteousDem Congratulations. Definitely time to reward yourself.  I quit over 20years ago and know the challenges… https://t.co/Bnpe7RfzmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nebush says what if that woman knew the man and he had given her a hard time before and bothered her again. He asks… https://t.co/W4fmLGWFGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know just leave shit where I put it. There’s a reason why I have a bowl of hot sauce in the living room. Leave it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMarkAwad I’m so glad you found this. I was trying to tag you but couldn’t find your twitter handle!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyskevs Beautiful!!!!! You're a natural Bob Vila https://t.co/fRFpLRFuvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: I LOVE @Jeopardy and have watched it religiously since I was a kid. I am so devastated by this news! 💔 Se… https://t.co/aGrGG4VwO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartyFreckle I’m self pubbed looking for wider reach. #apracticalguidetoawareness]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Women are predominantly affected by this disease [Alzheimer’s]...their futures depend on doctors and researchers,… https://t.co/WItlGpFjOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuluLemew @realDonaldTrump This photo, Trump’s reaction to Jeffrey Epstein/Trump buddy picture, is one of the scar… https://t.co/G9bqiOaAJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamexicana903 Hola, me podrían complacer con el nuevo sencillo de @julionalvarez #CuandoTeAmé 🎵🎶❤ @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to grandson Britton Miller and friends AND to mom n dad!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[raise your hand if you’ve ever felt personally victimized by nate zuercher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WYSIWYG2017 Lol. Yes. But it’s exhausting me. 😜.  I can see your point. BUT like I’ve “tried” to say, the power of… https://t.co/M35Bd3mPYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darker shade of hair to match the winter grays and my mood. 🤟🏼🖤   #belindacolozzi #artist #haircolor #darkbrown… https://t.co/tgQBiZ4nVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I very much appreciate this graffiti. To the point. @ MTA - Times Square-42 St Station (1)(2)(3)(A)(C)(E)(N)(Q)(R) https://t.co/iYI6zso1tY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shadowbigtail @charlessr1956 @pacelattin @pak38197 @GOPChairwoman Could be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plunder the silver, plunder the gold! There is no end of the treasure or of the wealth of all precious things. https://t.co/yAptcGjvdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MattBomer Wow...Episode 2 of @DoomPatrolDCU! Larry Trainor just has a quiet dignity mixed with his heartbreaking… https://t.co/slO7SOhSYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadChadR @TetroBro @Dic_Navis @GobAbiertoBOL @AOC Improving infrastructure and implementing new technologies with… https://t.co/WCbxhYAmsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeathersParker But not before arguing for several more tweets to try to win your argument of how “there’s nothing… https://t.co/1vn6TskjhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WonderWorkshop @BBInquirylab @LoveSciTech @kdoug_scitech we should make a elementary dash competition @SK4DL what you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah.. don’t mind me.. we just working on helping people with #epilepsy #autism and #ID   #syngap1 #RareDiseaseDay… https://t.co/rYzYvlW2qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lincolnspeedway @BrianMontieth Worth the price of admission EVERY week!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwcoastgal Cracklin Oat Bran, Honey Bunches of Oats, Honey Nut Cheerios. In that order. Yum!]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re sitting two rows off the glass for the preds/pens game that @MichaelaWood27 is gonna be here for next month so that’s cool I guess 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread. Can’t believe I’m just seeing this. It’s a MUST-READ. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness #AbductedInPlainSight   @evalois was right. It actually got worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaOt_mycat @chrislhayes @RepClayHiggins Oh yes.  My hope, too, is Stone goes to jail today. He has a gag order,… https://t.co/aom5G39XF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a rough day I can't wait for this to be over. #Bonemarrowtransplant #raregeneticdisorder https://t.co/vgUIhZAA44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our weather on Saturday.  THIS picture is so neat! #flaglercounty https://t.co/on42FOZa7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Video Game, to Spider-Verse, to Oscar-Winning Movie – Variety https://t.co/0M01wHQJVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xfilesdiaries The episode was filmed before Leonard Betts so Scully hadn’t been diagnosed yet. The order was flipp… https://t.co/Hj4YywCCQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get pancakes tomorrow and I’m so excited I could cry thinking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si hubiera pasado te paso que sigas chingando, pero ya tiene un año que sigues enfadando con lo mismo!! Ya supérame y déjame en paz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack That's something that I would expect, they are indeed the party of the KKK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrzej33430984 @JestemzWami @Mortici62754246 @Dorota_Dee @ewkapolak Nie wiem. Pewnie tyle co Schetyna. Prezio pra… https://t.co/fme484uVa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you don’t know that we can see what raunchy tweets you like and it really shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moutet Tout à fait. Et je me souviens des "dictées" empruntées à son livre Marie-Claire. Il faut espérer que "Tale… https://t.co/8bYZZG0zYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like my poetry, fav and rt it — I’m trying to build a reputation as an artist, so every share helps.   love you guys 🌙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessandboots I got keys within hours of signing at the title company...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dixon is a piece of 🐽💩 himself, takes money 💰from 🐷’s to serve himself. SHAME SHAME SHAME ON HIM for the way he has… https://t.co/39rEXnJimp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/tBihUCm8pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Love that she’s part of our country’s future. Gives me hope for my grandchildren and all citizens of our great country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dread the probable death of meal subscription kits. As a person on the autism spectrum, going to the grocery stor… https://t.co/fEyMchC7t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Prayed for new opportunities! I know they’re coming, I have faith in God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelmarixox @LKrauss1 I hear ya! It's going to be amazing. Maybe we should have a listening party hangout for the first episode!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mason_Balazs You’re crazy. I didn’t say best receiver anyways. Pure athleticism? No one comes close]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geraldo has always been a publicity seeking drama queen without respect for veracity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm thinking she doesn't go without her father months at a time so America can become a Socialist country]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar This is exactly why I would never vote for you again. Border security includes barriers where needed… https://t.co/kwTuA7U6PU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r9miles Go to the state department's website for New York and analyze the data. Schools working with Teachers Coll… https://t.co/FDvMLgl81v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@number1slacker1 That sounds like fun! I'm watching Criminal Minds. Just relaxing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouSchoolBeat @avandiver3 @Joe_Gerth Line 3 of page 13 seems to apply to new recipients.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Thank god for @sbg1 setting the record straight! We were embarrassed on the world stage!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wackyvorlon @RueNahcMohr I don't know what that is, but I'm going to faint just from how it looks]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth is that he is the national emergency.  We need to get rid of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#inthenightkitchen #buttersugarflourjoy #cakeforbreakfast #raspberry #buttermilk Recipe from smittenkitchen My fres… https://t.co/VHc4jcUP1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will my weekend house guest ever wake up? Time to play! #Hudson&amp;Nana @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/1NoBFIUx5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[FML, flight to Chicago was cancelled so looks like this Queen is stuck in New York for another day. Happy I get to… https://t.co/FARqfFDrJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lilajev @BigHitEnt @BTS_twt I’ve never been so entertained to the point of exhaustion by anyone ever! And it keeps… https://t.co/acDIye1Gdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers to @pa_rouge 💙💙💙 @MWFemmeFeline is with you!! Hugs and Prayers! #1cheerfamily 💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@librarytce @HSESchools @Daniel1Teach Thank you @librarytce! We hope to be great ambassadors for all of the incredi… https://t.co/VNBBNQNDU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare 'mega-storm' could flood dozens of cities in California, reports say  https://t.co/T68J9pKs2P It had been raining alot ahh hell nah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angiecthomas @authorMsBev Ms. Bev - wishing you a grand birthday and every day after!! https://t.co/LW14MccCAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#someonelovesme  Found this next to my Keurig this morning ❤🥰😍😌😁💌 @ Phoenixville, Pennsylvania https://t.co/j0VR0D0dtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[HERE ARE TO MORE PICS OF MY SWEET KID PIPPA  LOL ❤️❤️🧡🧡😻😻❌❌⭕️⭕️😻😻😸😸 https://t.co/QqLkERrY8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackHighberger @HannahEverman @NBCDFW @LouisNBC5 It’s finally open?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Spoiledqueen Pure aloe Vera gel! Girl I have stretch marks on my hips/butt and I’m on day 2 and I see a difference 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyofD_ @dgb0711 Thx girl. You definitely need to. I have an Eagle on my other arm carrying the Super Bowl trophy. 👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyLuvBird Oh nah , i don’t do that 😂😂 well I can’t with the type of stuff I deliver they must be ground ground is reckless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidleemurphy you put on an amazing show. Everytime!  Thank you! @JoesRosemont @OltmannsJim]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait for all the cute little old ladies to ask if I have a boyfriend today!!!! 🥰🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday X 2 to my twins who turn 16 today🎂🎂❤️❤️ https://t.co/zAiYeg1Qg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oof. So the phone was real and it was backed up by sexual hidden cam footage?! I... didn't realize this could actua… https://t.co/HHWV94DE3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who Sang The "Nessun Dorma" Climax The Best? https://t.co/gARQdIBxGc via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck Shoonhsin Li!  He volunteers for Horseheads Special Olympics Aquatics. https://t.co/jftneJcdSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @Pinterest I’m sorry if I offended u for trying to pin too many pictures of street tacos at once just please lift… https://t.co/wzoueucFbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Good morning Monday, I am #Thankful for the ability to meet with each week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um..Shoyu (soy source) and caramel might go together but adding coconut?!? @ Whole Foods Market https://t.co/8nuCkPcoFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chandlerriggs You were great on A Million Little Things!!! ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sample of Sayyid Qutb’s gripes about America: Why is football called football when they use their hands? Why is B… https://t.co/sK4XVk1W8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backt0nature @PaulLeeTicks Don't let donny jr. see this magnificent animal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonMitch None of the students want to spend spring break (or even the weekend ahead of spring break) in jail, s… https://t.co/KXaepIIDZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh NOPE!#TrumpsBandOfBandits #WHCrooksAndCriminals #LockEmALLUp #RESISTANCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st Birthday to this sweet boy 💛 Uvas brings me so much joy in life. I wouldn’t be getting through grad schoo… https://t.co/f2EKeVbYpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We aren’t all famous and disabled, so how can we help disabled young adults not become homeless?? We need solutions… https://t.co/dCYTRPmwMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyPartTwo This is very funny but also something I would not want to put in my mouth.]]></document></documents></author>