<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[All because the Maserati gets lonely without the Ferrari next to it. I mean.... sheesh, what’s a billionaire to do?… https://t.co/rTFVONrxSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing “Growing Apples to 10” in @eureka_math this afternoon! 🍎 https://t.co/xW9kFzOQMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmedicineMI @Kunzitoons @renegadestyle @AlexisBortell @EmeraldZoo @Cogitatorium @cannaworldsite… https://t.co/KwxXG27hcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotelsdotcom Mytoes are effff frozen together! Needing a thaw! #WinterSwearJar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 44% Off Blow-Dry at Studio B Salon and Style Bar https://t.co/U6mWVnkF8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JewishConnectiv My deli list just got longer!! Thanks for the recommendations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleBruton It’s the best part, like ask me to name the Murray State roster besides Ja or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I reach all matching numbers I'll post a video of me peeing since I've had at least 100 of you ask 4 it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today special guest at the station, promoting the new season of nbcgoodgirls @RenoWilson !!!! #muah #houstonmakeup… https://t.co/J9KdSaSS8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[my girlfriend is the most beautiful human on the planet. period. point blank.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my baby boy, Casey! No longer little, I’m reminded how quickly life passes by....Full of curiosit… https://t.co/noc412HBrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fixed it @AOC @RashidaTlaib @AyannaPressley #SquadGoals  💪🏽💪🏽💪🏽 https://t.co/8vT4wy4dFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk I do agree!  Our own legal citizens should be first....   my taxes are going to so many projects an… https://t.co/gUdb7A7plu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MezzoPips Right, you did mention that already. Dammit.   And yes, #UK uses same tweeting tag “#AntiquesRoadshow” O… https://t.co/99t9DNPZma]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved this @TonyRobbins quote I bumped into today: ‘The quality of our life is the quality of our relationships’… https://t.co/UvuYOAfErC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for reminding us the flexibility and twitter-reach of our actions and our impact on community!! 🤛🏼🥳✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I scored a hat trick in the #NHLHatTrickChallenge daily game. So did 36% of @NHL fans who played. https://t.co/bpCCiQfWCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmaooooooo we really drove all the way home and when we get out we realized we forgot Daniela 😂😂😂😂😂😭😭😭😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support and love one another! #internationalwomensday #womenempowerment #balanceforbetter #strengthinsisterhood https://t.co/DXJzNCa5Vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luscious__Legs That’s an eventful day, the chips &amp; salsa being the spotlight 👍🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare 'mega-storm' could flood dozens of cities in California, reports say  https://t.co/8GeEJkD5iE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening bliss #restandrelaxation #chill #vacation #noworries @ The Briars Resort &amp; Spa https://t.co/eIXZ4oLWte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJ_Cats_ @JRmarsh_all Literally what about all the campaign rallies and golf games Trump plays? Are you sure you w… https://t.co/DcLHoC7LUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppakendo LOL you was crackin uppp &amp; I wasn’t even doin anything 💀 &amp; lol i will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llpetersen1947 @debra_gm @foxandfriends My Husband and I really enjoyed Jimmy Buffet till he chose Wrong Platform!!! HE IS HISTORY!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RinChupeco What a wonderful person who didn’t just manage but build relationships and life connections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyKempson @ruthmen @Gdad1 @Falconlady7 @giselle1900 @DogCrusader @Davidkuenstle @Reynolds2G @CeylonBlue94… https://t.co/FacdikYBIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBT do you have an after hours number i can call and not be directed to an automated call?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did it .. gave him a chance &amp; his dick and mouth game still amazing til this day 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi How about th AntiSemitism going on right Under your nose!!!!😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[The despair and cynicism I am experiencing is the fact that you are seeking the Pres. nomination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideSeansHead wins the award for having THE HOTTEST girlfriend. Like damn 😍🤤🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WATCHJUNEEAT Not your average breakfast sando. The “bun” are fried eggplant slices...🤯. 📹: dantransform @ PYT https://t.co/PUHGVmuvd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcorippo @TechMikeBUSD @TosasTalkinTech @CateTolnai @cueinc @SGVCUE @TechTomBUSD @BetweentheJohns @AndersonEdTech… https://t.co/OWG2VGpzvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Shame, shame....now continue what you were doing....a slap on her hand?]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that @SubsonixOK is bringing out @Midnightasaurus for our 4 year anniversary !!! oh my god this is going t… https://t.co/x6Reeg5PpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firehouse subs is open in Oakland Park! Support our first responders by dining here. They provide a ton of communit… https://t.co/7v0dfE3XdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few detail sneak peeks. 🤪🙃 I guess this thing is happening. See you tonight at 6pm! @ Gallery 1010 https://t.co/4weye2jNc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaricadavis @TarynKelly7 @RawStory Plus, to me, he doesn’t even look like trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyy_dee_ you right!! the multiple choice freaked me out too though with all those “all of the above” &amp; “none of the above”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone interested in empty wine bottles? I have an embarrassing amount of them 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[True story at my house! I can't even take a shower without gettin yelled at! https://t.co/13AP9TJqEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTechRabbi @amber_heffner @Ryan7Read @teach42 @ShellTerrell @Rdene915 @edutechguys @mradamwelcome @k_shelton Gre… https://t.co/dZRZYeANOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eltonofficial  Thank you very much @eltonofficial  I was right by you in Portland Oregon. That's the best concert… https://t.co/sZ3sv9aRP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump @POTUS They need serious prayers. We do not wrestle against flesh and blood but a… https://t.co/KFKS1DAN3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@augustin_stacey @michaelmuhney @joshgriffith59 Stacy just read that it would be mm so I’m done I just deleted the… https://t.co/2TlwSHPG8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpd3585 @airmorris05330 He shook his hand, that’s all he’s required to do.  I’m fine with it. Stop looking for reasons to hate him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st meet of the season- @iamconnorwebb clears 6’ #lisletrack #proudmom https://t.co/ECts7woQWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 2415 Garden Falls Drive #Conroe #TX  #realestate https://t.co/G4FJy7hJmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWAnimation I did a Toothless doodle.  I cant wait for #HowToTrainYourDragon3 Counting down the days 😁 https://t.co/CMPgtwkeFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBSOnTheRun @AliOnTheRun1 Hallelujah! My two favorite podcasts coming together! 🙏❤️🏃🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much wonderful color coming to the walls of @RoyseContemp from @toofangskinny opens 2/28 6-10pm https://t.co/5KBTaWzWIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carolcorps We made it!!! @captainmarvel week is here! https://t.co/G1TCQSZo9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why I choose to read your books as well Brad Taylor and Matthew Betley all those girls kick ass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing experience! Thank you @JDRFIndiana for the opportunity to speak about #diabetes research and some o… https://t.co/CaQIbbWoSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who take break up with your girlfriend, I’m bored too seriously always have boyfriends that use 3-in-1 shower products]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if happiness is something we CHOOSE... regardless of our circumstances? - Jonathan Lockwood Huie #missysquoteoftheday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise in Cincinnati. The day after the time change is always hard. https://t.co/OBYMUlR3JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyCassyCat @AngusMcPussPuss @sharon_cantley @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @BloomNight2… https://t.co/YMCAXQAQ8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smollett should be treated the same as anyone created crime scenes, lied about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OleMissVideo @Devontae_Shuler @TerenceDavisJr @OleMissMBB I love it!!!  💙😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real GDP Growth Decelerated In The Fourth Quarter, But Domestic Demand Remains Robust https://t.co/hPrm1O6JKU https://t.co/b2gqWnyAnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkinKalmen @mhamann @justinamash @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Congress had time and did not act! It is a crisis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got jipped off by coworker for drinks after work, but what he doesn’t know is that I’ve got a case of apple orcha… https://t.co/e6A1IMsjBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always got my back... happy birthday Toni Roni! 🥰😩🎉 @ToniDee__ https://t.co/FrIUTufTuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting more irritated by the minute . Is this how you treat your customers? Let your drivers not deliver food and… https://t.co/UkNEYZYD74]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will literally get so mad and overreact about wedding stuff text or call Brandon and vent all about it then it’s… https://t.co/dzQ99xHwVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimemiserachi @JP_786 @loufrawar @wanderingstarz1 @Lovefilmz @EehHorn @heroldbarton @fevziates3 @RizzoGigirz58… https://t.co/1iCGnMLlwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the GOP blaming DEMOCRATS for things that go wrong GOP were in charge at least 2 years plus... the economy w… https://t.co/YLbdHG7BG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are in doubt, be still, and wait; when doubt no longer exists for you, then go forward with courage. So lo… https://t.co/16EEM90l7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part is just starting....living room became my gym! . . . . . #feelsgood #overit #takingmybodyback… https://t.co/As5Gyonvlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love waking up on a Feb morning to freshly-fallen snow ❄️ #freshstart (@ Up at dark-thirty… in Deerfield, NY)… https://t.co/zqKaZHVsbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlaKush420 OM Goodness @KarlaKush420 you’re more beautiful than I thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews @tarapalmeri Trying to show off? See what a biggly man he is? He's full of dog shit! And you ppl eat… https://t.co/PAwejitAIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of the day is talking to my parents on the phone and listening to all their gossip]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say unbelievable but it’s literally the most believable thing of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with LA singer, bestselling author, actress and speaker  @RosettaWalker I love making awesome friends 😍 @ B… https://t.co/NuxR2Z8vIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That @muse show was fun. Me thinks those boys may have watched Tron a few too many times. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brash_1 Met my Guy on FB. He friended me. He lived one block away from me for 13 years. Never met him. She could h… https://t.co/reCQizuJoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Matt and Aaron, You are good enough, you are smart enough, and doggone it, people like you (tiny hands and all… https://t.co/FgQronGpXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like you to know that @luisaomielan is my positive body image hero. Exhibit A: https://t.co/lBKR7LHwBI  That is all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[shininganchor you did it again! I am in love with my "NingXia gets me started, Jesus keeps me going" shirt. You too… https://t.co/9y1Sp8Beyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day to all of the amazing women I know, and the ones I don't. You all inspire me every… https://t.co/nS73eGer1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow has this game been unexpectedly boring. #ATLvCIN https://t.co/dbZlR3W0jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Not did she know compassion was a normal, human condition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always a pleasure dancing to the queen, even better when I'm alongside fellow tallies! As always,… https://t.co/xhQ6HY7xWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting Keke, Hal, Mario and Grace over the past two weeks has opened in me a space for hope that had been shrinkin… https://t.co/ir4tjkU4ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper @marcosanchezorg Thank you. You too. How are you feeling after your mini stroke?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need someone to drop the best movie recommendation to me within the next 5 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafiyahNoor1 @soledadobrien @GrettaLadygee Dead Jesus too. I bet they already waterboard Jesus if he's alive today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK who is 24 today!!! Happy Birthday Jacob Crochet!! We all love you buddy!! @HomeDepotEast @RICHARDLSEIBER1 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 https://t.co/7EI0InNuHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTechScribe I'm guessing this is your stay awake plan... https://t.co/PnkH5YU2EW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen.................Baby Birkin is IT and I’m not tryna hear otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah Clint eastwood the most trashy man to ever walk Hollywood, healer of men’s wounded egos, and symbol of “me strong man, me shoot gun”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PendantIndy @CaccioppoliMike @LeftwardSwing @CNN Do you know who funds this organization?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily This is just sad. I used to know a police officer and he said they never pull theur gun unless they intend to shoot to kill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[would threaten to boycott but obviously i don’t even believe that i deserve real food and that’s the only reason i’… https://t.co/3I6zlMHorL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being attracted to someone and someone being attractive are two totally different things but we seem to blur the lines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunningRoom @SauconyCanada @MadeinMaldia  @priya5singh  @karimreza584  @HSalvaged  @GibsonElite]]></document><document><![CDATA[So so tired. Gonna go to bed early tonight. And by that I mean trying to sleep before midnight lol]]></document></documents></author>