<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SNYtv NEW YORK BRICKS oops KNICKS  have been a embarrassment to the Tri State area for decades but they sell out… https://t.co/ichPuOyna7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this now. Wings 1980 US tour. It’s really good. They just went from The Long and Winding Road into Live an… https://t.co/k0mPgyz5rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone with information was asked to call Area North detectives at (312) 744-8263!!!  https://t.co/FiRnEJAd4I… https://t.co/uWuzR9aNld]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @NFL could learn a few things from the AAF.  Being forced to go for two just feels like the more competitive way to play the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parenting is a 24/7 job that is a career in itself.  Sitting on couch, kids upstairs, watched a successful rocket 🚀… https://t.co/Lw67HG9pLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrewCity_Jo They tryna make the playoffs and get swept by the Warriors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ain’t know I am fucking art? TALK ABOUT IT BITCH🗣 https://t.co/bjSHtyV225]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thought of going for 16 mile run or start all over to 8 miles for sunday long run😥😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duffy_ma Weird number of middle of the week snow storms. Last year they had the good taste to only knock out the occasional Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion! DAZN and ESPN has had the best fights so far this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thumbs up Listening to Around The Bend (Live) by @JBONAMASSA on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/93DBK54i8Q https://t.co/GLGhCOy9I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWBraithwaite1 @RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump And for the record. I am not a Democrat. I am a Republican who happens… https://t.co/irCVAiXGpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbtduluth we will be at today's show in Gruene, TX. Anyway you guys can work in #Wildflowers for my wife… https://t.co/7hXQZNYApD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorMBTosi @cselston @wbellauthor @Native_Shadows @CasamentoArrigo @CarolineMCook1 @wordrefiner @laineyf1… https://t.co/BPRORqGaDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a creative and engaging way to use #MinecraftEdu! Cc @SACTVDSB #tvdsbtech #tvdsb #tvdsbminecraft #tvdsblit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at the Reef Ball Saturday night. Congrats to Friends of The Environment on another year of promoting env… https://t.co/Sd8neA8VkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine meeting Prince William but it’s just your nose https://t.co/KSuHiDhA42]]></document><document><![CDATA[AD &amp; Kyle Lowry... lets hope this pickup game isn’t in the postseason]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the @Padres believe #MannyMachado is worth 10yrs-$300million...What is the @Angels @MikeTrout worth?⚾️💰💰💶💵 @MLBPAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's amazing how El Chapo is an accused pedophile and people are still rooting for him. Baffles me man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost time for Kalifornia Karl to close the curtain on February. The Valentine month was great and relaxing. It wa… https://t.co/WEY2rkyLPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies,  Fewer waist trainers No more cling wrap around your waist Less attempting to “roll off” cellulite  More...… https://t.co/1lz7yHvtIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kylorae716 Forecast after tomorrow for the rest of March is all above avg temps, then we are into April and should be fine from there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five min into @DoomPatrolDCU and I’m giddy.  @AlanTudyk @MattBomer Brendan Fraser!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been humbled more times than I’d like to admit to all of you over these past couple of years. In fact, I was h… https://t.co/DzHPfgGi9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an inch of snow on the ground in Chicago so @AmericanAir is obligated to skullfuck all of their passengers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are a servant of the People, Not "in charge." Your idea needs to be more than Ambitious, you need practica… https://t.co/cV1PLD6em3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_BOOGIE_5 Jordan is good man!  Spring ball rollin, good luck to you this season!  Enjoy all this bro!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USTA_Georgia @georgiapburdell Tech people excelling. It’s just what we @GeorgiaTech do. #TOGETHERweSWARM]]></document><document><![CDATA[2014-2015, 25-9/12-6, again 15-1 at home, Swept by BU, Swept WVU, OkSt, UT, and TCU, BigXII Champs, then the UAB disaster...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budweiserusa With the GREEN NEW DEAL, you will not be able to make Beer like you do now with out Machinery, and Tr… https://t.co/bDvqZ5C70m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the American people want Hillary Clinton and other dishonest Demacrats prosecuted so we can watch something… https://t.co/VDCbDYXkcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zhinse There are face models, but they only sometimes overlap with a characters total look.  This is absolutely fa… https://t.co/lMvOGtHjMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#peachbellini just in time for #sunday #brunch #Lip #Crave $3.99 @ https://t.co/ICQ6zfr3nn 🥂🍑 @ New York, New York https://t.co/FsLs5YNgX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not transit vs. cars. That’s the wrong model. The correct way to design a city is at the scale of human legs.… https://t.co/5TeNjLJeAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning after the Storm @ West New York, New Jersey https://t.co/LRaCPMLvTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[That same week as our pride week shoot, we met up for our third shoot. I HAD to give this photo a single post. It's… https://t.co/GpQ3KZjXQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday We were looking for some food items, &amp; Ryan knew where to go, get them. Great guy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WokeGabeWalker @bourgeoisalien @XoXo__Kellie It was an edited tape to make it look confrontational. Did you learn… https://t.co/1pZV5Moiq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome time this morning talking mental toughness in golf and sports with @hamiltonespn on @espnwestpalm !!! Make… https://t.co/ta7OKOAyxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero que seas feliz  Con la persona que tanto deseabas y me hablabas...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris There are already established procedures. Your suggestion is not it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 things I take from this memory. 1. I listened to this call by @TonyCaridi on some @SIRIUSXM Big East channel in a… https://t.co/g4oZjhXgPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beth Palmer has led the Inspired Youth Tutoring Program on #Chicago's North side since 1990s. I enjoy reading here… https://t.co/5Ih3x2aMVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danbharris  your broadcast is not till 9o’clock here in Atlanta so you’re getting my morning Yo! Now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohanBBT @cedarflats @EpicBrewing @zappafaye @lhtetrick @cellmavin @wrayzors @badhopper @bertrand_boily… https://t.co/Lf3nQi0U2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJollyFL Even if it is struck down, the power-grab itself lays down a precedent that won’t be forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @DonaldJTrumpJr McCabe, Comey, et al never thought Trump would possibly win. So they were very careles… https://t.co/WvzUj3piqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burnsville Mayor Elizabeth Kautz speaking at #IAFFLegCon touting the services of BFD! https://t.co/DlVWpnCIhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXIScott Remember the show "Gentle Ben" one of my favorites along with "Sea Hunt" and "Rat Patrol"!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is going on here? This is just beat the hell out of people for no reason and try and get some ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for healing of our land, revival in our churches, and unity in our nation, for the Kingdom’s sake, and to p… https://t.co/7l9XU9XymK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylahchanel @AstasiaWill I love this thread! And I’m so happy I know both of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FORT DRUM/WHEELER,NY (GTB) ASOS reports gust of 51 knots (58.7 mph) from SE @ 1009Z -- KGTB 101056Z AUTO 15028G41KT… https://t.co/vUkgQCYKbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDDCA @NYPDnews @NYPDChiefofDept @NYPDDetectives @NYPDCommAffairs @NYPDInMemoriam @NYPDchaplains @NYPDCeremonial… https://t.co/OltyeBMTJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shuffles68 Looks like a crash, Chris. I dont have many details but traffic breaks loose after Tomah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleedcubbieblue Today is a TV game. Where’s the stars Joe? U know; Nico Hoerner! Batting first, playing 2nd; Niiii… https://t.co/PxqARt4vzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaxAlertWeather John.  On radar doesn’t it seem like the storm will slide east under us??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Registered Nurse - Emergency Dept. - Part Time - Days -… https://t.co/y1vyL5wAEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill @23kissmykicks It’s really Sad that my foundation posted on Facebook asking for people to donate to a Sin… https://t.co/LrSzJC5SH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knock knock.  Who's there?  Interrupting cow!  Interrupting co....  Moooooooooon!   😄😄😄😄😄😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Patriots are good, that dog was HORRIBLE, no style, the hair was shit. The dashhund got SCRWED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me powering down pre workout, Lindsay drinking wine while we listen to Post Malone's remix of dreams by Fleetwood m… https://t.co/HHjkgNvzbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suade99 @briangaar @InsideGaming @updownmpls @Borderlands Dude, the joystick on Mr Do! Right now #realqueezed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Were the Hoosiers and Boilermakers trying to channel the 1950s? Those “drastic changes” really paid off. What an at… https://t.co/absVaaxRKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceAiston @cmclymer He criticized the Democratic Party for wanted women minorities and lgbt candidates. He jus… https://t.co/yNHFTTVS1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Boys’ Basketball, the Ithaca Yellowjackets, @STLSharks, and @Huskietweets are all consisted in District 94 in It… https://t.co/LCjcZXjvcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roomway @ben_davis113 @sportingnews No one's arguing that. But it's more than just simple accounting. There's a le… https://t.co/OGEqMVMlrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachYourKids @aspito28 @sixfourclub @nextlevelbb @_JeremyBooth There’s a time and a place. The Oakland A’s did it… https://t.co/v1tEKPb37n]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we’re out of position, two things happen: 1) We can’t fulfill our purpose. 2) We’re blocking/delaying someone… https://t.co/f8iREbtnoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JYSexton So Republicans don’t like it? Thanks for the feedback guys. https://t.co/zVaKIVkd32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zoned in on Father of 4. @OffsetYRN Zoned in on making it. I hope you’ve Zoned in too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlyrenee_44 Nookie objects to Siamese twin discrimination!!  Especially against Carly Rae Renee Jepsen Woodard.  “Call US Maybe”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[jump force coulda have been so legendary if it had its own cast instead of becoming a mashup of anime’s that just aren’t compatible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KLG3 @DoItForTheMain4 why’d unc win this game? bc they dominated the paint, we couldn’t do anything with our prim… https://t.co/sgF6tPThKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered @McDonalds #takeout from #kiosk at 11:25am, paid with #iPhone #contactless. Finally handed order bag at 11:… https://t.co/11iWm9M9XV]]></document><document><![CDATA[AJ XI Low ‘Breds’ 🍞 #todayskicks #jordanbrand #jordandepot #whatthekicks #solenation #kream #sneakerfiles… https://t.co/YuN11rp6lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help Children’s Miracle Network and UGA Miracle by reading my story and consider donating!!! https://t.co/KUIBf474fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devindra Your being too hard on it Devindra. That movie was really fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[women will not text you back, be on social media, then claim they’re not on their phone lol just be upfront with me, damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patch Notes / improvement list for the Open Beta. Lots of work went into this.  Spread the word.  #TheDivision2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annendil @tharpel @NorgeAlba @jlwesterfield I wish! https://t.co/2Rc5DRlV8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inthefade 13-year-old dog equals 4:45am wake up and coffee in the microwave. Happy Weekend. https://t.co/VvbeKMbsO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was all the fake QAnon/Pizzagate child sex abuse conspiracy theory crap a way of taking the steam out of the very r… https://t.co/DBdN8FHKWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many of these debates are twisted so that you are one extreme or the other. Don’t do this here. I recognize he’s… https://t.co/KoYOvsHl9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlghere @realDonaldTrump @GOP Lemmee guess ... there are 20 people in your county?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong I guess they think they would have better luck this time if there is a Civil Disturbance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Outkick @ClayTravis When are they going to subpoena Burrito Bill Self.....?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissSassbox you Just earned a follow so didn't the the others that Supported me Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Innocent Man by Billy Joel - lyrics https://t.co/YzfkjemigZ via @YouTube hope this helps]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG #EngineRoom this FRIDAY for my brother @YB_PuertoRico BDAY CELEBRATION. In the #Surfathon going GNARLY !! 🤟🏾🤙🏾… https://t.co/q9lHBK4ULB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to play some Deltarune on the switch... This game literally came out a couple months ago... surprised… https://t.co/rZ3V7kKNgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[She rolled my tree, smoked my tree, then said "was why is it so potent?". cuz I want to fly away for the moment, tw… https://t.co/8bPsqq8Wkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to Wellington County and I just hit full whiteout east of Orangeville. @weathernetwork #onstorm https://t.co/TXEME8hE2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[ليكو هل الختيار بمثل نبض الشارع كل العالم شيفتو هيك الا هو شايف حالو بطل واقنعو إذا فيك#صح_النوم https://t.co/QFA016k2En]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @AriMelber Well hes getting 3 years instead of 20 been caught liying made deal with Democrats lie on trump a… https://t.co/uhf3mOAnNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembering the last championship that we won in 2015 at WSU. https://t.co/ZmRtf8fLWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it ok @SkylarStecker if i consider you my BFF, you are so kind, funny, smart and compassionate, everything I wou… https://t.co/09jasZMfTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoardGameGumbo @jasondingr Yeah - been awhile since we played, but we really like Marco Polo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pompeo rejects legal claim by ISIS wife: 'She's a non-citizen terrorist -- she's not coming back'  https://t.co/1SCo9YNAKg]]></document></documents></author>