<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[SELF CARE IS IMPORTANT!!! Don’t let anyone steal your joy! Forgive... even if you never accept an apology from them… https://t.co/tSI5kS0KR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleyForMayor Does your #ClimatePlan for #Chicago include expanding #recyling and adding #composting?  Do your ini… https://t.co/rg3mCL1pUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when you stay at someone’s house and they are the best host ever like wow I don’t deserve you   @Rebecca_B18… https://t.co/lvfO8iU7V3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @wenbychazdean with get_repost ・・・ Soft, fresh, lightweight and soothing, WEN Lavender was inspired by the… https://t.co/dKlBdthv0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPS_LoganSupt @OmahaPubSchool Thank you! We appreciate your dedication to safety! Strive for 95 on Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random picture, obviously 💗🤷🏻‍♀️ #GoodNightEveryone 😘 https://t.co/dbhedv6E8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News12LI Good.kid deserved it! At least 1 adult stuck up for another child!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New inspo for @RoyalCaribbean #royalcaribbeanobsessed #snowdays #8yearoldlovesships #dreamingoflabadoozies https://t.co/FjhE6riBzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swon26 @JillWineBanks @danielsgoldman I feel so relieved he was brought in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tagruber @mymynags @nancy_hamm1 @LadyNY4Ever @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs @grgbkr37 @mickelodoole @ChrisBragdon… https://t.co/YSs5Qr8dKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @senatemajldr @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @SenateFloor @HouseFloor @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump When is America… https://t.co/hHiUoAG4Sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save this for the next time some bonehead tries to tell you the cause of Seattle's homelessness crisis is all the p… https://t.co/pDHipNEpn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin @DiamondandSilk @GOP What you see is the GOP getting animated after months of watching the Democrati… https://t.co/2yU3x4rZv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Because it's a freaky song. About a Hotel with vampires or ghosts or something. LOVE that song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of shocking how militarized this generation is about anti-vaxxers. We get it, you saw a PBS special! However m… https://t.co/8R2Xdo2pzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Twitter !   I so support our LEO’s and hope they support me back  my daughter in her time of need with her f… https://t.co/clgXp2eLrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riseofbunny #lawfulgood Everyone doth possess the right to gaze upon da nice booty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new game addiction #BoardKings https://t.co/lBO1xC0cUg https://t.co/T6mQ4SdeCf https://t.co/lBO1xC0cUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un amigo me mandó mensaje, que se puso una peda y cuando se mareo se tomó dos aspiras. Esta fue mi cara 🤦🏼‍♀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your fictional citizen would gave joined a group of POWs and slipped back into Britian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless Kimberly Whiteside on this fine evening.. lord only knows what she’s doing but god bless her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanJuan_2020 Hay tanta unidad en el PPDead🙄 Jajajajaja https://t.co/Aryeyl2A7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoHo1118 @MJGWrites No. Looks like someone's pet sloth painted that picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil whispered in my ear. “ You’re not strong enough to withstand the storm.” Today I whispered in the devils… https://t.co/8j3TnBQr6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaRN4USA @SchlimmH @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump The jobs that are available pay minimum wage or less and are furth… https://t.co/0EzYx99TS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyfulSyd @naterade_23 @LesHugTX Messy just messy LOL💕😂😃😃😃But I thought that too🤔🤔🤔🥰🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel This “trump world” is just tooo weird! I just can’t believe any of it.  I just keep shaking my hea… https://t.co/EkHcqnjnTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nopmobiel @MobileMaggie @DarkSkyMeter @GLOBEatNight @SciStarter This is EXCITING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed @Cwallll and @autumnlynn1212 will be here this weekend 😩😩🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[momma is a saint ya she raised me real good all bc of her ion do you like i should don't make me give u back to the hood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sarajean @pen15show I just saw something about this the other day! I should check it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 weeks until @sanbenito at the Tacoma Dome !!! Let’s fucking goooooooooo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pssst! If you like wise-cracking Patsy Kelly in MERRILY WE LIVE on @tcm , then you’ll love finding out all the fabu… https://t.co/GBNqEtadJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got my mits on a sold out shirt from your store, it’s gonna be too big to fit properly, which is properly o… https://t.co/bu5jNqp6Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully Tonight I'll Get To Watch... Been To Sick To Watch The Last Few Episodes.... 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coolworld0 @TeddiMellencamp It is about @doritkemsley1 being a dimwit because,  who rehomes a dog that bites? I am… https://t.co/Xh8SC7TBOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nel84873318 @mtracey He testified DT did not tell him to lie. Was he lying then or b4? That’s the problem for liar… https://t.co/6Cu6Xka1SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I somehow ended up at work today 😆 Once I get my client settled in, @TheNightGallery and @Deathnote_2016 are on the… https://t.co/EnirUzPiXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trice showing Desiree some #ChilisLove tonight for being a rockstar team service partner!! @ChilisJobs https://t.co/o36Eo7ieV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow Who is this idiot interviewing the Multi Talented Melissa McCarthy.  They ask the dumbest questions to the most talented people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter @lexi21699 is on her way to Toronto to celebrate her 20th birthday! Hoping that she runs into… https://t.co/ISsHmHAjPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[How 2 PAY 4 MC4A STEP 1:   Invert Medicaid. Instead of the Feds sending money to 50 states w/50 admin systems, whic… https://t.co/6dv9bFmaUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day for wrestling state championships! Lots of Birmingham-Area talent a top the podium! Highlights on @CBS_42… https://t.co/zjj1c6HyN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are also anti native hardly any were even represented and that hurts a lot more than what I asked for then the… https://t.co/EaYEsMIlAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me, or have you seen the development or emergence of a writing and speaking style permitting sentences t… https://t.co/nBLByQbvNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[U of Guelph prof first nominee in race to represent federal Green party for Guelph riding https://t.co/edvpeU6hQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[In kindergarten, I faked an asthma attack to get out of nap time because I thought naps were stupid and only for ba… https://t.co/YMvUAHttNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaSavarese @AndrewYangVFA Are the habitat of the species that will surpass us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iconic @KitchenAidUSA brand @WhirlpoolCorp is looking for a Senior Brand Manager to lead a brilliant team, it’s… https://t.co/p9tBgVVFDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/EeSWYhuMq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lozcurtis Because Khloe should have torn him to shreds first instead of blaming the girl. I mean, she didn’t have… https://t.co/0q9omSHwI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenjstoddard @Target Target is a safe space - grab an icee for breakfast while you’re at it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stackedupariana like i’ve only heard the chorus part that EVERYONE is posting on social media]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨🏰✨ @alainarichard  . . . #cinderellacastle #magickingdom #disney #waltdisneyworld #disneyworld #wdw @ Cinderella's… https://t.co/cHKLZ7IuQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said there will be turbulence 😣  pray for my safety! https://t.co/LhOTnCVyxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimeHathCome @VicCervantes3 Now see https://t.co/CU6vwVd0oH   We are all slaves, Trump is trying, I believe 2 get… https://t.co/r5yWwLd1Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a stuffy nose and insomnia is the worst combination ever. https://t.co/WjZOdOha4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyWHills1 Yes I agree not sure why you say I should have a black eye tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a blue light flash through my window and let me tell you there’s a storm coming... but before all that c… https://t.co/L90imJWc4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @FionaMorgan79 @CaththeWineLady… https://t.co/uJmBOv4Mun]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to be a speaker at another Aspire event! Talking to the youth in the city about the wonderful company I wo… https://t.co/so5hhAQRcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A step in the right direction toward a greener county and schools https://t.co/beQZWhBriT Thanks to students,… https://t.co/FqcLYRwBFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel The ole turtleman is beyond comprehension, did the viagra rot his brain?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachie_claire shocked and heartbroken that i, a card-carrying EEC super fan, didn’t know this]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s getting close and real! Just ordered my CAD from @Chase for my trip to #Montreal and #QuebecCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmagrino You reset your forgotten PASSWORD to do this? A true American hero.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may be #MAR10DAY but uh.. it’s-a me, Karen O 😋🤣 Hope y’all take some time to enjoy the sunshine today before thi… https://t.co/Vf84OsqZky]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, where might one find a Star-Wars-themed bolo tie ... if one was in the market for one? #justcurious #askingforafriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been laying in bed for the last 4 hours listening to Christian metalcore and honestly that is the hardest genr… https://t.co/2b02xPMKKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Spring flower 🌸 Cleaning 🧹 Time! https://t.co/Hvil3Z3HKG #SpringCleaning #CleanBathroom #CleanHouse… https://t.co/lVJAAj3mVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BestDressed was @RobertsEmma at the @VanityFair #Oscar2019 party 🎉 #OscarsRedCarpet #OscarSunday #oscars… https://t.co/V74USsIc2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapping up another great group of #ambassadors in @forneyisd with @FOTPSLeslie!  #beproud #tellyourstory #vote… https://t.co/UNKlYJKAwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t be here today. I wouldn’t get up on the days I have no motivation, the days where I have to face my bigg… https://t.co/rxdByuUcDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Workingman711 @BintibirdC Members of Freedom Caucus? They’re very dangerous, most likely believing white Americans… https://t.co/0HshIjaXP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTRiiBE Thank you! And I can’t believe people are reading this half-assed speculation and making judgements. Wis… https://t.co/NfmPEA4vRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A los #dermatologos que anden x #DC aad2019 abriguense bien y nos cenos esta noche en el clasico #cocktailCilad… https://t.co/d3BJDX7tHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A noite é longa, e esse é meu momento Gato, não tá satisfeito? Eu só lamento]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWolfeMusic I don’t have a clue who you are; therefore I can’t judge that you are getting more famous. Then you… https://t.co/brYS1Dpsv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell in love with Sigala’s music while backpacking through Eastern Europe in the spring of 2017.  When I found ou… https://t.co/mpSt39dhFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hehehe 💕 @RepRashida  “I said someone doing this was racist. If you think that someone is you.... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMooreLPM After Reese Witherspoon won an Oscar,someone asked her about the red carpet experience.  She said it… https://t.co/nNwnZFTTIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freedom to uphold the Confederacy... and Freedom to nationally protest...  Give me LIBERTY... or give me DEATH💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, well, this is now the situation we’re faced with, what are we going to do about it? https://t.co/RKp6oLN2Yx… https://t.co/Gy6mZpvAxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Both these guys are Jerks!!!! The vote of the Patriots and the American Citizens CAN NOT and WILL NO… https://t.co/JA2JRtWR2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thinking my Twitter is popping, and it turns out it’s all of these other people’s notifications]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us LIVE this Saturday at 11am EST. We're featuring the amazing @ItsBrentLyles! It should be a great show!… https://t.co/7Xiw7aWPNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I represent the citizens of three counties. Hidalgo ✅, Grant County should pass today, Sierra County should pass ne… https://t.co/ZkXkFarduW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesaratariq Yes girl. You’re gorgeous. Other than that...what would your channel be about?! Lol https://t.co/r4EiEbduK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather listen to someone else.  I gave your nickname to someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yippee ki yi yay!! It's the WINE 10K 🍷  #FlatSVT is ready for all the festivities.  • • • #oisellevolée #bamabirds… https://t.co/3K2XiEhfng]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather watch a comedian strip than a stripper tell jokes @StormyDaniels Come to think of it I have @bertkreischer]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's frustrated because she is a child #TheBachelor https://t.co/S5xB2tnVWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love, love, love @captainmarvel!! If anyone wants to get me this jumpsuit for my birthday, that’d be cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel really sad when I’m laying here and one of my cats comes and lays in my lap and I have to wind up getting up… https://t.co/ifWsnBIxOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveBlacharski @maxwellhwhite @PeteButtigieg I'm also curious as to why people that believe despite evidence ther… https://t.co/SNhI10ncLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my sister moved out and I never thought I would say this but I miss her ugly ass 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my baby! 53 seconds left in her very last high school game and she pops a 3! We lost, but she finished… https://t.co/okjIyke0Ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troy_andrea @AllTimeEDM @EDMSofa @Edmism @AZRavers @PreciousPetts *u think i don’t know where u sleep? get that ph… https://t.co/bg7ve3hzil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxRaphaelGreen @WBEZ @frontlinepbs ** Revocation of parole pending outcome of two misd charges.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Enterprise Holdings? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description an… https://t.co/bOkRKFyzdR]]></document></documents></author>