<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Having a conversation with Sabina Montinar the Operations Coordinator @FAB_SCRAP #recycle #enviornment #fashionindustry #helpingourworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[just asking cuz I ALWAYS go to insta first out of habit even tho I find twitter superior 🤷🏼‍♀️ weird habit I wanna know if y’all do the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye q pedo. .... Desde cuando nuevo leon se convierto en esto ......  Yo pense q puro norteño 🥺🥺🥺 https://t.co/0t6UrXTSHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLittleMLB HAHAHA....completely agree. I wonder why, though. Seems so random]]></document><document><![CDATA[#igotthebouquet💐 😯🤷‍♀️👰🤵 @ Queen Mary, Longbeach, CA https://t.co/HEnILV7Fz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodbyetoaShoe So this is the room where you rehearse with your Gordon Lightfoot tribute band.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved watching you today @JennyMcCarthy with Sherri . You looked soooooo pretty and loved seeing the pic of your ha… https://t.co/A5TltJXoR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_green_sox You’re very welcome! 😊 Remind me on Wednesday.  Tag you’re it. 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[These girls are halfway to their Girl Scout Cookie goal, w/a month to go. They really want to donate 500 boxes of c… https://t.co/sXv5t9I1Mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSUmom19 Actually, some parents are so annoyed by me that they pull their kids out of my class. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNET I prefer 4K UHD now but will get the player I can play them on. As that is on my list next. But I still have blue ray movies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Registering for medicinal marijuana card:  Dr: what’s your diagnosis? Me: anxiety Dr: what’s causing this? Me: the… https://t.co/sNC895Ugc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinah has feelings about Mondays and losing an hour of sleep. https://t.co/kmRhuDIIYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for Kelsey Morgans, she has been nominated for scholar athlete of the month!  #LibertyPrideNY @LibertyHS_NY… https://t.co/nQkbRALFW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another story of an American hero being persecuted and villanized by the govt for truth telling. https://t.co/akHJSANjQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me on SnapChat for all my daily tom fullery, dinner, snacks, workouts behind the scenes and more!!  Oh snap… https://t.co/5aGT9cgJ8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_magnussen @MamCivi @letgolifeflows @BabyGo2014 @pratoshnivedita @HarcourtDoug @CarlosD27801704 @gerrinnesmac… https://t.co/lQiwH0UQDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently have my heat set at 70 but my room is freezing and my hot water wasn’t working earlier @ RIC wyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY BODY AND SOUL ARE NOT READY FOR THE JONAS BROTHERS!!!!! IMDAJISKSK😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken fajita poppers (air fryer edition) over riced cauliflower topped with fresh salsa &amp; cotija cheese. #yum… https://t.co/a3SS7Y054G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me introduce you to my new tree friend! His name is Sol and he’s got many goals but most importantly he’d like… https://t.co/FHkHuD8Ujq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: Judge voids Paul Manafort plea deal after saying he intentionally made false statements to prosecutors a… https://t.co/q5YAbtQEa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @DMcIntyreWWE @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins @TheDeanAmbrose Finally some justice.  Thank you Shield.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayhypo got into it w someone yesterday about this 🙄🙄🙄 like how are y’all still drinking COW milk?! can’t relate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhogues32 Boyyy ik you heated asf 🤦🏽‍♂️ would’ve been put that bitch out 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t the people on my finsta who snitch send Seth all the cute shit I post about him not just the “bad” 😴😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #LizsKitchen is coming tomorrow and it’s the perfect match for this cold snap!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirrlynnn @yenny_117 I could crop you in next time lol jk you should come with us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture of your niece when she finally was not projectile puking and you realized Down Syndrome was not contagious.… https://t.co/0FBhVTgkuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kactuzkickz @WashedNDried @J23app @xFlyNatioNx @snkr_twitr @SOLELINKS @cardiakdovu Plus also all three pairs I hav… https://t.co/XHi7bYt6Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Discover on Google https://t.co/HxhiPQaPRZ Surprise? DoS, an audience, publicity, applause...... where's the surprise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GPTW4ALL Does your workplace have a donut wall for all!? Come check it out! https://t.co/mu2n7PraVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My instructions: “you need to leave by 11am”  Me at 11:10 am: *in a robe with a towel on my head still not done packing*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tristan’s been proven a cheater. Fool me once shame on you, fool me twice shame on me.   Jordyn Woods though?!?!?!? BYE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at @theeveningmuse, check out "Find Your Muse," one of the most popular open mics in town! Music/poetry sig… https://t.co/XWslaTcSdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you get out the shower and have made plans with someone and they text back just to cancel 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stop listening to thank u, next album. Plz send help. @ArianaGrande]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we the best we can be? Is winning on the scoreboard enough if we are not pushing the limits of how good we can/… https://t.co/QLIkPLtX2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I appreciate your speaking up for representative Omar's right to speak her mind on a controversial topic. Howe… https://t.co/mLTsSC9HeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveCallaway2 @joanhcallaway 98% is higher than I would have guessed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astylishteacher @PeterEGriffiths @HPrestonEdu I am SO down for this. I used to do something similar to this in sci… https://t.co/FOJxz4Fdyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateReadingVO @elizmccracken Yes BRING CANDLE PIN in your pocket. Props are everything. Maybe a ball in the other… https://t.co/oQmQMjIFQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BusyMissLizzy If you’re into murder and crime podcast I know a bunch of good podcasts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abisola_spencer @RwAccommodation It’s one of the most beautiful countries I’ve seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Amazing if you consider his ability to lie as amazimg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today #Gally1 has a random B5 panel with most of the living cast members *sniffle* whom I last saw 22 years ago or… https://t.co/cYgLilxZmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[EARLY MORNING GRIND BEFORE THE GRIND!!! HAPPY MONDAY!!! SUPER EXCITED SEE MY OLDEST IN 3 DAYS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think the Oscars would be far more interesting if they were full contact!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Funesta @tatclouthier @VicenteFoxQue Con todo respeto, @VicenteFoxQue no califica como oposición. Lo suyo son paya… https://t.co/TAOnAkC9lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWYMT @nwsjacksonky @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT It's been melting pretty fast. My husband works in Pikevill… https://t.co/nkX8Qnv4tE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greatmomgenes @madriannorman I can honestly say that I knew they were this stupid. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristanGorce still not exactly lookin &amp; still planning on bein single all 2019. just scoping my playing field for now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowercase_g @velveth0ney @lilgabssss28 @MMoorw It is true however Dr. Murphy (she’s on the board) said the morals… https://t.co/hALzOlAswK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yet another lie by you. At the rate you're going, u will have told over 17K lies after 4 yrs in of… https://t.co/Y6CGIYi2CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcrm22 Just in general.. negative things about people, life, situations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malinablue @realAliTweets Yes.  We have much better options.  Bernie is yesterday’s news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would be really nice if my body lost weight.  *not looking for advice, just venting*]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that move on to new relationships fast as heck scare me. They really do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what arrived! 🤗 This piece of paper symbolizes endless hours of hard work, reflection, and dedication! I am so… https://t.co/oOe5tk83cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieHanlon @NHSLMA I'm in the middle of "Where the Crawdads Sing" by Delia Owens  👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you sign up for our awesome newsletter! The one place to go to get all of our upcoming news!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @SimySemsem @angieservellon_ @consuiglesias @mich_onelove @TereOrt51687394 @Viviane6677 @Alcioni5… https://t.co/H8kIzQkEGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer R also did not have control as the judicial dept - 9th circuit - did al… https://t.co/qnJgLruk9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninadobrev hey Nina would you ever have Candice, or any of the other cast from TVD. Guest on Fam? You rock,  my fa… https://t.co/zMO0z5NF8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor of Baltimore Catherine Pugh in attendance at the Maryland Inn Hotel to support prescription drug affordabilit… https://t.co/ecMuEEfOUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[📕📕Can’t wait! Hope you’ll join us. ⭐️⭐️Thanks @TLep10 for organizing &amp; hosting such a unique event 🔥🔥🔥🔥… https://t.co/bVIpE8U6U2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelWoodby @dbongino They r all getting busted. Keep eye on foxnews, Michael Jordan, Barr happenings and whats… https://t.co/srZqdMznXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhovianFeminism If I could find a multicolored jacket for him, maybe we could smuggle him in as Colin Baker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mymusictaste https://t.co/M2wGBXhbCb please help bring the boys to San Jose my Bay Area and Sacramento ppl! Teamwork makes the dream work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giant inflatable human foosball...yes this is a thing. #gamenight #tessnet ⚽️🤣 https://t.co/EHMppUwRx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @townhallcom They wouldn’t because there are too many hidden democrats hiding behind Republican titl… https://t.co/bXNkmvdG15]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a sleep paralysis dream this morning 😭, I wake up like 3 times and was still in that hoe, I start saying Psal… https://t.co/kp6zsUgb82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumbs up for the chance to hang with @angelobav this am while Jimmy enjoys a few days off! 👍🏾 https://t.co/oMjoaL3FWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Cuál es la lógica de reducir los recursos económicos dirigidos a los refugios que salvaguardan la vida de las muje… https://t.co/HOsmDkDfjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate I don’t put ketchup on omelets. But the only ketchup I use on fries  is @HeinzKetchup_US   I may be… https://t.co/PlO7Gg0gHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[when u come up with a great response but u don’t care enough about some random guy’s theology or theology in genera… https://t.co/NAnDfKtwB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s spring break bitches   @SoundsByDodi @TheeGatsby_ https://t.co/SkzQ3JWhKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son has all the same bilities I do for voice except he really is not a dinner as I can and have had that educati… https://t.co/95pqaPXPRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just looking forward to the day when i can get gas and still be able to feel my fingers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Utility A"? What did you like most about that job? #FacilitiesMgmt #Somerset, PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gervontaa Don’t let these hoes suck ya money up bro ! Remember I told you this. #staydown #stayfocus never forget the ultimate goal. 🥊💰🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaioSoma Vc vai notar que se usar hidratante pra área dos olhos, vai sentir diminuir a sensação de olho seco tbm e… https://t.co/GMIREEm5ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[and Vic didn’t say shit about it but wanted all the smoke with a dead xxxtenashe for the same thing months prior 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeonBlakk I know what you're referring too, yo goofy ass missed it LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LWVCNM congress needs to do their job of checking the president.   https://t.co/yOdumA88ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet Donny gets away with saying whatever he wants to his base because they are so hypnotized that the lies j… https://t.co/BHZAB4ghRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I just wanna wake up on goodbye, out in the Rolls that's rented.” #WhenIGetHome   An autobiography.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamDriverUK when you became Lena and Shields Beotch. https://t.co/xNyc6zEXSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brandon_Bird @yellowcardigan @TheAliciaKraft We have a lot of towels but we have a pool - like I think we had mayb… https://t.co/oLmgrOD3ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was in Denver this past weekend for work ...El Paso today and tomorrow then Turkey 🇹🇷]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vote4LIZ2020 #ElizabethWarren @elizabethwarren #cannabislatinanurseceo #BUYMYBOOKABOUTOPIATESANDMEDICALCANNABIS… https://t.co/0KjfuTgECx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammy_jay294 @ZalesJewelers This is why people hate Zales. The sales associates try on your jewelry when you are n… https://t.co/TkbbLvGa0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 9 in the morning and I’m about to cry listening to The Vagina Monologues. Jesus fucking Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 here (11 mos after graduation, though!). Husband @jpp_77 is #3 with kind heart. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The premise with him is that because he’s rich he knows more than any one else. First, he might not be as #rich as… https://t.co/sXXKs8AE1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwbethdo @NickCannon @robinthicke @MaskedSingerFOX @donnyosmond @ActuallyNPH I hope it is Donny! Love him...]]></document><document><![CDATA[How To Make Homemade Ketchup - Sugar Free, Keto &amp; Paleo - Bobby's Kitche... https://t.co/SbfvNEMyjz via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliocuc   Hi Julio, Thank you for liking my tweet. Let us discuss your mobile app development requirements here - https://t.co/9FCwcjAIYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brassasin36 @BobLonsberry I get it. It’s a challenge. But man, living in Florida, you see how cavalier a lot firea… https://t.co/EjvlLJHZyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Let's pretend this was yesterday, shall me?)   I've been challenged by @serdundon to post covers of 7 books I love… https://t.co/6KyyuKlHbz]]></document></documents></author>