<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m buzzed but I just figured out what it is. You’re having fun doing every fucking thing I wanted to do with you b… https://t.co/x2nK3zeUFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasongay Plus the slide is going to be awesome the first 8 or 9 times down, then it’s gonna be “yeah, like we got… https://t.co/J6mKDpTtO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Art photography teachers in college at UNL would be proud. Thanks to Adobe photoshop and Nik  filters I'm finall… https://t.co/7ZkqYyZXIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimHillMedia @LenTesta  Hi Guys-any insight on when phase 1 of #MarvelLand will open #Disneyland? Everything I see… https://t.co/bvvKTyNeKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There hath no temptation taken you but such as is common to man: but God is faithful, who will not …… https://t.co/iTO0Deojvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Image artist) Nidia Castaldi, hotel room exhibit with Sarah Tell sarah_tell, Anna Feil @annafeil, and Stephanie Ma… https://t.co/gfyjlCTNPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always searching for the next Warhol. It might be you show me your art. @ Hoboken, New Jersey https://t.co/ya0mQuVhiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fighterpics @JRaberge So that’s what an airborne can o’ whoop ass looks like 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dussaultlinda1 @LoveBling6 @jenniferjsmall @misleadia @SuzRiebold @Slr64Q @WeWhoWait1776WW @conservcici… https://t.co/kdAf9pRlFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ve not even called or anything on my birthday a week ago, and I’m sure I won’t be able to see my daughter turn 4 in two weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Fall River, Massachusetts https://t.co/IRQhIuxaHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Your father is a POS criminal and he’s going to jail, same as you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalaceLaw @ABAGPSolo @lawsomepodcast @AaronStreet @jasonbeahm @Cianapowell83 @PalaceLawOffice @gsiskind How am I g… https://t.co/W3jrtBrieS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bilder_CEM I mean chained doors, sex offenders, capacity issues, leave a shelter for a perceived SAFER shelter. Th… https://t.co/zJMARS2WDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew @Lawrence Perhaps because Ross is the greediest &amp; most crooked in history?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_memenator He honestly seems like he would be a solid hang. He finally figured out the caps lock. I’m very prou… https://t.co/7j0894vKHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cloudtherapy #peakaboo @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/EyKK4QvzfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is incredible. Watch a young congresswoman SHINE.  https://t.co/dnEh9jMEoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Replies are amazing lol Loved Incredibles 2, but Spiderverse was legit one of the best animated movies I’ve ever se… https://t.co/jSg6Gje1Uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to prove I actually go to meets with people other than mikegriffin6. abbydunne toripriestley7 had outstanding p… https://t.co/4WmEf89aT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[La limpieza trae belleza. en Paseo Santa Lucia Nuevo Leon https://t.co/F15LvnvUha]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LMFAO 🤔😁😁😁 I Also Love Love A Good Belly Rub !! #Smile ,👊🏾✊🏾🙏🏾 @ Canarsie, Brooklyn https://t.co/2mQJfRiUdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[And.......Sheridan College won the coin toss and will host the Region IX Tourney. #TSPsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to like Facebook better than Instagram. They’ve been killing it with the memes lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations democrats! You were successful in making the president look foolish as he was trying to sign a deal with North Korea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mid of 3rd: Washington 3, Minnesota 0. Burgmann gives up a hit then gets a double play to end the half inning. Due… https://t.co/4EOcfIevtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticierovv @jguaido  "Viendo que se agolpaba la gente, increpó al espíritu inmundo, diciéndole: «Espíritu sordo y… https://t.co/V1f2qBqM8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stages of Twitter Users:  1. Create an account (idk why)  2. u don't understand (mannn f twitter why do ppl use it)… https://t.co/VpfXmRveXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzed29 @Tjonesonthenba A. Derick, Joe, Jae, Kyle, Rudy.....we do have others who can score. Take Ricky out and put Kyle in for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pure MKE magic.   #roostmke #roostweddings  #marriedinmilwaukee  Details:  Venue: @pizzamanwi  Officiant: Derek Mos… https://t.co/bmqTs9n742]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cornell will be hosting a teach-in THIS WEDNESDAY 2/20, at 6:30pm. Join us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh boy i can’t wait for the lakers to go on that 12 game win streak and make the playoffs 😅😅😰😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcarr In almost every case I'll take more mobility &gt; less mobility. Would be tough to balance tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wch_4 @bryanaustermann Also curious. Would you not fit through the door?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mosheroperandi @AngeloRover @Tracktwentynine Those freeloaders! Where IS the pedestrian license fee? We can easily… https://t.co/Dbg846rW1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking for a #GraphicDesigner in the #Atlanta area to design a #logo! If you know any talented #artists please… https://t.co/reYob6LPXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN KILL YOUR NEWBORN BABY! (Vote Democrat in 2020!) https://t.co/fndgYeXgBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldfilmsflicker @MarkHarrisNYC @mattzollerseitz @thehighsign Please drop me from any Twitter conversation going fo… https://t.co/Ra7IWmOCTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great morning speaking at BISA as a member of the amazing Victory Road team. Navy Seals, former Div. I football pla… https://t.co/RLcj65Cxk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Is. Just. The. Beginning. #PullUp #HitThatGL #DontBeLeftAtTheDoor 🤦🏽‍♂️ #WeLit #GreaaatVibezzz #CatchMeThere… https://t.co/6diWB7UiL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eGeeking @TriciaRansom @jachutchinson @marklearns @caranorth11 @myramade @AnnaRoseLeach @AnnibabyCan @Natachu… https://t.co/MdF0zTGfhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corvidresearch That is what I tell my students.  You can use Wikipedia to start, but follow up with actually going… https://t.co/pq7TqKN8c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_verynicegirl I can’t help I got kicked by a horse and went cross eyed, just happy u enjoy that shit A 😂😂🤪 https://t.co/XWXR8rgO8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day STEM Challenge ♥️ @VikingPridePH @MtDiabloUSD https://t.co/tfecpjAPPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[In The Sun - Chris Martin &amp; Michael Stipe https://t.co/E9f9GJY5q2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMarrazza @carlydermott None, then water after cause ice cream always makes you thirsty]]></document><document><![CDATA[from 33k feet (10k m) @ Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina https://t.co/xYbKcl41sU]]></document><document><![CDATA[In meteorological observations it's known as BS = blowing snow.  We had a lot of that in addition to what was falli… https://t.co/FuUw4uaTqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sunny day at the beautiful Vaughan Estates at @sunnybrook Speaking with the Department of Laboratory Medicine and… https://t.co/NMlxSJ8o3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah definitely. And y’all won 100 games last year, that’s really good. Surely you won the AL East right? No way so… https://t.co/oeiHPBYIqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBI So Roger Stone can put an image of cross hairs on a Federal Judge?????????????????????????????????????????????… https://t.co/PJQ7gtck3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivin50 @Bryan700 @buzzman888 She's conjunctivitising her wordporium😀😀😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millerak42 @ReformedBroker @OSAMResearch @tbfairchild CC: @tbfairchild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapillonUK @CNN @MSNBC @SenSanders @HillaryClinton @FoxNews ROTFLMAO  Have fun trying to sell that story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodsonLia @colton This isn’t Colton’s fault and he’s not letting it happen... they should problem delete their In… https://t.co/PShj2vP0ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's exactly that Democrats plan are we up to 25 million estimated illegal aliens that's going to change the demo… https://t.co/NLXDYuirJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialEGO @BenjaminBoone1 I was a spry 19 year old boy. That pic is a "good pic" (can it be considered good if y… https://t.co/8hJvEctcqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @thunderrosa22, @sammyguevara will be at @WithoutACauseWA in a couple weeks. I plan to wear your shirt to this… https://t.co/tSQCKYVJ7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardicKnowledge @Musicologess Effing Mothula! The Skull Woods dungeon enraged me as a kid, and turns out it still does]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindynorth1 I had to get it because it’s bae’s favorite. I also got her some soju.]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh hey kitty girl  @LatriceRoyale on the cover of @MirrorRoyal Miami at TWIST Miami https://t.co/7PUu0zhmof]]></document><document><![CDATA[I assume the all-white Avengers: Endgame suits are for a big musical number at the end of the film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamkuzniar @LumixUSA @GeraldUndone I vlog on a 10.5! Vlogged on a 17.5 for the first 8 months haha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united Which is a direct result of giving the economy people our business class seats. Since you took my business… https://t.co/zRoM1IYOZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @JewelsJfitness @KleioValentien @Violet_Monroe @AnissaKate @thecadencelux @karleegreyxxx @jessievolt… https://t.co/FBEF3i4Hm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer The problem for Cohen is Trump is improving his brand and making America great also. That's a problem for Democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 de marzo. Emigrar es vivir para trabajar.  No trabajar para vivir. 20 horas trabajando.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st half thought: Injuries this evening have been a disaster. Which could mean we may see more of Mctominay (who is… https://t.co/eVElpZX9ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber I’ve watched your show for years. But your combo tonight of Bill Kristol and then a flack from centrist/… https://t.co/AXC9vFR6FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@confessions_cup @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie @TheAngelOrsini @magee333 @Cbp8Cindy @suziday123 @ja2cook @Jay_Rombach… https://t.co/gBD2L9rkPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[27 degrees @ midnight, 13 degrees at 06:00 and the #wind howls, blows and it feels C-O-L-D. Stay safe out there, bu… https://t.co/sdeZChA9cT]]></document><document><![CDATA[That my friends is the way they roll.  I would call them sick, but it does not seem to be a strong enough word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Soulless person paid to read scripts ghostwritten by corporate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My humble opinion of #PleaseMe is that it’s a HUGELY better single than Finesse. Great work by the awesome duo of Bruno Mars and Cardi B.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd love to experience this live. I have to actually, shit https://t.co/fr4jMuPedi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Congress may need to cut DODs budget if it has money just sitting around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ribbon game is strong this year. #gally1 @ Gallifrey One https://t.co/cvzpYd6Zm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The King is one of thee Thuggish Ruggish Pimps https://t.co/DE5cqy3HmP via @YouTube @CHOSEN_P_Y_P https://t.co/IuOZ7euZD2 #thugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjones4223 They don’t call us “Gen X” for nothing. #ForgottenGeneration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing by the fact that it is an opinion, not that they necessarily agree with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredgatesdesign We’re trying that with Tesla and it ain’t going so well. As for your dat, I don’t believe so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a special day when I met Puddles Pity Party for the first time and I also Photographed soon to be Academy Aw… https://t.co/jjubeUsugF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustedOpenRadio I'll be at Fastlane, who's going with me ????!!!!!!!! https://t.co/d9tKSAytO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you ain't got drafted yet, don't mean you not a good prospect]]></document><document><![CDATA[get the right players in your locker room before you go out to play. #entrepreneurship #sphere]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you ask the crew to send you pics from the season for the wrap party. #AmericanHousewife… https://t.co/yEirVFKirn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever someone calls me ugly, I get super sad and hug them, because I know how tough life is for the visually impaired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chase McClain scores 35 points as Mountain View defeats Bend 76-71. @OSAASports]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know is tonight on #Raw whichever way Ronda and Becky encounter each other I'm gonna have the chills. Can't w… https://t.co/vRBgnibWQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATTCares hello I have lost access to my sbcglobal email it is linked to an old roommates disconnected dsl is there… https://t.co/jNcdIGrk22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chocolate coffee nose. Lacto, cocoa and light coffee. Body is quite light. - Drinking a Hoppen-Daz Mochaccino… https://t.co/xXtL3HueCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The search for the next binge worthy series brought me to @ThePunisher. Six episodes in and I’m hooked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wheeler244 @RandySmall Haha, you guys just gotta get out there and start doing it! I am almost 100% self taught. A… https://t.co/kI4NfnGQy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump They aren't really saying that they just know republicans want support https://t.co/wUwWeybACr long as… https://t.co/9lAgMP4XLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDUAirport It’s time to raise the price of Premier parking… I am willing to pay extra for the convenience of getti… https://t.co/hM5vBdanKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinsOfSid @sungodpxllz It’s not! Just showing how serious sh!t gets if that was 5 Mayo guys recording that to a yo… https://t.co/bPYCUdO97A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast When I saw a Biblical expert debate medical issues with Bill Nye, the Science Guy on TV, I realized… https://t.co/ZxSVK2VkhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost liberal_eagle with get_repost ・・・ Who would have such fraudulent lawyer ... oh wait #proudliberal #liberal… https://t.co/J0hF47b83n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those die-hard Disney fans w their 30+ pins on their lanyards lookin like AYSO All Stars lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicknewsdc @NatGeoMuseum @JaniceparkNews @wusa9 This will be one of those that I no I must see it's something I fe… https://t.co/YBCMxLJeOr]]></document></documents></author>