<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@stevielynlyn @gtnubbins What a lonely single negative degree there!! He needs a plus sign and some  buddies (like, 70 would be nice huh?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very proud to help tech companies in the community find Scala engineers in New York.   So if you would love to… https://t.co/zUMYJY96k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_steel64 @ILoveBombshell That dress was GORGEOUS!!! I absolutely loved it. I tried it on just for fun ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #snowmageddon here in the Pacific Northwest! @SandboxUS #sbeusa #blueheeler #winterwonderland @ Bellingham, Wa… https://t.co/qpwiVsj8I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is really nothing better than getting back into routine. Having @travelplacesguy back home and in the kitchen… https://t.co/zPDcltw5Jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Happy birthday from Hanford Calif! Love you and your family 💟🌼]]></document><document><![CDATA[starbucks needs to stop making this cloud trash and bring back the orange refresher]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends, family say last goodbyes to Det. Brian Simonsen at wake https://t.co/aZWVRtlLgQ via @nypmetro @NYPDnews @TamarLapin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatGirl_Annaa lol not even.. it’s just a scientific fact that women with that middle name ain’t shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaFaveLegend I’ll try my best to to match you’re attitude but I will bring it to your attention in a sincere manne… https://t.co/RdXWzbVhFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunningLonely My favorite "Feel Better" GIF, just for you! Feel better, Marsden! https://t.co/jCFE1p9F37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick patients dying ‘unnecessarily’ in NHS because of poor care | Society | The Guardian https://t.co/PkP7uB5spu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I spent all morning watching Shane Dawson videos and now I’m questioning my existence🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my first @boxycharm in the mail today and all I have to say it, WHY HAVE I BEEN WASTING MY MONEY WITH IPSY? #mylifehaschangedforever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StillUnsocial @Carbonbasedlady @orange_kool_aid @B52Malmet @KidCasteel B.S. reason. Not a golden retriever.  I sin… https://t.co/saRhLQnHuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wzuloag @Marga_Bejarano @GabrielaGrijal5 @LourdesLugo @michelleriveraa @MujeryPoder1 @cynthiagarama @demiandu… https://t.co/qw0jcgAh9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkAtdisney It’s a must! Even though I don’t eat it. The fam still has to stop and wander.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When kids call you pretty you know that shit fr kids don’t ever lie they’ll tell you exactly how tf you look]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all think they gone give my money back since I missed the induction ceremony? 😅😅🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[netflix should send out a wellness check alert to my mom whenever I watch the notebook at 1 a.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to give a congrats to @CoachChels_  keep working hard and keep doing what your doing to help grow the game o… https://t.co/DHgsSo5Bfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all storms come to disrupt your life, some come to clear your path. Everything happens for a reason. Be encoura… https://t.co/rz0UG6itjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to chat with Taunton City Council tonight. @semavav @TraceyMedeiros2 #education #suicideprevention… https://t.co/fkoxS5Eb09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JulieJujubear Mr. President Your son in-law needs to go he looks at you as if he hates you and I… https://t.co/FdOzSNCbMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masuo Kino has competed every Great Aloha Run and this year will be number 35 on Monday #mybestruns… https://t.co/7acIn0aARG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Missjen325 @JordiVilasuso @YandR_CBS Oh because of the coat she was wearing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[750-1,000 page due Wednesday. 😫 I want to start on it now but I just finished another assignment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremybeasley @ideo Awesome! Culture is definitely a shared responsibility. Good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raleighkeegan Um, I read through all of them and I can't remember the last time I've been to any of them! 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are doing the bedroom renovation in the apartment above me right now, at this second, don’t they know I am a B… https://t.co/L2DfIdwkba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 What does our citizenship mean if anyone can come in and have all the same rights?😳😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partly_cloudy That’s so good to hear. I would love to see you and catch up if you have time! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rico_stathis @Visit_PCB @Sostraveluk @RickGriffin @VISITFLORIDA @MattsRoadTrip @TravelAtWill @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/LISEcZCHuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@senatemajldr Get on Board #ForThePeople or #Resign You and your @GOP are becoming Useless under @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/dK7HmkAYg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAABlues @mohockeyyd @U18AAASTLBLUES @U16AAABlues @stlouisaaablues @04AAABlues Good luck 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Dr. Richard Wintle, PhD Assistant Director, The Centre for Applied Genomics, for taking time out of your… https://t.co/2fHF2v6un8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlahall That Kim K. dress she was devastated about,, Wasnt a very similar  dress designed by G. Versace back in… https://t.co/I2cmPcKGtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @rtmannjr for being a guest on TigerTv Newsbeat! Our students appreciate your time and insight.… https://t.co/z5C9wd6sNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[so to the ghosts from the abandoned house next door be ready to receive some tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIKE WHERE DO I EVEN BEGIN HOW THEIR HAIR COLORS LOOK AMAZING, the Song in its self Amazing and rain soaked Monsta… https://t.co/OyHcX9v7pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mabelgasca @Tatiana5oz @LuzO_ @anie1215 @afro_candombera @WriterTravelerR @bellalilli16 @_LisaRuiz @yoligrilla… https://t.co/ngNM5yj6a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanelleBrown117 You all look like you’re having a wonderful time. A family that laughs together loves together. Be… https://t.co/LvkF0qMeLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[They judge me without a question 🤦🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️ #youngdellz @ Syracuse, New York https://t.co/NHUZTmPJ4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casting Call this year in Detroit, Mi follow @CarmellaxRosell for more @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/0HhofRklEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle King Is First African American Woman To Be Named As LAUSD Super... https://t.co/iJLWlmOh9d via @YouTube Th… https://t.co/OsVdyNgz0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t trust these hitches. Can’t fuck with bitch biggahs. I’ll fuck your bitch, bigger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy Yeah but I made that happen by going to stage door 5 nights! That wasn’t luck that was persistence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint I am the pastor of The First Presbyterian Church in Seneca Falls, where Alice Paul first proposed this Ame… https://t.co/dcoiUiXdTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChickenandWaffles is baaaaaack!!!#WaffleQueen #BodyByWaffles #WaffleQueenCafe #WOW #WaffleoftheWeek https://t.co/DRTZVvECLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at The Creative Group in #Kannapolis, NC. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jo… https://t.co/bRbcnPD5Ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[And since they let there dog poop in our yard and I stepped in it I figured I would return the favor so mom don't g… https://t.co/Qn78eqzHjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to watch a Laney rap battle whenever you are, @acrook2 @scottebarker8 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Rhys Davies is so sweet. He read us some of an upcoming project where he plays a murderer!  Cant wait!… https://t.co/ZTFPASOTwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s says to reenact Lady and The Tramp you have to use spaghetti?! Chocolate is more fitting for us. Has been for… https://t.co/m0yjHSyWuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[luv the replies that are like “maybe it’s just undeclared...” glad we got those pesky ~diversity~ candidate announc… https://t.co/KnGmUgx7M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCRokzZzZz Read the books and treat them like a completely separate entity. Having read the books, I get very confused by the show too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[maybe y’all should stop getting tattoos in languages y’all aren’t fluent in??? just a thought 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieBarreiro @khloekardashian @jordynwoods It's just mor Kardashian publicity and drama because Kris Jenner didn… https://t.co/juKKnevxTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best relationship advice you can have is to not date someone obsessed w their image. if ur partner cares more a… https://t.co/OrBlFlDZOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Ud también  ha sido un tonto de la robolucion que ni ha útil llega, yo diria más  bien un tonto inútil… https://t.co/STW56rj2ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[تم ہی سے ہے مجاہدو 💪 جہاں کا ثبات ہے ❤❤ #PakistanLeadsWithPeace  #PakistanArmyZindabad  #NobelPeacePrizeForImranKhan https://t.co/M0ctk5bosy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Spelman College on https://t.co/lxVQ8w3D5A. The 2019 Home Depot Retool Your School Campus Improvem… https://t.co/9eowJVWeUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation TINY DANCER LOVES YOU VERY MUCH. SHE STANDS IN AGREEMENT WITH YOU 100PERCENT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’ve been watching too much @NewGirlTVF when your son sings the intro now, “It’s Jess” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddyOganesyan BITCH I play it with my hall mates they taught me! I’d teach you but like 🤷🏽‍♀️ you far ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackmise @ymorbeauty @lapetitenoob @bijuleni @shortpresents @FernwehSociety @rebecazulch @BenefitCanada… https://t.co/jzOqRZzx3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @grav3yardgirl's latest video and I'm sitting here just crying at my desk. Mental health awareness and… https://t.co/GuTFDT3QO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker No.  But many Dems would stay home and we would get 4 more yrs of Trump...prob not much of a differe… https://t.co/mfArdKSCjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinpaley What about when my body wants to just not exercise and listen to the mamma Mia soundtrack????]]></document><document><![CDATA[you just think they would’ve checked margins before hiring a person to promote their clearly dwindling sales, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[incase you wanted to know how my week is going, I have accidentally called 911 twice at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anybody on this app slanders nina west youre getting blocked and reported sorry I don’t make the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsTrixter @Zigmund_Fraud @mc40_e @SmutClyde @selphnb @Siubhan_H @mmelgar09 @maddpig @urbanx_f @EmmaGPaley… https://t.co/R3EKKKAsNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Editorial: State law for lawyer/legislators shouldn't be exploited https://t.co/q9yMwZmoIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJGoertz I get @TimHortons at least once a day. No, I don’t drink coffee- but they’re the only ones who make steep… https://t.co/mHuMepeWvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our team and our school!!! 💙🏀💙🏀💙🏀💙 Always proud to be a Cleveland Blue Raider! #lovemyraiders… https://t.co/PJqwAkldPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite was nick, still is nick, always has been nick and i do stan harry styles that don’t mean shiii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelBrownABC11 @hollyaiken It was on the 11 news. I only saw the preview after my recorded episode of 20/20 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferYovino Good morning Jennifer. Here the sun is trying to break through; streets are clear. Hope you have a… https://t.co/iOhh4XIuJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 50/66 is my first #legday back since straining my hamstring, focused on light to no weight with high reps worki… https://t.co/tqpwBGBa15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful new black and white pots, vases and pitchers!  Any one of these would be a beautiful addition to your hom… https://t.co/8a9aKZvAh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the places I have been, I'm no place without you ❤  #MondayMotivation https://t.co/aA3jP9vAzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @LindseyGrahamSC @HouseGOP @SenateGOP Of course!   Let’s start acting like it and get them jailed.  Treason anyone?😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ @therealroseanne @ABCNetwork @JussieSmollett @EmpireFOX @FOXTV https://t.co/ptPQjuCFQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to record for season 2 of my podcast. But I need to set the mood first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myfriendalex015 Oooo can I ask wat game?  I mean yay u! https://t.co/OeEul3aKDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how much I like colors, I love a perfect nude palette. Browns, creams, beiges, and taupes are the shades… https://t.co/n76pf8ozPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without Warning @MetroBoomin @21savage @OffsetYRN has got to be one of the best albums of the decade 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a good heart only attracts Beggars, liars and leeches. The unappreciative and ungrateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss my try-on in my IG stories ❤️ So many cute pieces that will arrive in time for Spring Break! This lace t… https://t.co/WIgO93wCkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandagiroux28 Your most welcome. I know you can't help your adorable. If I had a son. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[christine said she liked the font I used to write my notes on my ipad   girllll that’s my handwriting 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhm, so... this dude brought in an old-fashioned typewriter into work today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[36/ ... but I don't currently feel that I have command of sufficient undisputed and indisputable facts to counteract that narrative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also fuck - I still don’t know if I’m doing Calamari in LA or New York. Halp. 🐙 @LewisCapaldi]]></document><document><![CDATA[MICS PARENTS!  Don’t miss the upcoming parenting seminar presented by Dr. Paula McCabe! The seminar is entitled “Di… https://t.co/DEuAhyyfqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Bears ⚽️ hosting @AhsSparta will start at 4:45 GO 🐻 @MaNewsSports @MACSchools @GraniteBears @granitesquad @johncate73]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟Charging up the Chi for Abundance with my Favorite Helper in my auspicious area 🕉🙏🏻💖.  . 🌟 Stay tuned for the resu… https://t.co/pP84lkJHtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The adult equivalent to “I’ll finish this homework in the morning” is “I’ll get gas before work” and I have fallen right into the trap]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in Athens, GA, check out this #SupplyChain job via the link in our bio: Sr. Associate Lo… https://t.co/HdOPuHU8wW]]></document></documents></author>