<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork The DEMS are terrified of Trump because he's doing a fantastic job..I wish they would go along for the r… https://t.co/8box9JDIwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the message we have heard from him and  declare to you: God is light; in him there is no darkness at all. 1 John 1:5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasamos frío para ver el #goldengate en San Francisco, California https://t.co/zjcKZiMrZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then they asked him, "Where is your father?" "You do not know me or my Father," Jesus replied. "If you knew me, you… https://t.co/FLK7SW7LZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 160th Birthday Oregon. I feel privileged to live in this beautiful state! #HappyBirthdayOregon… https://t.co/JlhW8P5yzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys Basketball: Ranny leads Jackson Liberty 52-16 at the half! Highlights to come on @JSZ_Sports @Scott_lewis_23… https://t.co/8MvqsPKgZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video is now up. Cinnamon spiced apple cider muffins | only 2 points on WW https://t.co/cQ59iPABsj via @YouTube… https://t.co/6gndaCYoMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Last #Shutdown Shows How  #Precarious Federal Jobs Have Become  https://t.co/faNkoIyPEH via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the first thing I’m gonna do with my tax return is cover up the cross tattoo I have on my wrist because my… https://t.co/ZPeQ2RbCoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[But they didn't do what YOU did! And you kept getting away with it for 25 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2019 music mood has been Urban Latino/Latino Trap https://t.co/FeDBHbtr7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Send tweet back to Max, remove “no” in collusion/obstruction💥 bam-did we find some truth in Maxine?🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twdandmetal @elena_elinka @crazymom50 @ldavisusa @JenYeager6 @Merve_TWD @justmel_li @emikoko896 @sparkle4meplz… https://t.co/LHjUPa2MGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ageingasai for your impactful work. Thrilled to have been a part of it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh shit I have a morning class! I need to stabilize my mood and hit the hay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that you've written your ending, write the beginning. #intertwined2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoKnowsNews @KamalaHarris @60Minutes And you believe,the word of a man whose lied to Congress what 3 's.   Blow it out your arse KH!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a veterinarian, I bet it’s really difficult and awkward to tell someone their pet is obese and needs to l… https://t.co/RP0wYKB1ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylenntrayy Cassies is seriously my favorite.  But also haven't seen tonight's episode yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinSWoodward @repjwayne @courierjournal I don’t know enough about JCPS to comment on that (and this article and… https://t.co/1GsQUlatgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump THE LIER. If it does go up it's because of what President Obama left behind. Because you haven't done shit to… https://t.co/Zy2vtb15IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[There hasn’t been a moment when I’ve been sober but idc I’m about to graduate and become an adult]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleEdmun I obsessed with the Claussen pickles 🤤🤤 and the baby dills or the pickles chips that go on burgers/sandwiches]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww... poor trumplethinskin, are you going to call another national emergency to outlaw comedy next?? IF YOU WANT T… https://t.co/CVLEDYv9dY]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some laughter. Funny Pictures Of The Day – 74 Pics #comedy #chuckle #smile #laughable https://t.co/Pe7evBRhyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fgjourney Oh I KNOW it's coming. But after 10 yrs I am like ok God.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNotScottySire last night was amazing 🤧❤️ (this is the only video where you can’t hear me fangirling in the backg… https://t.co/tlLO0bv0Il]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting news for everyone who cares about the country, politics and media. Congrats to #GrayTV and @greta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieHolbert1 YES!! You were?!? I wish I knew that before this second. I thought you moved her but went on tour...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass if you’re around me you’ll notice that I don’t say it. That hasn’t been part of my vocabulary, even in song… https://t.co/ZMpea7EiKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_ohagan i mean like deluca is harmless so i’m fine with his mer pairing but they have zero chemistry imo? yeah… https://t.co/KIco4PUirD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Na their the ones out there snap chatting there class acting like they teach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol two of my coworkers just got them to LA when we were at lunch Tuesday so this isn’t true]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Invisible Cowboy @RODEOHOUSTON 🤠 @713News  #RODEOHOUSTON #713News https://t.co/LqPL4euNr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like seeing people in the hospital letting their little kids walk around with no shoes on. THAT IS NASTY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gidgetcoyne @RepJeffries @Resist___45 I agree. He had two years of Republican control house and Senate.  Why didn'… https://t.co/xkRY0fKLhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This resonates with me! 👊🏻 It’s the difference between serving and pleasing others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubblesVampire @theboltchick @juliemason I  agree that the short clip shared by the group was a bad look for Feins… https://t.co/krZcWTR58E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a real ride or die. my favorite twin who’s rly bout that choccy milk life. love you always ❤️… https://t.co/IJSuty0Vz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brianna_byrnes1 Oh girl trust me I know. I was lucky using all the same stuff because I had both boys, but if Wes… https://t.co/n2XNEWLBl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[As well they should. I’m sure if I said the same to him Imwould be under arrest right now. #stopthedoublestandard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder You are pathetic.  You Democrat’s. No matter what he does you complain sic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and Happy #internationalwomensday to all! Today I'll 👮🏼‍♀️ be working in the @TorontoPolice Operations… https://t.co/woA9bOWmsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another home #undercontract ! Call #georgialivingteam today to help you #buy or #sell your next #home!… https://t.co/Nw9TOfHwnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayingPolitix @natehoIe @GrabEmByTheTwit @MelodieDennis3 @RunningtoResist @NatalieNsm @lalasamples… https://t.co/k1MWpOoGUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[As soon as I get my new license I am changing banks. I’ve had enough of TD. America’s most inconvenient bank.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m prettier when I cry” is my whole mood for 2019 @agedeporzio  #prettieraftercrying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatnPark , yay!!! Mini potato pancakes!! ♥️#allthefoods and here's our fave server! #putusinacommerical https://t.co/JEorrgwFXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the bass player from @planetshakers would marry me already! Been crushing for years! #winterfest19 @mywinterfest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok RDC 5084 making me feel all special..got my locker today, I go to it.. and it has my name on it. And it also had… https://t.co/jp3eWBe7RG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Do you know that this museum has lovingly tended the taxidermy statue of this goodest dog for decades, a… https://t.co/Z0BXCyx4DU]]></document><document><![CDATA[instead of asking god why, i've been asking what lesson he's trying to teach me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impinkestgirl @boba1959 @JustKathyRay @BandieraNancy @gheetar @keanothedog @KeepLadyWarm @Creativempathy3 @ldog562… https://t.co/k7WDznly3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh.  Rasheed looks like he is supposed to have a cameo in a Dave Chappelle film]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even Republicans! He’s only president to people who agree with him and go along with his lies! The republican p… https://t.co/489EvtdXFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coldhands2 how are you doing, buddy? Still making it one day at a time??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherrodBrown Trump left it to his brilliant (NOT) tariff plans instead of actually getting companies to stay here… https://t.co/pPQBkEnbQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynBlogger @TeaPainUSA It might kill their Russian campaign contributions and their bribes from billionaires/milli… https://t.co/LwDGu9sJaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially become a crazy plant lady. Had to bring my babies inside last night because it dropped down below f… https://t.co/9PQ7GIoXD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amo la sensación de caminar muy temprano los fines de semana en cualquier lugar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hershelthings Can it be made into a burrito? Can it smother a burrito?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and KG (gluth003) and a bottle of PopCrush after a long day. @ Hilton Anaheim https://t.co/T8m0LRgKZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexuslevert I haven’t been there in four years it’s LONG overdue. Miss u, hope you’re doing amazing 💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soultweeting @dka8604 @girlscouts I quit buying GS cookie a long time ago .]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's funny how artists with no insurance and no performance experience got picked for @backwoodsbash but people wit… https://t.co/jGayXXAece]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one doing harm to this country is @realDonaldTrump You are a criminal. The large white residence you should be… https://t.co/2bdb3cvjWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tia_Lunes @quisqueyana1102 @Sammy_Markle @StephInSuburbia @benzie55 @LadyVee35264999 @FrancoisOsamor @EzrasJoe2… https://t.co/AuPyFDzXic]]></document><document><![CDATA[At urgent care baptist with my daughter....emergency procedure...on mommy duty! Just cuz she's an adult doesn't mea… https://t.co/hNaSLppBzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just taking a look through the #DoomPatrol pilot episode. 🕶️🤖 #DCUDoomPatrol @DoomPatrolDCU https://t.co/sPETpSDFiT https://t.co/zOXayDFcS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuellerSheWrote Oh dang, @AriMelber just reported that AG Barr announced Mueller Report may be out by next week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliant point. Thanks again for joining us on #AXSChat each week. #cybermindschat  #RuhGlobal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren This is what I received for Valentines Day. What did you get? https://t.co/7ozuQWSllb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't Bill Maher say we are jealous of NY and CA?  CA is a garbage dump and now violence is up in NY?  Why do we w… https://t.co/ArJzTNcrwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that i've brgin casually calling @aye__bb "posk" is so amusing to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye man, Duke sucks. Why is this game so close with arguably the worst team in the ACC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendelCooper One of my best friends from college is from there/lives there! Great people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flew in from my vacation last night into ATL. Drank too much Jesus juice so I was sick all night. Woke up this morn… https://t.co/W1UR5YazQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XendraXrossing @XendraXrossing you really loving that blonde sexy wild hair @tesswigs.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker STFU and resign.  #FireKushner  #FireIvanka  #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #ResignNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Union Station Los Angeles https://t.co/YLTL4KdWvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[ORR over 30% and very acceptable safety. PDL1 positivity seems to play a role ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weirdradopinons @kkelseeey_ @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley You’re truly a mean person and the fact, if it is true, th… https://t.co/tZpMcGjiko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Micrograma @RepMaxineWaters Hahaha😂 That’s why just today not only was it reported—the American spy planes sent ba… https://t.co/SIi0VyeYRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first cup of coffee after morning yoga literally tastes like liquid gold/life force. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the point of medical insurance if you just have to pay for everything anyways? I already paid like $1200 for… https://t.co/wq9o60mFVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is such happy news. He’s one of the best pups we’ve ever seen and we’re so glad you adopted him.  Please give… https://t.co/rdxLSHlHOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTLA Omigod... he's a monster... I can't even read all the stuff he did to her while she was alive. 42M isn't enough for what happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBD TO THE GOAT , I love you so so much and have a great 21st 🥳🥳💜 @LexiRich11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheap rent ain’t always wassup, this house nasty af with nasty af tenants 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only when we have had a deep encounter with the heart of God, can we share His heart of love. If David could love l… https://t.co/nl7yOM3pgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjharrispretzer @BoSnerdley @realDonaldTrump Is it pictures of some blonde woman from a magazine cover that motivates trumps base? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In watching Cohen testify today I hear a desperate man contradict himself again and again w no evidence, hope for a… https://t.co/qqiQOydNEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phish to raise summer tour merch prices 25% to cover cost of lost revenue from tonight's webcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CfieldsVFL Orange top and orange pants are my all time favorite. Give me the white helmets though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si alguna vez compraron labiales marca Exótica debieron de darse cuenta que eran los mismos que FR🤷🏻‍♀️ no creo ser… https://t.co/YRkGidAyJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My other fav kid! @ Outback Steakhouse - Winter Springs - Tuskawilla https://t.co/j74XHM1DCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ning took us to one of her favorite spots on the island. Crab stuffed salmon, again plz!! @ Blue Giraffe Sanibel https://t.co/Bnh9qFXO2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current inventory of "Hope" Celtic Crosses. #wildflowersofscotland #arizonadesert #seasidedaisy #seashanty… https://t.co/NLglwJHM8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will probably eventually delete this later on, but enjoy! Here are a couple clips from my fight. 🤙🏽 Video cred fr… https://t.co/kw5McIY5k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller It’s cheating and it’s unfair. If I had a daughter in track in those schools, I’d pull her out. Shame… https://t.co/7UJM0vnNyp]]></document></documents></author>