<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The #arnoldclassic was TOO much fun! I got to work the quornusa booth and meet @ArnitaChampion1 . I got hooked up w… https://t.co/F3HwnjVPPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosLoret Yo no escuche música, asi que no creo que hubiese orquesta...o si? Tu que opinas @ChumelTorres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw The godless progressive left. Have you ever voted on another country's election? Moronic on every l… https://t.co/y595GohVEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS NASCAR, Columbus playing for the cup, Masters then the draft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MK64036656 @SteveDoran11 @OwenJones84 Speaking of facts, the fact is that sin is just a made-up myth of humans to… https://t.co/8HppfzViWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @joshshreck @joerhoPGH @dgulasy_Trib @gguidobooks @MikeKilroy7 @MLove_Trib @NittanyState06 @DPyda… https://t.co/Ve1sWtZLdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisPeitzman @anunlikelybrit @adam807 jumping in to say that one time I sang a song for Bill Finn, about Bill Fin… https://t.co/PSU8ITyeCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMonje27 I agree, there’s a lot we don’t know, but if you’re a cop and you walk up on someone asleep with a gun in… https://t.co/GwT9YbSsY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que les pasa a estos legisladores de Morena. Condicionar la función de las calificadoras?. No me gusta expresar mal… https://t.co/bhpCTR2Hd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go @EdiVerdugo in the #oscars2019 commercial break!! https://t.co/XbERJzcU0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop it about anti-semitism. We women don't like the descriptions of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraJBenincasa @UmbrellaAcad No. Seriously. It's Timothy Dalton at his best. I have never steered you wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing beats the adrenaline of cops knocking on the door of a party repeatedly then coming in and giving everyone a warning #IloveBPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComplexSports Seems like this is reoccurring thing for Kyrie on teams that have the potential to win championships… https://t.co/5zRyr3kLu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyeItsBen_ Bro why are you attacking me honestly just makes you look small]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really only getting 28 days out this month and I still have to pay my rent in full https://t.co/X5D2mSePgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some links from the long weekend...  @OffThePostRadio Stadium Series special with @Brian_Metzer:… https://t.co/GdcsoZRRJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@midoeru @PabloLayus En #Peru eso NO se supo puesto que el incidente ocurrio aqui en #Miami y todos los medios loca… https://t.co/p0pZkInw69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public market complex planned for Dickinson https://t.co/w69JsP7Xqd via @houstonchron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @SpeakerPelosi should have retired YEARS ago, in my opinion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the deepest depression of my life bc I’m injured and I can’t play soccer😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wasn’t it kind of my family to put all these pink puffballs on lines for me! @ Versailles, Kentucky https://t.co/5T2vUt3uRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samhaist Albums:  Brandi Carlile - The Joke Maggie Rogers - Heard It In a Past Life Robyn - Honey (!!!!! this was… https://t.co/DbLTWdj8TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcarrick Ah no, Rob.  Despite your moron article, it is in fact NOT possible to save money without effort.   Rob,… https://t.co/tkJ68Nb8uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therunchat A4 more time in the mornings... without having to get up even earlier  #runchat https://t.co/Mvoq8DxtHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laurettamylove Thanks Sweetie for the @kirstenstefanek and @skylar_shupe song RTs! Have a sweet night ladies! 😇😇😇🎶🎶💕💕💕🌙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 @NoMoreElitists Not judging just looking at the facts. He really screwed it up for allot of people… https://t.co/yNdSAGfyif]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Wake up.  2. Check the Twitter. 3. Read awesome @LydiaCoutre interview with @CommunitySolsED for… https://t.co/H6TGYrF1O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing good luck to Cougar Kid and Brodie Hampson @BrodieHampson1 racing on Sunday at @WarwickRaces for John O'She… https://t.co/jCdxEnf3IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or do other people feel bad for the dogs when people throw cheese in their face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyNameIsCheeks @RuPaulsDragRace Your doppelgänger. https://t.co/BjZE4LxBLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a few weeks I find myself reaching for my phone so much less than the people I’m with. It’s a pretty freeing… https://t.co/Pv3KzFej0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be like an award for the lady who posts the realist shit ever 😭😭😭 Fr fr @Chantelitoxo you speak nothin… https://t.co/Y04FTZ2GH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who cares Bernie. Sell one of your mansion and give your followers that money. You are an elitist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Psicovivir @LaIwua @Miguel_Pizarro A mi mismo me dio asco cuando lo leí temprano. Me pregunte que tiene en la cabe… https://t.co/tKqS1B5NpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ATLUTD tell De Boer to play 4-2-3-1 so we stop getting fucked in the back and midfield and also you might wann… https://t.co/jeGMYl7rMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salt Lake Stallions give up late lead to Birmingham Iron, fall to 0-2 in inaugural season https://t.co/CUCCwJK1HV via @KSLcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakotaLeo @jjuston Like this group that came into the Mexican place I go who were MAGA supporters and wife shushes… https://t.co/kc6EU33lUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this? This was a publicity stunt. Yall just gonna show up to the event in the same damn fit, color coordinated?… https://t.co/PBkbK9FVBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[McDowell backing up on the straightaway like Daniel Suarez popped out in front of him #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated the accomplishments and contributions of @OhioState faculty and staff at the Women's Place reception ton… https://t.co/Lnaf3WUi88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMartyFox @baalter @realDonaldTrump Wow she’s gonna lose in court so what’s the difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @revrrlewis I’m so glad you are on the side with common sense . I don’t think you have any flaws now ! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashley_nycolee Killing it, babe. Keep pushing through the struggle. Makes you stronger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Words: #harrismint #inspiration #wordstoliveby #positivethinking #share #wordsofwisdom https://t.co/BKPZjYdlVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Old Town Square - @downtownfoco in Fort Collins, CO https://t.co/4QI01Usi3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whatsinyourtoolbox #lilkim #eyewear #mens #apparel #accessories and more #money #generous #onestopshop 20% #thot… https://t.co/2GSktMlDBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Callum_Lennon @the_tpa I already left. Fatties put strain on the NHS even after they were banned from surgery if t… https://t.co/osaoGE68yH]]></document><document><![CDATA[not many people are doing what you’re doing at your age. always be proud of yourself and what you’ve accomplished w… https://t.co/erJYb0CvDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teague or Jones gonna have to get injuried cuz this man gets less than 20 mins off the bench.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hiramboyd @DaveBorcas Kinda feel he gets a shot unless he really tanks in spring training. Do think the Ramirez si… https://t.co/3TTBmkKF5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coldzera conjulgando o verbo carregar: - eu carrego o @FalleNCS, eu carreguei o @fer, vou carregar o @felperaa e t… https://t.co/qhhNKT1xvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/dKeFAJnJY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgMagazineUK @cellar_darling Happy 75th Birthday to #MickAvory of #TheKinks @davedavieskinks .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Accept you're not relevant anymore, will make your life easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Engelland meant to say in that Kia commercial is "You will never see me inside a Kia".  He don't drive a Kia,… https://t.co/Vk8W9DtXVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Smith24 Ah you are right. Definitely will help the bullpen log jam for final sport]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had 8️⃣5️⃣ amazing #RamFam🐏 students show up for Saturday tutoring, the most we’ve ever had! Absolutely fantasti… https://t.co/FaeTq2s8rI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my Michael Bradley slapped my ass idk how I would feel, (definitely good)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni 🔮’s Del Mundo Del #Espectáculo @mhonividente 🧿 @ClubMhoniFans @magdaproducer ✨📺🎬🎥… https://t.co/9jNZLT6pub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denton Ryan is 55-4 the past 4 years. Before that, since 2009 have won 115 games total. Not in the Top 5 discussion… https://t.co/GIF1qqMDMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be next to impossible to remove from this nation all those who are undocumented. There are literally milli… https://t.co/sx6bBw0810]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MooreForGeorgia How dare you mention God as you support abortion - the killing of his creation. You are delusional… https://t.co/YUWGvk3NVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm using a lot of metallics in these recent portraits: bronze, copper, gold, and silver-always mixed with another… https://t.co/LrdUj3bvqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to AOF Squash on clinching the Founder’s League Championship today, 4-3 against Hotchkiss! https://t.co/WMrdRrl5Kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eaner0919 @mai_yo_nessa Lunes fought in front of about 50 people at midnight on Fury and Wilder]]></document><document><![CDATA[I having a horrible week. This is my current escape.  #gym #backinthegrind # @ LA Fitness https://t.co/osOXaJKDeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timarific @Adef187 @MercedesB3nz Might have to reconsider my decision now 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ Beautiful. Inspirational.  Humbling.  Encouraging.  Thank You for sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socialism_doer @Shaumama I haven't heard anyone argue that we just endorse or don't and that's the end of the issu… https://t.co/b6uD7iJZT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStigall Ralph #Northam was a victim of institutional racism. 😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDos @Pabstpondhockey @purenoiserecs Come to Buffalo next year and play in the @LabattUSA pond hockey tournament!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to tweet a video but it won’t let me 🙄 add me on snap to see  maplesqb12]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not going to say Huntsville has the best libraries in the world.  I’m just going to note that I just bought a *… https://t.co/5YOgqTzAlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to have @Browns K Greg Joseph @greg_joseph1 back on the FAU Coaches Show. No @FAU_Football player has ever be… https://t.co/mVhqkyoJwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why boastest thou thyself in mischief, O mighty man? the goodness of God endureth continually.” Psalms 52:1 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funtimeseddie No shit.  And make it Havarti you savages- American is so YESTERDAY. (eyeroll)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior Was just having this conversation with a younger friend of mine last night. How white supremacy even… https://t.co/1DUcxUKXww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFILE @RobCalfee @JudgeJeanine doesn't even understand American law, much less sharia law. Her brand of racism has… https://t.co/OCz5PyAqbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charged Shot Gamescast Episode 104: My kinkshame is to kinkshame  https://t.co/A9kAOBWXrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel me cuz 😭 deadass showed downtown and then a block away from downtown like we wasn’t gonna know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUEtheTrex @DOfaquarius Not possible in a Tesla with their new “Dog Mode”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pab200uk @John_J_C_Moss What do you mean set a precedent? The kind of president we have at least once every five y… https://t.co/nfBaQATfRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We stand together in betterment of each other.  Unfortunately, there are those who's only wish is to demean and dim… https://t.co/rTgEugQBrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful,Beautiful,Amazing song about my God’s love for me &amp; you!  https://t.co/BeVano7jS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitneyarner @iansensei Ian you can just buy real weed. No need to buy snake oil from Christians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComplexMusic @Complex Where can I go listen to the entire tape? No luck with Spotify 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, it’s spear-mint not spear-a-mint. Sorry #PronunciationPolice where have you been all my life with a ticket for that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curse you @Disneyland for getting #GetYourEarsOn permanently stuck in my head. Ugh! Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest available exclusively on Getty Images 💃🏻: sarah_aileen_  #model #women #fashion #beauty #portrait #bnw… https://t.co/nGBUS87WlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kmtc4b0aLa we got rid of illegals an refugees an a traitor an co conspirators the RCMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalDemIda @rulesofblazon @EJDionne I’m starting to think you just hate men]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crushing loss for the UHA community and Hopkinsville. RIP Dick Weaver. https://t.co/mbNpUixtav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hah! Gov. Cuomo Whines to Trump About NY State's Budget Deficit - Trump Tells Him to Start Fracking… https://t.co/NLtsgm1Kfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generally speaking, are gay politicians too self-absorbed and self-centered to adequately represent ALL of their co… https://t.co/vmCnpbr4hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJCMorning I was really disappointed because this was the game I was looking forward to. If anything this is the… https://t.co/7c0zksAit1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilimateo reunites with her beloved sea. 😂😂 @ Clearwater Beach https://t.co/zG4sbwtiGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[During Nam, a lot of Minors that had commented Stature Tory rape were given a choice. Go to jail or go to War ! Old… https://t.co/CcPXLBko0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RugbyPodcast Hate to speculate and write Newcastle off but if they go down what happens with Mark Wilson? He is a… https://t.co/wqMEPo2vH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re not really criminals. They’re just coming to apply for employment with Amazon ....oooh, wait...… https://t.co/T2O6WfNubw]]></document></documents></author>