<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i luv when my job makes me feel so bad about myself when i already feel like i’m the worst at everything !]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in Washington DC Saturday February 23, join us in walking in Race for 7! https://t.co/2rgmDrwtm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[In sisterhood with @AleLaPlebe #KeepAleFree #AbolishICE https://t.co/B9q0TUYnhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @iyem1 Though, with the Ides of March around the corner, perhaps Julius is the appropriate answer.    O… https://t.co/zgCNjG6jCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing belated Vday dinner tonight with the boo. https://t.co/3OFIVc4aPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scopedbylarry I have been through this &amp; it’s painful, I know. Hope you feel better soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz Bless you, bless you, bless you. For your courage, perseverance, support, and willingness to see past your own pain to help others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dynamic, narrative drawing event tomorrow night @ADG800 with physical storyteller @StacyEWalker1 #actors #model… https://t.co/FHGaOnNQzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joenassar77 Wisdom through experience gives the direction. See you soon handsome. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent one of those “Fuck them kids” meme to My Mama,she wasn’t pleased... Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @KyleKashuv @McDonalds @ChickfilA Chicken minis!  nuff said!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinfoox Hi 👋! Would love to chat about Bustle with you! Email me zahra@bustle.com if you’re interested.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theskiff13 This is true. And what praise or thanks do I get? Zero. That’s why I’m convinced most of it is made up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Xj09i5kMce 4:17 not at all mad if you simply changed your mind !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allisonperri1st i hope it gets better!❤️ Sending positive vibes your way! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @padenpur He’s s tired old man. Well, a tired old nasty person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMZBEST1 @Aviva_Polonsky @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff I can pass a drug test. You can’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMurph24 She's a both sider.  That is how we got Trump.  Fuck the justice democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Murphy and David J.  The Flat Field. Awesome show. @ The Phoenix Concert Theatre https://t.co/eidF5fzPx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SammyBoy24 @KingJames @MAL___ @thisisrory @JoeBuddenPod @JoeBudden @Slvter He has a job as a hip hop historian too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump tax reform in action. We made a little less in income but are paying about $8000 more in federal income tax for 2018. NOT HAPPY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlaRedDirtCC @KyleCoroneos Was at a Jinks concert this weekend, and I was so pissed at the people talking behind u… https://t.co/47tLSxFZ9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[En estos tiempos también debería ser considerado un lujo tener una buena y larga conversación.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is truly special,never held a job until elected mayor at 53;  lived off welfare/with 4 different wom… https://t.co/4Ao4QIOXGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Groups intend to sue over new Wyoming grizzly hunt law https://t.co/A2llCnuZvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedPill78 is doing a great job pulling apart all of the recent events. What is interesting, although we have follo… https://t.co/Cbf7SghJf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely review for two wonderful Canadian singers! @MireilleSoprano  and @meghanjlindsay 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGSentinel @KirstinMorrell @CharlieAngusNDP @Canada Without intending to be harsh, other than critiquing me, what… https://t.co/7nbz8zuk0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work day from hell, eye's are heavy as anvils, it's that time... I'm out! https://t.co/xt7QKnw1Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sonia554 When first posted, she hadn't mentioned the name of the restaurant.  Her post then practically went viral… https://t.co/DkOyegacNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bond with my niece on so many levels, BUT one of the small silly things I love to do is let her choose my eyeshad… https://t.co/Gk0YhLzk6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost  are u going to publish how a disabled NYPD Det and a first responder of September 11th (me) and th… https://t.co/muNOfLVJTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t understand just how much I love my bed, like that is my happy place. If I leave it after getting all co… https://t.co/DhcmbSVCdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robjh1 @rdp24k She must live in a district completely made up of Muslims  who think just like her.  We are being i… https://t.co/AT2EuoXW3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriots @Edelman11 You are a fabulous club! We are huge fans (my grandson and I)! We will NOT be supporting the P… https://t.co/R9WBdMSwaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a blast tonight at the Vermilion County Farm Bureau trivia night! 🥳🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhabLives In my previous buyer position I bought romances based on the cover.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my best friend in the whole entire world! She is the strongest, kindest, funniest, and most wonde… https://t.co/hHW23VuaNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Never before in the history of MLS —or any other major professional sports league in the U.S.—has there been a del… https://t.co/txHaaw6ZqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gender Equality project at Pérez IB Exhibition. Great work team! @2BMULTILINGUAL @HildaELLCoach1 @perezpioneers… https://t.co/aBViBaptA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“we’re headed to the plane station!”  -my VeRy competent 20y/o roommate on 3 hours of sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBread_OfLife @DavidHarris707 @DavidAJMHoward @Jj051301 @d_ast777 @RosaDeliadelos1 @RosaryMysteries @satribesman… https://t.co/KHGNngUtCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep being reminded about daylight savings and I just want to remind people that our technologies take care of it… https://t.co/itWkQcjfAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I love whole milk.  And it’s most delicious in a champagne glass with about 4 ice cubes so every sip is soooo… https://t.co/aNhK9q3V00]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAG a baby pink fan! I absolutely love this soft pearly pink from @gelish ! 😍 #babypink #softpink #lightpink… https://t.co/ZZ3PFR8bsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNCOmusic Thank you guys for an amazing show tonight! 🖤 #CNCOWorldTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zacksoto @Marvel For reaaal. In the next scene she yelled at Remy for literally no reason besides his existing so that felt more on brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently he’s a user, not part of the scheme. Question: Where do these big spenders get their tips on these place… https://t.co/9DlJs1797h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaDavisNews @RussianEmbassy What's cooking is your mother country, Russia, for it's human rights violations, fo… https://t.co/81yIs1nmaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol me and char really have convos about what type of noodles we eatin lolololol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're a picky eater (not veg or anything) JUST someone who hates FLAVOR then  F U C K  you you F U C K I N G  c… https://t.co/FMu8Zq1VNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @LindseyGrahamSC Whatever the Russians found on Republicans when they hacked the RNC has turned man… https://t.co/fuS8aB1wB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck Terrence ,so glad you get to go 🏡!! Will continue praying for you &amp; for a safe trip.🙏🏼🙋🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[but this is one of my fav thing about tarot, I see so many new perspectives and get to keep a little of piece of everyone I read]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidaCuevas Ud es una campeona!!! No soy mexicana pero me sentí muy orgullosa al verla en la alfombra y cantando ta… https://t.co/f9mOORywqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very strange...this police force needs as much if not more help than the Palestinians...if ever there was an oppres… https://t.co/bVo0U3nuHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the donations to the St Jude Mathathon ❤ @DrTemp @s2mjyates @MsFrevertVDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egrasmussen I wish I could blame my emotions on pregnancy because I am losing it over here!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREYS ANATOMY HAS ME HAPPY SOBBING RIGHT NOW. But I know it’s not going to last 😬😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seth_yoder any kind of toast, right now it's a delicious multi-grain but sourdough or raisin bread is probably the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga finally watched A Star is Born.  You, beautiful lady, were amazing!  I am walking away in tears, not just… https://t.co/1APQUGQ0Xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellow Joker fans: If you’re always trying to be normal - you will never know how amazing you can be! 💜💙 #BeKind… https://t.co/ftv4ZSKMTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shilee having fun in the ❄️SNOW❄️?!? #southernutah #ItNeverSnows #utahgreatestsnowonearth @ Washington, Utah https://t.co/9FQexTH2i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolidFooting @celliottability Congratulations. That’s fantastic Julie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadelynKnecht Thanks for telling me. I've never actually seen it in person. I don't know why I've been thinking it… https://t.co/MXVPIxozdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy your day! @dana_krabbe  Love you! ❤️#march1st https://t.co/yg8OuXOS2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeAreks @daisiesinboca @ArianaGrande @Starbucks we shouldn’t be praising people for doing the bare minimum dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ride-inside #Granfondonj #bicycle #kinetictrainer #trainingpeaks #jamis  #homelesssolutions #ridingforhomes Thank… https://t.co/webt3mVx6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAGU____ push your hips up hard to make sure your leg completely gets over your hand so that you’re able to get th… https://t.co/KfPIASnzYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my friends #48isgreat🎂 @ The Boathouse Tiki Bar &amp; Grill - Fort Myers https://t.co/6GfKVWGr4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You did say nothing happened in your campaign that you didn't know about.  Now it all comes togeth… https://t.co/pZzxDQyWec]]></document><document><![CDATA[It happened and he was wearing a MAGA hat but he tipped my liberal ass $30 and told me my name was pretty so I guess I still win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganElaine_ You should definitely do it!! ☺️ I do love mine I’ve just had it for a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My God Son lives in Hawaii,  we have a 4 hour time difference.  When he calls its midnight here.. 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey #FuckFord winter ❄️ is over #SpringIsComing 🙏🌹🍀 u ready B’s 💅👛☔️#ForThePeople 🎩🐽🎩 #IWD2019 #IWD19 #IWD… https://t.co/7r3E60KxMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[as for Mau5, I have respect for the apology but I have no doubt it’s fueled by a PR team’s reminder where this can… https://t.co/aMddZ1MwSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isham_Literacy @nankr1120 @SFecich @sarahdateechur @smgaillard @EMercedLearning @mlarson_nj @SteinbrinkLaura… https://t.co/YNgzAuO3ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWildeGlobal 4th D in ice time after 2 periods...possible he's got a virus as well?  #gohabsgo https://t.co/PpeUAkElWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always sad when you hear “alright everybody that’s gonna be it for today’s daily vlog” 😭 I just always want to… https://t.co/XIk8EgvkkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armonandtrey Spontaneous Total Combustion 🔥🔥🔥🔥 @armonandtrey https://t.co/JdS4OMj5jL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex ending his ranting input on my exes: “I think that’s the saddest thing I’ve ever said about a relationship, and I’ve been DIVORCED.” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[6am mcdonalds breakfast runs after a night of dancing with your friends &gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to keep fighting Meredith Hughes '16!! So proud of you! #titans4life]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 photos show the adorable pangolin in all its glory https://t.co/LU2EBGLQFw via @NatGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGLearns I have a rule and I've proven it to myself over and over again. If I'm complaining about my students, cha… https://t.co/B5CPLg41aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk that shit!!! #HisAndHers #PullUp #GetYourTicketsTODAY @ Some Like It Black https://t.co/3s2bcGJXz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to go in late tomorrow to get my bagel and coffee but damn students want me there early 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeLong22 @GroupHomepage @SunshineLK10 @SmithsCoffeepot @prokaski @RL9631 @fuzzypoppy54 @Linda18319822… https://t.co/ZDOtURw7Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukasbattle What is it, that he says? "I'm country, you're saven? I want you, all to my self now?" What is it??? Lol, I love this!!!🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what I’m thinking about.... #NationalMargaritaDay @BethANJax https://t.co/4sYk4fjsMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone help! I would like to be able to sleep tonight without several game recap conversations! 😂 #Basketball… https://t.co/PBw47B1ANj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting day w/ @peckwilliams working with Ts on  #msftia Imagine Academy in Garland ISD @GarlandTech https://t.co/RUFxW0unaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BOOMER4_Life @Markdunlop1 @news_newsy @davidmweissman @KamalaHarris Ridiculous statement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Together, yes; alone, not so much—Inspiration from Spin Class, February ... https://t.co/JvBaMJVYXj via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[and I always try to avoid arguments, cause it’s honestly just unnecessary and I usually could gaf less. but I got sum to get off my chest 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My neighbors daughter was on that swim team.  She graduated this past year!  Sorry to read the swim is no longer go… https://t.co/Q2bYqMK9Mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WizardDeO_Z The curly fries get me every time. 10/10 would cut someone off to get @Arbys fries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daralebrun @tomwatson WTH did he inject into his overblown head?  So weird, it's like he tightened and moved it ar… https://t.co/XZxQRlsFUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKornacki @TheRickWilson Stop including Sanders in your poll he is not a DEMOCRAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi niño me chifla mucho. 🤤❤️  Aún no entiendo el porqué de la velita jajajajajajaja. 🤨 https://t.co/gGGCaqdpCO]]></document></documents></author>