<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SheinelleJones should have mentioned that many stores honor #presidentsday sales prices if purchased about 14 days… https://t.co/vERqoJAAst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetDownin @JeffersonLeeTV Been that way since John Brown. Protestantism is the strongest drug America’s got. I think it killed Rick James.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GareyPrice31 @alain_becile01 Une boîte de condom serait bien aussi pour préserver l’humanité]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TigresPorLaRemontada #HoyGanamos #Tigres #VamosTigres #SomosTigres #Concachampions #Tigres vs #Saprissa https://t.co/qFbVlAUG3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PodcastBLU @BluRadioCo @JulioBorges Era la estrategia perfecta, se sabe que Maduro tiene el control territorial, l… https://t.co/osRgp5x49c]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖕KC @KellyannePolls #kellyannecornflake #absolutthisbch 🍸 #wrong #bruja #JaredLoveWeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_SmexX @TheExo__ Mat no disrespect you are not good at cs. I will play with you but all you say is that they chea… https://t.co/f6r5osLLiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin’ at the bar with a drink and fresh script at the Hilton Waterfront Beach Resort while Kristy is getting a p… https://t.co/TkIJOXElwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is where the day job has taken me today. Not a bad view, huh? @ Illinois State Capitol https://t.co/V450Lj5AHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this. and I guess this solidifies my move to LA. Because holy shiiiiitttt AHHHHHH THIS IS REAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS HOOPS FINAL: @ETHSports 68, @Glenbrook_south 60. Titans season comes to end in sectional. #22CMGBS @TitanBoosters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wanyamorris64 I watched this and thought this. 17-20 years from now this is gonna play in the club somewhere and t… https://t.co/j9h1PLxhEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st concert of 2019 - @timbarryrva @ The Taphouse Grill https://t.co/Oz1KlSxQEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion. Fuck that fan That’s the only power Dolan has in the situation. You want him to just take it. Fu… https://t.co/y0ZTW8ulUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're beautiful. You're loved. You're needed. You're alive for a reason. You're stronger than you think. You're go… https://t.co/Q8xvbLfRl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darlainky Okay. That one is dad. Major penalty. You got ten minutes in the sun bin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlSacco49 Yeah this report leaves me scratching my head as to why? What are they thinking! He has sucked ass from day one!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsReesesOrNone @OriginalFunko @TheAcademy It does indeed exist! FYE Exclusive! But as far as I know, it hasn’t been released yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mauiyank @errhoads @kasie @ScottWalker @MittRomney @LindseyGrahamSC Not a journalist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@210RaisedMe @TerrenceEdwards @BleacherReport @mcten Exactly Zion is only what 18 or 19? People acting like he can’t get better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StillConservati @ggreenwald OK stillconservative. I think you need to do some reading yourself. And try opening your eyes as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@degomikec If you think DK Metcalf is about to gain “more speed” he should be taken 1st overall]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m up ... had a dream that i ran over a dogs leg and out of guilt i agreed to pay the lady’s vet bills and they ca… https://t.co/YWelyiRFb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iameddiepinero #yourworldwithin my number 1 running playlist @YourWorldWithin https://t.co/i75Qso5e4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked to see a picture or screen shot of these tickets before I purchased them from a third-party person. That pers… https://t.co/xNd8hAMq3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash The biggest dummy of them all he thank he got mr Trump that is a freaking joke just like him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distributor_Rex @TomGMS @JWBeigs @dankdaddydave @champybeats @DrDistribuDad @TaylorRMarshall Talking about politic… https://t.co/Fi8loMYv1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea we were getting snow until @celticsvoice just mentioned it on #celtics telecast.   Gorman is also a m… https://t.co/nVACfJmKfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fstoppers The image I will take tomorrow!  When there are no more tomorrows, I won't be around to answer that ques… https://t.co/w6NanQiFod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fishon2731 @DonnaMarron @l_abbatecola @Tim89373846 SMART crew right here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachShiffman Don't blame it on me!  This spread guy loves 3 point stance.  Seriously, I've never seen any research on how this is a thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lanie and I drove through the same exact storm to hays at 2 in the morning last year idk I’m going home lmao hopefu… https://t.co/wBF5I0a2CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, @leesilee151’s bf is cousins with kacey musgraves. Like, they grew up together 😭😭😭😭😭 #ETXLiving]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepted the challenge from @Coachbfitz to post 7 covers of books I love; no reviews,no explanations- just the cove… https://t.co/Zx6E16i6WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶The Yankee imperialists come to play🎶 @FishboneSoldier @woodywoodstraw @FishboneFilm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRoseWXYZ Ummmm you do realize it is about Scott Bell right? #FreeScottBell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Farm Table: Dry Irish Stout by @beausallnatural @ The Pilot Tavern — https://t.co/ebSTQQozOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[making solar great again. Rofl Making California a leader in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels$]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie: Fighting with my Family (@ AMC Plaza Bonita 14 - @amctheatres for Fighting with My Family in National City,… https://t.co/ypA31UHZnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredNBCLA @RodneyPeete9 @RogginAndRodney @AM570LASports @kfigg1 @vicfeelingyou https://t.co/ssa35y33kY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport @realDonaldTrump while we're at it let's also investigate Pelosi Schumer Muller and the rest of the c… https://t.co/InlW08TCKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[They've Been Planning It Since The Beginning Of Time (2019) https://t.co/ODLusRkWJI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealLouBega @JonahNRO @RealJacobPerry If the crimes were so in plain sight then why is there no evidence of col… https://t.co/uE9eFEoXMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historyinmoment @LouiseQuoVadis She really was #sexy. #WhosZoominWho? #RKelly let his hormones talk and run over t… https://t.co/9Gulf0svSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4hill2018 • two hour church?✔️ • weekly missionary call/texts? ✔️ • no more “Mormon” branding?✔️ • facial hair? 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The news station intentionally slandered my name for years I have been unable to get an explanation as to why those… https://t.co/JQ65vKaPxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legacy media Op-Eds are approaching their rock bottom. WaPo, NYT, and other important media brands would be wise to… https://t.co/se90YS87vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fitzstrength275 @alliseeisgold @ChamizoFrank @FloWrestling @Benaskren @MiddSouthWRESTL @MNLionsWrestlin So if I came up could we do lunch?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samueleteeee @EVeracidad @notelocreastodo @dexamina_ @gabrielrufian Más grave es juzgar una ideología y encima no… https://t.co/ivjZGnVTsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigbillshater @ekim_yeldarb @Briteeye777 @18hariprakash18 @AmyCarter3110 @SassySouthern10 @Redtowel4… https://t.co/XGSdm1Ktvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatinaStevis @jbarro #Boeing -9% pre-market will cost $DJIA ~240 pts on open. I assume all 737 Max 8 planes will b… https://t.co/qRh3xhLW7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hundreds stood at Brampton's Garden Square, in a vigil for 11 year old Riya Rajkumar.   People's hands cradled over… https://t.co/hBoV06ZB1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3 decisions we make in every circumstance is: (1) What am I going to focus on? (2) What does this situation/eve… https://t.co/hcRz7hfnfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinelizadrew Him? Me?  No, it was a subtweet of a UW prof I follow - spurred by a tweet that was 100% not problem… https://t.co/6orgO8uors]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Kites rise highest against the wind, not with it.”   - Winston Churchill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @KattyKayBBC But He already has enough to do a lot of damage! 'Between that and what the NY Attorney Gen… https://t.co/syfiB9w90e]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what? Might say fuck it and apply to the Ruth Lily with some drafts ion care]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony of wanting to get out the house but also not wanting to do anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panekbill @BriankgambleNE By line 3 I was thinking bail money would be on the list....]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s all this talk about an 18 year old kid shutting down for the rest of the season? Man sports are really diffe… https://t.co/gDy0c19kDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElectriKLiDD @CanIBeRell @idalismediatv @MeekMill You speak a a a English boy ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Chicago Police Chief is completely obliterating #JussieSmollet right now and RIGHTFULLY SO! They need to prose… https://t.co/y0P5NuaESw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders isn’t running in 2020. He just thinks it’s 2016 and is still refusing to acknowledge his loss and concede... 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MudCreekNation Posted we were having Lunch Monday at the Westside shop. Next time I will ping you in Advance-My bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me tonight at 7pm on @KCPT for #RuckusKC. Ruckettes discuss latest @KCIAirport developments, @JacksonCountyMO… https://t.co/VTkoV0lW5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kris_tea @El_Cabron_87 Man is dead in sin and doesn't desire God, so if the individual is unregenerate it takes mu… https://t.co/VIDZ7EmkNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaFdaCabal Muy bien María FDA;la jep es el tribunal de inquisicion de farc;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu You’re disgusting, take your liberal socialist ass to the border and walk in the border patrol shoes! You… https://t.co/YARkOMRUfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the waiter is bringing the food to your table https://t.co/jCRGp9nE4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus was not guilty, but he suffered for those who are guilty to bring you to God. 1 Peter 3:18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickersonESPN Welcome to this terrible brotherhood.  I lost my Jackie 9 years ago after 5 years.  People who fight… https://t.co/F4rfmonAoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwj5596 @JB1544 😂 see i never said he could be an all star or the best player on a team I just said he still a gre… https://t.co/kiCZdpND5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we know who will be taking over for Gary Frank's.... hopefully it's you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I really don’t understand what is meant by reparations. It is very scary to imagine how one might calculate… https://t.co/Gj1jo9r725]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @GOP: @NRA President @OliverLNorth like @MichaelCohen212 is also an ADMITTED deceiver of Congress  and now spen… https://t.co/oujdycf7Nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished with work, the driver was actually going in the wrong direction, when I asked him why he cancelled the trip. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noctiilio @twinstails 1/2 Want to be clear that https://t.co/PKNh57JY70 neither has an "official [F]rench translat… https://t.co/6aQKGYYiff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMurphTHS Do you think there will be hints of mutants in the Eternals film?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedSox. The Red Sox are #mlbworldseries #Champions and So is @shimlin who won #AGT on #NBC in 2018 and there newes… https://t.co/qqkI6JhpH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyKaboom @bradleyu Kaboom!  Charter us a bus back in Peoria!!  Haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve know Jonathan for a while you  have to be happy for him cause I don’t know who’s been a bigger wiz Khalif… https://t.co/kae99oFIXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you need this for your job sites @Iraceamtb. https://t.co/WH5ED1FEpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[temperature down 38°F -&gt; 35°F humidity up 86% -&gt; 93% wind 3mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incident appears to have been “something” lit on fire. “White Allie’s we appreciate you all, but don’t go lighting… https://t.co/lN80Nq2Ear]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Smiling in your Toyota is way better than crying in your Ferrari.”    - @garyvee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texasgirl1968 @RNCastaldo @AngelGotti5 @realDonaldTrump @KaraSewellTV I think that’s a reasonable assessment that… https://t.co/ardJXDZGzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MairavZ @PeterBeinart Why exactly does it deserve wide circulation. Confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealmark60 God is Good All the Time Congratulations on being Cancer Free https://t.co/kOpodjbmHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dude just busted out the all khaki fit in my class and I wouldn’t even have come if I would have known I was g… https://t.co/eiBMTVfIOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner There are many millions of Americans in your way, crazy unhinged snowflake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that can’t wait till baseball season? Not to mention, baseball season means golf season. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's summer in West Palm Beach!  Cards vs Astros https://t.co/2kjrRQyD10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOELBALTAZARCAU Se deberia ir al fondo pero con estos viscales corructos, todoa quedaran en blanco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/B9nUKP3r8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @MitchellsCleve for hosting our #CIFF43 Program Guide release party!  And thanks to the 300+ Festival fan… https://t.co/YHYl1X2KFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuntKimmie_GG @shape_u_up @cnnbrk And you don't know me, and yet you said all I do is hate. So please don't even t… https://t.co/qTKeS8NnG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbated @dneedles12 @mitchnelles I am not sure what to make of +/- but when looking at the boxscore, It stood out t… https://t.co/RjfoESid5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAT1PRO @MattKEZI @KEZI9 @ChynnaGreene @MarisaWoloszyn @KEZI9WX @ORStatePolice @EugenePolice @LaneSheriffOR… https://t.co/9lTsB5HHHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dan8570 If he plays football he cant bitch about nobody wanting him. He has to refrain from playing in order to co… https://t.co/yXMjLJGeng]]></document><document><![CDATA[#caminerosconsulting PROCESO EN LA TÉCNICA DE RUBBLIZING PARA PAVIMENTOS DE CONCRETO. https://t.co/ymeGn3D99u]]></document></documents></author>