<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@nyspawtsguy_spi @HOLLYWOODdeezy @DanGrazianoESPN He’s actually just barely a top 40 safety]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes the great economy! Over 55% of families are one paycheck away from financial ruin. MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN?… https://t.co/kyXs3NqLUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELP ME GET MY NEW MUSIC VIDEO "CHECK ME" TO 1,000 VIEWS!✅📊 PLEASE LEAVE A 👍🏽 SUBSCRIBE!!📲 THANK YOU!  - G~Lo Barzz… https://t.co/dzxNQcHqwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nascar_opinion Exciting race. Amazed and bummed for the 95 team. Not a Denny fan, but I’m happy they won for JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my coworker texted me saying someone came into my store asking for me and gives me details but now left me wonde… https://t.co/DlSkkdfTSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalism “happens” where people are free.  Socialism has to be “imposed” on free people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can confirm, #AStarIsBorn is even better the second time around ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye @ShannonSharpe try to get some rest tonight you know @RealSkipBayless bout to have a field day on ol Bron Bron and them Laker boys 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiSportsHomer @KamalaHarris And it’s bs. I’ve not paid several hospital bills simply because they didn’t tell me… https://t.co/6yxtkK1udC]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG the #incredicoaster was way better than I could have imagined!!! @DisneylandAP @Disneyland @DisneylandToday… https://t.co/nneYpIuDhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bannerite You can never take your eye off the target or you may be the target]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDeniVal Breads Dry As Shit On Stage Had Me Cryin https://t.co/GgdrLBlUNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Charles Barkley advised on national TV: if you are going to break the law; dont pay with a check!  LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyndseyfifield @NGrossman81 Problem comes when diversity is presented as obstacle to “unity” or strength. Diversit… https://t.co/7VsqztFdk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaleigh Bierne hits for @TZeeAthletics, its 39-36 3:17 left https://t.co/POBSNtFPq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champwebdotnet I'd be fine with it, if it is a all expenses paid trip. Teams shouldn't have to foot the bill to tr… https://t.co/se9UcxwBRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder since he declared today: to serve a full two terms Bernie would have to live to 86 or 87 in the most stres… https://t.co/53gwd7v2wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westy7278 @JohnKincade @KingJames He would be the3rd option there...he’s had a fabulous run and is easily a top 10 all time player !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still convinced Shane Battier and Carlos Boozer are the same person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made me smile today, check out @SweetPe46692507 looks freakin delicious 😋😜😃johncampbellmacofficial #actorslife… https://t.co/JcTqnwf2pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Can't we just enjoy the #SWHolidaySpecial as a special thing in itself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaWR8 @petluvers4Trump @ReneeCarrollAZ @joegooding @LVNancy @MahuRascal @mikandynothem @SuperEliteTexan… https://t.co/aJph61g2yC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you search gofundme to find if there is one to buy the Patriots if the franchise is revoked ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CenterHavana @Allurelively @jguaido No es un títere, los títeres de los cubanos comunistas son la mal llamada FAN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, let’s elect a socialist just because my college debt won’t be as much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[(•_•) &lt;)   )╯i /    \  \(•_•) (   (&gt;  am /    \   (•_•) &lt;)   )&gt;  sad. /    \]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day of the week it don’t matter what time it is. I know you could hear me. I don’t care what you got, how you… https://t.co/bbJCPnYgXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@30SecFight Besides Ali Tyson was the greatest fighter until the robbed him of his time]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s high-five Friday...greeting students in the morning and in the hallways is definitely one of the things I miss… https://t.co/sWdGqdY36K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh You really have to wonder upon whom this President &amp; Republican Party would have turned our guns in WWII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck on messaging. I’ve seen folks complain about their HOA on home values - without mention of the financial… https://t.co/rGQiPs6ePU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lurkinazzbennyd @So_Icy_Shach @LOYALJACC So what you getting at Benny D ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanieVanHalen @JanieVanHalen Hey...Good Morning and Happy Monday! Hope you had a nice weekend. Prayers you,… https://t.co/8IOjQ8Bh1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet the people of Venezuela once said we will never be a Socialist country??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RotoPat Still did better than Donald Trump’s American Wasteland https://t.co/F0HM5lr5vD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cerridwensheart You are so spot on. Songs allow memories to come to life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update 2: There are now two broken seats in first class. Lmao am I on a prank tv show @AmericanAir ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilsonRoseline1 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump I think I she liked you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tony_3163 @kashthefuturist I would argue that some professors lack empathy. As long as AI doesn’t develop an ego a… https://t.co/2AQgMURuVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milano's tweet was a bit hippy dippy, but the responses go FAR beyond mocking that. We get a decisive demonstration… https://t.co/QvXoQqoHun]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve resisted railing on these idiotic commie takes I’ve seen this week, but can’t stand it anymore:  Per this fuck… https://t.co/f6jTMzXC5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Wainwright wearing Jordan Binnington’s number https://t.co/rXbh3THvey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some fantastic stuff here including the real Pudge tagging out Berra and Meacham at the plate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patottas 🤣😂🤣😂 ni el chaton enrique sabe cómo llegó al #tri 🤣😂😂 todo seleccionador tiene a su cadaver Valdez https://t.co/Q2l5a3pDFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I think dershowitz is the only sane Democrat in America !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis Jesus nor any of His Apostles in the New Testament never told us to communicate with dead Christians… https://t.co/NlBUz7ujQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @Todd_Gutner temp in Topsham is -1 and crystal clear skies and no wind. Hope you have a good day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hardest pill we have to swallow sometimes in life is... that God will sometimes take something good, to give you better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graves County’s Brittany Harrison will sign with Southeastern Illinois College Friday. @graves_softball]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 25th, 2019 (2) Lake Series - Lake Michigan  https://t.co/Pw5Lu7ILEd https://t.co/otccvI5w1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris @SaraCarterDC Have him show up in front of Judge Jeanine I’d love to see him in her court]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews Reported as "news" for the 8th straight day. Let. It. Go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 4th birthday to Cole. He had a great time.  Thanks for everyone that came to celebrate. @ Belle Timbre, Brand… https://t.co/s3ofzlTk2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive… https://t.co/GsAJW2PhUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Cuomo is not a news anchor.  He just pushes his own extreme left wing agenda.  #CNNfakenews]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the Houston #Rivals3StripeCamp, DL Chidozie Nwankwo will visit #LSU. He has a #GeauxTigers offer. https://t.co/L4SgpBFFBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertGiesey1 @AlanWannemaker @pinerat @WVTM13 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS If anyone with children want to bet on big… https://t.co/fnGLzLoNAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish there was a DVD version w/ American subs for this. 😀 #SuperSentai #SuperSentaiSaikyoBattle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaltonBarnes @TheHarper88 Let’s hype this up and make it a pay-per-view. Or at least broadcast it on my twitch 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would’ve have The Revival beat the living piss out of Roman Reigns  after their loss. 🤷🏽‍♂️. Seems only way to ge… https://t.co/TKlhVGlKFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers sitting Ingram for a sore shoulder but continuing to put Josh Hart out there on 1 leg is wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mejor manera de disfrutar una @Corona_MX  escarchada mientras espero la deliciosa pizza https://t.co/RdLeSz0PDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liverquake666 That’s right. Down goal, wait until 3 min left and put in Ockford for Cummings #StahreLogic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check this out! Great analysis at the American Prospect: https://t.co/y4yDQiabuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green lights means they don't have the super license fully yet #F1Testing #F1 #F1tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was able to see the homie @nicolaymusic and the #HotAtNights at citywinerydc last night. No lie, his solo work and… https://t.co/UbjrhGBX6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Brilliant Achievement of Imran Khan and Qamar Bajwa https://t.co/cbWK2BrXDk via @YouTube PAF could have killed… https://t.co/jJ9I0Ly0RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CKurtzman @benmaller @DArcyWaldegrave @radiosportnz I was gonna say that!  Way to go Ben!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hipismo #ChampionshipMeet #1CoalTruth de punta a punta y galopando se lleva la última de #GulfstreamPark , especta… https://t.co/IkOfluIgDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theBSOLZ Meanwhile Greek Freak and some roll players got not only best record in east but entire NBA. If GF gets t… https://t.co/Q5Ja7ScC7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #JonasBrothers music video really just established all of them as such powercouples and tbh I’m here for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wraithyn1 @Reign_Backpacks Then in 2nd place there’s Merlin, poke from a mile away with 4 of his 6 abilities, all… https://t.co/bXzdqSSdIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joey_Schwartz93 @Vmbritsch @realDonaldTrump #RussianAssetTrump #ImpeachTheRussianSpy https://t.co/EWzy1Fmd2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[GPD Captain Robert Berry gives details about confession of Javier Reyes, who was taken into custody Monday for usin… https://t.co/5P2mlVfI1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiKHOU @BrandiKHOU #1 is my guilty pleasure, #2 is always in my house. I do Post, Kellogs too soggy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNyJetsFan I don’t see that. But I’m not avoiding a trade because it may help them get bell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom Of course so let’s spend another 2 years and millions to once again prove nothing because there is nothing to prove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch I muted Cernovich soon after. The guy is a Chicken Little wacko.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewzimmern Agree! Who cares. Airport food is generally so good now. Like you, I grab a sandwich and settle in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsflash: Smirky rich fuck gets away with not following the rules in job working for father-in-law]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okstevenray @RobertW_OkSt @KcHolz Right? He didn’t even give me a chance to reply. He tweeted back to me, then as… https://t.co/Drb97JXs7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @samelilydia1 , check out @Science4UsSays for some K-5 #STEAM ideas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessecrall I think you’ve hit it for me. They are “impeccable sensory experiences with vibrant performances” - all… https://t.co/vamTDw8dKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haveigotnews @davidgraeber To the best of my knowledge, income inequality is not limited to the USA.  It's like a… https://t.co/zTH9cRgrMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My surprise in the last week has been learning there is such a large "Never Bernie" crowd.  I had no idea it existe… https://t.co/eOeu25vIuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 میں اپنے بھا ئیوں اور پڑوسیوں کی خا طر دُعا کر تا ہُوں     تا کہ وہاں سلامتی کا گذر ہو۔]]></document><document><![CDATA[People be posting their pregnancy pictures comparing the size of their baby to some random ass object i have no ide… https://t.co/kzjleKC0AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiVgirl Yes and I have not yet had the pleasure of meeting you. You are stunning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO: STILL MARCHING!!! Third road upsets sends @WildwoodPSD into South Jersey title game https://t.co/aIg776rKPT… https://t.co/ALeSZc43Ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upon watching the Game of Thrones trailer my heart rate rose by 10 bpm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnMac2 @sherred_ellen @ninigirl84 @secupp You do know how we end up with a budget right?  House, Senate, commit… https://t.co/YI3831sRT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheForkliftBoss @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump 4ever on phones? It's not on the news, its in ya school. About fake n… https://t.co/pvz9TT9Edj]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL | Manchester 61 Vandercook Lake 54. Dutchmen escape with the win. @SunTimesSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going in as boring #localman. Coming out tomorrow (we hope) as Steve Austin.  At least the titanium shoulder part. https://t.co/UvFA9GA6ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @mulaney @nbcsnl Exactly what I said to my beautiful wife last night Preet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasoumehMirzaee AS SALAMU ALAYKUM  Peaceful Resistance ALWAYS  Perseveres!! INSHALLAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[President franklin Delano roosevelt proposed a law with congress to start social https://t.co/axdR7FDJMJ parents we… https://t.co/GY7TQuFedd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pittock Mansion.  #Portland #mansion @ Pittock Mansion https://t.co/D8fGwb8Amx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let it snow! 😜❄🌧 #snowing #InlandEmpire @ Rancho Cucamonga, California https://t.co/7l0CeFlJKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to change your perspective and view things differently! 🌅 https://t.co/H3VcganKqj]]></document></documents></author>