<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Maybe Philpott and Wilson-Raybould could have taken one for the Liberal team? https://t.co/nLNaNoyF1u via @torontostar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallonTonight The guy with the mini drones is creeping me out on #FallonTonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pewdiepie @pewdiepie  really loved today's video. Very cool. I like how Neil tells this woman they're in Vegas whe… https://t.co/sUCCHXIVTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews you better stand up for @TuckerCarlson, or MILLIONS will NEVER watch your network again!!! Don’t forget wh… https://t.co/FU4MMt0stZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kngofstrngs @LisaMay_ @skjald1 @RealJamesWoods How is Capitalism working out, surely not for the rest of the count… https://t.co/HZmkfS98cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugeneHowardCo2 @thehill ???   You might want to read the article in this weeks Time magazine about members of the… https://t.co/8q34WoT3g7]]></document><document><![CDATA[whoever thought it was a good idea to have lanes merge on the freeway... i just want to talk... https://t.co/DgyvI0V2OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salexis19 @IRUNIPASSIWIN @ajplus it’s not irresponsible all the time. Birth control reacts differently to each wom… https://t.co/TXgphn7VL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coronado85_m @arredondo_edgar Edgar always says “you won’t, right here” makes me want to punch him even more😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all can catch me spending my whole income tax return to buy a ticket to the Jonas Brothers reunion tour👐🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Grail 3.5 for $25 today at The Apothecary Shoppe 4240 West Flamingo Rd. https://t.co/FIKYZ6rkZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @octaviaspencer for making #HERstory AGAIN becoming 1st African-American Woman to WIN an Oscar as a Bes… https://t.co/ZUwDnoqRkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IceCreamMolly Lmao 😂 Why dont u try to get some friends!!! Wow, sooo many followers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[While CDN MSM have us running around in the weeds, as if either Libs OR CPC weren't historically complicit, as if o… https://t.co/tDgyw5LMpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend got her first apartment w her boo man - Mostly BY THEMSELVES! I ADORE seeing my friends thrive 🥳 #yougoglenncoco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s just cause he’s my white boy of the week or something but Alfie Allen’s performance as Theon is so underrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for the weekend? I am ! Have a fabulous weekend everyone . #sthelenaweekend  #roedererchampagne  #i❤️… https://t.co/hEFDmvB7hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efflorescings Vaguely remember some girl’s “mom” saying her fan fell off her ceiling and took her out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dating is weird. You don’t want to try TOO hard because you want to be met half way. But then some of you men can’t… https://t.co/Dzx5EitEE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the race, @SenSanders. The American people will have a choice come 2020; continue on the path of economi… https://t.co/SfKfNEOeWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And finally, if you voted for Trump bc you agree with all his policies, you’re the biggest piece of shit of them al… https://t.co/upuKevSKyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RettSaiah In an indefinite number of years I will have a book for you to read]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiHEAT I'm so for the Warriors but Wade surely did his thing last night!! Congratulations on your beautiful dau… https://t.co/B1xse5sNuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to decide if I should die and be a full-time student in the fall or keep going part-time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knebel_greta Thanks Crystal! This time it’s Johanna’s bff who leaves a lovely wife &amp; 2 sweet boys❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeatrixAnn1 We ate Trixie it's fun n the sun here on the east coast of Fla,Luff Axel https://t.co/Bj9bYcQ1hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @WSU_Cougar_Pres for the donation of ties to the Cougar Closet in @wsuascc!! https://t.co/NuxW7r7z2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breadnoden27 @esnjay Ain't that the damned truth.  Friggin boot lieues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I decided to do something different and put lashes on today...I definitely chose the wrong day to do it but hey,… https://t.co/MRN02XRe0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the REALEST post I’ve seen today!!! #youjustdontknow @ Old Saybrook, Connecticut https://t.co/ePE9xXozBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[King of Los Angeles #losangeles #macarthurpark @ MacArthur Park https://t.co/XRkVzLPt4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willfleet @AmericaFirstPAC @seanspicer @Ilhan Then why are you on his Twitter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePeriGirls @B2the7 @JanetteSpeyer @TawannaBSmith @GoalChat @irishhealthhour @MadalynSklar @jencoleICT… https://t.co/uRcoS0oXSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katmarie2014 Because I wasn’t driving myself home so she knew I’d be home by 4:30]]></document><document><![CDATA[For when Gentiles, who do not have the law, by nature do what the law requires, they are a law to themselves, even… https://t.co/sUQWZg9XBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@immamajojo @Trump454545 @LyndaJeffs @POTUS Be sure to accept the collect calls... #PutinsPuppet  #TraitorTrump… https://t.co/PztO5tEysl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que se hace con amor está bien hecho❤ Vincent Van Gogh . . #HappyValentinesday 💕 . . . #sunegociomiami… https://t.co/uRC2FPuszg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have called you friends, because I have told you everything I have heard from my Father. It was not you who chose… https://t.co/7feaAnZJew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni As if China's planes are better, how about experienced pilots, might help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump It’s just disheartening and digusting ... where is the Lindsey of y… https://t.co/0LIggBWhPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @mvickers4 to post 7 covers of books I love-no explanations, no reviews-just the cov… https://t.co/pGWimFEkfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[AGAIN... if you are going to be bold enough to put your hands on a man, don’t be shocked when he’s bold enough to r… https://t.co/6KWGfPgv3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @DrLupo ‘s Dark Mode is like hanging out in a pleasure basement 😏😈 #gamingafterdark #loveit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pesos4Guns @CraigRWhitworth @emzanotti @ABC7Chicago @CNN @MSNBC Oh, it’s Trumps fault😂😂😂 Please shut up🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlie_shields @serbarica @Lobefasa @mil182 @SSavich12 @eggsniffing It wouldn’t let me tag him in the photo and I… https://t.co/nU3NmY8Dvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all Hotch fans ... Saturday marathon of Criminal Minds on now on WE TV! https://t.co/nNwY2PfTd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[the hour change is making me think I have all day left to study but it’s really 6pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems to me that the birth referred to here is our salvation, as is suggested by the prophet Isaiah. This reache… https://t.co/y5ANdRQiMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear his ass is too lazy to get the game for himself, that's gonna be his birthday present next month so he can stop playing on mine 🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 places you can see #SciArt in DC this month: Dornith Doherty @CPNAS https://t.co/b96VbQOr11 https://t.co/RY6A1w14Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly that last #Shazam trailer now makes me want to see the movie.  Who's going?  #moviebuff #detroit #motownmoxiemom]]></document><document><![CDATA[whoa. Get outta my head Mindful team! 😁  I jusssst wrote a post on this.  I’ve been there SO many times I staked a… https://t.co/7uvd9g3all]]></document><document><![CDATA[ouu just wait till i learn how to control my butt like dude in the pink 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perkthethird Also, your profile picture is amazing. Spot on, actually. Thankfully you have portrait mode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nampam12 @maydaymindy9 I find that a lot of us scientists use that expression when we collect data that we don't y… https://t.co/mi4V4Axwvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to visit @campbelljulia at the @LocalMediaAssoc booth #2019MegaConf to learn how to apply to be an alpha pa… https://t.co/zedMgBmvcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are lying. But I understand. For I Am not testifying about the God of Death and I Am a Death Angel. Death passe… https://t.co/iYpOVsD1Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall I don't like the special deals given to Amazon. But AOC wants govt to provide income. Socialism sees… https://t.co/0JMUwRkmv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t make this one up. Sorry client, the 3 TV stations that were coming to your event are now covering... wait for… https://t.co/gmTkj696KZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara The apology just adds insult to injury. It's a felony to threaten a Federal Bench Judge. Remember Jud… https://t.co/G77hlNRYcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen will be giving his public testimony to the House Oversight Committee this morning. Here’s what it alr… https://t.co/FJQ4phxkN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJenniMurphy So proud of you for being a voice to represent so many of us! I was so happy to see your beautiful… https://t.co/oKp2r6WZna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madisonlawler07 Girllllll, I should have and I don’t know why I didn’t! You’re literally too sweet 💕 Thank you girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so, Father S, to you as I have always called you,   a stiff-necked people...   meaning you are puffed up, full… https://t.co/48489UCS91]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am freaking out !!! For some reason my email quit working on Thursday! I cannot receive or send any emails! We ar… https://t.co/v7V9IqEIxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why it is always tempting and irresistible. “The woman saw that the tree was good to eat and pleasing to th… https://t.co/O6GRV0ExrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[2DENRAT PARTY+FAMILY OF RUTH IF SHE IS STILL SICK OR IN COMA IS UNFAIR NOT 2TELL THE MANY PEOPLE WHO PRAY 4HER + IF… https://t.co/tMpo7yGOmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[And some cuddles and a dog and a kiss from my love- IS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little wall hanging is made of 100% cotton boutique and other scraps features a Wendell Berry ...… https://t.co/sd3lFWl4w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @DonaldJTrumpJr @kimguilfoyle “Give me your tired, your poor, Your huddled masses yearning to breath… https://t.co/EqiYVRhohX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ella had her checkup today and it’s a little guarded.  She has a tumor that has came up in the opposite side of her… https://t.co/G5YR2F1t1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will provide everything u need 2 follow through w/ the tasks that lie ahead. Always remember that the Lord is o… https://t.co/uRZ8tdzP2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Hump Day - do something nice for yourself today (even in the chaos of it all)! | #glutenfree #dairyfree… https://t.co/k9t5PvKsSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thompsnh4 Coming from an exceptional teacher leader, I accept this compliment with grace. 😊 I share so much of wha… https://t.co/sKr65IuZ43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braxton Hicks and heartburn= 1 uncomfortable pregnant lady. Hello 3rd trimester. I have not missed you 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[me at 10pm: ok i’m going to order this shirt on amazon then go to bed.   it’s now 2am and i find myself on google s… https://t.co/QPcGZi71gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biosunu 😊 I will put that topic idea in the file! Hope to see you, even for a little bit. #WeGetOutside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Would someone please point the way to the nearest breadline?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Company Support Center Application - https://t.co/KfVamxJsCh #CustomerService #Raleigh, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollysparklez Jesus drank wine, and so should college students 🤷🏻‍♀️✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #StargateSG1 "The Other Side". My daughter says, "Alar reminds me of Odo." https://t.co/iyrAN3rrHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byron100 Will you be in the second Kissin Booth? Warren has to be in it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I'm little blue 🌚 and need to change my mindset 💯on where I am going in my realestate business, I look for the… https://t.co/yqTvaJMlNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last session of the conference is all about the magic of math and science! Great presenters. #t3ic #t3learns @ Balt… https://t.co/Ys63K2s3Hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in Washington, DC? View our latest opening: https://t.co/0b9RrpdjDb #Aviation #SafetyInspectors]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm writing down in the gazebo with an anhinga and a heron, all of us fishing in our various ways ....  #Florida… https://t.co/2YtBQnTWrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLAlexandra @TeddiMellencamp the way she immediately assumed that @LisaVanderpump had set up the meeting for them… https://t.co/pvGz8daINU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonJOBS2 I wish he would have taught me to watch people to learn who they are rather than placing all my trust… https://t.co/TqzQTKPdeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Majezticpoet says he went to grab fast food without asking if I’m hungry 😭😭😭😢😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodiePrevostUK @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @Southappie… https://t.co/qJWQ9bK3dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A workout should only take bout 45min if  you are really working out hard and focusing]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful tribute to one of the Reservation’s greatest of all time. Thank you, Coach Solis and @YHSbaseball4 ⚾️#4… https://t.co/nA6VdMLe7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my favorite scarf at the casino. Should I even call in the morning 😞 it’s my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne can I borrow your glam squad for my wedding. The hype is real and I love it!!!! #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Becca_Brown20 @_KiahRuppe_ Mines been in the dash of my car for 3 days if that counts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, this president is famous for hustling reporters out of the Oval Office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday took my mind off of a lot i needed that , my week had been so stressful 🤧👵🏼😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[After two long days of watching sports, what do I do to relax?  Watch sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNCBank_Help It wasn’t too recent, no. Is it because I’m technically still under my dad’s account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a tutor st an elementary school, I used these symbols for teaching enrichment.  We made beaded bracelets… https://t.co/H22xJIQ6Fe]]></document></documents></author>