<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[UPDATE  Southeast 21 Liberty 14 5:00, 2nd Shelby Morehead is one of the best defensive players I have seen all year… https://t.co/N0M3VCWRwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[People rally to #FireTuckerCarlson over past remarks on women and child abuse  https://t.co/WwBJ9fQKAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikefiggs @MattyC801 @Alyssa_Milano Now do those who accused Corey Booker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workshop well represented by Ugandans in particular to pray for Africans in particular Ugandans who are always faci… https://t.co/kZZqj2F2v9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Kingsbane @clairelegrand I'm elated that you will have another book that we your readers will be proud of. Your tr… https://t.co/szfEVFvTpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @dlolley_pgh @CarterCritiques @HunterAHomistek @Dejan_Kovacevic @btsteelcurtain @SteelersBrazil… https://t.co/5JLVyVkIRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRPellegrino @DragonEmbers @TeresaRJ3 You need someone to carry your suitcase around for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcrab5 Nice job coach and team . You will represent Phs with class and talent !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ash_mendes @Stagecoach You got a point there lol. I didn’t see Tyler’s point last night I was stressing over school stuff 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesMill Each reporter has their own method. Most fade evaders I interviewed gave me their names, reasons for eva… https://t.co/OMNFfMooKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fix by @fifth_frame @ Fifth Frame Brewing Company — https://t.co/D7CRp0Kv5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boston__Sucks In Dec, how many people would have said "Padres" if they were told Machado would sign for $300M with… https://t.co/eoqEQEjsMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely. A new marketplace can be built. Begins w/ Preference Center that allows reset to zero data owned by bra… https://t.co/zsRn3ioqKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[While all the talk is on Republican dreams of stripping women of the right to choose, appears that Rhode Island is… https://t.co/QjZRDnSJWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm (pretty) sure i'll find love in my heart for Muffin but rn she just... feels like a random cat that we're just… https://t.co/2NsK5sErpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saratina_miller @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump I have no idea what you mean.  Your language seems incoherent to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our question - being asked by many, including families of the 43 dead — why the response was so slow? Even you were… https://t.co/dvyFa4K6TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franklin Schools (Somerset) early dismissal tomorrow, Wednesday. After school Activities Canceled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And neither one of them has taken a firm position on a controversial issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones I’m mad they made me wait so long but I’m still going to watch...anticipation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwhitehead999 @AlanaBache @DrDavidLey @MarinaAdshade @OMGchronicles You’re 225 now? Shit, I’m doomed the next time… https://t.co/PR3mPGaGMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow, we begin the month of #March already! 2019 just started and it's already flying by fast! #MarchWish #ThursdayThoughts #NewMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @CoachEidsness talk offensive football. https://t.co/edFCLHCgjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from the birthday girl. @ Carrabba's Italian Grill https://t.co/q6ZZwSXWYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkLazerus @C1McKnight They’re  a fraud it won’t last and they won’t make it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyC6 from all my tweets, Have you ever known me to run leagues that weren’t Uber active?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoradoGirl2A @Jali_Cat Brainless babbling is the only reason we know her name. She says this shit for the headlines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chic011518368 @TheAmericanVets @CaraMariatea3 @iammikeyp @kailah_casillas lol who said I feel disrespected, your a… https://t.co/u4HSlNZDxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieMcClintock Thanks for a peek into the process of making Lattimer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guillier Hablemos del traspaso de competencias para regiones ... cómo va eso Senador ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Barton Health team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/WjzJokQcR2 #hospitaljobs #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejoy500 According to racing reference , 64 was the only year over 60 at 62. After that 55 49 49 54 48 48. Then… https://t.co/XtAsNy1vrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#40 🎂🎈🎉🥃 #70sBaby #80sChild #90sTeen #00sYoungAdult #10sStillYoungAdult;) https://t.co/b8PTsod9G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Great first night for the NOBTS Certificate program.   God is Good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyODonnel2 That's adorable Timmy, nothing surprises me more than the fact that you have spent hours debating… https://t.co/TfjYkhGt0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite scene from my NEW VIDEO for ‘I-95’ 💔 LINK IN BIO (motherofmothss and I killed this scene) @ New York https://t.co/1Za2pZUIbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigSearle1 So much is timing. Vegas was rolling and the coaches stayed loyal. Summer trade is always easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron01jj @ProFootballTalk If your reason to sue was for money than the issue to sue for wasn’t that important to see till the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZombieTrev5k Perhaps.... With a Bojangles biscuit. 👍..... Or straight to bed. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Met It is almost like all the tension of the winter is just released.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @dreageekgirl thank you for providing an awesome community and streams I can pop into from time to time. You are… https://t.co/uAkk1llB3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re asking the wrong questions. You’re focusing your anger on the wrong things and objectifying human beings fo… https://t.co/XkPUjJbBa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/1WE2UjR276]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds fair to me! I love Pizza and as for dessert, who can say no to a tasty piece of Pie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current open coaching positions at SENECA High School for next school year. B/G cross country, B/G bowling, Boys so… https://t.co/9geUytSmEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My candidate for the most ridiculous headline ever: "The Grand Canyon Turns 100 Today" - Fortune Magazine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickeJohann @VanderWaalFan1 @Here4Grace @LonnyRaye5440 @GraceVanderWaal Actually it was pretentious for me to say… https://t.co/xdTLg9tfvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please get this man a #Oscars2019 trophy instead of an envelope 🏆 @NatGeo @AlexHonnold]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE NEWS ARE OUT!!  First look at the 2019 GT3 488 Ferrari. 2019 Season Will begin this weekend @COTA #Austin… https://t.co/x1rjvZINtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger She’s hardly objective—just trying to milk as much political capital as possible. What would she say… https://t.co/jFasw8F2mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[From breaking tv monitors to breaking news 😂 Up early anchoring kwgnchannel2  Daybreak. My official start date is o… https://t.co/NSvBPdBvI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MowatCentre Andrew Parkin "Veiws on Local Economy differ noticeably within communities" Rural, #EastOnt #SWOnt,… https://t.co/Jx3JyZYsU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dreaming of a white Genghis Con... This is the view outside my hotel room window this morning! https://t.co/yPdxAMXHzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OHGalAtHeart Going home after work and putting on some soft music. Afterward, sipping on your favorite alcoholic d… https://t.co/tB18rPajLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boldandhandsome @alecrieger I was just wondering if you somehow missed that.   The reasons are: 1) Judaism has nev… https://t.co/zCNHt6fL2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would've been best to listen to his military advisors and intelligence operatives in the first place and not pulled… https://t.co/O1o2N6s3WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garciabanchs Muchos dicen que la MUD es responsable de la tragedia, pero ignoran lo complicado de la situación, y… https://t.co/RM3J12v9vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite here so far! - Drinking a Lady In Red by East Troy Brewery @ East Troy Brewery  — https://t.co/EFDA0rx2cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laguaira_ma @TecMotivacional No estoy al tanto si todas pero si deberia. Se supone q el openjdk debe implementar t… https://t.co/fPz2eMqBfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i could really use a getaway with the love of my life to refresh my soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StJohnsBBall coach Chris Mullen in the house tonight for @BrooklynNets and @spurs. https://t.co/vrv89FKemb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dillzilla99 @DonaldODaniels1 @Lainyy626 @fritchee @george_capen humble opinion. Do you know who the majority of il… https://t.co/bDBqpAAPML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ineffective VACCINES due to improper storage temps as they travel across the country or sit in physicians' offices… https://t.co/S3EDoizVmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time of year state wrestling finals such a great venue https://t.co/0WUFEMS9FN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawitso you rock I love your profile pic your a beautiful woman have a wonderful Tuesday from John in Manhattan NY 💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been brought low many times in my life. It was always of my own doing. I was only reaping what I sowed. I wa… https://t.co/6Cm4jxZUIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Harper_78 @dbongino And too many of her piers believe these lies. They are brainwashed and have all lost comm… https://t.co/DMa8zVgezL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back to #rhodeisland @mumfordandsons looking forward to the show tonight! Video was captured while we shot… https://t.co/Vzfxi44xnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRLagarde @TheDustinL I’m on a very relatively restrictive diet plan through a weight loss center here. They… https://t.co/IRTJM9SjAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A double rainbow? Pretty cool. @ South Pasadena, California https://t.co/GSY9OwOxJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time I say I wanna pet bear and someone wants to hit me with “that’s dangerous” imma pull this out 🐻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo There is No emergency! Trump promised that he would build a Wall and repeatedly said that Mexico would… https://t.co/5K2ToiX9Fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEFBookClub @Davos @BehrouzBoochani Incredible story - I also recommend reading “Refugee” by Alan Gratz. Fictional… https://t.co/5mn7Jfthmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coach_jones51 @dailey_scot @B_Green_08 @AdamZagoria @DickieV @RealJayWilliams @matthewtrader1 @bigcam2150 @xea76 N… https://t.co/ZhlnNimVPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgearechyga @Telcel @ATT Cámbiate telcel vale vrg att&amp;t es la mera pistola]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJ66616 @EthanVanSciver @raulmares72 Stupid really dumb in his part. He should have just talked to him like a man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbbradford @PenaltyBoxRadio “whWhwhhfgg... WAYNE SIMMINS IS BLACK???”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovRonDeSantis @RonDeSantisFL If we are to improve the environment, for heavens sake help curb these insane antiqu… https://t.co/N3Ht4IasmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Bridenstine: Commercialize low-Earth orbit while NASA focus on the Moon...starting with sending NASA payloads o… https://t.co/ihbwqLK4nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mata_Diwi I wish my family communicated with me more but some are distant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler You really have nothing better to do now that you’re done using that fat Mexican midget as your prop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arttavana There are people you probably know right now who are ambivalent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare win for Android over iOS: every variation of the F word shows up in my predictive text after I type "f-u-c"… https://t.co/Yz9FRHYXot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGolicJR57 Plus if we break the bank for Bryce Harper and put them in right field it means Nick Williams who one y… https://t.co/OV9zw9k1Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really? #Trump signing the cover of the #Bible only confirms there is "No Collusion" there..there  @morningmika @Morning_Joe @jmeacham]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read that the zoo in Knoxville is considering selling alcohol. I’m sure that will go well and nothing will go wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PennyCruz Books. I pray and get recommendations from trusted people who know those in our church who would be good for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Create a Content Strategy in 6 Easy Steps https://t.co/EVPs9LAddC via @rebekahradice another excellent examp… https://t.co/56F3y6rXfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin with me. 50 CLICHED DIALOGUES TO BAN FROM YOUR SCRIPT {the pictured interaction is an example of good...… https://t.co/dH07cgPdT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And let the peace of God rule in your hearts, to the which also ye are called in one body; and be ye thankful.” Co… https://t.co/sVrKV8uMGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@droid_life Don't have a single of these issues. Sounds more like my pixel 1 after 2 years lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't afford a chinchilla coat , but the hat was in my price range #zoo #dresstoimpress https://t.co/BcDlCDpIPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 64 VR Workforce Studio with updates on @NationalRehab NRAs 38th Annual Disability  Employment Summit.   And… https://t.co/hnKngLlAN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly lucky to work with such an amazing team! #northeastfam #nearpod #NYC #TeamWorkMakesTheDreamWork https://t.co/CLPiOpUnS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUDE, GUYS. Look what's back at @BurgerKing! #Ciniminis #Flashbacks https://t.co/3S0kPa6x9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JL4486 @Sz0ACiiDRaiN I'm an asshole, but a funny one. Lol. No i get ya, just can't hate on Boyle deal. Its not sexy though..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine sitting by a clear, cool stream and peering at your reflection in the water. You frown the person frown bac… https://t.co/HchQfRpoly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffjaguars Well deserved honor for one of the most amazing athletes I have had the privilege to coach! ⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@im_kiyahh Give them time, we’re gonna push for change. Don’t be forced out of your HBCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 just putting this out there: if you haven’t signed w/ the Braves by March 23rd, Williamson County soft… https://t.co/YQ6VDgra0H]]></document></documents></author>