<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Way to go Purple Tornado! 🏀🌪️ Onwards to states!! https://t.co/C2hThLqfCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @reversedimages @NYCHA @realDonaldTrump Ok, let’s do a deal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByMHarrington I’ve always followed you even when I disagreed with you because you still put out good content. but… https://t.co/VUzTD7MY13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RemiPerry  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[KP Football getting warmed up yesterday for the first day of testing. Squat Day. Great job by everyone. Keep Choppin https://t.co/nC8TEBcUY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorillas also shot 70% from 3 in the 1st half, 61% overall from the floor then had just one make from three in the… https://t.co/O05NqDWrXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mavewreak You can only cry in HD if you’re on premium. Miss @eunirodillo please catch up charot hahahahahaha luv u sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big tilt in Ames with @CycloneMBB trying to stay in the Big 12 hunt https://t.co/9rH2Cp44gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Escarcega @breezepreps @SGVNSports @DamianCalhoun @thewillernandez C House!  Coach Mase!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_clown_prince @badboycraven @TheSun @whitneywrightx @DOOMS_Whiskey @mikequasar The end of that movie was my limit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desvltory__ Lmfao the struggle is real right? 😂 I’m just trying to find a fitness girl who will meal prep my shit… https://t.co/iIWxI75BhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett @LindaPar0380 @BarackObama He has the same qualifications as obama, but we are hopefully beyond ele… https://t.co/zaMaRBMMEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw an @GetSpectrum Mobile commercial with a “BIG” offer of $14/gig. My 25 gig unlimited plan is $50/mo. What… https://t.co/GhxQn0pHQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[El medio campo de @Rayados bastante flojo y sin generación de fútbol, Charly Rdz, Meza, Pizarro, y Dorlan no mostra… https://t.co/0uVmCZGCX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I love about #nyc. You can be feeling the winter blues and then stumble open this https://t.co/akbI766N6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xznorg2 @IntroSpecktive Ah okay then thanks for the clarification I was about to go crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[2002 Nissan Altima 2.5 SL auto Pw Pw Leather seats  www.escromotors2 @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/gGHIHcpm06]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needed a Dole heal and a turkey heal.  flarenfest #deerfieldbeach @ Quiet Waters Park https://t.co/B00Om1iKdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY BLUES!!! What a shot! What a #game! #LGB #stlblues #InItToWinIt https://t.co/B5enWjrJUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dems can not win the elections of this country, with the Americans Vote, so they want to bring illegals immigra… https://t.co/5vtp8XOELq]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are times when people genuinely deserve criticism for certain comments. And then there are times where people… https://t.co/lIaAXy3eXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lady’s name who stopped and helped me change my tire today, was Loretta and she was from Texas.First off, I’ve… https://t.co/9dEqCdih16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingHippo42 @shogunoflive @Osu16Bit Ok but if you dress like mk9 tissue Mileena and walk the strip and become appa… https://t.co/as1aG3btet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdr_bdr9 @funnygurl01 @Turki_AlOwerde With one of his corrupt kids under each arm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sschiavoo As excited as my fat ass was to take your stationary bike last night to make room for that treadmill?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@80suburbia Only when that "Arthur" grabs us. Or that football injury from back in the day says "hello" 😉😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escucha ahora predicacion dantegebeloficial #DanteGebel en https://t.co/K4jv9gVtS7  #ComunicacionDirectaRadio… https://t.co/XaUZEyTh6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last game before the tournament. #admhockey #mitehockey #hockey #youngstownphantoms @ Wheeling Nailers https://t.co/e680IcpZ8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜African American History Month💜  Howard Payne University Black History Program  ~May You Be Blessed With Enough~… https://t.co/Pr6yGoawzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shannon types out entire usernames confirmed. Hate to see she’s not taking advantage of 21st century shortcuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr President, how can America ever feel justified to interfere with any country that is accused of… https://t.co/Nlx0T28AK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonRLiguori remember last year when you said you’d see Lipscomb in the championship game this year? #OneAndDoneInASUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjeffreyross Jeff, I know it’s unlikely you see this, but medical bills from stage 3 Colon Cancer suck. A retwe… https://t.co/7NUEx7meJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLeanaWen @realDonaldTrump If death is judged by no heart beat, then life could be considered at the sound of a h… https://t.co/IhcdNsBN6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lashvwn Must've been watching Dashie around the time you made this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNC LAVALIN. Ils ont compris le message! L'action en hausse de 6% 36,95CAD2,19 (6,30 %) 25 févr. 16 h 00 HNE  Le go… https://t.co/OJybXCpJkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soulmuzik_1 @SarahPalinUSA Are you on the train to Hawaii? If not you should be it leaves in 5 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chatroomgirl @markamlz hey, do you know who my father is? (most of the time i feel like i don't)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I gambled on politics, I would be a hard buy on Klobuchar and lesser but still buy on Brown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both sides agreed to a 17-page jury questionnaire. Prospective jurors will be asked abt knowledge of case, pre-tria… https://t.co/JmteeII0xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intheMatrixxx @POTUS Ah The Sands Of Time Barry https://t.co/n3R2ezigqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyMurr Louisville is actually a talented team imo. They just suck at closing out games and are facing a HOF coac… https://t.co/buOv1jJwaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham @AOC @girlscouts I think she was drinking that Brake Fluid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ready for coco does “pop punk vs emo night” Chicago style? It’ll probably be a lot less whiny than the Brass… https://t.co/EstF03n97h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Then why in the hell is he telling our European allies that they have to repatriate their foreign fighters immediately?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hellraiser Dark Amber NA by @Wellbeing_Brew @ World Wide Technology Soccer Park — https://t.co/xPLrGgRt8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@himymari ainda n vi essa n mas como vou morar aki vou ter tempo de sobra pra procurar kkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this district is saying this was just on the actions of a sub, how did police get into the school and into the c… https://t.co/7nLxpDFnZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers If my grandma told me those 2 bumpkins were my cousins I would call the men in white coats to bring my jacket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kurtvile #kirtvileandtheviolators @ The Ogden Theatre https://t.co/vKcUl4A9Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXI If Detroit Police are correct and charges are filed then Allegheny County Controller Chelsa Wagner needs to resign from office]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to be with these fine gents at the @NBS_ENB Gala Dinner last night. As always, NBS reminds us why they are wor… https://t.co/XcbIRmh4Rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for some Campbell basketball?? #RollHumps #GoCamels 🐪 https://t.co/c36lk7K4id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbeautiful_cats How beautiful. Your cat is  beautiful. What kind of cat is he or she? He or she  is also very cute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Munich, here we come (with a planeload of great transatlantic friends and colleagues).  Get ready Wolfgang!@ischinger #United 106 #msc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 15:14 King James Version (KJV)  14 Let them alone: they be blind leaders of the blind. And if the blind lea… https://t.co/rJudSh5vBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chscoachk @coachjbertrand @EddieJ_Hamilton @CoachRusstough @DexterWashing19 @CoachJRoss @CoachCollins17… https://t.co/sh0N8vPnVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about a little mirth. #comedy #snicker #smile #funny https://t.co/fN54L803aQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@data_poetry @quantum_relic @DataDavidDeluxe @tableauing @FlerlageKev @flerlagekr @sarahlovesdata @_gringuinho_… https://t.co/FXKbMfZ8wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Azura Interventional Radiology Technician - https://t.co/apiawctrlx #Healthcare #Cary, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffreycook1965 It will not they’re going after him don’t want to win in 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path.  Psalm 119:105]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EeeJaye9 Get your rest and come back strong! Hope you're feeling better soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokeGirll7 @trnrtips My face when I saw this at my local pizza spot https://t.co/bVrEjJuhfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8VAC40 Arrange for treatment of unearned tuition ( payments not earned)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know, maybe this #MetabolicHealth  #TherapeuticNutrition thing is catching on 😉 - ⁦@GeorgiaEdeMD⁩ shares… https://t.co/LI9BdCqJkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not like I didn’t know Limbaugh was a tool but wow. What Trump’s doing is ok because it’s “right” and what Obama wa… https://t.co/2Vnly2mvv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple Pils, but it’s nacho time!! - Drinking a Nacho Daddy Who's Ya Daddy by Beer And Brats at @nachodaddylv  — https://t.co/MmZcR9FT9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can not wait to leave for three weeks just to turn around and leave for 1.5 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHSidhu @bungarsargon @RepJerryNadler @Jim_Jordan @GOPLeader @senatemajldr Probably right.  The GOP’s faux love fo… https://t.co/dPpF0VJOCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back when an attempt was made to repair the crack in my home office wall, which failed. https://t.co/ThS2goT1kT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just boofed a Gatorade™️ gonna absolutely tear up my flag football game]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE TEAM WIN!!!! Took the series tonight. Back at it tomorrow! #NoQuit #LaFamilia #NoFormula]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josepcampo @ValerioLivia @RosamariaNoia @eurios @pixiedixi @MomiraMonika @lucekerien @tizianacampodon @KglLaura… https://t.co/hQnjh2v8Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaned07 @dataForTEL If you need some recommendations (where to stay, what to do, how to get around ... ), just let us know 😉✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Only because he doesn't have to eat that stuff himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISI thinks good chance $DRNA's LDHA target for PH is superior to $ALNY's GO target, even in PH1. GO target is not r… https://t.co/iBv8Yjtdus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you not known? have you not heard, that ELOHAI OLAM, YAHUAH, the Creator of the ends of the earth, faints not,… https://t.co/6RdwGmUf4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘She will try to rip your heart out’  A fantastic profile of Sarah Nurse, a rising star, from @hailey_salvian]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KindaBleu @scottmerkin @BMcCarthy32 Too bad 2005 was a fever dream and didn’t actually happen. That’s what ESPN says at least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedarflats @cellmavin @beerguypdx @RJellyman @zappafaye @JonMontag @DRE_Go_Fish @ephoustonbill @badhopper… https://t.co/6Lu2RD8lxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piedrahita2010 Como no vote por Maduro la verdad me da igual pero eso de la frontera lo van a pagar bien caro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbennett24 @kaj33 @JuliusErving These days he could do it with free throws alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactamente a un mes de mi tierrita bella 🇨🇴 y por más tarde que sea con más ánimos que nunca para darle hasta el último día.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raagatodi @dgalpin2 @AOC If you were moving into an area to set up a business, but the locals were just plain host… https://t.co/aG8JLZ5g0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GALancerAD gets close again, but can't poke it in. Great, GREAT defense by @FlowHud thus far. 5:30 left in the gam… https://t.co/MsVvGYHdPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye we all grow up n move on its part of life ion kno what’s wrong wit that happens to everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@l3r0y1145 @5STARSLIME I takes a strong black independent man or woman to date a white person and not give a fuck a… https://t.co/JMpdstk8zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ducks #floridaphotographer #florida #swfl #swflphotographer #waterbirds #birds #photography #wildlife… https://t.co/wZL31m4cIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stout by @echigo_beer at @baku_restaurant — https://t.co/g9cYbVWRp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If yall dont get your Azz back to work! @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/3k7jL7NFhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PredsNHL @cmace30 “Ok so you like fall on your knees and hopefully the puck hits you” -mace probably]]></document><document><![CDATA[@synhershko Most of my other books have already been recommended here are a few more that i recently enjoyed: Artemis Children of time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunshine #vitamin D #californiaair @ Palm Springs, California https://t.co/EiaeESQiq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfAwesom That’s WWIII though if that happens and the end of the world as we know it. They’re smarter than that a… https://t.co/a4OMHV2qOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love getting drunk when you don’t expect to get drunk. Like you just kinda walk into it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseKGreen #offbroadway rt@BradForenza and his play TheRehearsal premieres at #EmergingArtists (@EATisTweeting) o… https://t.co/ai10V9Sd4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATKGirlfriends @emilywillisxoxo @ATKINGDOM @AMKEmpireXXX @KimNielsenATK @ATKHairyXXX @emilywillisxoxo - what an ex… https://t.co/xPQlDLulMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ The community looking at #JussieSmollett after this Chicago Police Department press conference. Ready to listen… https://t.co/txxOvKVp2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting target demographic.   Women (I assume of all ages and geographies),  Millennials (any gender and any pl… https://t.co/6gwsYLYKHN]]></document></documents></author>