<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's early....soon more will "pop" up says every home buyer out there now.  . . . #listyourhomenow… https://t.co/Py6azxi0VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate your family’s special moments with #beautiful jewelry! See the entire Spring/Summer Collection… https://t.co/bF9iSXQx8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard fought comeback but man we gotta learn “end of game” stuff. Didn’t stop the mall against LSU and missed free t… https://t.co/yFAB3Smlqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/LzEWYx5vTH… https://t.co/QNWC2TlefQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 11 yr old loved watching me try to down 30ml of Nyquil. It was so nasty. Usually I’m the one enjoying watching h… https://t.co/ZbE0FsIAcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessiemae @BernieSanders But I will still vote, with a person I trust and believe in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will give my drunk self some credit she always always gets that forehead selfie at some point in the night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!! Missing sweet Jennings in Memphis!! Don’t you think every mom needs a Louis Vuitton bag?? Well I’ve… https://t.co/6KWhxJDAko]]></document><document><![CDATA[#makeyourmovewithmari #marisennottandassociates #capecodrealestate #todayrealestate @todayre @hjs423 https://t.co/wxtWvoooMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m not ready for kids yet because my coworker told me his son was picking his boogers and handing them to h… https://t.co/6AEfKKXTtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSJ_Warriors_JV games didn’t go our way, but the team bonding was great. Love this group of boys and their parents… https://t.co/YNGOFqLfsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillsprokop @MAFS_Original I'm not sure what kind of contract they signed but Kate needs O.U.T. There is no way an… https://t.co/GI34fYadI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24 @madeleintlSUR Aquí el momento donde agreden a @madeleintlSUR y le tiran el celular. No, no eran sus “colega… https://t.co/XNxqWNys3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We don’t have the political luxury of a cathartic performance.  Open the table to unsavory allies.” - @nguyen_amanda  #Naspa19]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are celebrating Harper's birthday weekend with a free cupcake! acupcakeaday is Harper's happy place 🧁 @ A Cupcak… https://t.co/opxdQ3Gs5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started watching Northern Rescue &amp; the first episode had me crying 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how my mom recently commented that my baby was “worth the wait”. Umm I didn’t know my life was on a timeline… https://t.co/EjTv4d3DL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIAnders @PoliticalShort @carolswilliams_ @sruprect @realDonaldTrump Once again, our asylum law declares they must… https://t.co/k1VkYUFoQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get into the LOVE of things. GOD bless you may the Lord BLESS you mightily may you have a GREAT and WONDERFUL… https://t.co/bKlxHi4dWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @BarackObama I do too!  @BarackObama is 100% better President than #TreasonousCorruptTrumpTraitorIs… https://t.co/8J0XesLxra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg Caitlyn is using the fucking funeral director as a marriage counselor #LoveAfterLockup]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE OPINION: any one who wins the most prestigious award and says its “humbling” has never looked up the definition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin This may be the answer to why the repubs are so complicit. It's the Kompromat we all have wondered ab… https://t.co/tScTiFJE8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beer company is giving all its staff a week's paid "pawternity" leave ➡️ by @lee_moran https://t.co/JGlZYtff8L # via @HuffPostWeird]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm doing a Hip Hop Total Body POP UP in Cobb County on SAT, MARCH 2ND! Come burn calories..get in shape with me! G… https://t.co/I4U5u4970w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to win tickets to see IL Divo: Timeless Tour https://t.co/YnCqJ3KjuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DrBryantMarks kicks off our second #ImplicitBias training for @LAAreaChamber members and staff https://t.co/KZjYUZ0jD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a new beginning postcard  used Pcos teal and red for heart February month @ Mattoon, Illinois https://t.co/ggqc6VhSFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost too short to see over the lecturn 😅 but just about made it and had an awesome time presenting at #DevNexus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyPhilipps ❤️The ONLY thing I DIDN’T adore was the mystery PR person’s last minute word switch, from bangin’...… https://t.co/vUBvpiyDMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hilsilk Just LMK if you’re geographically near me (always in my heart 😂) and the planets will align!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 I wouldn't say a thing m I'd simply hang up. He's not worth my time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part about this is that the original video is 35 minutes long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocketisfine @elonmusk This is a fantastic picture of Elon... honestly, lately he seems happier and happier.. so h… https://t.co/S49VIPdQ9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LandusCoop Check this out @Roots_Journey . We're doing a session on women getting involved i on their boards of directors!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when Colton picked Cassie over Caelynn #TheBachelor https://t.co/A1nw5ptolw]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT NEWS STILL GOING ON FOR FEBRUARY HOW TO ENJOY $15 OFF  #Birthday #February #FSA   #Massage #Couplemassage… https://t.co/mzkGPvdgwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linda96111140 @B52Malmet @TheRynheart @senatemajldr Oh I thought it was revealing that he was getting himself some… https://t.co/gZx5Zwy9m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@00_Barbara_00 @bobcesca_go Exactly.  And if the president is a real Democrat, then how long would it be before VP… https://t.co/vY3myNVmr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mekarre1 @JeffreyGuterman Please stop being in denial - be an American with decent values. stop Trump’s Russia and… https://t.co/GpOAwzLP32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlsOlives @Costco @SmrtFoodservice @TillamookCheese @BaloianFarms @WindsetFarms @mccormickspices @mortonsalt… https://t.co/7DCuBqTCia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTO1ChipNagel @MalcolmNance @dc_tribune I can’t believe it took him so long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I rarely shop @Walmart but if this decision goes through will never shop there again. Bad greedy move… https://t.co/qhxAHhtMD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlyeKyle I 100% agree with @KEEMSTAR also put your feelings aside that yeah he can have some A##hole moments he… https://t.co/P8YoewwEbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign Jon Stewart's petition to support 9/11 survivors https://t.co/xJx3TPnJZK @jonstewartbooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyanchristine You could afford to give me all this gas in dis economy 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got me with that free trial, @hulu. Just saw that first charge hit my bank after watching exactly 0 seconds of content my first month. 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody could not wait for basketball to begin! #basketball #elibowen @ Memphis, Tennessee https://t.co/Dd3Tk1TfgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way chefs drizzled sauce on 'fancy food' was an elegant, post-modern methodical homage if you will to the Class… https://t.co/ghC3ov1vjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bebefehr @SibilaMan @vickijcomm @GoEpicurista @winechix @terraasmith @SammyCik So many. @MichaelHyatt… https://t.co/HZhvmUVWWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CybelDP @ulkaM Love Grace Jones!  Fantastic Entertainer and Person! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the Mandarin version is okay, it has nothing on the Japanese version if u know u know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen is the most critical and practical thinker. No other Mayor has that ability.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen many interesting abandoned eerie-looking houses, but this one came complete with a miniature sister house… https://t.co/P51pavZ4qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I NEED a coke from McDonald’s someone help before I pay door dash $9 to get me one 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @gba456, Naomi and all the #trfambassadors. You too can make a difference! Become @TRFdotORG ambassador… https://t.co/SxMZdbcXeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s all fun and games until you’re alone and can’t go to sleep because everything sounds like someone’s trying to… https://t.co/gp2cNukR4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@will2survive71 @TheStJohnFamily So yes, it comes from “self”, meaning someone cannot give you self esteem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La rrgadera tiene un modo masaje 😍 (@ Hyatt Regency Toronto in Toronto, ON w/ @mehboob25981754)… https://t.co/2oQsI3uyge]]></document><document><![CDATA[just out here living my best life. sometimes when the universe does something really really crappy, it also does so… https://t.co/RvCfT7YZ1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cauliflower is no substitute for rice, or bread, or pizza, but it sure is delicious when battered and roasted and t… https://t.co/Lar3vkE9kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[when he wanna annoy the fuck out of you a day before vday https://t.co/jt3sUFKaYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your child needs homework help this is a great place for them to go. Assistance is free. Just call the number fo… https://t.co/CQJaRDNFO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmeeagles Magical Monday, investigating author's purpose https://t.co/vz1Jvw2W1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Justin  @Esther188rod  THANKS FOR LETTING US HAVE THE WEATHER  UPDATE 21 SECONDS AGO HAVE A GREAT SATURDAY ♥️… https://t.co/XS0U7F3Zp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @BernieSanders @HillaryClinton Do you also remember how he dragged his feet and made unity a dirty w… https://t.co/wyWnM4Cmuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling my mom to catch up for an hour makes me feel like I can plan to do the same w my dad tomorrow or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humor Heals - So Laugh Often - FB! #Mueller #LisaDCTComedy #MinuteToSpitIt https://t.co/RSsF9p5kvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to go tap do celebrities on the shoulder and remind them Obama did the same thing and then tell him t… https://t.co/ICl2pjMXfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalDetective8 Oh for god sake! I’m supposed to send this tweet to the Roseanne Bar thread. I’m at work on my overnight shift I’m loopy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are called to believe not with our head but with our heart. It is the inner conviction that Jesus is Lord that w… https://t.co/yfTaZZn2IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ticketmaster is the worst!!! Hate they’re the only outlet for tickets!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channel 3 News on Your Side never got back to me and it’s basically pointless to take the vet to the board because… https://t.co/yxgd1yQVt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgian Architecture home in the heart of Bunker Hill. This is a Broker Luxurious home with six bedrooms and 5.5 b… https://t.co/ZYq8F5y3df]]></document><document><![CDATA[i woke up at 6:30 knowing fully well i had to leave my house at 6:45 loooool dangerous game im playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies. Never let a boyfriend tell you who you should or shouldn't be friends with. Never let them isolate you. Lis… https://t.co/jBD4XJKsdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobBrainerd @mitchnelles @garbedianongolf @TheGameMKE @dneedles12 I was trying to be kind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, the video was meant to record Addy but I got distracted 😍 If your man isn’t the hottest ish on the planet t… https://t.co/rAQFpru2b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This painting is on loan with one of my favorite Designers and seeing it installed makes me fall in love with it al… https://t.co/smKR4UqgMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TheCowboyCDN is away in Arizona, roping. He does this every year. He goes to Canada in the summer, too. When he t… https://t.co/gTdHjpYiZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick is a sweet young Pyr who is still a big puppy, and he'll need help continuing to learn manners. He is neutered… https://t.co/lAoqTYekIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine someone making a playlist of all the songs that remind them of you, wowz]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCabe thought Trump was a Russian agent yet he wanted to work for him 🤷‍♀️ #mccabeisaLIAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[But why are you talking about other girls on your one-on-one? 🤔 #thebachelor #BachelorNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Bernie, there is a lot of criticism to go around on both sides but this is a lie. Stop scaring people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlosrojas @PoleoRafael El no dijo MC. Por que tu asocias de una vez??]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎥Video of the week:🎥RACING IN THE GREEN HELL: Manthey-Racing (EN) https://t.co/29xQhqdhdD @PorscheRaces… https://t.co/snjkcR0Ty7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never eat McDonald’s but when I’m sick I swear their sweet tea cures me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Author #JamesHansen shares stories from writing a book about #NeilArmstrong. You can hear the stories for yourself… https://t.co/ouiyiIXBgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te gustan las novellas? Has visto amar a muerte? Esta novella tiene una pareja de dos mujeres y tiene buena represe… https://t.co/fMxHqCTnMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Congratulations on a job well done Mr President.  Make America Great Again.  God bless you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motherhood 💙  #blueprintphotographystudio #bppclients #bppfamilies #maternity #maternityphotography #babybump… https://t.co/ZQ3TATkdxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonjatMorgan I LOVE UR NEW APT. U WERE FABULOUS ON THE SHOWS SEASON OPENER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for #guestpost!! @USBloggerRT #BloggersBlast #BloggersRequired #bloggerswanted #bloggerstyle #blogpost… https://t.co/lEIDzMnzuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made out w carter and I’m drunk but I know my heart is finally full because I made out w carter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crimsonace Always enjoy listening to the games when @crimsonace is on the mic.  Really enjoyed @ABarton_NP view of… https://t.co/bAfOxw2HlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my dream my guardians kept repeating 4:18 4:18 4:18 https://t.co/bzt5Cu1exT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericapeplin This made me a little emotional not gonna lie 😭💓 enthusiastic bubbles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha this is the funniest thing I’ve seen on Twitter love your graphics❤️😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day y'all! ☕💕 Guess who just finished recording a podcast interview about Kubernetes workloads, d… https://t.co/5Zw59EhpQw]]></document></documents></author>