<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[An Extra Snooze from an Awesome day I had to the evening, should be fun next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/Zy6aCe70nY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dame_Lillard awesome performance you'll win the all star MVP next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mission Driven Culture(MDC)is the outcome of deliberate alignment of an organization’s operational culture with its… https://t.co/8wzO1ZK6I2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please run in 2020, to the bathroom, not the voters.  You will be the laughing stock of Sweden if you do, run to voters.@HillaryClinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Yesterday was bad, but it was mediocres as usual, but the service you delivered today was a real disas… https://t.co/EfVrnkg4pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaOra - #OnlyWantYou (feat. 6LACK) [Official Video]  “No, no, no, no, no love All I wanted was you I don’t want… https://t.co/TgdFcxPWrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Anzeige ist raus, Gerhard #Henschel. Es folgt ein  #Gegendarstellungskrieg, der sich gewaschen hat. Das… https://t.co/ZN6Xu0kRiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgourlaycgcs Front page on the day of the sunflower showdown...That's big time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CrosswordMysteries @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott we are only an hour away till  #apuzzletodiefor starts. I can… https://t.co/TTiAyGLltK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aussietrbl @JamesLombardo13 @zakj500 @chrismturner1 @funwaguy @luiscastro1478 @querico26 @MattiasUrban @121273Roby… https://t.co/2u9P7v9ggX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLPenington This picture is SO good. Hope she’s doing well. This is Izzy, our Schnoodle. https://t.co/WUJvw1wmxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecologist_amy Awesome! Get ready to learn a lot of cool history facts! Once you get through all 800 pages. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @kylegriffin1 It would be better for Congress to stop this, not the courts. We need 20 Republican vo… https://t.co/LkLJmmLUjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunny Monday’s call for preseason note taking at Sager Field https://t.co/umn7yZBOd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EuropeanTour The sound of this bunker shot is mesmerizing @NoLayingUp @TronCarterNLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Poor_Wayfarer @mamasaurusof2 @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse @POTUS @Kaepernick7 Idiot ya mammy should apologize for having u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cubprospects I didn’t think so, but I’ll be looking forward to seeing him at some point of the season in Chicago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Sorry, Senator...there's no GOP Anti- Voting Crusade.  NC is a case of a person hard u… https://t.co/sBOdddhXen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to these wonderful Vizionaries for joining @OptTheVizion on this trip to @amsupdates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there be any one point in which the Christian church ought to keep it’s fervor at a white heat, it is concerning… https://t.co/Wly3vsZphv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coldplay One I Love https://t.co/9BAZmzLVZ1 via @YouTube #Musicmakesourwolrdbetter 🎧🎼🎤🎹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceFan23 Anderson not even close to walker so there is a significant drop off from him .   Darnold and Adams very… https://t.co/AFxIRrF9DF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine today is the @overwatchleague! We will spend some quality time together. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna attempt to get Todd into vinyl, just bought him an album from his favorite rapper for his birthday. I hop… https://t.co/xzIRQtsi47]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad that after 15+ years I finally got to see @DJAndyMoor last night. https://t.co/V7rVLuclrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funflaps Poop jokes aren't my favorite type of jokes, but they're a solid number two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @DiabloStadium for the inaugural @Angels College Classic                                  R     H   E… https://t.co/I97NO59B4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished ep 4 of Russian Doll. Really digging it, especially since Alan's introduction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guns are lethal weapons. Marijuana would not be classified as such. There are good reasons the people of Washington… https://t.co/z9EJUEYz7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg @EmmaBunton I just preordered your new album!!! I am excited !! Bring ur music to USA plzzz https://t.co/cDyfHQDdTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched Derrick Felder play a lot of basketball games. I’m in awe of how he’s grown as a player. 15 points and… https://t.co/qHT77xfFz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i reviewed isn’t it romantic (now streaming on netflix) for @LWLies and had a blast https://t.co/NajN0QqsGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left for Thailand... should I take him his mimosas there? #friends #bff #casey #pooh #bighuman #mimosas #thailand… https://t.co/oRDzm3BY7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonIsbell Hope to see Charlie in another movie after seeing "Blaze". #talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a commercial for a medication that "may cause bone loss" and this is all I can think of. https://t.co/ZD2zi3lPcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Your kisses lift me higher Like the sweet song of a choir You light my morning sky With burning love”- Burning Love by Elvis Presley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soeightiesgirl So I can be turned on and terrified to sleep at the same time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏻 Great job by @NazHSLibrary and everyone who participated in Story 📘Slam this year!!! Congratulations to the winn… https://t.co/DntiOROcdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janemwilson I drive over it every day. They haven’t closed it in quite some time. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walt Disney World interview on Thursday morning!!! AAAHHHHH!!! @WaltDisneyWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them: don't you think this is a bit drastic?  Me: https://t.co/ftj8IKNBH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird thinking that I'm on the same interstate at home that I drive on the other side for work. https://t.co/ZXEirr2c0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson  #FireTuckerCarlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg The "Mr. Runner Up: My Life as an Oscar Bridesmaid" episode of Documentary Now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1850s: The U.S. census registers approximately 8,400 hemp plantations producing at least 2,000 acres each.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvaz147 @xginiramos That happened with me but with conditioner instead of shampoo :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealDom15 @SteppenT2 @BBallScientistX Your team beat a sub 0.500 team. Defusing ok. You’re still defusing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually the heart-wrenching father &amp; son moment was between @AmosBocelli &amp; @AndreaBocelli @MetOpera sorry @bocelli_matteo lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another incredible Give Marquette Day supporting our student-athletes. Have surpassed last year’s total with a coup… https://t.co/IYwa1iARHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rivergianna1 @TeakTeak1822018 they have sour patch kids cereal. Good but just feels weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/M2WBIovFuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Al green should be impeached for not controlling the beard. No one intentionally wants to look like Abe Lincoln.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHRAReinhart #TBT I caught you taking a rare break at the 1998 Southern Nationals in Atlanta (wish I still had tha… https://t.co/peos4dmpVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dennis Gonzalez / Derek Rogers - Certain Aspects  Upcoming, on super limited 3" format in custom packaging from… https://t.co/kHFNx5hA3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't want to be bothered at night ALL phones have a " do not disturb" as well as a power button. Use that i… https://t.co/V8uexhVC09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill 100% of the people against socialism don’t understand what socialism is? Is that what you meant to tweet? Are you high?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official @PremierLacrosse Team names/Logos have been announced.  Can’t decide which one I like best 🤔 https://t.co/sTDvC1tCob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOLAZODEPABLO qué pasó con la @chapis_herrera porque la mandaron a volar con TDN?😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat has decided that 2am is our new wake up time...of course by 2:15 I am ready for my workout and he is back asleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still mad that manny marchado left the dodgers to play for the padres. Completely understand why he did it though.… https://t.co/b5dSzaChc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PedroOrderique @luchi_alarcon20 Siempre es bueno revisar datos. Asistencia a estadios en EEUU para partidos de sel… https://t.co/kBp4iDbTAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubisM00n @skylar_tommy @AlitaMovie @captainmarvel Look at the difference between domestic between this two movies… https://t.co/KjJkWExl2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack @CasaHODL @jeremyrwelch Hey @jack,  Post your pub key so we can open channels with you. Here’s mine if you’d… https://t.co/IHaEsIZKAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Machiavelli the Mouser Snapshot. #machiavellithemouser #catsofinstagram #photography #photoofthenight #cat #greycat… https://t.co/sLzzq1wG4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love using a mirror for pictures of Mason #funniness #tee-hee #smirk #jolly https://t.co/Vb3HaeXnZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pufpufpafpaf @mumonamission5 @local_sun I love you too, may peace be upon you and your family!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @NASCAR @DISupdates 500 Day!! Ideally my man @KurtBusch will be pulling into victory lane as I get a notificat… https://t.co/9mbCtFkKi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see a Twitter friend talking about watching a movie for the first time and you get that excited feeling in… https://t.co/vLP3hoBQiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CruzEmylopez1 @AdamSchiff Just nother statement with no evidence from a #LowIQLiberal...hahahahaha...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMackeyPG Because it was a Penguin who was concussed, so the league has no problem with it. There. I wrote the article.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sue_bornstein @docwithapurpose @ACPinternists @SEricksonACP @DarilynMoyer @PDX_Tom @jakequintonMD @DrJFincher Wowe… https://t.co/KRfOORZQFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones @GeeDee215 Right. I could only use that phrase if I said "Shwsflapgorks" or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump told Republicans to ignore the constitution?  That should be grounds for automatic removal from office.  No v… https://t.co/7fsgoDy0XT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels Justice, hopefully just around the corner. Just can't swallow there is not any copies of the emails… https://t.co/qqFwCR7tnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldNationBrew Boss Tweed @ Old Nation Brewing Co. https://t.co/6BHO4pubds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy on tinder messaged me saying “did it hurt when you fell from heaven“ and I said “no, cause I rose from hel… https://t.co/eZy7VdImK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacred Heart Prep boys beat Half Moon Bay in D-IV hoops 63-62. @GReeves23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IplayWr_Db_Rb Don’t do it cause you fuck up one time and everyone on the staff pissed with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing that one more day closer to @Rockies opening day at home https://t.co/ezmnQsOBJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkfla737 Come on all, buy USWNT gear to help US Soccer pay their lawyers to fight the USWNT lawsuit 🤑😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bling for my ride! @harleydavidson #fxdwg #dyna #customizeyourride #dynawideglide @ Camelback East, Phoenix https://t.co/qwO4xEqHKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damon Runyon-Rachleff Innovator Wayne O. Miles @OhioState impressed with a talk about his ambitious approach to und… https://t.co/37lnqXVKsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secretstranger9 @G1rly_Tattooed @MailOnline It is not a civil Ideology, it`s the embodiment of evil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for my military friends @memetwalker @brenthatley @selectedwisdom @JamesAGagliano: isn’t 49yo a little old… https://t.co/xkoGm7A9qI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome! Too much #cute here!  Reposted from blackmothers_  -  tantoluwa.como -  If this doesn't make you s… https://t.co/kvsseul616]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s great to see that A&amp;E still cranks our quality programs to keep me tuned in like “The Toe Bro” I’ll see ya March 5th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unpersuaded112 Would vote for Manson if he was here over The Red Clown 🤡!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BomerKelli Gotcha man if added that to my every day would kill my back lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone that enjoys watching fortnite or playing fortnite should definitely check out my friends stream one day. @StashisLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EffinHell666 😂😂😂 “You gotta walk that lonesome valley, you gotta walk it by yourself, cause nobody else can walk i… https://t.co/CfnYhoEbZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJasonWebber I don’t usually respond to people on twitter but this is serious. Have you ever had a honey crisp????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spiceadams have you done a video of “when you didn’t know Will Smith sampled The Whispers.” 😂😂😂 https://t.co/ypik60Zciw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA_CR @KeolisNA - fellow riders please be careful out there - platforms and mbta parking lots untreated this mor… https://t.co/pEH1eMhrk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtonMorgan7 happy bday to the ole pburg boy! celebrate accordingly 🍻 https://t.co/fQ5Hj6xDr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Rand Paul Please help our President not hurt him and the American people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Draft dodging Trump shoots blanks in Vietnam.   On another topic, Cohen...wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrocNessMonster @RyNoonan And then when I said “dude it says positive”, he laughed and was like “well obviously ma… https://t.co/3BHRak7WAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pheasant mf.deli was sensational last night. Tonight is the final night of service at the pop-up from eightfinchone… https://t.co/a80MyJ5Bba]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Celtics take a lot of stupid shots, don’t they? https://t.co/SiPYDYVnj1]]></document></documents></author>