<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Repost malikvice with get_repost. Awesome cause! Please support #onpurpose #forwardthinking  ・・・ . I’m super excit… https://t.co/6q1phmGSOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deplorableshow @DarleeD @w_terrence Prayers for Terrence full speedy recovery. God Bless you Terrence.🙏💕🙏💕🙏💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you walk in the Disney store and the Cars ride water fall music plays 😭can it be next month already!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanklebold24 @CPawlaczyk53 just because someone has different views than you doesn’t mean they are “small-brained” or “uneducated”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello to all my followers.Sherry Collier,Cleveland Mississippi @ Cleveland Nursing and Rehab https://t.co/8euRzAdIvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great example of a husband #rewritingtheNarrative Thank you @StephenKing May this inspire other men too ✨✨✨… https://t.co/luTz1V6AoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriscoffeytalk @Merleliz @sandibachom @CarriageCavalry @Edita_NYC @LostInAmerica77 @nicolegelinas @NYCMayor He sp… https://t.co/K8VFUCyUCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making some Monkey Moves in Ft Lauderdale! #officialvodkaofParadise #bestoftheday #ilovewpb #southfloridafun… https://t.co/HXspJtxNOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@signaturedoc @AmerCollPhyAdv @instagram Bring it, @signaturedoc! https://t.co/kiSqH765RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I signed up for the Ladin Subaru Love Run Westlake 2019 on Jun 02, 2019! Join me in providing meals to home bound s… https://t.co/mpbPuleTOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dinner #Overrated #NeverAgain #GoodDrinks @ Gordon Ramsay Burger https://t.co/hbZbwRoCP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Angie_Harmon Thank you my friend, I love this women's prayer. This prayer has come at a good time. I just lost a g… https://t.co/aS2hdS6q6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GigCityChick @natureslover_s So cute! Thank you! Have a great week. ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hansonmusic Wish I had been there for those epic nights!! Can’t wait for the Tulsa show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/cNPTP31NrU… https://t.co/LLGCe03Sw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@521625_Sandy_Ln @Ironhorse76 I can't even imagine what his arteries must look like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirstiealley I had no idea that you are from Wichita Kansas I am from Courtland Kansas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy”  🍪🌅✨ #PurpleHouse #SebagoLake #Maine https://t.co/2oDR814VTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahmarasmithart It's something I don't understand either! But this is a gender/attraction thing and like if you're… https://t.co/1CLXSgllt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's Chenchule' Capital Raising Island Style event raised $8450 in equity investments for The Lei Company in j… https://t.co/xuikyvs98a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SansMerci86 @BarackObama The most truthful thing I have read tonight.😭😭😭 The BEST!!!❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[#evillook , 🤣🤣🤣, i look so evil 😈😈😈😈😈👿👿👿👿👿👿🤪🤪🤪🤣🤣🤣🤣 @ McAllen, Texas https://t.co/hPNQwLPFgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awelch744 @KatiePavlich True, but I expect better from her. Maybe it's Salem Media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yer jaw! @Brendan62 makes it into the #Daytona500 for @beardoil62 ! Think I’ll have a cherry @CityLightsShine and Diet Coke to celebrate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that I can’t talk to anyone about how I feel, &amp; the only person I couldn’t doesn’t even reply]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw @BrodyismeFriend do standup about 20 years ago in a little Lower East Side room. I think it was hosted by Fac… https://t.co/lZPnnueVpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet everybody wanna fw somebody, wether friends or more. Cool on all of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timfenske @chadinabhan @JohnPLeonardMD @DrMatasar @MediHumdani @VPrasadMDMPH @graham74GC @tobyeyre82 @DrJFriedberg @jonathonbcohen Agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't get this photo posted earlier of indigoquilter and I before the race @ POSTOAK Lodge &amp; Retreat https://t.co/4uSBvYwo5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka And to think he’s getting paid with my tax dollars. Who elects these people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I would find Jake Gyllenhaal unattractive yet here we are #VelvetBuzzsaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheReturning1 @NBCNews It's one of my 6 great-grandchildren. If I hadn't had them, I wouldn't miss them. And if th… https://t.co/85WMkfXajj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally laugh out loud so hard when I’m watching friends hahahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland arrived at the attack scene north of Columbia Falls just as Broste was getting loaded into a medical h… https://t.co/DHdTCy2Q5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatcha doing tomorrow after 4:00? Spoiler: you are going to need the internet or a radio. 📻🎙🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have slides for different parts of the house and different ones to wear out in public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to die from suffocation if this baby doesn’t get the fuck off my lungs. 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saltysixties Good Morning Dear Sweet friend Marcie  Happy Tuesday Have a great day  😇🤗😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVUE @_JuanRodriguez_ Happy birthday, Juan!! Thankful for such a positive and kind person to work with. Hope you had a great day!! 🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aleida tryna party with cardi this morning and I am NOT here for it #GoToSleep 🤦🏾‍♀️😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[These crybabies want everyone the same...nothing says crazy like not talking about people as individuals]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take no pleasure in the death of the wicked man, says the Lord, but rather in his conversion, that he may live. #Gospel #Catholic #prayer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @VanessaHudgens  PLEASE keep doing #Fox live musicals and portraying my all time favorite women. You were the… https://t.co/aAWwFDuD0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaBananaCA223 @NatashaBertrand Cohen's lawyer is Lanny Davis, a Clinton minion from way back. Hillary destroyed… https://t.co/RGViNrrtYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl Delete This... "middle school", "I'm not a grown ass woman yet" "I don't  know my man is TRASH" "I act like i… https://t.co/PY6qtZLc3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to s/o my girl for just being who she is every single day loving me and caring for me when I can’t be home t… https://t.co/8xwIGFSZef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxingKingdom14 Maybe not because the big guys are often slow this little guy might just be able to Jump Around li… https://t.co/bUrk6FDakL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Tiny, you ain't SEEN the RADICAL LEFT yet!  Wait until we remove you from the white house in 2020.… https://t.co/FOEDVosMuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up in the middle of the night and started stressing about every little thing... Couldn’t fall back to sleep… https://t.co/aLYE50hp3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/PVU0lksQlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The noght is darkest just before sunrise. President Pinera, Chile #VenezuelaLiveAid @sebastianpinera #humanitariancrisis GRACIAS !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndividuallyX @CNN @CillizzaCNN This country is a Republic.   Can you repeat the Pledge of Allegiance. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... that period was a clusterf***. #COLvsNSH https://t.co/xzBD14l1g7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner How do we fight propaganda? Fox and friends, the Five, Hannity, Lou Dobbs, Carleson? When half he countr… https://t.co/ToiXt00Cds]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏼 (@ John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY) https://t.co/lgcQfITSZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Gabriel hands me nail clippers* Mom- what did you give her? Gabriel- Drugs  *he walks away* Hahahaha I hate him 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[since i often read books while working, i held back my tears after reading “five feet apart” fiction novel by Racha… https://t.co/fl7say6lG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's pure evil? Really? Bless you 🙏 Mr. President and First Lady. https://t.co/zAk77tbsV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StillAwaitingI @BuckSexton Thanks. I voted for him, but I’m not dishonest enough to not criticize when he’s wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6: Yes, it should be one tool, just not the only tool. Kind of like how I use three tools to edit  my blog posts +… https://t.co/Wj94M4FqHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCVB Movie &amp; Oscar performance both made me cry. Thru were awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Does it really impact your life?  Someone else's tax returns?  Will it assist your freedom, community… https://t.co/bU7rs7696n]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing 🌨 ⛄️ ❄️ ☃️#2019february19 50/365 @ Town and Country, Missouri https://t.co/d6wOeHdqDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sushilpershad @abide_kamran @khanhakim_k @laboriqua19293 @love_somka @reeves5150 @seaweed115B @BrownieJohnston… https://t.co/Ku3jdauOPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyVBehar are you watching? What do you think of @MichaelCohen212 testimony? #ComingClean #truthorlie #compelling #trumpisdone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gone, but never forgotten . “It’s not happiness that brings us gratitude. It’s gratitude that brings us happiness.”… https://t.co/vFsfMmVz7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was a dreamer of all things wondrous and magical as a child. The years wiped those beliefs away and it wasn’t unt… https://t.co/bahxcf4z6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made my mother in laws home made stuff shells and my husband said they are better then his moms. I said your just s… https://t.co/vMaMXqQI0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travis always draws a crowd at the park between the guitar and Randolph! And check out that huge amazing tree! Ther… https://t.co/1N2YY3yjaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West Orange - Pleasantdale Section in West Orange, NJ https://t.co/ASaRZyIyvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[White saviorism looks like: a white entrepreneur talking about how scared she was to go to Africa to volunteer but… https://t.co/PqXAhCmMDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am simultaneously furious and desperately sad. The earth needs bees to thrive.   We’re just temporary guests on t… https://t.co/xa86HxpdFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZursTom @charliekirk11 Beautifully said!  2 set of rules, Theirs and Theirs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desperately seeking extra hour #daylightsavings #coffee #Sunday #203fcoffee #totemlakeplaza 203fcoffee #cheers… https://t.co/J9IMuTouji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowBert @peretti @BuzzFeed I don’t want to speak for @peretti but I took it to mean that content has a job to do… https://t.co/aWyFH9djg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never too early for a good pie!! (@ 3 Palms Pizzeria in Orange, OH) https://t.co/Mq9VeAcj6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump Someone please stop these mad man Dems... and the witch hunt once and for all... sto… https://t.co/c1sRspjkPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dermatillomania #dermatillomania #scars #baldgirl #girlswithshavedheads @ Sedalia, Missouri https://t.co/CSWjRhmB8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letting your self worth dwindle over fears of failure is failure itself. Right now in this very moment there is suc… https://t.co/VbnszNVB6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow males have absolutely no brain cells and I think Ive made the decision to be gay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattScalici @CassieFambro Also NASCAR is drastically different now because the sponsors are companies you have never heard of]]></document><document><![CDATA[The scandal will be abt you stealing our WH.  And you will be remembered, but in a bad way.  But at least you’ll go… https://t.co/sp1rWBcW5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nich__elliott oh baby you know I love an all natural beauty thread! you stay GLOWIN king https://t.co/QRGVsCsHpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever before! Oh! It also states that “the great leader( make America great)will actually do some good but that by t… https://t.co/31EYZQiN5j]]></document><document><![CDATA['Combat Proven': Israel's thriving war business in Europe https://t.co/asD9DPDaCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day ❤❤ #ValentinesDay #Valentine #love https://t.co/CKqY8gTdJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLaurenRuby I feel like @Jhunnn08 would be very offended by this tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m waiting on my mom to bring me coffee and flashcards which means I can procrastinate so coffee and procrastination I win]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you can never go wrong with high-rise denim and a leather jacket ➰ This stunning lavender leather jacket by… https://t.co/t4sKxyY8x1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MRandallABC6 @APittsABC6 It’s officially official when the number of coffees you drink in a day becomes more than… https://t.co/jh6MVWpq6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Don_Vito_08 @LisaSmith4680 @realDonaldTrump ANTI-AMERICAN PIECES OF GARBAGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDroTV The 7th movie is terrible and completely different from the book though?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Destacando algo positivo de @iglesiachile en medio de tanta crisis. @isabelpla Bien por su ministerio. Así ayuda la… https://t.co/VvF6VkXZJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night...me and this guy! #emptynesters #outonaworknight #whatkids #mybestfriend @ California Pizza Kitchen https://t.co/uIWAW1KTie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misskarissab @TiaraMonet__ @AngelNicole__ lol nah we was in bulldog crossing 😂 in the back room chilling ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennifereliz82 @ColourPopCo Me watching Keith run out the door early https://t.co/1duooH3Nhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're calling someone weirdo on twitter? Boy that's class and so mature.  What's next pukehead, b… https://t.co/8WFELH7EZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was the Artist Talk and close of our second exhibition of the Audacious Agency tour. I am thankful for so man… https://t.co/5l2s4FBUbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Why don’t we give the unemployed and #singlemoms a chance to get a descent #job and have some dignity? Who spe… https://t.co/D45SSQDfKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican Collins, Murowski and Tills will vote AGAINST "National Emergency "! This is why I'm  now an Independent… https://t.co/zS5ddUESuE]]></document></documents></author>