<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[De Verdad ??? Alguien considera la posibilidad que este ser despreciable, sin ética ni moral . Pueda ir por la cont… https://t.co/QvrS6Ysclo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cutler18 @JPSaysHere Great to see u last night AC!   Been a long time.....retirement seems to b treating u just fine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon Sorry, 1st post= 2nd time,1st time was also in marines. Got msg-father contacted Red Cross -flew from Memp… https://t.co/RJqbrCymmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@carloSanvee advocating radical collaboration and an ecosystem perspective between various stakeholders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theMrBitchin @DIorioNathaniel @RockyMntnMike It amazes me the daily show had so much talent and let them all go an… https://t.co/8Tzgj9slC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday ❗️#NoChaseReplace #FixYaFace #WhatsMyFavWord #Bitch #Lol #HezWorkin #ImGoodLuvEnjoy @ Hedz Up Salon a… https://t.co/ovRH70h66q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegJonesNC @680TheFan Crushed a homer and nearly went oppo a few innings later. He’s hit some balls hard in the first week of games]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RowlandRIVALS Agree. Win or lose doesn’t affect the psyche at all. Seeing some standing around on loose balls and… https://t.co/0EJD8UPjLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods You put your trust in a nigga stupid hoe How you figure he won't fuck your best friend and your sister]]></document><document><![CDATA[@singletrigrero1 Gracias por los nombres de esos lenocinios. Iré a fiscalizar y a denunciar esos lugares de vicio y… https://t.co/rO0WTzs4WR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the opportunity to educate our state politicians about the profession of Athletic Training and watch Pima Colle… https://t.co/gnASSbGms3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con nuestro ahijado Leonardo 🦁 y los Compadres! https://t.co/A79MqZYuUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@navy09212010 @RyanAFournier Why does it have to be about party, why can't they just get things done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que vaina con la toxicidad de @petrogustavo .... ! Cierto don @DCoronell ? Y los tibios @sergio_fajardo y… https://t.co/KSrUXiy423]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Co-workers know me well  #lmao #singlesawarenessday @ North Carolina's 10th Congressional District https://t.co/9rxh3A8UFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn’t suppose to be the focus of the picture but Imma act like I was. #hookem #matdrills 🤪 https://t.co/4dqNeMWL4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_haaaaleigh_ @KYNHL00 would either of you be available to judge the NSDA district tournament next weekend (Thursda… https://t.co/L0vU9zcXmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Marco, mosca con los militares que estan llegando, por la experiencia de ALTAMIRA, podrian infiltrar mi… https://t.co/VfOv31020V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicks lead 42-35 with 2 minutes remaining in third quarter @NEATC_MarkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanna_lynne1 Good to see you take such a positive outlook. Some people's souls just want to just up and dance without our permission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBrimmer @Samy_III That was clearly intentional. And he handled it appropriately by not doing his normal scowl… https://t.co/ReAuyXK9Up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwww missed my paints after being away for almost a week💚 Almost done with the latest 14x30" 🤗 🌊🌊🌊… https://t.co/6ObqyBh8L1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1EverettAnthony Funny. We moved out of Texas to Georgia to get away from the San Antonio crime. Didn't want to raise my son there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodzillaMovies @Mike_Dougherty https://t.co/FEZfj1dFNm #forgeorge @RoswellPark @TransitDriveIn Can you  find it in… https://t.co/0CH9af26F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roblesmaloof @LatinosDeNoche Las palabras se las lleva el viento! Apenas "entro" y ya saborea millones..   https://t.co/M6MoSnukME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chet_Cannon Actually 100% of us who don't want socialism know how to read history, what's your excuse? If reading… https://t.co/ATufEe3bCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigHong @samesfandiari @JonesOnTheNBA They had won one playoff series total over the previous four years, and an… https://t.co/Pc11nlfaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just playful. #funniness #giggle #smile #cute https://t.co/05UmEk0N6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinReidBRN Maybe. All I’m saying is we missed a great opportunity to pelthim with snowballs today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@y2shaye70 @TheAAF @Kaepernick7 @Nike How does it feel to be a sheep? I’m seriously asking. https://t.co/4gXJ2LnAqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got home a while ago from work &amp; I can’t fall asleep &amp; I have to be up soon for work again 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little sneak peak behind the scenes with @RugbyCanada HC @mcgrath_damian getting the boys ready to take on 🇼🇸 at th… https://t.co/plNcrKVCYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YYd9G9lrir ha ha now they going to Canada they are a joke what next Russia they is funny people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealsacil The person that tweeted this is brining up race and gender. Which is pointless and idiotic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Paddy’s Day Tournament in Franklin - Gracey serving for TEV 17 Abigail. #volleyballdad @ Franklin, Tennessee https://t.co/kREQRZm3vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many people have the misperception that people like the Dean or other administrative staff plan the school, but the… https://t.co/A0cqH8Hb5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is it possible to pardon Paul Manafort ? That would drive the left crazy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phishfan403 @spence_jspence5 @Wittmeier @rover196309 @MarieFrRenaud Yup. In reality, it was about a 1/10th of what… https://t.co/c3nbIMRJl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitstagram #fitover50women #fitmama #fitover30 #fitover50 #fitover40 #fitover35 #fitover60 #fitspo #fitment… https://t.co/omeVHmVwjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Admirals Club in Grapevine, TX https://t.co/UWN5wyvzFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @A_kamara6 rolls up to @Sneakerpolitics on a scooter with a Louis Vuitton bag on the handle bars. #MardiGras #KamaraStyle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MenkesLife @OneYorkSt @Fitwel Proud of the leadership that @MenkesLife has shown in promoting #wellbeing in… https://t.co/ah62A8m9LZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting here in my room with everything off and Xbox just turned on by itself. Wtf is going on here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SofiesMom2 @netflix @AOC Yeah and Channing Dungey works at Netflix and Obama just signed a deal there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlySonier @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/TMaMYTiIWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Velvet Buzzsaw is smashingly intense #VelvetBuzzsaw #LosAngeles #netflix #art #thrilling]]></document><document><![CDATA[You wore that poor woman out! Kudos. I'm an English teacher and I could probably figure it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my wife this morning that she is the best wife I've ever had. #oneandonly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovAyoFayose O.M.G ! Baba Peteru, E ti e wo se Fun. AMOSUN go have some SLEEPLESS night. Any way he go thank God s… https://t.co/n0H38gZooS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would be nice to make it home to see my family. @AmericanAir Flight 5775 has been delayed a few times, and about to delayed again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HipHop_News_GTV @WeedWeekNews @YoungDolph @DatPiff I heard about this. Cracker Barrel must have changed since I have been back East]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind your tong hold your assumptions! Feelin the vibe from this untitled track? Collab from ibis.giant and I produc… https://t.co/ivJTq3s4m0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for this night!! The Hollywood Palladium holds a lot of special memories for us and we can’t wait to mak… https://t.co/tYT3gVU5Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bambambigganose He’s been outstanding finding guys. Really doing a great job elevating the rest of the lineup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Unc new a-thing-or-two about runnin’ some pipe.. at your moms house. #electrician #constructiontrash… https://t.co/WiGtk6Qdgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen Jueves @ExaFM , Me pueden complacer con "Deberías estar Aquí" de @RioRomamx 🙏🙌 pooorfavor! Muchas Gracias 😍❤ #OAMty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdyPackard @LadyJessMacBeth @SahilcdesaiC Ordie, have you really not had enough?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a really great day filled with lots of positive energy. 🤗🤗I had no choice but to push out that same energy‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[While simultaneously ignoring the #PublicHealthCrisis of #GunViolence 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christaylor89 @ryan_landreth A guy named Poop just seems so fitting for the chiefs defense]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ain’t shit. He cheated on his pregnant girlfriend with you. No one is surprised]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cruciverberella @frakincaprica @3x1minus1 @MarkWhyy what about...  https://t.co/fV044yyIKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’m talking advice from a Panda Express fortune cookie, but they’re not wrong... https://t.co/GZfB4ULm5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Your a disgrace where was you when Virginia gov was found to be a racist in his younger days. I di… https://t.co/KCnrM0pgGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not saying I should bug @bra7ely since in somewhat near to Sacramento, but I could!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to @Meryn012 and her first official college game day. Just do what you’ve always done, be the best teammate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HeatCulture lead 63-52 against #TimeToRise at the half 🏀🔥 #NBA #OneLastDance https://t.co/SDkfSNwipb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWLRec official event tonight folks get your #acid #detroittechno on! bases loaded with some good Detroit sweatbox… https://t.co/fq2Ih10Lft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone actually know what you’re suppose to do when people are singing happy birthday to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleAbernathy85 @lana_fincher @SuzOsborne @lauraaldridge01 @loudlearning @j_white_math @FloydCoSuper @iamryanwhite… https://t.co/OIuSRy9tJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an ExperimentAle: Brut IPA by @AveryBrewingCo at @AveryBrewingCo — https://t.co/RwUWTRf4jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnpike_Tony @ercthms LMAOOOOO I’m still spending $ from what that technique saved me in cost of bags]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I've learned anything today, it's that    @Jim_Jordan is probably one of the least likeable people in Congress.… https://t.co/C0nBVZeXQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the ol’ weight belt can’t keep up with all the plates I’m liftin’. #elkonv #weightlifting @ Elko, Nevada https://t.co/NP8BfEl3Cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3LauraAshley It would be so cool if you visited Nashville in the near future as I would love to meet you. #gorgeous #amazing #talented #wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN @CNN @tomforemancnn Dem’s got their perfect 2020 ticket! Just need to convince one to take an 8 year si… https://t.co/Hz2DzWZw21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcast @Xfinity your service is horrible and you never compensate or do anything when we experience issues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PSG eliminado de la #ChampionsLeague!!!! tras caer ante el #ManchesterUnited 3-1 con un penalti en el agregado (3-3 global).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrtnz_jackie @KhariHeru @AngelCooks3 @Rubi2060 @Constan91994576 @dana_patin @thump1828 Nice job Tasha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdevlin11 @LaSalleMBB No doubt about it!! Clock started while ball was n the air!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ned2au @nuclear94 Hipster: Avocado toast paired with a micro-brew IPA with a splash of radioactivity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a wrap #Classic19. Well done @ComClassic. Certainly a focus on trade and market access this year. Looking fo… https://t.co/Zo3JciWXpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥⚾️🇻🇪❤️🙏🏽 en Hammond Stadium - Twins Spring Training https://t.co/OA7L02dbYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Boston for the National Golf Expo and had to head over to @uoh1826 for some chowder and some fresh crab cakes.… https://t.co/M3zgQk4zdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izzyrz @YouNicks @58isthenew40 Or We don’t like Tump because he is a disgusting human who boinked porn stars while… https://t.co/8Qb3Bg0ls0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost trevorbell •  •  •  •  • Zuko ⚔️ . PC: @sofiaroman_ Jewelry: sorrelloriginals @ Diamond District Block https://t.co/duEGXyjlYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Thinks @Alyssa_Milano should shut up and make another porn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelSanJuan313 SURELY the City of Beaumont didn’t just throw away $2.15M tax dollars!!!  Any idea when we’ll know… https://t.co/CxYiU6LWza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dean Acheson #inflatedpriceoncollege  #inflatedpriceonMedical #inflatedpriceonHouse… https://t.co/BXfhvnFAuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortunate to be able to support such a great cause tonight with @MHettingerTampa #JensensHeartOfGold https://t.co/LzGZtOoGVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @MelendezMiss for attaining Google Level One Certification. @RiderCEHS @sharonjsherman https://t.co/c0413h5fkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pat Healy is a smart, diligent guy. This report’s importance for the upcoming election, and policy discussion can’t… https://t.co/YeXNWSBvZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/RNN13QnN2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayo idk what tf happened to KFC but they done completely changed. The food actually decent, sweet tea is amazing. Niggas is woke now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @MrJonCryer I think “The Art of The Deal” guy (Trump) is trying to negotiate DOWN that 239 pound thing. Just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Elisha Whittington @elishawhittingt and Kath's Boy an  impressive winner of the opener at… https://t.co/sE7gVEgXSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FastPatriot @Lrihendry @billslater @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer I am a soldier for a king.  I got fake news. Mos… https://t.co/oWHkSmv6QA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethGRosenberg @AOC History shows the negative effects of the Reagan tax cuts. They only encouraged greedy, antiso… https://t.co/WGiREOq8Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met: Mary Steenburgen and Ted Danson (TOGETHER!)  Seen: myself in the mirror 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@occupied_stall @TattedSoldier83 I'm Owen. Driving the stereotype Pig Farmer that everyone is in Nebraska. God,get me out of here.]]></document></documents></author>