<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PatRunner89 So I successfully pulled it together?! Thank you for your kind message!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevESPNKim Stiverne looks defeated, even before he walked into the ring, Wilder broke him]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a really cool cover of Powderfinger as pre-show music but some jerk roadie started tuning instruments lou… https://t.co/zIzVlynqtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[On The Low by Scott Morrish | Free Listening on SoundCloud https://t.co/OYdb2SvSwr @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now… https://t.co/ii4FfSQKt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilton Manors FL Sat Feb 23rd AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 81 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee @JohnHayes730 @BigKuntry_2001 did you see those Busch cans made from Harvicks car?  I’ll drink some Nats… https://t.co/lxdO2jU9iC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We need to de-focus on church as a place. The church is people...  Our mission is not to fill a building. Our miss… https://t.co/kcozJzGZaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best game to play with loved ones. NOT! #BoardKings https://t.co/syHjiJl04r https://t.co/FFeQoMeqKv https://t.co/syHjiJl04r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t the golf simulator be real and our buffoon president be fake? @realDonaldTrump @TrumpGolf #ExecutiveTime… https://t.co/SwG4QILvGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vikings RB Latavius Murray wants to start for his next team. That outlook makes the #Eagles an appealing destinatio… https://t.co/Loha4aFk9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lip smacking on your chips should be illegal during class. I can't focus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emiaddisonnyc Sooooo beautiful #amazingbeauty #greatboobs #fantastic #perfection https://t.co/WJqYn6Adqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a coconut milk latte with raw sugar and no flavoring https://t.co/RPA6rPBSRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHLEaglesNation @AB84 Rumor has it you good get him for a 6th rounder??id jump all over that !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting on a beach bar drinking a marg in February..and this is my home. life is crazy if you get out an take chances. #Jacbeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how much money or things a person no one is better then anyone 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlsenneyehc @CalgaryBornBred @Franktmcveety So it's okay to post his home address and suggest people burn it to th… https://t.co/vI7WSNApAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyHaracopos @DabotaSmith Shit when you are in lobbies with me we play Xbox players not those bots you play against on ps4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings from Mount Pleasant! I'm here for "Ideas in Action: The Affordable Housing Crisis in Charleston." Looking… https://t.co/bU6htqNU0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy first day of METEOROLOGICAL #spring! #ILwx #MOwx #IAwx https://t.co/UXlgjfrGxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamspeters That’s what I’m wondering. But how would the Cowboys handle it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two ride or die ships atm for Marvel comics: ClintxBobbi and BuckyxNat. Seriously. I’m just asking that my s… https://t.co/7znQXVl0xW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsemezing É uma hérnia de hiato que dá esse refluxo, mas é só de vez em quando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsaymills I completely respect women players and know they are way better than I was in my prime, but I still h… https://t.co/drgw0qYj3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLowedown1 @MyOpinionsMan @TLDR_MovRev @Jaws19show @CrisMovieCorner @sttepodcast @w_ott3 @s77tux @MovieCornerUK… https://t.co/p1Lkqx50D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t have an ego” 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 lying through his teeth miss the old AB. When he used to flash his smile 24/7 and did… https://t.co/5PfLdyZS1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[This white girl has gotten into the Uber express pool dressed way warmer than me I’m over this I’m going to get a cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 things negative people will do to you: 1. Demean your value 2. Destroy your image 3. Drive you crazy 4. Dispose y… https://t.co/HPY9saawFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moondog2138 @abgutman @mattcurtisnyc You go Dominic. I'm sure you've had plenty of experience in your kind of work… https://t.co/l9Zso0TiCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camilocondis @DiazCanelB @leticiadeCuba @op_salomon @cabrerad26 @InesMChapman @SalvadorValdesM @HomeroAcostaA… https://t.co/aHJELMrgYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHInfrastruct @UToledo @UToledoCoE @Wambopuff @UTLaunchpad @UToledoCoE : #MSCE ‘18 @JHInfrastruct: Director of #Infrastructure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas Nice gesture guys - sorry I can’t give up my tix - have to see Stone in person]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having #1 selling artist like @Joy_Villa doing what she does and speaking out is incredible for conservatives invol… https://t.co/EgokSTtSui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayMoffo I have a good Midre Cummings story: a year after the phils had him he was with the Red Sox, me and a coup… https://t.co/kRTQVepfsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @Teram323Tere They all think they above the law.  Lock them up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love waiting in @HRBlock for over an hour for my appointment because the tax guy is running late. So fun........ first and last time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom If you can’t understand the system is rigged an you can’t live off what McDonalds pays then you need… https://t.co/VU1MoPO4jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayGunVoss @Jeep @JeepMafia @TopJeepers @ItsaJeepWorld @Legendary1941 @KrawlAmerica @Jeep_Familys @JosephPallotta… https://t.co/hxwSDsWkk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMAO_in_Fla #877877 Just Text Brady to #877877 Just Text Score to #877877 Just Text Go To #877877 Brady here: Hous… https://t.co/HDoSXKUWpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“El secreto de la libertad radica en educar a las personas, mientras que el secreto de la tiranía está en mantenerl… https://t.co/Spv5zsMXcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillMcIntyreIII Keep it up! I just made it 5 years cold turkey in January. You can do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not even have none. I did not even...I could not even really comprehend what actual product we were talking a… https://t.co/1KpJ99vTv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLTripGuides My favorite thing about Florida, is the past, present, and future I'll have in a place that continues… https://t.co/3jGOawCqdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneLuckyGay I used to be like you. I used to believe in “wrong winners” and “bitter juries” and now having played,… https://t.co/XXQ06d1SeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I “just imagine” @StrazForMayor showing up to a debate with @JaneforTampa https://t.co/mCQeL0h5Rz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: ( walking on stage for a talent competition)  Judge: "What is you talent this evening?"  Me: "I can pet 2 dogs… https://t.co/0I2TKjxStr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Baisden @BethHouf @burgess_shelley @mikelubelfeld Great stuff Brandon - Thanks for sharing!! @Glennr1809]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JiCLajoie JiC c'est parce que tu fais partie des FAFANS qui ne comprennent pas année après année après le match de… https://t.co/HMbyqE67rZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovinoandRich @stevecovino @richdavis @spotcenter @PiperWaffles just watching this great #Christmas #movie. Am I r… https://t.co/Rr9DOEiEAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should just take rapists, murders, etc and put them on their own island in the middle of the ocean for them to j… https://t.co/Bx711IkCfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Completed some upgrades on my site https://t.co/eQ5PhPKJhY go check it out. Don’t forget the devotional page]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillies I didn't know Valarie Harper played baseball!  I haven't seen her since Mary Tyler Moore.  #NeverChangeThisLineUpEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RClaudia89 😖🤣🤣🤣. No m... Este Xolos fue otro al que veníamos viendo en la perrera]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impeach &amp; Prosecute Trump now! "So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew" One💚!☯️☮️🤬 ! FREEDOM! Freaky Friday! https://t.co/7HciLhN0mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marcusdstewart @30ASeawitch The “link” is an outcome from meta analysis where the original papers show slight sign… https://t.co/fX6sEX55be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job! @FRSNewJersey @RobFerullo4 @FAmato53 @WeehawkenSTEAM @PerryWhs @SWeehawkenhs @eslxiomara #FutureReadyNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @SweetMotherBlog @selenastamm360 @jes_m_wilson @GooseInspired @amkeane_22 @3DBrewing @Caitlein @GroshekLaw… https://t.co/t0n5BljRMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony is that this is a pretty good description of Jordan Peterson and other right wing thought leaders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great story on draft nuclear plant bailout in Pennsylvania that could cost $900M a year by @Maykuth https://t.co/B15BOkr9sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[woooooo I finally hit 1k. go follow me on insta @rspacker https://t.co/etYoh6Xayy]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re off to the races with the Repugs trying to pull a fast one by trying to stop the Cohen Hearing from happe… https://t.co/ET3pJYpyYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow at 6PM for the annual Washington Women of Excellence Awards!  RSVP ⬇️ https://t.co/B7jCjqINjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...but given the way it seems to churn out people who are either miserable or help visit misery on the rest of us,… https://t.co/wSkZlCSoxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: Luckenbach has gotten ugly with all the modern tourist updates. (ex: the new bathroom building)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter made me remove two posts. One was a response to @VeganGains that was quite a bit more mild than his.  Two sets of rules folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[look all's I'm saying is that if you're entrees start at $20 you probably shouldn't tell me "actually I don't know… https://t.co/n9Bc34lG4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @PressSec @POTUS If this is a fishing expedition: #NeedABiggerBoat]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'ai reçu un draft basic de la pochette de lanpremiere parution de mon groupe psych doom En Fer... Ça promet... Ça va être nono...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE @Knight94501 You sound upset.   Thousands of reporters looking-nothing Senate investigation- nothing Hous… https://t.co/shSVdj49IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[que pedo con la gente que proyecta pura buena vibra y luego hablan mierda de los demás ????????  get your shit together]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things that haunt me: I met a date’s parents’ German Shepherd and that dog was NOT feeling me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta need some help. First flight was delayed from Dothan AL and there the rep told me Delta would provide hotel… https://t.co/KL9eGc06Ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Me_PhiMe Off a St. Andrews Dr subdivision in Murfreesboro yesterday. Water has receded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecPompeo Military intervention NOW. Unarmed people can’t fight these criminals. https://t.co/CbvbW2xC87]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG!! My mama DO NOT 🙅🏽‍♂️ need to be on social media... She just be posting 🤳🏽 all kinds of shit!! And swear she… https://t.co/dK66D542KJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We forget that launching and operating these “games as services/MMO-esque” games is a huge feat, and one that in th… https://t.co/p2uSk66qAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchos festejos y risas de alegría y satisfacción fue lo vivido anoche en el triunfo de rayadas ante monarcasfemeni… https://t.co/OHuBMsBNdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teofimo Lopez says Vasyl Lomacheno fight possible for late 2019 or early 2020 https://t.co/64sC8d17wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brent 💞 Mendi | I thought about a summer day And how the time just floats away Pretty things like incense and flowe… https://t.co/mMh8mxnVyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_farmacist @TuckerCarlson Hmmm, no, I think the word you were looking for is tokenism. Chris Wallace...sometim… https://t.co/BldUkBHnYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Central Catholic was a big winner at Thursday’s National Football Foundation banquet. Justin Traina, Kyle Jacklich… https://t.co/R9cGUY0EAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaSlatkin @BenjaminFrisch I read that as “unicornally” which is even more niche]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren't traveling with bma_mooto.usa than what are you doing with your life? Vegas here we come!   #bma_mooto… https://t.co/TdR8aO8feH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyMntnMike Be damned thunder of the Gods. I shall search through the ice and snow by the midnight sun to where… https://t.co/OsJGpWX2yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pain passes but the beauty remains.   -Pierre-Auguste Renoir, artist [responding to Matisse on why he painted i… https://t.co/3IsrRMVfdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 RAINBOW 🌈 UNICORN 🦄 COLORS! FUNK YEAH! #hailthehairking #hairextensions #illinoishairextensions #hairking… https://t.co/10fUMXg0Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAshleyDevonna Right lol being an only child then this usurper comes out of nowhere. It was an issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamarDealMaker @naval Everyone is an island and creates their own world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, have republicans just gone fucking insane? What the hell is Cornyn trying to accomplish here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I travel, I use motels, as if I don’t have people at home who love me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They going after some starting pitching?! Maybe that guy Keuchel? 🤷🏻‍♂️ He’d be real good in SD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They are thicc with 2 C’s” 😂😂 and that would be Duck donuts according to @k_e_nzi 😂😂😂@Blainey_dayz @JordanPaul7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me? Gonna’ need a mighty big Caramel Macchiato tomorrow! I should just put in my order now!… https://t.co/WmkQVvPQtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll just wait till the last minute to do everything like i always do  🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenatureboy200 @NWSBoulder Really doesn’t get much colder on a day in Denver PERIOD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EndtheStreakTX Don’t be distracted while driving. https://t.co/WGt1iimm9v https://t.co/0InciFaAAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JonnyBling Just like the old days habibi. So much love for the beautiful game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisoIIey @johnwintertweet @be_katz sue Nike for making shit sneakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth...#JHF #FSUICIDE #Faddiction #Fireproof #FPTSD #FCancer #Livefree #Lovelife #JustHaveFaith #tommaroisagift… https://t.co/Qryx8cXLNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SvuMariskaGirl @Mariska @clairekerrbear @mhargitayonly @Milinka_Peskova @hargitaygirl_ @MariskasStyle… https://t.co/JDjl3c8jgO]]></document></documents></author>