<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_ImChefCole My fool ass used to think i’d get married at 18 or not at all 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read every word of this. Wish I’d gotten to know Nick. Condolences to his family &amp; friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found guilty because he IS guilty. He should be tried &amp; sentenced the same as ANY man would be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya abrí todos los tuppers del refri y no encontré la capirotada, ya tuve que calentar lentejas MALDITA SEAAAAA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltingInMarana @Snowhitemy4b @letters4trump45 @AylaForTrump @Crazy1Colleen @kritter1963 @trumpshappygirl… https://t.co/aQRgezyviU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManUtd @MarcusRashford Look at this picture. A bunch of young kids having the time of their lives!!!! Fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glitzescape But also, I just did this in the shower and istg that one was like 2 1/2 feet long!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not here for this tweet and I’ll tell you why.  Being cheated on is Not and will NEVER be about you not being g… https://t.co/4uePTj2VkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland an 11-year-old Indiana boy who shot and wounded his state-trooper father has been charged as a juvenile with attempted murder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoloOrtiz9 @confessions_cup @JustJane2019 @TW2CayC @cazij @JackConnie @SteveHammActor @HighheelsDes @gigirules7… https://t.co/lH6MOgzF8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[New blog post is up on how to engage your various stakeholders through social media. Check it out! https://t.co/RasXv13xY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRodrineto @custodiolima vai nada. O povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @KarenSLeonard1 @roads2 @AnwarManwar004 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/QJwU5eqRqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you book a hotel online only to have the damn dates change AS SOON AS YOU CLICK CONFIRM. I am RAGING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi Because he’s giving you the same thing back that you give!! You are such s hypocrite! Haven’t read yet… https://t.co/CcTPpLglps]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I try to calm my mind before going to bed (busy day ahead). I think back to spring semester last year. I was in… https://t.co/0NxTABLxHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soup and sandwich $7 available for dine in or take out #delicious #soupandsandwich #mainstreetmitchell… https://t.co/SzJsjYQAuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoosyourdaddy99 @GovernorVA Seems like an automated bot network esp outside of Virginia. #DoNotResign #VA02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tae_thuqqin It’s not always ur relationship sometimes people feel empty even tho they have somebody special in there life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropping off dad &lt;3 (@ Cleveland Hopkins International Airport (CLE) - @goingplacescle in Cleveland, OH) https://t.co/XMbMcJp2NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, how I love these girls! 🕊💜 #udsigmakappa #bidday #bluehensforever #imtheonlyblonde @ University of Delaware https://t.co/3q5T5XJPWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaflanagans @cinna_BONS Stpattysgay is way better. You’re not a sad human.  You’re gay 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[I threw up everyday, multiple times a day from the day I turned 5 weeks until 13 weeks!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend is amazing!🥰✨ @ Casselberry, Florida https://t.co/FMKnHHtEYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isiordiamariana @DianaCasteloB Bebé, tú no necesitas invitación, allá tienes tú casa💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryMac28 @amsupdates So did I.   It wasn’t good for them because their driver didn’t win!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs.Boissiere- you’d be so proud of our little researchers. They don’t need much guidance at all about how to resea… https://t.co/HIWS2ec2l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And what's scary is you can probably compare me to your car because I'm barely getting started @ Los Angeles, Cal… https://t.co/NP7ts3QSfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ML01102017 @EatWithNia @mykelldaking @Lord_Wiber @tehdawghouz @EdVorst @brettachapman @jsjbird01 You a dumb bitch,… https://t.co/1wxDgyFVPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Lord Baby Jesus, I am now registered for College Algebra. Please don’t let me die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielvmachado No sé qué me parece más repulsivo, si los pelos o el pie de atleta 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just call me!!! 📲757.209.4599 #yourwilliamsburgagent #realtor #realestateagent #alwaysavailable #topproducerrealtor… https://t.co/ZLmDyRWnRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um #tbt de valentine’s day bem turismo da vida real, chega a cabeça mais pra lá que a gente consegue uma foto com a… https://t.co/JkhUHzG9mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCALive Police should have taken him out so much earlier! They allowed him to hit 2 innocent people because the wa… https://t.co/a9k5vtY841]]></document><document><![CDATA[My not-so-secret social media accounts reveal that I hate 45 too...and he didn’t accuse my father of orchestrating… https://t.co/TZOIiHmx63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @JussieSmollett @BennettCollege @ColoredGirls1 @IAmPowerRising 2 lying phonies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help! I have several buyers in need of a home. Various price ranges and areas...#realtor #realestate… https://t.co/1vsrodqtbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga Congratulations to Lady Gaga. Everything happens for a reason. Lady Gaga is single. They make a cute couple. I’m jus saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @zacharylevi in “The Marvelous Mrs Maisel.” I love the “Shazam” trailers. I loved him in “Chuck”. Ah, who am… https://t.co/rqXqf2aY1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign up for this event!! 👇🏽👇🏻👇🏼👇🏿👇Great information for immigrants ... @UNLVLaw @unlv @NILC @SenJackyRosen… https://t.co/RUIiVvsgSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly You have the nerve to talk about Democrat socialism when Trump admin gives $7.7B to farmers to relieve effects of trade wear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got stuck into a KUWTK coma for like,,,,,,,,,,,,,,, four hours how did I get so invested]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re a nurse when you get home, shower, eat and crawl into bed and not care about the Oscars? Why? Becau… https://t.co/ohkOlE1KHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just thought “ugg” was the funniest sound. so THEN the made up word “puggle” became off limits to use during our… https://t.co/JxqhK47arO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMr_P @BetoORourke For sure worth exploring ty! For this piece tho i focused on those who have declared their ca… https://t.co/QsOLhoifTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone is caught up on the song and the video not matching but i just love the scenery 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a lightweight now 😓😓 two drinks now and I’m down...why lmao 😂 I hate that I’m like that now]]></document><document><![CDATA[when your school is having a vintage clothing sale but you can’t even afford looking at it 😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay cool bye Cassie, but like how tf are Tayshia and Hannah G supposed to take this ya know?? Like when they see t… https://t.co/B4mEd6oUeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I do ...he is too old!  This position needs young minds and young bodies]]></document><document><![CDATA[#brusselsprouts #baconbacon #jimmymadisonssouthernkitchen @ Jimmy Madison's https://t.co/2UudsrsFMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohiganAthletic @U_Athletics @MohiganHoops UHS posting 7:30p start. Hoping its 7p like we think!  (?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zoey’s Full Pull at the Farm Show Pedal Pull #NFMS19 https://t.co/EA4febbSSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendenfingers Lmao are you never not bothered by anything I say? Why don’t you just mute me, I don’t get it. Anyw… https://t.co/cucc7gz2PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@battleofever @BadAssGramp4_45 @rn_deplorable @petluvers4Trump @loveshoulas @MikeZito9 @colliertimothy8 @GKeile… https://t.co/V9AHBGu0gT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which SpongeBob Character Are you? You got the Sash-Ringing, the Slash-Bringing the Trash-Singing, Mash-Flinging, T… https://t.co/pTUkoKhYI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad I had a daughter for multiple reason but one of those reasons being that all these boy dogs and actual… https://t.co/U3n79djJq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AustinSwain #AustinAntics  @ndaustin @LoudenSwain1  VIP Meet &amp; Greet.😍🤩 https://t.co/Fo30ITIkWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all still telling me astrology ain’t real????? ... (idk what this means) https://t.co/0wf9rLM3yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the Havre Homie @ajrucinsky doin his thang! The creativity just flows from the brain! @ Havre, Montana https://t.co/JLSXx0Bhrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Might” get ugly Thursday night at @NYCBLive when @MapleLeafs and @91Tavares visit #FirstPlace #isles @NYIslanders… https://t.co/jb8H9IGUuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG seriously?? So adults attack kids over a hat. This is so freaking wrong. #smfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can only do things after coffee has entered my system... approximately a pot of coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBattOnline I struggle with the statements of debates creating a divide as I think this wasn’t as much of a deba… https://t.co/NAvAo0MjC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever look at two photos of yourself &amp; decide you really have no idea what you look like?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Video / Mini Mukbang / Sashimi Slab https://t.co/k9SfNPcyjD via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_yungpasta I was thinking the same thing when I say this. No way they should’ve ever gotten up to that speed! 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[i swear to god if i ever see a big ass spider like that in my car it’s over for everyone on the road]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who workout with their hair down should be on the top right of the crazy girl matrix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poking yourself in the eye with your mascara wand; with 5 min to get ready for work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite breakfast is just about any leftovers in a bowl with an egg on them. (Cilantro rice with Cuban black be… https://t.co/bt55hZsSHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews You are the biggest abuse of power and corruption, sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld what the hell is wrong with Juan 🙄how do you work with that moron🇺🇸💃 #theGreatAwakening https://t.co/RzLLjoRNrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the FBI is reading this PLEASE don't send me this shit  because I AM NOT HAVING ANYMORE FUCKING KIDS!   Thanks i… https://t.co/VkSxSwq0lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What doesn't #TraitorTrump understand? These investigators and intelligence agencies were concerne… https://t.co/dD4D9cBEVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did they choose a fact or an opinion out of the paper bag? 🤷🏻‍♀️ 😉 #FREOwls 🦉 @FreOwls @CitrusSchools https://t.co/utDUMq36df]]></document><document><![CDATA[uh so anyone see that Kylie accused Travis of cheating? Lmfao what the fuck is going on man?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianagrande’s NASA Has me telling chad to go home so I can have ‘Me’ time but we live together sooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FamilyOverEverything #FOE ❤❤❤ @ Wilson, North Carolina https://t.co/wGNrm9PkZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚔 "Pennsylvania man made Parma school shooting threat on Snapchat, feds say https://t.co/WSsGrMZHAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the Salem Witch Cemetery, where some of the key people from the Crucible were buried after being tried for… https://t.co/zeut5PzYep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but why does this picture at applebee’s look like @nickjonas https://t.co/wzmBMXd8uJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did the people that are saying that the Skrull are the bad guys in Captain Marvel actually watch Captain Marvel?  B… https://t.co/64C2v3BHOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[WH pushing prison reform right before Manafort’s sentencing: does anyone else think the timing of this initiative i… https://t.co/xj5GWNiVxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NabehaJuma Dead. I’m dead. You don’t have ears in yours...right https://t.co/VSpQL99966]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early birthday/Valentine’s Day flowers from hubby. ❤️ https://t.co/nBSXnWb46V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @VanJones68 It is very limited in scope; NY AG will take down Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@froehlichm @evanabramson @techyturner @JCasaTodd @bethhill2829 @tishrich @Rdene915 @jbormann3 @JaimeDonally @EMercedLearning Always ♥️🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anddd my bestie @mikaylamudford gets to see the mau5 for her first time ever!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hills02 @Public_Citizen @AOC If you are talking car insurance , I did know that, and it’s ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMGlastonbury @ASHNRSociety @rhwiggins @MedPierre @CDP_Rad @StefanTigges @cmtomblinson @gmoonis @phudge54… https://t.co/b7Xv44xvn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN About time you returned you disgusting POS.  You have no respect from r American values, the people who yo… https://t.co/hPua8DNXQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishopStika The child starved to death, beaten to death, sexually assaulted for years until killed, sold into the… https://t.co/BTFWho0A2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thread &amp; update on the #Mueller investigation. Getting clarity &amp; understanding terms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhona0505 It smells divine as it cooks. Looks fantastic. But I just can't get past the texture and the aftertaste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocStrong26 @KhanStopMe I do this too.  I have found it far easier to keep up with little things this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @smerconish CNN go n lick Aoc rashida  Abe’s Ilan Omar #your favorites]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairbolsonaro Y del mundo Mr. Presidente especialmente a las que admiramos Brasil y a su presidente, jajaja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Optimizing your web content for #SearchEngine discovery; think of valuable Entity Metrics vs being keyword based.… https://t.co/yDyAVGBQ8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[people really out here saying your race determines how trustworthy you are i’m deaddd]]></document></documents></author>