<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I watched John Oliver last night and thought ,”Putin is playing chess while everyone else checkers.” Brexit, Poland, Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @RepMattGaetz Matt Gaetz is a fucking pussy. Just a little Donald Trump ass kisser!! Someone should whip his fucking ass!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Of course,besides crime being down in el paso,,da wall did slow down https://t.co/rRrvDt5Osh made them… https://t.co/IqHf6PYsYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @trashtvaddict @pitsagainst @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/7cpd1u5ERr]]></document><document><![CDATA[sports bras with a sense of humor; melons, coconuts. #swag lmaooo #funniness #laugh #smile #merry https://t.co/4CnGN5j2lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[republicans are “pro god” and “pro life” though smh how ignorant. people wouldnt have to depend on “white peoples m… https://t.co/aG8FbcxmBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey remember as you head out for Spring Break to CLEAN UP AFTER YOURSELVES and RECYCLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a spoiled unloved child doesn't get what he asks for he throws a tantrum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deenie61 I'll try to figure it out. He was an adopted farm cat just like my other 2 but he was "dumped" at our pla… https://t.co/fJmPIkF67r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #BankTwitter...@FDICgov has their annual report for last year out now.  Hadn’t fully absorbed it yet...but...sh… https://t.co/WGNqdZ0AyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Devil's Backbone by @RealAleBrewing @ Alpine, TX — https://t.co/HLycarxWJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arrowheadphones @ArrowheadPride What opener would you prefer of all available?  Me is GB @ KC late afternoon game… https://t.co/lwCR5WErcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuFan130 I think he plays it out. Gonna look for his own shot down the stretch. Wants to catch Jabbar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliviaMesser Nah gonna take a hard pass on reading this story and other because they are all just bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article also reveals that Trump asked his newly installed AG Matthew Whitaker whether Geoffrey S. Berman, the… https://t.co/CWa1XFqx1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, I hope to goodness you're a satire account, as I'm laughing my ass off! But I'd dasn't say...ya' never know, th… https://t.co/U8444HcQ0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Moon point and shoot camera with built in 24-3000 zoom lens #p1000 #nikonphotography #nikoncameras @ Delr… https://t.co/wQxwDnhBMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atiku @UN @inecnigeria @officialEFCC @DefenceInfoNG @HQNigerianArmy @PoliceNG @AsiwajuTinubu @amnesty… https://t.co/zLWfYvFCoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see our abstract on 6 column vs selective THD in Cleveland during #ascrs2019. It will be a great conference an… https://t.co/t0DiBXotzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[nicki stan’s out here on ig dauing nicki minaj MADE arrogant tae 🤣🤣 also she fired him but this the best she ever looked LMFAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[11/ I understand that there is a tremendous amount of fear associated with nuclear energy. In many ways it is unkno… https://t.co/dcNkCqAnVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[No excuses every legal voter has an ID and should have to use it to vote! Voting is not only a right, it is a privi… https://t.co/YeTecnHWI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlaPanthers look to trade at deadline - but lock up a talented youngster with extension first: https://t.co/kESpeSEn16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdegen8 @BleacherReport @ProFootballTalk Showed success his entire career until the last 2 seasons when the Niners… https://t.co/gNwwBregx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Bryan  I was born in a good way  My age is a little bit more than the last  I like to think about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 years ago today, our lives changed and we heard the greatest dance song in history. ✊🏾🙌🏾🙏🏾 #BackThatAzzUpDay… https://t.co/sMoLVbfhgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another gem @HillaryClinton delivered, proving #PresidentPinocchio was, and will always be a lier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MSM and Democrats do morecto hurt gays and transgender people  - bother the MSM and Democrats are self serving ego… https://t.co/Kh8xVD7Zp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConservationAL @GovernorKayIvey @PriusChat have you seen this?  Have your Alabama dealerships seen this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you want out of your hole, then it’s time to put down the shovel”  So many times we dig our own holes not realizing it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCJ34 I’m saying I can’t fuck with you if that doesn’t make you cry like a baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aoki5Chuck @xan_desanctis I don’t think she’s pandering. I think she sincerely believes what she is saying. Which… https://t.co/RuUvDwk6Ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Anthony our chef @Benihana in SLC tonight - mistakes happen, thanks 4 fixing it! You looked sad. Don't be - we a… https://t.co/2NAID3eFPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question of the day: @realDonaldTrump why do @jaredkushner and @IvankaTrump have security clearances?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @Kat4Obama Trump loves and believes all murdering dictators.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soberpod Someone who wasn’t hell-bent on the whole “God as a higher power” thing. I’m an atheist. I don’t do God h… https://t.co/6cQZwJb1EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like that 🤷🏿‍♂️💯 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/Om9lbPVdKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttawaMorning I met a wonderful woman online. We moved in together 6 mo later. married 2 yrs after. Still in love since ‘96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started at a community college. By the time I earned my bachelor’s from a state school, I had multiple national s… https://t.co/gshpDyoWLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenlpaso I need one if those. Hmmmm. I’m sure @JHInfrastruct has something we can trade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark @BRChronicler Wasn't married when this was taken. Unless you count the 13-year-old]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less energy transfer toward to coast will mean more snow in the Pittsburgh area. Generally snow will increase the f… https://t.co/spN5t2DKRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anth_moose @JonEstes11 Jk. I love you Spice. Miss you buddy https://t.co/yGdOAnab3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dímelo @vikingomartell como están los ánimos en la cueva. @FirmaEspn 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Assemblage_23 When you do stuff like this it makes me not like your or your music any more! Musical should be a av… https://t.co/Ic7yEToDeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @TrumpsSouthHQ Ask @RepAdamSchiff where the indisputable evidence is that he’s withheld for 3 years… https://t.co/PSNKp3t3Hn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my GoFundMe campaign: https://t.co/t9EtQGCsNs @gofundme https://t.co/y1JMMWBgxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have the bad luck to get in line at Starbucks after the P.A. with the order for the whole office, remember… https://t.co/JfNB6SlkoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Winger1500gl @catturd2 @GOP On phones? Tv? Paper? BOSTON had paper.  I still got fake news. Most valuable thing on… https://t.co/dAVGYzcKaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight instructor killed, 7 miraculously survive after plane crashes into home https://t.co/B7FuvLJ1ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to believe I was a drop of water in the well like all the other drops of water but I've come to realise I wa… https://t.co/G0o2UMOxz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Witness - Red Dead Logic (Getting caught in Red Dead Redemption 2) | Viv... https://t.co/fu75HOdgAy via @YouTube fr… https://t.co/QOfRg7uVYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaSterritt @danicamclellan Nope. As far as we know. Always room for doubt of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been listening to this guy on the McLaughlin Group since I was a kid. This is wildly dangerous “reporting”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of race, I think y’all equally capable to do some messed up shit and that’s why ion like y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with Barb in Germany #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #epcot #werehome #Germany #Barb @ Germany In E… https://t.co/UdfHYQmkbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[6424 Wilshire Blvd 6424 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90048 https://t.co/ylNukOfWgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these istanbulagop #xistcymbals that I’m playing with ajfullertonmusic . Playing them softly is so satisfying,… https://t.co/LnGUtYyc1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good midweek morning hobo thread from the sunny and extremely frigid high mountain meadows!  Lots of good news to c… https://t.co/0ydJUvHwCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT BROWN PEOPLE RACISM ARE LIVING IN THE PASS\THEM WHITE CAN`T COMPETE IN TODAYS TIME\\THINK]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/TC1VZwXQvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a day off is mentally harder than running 5 miles! #runnerslife #runningprobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @wesindyan I blocked her and read some previous tweets...one in particular where she was asking “T… https://t.co/vM4zXM1Kqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daxshepard @IMKristenBell The kids is going to be the funniest coolest kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[No  never ever. Send her so called father to her. He was always a bad father and should be thrown out of the United… https://t.co/ZR1IWabdCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis It’s LITERALLY all Zion does. There is no end to mikes insane statements]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs @THETXEMBASSY Why not? He already surrendered his heart, soul and brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bretontheradio It’s so true. Every time I look at clock today I feel like I’m reliving some kind of terrible and u… https://t.co/45QmML4gD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best deals and coupons for Etihad Airways US https://t.co/fGybyXkMWe via @yazingllc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This game is pretty much a xerox of the recent losses to New Jersey and Carolina]]></document><document><![CDATA[Large numbers of people from local schismatic groups (SSPX and sede vacantists) in Spokane have come out to venerat… https://t.co/q9QdQuIXwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you never heard of Oddfellows and it shows  #darkwave #postpunk #dtlv https://t.co/V7DVPXnb05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackWendigo @latimes Issue? Enemy of free ppl 2/24/17?  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Eart… https://t.co/C1q4M4hGKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvlly I did the same thing but copying out of the back of computer magazines.   I’m old. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't heard anything from mistress @britneyspears in a very long time here on twitter. I hope her and her dad a… https://t.co/AzzKOXLdMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's happening tomorrow at 2:00 p.m...  We have 4 students fighting in Sityodtong's In Gym Training Event. .  $25 G… https://t.co/f4Pzxdo1Jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Carlton Please do. Love the hair, the cars, and the haulers. Great post. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[البجاحة مش طبع ولا اكتساب ، العالم دي كلها البجاحة عندهم چينات بتخليهم متفوقين في مجالهم التعريصي، ميتين ابو وساخة… https://t.co/3pZcmP2GKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuriyATL404 Facts but since I’m just 21 I’m not really old enough to appreciate Vikings moss but he was a beast]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a positive note conscious crew killed it tonight everywhere. Now t dome go suck my left nut because you will nev… https://t.co/3hdDX9heya]]></document><document><![CDATA[8yr old to 6yr old after receiving sticker: well i guess you out this on your laptop. That’s what you do when you g… https://t.co/MciHm0Dzo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good one tonight on @BRC13Sports channel 13. Notre Dame East Stroudsburg takes on Nativity in the @PIAADistrictXI 1… https://t.co/EFZgOAuDHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichPitre_CO @John_Gardi I wrote it and I worked out an approximated toy model to compare the calculated added mas… https://t.co/HsTMIw3yfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her Presidential campaign reminds me of the video of the special needs young man scoring a touchdown. Only way he r… https://t.co/fCZOMJVyP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit funny lol I’m getting dress and we both leaving . Fuck wrong witchu]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@tednaiman I’ve been following you for awhile, just figured out you’re in Seattle. Don’t suppose you’re accepting… https://t.co/Nb0RyYpewP]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYT Bombshell Outlines Donald Trump's Efforts To Obstruct Investigations... https://t.co/Y7awx0ykLx via @YouTube#Jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know In-N-Out doesn’t really have the best fries in the world, but I think I may have found a solution? Put the f… https://t.co/qsCVKhkrAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_olney I said “rightly or wrongly.” The point is that’s how it’s perceived among tennis players and Kyrgios knew that when he did it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day slanging Kratom at The @RedCon1Official Festival. It was so awesome to see the response to A Leaf Of Fait… https://t.co/wdam0N24OZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FD_1010 @GCTigerTracker Should be able to follow anyone you want.  Just keep play by play on the featured groups.… https://t.co/n2WXLJWFdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madd_slander Terrible promotion,  that album had dope bars,  nature was killing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runwithskizzers There is an episode coming in season 3, just wait. https://t.co/17vlnIwRM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alen_Ars24 @Cbreezyy13 @MiamiHEAT Wait till the marlins play... then it will be the worst time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitlockJason @marcelluswiley @SFY @Darnell_Smith95 https://t.co/1IXqvf4gd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know how you small town Republicans like to think of yourselves as independent, pioneersy types who can get along… https://t.co/0u0SibwCIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirlineFlyer @iamwellandgood Interestingly, I find using twitter to contact an airline either really impressive or… https://t.co/TctPZF6dPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinos y Rusos de MIERDA agarren su VETO y metanselo por el  ese CULO. https://t.co/KwTDETTygI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ViktorTheViking Been a Viking fan for 45+ years. I know, I’m a glutton for punishment. I live in Baton Rouge Louis… https://t.co/MNy3guF8j6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callowGuru I'm not trying to say my word is law, but based on what I can see the community passed the casual state… https://t.co/7ZK8gyuKc7]]></document></documents></author>