<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey @bryceharper3 how did it feel to have a home crowd of over 10,000 people cheering for you for the first time in… https://t.co/SIXCnhR7xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dclaytonbarnes2 @therealpcus @JimmyTraina I actually agree. Knox is in a tier above AB, KD, Manny, Odell and Judge… https://t.co/o1Nr9CWwUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot about this gem from last night. Only the best mentors would share an Original Signature Baja Bucket with t… https://t.co/FFWN7nzXFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our contractors are almost done installing our new floors. So much nicer than what we had before. The new ceiling f… https://t.co/V0zgBIkSgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Specter by @fultonbeer at @RALBeerGarden — https://t.co/d4aPd0Wfgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaRush I agree Joshua. All kids need to be loved regardless of their orientation❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[WILFORD: Illinois Looks To Raid Private Retirement Accounts To Solve Its Pension Crisis https://t.co/KWxq8OTVpe via @dailycaller]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyHomeMatters Yes, though causality runs both ways. Higher subprime debt to income ratios push values up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough with Luff v Brodzinski TOI issue. As for the current RW1...  All for giving Tyler Toffoli final 15 games as… https://t.co/ZpNJOJzVnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellatwins think my wife could model for birdiebee? Mother of one (so far) https://t.co/fPKjiSHhKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t thank Jake Muzzin and his agent Joe Resnick enough for taking the time to meet with the boys after the Leafs/… https://t.co/im7crT6jpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leesville Road and SE Raleigh split their matchups in the regular season. Both teams 11-1 in the conference. Cap-7… https://t.co/eeOQwzfD8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweet_harmony69 I’m tested let’s do it we both are available @TruBlacMedia]]></document><document><![CDATA[me learning from my past to not make the same mistakes again. https://t.co/wDGWR3ktMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - NBC Nightly News:     Manafort sentencing; Anti-Semitism firestorm;    Cop killer standoff;    E… https://t.co/y4j5nqRwRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FattGreening @RyanJKosior He also has not had the best supporting cast either. In fact, a name I might watch for D… https://t.co/0clf8ZWviC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snbitstt @SkinTrackerCom @FortniteGame It's clearly a skull, among other things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macgregor63 @StreamingMagic I’m going with “I cannot believe my kid left his Mickey Mouse in the store and he cann… https://t.co/Ynx60hktOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren offered $1,000,000 &amp; A 🍺 W/ “Hubby” ( If He Shows Up ) @RealJamesWoods @ThomasPKennedy3 @dmitriperov1… https://t.co/hvI7FPame0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family programs at the @whitneymuseum are really amazing! Family Open Studio every weekend, plus regular family… https://t.co/KaO0Q2RALS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like seeing red when 100 other people tell you it’s blue. I can’t comprehend this shit!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This going to the field shit got me eating beef jerky..fml it’s actually pretty good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read ‘Cat in the Hat’ with my son this AM. Mom leaves kids home alone, and they let a stranger in the house. Am I… https://t.co/QcInLuOwD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Veterans should be taken care of by the goveand ppl of this country including health, lodging and employment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es más divertido iniciar un mame que investigar, es por cuestiones legales desde 2017 #MillerEnvenenada https://t.co/JVnh4BVGaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joebereta @TweetneyMoore @darenvongirdner @MikeFalzone I love it when you guys clean your buttholes 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikkis_Spleen Haha!! He never explains much of anything. Always testing and hoping for the best. He took Niki’s sp… https://t.co/iRNTFORLTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_lieber The water based version of this pen ruled, but idk if they make it anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I had a dream I was back in LA and there were yellow balloons and zebras all over the beach and then I w… https://t.co/QcpHIWMUt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverRion Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbgraeber Or....super meta. Tell you what, use it, then tell everybody you invented a new poetic technique: metaMAX!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller Huh, guess Hillary, emails, deletion, and OPSEC mean something now to you then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 @TH55202331 I absolutely agree it just makes sense they’ll still have to keep an eye 👁 pilled on the lib… https://t.co/aAdwbNIHkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bcorks30 @ByMHarrington Absolutely not. I’m upset sabres didn’t do anything with him at deadline sign or trade.  N… https://t.co/iwQPXml1bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[No we,tremendo error. Al uni le caben 41 mil y fracción y está lleno, al bbva le caben 55 y entran 30. Que chingado… https://t.co/R7rYv1qPO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdeebocane Good morning Dee and happy Friday from my alternative music station ☕️☕️☕️☕️☁️☁️☁️]]></document><document><![CDATA[how come it ain’t ? lol   in order to be “pro” anything, you have to disregard it’s con]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse My mind lightbulb has just told me that best way for party to get away with bigoted statements is to do lots of them. 2/2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercedesAMG @F1 @NASCAR @NHRA In a virtual simulation indistinguishable from the real thing it completed over 21,0… https://t.co/Z2c9c2ef8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya han pasado meses y meses que miembros de @AFSCMELocal3299 @UPTECWA y @UCAFT han estado trabajando sin contratos… https://t.co/NwtJiKmwMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NESpower @SmeeWeber Thanks for keeping us updated. Y'all did a good job yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m grown, texting shouldn’t be like a requirement to how much you fuck with some body]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNWwonk No Governors though. We historically elect Governors to the Presidency, not Senators.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE @RalphMRivera says the #PodcastersToolbox is a project management suite for your podcast, giving you all the to… https://t.co/PCYyrUCEZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donovan97655972 The separation of church and state was as I was getting out of highschool, I have not pledged to t… https://t.co/9m902LUkbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Review: Lao-style barbecue seizes the spotlight at Kra Z Kai’s in Corona: Youthful and energetic, Musky Bilavarn pi… https://t.co/FblFOk4XQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamAppleMusic on @TheTylt—I stream music from Apple Music https://t.co/kgK7beSifw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorWarren82 @pattieqld 🔺🔺JOIN THE ILLUMINATI FRATERNITY  GET MONEY .POWER FAME. In JUST 2WEEKS.ARE YOU A BUSINE… https://t.co/b7kXIGhdmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityoftoronto MISSING WOMAN - Gabriella Antoine - Missing since Jan 23rd. She has a medical condition that affects… https://t.co/QYJcuDVPPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a wave coming. The inner circle will be here with me along for the ride as well as my supports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatoNegroJazz @jazzcanarias many thanks love! we #jAZz https://t.co/464ywqvJqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavisScherer don't let the trolls feed you. If Twitter gets its knickers in twist over something, it's probably  B… https://t.co/qPbkVKDimA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Panzer AR-12 Shotgun from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $500! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/2zoqzYGNmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's the way to start the season with 3 points @SoundersFC https://t.co/Hft6Cxs5Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟 #America https://t.co/drJ5K96zZP  🌟 #WarOrPeace https://t.co/MFYGahxzFI  🌟 #ItsEverybodysBusiness… https://t.co/NPquS79dI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t even try to tell me that there are people out there who don’t entirely take their pants off when sitting on t… https://t.co/xsj2T2s5GS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's close it out @BroncoSportsMBB!!!! Let's get this Win!!!! Need great energy, great effort, great discipline, g… https://t.co/AfSUrGCFLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂 can you see the excitement when I tell her ima pick her up . Colors and everything 😂😂 https://t.co/fatwxOIkha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my feature on the .@OrlandoMagic and #Montenegro’s own .@NikolaVucevic’s first trip to the… https://t.co/RYNvRG65Ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabeth_Cook Life on the Road Baby - sounds like theres a good song in there somewhere https://t.co/N7XVSUk4Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haslametrics Well, it's good to be in the 90% percentile in something, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mercury205 @mattmurphyshow Translation: "Only those I agree with have First Amendment rights!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenVolin @McClain_on_NFL Actually Bill could give a rats ass about diversity, what is important to him his unity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee still tastes sweet #SundayMorning after a special season from @ncbison hoops. What an exciting season and aw… https://t.co/Co1ZtV4xjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Last Doll Lady” is an excellent documentary!  These ladies were a part of American history and it’s great to s… https://t.co/vAyOkPxSSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Watkins really act like he was going to go for an official? 👀 That's sort of what it looked like on TV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeCaputo19 @DineshDSouza @JussieSmollett @IngrahamAngle He be going to jail!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coutinho9 Cooperstown? Cano? Better chance you get in the Baseball Writers HOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #VerdeCanyonRailroad #timelapse. #trainride #trains #canyon #Arizona #travel #ShotOniPhoneXR @ Verde Canyon RR Ex… https://t.co/9Y5Og0Rm9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low key miss the house parties from back in the day. Going to have to have a all house music party this summer to bring them vibes back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wwhitehead88 @RandyLHallman @NASCARONFOX @amsupdates @mikejoy500 @joeylogano Director needs to put a squash on it.… https://t.co/C8lUPeBAOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[King of BS off to a fast start.  After proclaiming “things  are going to be different around here”, Kapler could no… https://t.co/3dRt4nO7Pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 WBRET-FM: Honey Molasses Radio on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/0GHq6eqEOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chiefs to propose overtime rule change giving each team possession https://t.co/mZ8py0YQzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smh As a US Citizen and a voter and Reside here in Massachusetts I would NOT vote for Bernie . I want A President… https://t.co/J1KA8NN2QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody panic, but my comedy hero @Randazzoj just followed me on twitter, and I forgot to learn anything about being… https://t.co/AYPYTpKnL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprovechando el clima para entrarle a la horneada 😍🐷 #Sonora #Comida https://t.co/BANJEj1fEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NenyVolandoalto Buenos días Neny, que tengas un excelente domingo 😀🌷🌹🌺. Te envío un abrazo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @JacyFranklyn No nepotism here, did he find a spot for granny yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME. In Class AA boys basketball regional, Niagara Falls 34, McQuaid 34. Entertaining backand forth game so far. #preptalklive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mark_a_510 They gave him 10 minutes alone in the Chamber with DB and he didn’t ever quit. They’re gonna build him… https://t.co/v9JG8Omt9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Malik4Play Let me know how that looks! I heard it’s an upscale since the series wasn’t originally created with HD in mind or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...focus on what you #cando, what you would #like to do, what would #make #you #happy and #Meld them together...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls A-1 Semifinal end of 1st: Omaha Marian 10, Lincoln North Star 9.  Hear it on @ESPNLincoln 101.5FM/1480AM and… https://t.co/KncltXokPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrotTop1023 @kd6cae @theqonline You’re not late. The show starts at 4pm Eastern.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ESPM_Berkeley social co-hosted by the Carlson, Grantham, and Ruhi labs was a lot of fun! Tried these nutritiou… https://t.co/uPKDnWFdqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerkswan Guess I adopted that expression — loved the church lady.  LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EngagePDX drinking game. 1 drink every time a speaker says Voice Assistant @SEMpdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin Richardson crossed 1 Mile to GO!. Time 06:03:22, pace 13:09 min/mile, est. finish 1:38 pm https://t.co/f1lc0K9HR1 #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@49ers I finally received my personal authentic signed Jimmy Garoppolo ball as a 49er! https://t.co/PiW8Ggc6bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance And hopefully, he will join him as the second president to leave office early]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bradley introduced to "Enter Sandman" by Metallica. I'm liking it - despite the #VaTech ties. #ArchMadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[#theallegedlyshow premieres at 8:30 Pm Est @ Hamilton Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/lTPc0AKzBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full disclosure I am still salty about Barstool dumping on my favorite pizza place, but this is legit shady on thei… https://t.co/xpfe7e0laK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GauchosARG Eso no tiene nada que ver para el ranking. Esta basado en Los puntos que logras en las ultimas 52 seman… https://t.co/pWy2wt90rE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA @Marla68983234 That’s the left for you. Asshole useless violators of civil rights freedom and personal li… https://t.co/Uo3Fg3nVNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch my name Tra’ not Jacquees, I ain’t finna be you or your bullshit😂🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yelp Weird after being an active member for years the UI still doesn't adjust my usual search pattern and it's mul… https://t.co/lWkStYqP4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the bank tellers who saw me drive from the ATM to the ‘21st Amendment’ directly across the street, at 10am on a… https://t.co/A9wZ2uVB55]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in addition to Aaron’s eloquent observation I would add your piece is just poor journalism.  Your job is not to… https://t.co/G1ZLzBLl6O]]></document></documents></author>