<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Homework is stressing me tf out tonight. I don’t deserve to be this stressed so I’m just not gonna do my homework.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday mornings at #GoTeamZoll’s house #pancakes4LYFE @ Swampscott, Massachusetts https://t.co/auEKdZWf8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FENDI DM #VanessaJ  #fisforfendi @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/6PaOeHPoPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just me and my @comcast @Xfinity rep trying to figure out why I have no internet. Another day in the life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayInslee Sure..Dems should go with 93 trillion dollar green deal, open borders, socialism, and killing newborn babies. Great start there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll show you what love is and all that you're worth You show me how to put somebody else first You belong, you bel… https://t.co/GH7jPQbnXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t wanna jinx it but life is dang good right now! The best family, the best friends, the most beautiful smart da… https://t.co/sON5up986f]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one more person calls me “goofy” today I’m gonna....... do absolutely nothing because they’re damn right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charter Schools USA is hiring in #WestPalmBeach, FL! Click the link in our bio to apply: 3rd Grade Teacher - Renais… https://t.co/MNOzrNh3td]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Drug dealers help out their community...” gotta be the dumbest shit I’ve ever read. Lmfao they also do a shit load of damage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this sunday relaxing as possible before this week of craziness begins 😬 i’ve never been so stressed/relieved/exited in my life ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatRudyguy Bruh. You know I love halloween. Why you gotta attack me like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be sleeping but trying to catch up on my instagram posts lol https://t.co/sNTmE7oyqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[so they’re putting the notebook on netflix... you KNOW my ass will be SOBBING every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times bowling for Junior Achievement 🎳🖤#JARocks #RQERocks #TCSLearns @Laura94818206 https://t.co/OnpYraFMRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealEdenMccoy @kinshriner @GenieFrancis I just love them I've been watching GH for many years so good to see that they're still on there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kez2009 And then...  Dig: Felicity, I understand, I'm sorry.  But the last time a woman went all Overwatch on me w… https://t.co/pYRMGpIxKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day at the  F/O household..... @lvlightsfc at 2 (first game and super excited) and the @GoldenKnights (obviou… https://t.co/kEJV3jmeJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever respond to your “thank you” with “you’re welcome” instead of “no problem” or “of course!” Just know that… https://t.co/YoBBQJdEZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Room temperature water is better for you” ok? Dat doesn’t mean cold water is bad for you nigga. So does it matter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjustjingles Ouch.  So sorry, Al.  That sounds very painful.  Will you go to a doctor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family throws nascar parties. When i was a kid i thought every family had nascar parties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[41 DIY Valentine's Day Cards Perfect For the Classroom Party https://t.co/tGmkVK3yOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[•Open House 935 Genter #lajolla #nelliehigh #realestate #bienesraices Willis Allen Real Estate • DRE 01945220 https://t.co/Myl65N6kL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like hearing leaders tell you the company has been doing it wrong. Change or die the easy talk https://t.co/ovSAZa1Hvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is a nice weiner &amp; some hot chics!! Lol!!! 🐕🐕💕💕🐥🐥💞💞😉😉😉😂😂😂 @ My Cozy Bed https://t.co/Af1AEJfR4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost my Anastasia eyebrow pencil that I barely got to use. crying goodbye to my $30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahamwitch1 @Stunt_Puppy It was part of her race name (she’s a rescue/retired racer from the track) 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captgordon @leestorrow I notice, G, that you didn’t like my good-game tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @TheGoldenRatio4 mom tonight poking around in my dog’s 💩 for a “foreign object.” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been studying for 6 hours and I’m still pretty sure I’m gonna fail my midterm 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[#captainmarvel #SPOILER although the ending montage featured girls who looked so different I wish they had just gon… https://t.co/ryounJpWCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterSupport I have been for days now trying to reinstate my daughter's account that you locked.  I only get bla… https://t.co/PDEvx42tV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part of my day was singing and dancing to my favorite song with some of my favorite people @NISDSteubing @NISD… https://t.co/EgJuXEWmvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernerSays A4: never had to do this before, but @SouthernerSays and I were planning on it for our trip to Alas… https://t.co/k192soAdRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What day is it??? How is it only Tuesday??? When was the last time I was outside??  @nasponline… https://t.co/7OqUgNXrR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelbyschooley @jamescharles I would fall out if one cost that much, I got one for me and one as a birthday present for someone else!]]></document><document><![CDATA[High today will be 25 degrees warmer than yesterday.🔥 Catch us at noon to see the changes in store for the rest of… https://t.co/xLiTlXA61K]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen, that is NO footage from 229 day🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 all from the internet from someone spring break probably .  last year… https://t.co/IgVkD4S4Kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the #DukevsUNC game two years ago and it’s easily the best atmosphere to be at in all of college basketball 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgraced former Congressman Anthony Weiner released from federal prison in Massachusetts. https://t.co/BcWYaaLWbQ https://t.co/PlF3nkzMeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstellaRupard @P25Kelly @LISDPTA @HuffinesMS @simplybadd13 So deserving @P25Kelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery From what she said he went to kiss her and she turned her head  . The two witnesses said it didnt happen ( sound familiar) ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a while since I had  a cat(over 8 years now) so I’m excited to see this “Gogurt”-type package for kitty f… https://t.co/28Gg42fJ2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaHaleRCSD @dianejeffersonc @HillaryClinton One thing I love is seeing all the women running for president@now,… https://t.co/jlDPTNNjBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWAnimation RT if you wish you were enjoying this #HowtoTrainYourDragon cake created by @livinglocurto #ad… https://t.co/ZNFuzXkq1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaloTopCreamery has the BEST chocolate ice cream and nobody is allowed to disagree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jingyeolbaeks Any footage that you took would be great! I just want to give fans a chance to show their pictures/v… https://t.co/1qpm6tb1BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EnoughIsEnough #Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping… https://t.co/c8uUQJhTmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew the second he did that shit bare minimum Twitter was gonna go STUPID smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKCorden  I think your a funny focker. But PLEASE stop making about politics   PLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTWCavsBaseball @CoachPolakWTW Meet Coach Night Breakout still canceled?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got to St. Louis and checked into our hotel. Round 2 let's GOOOO https://t.co/uhiqJoOwVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckennababyyyy Id like to thank my brother Scott and my sister Amy for same.  Theres a bonus to being the baby! 😂❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me, an adolescent*  Mom, can you pick me up from school, I hate everyone  *me, a grown woman*   Mom, can you pick… https://t.co/4IEvkVJpqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not real friends until you’ve spend hours in Target together for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddaniel_10 @hollymims @cosmic_Iatte @thvgcess @hipcated @khloekardashian Girl happen again? This done happened 8 t… https://t.co/SNsTQgRcrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 minute hold up at West Oakland bart, no word given to passengers as to why #bart #bartdelay]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were so confused when I went to go sit at my desk (which wasn’t the one in the front of the room).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyTolleyapp1 Good morning too you 🙂 Hope you have an awesome Monday 😁💜🌞👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenHatmaker @sarahbessey I feel like I’m complaining extra just to make up for SB’s stoicism.   Just kidding, comp… https://t.co/0JIeTZUbQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just have to make it past my 3 midterms this week and then it’s spring break. 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[SICKOS!!  Parents #charged with child abuse after Olive Garden #waitress posts photo on Facebook  https://t.co/tY1tWMcDGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NefertitiLeBeau @piktochart @pghs_spartans @JEFCOED Love the @piktochart !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t like their kitchen to smell like a bakery? With the the spoonful warmer and so many bakery fragrances t… https://t.co/ymBr5rdpnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Country Aire Mobile Home Park https://t.co/1mhrAuMsjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whimsywithinme She is a fantastic person. Hope you can come out for her book talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[How crazy is it that I turn on an episode of @CrimMinds_CBS and it’s the one with Luke Perry. #RIPLukePerry 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dinolich I’m at the dentist and dreading the 45 min drive I have to work more than the teeth cleaning atm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me just say going through name change because of divorce sucks. I apparently did not have certified copy of my… https://t.co/1ZbdUHfqHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pete58bos @kylegriffin1 #LockTrumpUp #ImpeachKavanaugh #ImpeachTrump #ImpeachTheBiggestDangerToAmericaTrump         @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oydeedoydeedoy @Layna2802 @BudKennedy @JohnCornyn I just read articles on the Internet about his recent retirement… https://t.co/ISrHesS716]]></document><document><![CDATA[I follow meteorologists on twitter bc I’m still bad at checking the weather but go on twitter 500x a day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotional vampires. Selfishly giving. These things are real! Praying before serving a client, a charity, or family… https://t.co/cQFq2kYIjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current V I E W S ✨😍 #arribalasmujeres phone cases that speak a powerful message 💪🏽💫  I cant choose a favorite, but… https://t.co/HncC5OWXg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfectly reenacting my inner thoughts. I can’t decide if I need a hug or a cave to hide in. Good times in #utah… https://t.co/chH9cYW5PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan Williams makes such ludicrous arguments. I want to scream at the sky... don’t worry I won’t though, im conservative ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in phenomenal company. Thank you @Breanna_Needham! #WomensHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got both kids down at relatively the same time https://t.co/A2pnt2GXrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sitting here wishing @TheStruts would announce more US dates.  Pretty please, guys. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your morning need to be about a solid routine that gets both mind and body engaged and ready for whatever your day has in store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/d8FKg5JoZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should get a week off for how bad my pms is every month. I swear I would lick myself in my room and not come out]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad to hear of Luke Perry's passing. My thoughts and love go out to his family and friends. #4everPike]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWalterTwiter @ilangoldenberg Did he say it was?   I’m a platelet donor. That’s “harder” than giving blood, but… https://t.co/pRpQcH7fW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working the oscars this weekend. Not looking forward to the Hollywood fuckery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why we go to All-Star.  Our favorite and I think one of the best of the weekend. @ Charlotte Convention Center https://t.co/ilue7ntVHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyAnarchy9 @EBGuitarMan @joeysalvia @ChefLouFWord @CreamyButters @Orionzdrm @Roksuperugly @Sungsam12… https://t.co/B55AYBHluN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you @jorgeescal #happysanvalentinday @ Red Lobster https://t.co/Y4EBOJCv2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fullpackagepro @B52Malmet @PrincessBravato What are the odds this guy used all his back channels to orchestrate Benghazi attacks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No temptation has overtaken you but such as is common to man; and God is faithful, who will not …… https://t.co/IYXID5bOg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @BetoORourke Shut up Lindsey. What do they have on you? U r a disgrace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let mueller prove he is a hero by  inditing or charging Hillary ‘s circle like he has president trump.👏👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I’ve been trying to figure out the name of these things for the past few months]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wooooooooooooooooooo Score by @mPinoe 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉 #USWNT #USAvENG]]></document><document><![CDATA[All students, regardless of race, tended to perform worse in courses led by professors with fixed mind-sets about… https://t.co/tLh7fweazf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing people’s alarms go off at the airport makes me sad. That’s probably the alarm they usually wake up to. 😂😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winn Dixie time!- (@ Santa Cruz Art League in Santa Cruz, CA) https://t.co/WNV0zcgdD9 https://t.co/klmliuzqtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelamgosnell Apparently because that’s the second time I’ve gotten a warning. The first was thanksgiving weekend… https://t.co/eUuU7QVltx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to ALL women!   “Each time a woman stands up for herself, without knowing it possib… https://t.co/WI1Ifwiuk3]]></document></documents></author>