<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is absolutely disgusting that people would form such a horrific bullying ‘group’ against any person. Worse tha… https://t.co/uQbsjRM6zL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of the time I swallowed a suppository, should have read the damn box 😐🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memories made with you are magic...❤️❤️ #anotherchicagoadventure #mattandashley #joebonamassashow @chicagotheatre j… https://t.co/Rv51zbGj7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson YOUR A  RACIST ASS BITCH AND YOUR SAYING IT WAS WAY BACK WHEN YOU  MADE THESE APPALLING REMARKS!  I… https://t.co/ZX1b6uQsBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump It is time for a peaceful march on Washington, now, if we do not get what we want.… https://t.co/10VgDaiDzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marceloclaure on my way to #FLII2019 @Merida super excited @BID_Idear @IDB_Lab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentions Hannah Sheehy Skeffington and Maude Gonna MacBride because they are famous, but they were not calling the… https://t.co/xATxmZIImK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APCentralRegion @AP And what is the Nationality and Race of these 100,000 individuals.  Do you want to take a Wild Guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 6yo just pointed out the window and yelled PINK! And no wonder. Or all the wonder. So much wonder. #goodmorning… https://t.co/dd1FutaVtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what I have done to deserve someone like her 😪❤️ https://t.co/pyurTNuHGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danentin @Paul_Rock_City Ahahaha was the first # that came to mind but between us and the people I've brought ther… https://t.co/zgzkcu3gAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yett hits the pitcher with a shot up the middle and he recovers in time to get the throw to first. Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@accordingtomio @MPCheesecake Yay!!!! The countdown is on!!!!! And I can show you the bakery!! Can't wait to see you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wivk1077 thanks for the shout out to all the East TN @JenniferNettles fans!!! #loyalfans 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capriroth @TribTowerViews The equity advocates aren’t actually that powerless in Sacramento. The most powerful sin… https://t.co/4hYyOfW1CZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westoriesstl @TravisSheridan @ONSLRG Hey @westoriesstl - kids under 12 are always free! (Unless you think we should bump the age up?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarsLarsonShow If a sperm donor can't hide his identity, then DNA should be considered public information:  https://t.co/Gz1M3XRMb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photography: Real Estate Home Staging Stager: upstyledesign Marlene Boney Photography 📸 @ArtistYvetteM designed for… https://t.co/23gXd9dxjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sensitive and overthink every little thing, idk how I manage sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make your appointment quick!! My book is getting full 804-691-8456 @ Allusions Barber-Beauty https://t.co/MBHxyjOyC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want a man who loves wings as much as I do, but eats the flats because I don’t like those kind. Who will let… https://t.co/SXN8WC68sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a good time when you get a big hug from @jimnashradio! Thank you for having me on air today and for bringing… https://t.co/8TV7k5boTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nonpartisnan When the issues are discussed in the long run We will be victorious when we work together to beat Tru… https://t.co/8dvmE38qML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslamRizza they better not dare touch this man, i'll chain myself to his tomb if i have to. leave michael alone, h… https://t.co/0evRu6NAIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else having the Mondayiest Monday ever? 🙋‍♀️ . . . WOD x3 Sets 》Situp Holds x10 》Back Bend x10 @ 10lb/10lb/2… https://t.co/6CYMD23zWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScaryMommy Mine is 14 and I bought him one that looks like this: HE STILL CAN’T FIND IT (also see @Josh_Friedman ‘… https://t.co/azjpJ3pLjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DojaCat in them purple tights. i was like SIS GO AWF #TiaTamera https://t.co/GiDOAowE1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankieInParis Thank you, Shauna! 🙏🙏I truly appreciate your comment! I say it's time for a writer's retreat to the beach! 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metrobusinfo You keep saying that but the bus service continues to be crap! Soooo freaking tired of your damn driv… https://t.co/ggxQGMZ7lA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbond20464 @retrosher It’s Spot! Somebody adopt Spot. Spanky &amp; Alfalfa send ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 1.57 miles in 32m:51s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/u61MEPvJdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[like softness/vulnerability is fine but quick reactions to harmless things that you perceive incorrectly isn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighWireTalk @RepAdamSchiff How dare citizens post things that disagree with Adam Schiff's preconceived opinions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5/ #SecondGeneration #Asians have a distinct #EducationalAdvantage over whites. But this competitive advantage disa… https://t.co/cBcGpPdZXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all are so disrespectful, nat &amp; alex wolff still make music. it’s really good too, so pls familiarize yourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianalopezbooks @Scholastic You’re welcome. As soon as our librarian showed me that Scholastic sent it to us for t… https://t.co/ZDgOXOm0ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil works hard, but Kim Kardashian works harder. #NorthWest https://t.co/giztUFKYOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isthisrealoril1 @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @GOP Not too proud to stand corrected. A CONSERVATIVE group on behalf of the GOP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericpthomas @ColoradoParaMan @AbilitiesExpo Have someone, friend or relative. Check how your party wants this done… https://t.co/6U9CS0gzQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have always said the gay community is going to find one day the Libturds will throw them to the dogs!!! Happened… https://t.co/ptpZYK5MgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sudesna_ghosh Wonderful. I hope she will be fine and will not have to have it on again.🐈💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[STARS WIN! STARS WIN! STARS WIN! #StatsWin #DALvsFLA #GoStars  💚🏒🚨🚨🚨🎉🙌🏼 https://t.co/wb047KkHMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY PRINCESS 💖 I love you so much and I am so thankful for your sassy ass, had so much celebrating you l… https://t.co/FZdpCiYpZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanonUSAimaging I’m constantly getting asked which lens I use!  People are amazed with my reply - the Canon PowerS… https://t.co/2NEf7SuTvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a society we need to remind young people to take regular unfiltered selfies. If they ever go missing they’ll be… https://t.co/zpkyGuWztE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s POTUS day.  I don’t really care but thanks for the day off 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 https://t.co/H9wCTI77ap]]></document><document><![CDATA[*shopping w my mom &amp; seester*  9 y/o seester: why do you always gotta be so extra?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed back to the #DisneyMagic for the last #Marvel cruise of the season to get more magical pictures like this on… https://t.co/CWmFP0SPsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannielleeeann Why not somebody’s daughter now? Come on! https://t.co/CZEPoLrt7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Women in Diving Everyone Should Know . Grateful to these women who have accomplished so much in ocean science, ph… https://t.co/jYtAh5D1Iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[she be looking popping with her Versace glasses https://t.co/V1t6rQSD7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathan_ht Yo no hablo de una sola persona, o la relación, pero en fin, cada quien toma las cosas desde su perspectiva.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reappropriate that 60 Million Planned Parenthood WILL NO LONGER RECEIVE - LET US GIVE A STANDING OVATION and APPLAU… https://t.co/FqgKUyHYEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub It’s all about hoarding for their offspring, which they failed to raise with any morals to guide them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vengeful Obsession www.gumroad.cpm/sylviahubbard1  📝😍📖💗👩‍💻📚💜  I finally got this book re-done and made it to availa… https://t.co/wcGtjo5diN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz please answer the question as to why you gave data to Russia sir. America demands your answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephanie Styles' and Dan DeLuca's version of A Dream is a Wish Your Heart Makes for SUREEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it hard to believe that anyone could love you as great as me ❤️ https://t.co/y6PEiUaQAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiffanytood15 @Fonziie @Lane8music Pregame starts at 9am sharp. Let’s get a case of champs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabZillAfoRilla @MeghanMcCain She’s ProBirth, she couldn’t give a hoot about supporting life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroncoHector85 @MichelleNBCLA @ShannaNBCLA @AleOrtizChagin Thanks Hector 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe @RepSwalwell Yes, drama is their business ! Fake news sucks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything’s coming up Ryan 🤗#winnerwinner #businessgrowthplan  #DECAstates #ontonationals #hardworkpaysoff… https://t.co/ybt2gGpdpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsaySmithDC Brilliant! Hope they emerge with the Longinus Spear...and more. Best wishes to you✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walls are for flat earthers and people who never heard of drones or tunnels. If you really want to stop immigration… https://t.co/bJZFvIOMXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I lay next to Topaz and I’m like “holy shit. I’m really lucky as hell. Like she’s REALLY my girlfriend”… https://t.co/VhhnmMj1Hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ll go to the gym before work!” Sureeeee sounds like a better idea at 8 pm than at 5 am the next day... 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representing @Hille_Huskies workingthe #PolarPlunge2019 raising money for #SpecialOlympics Chicago https://t.co/f0sc9hDCSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHale40630156 @SocialismSlayer @ChristineVozza1 @JimmyOC69859601 @EricTrump @realDonaldTrump So this hearing,  M… https://t.co/hAYrEG6kmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I read Jane Mayer’s article earlier this evening.  Newsstand copies of The New Yorker arrive very lat… https://t.co/WXkknEtlC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[As sad as the Celtics make me, the Bruins make me equally as happy. This team feels like the real deal...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protesters today outside the new concentration camp for immigrant children in Florida. Busloads of children are bei… https://t.co/Ez06HSNLUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[As bad as we were in the first half, we were phenomenal in the second! Great win for our seniors. I ❤️❤️❤️ this tea… https://t.co/N75QdbaL8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Krm Hussein @KrmHussein for retweeting my poem! Happy day friend!❤️💙💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyNumbers420 No!!! I am not Missing point I am not interested in Donald Trump he needs impeached]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m off work til Monday and I like haven’t gotten out of bed today and tommys telling me I’m gunna get bed sores if I don’t get up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Her politics are two-dimensional, so I guess it's fitting that she be visualized as a two-dimensional character...]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no way to be a perfect mother but a million ways to be a good one💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[se minha mãe estivesse viva ela estaria comemorando seu aniversário hj, pq eu tinha q lembrar em]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we please acknowledge the fact that rami malik is a literal meme https://t.co/mgaW4kt14L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @jflorez @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie @ja2cook… https://t.co/wQJFs8gUyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently, I was featured in an article in @runnersworld. It was such an honor. After the article went live, there w… https://t.co/67ulAcnw90]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time I saw this place I was in Hong Kong. There has been one in the East Village but we rarely go there. Now t… https://t.co/pUXt0UFSuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @Mil_FANet Is it a real possibility a cleft lip is from housing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah Brady crossed 10. Time 01:40:49, pace 10:17 min/mile, est. finish 11:28 am https://t.co/tHsx1Ud2Pi #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: kenz you need to date this guy @kenziekristinee : “with the wires? no AirPods, no thank you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simpostings @nhdogmom It’s not due to race. If it was, Kamala wouldn’t be polling third. It’s due to name recognition #nhpolitics #fitn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @BarbC1947 Awwwww - Tots and Priors.  Pfffft  Good riddance to the leader of the biggest hate group in the USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my recent tattoos are works in progress &amp; not ready to post, I thought I'd post some older pics.… https://t.co/r1xTWl8WyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore by the deeds of the law there shall no flesh be justified in his sight: for by the law is the knowledge o… https://t.co/PkaMsDkHXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridgetjoyce14 Omigod no this is the most incorrect thing you’ve ever said]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to be in NY shooting an episode of @BullCBS (my lips are sealed, but I will let everyone know when it… https://t.co/gF5fHKwOdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthMode So pissed cause I changed it from bob twice but apparently missed that it did it again a 3rd time when I wasn’t looking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castro moves into climate change, said his first act as president will be to sign the Paris Climate Agreement. (Ins… https://t.co/Quh01FF6UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie night in bed. Complete with popcorn, snuggles, and juice. #thegrinchmovie #familylife #daddyslittlegirl… https://t.co/gALBbjOK8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[men at gas stations are disgusting like pls leave me alone. it’s not cute, it’s creepy lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys of Summer #springtraining #philadelphiaphillies @ Spectrum Field https://t.co/CAAjJSkTg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protagonist’s gotta protag! . . . . #amwriting #amquerying #brandonsanderson #procrastination @ Missouri https://t.co/ILrLrQMeE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do liberals hate success?  @Alyssa_Milano @AOC @TeamPelosi @KamalaHarris @RepMaxineWaters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @nypl Just a question or more an observation (that we’re exploring here at my school). Although unable to vote… https://t.co/wAJyikdT69]]></document></documents></author>