<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Spotted: an extremely happy South African. 🖤 @jackandlilTO https://t.co/3ehxR5RK9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Historia de Tijuana en Muhti  - Museo de Historia de Tijuana https://t.co/ejGBSrExEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting to see a picture of @Kboston16 baby 😍💕 https://t.co/gi7vBE1E1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cake so good gotta have two! 🍰🍰 OH and adorn them with florals dripping in jewel tones, YES PLEASE!… https://t.co/7HniZrduXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @JMVivancoHRW Siguen, a pesar de  existir informes de sus organizaciones,donde consta lo que padecemos… https://t.co/qah70KnWWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg someone left 2 dogs on 237-W right before the exit to N. first street ):]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working on this death scene for days. I’m always sad when a character dies. Getting this one was tricky b… https://t.co/fXCjfXHLV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopCouruption I can't sit back and watch my life be more destroyed by uneducated people who only want to continua… https://t.co/4u6NRm9gUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoveCameron I just got hit with some bad news.😞 My mom just told me our dog, Chloe passed away 2 hours ago. Do you… https://t.co/mearhJIKfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[my girlfriend’s cishet professor keeps saying "f*ggot" in class and is teaching super transphobic material i'm livi… https://t.co/60ZlfW6wZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did you get for Valentine’s Day?  Me: “Girl – he went to @ChickfilA... ❤️😬” https://t.co/4VBLzC9A6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn was I dreaming or was a dude really snoring loud af at the theater yesterday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairewad Propolis echinacea spray for the throat. Powdered colostrum to boost immune system]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the episode when we say goodbye to a beautiful, innocent horse and good riddance to a very bad person. #TheSopranos]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we’re getting some snow again 🙄🙄🙄 #Sunday #snow #chillday @ New Jersey https://t.co/Zz9LEsWlNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[One week, it’s next week.   If you’re so inclined, share this with everyone, that’ll be the best gift yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisonmkevin Hi Kevin - I’m with CBC radio. Just saw your video of your skate on the street. I’d love to talk to… https://t.co/jCwphOTlTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m disgusted with pro-life protesters that harass women outside of abortion clinics. Have your own opinion but don… https://t.co/4085UQmndU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frank_is_Fun Can’t wait.  I carry around Kleenex, Qtips, and aquaphor. Just for prevention and preparation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are open until 8pm tonight!  💗 Happy Valentine's Day! 💗 @ Honey Bunz Organic Day Spa https://t.co/HuFqKLAPVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[cc: @SparkCognition @CNASdc @amirhusain_tx @august_cole @EBKania @jteurope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heather99851724 @briantylercohen Agreed.  If they did it like this they wouldn't need retaining access.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castaway Cay is the last stop on this incredible disneycruiseline which is bittersweet because none of us want to l… https://t.co/sEnRcJ3zE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the presenters make fun of the category they're announcing... Why?! It's a huge honor, no matter what! @TheAcademy #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMRealLifestyl1 @justuseapen @mand0xxx @charliekirk11 That is not the role of the media. That is the whole point o… https://t.co/H1dXkFgWJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hussonwbb @charmedmbv Good luck Vanessa!! Your hometown is rooting for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay 😭😭😭😭 I love you and AJ so much!!! One of the best mommas I kno! So glad I get to call you my best friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pneumatic tubes with local AD get wave of political support in New York https://t.co/GqjTwPWJVC via @WasteDive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSpuds @RidenerTina @72cricket @BxglL @sharon_schwan @sannbs @ACog1984 @rosemoczulski1 @CSonafelt I’ll take it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heh Brent, to keep the water bottles identifiable for each player, they could decorate them with their own special… https://t.co/joCk0dcIuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roco4033 @monsieurmach @ohheyjenna @HuffPost @Outback 🤣🤣🤣 your tweets are hilarious, bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were on vacation, and The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills just walked into the resort I was staying at lookin… https://t.co/028oVvKM63]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening☺ Avon orders in by Tuesday March 5th *https://t.co/s88lSmOLCq My eStore is open (24)hours for your con… https://t.co/eyeR3xxuaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t know if it’s the weather or just me but I’m in one hell of a mood. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never knew a heart could physically hurt yet still feel like its not there anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robincrown @KaceyMusgraves @StubbsAustin Safe travels! Talking to Dare about his day with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy day feels and all I want is to be under a blanket with some... Ice cream. Or at Disneyland.… https://t.co/eHfLJEGhKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanEiler @MaryOursWX I had my chi tea and watched Mary's forecast. I hope you all have an awesome day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to forgive myself, with everything that me and my dad went through 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_ehrenzeller @Mullins_Lyrics I love Rich Mullins—the man and his music ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottDemel @CarloScissura @NYGovCuomo @nytimes @amazon @EricBenaim @MaxRose4NY @Steiner_Studios Amazon just closed… https://t.co/wWY5vmpWS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @wtam1100 @POTUS Actually, Trump’s behavior had lots in Washington asking if if if .......]]></document><document><![CDATA[TITO CALLOWAY: "IF THE DEMS AND THEIR FAKE NEWS  MEDIA ARE TALKING IMPEACHMENT OVER ACCUSATIONS WITHOUT ANY REAL EV… https://t.co/J1jAUFWnga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colt is barking up a storm so I tell him to lay down and be quiet, this little boy has so much attitude, he lays do… https://t.co/5BSvfOAd6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzwordAthon I though Cher was replying to this and was VERY confused https://t.co/tJFgno6V4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec why to be defensive at the press briefings? Why not provide short answers? If you don’t like questions, o… https://t.co/2sOYiA5IQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartyCheddarCat Yes, little Goldy patches. You cats are my friends since I was 8. I got this song from " O, Brothe… https://t.co/vAPPAyX59L]]></document><document><![CDATA[El único llamado que usted debe hacer es el de una Intervención Militar. Siguen matando a nuestros hermanos, se sig… https://t.co/A2TPXUR3yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shameful? Like saying there are good people on both sides of the white supremacy protest? Shameful like that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro On an unrelated note - re. Roger Stone -  I think it would be prudent if media reps would stakeout Roger… https://t.co/duRdCQKMdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[God will always make a way and come thru for you if you stay faithful #PROVENFACT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airbornex82nd @sirbryan1955 @IlhanMN It offends me. That might not be right but all kinds of ppl say things offend… https://t.co/ujci6lsbZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I’m on board with everything but the Wawa egg white veggie thing. Made me puke 🤢 the other day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bedroom feels like it looks like crap outside   *goes back to sleep*]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #SundayBunday, we have a brand new photo of the beautiful (heart and soul) @adamramzi_xo, as photographed by K… https://t.co/liH2vTcp3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jovermyer1 @uncommondream @wafflesonwed @Mrs1500 @coffeesippers @mrandmrsmoneym1 @JHudsontraffic @WadeEgmon… https://t.co/LTX90UM05D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Not yet but they are standing by concocting a story she can use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @nyc311 the traffic lights on Flatbush and Tillary are broken and it’s creating a lot of chaos and unsafe condi… https://t.co/Z14n7n7ic6]]></document><document><![CDATA[in the snowy alder woods the faint tapping  of a woodpecker  #haiku #weather #Snow #AlderTrees #iphoneography https://t.co/APs4WLZmAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobChristie11 It sure does. So how much did they get paid for staging this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleLemke23 @MissMargoPrice @nwlc @EqualPay2dayOrg @EqualRightsAdv What planet are you on? Oh right. The manPlanet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revxdd So far I’ve had 3 tattoo artists before I found the above listed who’ve hunted down my Instagram or persona… https://t.co/mCLFzXzm10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simplicator @ShimonPro @nycsouthpaw @mkraju Unless it's a one-and-done, I agree they shouldn't mess with impeachme… https://t.co/dHe0o9hT4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great photo of one of our all female teams @BESTRobotics #PittsburghBESTRegionalChampionship @GroveCtyCollege on… https://t.co/MXquGzbOQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliGamer @williamlegate I think that’s the point! He wasn’t there to see violence! I’m  q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdrhwke @Littlleome @DoreenWisneski1 @lauralee4949 @Dramasong1 @AnneJohnsonckm @Joybell71450574 @lisa21910… https://t.co/bquM56lmeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone should ask Trump what all he believes in that Putin has spoken to him about maybe there could be some in si… https://t.co/KLDe4Ij14s]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET THIS SCUMBAG, OUT OF THIS COUNTRY NOW, SHE'S AGAINST AMERICA.!!! 🚨🚨🚨🌟🌟🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations What! Ron, don’t you think TrumpJr is “A”Cell Block Material? #LockThemAllUp #TrumpCrimeFamily (and… https://t.co/QZW2gELUwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amy Klobuchar has a lot in common with Comet, a household cleanser... grit!!!🤣😂🤣😂🤣! Way to go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWheezly @RepJoeKennedy Realizing it - maybe.  Caring - no.  Hell no. Not even a little bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the age-old question, if he's so innocent why does he go to these lengths? https://t.co/EvIVGbLshr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a slippery, slushy mess out there. I broke out my crampons for what I hope is the last time #Montreal #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m surprised Nick didn’t care to go out for margaritas tonight. Where did my husband go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to bed for a nap at like 2 pm yesterday, but ended up sleeping until 1 am. Oops. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was eventful I went to multiple strip clubs and the casino smh 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This small group is loving @PearDeck’s vocab factory! They are doing a great job creating these vocab cards with th… https://t.co/lKKn0DLwmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrologeranne1 thank you for following me! I am a believer, will definitely check it out, thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsaadrianaaa @KylieWoody ooooooo man I’ve really been wanting to see them since I missed out in Steamboat]]></document><document><![CDATA[so, burgundy on girls is definitely a favorite; how adorable is she !  https://t.co/Q1xdhJlo2a @ Shannon Burke Phot… https://t.co/1SkRDeucEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Yea people like YOU are the only ones using words like bigotry and etc... YOU are wh… https://t.co/PGkZsfXjMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@945Country It's #wishfulwednesday and I'm hoping to hear a .@TravisMarvin song today.  Would you please play any… https://t.co/xJz5m83tc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woernley_Raps And people can go ahead and sneeze, but the ones that are dramatically loud are simply doing that be… https://t.co/PxUYuN3MO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody stop me from doing a haul video about all the reason why I’ll never do haul videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little by little been waking up early on the weekends.  Guess my body wants me to do something 🤦🏿‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna go buy a house rn and all u guys can live with me if u ever feel like it thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crulge EasyBib for one-offs or EndNote for managing many citations you might use repeatedly. I’d do some research… https://t.co/zJsU86Zw6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real national emergency should have been signed November 8, 2016...]]></document><document><![CDATA[So like wait... is Jordyn Woods really trying to gain sympathy after this whole scandal? Am I suppose to feel bad s… https://t.co/PIdCg2W1Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should you ever be so lucky to work with @29designstudio_! Thank you Maureen ♡  #risingtideliftsallboats https://t.co/V9vXD9hqNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blah blah blah... Translation: We’re slippery as all get out and can change our price target anytime it gets windy… https://t.co/k2cVXF57kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shootings here might make it difficult for our current Mayor to get reelected]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCKthisNoyz @kstraith @JoeTrippi @greta Yeah I just was looking, in articles for cause of death and I felt it very… https://t.co/DjzmRD8NR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elena_berisha @Lem_Moe @jessjhupp dude I forgot her name but remember her she was at Charlie 131 for like 3 weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Where's your outrage over the Trump supporter being beat up by a Democrat/Socialist like yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Sending good thoughts from Napa to a man who has made this world a better place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really trying to figure out why my baby daddy constantly trying to take my happiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roof in port #Charleston port. Cc: @SenatorTimScott @GrahamBlog https://t.co/8Y93qMcqTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women’s Day ❤️ You are Beautiful ❤️ You are Smart ❤️ You are Worthy ❤️… https://t.co/GyI9JlzTeU]]></document></documents></author>