<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My contact fell out of my right eye as I was driving on the interstate and I was able to keep driving while putting… https://t.co/mDID7dyeGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay #REDFriday @XStreamFisher @WassmannBill @stephen_richter @MissAnnieChtrs @CMFishing @MattLFishing… https://t.co/dBEI2pJ4Et]]></document><document><![CDATA[@falseflag_info @CryptoKaku @AlexandriaV2005 @climatestrikeUS @ClimateStrikeNY Why does it benefit anyone to lie about Climate Change?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Coyne116 @WifeSwap @paramountnet that was on trading spouses, a different show... please do your research.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering a post on correct inflation metrics for transit projects. Too clickbaity?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlNGraham Any chance you could scan those and upload to https://t.co/fYGvd4uIgi for future enthusiasts :o?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodrighthander The Wilder fight shouldn’t be too hard to make. Yes he has ties to showtime but he isn’t signed to… https://t.co/c5GBYEKjPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@highhopespod Can’t think of a single reasonable excuse why it wouldn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people start leaving your life that’s nothing but a sign from God telling you they no good for you 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the @Nike shoe disintegrating actually caused the #ZionWilliamson injury? Thoughts? #NikeFail… https://t.co/bzLk6yRSyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[California Dreamin’ from Iowa @Dodgers #valleykid #SpringTraining #GoBlue https://t.co/bD6PLcLYT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracksideMikeN I woke up on the wrong side of the bed this morning. I need to start over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All spectrum gotta do is say some shit like you ain’t relevant ... then all of Twitter coming back for dis man lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCCPastor Awesome news!!!  Can’t wait to see how this chapter unfolds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Rep. @cathymcmorris for meeting with WA delegates on #JDRFGovDay to discuss Type 1 Diabetes #T1D issues.… https://t.co/AmssJuokK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time last year, I didn’t really understand what the next few days ahead would mean to me. This was exactly one… https://t.co/vQ5XgI5hj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to defend myself today. Just like yesterday and the day before that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In VENEZUELA🇻🇪 it is called "Parcial" or "10 es nota y lo demás es lujo"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun cleared out just in time for some birthday miles before dark! 😎 #winterrunning #snowstorm #birthdaymiles… https://t.co/XBdJ1orwKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how when I check Twitter in the AM...  1) I have people screaming at that me it wasn’t right that someone wa… https://t.co/8w3fUEfT4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #throwbackthursday first day in the #nolia beyyyybey.  ......................................................… https://t.co/Akbdu3lPNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Green Dress, 2017, Oil on Linen, 36x24  #EmilKazaz #fineart #oilpainting #painting #contemporaryart #artgallery… https://t.co/LjEUogXJfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[24. I originally wanted to be a journalist for my career, but I abandoned it because I was afraid of moving away fr… https://t.co/DBD511IaOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 11 of the sinus siege that just refuses to end. At least now I am just severely hoarse, but can speak again. I’… https://t.co/FBgY6iQ1Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC And why has productivity grown??? Could it be automation and efficiency?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyrebel907 @aagw @blackyngdave1 @james_bong13 @_dopedaneille @_jena4n @Mp1Mi @JonnyRotten1714 @enokian1… https://t.co/9p9S6zoJWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my representative to terminate Trump’s sham national emergency. Will you join me? https://t.co/0zzJqGTnmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pompano167 No. I’ve had a lot of very good inquiries about the hock protectors. They aren’t common but the farm I work on uses them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoStormWarning @Trancefiend408 @howtohockey @DevonCanales @TimHortons @NHL It’s either that or he skates I’ve to t… https://t.co/6NXkvcObMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerwinLGray My son got a TLW ring. It’s common in our church for the boys to get them. Of course, it’s somewhere l… https://t.co/Ztd6EqJYao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe Scott Walker rose economy two rows in front of me on a plane. Economy... lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHSLions @WHSBoys_Bball Is this regular season im missing, no way I need a schedule]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenmetzmusic @AMiles1985 I’m okay I promise! But @stevenmetzmusic I’ll be keeping you and your friend in my prayers! 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has any professional draft had the top 2 picks selected from the same High School before? @MLL_Lacrosse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uograd66 Just catching the game midway in the fourth quarter. Cousins has a real talent for pissing off the other… https://t.co/2SGGczVp7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[My high school jv basketball coach is now a registered sex offender sooo 👀👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I scored a hat trick in the #NHLHatTrickChallenge daily game. So did 4% of @NHL fans who played.… https://t.co/CPW7cXadAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner 👏 is 👏 not 👏 a 👏 self-made 👏 billionaire. She was born with a silver spoon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deaslefin9 But what about Paul George? I mean the man’s an MVP candidate. Who wouldn’t want him]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are people’s lives.. but also, I’m their lawyer..: they are clearly on the adventure ride!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[wishing you the most special happy trails!! it meant a lot to me that i got to see you shine in mean girls 🥰 i’m se… https://t.co/nKDhgs3NJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bagleyriskmgmt @summitfarms_llc And they treat their franchisees better than just about everyone in that game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aram68 I don’t think I can afford the ring JLo got.  https://t.co/I136JpGDQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your kid is not working out with this trainer your kid is missing out of being the best athlete he or she could… https://t.co/y09Mm7XEmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbbevilacqua ¿Por qué no salimos a votar en la de Gobernadores? Ganando esa habríamos tenido chance de entusiasmar… https://t.co/lqcBuk4BnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanyelReneeBB I hope he’s forced into retirement because nobody wants him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zed1291 @POTUS What is funny is I don’t think you even realize how right you are. One book brings life the other L… https://t.co/2JmnFZC5Ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Icing my knee after physical therapy... oh, what a feeling as I'm panning toward the ceiling... . . . . .… https://t.co/KXLWYTa52J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @DeplorableJuJuV @TWITMO_INMATE @RNRKentucky @Maggieb1B @PauWitkowski @cindy_nurse @Rbigzs… https://t.co/pQoBG2LO73]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatsandwine You have my thoughts, prayers, positive vibes--whatever you need. So sorry for your loss.  ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was it the same for those 2 as fresh year w/ 3eb and Matis, SL..? (or was it mainly just me and him for those..?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePMoffatt @MacLeodLisa Video shows that she does not know what she’s even talking about]]></document><document><![CDATA[They do exactly what their leader does they follow the leader. And that's Donald Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marehair @newtgingrich @DonaldJTrumpJr “I’m smart Michael” (Fredo) “I’m your older brother”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinDavid22 @PalmBeachPeezy Austin this guy you are talking to is a tool, full of anger and frustration. Can’t w… https://t.co/5zlm7Nt0va]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 19 #authorlifemonth Non-Bookish hobby. Some of my cosplay adventures. I’m always in awe at the talent, imaginat… https://t.co/y4OQiF9Vgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check me out in supernaturalassassins along with so much more awesome and talented individuals! 🎥🎬🔥🤟🏼… https://t.co/qGzYaLMZMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sosababy3hunnid Are you caught up on sword art??? If not you should try]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ApologiaForce Contingency and Kalam are a False Cause fallacies.  Fine tuning is a Personal Incredulity fallacy.   Next...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikenedie @yourmumspants @tklforgiven @KotobaruSanSama @Heliocoptero @PittsburghTodd @zapher134 @zypisfy… https://t.co/YEKGlbVYGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow we get high and show these guys weed kung fu @HOODSLAM https://t.co/Vp4BmAfdpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCGalloway @Alyssa_Milano I'd guess 15 million years on phones?  What galaxy? https://t.co/0udg8WzeOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brief shoot-around session @ Tucker Road Athletic Complex 02-22-019 @ Tucker Road Community Center https://t.co/rl3Tb5AFaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @MindiMink @karleegreyxxx @RachelStarrxxx @Zoeyfoxx @SummerDayXXX @JillKassidyy @onlyjennafoxx @APOLONIAPORN… https://t.co/eLDsrYJWso]]></document><document><![CDATA[The doors are OPEN!!! #mesports #goubears #d3hoops @bowdoinwbb https://t.co/WN6DcRNCbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea, bring on more Socialism even if has a solid record of abject failure everywhere it’s been tried!]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing investment property in Denver! #realestate #denver #coloradohomes #realtor #denverliving… https://t.co/vEeZyngc83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner Ah yes let’s judge all historical figures by today weak kneed values. Here is an idea how about all yo… https://t.co/CAxInNgrUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we move forward we need to look at changing the system. Often times the content is viewed as our issue, but if w… https://t.co/NfnpzLAWRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greater Cincinnati NAACP VP Joe Mallory and Black United Front's Iris Roley both praising a deal before council tod… https://t.co/9C8gNiT8tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unlike with evolution nobody in The Riott Squad kisses Ruby's ass and you know who I'm talking about His last name is flair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earl_Thomas let bygones be bygones. JS get on the horn and earl get on the horn and let’s get this worked out and… https://t.co/87d0pm7LEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberRoseRevah Movie time!!  Hey @007, here's your golden opportunity...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Valentines Day by watching House Hunters, the TV show with couples that always get along....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love a good challenge but I ain’t workin like no fool for sum I didn’t sign up for. Gtfomf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDessau @kimguilfoyle All that matters 249yr is FAKE NEWS. Also called freedom? I got it Most valuable thing… https://t.co/CBTp8qQ2Hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam_orth It’s over 7K maxed out in Canada… and it doesn’t have a real escape key!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBC4Sports @Capitals @Kuzya92 @nbcwashington @BizNasty2point0 @RearAdBsBlog]]></document><document><![CDATA[manemob @karl5026 iamtiffanyray #ManeMOB #StyleLIVE #fashionstylist #fashion #style #fashionstyle #fashionista… https://t.co/6cQV7UKfU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolWSD people are ripping you apart on Clancy &amp; Carrabis... jump back on the phone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that saw the titles for these games and was like, “huh. Odd flex”? Because before it was at least… https://t.co/2euQZKn1d9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vacancy declared on @BentonCoAR  Quorum Court   https://t.co/s8MvjzffKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! No one is in Twitter everyone out there having sex!! Be safe out there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinpurcell @MikeDrucker Hey Tim “Apple”, how do I apply to get a job at “Cook”? https://t.co/WthEq7f7MS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaergon Yeah for sure, but now he’s back to being healthy and playing well... definitely feel turning 21 and not b… https://t.co/thwLW0Ywuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickiGrafWX Happy Meteorological Spring, Vicki! (Although winter isn't ready to give up without a fight). Stoneham… https://t.co/GglzTBdqUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to see the new Gundam movie tonight with one of my oldest best friends.   He’s never seen a Gundam series… https://t.co/Swq8Ky8f01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Budweiser barleywines, Batman... This shit is too fucking good! - Drinking a Bourbon County Brand Barleywine (… https://t.co/si3bAzlNvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What in the world are you talking about? Is... is this a thing? Are you trying to make this a thin… https://t.co/ODoLNG6yAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oxym0r0nn @dooda313 @FrequentSmoker So I watched this a few times over lol he tricked dude first time right second time left 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Will never happen; the left is blind to their idiocy. They only want revenue , profits , ads , $$$$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin Trump will give the store away now that Cohen is spilling the beans on the Orangeman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndresCitizen1 @Angel3614 Para ti y los que piensan como tú para millones no simple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[De febrero fluye la fría fiebre y el fervor. Fantasía también fluyendo.  #Baylor @ Baylor University https://t.co/yJtVdalR9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sylien__ @Different_Elves These look great! That color blue is fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLLNNLmotivator Dude I love it.   Also, is that a gas mask next to you?!   It’s yellow ... which means I want one… https://t.co/10zXD4YG7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino @realDonaldTrump SHOW US YOUR TAXES, THEN REASON FOR THE GOOD OF THE COUNTRY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Peanut Butter Chocolate Stout by @PipeDreamBrewin @ Linde's Brewhaus — https://t.co/mpo9RvuL0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up way too early, seeing posts by followers I don't know at all. It's like the night crew or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feedtheball @craig_colton @tonyjdear CCO and Forse is a great example of where proper credit should be given. He d… https://t.co/zfnSDVu5jm]]></document></documents></author>