<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Gente o Laio é gente boa pra caralho, cara firmeza mesmo q eu tenho muito carinho, amei saber (de novo) que ele tam… https://t.co/poP2b10Wxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I hold this small box that holds what was ONCE my Bubba Bear, who crushed my boobs and spleen as he climbed up… https://t.co/2bah8xmzXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Walt Disney World Vacation! https://t.co/WTedMiya33 Would love too go here with family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peto_hs @juanburgos Fue súper gracioso, sobre todo la forma en la que fingieron que estaban trabajando en sábado a las 6 pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icantgetenouqh Get a dam life your definitely obsessed with Justin and Hailey just stay out of their life and leav… https://t.co/1gpietMGVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_fReeRich I like him a lot more now that we’re co-parenting a 36-year-old]]></document><document><![CDATA[My public service message for today: Its Very Windy. It can be dangerous outside. High wind warning in effect. Doze… https://t.co/7uTxBx2DzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @Itridpm @poppij @DudekLinda @andrerucker51 @_Delathor_ @OutlierShME @Mooncatadams @hey_butter… https://t.co/Q7zuxgMnmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJTheRealOne @TheValuesVoter Agreed, mostly. And I like the responsibility laid on the man, but women should never… https://t.co/0uZO0uk2TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 12:43am and my roommate hates me #IWEARYOGRANDDADSCLOTHES #macklemore #goodwillgang #salvarmySL #2019yop… https://t.co/GKLRfmQhll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne That's a fair response by you.  Besides, technically, white plantation owners are the ones who dra… https://t.co/raRIAIHpL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[but can I just say that I LOVE when I’m at work before the BGM is on, I love a quiet theme park]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson learned you simply do NOT open a bottle of nail glue with your teeth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably the Mafia, the CIA and the Pope are who he answers to, and probably signed a contract to sell his soul, so… https://t.co/XiVjAGsV5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themetalenock @neilrao42 @LoonisBaboonis @BlameGirls @EcoSenseNow @AOC no,  ding bat thinks we can somehow travel… https://t.co/C1boA2MlL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I disagree with letting someone so young get semi involved in politics but bullying a seven year old for somet… https://t.co/ABNpHUbaP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetroBoyJon @Radioactive3D @ColonelFalcon @RetroGamerDaz @BloggosPow @RetroGamersClub @replicantpinky @CardiacDrop… https://t.co/pi6yS6VwWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still very much on Jussie's side but if anything else. Comes out... https://t.co/QiiSVFnSyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another beautiful L.A. Morning 🌴 ☁️ #nofilter #losangeles #sky #ilovephotography #nature @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/lEPY6ri4xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be part of this important work. “Because kids are people first.”@BuggMagnet]]></document><document><![CDATA[💛🖤 HOLY MOLY! IT'S ALL ABOUT SPREADING THE LOVE 💛🖤 Great times tonight at hobboston with @matomaofficial… https://t.co/wfaFp9BO0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThirdEyeBlind @3EBLIFESTYLE @stephanjenkins @jimmyfoundation So many edits needed lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official response from @Douglasville_PD re: sirens we heard and many of you heard this morning. https://t.co/fQMwcV35Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy mi cuerpo necesita de ti, saber que la dosis perfecta está en tus caderas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work work work... but hopefully we get of bit of sightseeing @ Delta Terminal - Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County A… https://t.co/TKlNznRZZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[DALLAS COWBOYS NATION TIME CHANGES TONIGHT @ Valley Ranch, Irving https://t.co/YtS5HP7dAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@que_sera_surrah Lol is that target? Asking for myself because I will get that mug if you don’t haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGodOfDeathA1 Well then. I’m gettin’ myself to GraceLand for a quick breakfast taco this morning. ☺️🖖🏻 #TaraAnnMoons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unite4Truth @POTUS @JudicialWatch Yeah, let's hear your Explanation after all you work for us. Or so we thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is worth this.  YOU deserve someone who treats you like a queen because you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting in my car at school and completely daze off to space with a dumbass face and forgot there’s someone in… https://t.co/Td3b18oCyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tal7291 @headdock @DanLairdMD @RogerTh71142375 @ravensspirit68 @rlamartini @scleroplex @LelenaPeacock… https://t.co/eFZK4Cx2EB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survive 12 rounds of trivia and win real cash! Use my referral code buzzvideo to get an extra life@Buz... #BuzzVideo https://t.co/SHcyu4gbFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking drive correctly so you don’t total your shit and leave the rest of us backed up in miles long traffic plsz thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JK_followers @BTS_twt Me too, love seeing #Jungkook out socializing with his friends. That ADORABLE face I love SO… https://t.co/DioIU0x0EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you think of something cool and everyone is sleep then years go by and everyone likes it 😐 I told y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like they can’t get enough. Until enough is enough, and then it’s too much 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec  Wow sweetie, you have really crossed over to the dark side  a trump mini-me The more you lie for him the… https://t.co/oBtDqfveJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trade deficit is higher than it's been in 10 years. We sure miss Obama!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beauties playing underneath a beauty! @CStateWSoccer https://t.co/8rlmdEEaYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i miss my old life :( everything used to be so easy and it all made sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name This Group 😭ft :@MekaJusRight wandafulwoman straightnochaser247 @ Mountain Resort Cabin Rentals in the North G… https://t.co/qhVM1P8zKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mf said Michael Blackson look like https://t.co/QOisMrMgvz dad and now I can’t unsee it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealityTVBliss @Andy I knew there was no lady that wanted to adopt Lucy. That was another of Dorits fabrications.… https://t.co/z8hqdpnWnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I THINK......i’m just gonna pack up everything I own, move out west &amp; call it a mf day. see y’all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suddenly my mind went back on that day and now I’m mad.  I feel like I was scammed  Common curtesy mofo https://t.co/OI59SxdcVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) my coworkers like me *way more* than I thought and I feel really good about my work relationships]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math contest! 2nd place for 3rd grade, 1st for 4th. So proud of Anjol. Then basketball after! #TMEbulldogs… https://t.co/Lf66TTFWTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen,,y perferred communication method is thru tinder ok deal with it,,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedastaff party night @ Sagebrush Cantina, Calabasas https://t.co/zxpMREoog6]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do you plan a whole future with someone and then one day that just all be over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @KamalaHarris @SenKamalaHarris will never be my President. Hypocrisy at its finest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieGarson @LindseyGrahamSC Willie, it must be something bad they have on him.  Lindsey used to actually listen;… https://t.co/xsYBqEi2pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many viewers on social media have been reporting trouble with shoveling sidewalks, cleaning cars, and busted snowbl… https://t.co/Dw94DevA0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[all my friends are going to lost lands &amp; I cannot even afford the payment plan 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stalker and his partner paid imdividuals $1000.00 to stalk and photograph me on my own property. They trespassed… https://t.co/bxEnPDJgca]]></document><document><![CDATA[A client brought us in huge trays of homemade vegetation noodles and egg rolls. So. Good. https://t.co/PSe3Qgwwth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dossettswift @ryancortez One of the shows I like is Night Court and it is so funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And dont forget were also dealing with a dumb fool like u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eye-opening read on gender inequality rooted in use of male normative data: e.g. "We know everything about dust dis… https://t.co/DCMW26rz5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueCFlorida @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Bully for you!!!!!  You go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daisyybeam Please visit my webpage https://t.co/KD21OsReEi and email me your mailing address and how many dogs you would like to enroll!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of me wishes Rachel would’ve ended up with Joey. I love the episodes where he falls in love with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nathalie7News @7News So fun anchoring with you! (And also glad to catch up - it has been too long! 💕)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cameron seriously needs medical attention. This part of the movie always bums me out. #FThisMovieFest https://t.co/aEodQ9fZ6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister That's terrible. You don't deserve that. I do happen to agree with you on most things. You are able… https://t.co/PzZ20nYHhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly just so lost rn it sucks things just can’t work out for us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relationships that build, strengthen, encourage, and add value to life are as important as eating. Value those who… https://t.co/UsPCotlSVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time I try to take steps forward the universe wants to push me back😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Lol. You bring the lowest charges, a $100,000 bail.  Seriously?  Do you think this POS will be punish… https://t.co/8SFsYos5nM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I don’t think I will be spending $8 for a branch of cotton to put in a vase on MY table at home 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you fit 10 banker boxes in the backseat of your Jetta: https://t.co/6FsBD7orbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers For some reason some racist don’t think are racist but demonstrates racism on a regular. Having a b… https://t.co/9HhXW0Ujeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NonnaSJF @JJWatt @CoryO24 Thanks to the #GirlScout Cookies🍪 for supplying  us with our sweet fixes. #TemptationIsland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLusk: if it’s state $ going to private school, doesn’t that violate Article VI of state constitution? Eddie n… https://t.co/4LZz6tTunT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Private lanai setting and disappearing sliders enhance the open indoor/outdoor feel.  Visit link in Bio OR Discover… https://t.co/8ahpfKrh1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@502_Kamaya What about it? Do you limit yourself? Or you are scared of what other people will think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to #NorfolkCounty #OPP for keeping our roads safe last night! #RideProgram #Waterford]]></document><document><![CDATA[His last 3 pointer as a Hebron Hawk! I’ll always remember cheering from the stands (in or outdoor) ‘Remind me why I… https://t.co/RLSN4C9CE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made one of my students mad today and for the next 5 minutes she proceeded to sing “i don’t like you i don’t like… https://t.co/96qzD96tAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaththeWineLady @pietrosd @CaptainKob @Julianna_glass @winewankers @wineworldnews @DemiCassiani @suziday123… https://t.co/Q4EiJHWXy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ans!! Love ya ❤️❤️ @AnsleyTrunick https://t.co/uGxWhIKUfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hansonDigby @daveweigel @SherrodBrown This is the Obama map when he ran as an anti-war, pro healthcare hope and ch… https://t.co/WMBqPIcvtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i??? reading this??? correctly???? someone COMPLAINING that @TPAIN is gonna be performing???? at their school???… https://t.co/gWiwaOAjec]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of today was going to the MCV to get my 21+ license and being told that my head was too big for the frame 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Saturn V rocket. It's the biggest rocket ever built and was used for the Apollo missions! It's as tall… https://t.co/pqhrXq0cnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_havely @medwoman1 Damn! That is awful. I sure hope u find your baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a water main break reported at Hoffman Rd near Perimeter Rd in Plainfield (close to the airport). Expect road restrictions @rtv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianambl @mmpadellan As well as I could be yours but all I see are mean tweets from democrats! You are an except… https://t.co/4iid5Z6AQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelDick Shocker! Boo-hoo for Lolo.  Were you surprised Tamar won by a unanimous vote? I sure was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“‘The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.’” -Emerson @DariusForoux https://t.co/CJJqE27DMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister brought home the most incredible boyfriend, almost 30 years ago. He is a wonderful Asian who truly immers… https://t.co/W1tSnQP9Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dy7764 @KYnurse45_ I’m not reading yet lol I have to watch show still 😂🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkocharmd @AmerGastroAssn @UNCGastro @CMSGov Thanks rising star @bkocharmd !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDChiefofDept @NYPDTransit @NYCTSubway @NYPDChiefPatrol @NYPDCommAffairs @NYPDONeill @NYPDDetectives… https://t.co/fB4adsHdUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @aurarivera11171 @LindseyGrahamSC What a jackass!  Lindsey graham thinks threatening his president'… https://t.co/IbJNtnUI59]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indianapolis  has declared #gunviolence to be a public health danger. So why is @IndyMayorJoe allowing the #NRA to… https://t.co/orlglbBEut]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you "captions" this valid criticism as anti-Semitism, it feeds into the shadowy-Jewish-world-order myth. Sayin… https://t.co/eZgEatYSQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now fight with the Night King! I just entered for a chance to attend the #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How do you p… https://t.co/pWaejfpTIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We are so excited to have your presence in Lee County, Alabama today to support those affected by… https://t.co/2wIp8DCvmO]]></document></documents></author>