<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ramp to miami blvd closed til the end of july for construction in #Durham on Hwy 70 Byp WB and Miami Blvd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaterCrunchy @JohnSmi52322821 @DonaldJTrumpJr You need a brake to put in drive moron, not to start the car. I was… https://t.co/p6jDRnkfv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsChatfield1 @suefigueroapbc @pvcobrashs @southPbcsd @Dr_Corcoran @FdlrsAlpha @LeadInclusion @PledgetoInclude I'l… https://t.co/AM7YsJwcrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thismorning @AlisonHammond2 chats to @SeanBorgLA at @ejaf Oscar bash #Showbiz #seanborg #Entertainment… https://t.co/MTyd77oout]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:34 to go - Benton 40, Country Day 40 #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops @LCDSsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[NC legislature to consider a bill allowing judges to determine sex offender registration status for sexual battery.… https://t.co/9NU8rFaKnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[In some ways it's a difficult path-2 follow our Maker/Jesus said: 2 take up our cross 2 follow Him/It requires unco… https://t.co/sKvUCdRo3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greg Tombragel crossed PioneerHD KOM #2. Time 02:37:26, https://t.co/wwjHMWOEZo #ToSH19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CA_Showcase @ULVAthletics That's a real hoss playing center right there.  I hear he coaches for the good guys now #F19GHTULV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Individual1Pod @Zigmanfreud #He thinks seeing his Love in the Country he Refused to go to , will take our eye off… https://t.co/Di9u96fkjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Linares, Pueblo Magico https://t.co/XpQdNfrJAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time volunteering with my son, P.J. at the #BlackCanyonUltras last weekend. Next year, run it. https://t.co/YaVmjZOdzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyRussell900 @Bowenchris The average top corporate rate among EU countries is 21.68 percent, 23.69 percent in O… https://t.co/xnDGFDxad5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChenGonSol @NightlyPolitics Populist thought brought the world America and that turned out to be a boon for the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a reason I’m making this face...ask me if I see you at ComicsPRO this week . . . . #comicspro #comics… https://t.co/sCZVjz4uJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on my way to Albany for the @NYSPHSAA wrestling championships!   Get set for the action with my #lohudwrestling… https://t.co/0FgyBpI8sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dawgtoy_ @SuperNovs1 Different mentality than your franchise I respect that]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t fuck wit anybody who takes social media for real life. I just can’t . I just be on the internet to see diff… https://t.co/OuJ33TyLIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbcecilia @Jbuehler777 @ninopagliccia @cafreeland @jguaido Only CUPE eh lol https://t.co/THzBex44fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Epcot - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/F6xqg97q4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3YAlRkUIF2 Will forever think of this iconic vine when I hear 21 savage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the Ports of Entry need better technology to remotely detect cargoes that contain illegal drigs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dog: *jumps up  on hind legs for hugs cuddles* Owner: “Down! Don’t do that!” Me: “Come here you big heckin’ floof!… https://t.co/mGp5J6B1kC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly Reminder .... 😁  Far $FAT $Fat.c and Parcel $PKG $Pkg.ca are the two biggest piece of shit pump jobs!… https://t.co/8Z77znw91A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE Story lines a little wonky. I wish it was You vs Ronda 1 on 1 but Ms Flair getting added will be ano… https://t.co/RkwnWUY36s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pflax1 We have our share of those on this coast, too. Let me introduce you to Father Santora. https://t.co/RfgTrqIxs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just minutes away from seeing if @BourdaisOnTrack can make the impossible possible 3 straight years @GPSTPETE @IndyCar Go get em Champ!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bill is a direct result of a 1998 audit as well as a more recent review by the Finance Cabinet. Both reports fo… https://t.co/JeEwof3SPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[👌 greatest 👌 @saferprint @sherrig108 @VipEurope5 @blue_angel0126 @SamosumSihammm @CarlonetCarlo @ThalaBeratung… https://t.co/7Ot9J3pmiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your DJ on @933WMMR till 5:30a. Have your shot at lift tickets and @Badflower badass new album “Ok, I’m sick” for f… https://t.co/5oGvAjQ35v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nildarosario @YolandaT47 @lgnunezT47 @RullanT47 @allanvT47 @PablogtzT47 @AlfredoT47 @TairyT47 @analedoT47 Buenos d… https://t.co/RgPKGg9FXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W2E4DAVID Again i heard that too but I’m not jacking it Drizzy been the same since day 1 so no sir I’m not convinced]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii they already have...that's the fucked up part of the all?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Sammie dean ! I miss you lots @sammikeane https://t.co/RzhsRhkTAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaidersHLP @DNC It sounds pretty close. I heard wrong and.thought it was done but they are real close and by Frida… https://t.co/FTrJ5qeDUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOOO IM GONA MISS THE JERSEY RETIREMENT!!!!! My boss scheduled me till 11 on saturday when the game starts at 10😭😭😭… https://t.co/0CNjEsywyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riddle me this...  How can you reason with environmental activists who demand no-animal-hide automobile interiors,… https://t.co/e4lagsQGeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarJonasson @IlhanMN @omarsuleiman504 My goodness you have a lot of anger.  You just can’t accept that a fellow li… https://t.co/qKsiRH467D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitoBenach @PanakinCaboose @AlexMSolana @MarcHochman @OfficialCrowder @560Friedo @ZachKrantz @JoeRoseShow Without… https://t.co/GLoKAogepu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching #SoTightSheSqueaks #ExcitedEmmy #Poker is fun because when you she brags about her hand you can always buy… https://t.co/p1fXkQWzmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@17Kandles @exiled2KS @SoCalMusicGal The Zep list will either endure Trunk to me or make me despise him even more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4PM fcst sounding for OMA from the NAM. CAPE is showing, but it’s so high up! 👎🏻 Also, interesting to see the shall… https://t.co/jSGNiYpf8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jude_Thaddaeus Obviously, the plastic-panel Hal Riney mentality is why Saturn was ever relevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownFish83 @nowthisnews @AOC Isn’t that he USA population for blacks living in the USA at 14%.  So if your saying… https://t.co/fMRo3dmm70]]></document><document><![CDATA[can't say I ever thought THIS was going to be how my PS4 was used https://t.co/1PVYXkUPzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking #basketball. “What started as a #podcast between three college friends 13 years ago, recorded in the mornin… https://t.co/RW6W7YlWoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No notice of attempted delivery from #ups even though I was here ALL DAY! Also no 24/7 customer service this day and age? Unbelievable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats #SpikeLee .... Glad the Academy finally decided to #DoTheRightThing  and give you long overdue hardware an… https://t.co/91nuNvqtF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a little fun. #Lamb #Rare #Amazing @ Sun Valley Resort https://t.co/tfLp00HjvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG S/O to @KD_king23 for the taxi service today!! It pays to have great friends that are always there when you call ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Securing = segueing with iOS autocorrect. Basically he says “No that was...”, the one who was in xxx , no that was… https://t.co/nZrPvl1L1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[On that note..... Good Morning. @ New York, New York https://t.co/7XKU9C2WSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allooshy2 @chardonnaymami Still waiting for the receipts https://t.co/tAGLM5MP71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TXRaveChasers @KayzoMusic @C3Concerts @LiveNation @UsaEDMFamily @texasedmfam @Nocturnal_Waves @HoustonEDMfam… https://t.co/VYRDvnLjN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In Arizona, poor, primarily white school districts get about $19,000 per student — while high-poverty, nonwhite di… https://t.co/Fs1ahjVAML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usajuliette---On YouTube, "Just Like Romeo &amp; Juliet," by The Reflections....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proposal for payroll withholding sets off debate on student loan system https://t.co/zPdSn7x3RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even hiding the fact that there tanking, bet that’s why Walton’s not fired yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrystalCoRandy @MicrotsE Some might call ethanol made from sugarcane rum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day with nothing to do tomorrow...can’t remember the last time that happened! Probably gonna stay in bed, read, and watch tv/movies! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmiRenee Well I’m saying fuck your menu.  Life is a dick. But you got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @mllesrta on being named Jacket Nation’s Teacher of the Week!  Ms. Schmitz is an amazing French… https://t.co/wuGJyWJcvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama I agree with you sir. People like @AndrewPollackFL and @KyleKashuv have been exemplary in the way they… https://t.co/CuOm2DdSMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Di Filippo reviews &lt;i&gt;The Clingerman Files&lt;/i&gt; by Mildred Clingerman https://t.co/XGYNCHBXps via @locusmag]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to raise the volume on my Bluetooth speaker over half just to drown out the sound of my puss licking her pus… https://t.co/gEILyAAj1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cardoso_deli @Gorpo1973 @DeSouzaBraga1 @DickVigarista76 @ElaineG16 @lemos_dr @AnaRoch335 @Izidoro09414672… https://t.co/mIp9E6w3G3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artist Project opening night party starts in a few. Show is open to public tomorrow through Sunday! Come see me at… https://t.co/NFbUmdvQPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to participate in this @TIMESUPHC initiative from @janevandis, @choo_ek @drjessigold and many others!   It… https://t.co/c9G63EGMlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días Papás y Mamás Feliz Sábado 💪💯 ya saben 6 tarjetas de regalo de subway de $30,oo c/u voy a regalar entre… https://t.co/lWJ2dRcEEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritAirlines why can you not get me to JAX ? Not acceptable. Who is going to reimburse me for my resort?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s growth and opportunities all around us at Diamond Resorts!!  Contact me for information on marketing leader… https://t.co/5XUuw4VZu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rand Paul told reporters Monday that based on conversations with colleagues, there are “at least 10” GOP senators p… https://t.co/HW0ObngNvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildbillphoto @CSRussell69 @tassiekeith @brucetroxell https://t.co/ZpQXaGZtF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpkrier Why would Pagan's want to celebrate a man who expelled their people from Ireland and established Christian… https://t.co/8MpZNrhiD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliceswiftjam @hayesdaneaurora Put my tongue , then my little guy in as far as he will. https://t.co/YnJXpJlsDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennyDamazin @MichaelRapaport Drake won cause he out rapped his ass and he made sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Ever hear of RICO?  That's how it works. Cohen comes off as credible. Unfortunately, you and you GO… https://t.co/ysHGYOQuWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djarrat @EMjennielle @sarahewhitley Exactly! Shared some data from Eduventures on a webinar with @Strive4C on this… https://t.co/tdMOKZ8EYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_friend @MrOBrien314 @HebronAcDec Clearly Art: statues Music: the songs inside my head (the genre is huge)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck yes! - Drinking a Thor Is My Co-Pilot by @drekkerbrewing @ The Fire House  — https://t.co/NqiLqBKSBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RantingGAPeach @chucktownregs Crystal Coast in NC is where it’s at! Good times and clear water.  Plus if your a hi… https://t.co/srTbvk6iKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing to shoot up every enemy in the path of Terry Crews! @ The Goofball House https://t.co/DgsLxKLegm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The continuing resolution contains $2 billion for Planned Parenthood, more than it spends on border security (as it… https://t.co/GdJJ2wukBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to beat FSU or win one in Charlotte.  Dangerous territory for NCAA hopes and hopefully keatts takes this into… https://t.co/W1qTWqv3Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eagles improve to 4-0 after a solid performance at The Water yesterday. Rodriguez got the win on the mound. Simmons… https://t.co/8cTva1l61c]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst thing WWE does (other than give money to Donald Trump (maybe not as an org but definitely the dude at the… https://t.co/qZabpfokfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonGChang All you have to do is read anything Gordon Chang has ever written about Asia in the past 20 years to… https://t.co/Dzvi5Wcqcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenKts11 I personally believe that some (most?) never had any to begin with and current politically sanctioned n… https://t.co/5u1Wx6qhLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha, ha! For dessert, they’re selling nukes to Saudi Arabia. Because peace in the Middle East. #OurNationalNightmare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tak to z miloscia braterska bywa...Szantazowany od blisko 40 lat przez Sily Wyzsze,za swoje preferencje i orientacj… https://t.co/REmvmzRexT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsBBell Good morning Mrs. Bell. Happy Sunday. https://t.co/uK19PIQfpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s already a hole in the wall, you KNOW that door is swinging full FORCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraGomezNews @victoraraiza @jesus_acevedojr @JorgeClara @jsjuarezjr @jzamoranotv @frankspizzaTX @ChickfilA ¿Cómo… https://t.co/OaGPdGQmYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaBRosenthal @ACSCAN_NY @ParentsvsVape @theyouthdecide @TobaccoFreeKids @AHANewYorkCity @LungNE @RoswellPark… https://t.co/LSIuG73Rmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FDPascual Whoever can do the job right and no corruption, it should be alright. It's a lot better than not doing something about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very bad that Republican foreign policy these days amounts to showering praise on the North Korean dictator and sha… https://t.co/5hShjXJwBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful and inspiring! #betterbrothersla @ Taglyan Cultural Complex https://t.co/bBv5XML8As]]></document><document><![CDATA[•••••GIVEAWAY ALERT 🚨🚨🚨•••••  Do you guys like great Mac N Cheese? Check out the pics for these great cheesy bites!… https://t.co/8rNNMW9Qd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to play dress up this weekend at @Southpark alloh #girlsknightin #girlscoutlockin #KingJeremiah 👑 #latergram… https://t.co/GVsdJEsTcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSteveCox I’ve deleted thousands of comments man. Or do you think I’ve only made 100 comments via Twitter? I do… https://t.co/aGfq7SXLiT]]></document></documents></author>