<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Well I’m back at work but I was gone so long I have to have my security stuff reset]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day of protest all backed by George Soros organizations. Is this really who we want to have running this country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t ever say I fucked up , we was good till you switched up . now you actin like I folded 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[These HBCU students must’ve never stepped foot on a PWI. Y’all can be yourselves and don’t have to worry about bein… https://t.co/pTcrSHDMsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attendees participating in a workshop #Catalyst #SalesforceSaturday https://t.co/m08WG8fm6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[this song is underrated! just wanted my 26 followers to know! https://t.co/85scaNB5p3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @DavidHarris707 @RosaDeliadelos1 @ArleneKowalczyk @SeptemberJulie @PrayHard972 @carmelitequotes… https://t.co/0aX4FjF4X2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedwarvesband @VadgeMoore #maximumrocknroll #gilmastberkeley #thedwarves1989 https://t.co/Lybj1bVx4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyABC13 I hate when that happens 🙈 “back to you” is my best friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We remember!  We thank you for your service to make the world a better place, and for never giving up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonG40210896 @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @JeannaMarie32 @jeanine_new @Mary60053440… https://t.co/7zYoxQsKpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTW633 @trixibe @mimimjfan @SouthernGemGal @brucepknight Happy Valentine Day to you, my friend.❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyhoff Thank you for sharing your expertise. I definitely came away with valuable info. 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! What a day!! Ending with @ABFF Thank you for a full day!   #entrepreneur  #entrepreneurlife  #abff… https://t.co/Sq2vtpe3cW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good pointers...and yes, I'm guilty of several of these! #socialmediatips #SocialMediaManagement  https://t.co/UKsIID02rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nordau1986 @artistmerryjest @dona_c_bailey Me too! plus the time I spent in the arcade at the student center at Rutgers U...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsVascik @BOEwarriors Ugh, thank you! I learned from some of the best 😉❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daaammmiiiit... sometimes the Universe plays the music that loves to break your heart! Foh with that sexy beat and… https://t.co/xRuWmBnjJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated He’s like 423lbs @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/DKQamdMIL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Uber for getting me home safe. It was a good night.  I'm glad Alexis got to start her b-day month off right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bumblesnot @SoCalBulldog @RescueSocal Hope they are home soon. 🙏 I put it on Facebook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud to call @RoySpeckhardt my partner for life #HonorThemAll #SCOTUS https://t.co/KSYibGp0v2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started off second round with a 9-0 win over Silsbee! #1e9endary Reagan ⚽️⚽️⚽️ Kambrie ⚽️⚽️ Isabel ⚽️⚽️⚽️ Ocean ⚽️… https://t.co/GY1Pkg0Nce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s called satire, dipshit. Get a thicker skin, President Snowflake....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately I have been craving an adventure to a few new places in  #Europe! Who wants to go??? 🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[March comes and you think, “finally we’re near spring” ...and then you’re reminded of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Follow_mee18 @Sissy_Trainers Mmmmmmm sooo sexy I'd love to rub your breast...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched what I first thought was a beaver hunt and eat fish for a few minutes before I realized it’s likely a mus… https://t.co/uVR4Gi7erb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah sure is nice... all that WATER and no reservoirs. But we have a bunch of sticks and a no show bullet train… https://t.co/zwWQ97Luo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy your snow day! We most certainly will! @MsClingenpeel @MrAbouraad @MsKohlmiller #Hazardneedstwitter https://t.co/rAZ7hq2mwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for @StickWithHicks and KC (potentially wehrwegrow) for first steps building the bridge between… https://t.co/0mBdMiKK0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me hizo falta el “anfitrión” en la entrega de los premios #Oscar !!! Más tiempo para las celebraciones, los buen… https://t.co/6h1fp41kP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered @UberEats and it pined me in Denver 🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️ but I still have to pay for it .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to personal reasons I'm no longer interested in this case. It's too much going on. Gtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s midnight and i’m watching car crash compilation videos on facebook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd @WisenbergSol Keep publish that BS about #Mueller report about to drop for the sixth time in a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about high school when I had Mardi Gras off... truly what God willed... so far we have strayed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my people! #communitypolicing #Lovemyjob #FallsChurchCity #FallsChurchPD #LoveisLove #Police #femalepolice 💙 @… https://t.co/QYyCikowPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always viewed art that took effort to understand was better art. I'm like that with people as well. I like the ex… https://t.co/bWlBdOMJFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shoutout to @iflowacoustic for letting me share the stage with him for his song ANCHOR at the conference this w… https://t.co/ulbeDVpfyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass wasted $80 in 2 days and can’t remember or have a clue to where it went other than some shit I probably did… https://t.co/D0gENMgG6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I used. I felt it working right away. I've been told how good it is, but I had to try it for myself. W… https://t.co/GyskZJj8BT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BigArtDay Today‼️ Let’s Celebrate an awesome turnout for our P.E.A.M #Rodeo Roundup‼️(K/1-Dance,2/3-Song,4/5-Art)… https://t.co/HUkqBItz34]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are my upstairs neighbors absolute meatheads that only come alive past midnight and insist on banging on the fl… https://t.co/9rO17iyR9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at these fools. Eager to get on a plane just so @united can hold us captive for another 4 hours https://t.co/6V2EUQTu7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a Cuban-American raised way half of her life in this beautiful country, thank you President @realDonaldTrump for… https://t.co/JNBOMVnHVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#outandabout #beautytime #venezuela🇻🇪 #livelifetothefullest❤️❤️❤️ #🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈 @ Envy Nails https://t.co/Le7Enwh4cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. Im drunk. Woooo. 😂 or was I always. I shall stop before I regret this tomorow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fatheranddaughter #mynephew #eddiemendoza and #myniece #nicolettemendoza sharing their love of music with some of… https://t.co/GRbbjCK0hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Brown Eisenhower Speeches! #abilene5starschools @ Abilene High School (Kansas) https://t.co/kwGwV57RNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicabarragan_ Soy Virgo y he tenido mejor experiencia sexual con Aries]]></document><document><![CDATA[laughter coming your way. Ob how I would love to write this on some walls #funniness #lol #grin #funny https://t.co/Os9NIsQLWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU GUYS!! I’m already crying at 5AM!! This race is my first half away from home—SHOUTOUT to my AMAZING Buffalo fri… https://t.co/b9CLViOdNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckennapctty @theacesofficial @mckennapetty @cristalramirezn @Alisa_M_Ramirez @kt_hendy this is so cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadityyyB 🗣listen...it’s like the music reminds you to be loving and generous 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[FaceTime calls from @opaigeb have the power to make any good day a great one 🤩💘 ilysm]]></document><document><![CDATA[we got several nationals gifts tonight but the socks are my FAVORITE. i’ve wanted some for so long yayyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn really put herself in the position to be caught. How you be involved in that big of a scandal when you’re ba… https://t.co/G5rvnnLUgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo I assume you saw Bohemian Rhapsody? For the record I thought it was excellent and I ugly cried several times!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa. Well, of course Trump would, but still - to see this laid out, wow. We are below a banana republic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need wwe shirts that say one last mother f'n time.  Make this happen @wwe hehe 😁😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨 IT'S COUNTDOWN TIME! 6 1/2 HRS TO GO!!! 🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨🚨 Mark The Date! First time shared Publicly Befor… https://t.co/rCj8U5OQHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, this checks out. If I were the opening DJ for Robyn, I’d also play a remix of Kate Bush’s RUNNING UP THAT HILL to start the night too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro That is the strongest point I have heard so far. They will try justifying it by arguing "emotional" health. Pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[So San Antonio decides to move exits around and now I’m stuck in traffic for idk how long. 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bill gives towns the option to use RCV in their local elections. In RCV, voters rank the candidates. If their 1s… https://t.co/9pvEjtMsZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The election is tomorrow! Go out and vote for Jasmine Louras! Polls are open from 9:30 AM to 9:30 PM! 🗳✅ #Outremont https://t.co/m8EtLkRjlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I enter but it comes out as a cough and I never know how to feel after it happens. But usually it’s just confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fxstshd1995 @earmitesyummy Putting oxygen in your blood stream . They think that will be good for your headaches?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop the U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement: No North American Union https://t.co/nfGcTLBNAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[deadass this is exactly what my floor looked like in teter before we moved out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them keys for that Cadillac cost $700.... man I’m outta here. Truly some negroid shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I wanna do is find new an innovative ways to Launder my drug dealing Mans money. Full time.  Morning Saints. https://t.co/3J7IFFuu6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make this the week you change your life! #MondayMotivation https://t.co/DUh3ut5zyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I was peeling my banana over the trash can and then I dropped it in the trash can.” - martina]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish @KravMagaCDK would stop ghosting me since verbally promising a refund.]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember when I was so emo &amp; desperate to meet jb that I started making manips of us together yea that’s about to be me with shawn .]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. | Kermit The Frog's Top 10 "But That's None Of My Business" Posts #laughter #chuckle #grin #humorous https://t.co/i2C7gv0MoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejandra92426 Dude one time this guy flicked me off with so much emotion. He was mad mad. Called me a dumb bitch… https://t.co/td0WA5DjZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Would like clarification as to why ALL SW flights are on hold out of Jacksonville International Airport?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cómo no acordarme de Peña Nieto diciendo “ya sé que no aplauden”. Bueno, este es el “ya sé que no aplauden” del pri… https://t.co/0FtqY5dEWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well about a really good girl my great granddaughter was born. About one week ago.she had a little issue but she is… https://t.co/stEovroPLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debes tener claro que el perdón no es acto que sucede de un día para otro... En realidad, es un proceso que lleva s… https://t.co/vsvlJGjXCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents went to Katz 21 for dinner and didn’t even invite me. How rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frappes are back! I may have a problem. 🤗😍🤦‍♀️🤷‍♀️ #BKcafe #NomNomNom @ Burger King https://t.co/w8VQ9XKAKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Holy cow. Let's say a white guy did what JS did during the Obama administration......can someone get this bozo off the air?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion: I feel like im the only one not pressed about this online voting shenanigans.  No way was it sus… https://t.co/nL0pRQMTO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Monday 3/4 at 10am @frankrossano will be spinning another track from @blueashes4 . Don't miss it! On Rossano… https://t.co/2cAgEBqLdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldixon1394 makes me cringe!! also videos of chiropractor adjustments!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then @realDonaldTrump says he was misinterpreted. He cares not that #MBS murdered a #WaPo journalist. He takes… https://t.co/OzfzP7miZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are rigid, self-righteous, lacking compassion and judgmental.  They become more like the Pharisees and the ric… https://t.co/ShDaxiMHP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo I don’t have my daughter all day who is coming over with champagne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Approaching my year 2 in LA anniversary with gratitude and a headache. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/9EkRfR0C9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do both of my besties look cute today and I’m here looking like a troll]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DID I JUST WATCH THE PROCESS OF A CSECTION.......... why why why.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. I passed my #LeanSixSigmaBlackBelt class... time for certification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“not to sound awkward, but you smell really good. it will drive all the boys to the yard.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everything is bananas but I am glad we’re on this circus ride together, twitter frens. #DogsofTwittter… https://t.co/3uKPiryk02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15JudicialCASA @AriMelber Your are amazing ❤️❤️ I know many wonderful lawyers that’s why I despise the bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ComeAsYouAre this National Eating Disorders Awareness Week (#NEDAwareness). We’re raising awareness, busting myths… https://t.co/LMIaUe7pG8]]></document></documents></author>