<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BHradsky Even moreso, when the AG only provides a summary of his conclusions and puts the full report in a deep fr… https://t.co/J7pa9DnjE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out https://t.co/swo48EonOF @XwearActiveWear https://t.co/7ndwfFjMxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaxRecords @UMichLacrosse @KMHSLax @KMHSathletics @_KMHSNEWS I have the chance to watch this kid every day.  Not o… https://t.co/9LzN5Y6PuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Pelosi.  You are a true status setter.  Enjoy the wine tasting tonight.  You deserve it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irritate me and I’ll fucking melt your brain on how much I’ll piss you off 😂💀😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es indiscutible que nuestro valiente y honesto presidente con su información matutina diaria impone la agenda a tod… https://t.co/HJH5xThsts]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how badly I need sunglasses, I refuse to buy them from anywhere referred to as a "hut." That's reserved for pizza and Jabba.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice that Blue Diamond coats these in crack! Impossible to eat just a couple. #bluediamondalmonds #wasabisoy @… https://t.co/tTPjkdT1eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're getting set for two full days of production w/ client @MandT_Bank in Baltimore. We love working w/ clients wh… https://t.co/spRKlo4mMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If we have the courage and tenacity of our forebears, who stood firmly like a rock against the lash of slavery, we… https://t.co/Hp0KCgNgMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to do a movie called Magical Mexican where an immigrant couple from two different Latin American countrie… https://t.co/1UCzSGwJoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump is that the same as the original demo party that became the blueprint for the nazi party in Germany?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachLaVine showing the Celtics some Chicago 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥 🚨 🚒 @chicagobulls #BullsNation #SeeRed #GoBulls]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 10 pick results last 10 years from NFL Draft:  1). 2018 Draft: QB Josh Rosen. 2). 2017 Draft: QB Patrick Mahome… https://t.co/bzDvLmbRYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frock yes - Drinking a Friar Bacon Smoked Bock by @listermann @ Christian Moerlein Malt House Taproom  — https://t.co/6TXvplNmeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope come you and @loudibella never had one of those celebrity boxing matches?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewcooper86 @sulliman_zamani @JacobB_TP @kblyndon @EDCManager @Bristol_TP_ATT Go Bristol]]></document><document><![CDATA[These places have phenomenal colleges and universities. Each that lead charge in specific industries. This type of… https://t.co/eStlwRNRiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, Ness City [Ness Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 6.00 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road sign: falling rocks  @YokEdDevoti: falling rocks? I always thought it kinda sucked]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never forgive Pete Davidson for making this guy randomly show up in my timeline so often]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonrakerkih @andrewjskatz @mikedav57 @janfromdevon @margarethodge @JoRichardsKent @thetimes and how does this hav… https://t.co/ycH7amEOmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFBehavior @Tcorreia @DalmatProd @IAFC_VCOS @IAFC_SHS @DanKerrigan911 @NJNFFF @BobbyHalton @OnSceneTraining GET CHECKED!! #maydaymonday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Pence:  God frowns on those who ignore the truth. Probably remembers it when you arrive in purgatory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are all the @penguins haters at? Meaning our fan base! #LetsGoPens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi la encuesta de @BankofAmerica entre inversionistas https://t.co/fd3qYknmHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s passed 3:00AM and I’m having a wine night, laughing my ass off with my husband while watching our baby sleep. Life is cool. #momlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[This short story by [redacted] editor of [redacted] (speculative fiction about real estate speculation!) which I li… https://t.co/brLES0gYsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Shift Sup… https://t.co/v92lIsRF2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Movie with #Cheech in the middle of the day! Sure... why not! Hopefully I won’t fall asleep. Back to the book rep… https://t.co/rTTSQlfQgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cesare9950 @andrewr12303947 @MSU_Basketball “Like always.” What a fucking stupid thing to say. Izzo has been to mo… https://t.co/V3EI3YMDya]]></document><document><![CDATA[This teen who self-vaccinated just ripped his mom’s anti-vaxxer beliefs in front of Congress  https://t.co/htl69bSNE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our schools SRO winked at me today.... do you guys think he’ll ask me to prom? :O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCBaseballGA the ☀️, just in time for first pitch(es) tomorrow night! ⚾️ https://t.co/OU8CmC2JGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one of my favorite breakfast spots. Super cute waitress is Israeli Russian. We talk. A lot.   Turns out her fian… https://t.co/5BGErg7W9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NolanRosenkrans @bernielunzer @news_guild @apantazi Likewise syb - can we say syb or cousin? Is cousin considered… https://t.co/TR8DDWIWUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stn022 Fox has come out and said they were not planning on writing him off the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @saikatc @AOC After you had @AOC send that campaign email fundraising based on words attributed to u… https://t.co/FgQWAocgjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timwells51 @cormac114 @thefr0g @maybrick350 @IlhanMN “Done in Convention by the Unanimous Consent of the States pr… https://t.co/zbhQInBy79]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really be tweeting straight thoughts without any form of spell or word checking ☠️☠️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of my girl and her Carter Middle team mates. 1st place 4 by 200 relay. @CMS_principal_ https://t.co/7yxjvnd2na]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Only in Soviet Union? Only in Nazi Germany? Only in Saudi Arabia, America’s bed-partner? Or perhaps… https://t.co/rqIdIYJPON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gideonro @AlexSteffen It would be genuinely interesting to know the top 100 producers of emissions, I already know… https://t.co/rfmT6kbOCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've got to be one that, wherever you’re like a flower, you've got to blossom where you're planted. You cannot el… https://t.co/pLucCrK5jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better Choices for New Jersey Coalition Statement on NYC HQ2 - https://t.co/XPxaE7RdaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to state for the record that I do not like to get into politics. I prefer to let my actions speak loude… https://t.co/Fs2CILof2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NextDoor Carrollton is absolutely peak New Orleans today. @bestofnextdoor https://t.co/ZfByufVUi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MWE DAY 23: Jackie Shane, ‘Any Other Way’ (2017)  This compilation, approved by the late soul dynamo/trans pioneer… https://t.co/NmAY6vYnwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored and humbled to be recognized for 13 years of dedicated service to the City of Livermore during my last Plan… https://t.co/hLsnxAVOLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[...  of the most hard pressed and deserving Venezuelans who are wanting asylum, bring them to the USA, most probabl… https://t.co/hE77NSuBlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theotherstevec I know we only saw each other maybe a few times but it was a pleasure to talk to you for those few… https://t.co/XCf5oACErn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flappy Valentine’s (at @Hooters in Milford, CT) https://t.co/D8PYInYhtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Check out @RodStryker’s Tweet: https://t.co/GSZ2YygibR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 - I made pancakes this morning and luckily we still had enough eggs and milk. The #LogCabinSyrup is almost em… https://t.co/jmzUmQ3zgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDates and @perrinrogers I am ole school where the preacher consecrates themselves on Saturday night - and n… https://t.co/E5N9pyXzTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuosoAssist @GlenRidgeFleet @SPNlocal @KHetrific @GenePetrovLMC @JayBusselle @MeetEdgar @StonehamPress… https://t.co/iOIGRUaHST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Summer Strawberry by Cage Brewing @ Cage Brewing — https://t.co/1kSIEHdoZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever wrote for WWE in 2003 went out of their way to make @IAmJericho look like a complete ass agreeing to a dollar bet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq Well I may be 70 poor as a church mouse. But was blessed with a little common sense. That's something… https://t.co/ZAgNFRyLZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp Show us the lies the press got wrong. We’re long past people making unsubstantiated claims like yours. Pu… https://t.co/FCm0TMWzG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My absolutely last, hot off the carving knife, were hand delivered yesterday to be in time for #valentines - phew!… https://t.co/c0u4M6v0th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBonillo @hburch64 @Dethlefson1956 @IlhanMN Think they mean *Ihman 😂😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:44 2nd  Alexander 23  Valley 15  Let me tell you something: Andrew Shope is here, and he wants you to know it. Ho… https://t.co/XESrnwUZD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Estrella Jalisco by @GrupoModelo_MX at @candlewood — https://t.co/hjVyYYnHBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennisChannel @BNPPARIBASOPEN Ten different nationalities in @ATP_Tour Top Ten. Not unusual but worth noting how t… https://t.co/ALmioNw2ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treanor97 Thanks for driving me back to the house in Tahoe m8. I appreciated it more than you know. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle I wish my neighbor wise up and stop putting up Democratic sign every 4 yrs being a Jewish family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I think @billmaher's point was that in blue states you have a choice where in most red states you hav… https://t.co/rHALfzGe6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drjdanielguerra @castillejos_m @AdrianPedro Me tardé en encontrarlo jaja pero se tenía que enterar de esto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kirstenjoyweiss I am getting tired of that logic. @gun4hyr, Anthony Colandro says it best. 3 tiers in NJ.  1 polit… https://t.co/oUrrriAaeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GonzoSoriano @NPTrojan79 Phillies were average at best last year and made 329 M in revenue lmaooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DubbyGoodell I did 10 full time That was enough 8 only do it part time now, I'm about to stop.for good next promotion I get]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3 quarters, @STAsaintsgbball has opened up a 43-31 lead. @STAsaints #STAte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only one girl I really wanna fuck with but she likes niggas that got felonies 😕LMAOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good day from #broadwalk #hollywoodbeach #southflorida #saltlife #realtorlife #workingsunday #lovemyjob @ Hollywood… https://t.co/hoLL0A6bk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swazi4 I'm sure he had access to tweet but that's very clearly a scheduled tweet. The syntax is identical to every… https://t.co/eq5nwZUMd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjillian Howard played a clip of you being interviewed about Russ Limbaugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is fucking snowing in Arizona. this feels like a life is strange episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the end, True Detective was about how much we want life to be about successes and connections. And how it’s more… https://t.co/hyS0I1pbhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot compete with #zenqueen and her #yoga moves so I’ll just keep competing with myself. #balance #namaste… https://t.co/ozLxkq0NSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guyincognito Oddly it was that thing where you drink too much water. A pee for Wii scandal hidden in plain sight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewMI2018 #LGBexit #TakeBackPride Recognition of The True Gay Community in June by @realDonaldTrump is imperati… https://t.co/qofrvjknbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Nothing wrong with picking cotton, I picked cotton when I was a young kid to help my family. It help me to com… https://t.co/d25OTpyRpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peggynoonannyc the WSJ article today was your very best.  Should be taught in schools across America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinkieferwx if we can’t see it then it didn’t happen..::..... https://t.co/FEeXu74QEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thestevenwoods @PaulReindlSD @BenHigginsSD @Mighty1090 https://t.co/bOtuQCkG2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnRodr58143121 @JayashreeNara14 @LindseyGrahamSC You know that actually sounds like you retarded libshits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcsupt @tour18houston 2T125104. 6”, 1/8” diameter needle tine, 3/8” mount.   JRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobatl WHAT'S UP B.o.B I RAPPED ONSTAGE WITH U IN KALAMAZOO, MI DURING YOUR ELEMENTS TOUR ON JUNE 15,2017 AND IT W… https://t.co/1Au6HC26wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting notifications to “Persistent” in my todo/task management app has probably increased my follow through and c… https://t.co/7D3mgT4AN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Story of Always Believe coming soon! #AlwaysBelieve https://t.co/OebhIFtF3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KT_So_It_Goes @MollyJongFast Tires are useful.   Tire fire as mentioned or the shredded rubber blown out truck tir… https://t.co/uWYf8KPaOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLS_Sean I think people are more intrigued with the jersey than the analysis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[High grade custom built PC with 50” 4K HDR display, 2 year old watches CoComelon / Baby Shark on it. https://t.co/ehgezhis5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacksonville Shrimp Baseball  Enjoying the vehicle experience  @LoveBuiltLife @ Prime F. Osborn III Convention Cent… https://t.co/uJjPvmJkbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texasagg87 @finebaum @slmandel I agree the last couple of years have been dismal, but no one in recent years has done more with less. I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masterson333 @WOWT6News No, I am not representing Minnesota in Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhreshOutFenty @rihanna HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS VERY GOOD, BUT SHE LOSE TO THESE #MUSICIANS, WHICH… https://t.co/96tLRhyXd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @CoryBooker @BeefUSA You're right. Plenty of cow in this picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Come to Florida we have only gone backwards under Rick Scott and the republican controlled legislatu… https://t.co/aNuAxwkORo]]></document></documents></author>