<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It requires strength to stand up for yourself. It requires even greater strength to stand up for others ✊🏻   Pretty… https://t.co/WQSf6bXNEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejand71152542 @2018Ria @MarshaCollier @SusanGilbert @ShiCooks @cynthia_lardner @AKD09 @starseed009 @LOYALFAN1… https://t.co/IFsjvvKauL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This rumor has been kicking around Merrimack, where the IHC plays, for the last few weeks as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when @EmpireBrewTim and @EmpireDKat come up in conversation at an NYC bar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid Icarus Ghosts n' Goblins (C64) SimCity Adventure Zookeeper (Arcade)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregPugh18 @NumanJoseph Greg, silence yourself! You don’t have the same problems at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘The Irishman’ Editor Says Half The Movie Will Feature A Youthful, De-Aged Robert DeNiro &amp; Al Pacino… https://t.co/fgohSyQQDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/9fuG6cCBLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse me may I please have your attention   My stomach hurts  thank you -J.C.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillsdale 20, Walsh 19, End of 1st Quinche Carter has 6 points to lead the Cavaliers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebryantt I don't exchange info with these niggas They some opps, you can kill 'em, they ain't with us Ordered a… https://t.co/r1VFj16icW]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMOGEN: A Dark Romantic Thriller  https://t.co/E1V2L3Z3GH via @amazon This is a great read which I edited. If you l… https://t.co/Mwt2LohKuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalPistachioDay @getsnackin @WonderfulNuts https://t.co/yTrYKAmA3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Car Hop Creamsicle IPA by @atlbrewing at @RedBrickBrewing — https://t.co/YeYLj3saVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I have a waking vision sometimes of the future.  I was wrong and I was right.  I find love and have… https://t.co/HVOAcZiALc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @itsdanianderson @LuvKatiie @Sugarbutterluvv 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssharmaTX @ChrisSacia @MQSullivan Be honest, this was just a way for you to humblebrag your favorites with a few less smug points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPGroves It would be nice to see the other local teams that made it to the state tournament in your article]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aleutians were on the move today as our next storm rolled in. The sound was impressive. #birds #birding… https://t.co/00BTt62ziW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelin-Starred Entente Will Close in Lakeview on March 2!!!  https://t.co/vDsW7r7YCf   #ShoutoutSaturday… https://t.co/Z0PnOJyY3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @NikkythaBee Looney old Communist Bernie never left the USSR did he?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuryFanatic @BergeronKrejci @StonyMondayRiot Wait, they live in Jasper? People live in that paradise? Lucky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBGTBCK Noooooooo. Holy fuck I can’t even imagine the calorie count 😖💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyD1021 seller sitting on the offer I been buying 700 shares lots up to 4900 and offer does't move.  oh it just  did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRWTheCreator I disagree with that, not all reveals are the same. This just shows that they wear them but we knew… https://t.co/4mDCftvDOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is farcical. this is great for boys and guys who need to pee in the dark of night...... https://t.co/K9ky3H79PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JodyWHL This morning’s iPhone shot of the snowy mountains with low-lying clouds, taken from my deck in Anaheim Hil… https://t.co/Kch8QLdgZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to know why Risch is still on any committee and why he hasn't been arrested. @SenatorRisch the US Sena… https://t.co/928s4gKbQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[immediately ordering an ill-fitting “Prosecco Made Me Do It” sweatshirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencermorgank @AaronWagner_ @Cheddxh Regardless of which shots Simmons gets... HE GETS THEM. Nurkic is either tak… https://t.co/SCbxGoOM1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago 42 million in debt sounds like dude should of been gone long time ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo You know Mueller final report is not what you had hope for. Now putting all your hopes on SDNY😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first guitar hero. I remember my brother playing CTA when I was just a little kid. Had to learn guitar after tha… https://t.co/6QIgprMWKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @MeganInky @NestyXXX @VeroLealX @ZazieSKY @DeeWilliamsXXX @siennasinclaire @BlairSummersXXX @1daisymarie… https://t.co/EnfZEyLxSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[To get chick fil a, maybe but bojangles ain’t worth bringing out an AK-47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreseaVolt @theebeandip Bean @theebeandip I want them headphones 😂 and @PreseaVolt y’all look cute in this pic 😉 https://t.co/6t7RJ0q7AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameSack If I said anything to offend you guys I apologize. You guys are awesome 😎. I like your honesty in the videos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Tlaib is a coward for backtracking on her comments, and the issue has not been resolved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AreliPaz @alfonsocuaron @chiojardinezh @WRADIOMexico Gracias areli buenos dias desde laredo un abrazo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great exercise for balance and backswing extension. @ Olney Golf Park https://t.co/PHdckhYNyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yogagenie @mtaft48 I’m sure if the books were audited by truly non partisan auditors, The 8 years of Obama would s… https://t.co/iu88SLVral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clevetidwellusa all Californians are in the Jim Morrison cult of   " The West is the Best "  California is where t… https://t.co/BE0FRlZGUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_NoiseWaterMD It’s a bit of a fine line, I think. I, in general, think his critique of income disparity is valid… https://t.co/OpZAVH6Rc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sanfelippo thank you .... I am a teachers union President. We are in this together. Politics, media misuse, an… https://t.co/qCSu72e6eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCaden If you like crime docs, “The Staircase”. Can’t remember if Netflix or Prime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peticolas Fantastic. Will stop by @Peticolas this weekend for a couple #doctorsorders]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may be the best comment thread you see this week. 😂😂😂. Sarah, have a seat, girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A glimpse into a day in the life of an #NWHL goaltender. Thanks for being such a fun interview @kfitzy94! https://t.co/6SvoJJ6Yl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our NorthHenge. What a gift!...The sun still waiting for us after 5 o’clock! @GrayslakeNorth @GNHS_ART @GNHS_ArtClub https://t.co/ksNLEBPpPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGRFan716 Oh no! Don’t ask these kind of questions frank! This is too much to handle!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live with #Lightfoot and #Preckwinkle at #chimayoralforum in #Chicago on #NBC Channel 5 #WMAQ. https://t.co/jSsmLvCmgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamChaser_JP Lmao forex will change the way you look at money. I remember a long time ago waking up from a nap j… https://t.co/TFB6Lm50Wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller Hollywood is missing out they could make Weedman at Bernie's 2 guys who don't know what the hell is going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers - Paranoid https://t.co/YtUI2j0bGf via @YouTube  Why has nobody acknowledged that the Jonas Brothers… https://t.co/WzhyzvcN6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que golazo del Ajax. Merecido pase a 4tos de final.  Magistral partido en todo aspecto de los holandeses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come when I keep it real with you , you gotta start acting different like Ian catching the bad vibes you got now 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swardley @kelseyhightower OpenStack's bylaws specifically forbid alternative API implementations in order to avoid… https://t.co/W0p5aCPU24]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NFL is a cold business. Anyone faulting guys for chasing checks needs a reality check. Guarantee contracts like… https://t.co/CozC3K7gzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caissie @MusiComedyTweet I blocked a guy a few months ago for accusing me of a humble brag and as I was walking in… https://t.co/RQuszeankW]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/21/2019 -- Earthquakes strike multiple volcanoes on the US West Coast ... https://t.co/JTTJ46AyuU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The link below is the News coverage of our test drive in the next generation of transportation the Autonomous Shutt… https://t.co/cT97hQj8sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fact-Check: Former Immigration Judge Debunks 5 Claims in Democrats’ Border Wall Lawsuit https://t.co/RVwa3AC7kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story with the happy ending massage and selling access to the White House isn't  complete. With this criminal… https://t.co/WdqgjGwE88]]></document><document><![CDATA[| Excited and honored to announce that yesterday I was unanimously voted in by the Board of the Texas Chapter of Ba… https://t.co/pPsXQDJ5QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennettTomlin @arjunblj @lawmaster @_RJTodd @teo_leibowitz @i_woodford @johnbiggs @Dogetoshi @TheBlock__ I ❤️Bennett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, common sense. Too hard to do? Just email me and we will talk about the easy solutions for our cities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's taken a while, but I feel like I am finally hitting my stride at 35 and after a rocky road to get here. There is no overnight success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeEmison I’m dealing with their sales pitch on cost savings right now. :-/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldenburgSTL @AndrewArkills @BTstl Any merger plan would be opposed by large constituencies for not addressing the… https://t.co/HDBuVlSpDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selena la Primera Diva Latina que triunfó en Estados Unidos cantando en Español....❤️ https://t.co/zir2MqM7Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mianxxtdoor @NerdCage9 Real question why do y’all get triggered so easy 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Mayor @CamGuthrie for hosting the city mayors Friday.  Moving Ontario forward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiggsforAZ Why do you have such a problem showing empathy? The story is about two teens, including a girl who clai… https://t.co/3W6aL7P1BN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valp_edithh I’ll try to start like 2 days before and I can only maybe start the introduction and maybe 1 more para… https://t.co/gVlFlg8qZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Just like Trump, you’re a fucking liar. https://t.co/jatfDszPAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started the day with snow in the early hours of this morning #NewYork #TimesSquare https://t.co/8tZIgojir2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter how many retweets will it take to have an option to block all chain tweets. Cuz to be real with you... they annoying asf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day One of #BrooksInFLA was a success. Just finished an amazing dinner at @Columbia1905 on Sand Key! https://t.co/7J2kmETurF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Mechanic - https://t.co/vfZS8HsYyO #Automotive #Toledo, OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 7TH BIRTHDAY TO MY LIL PRINCESS. WOW YOU HAVE GROWN SO FAST. HAVE A GREAT DAY....LOVE DAD @ Hamilton, Ontario https://t.co/SXBEmldlaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProWrestlingMag Where’s the story on Zelina Vega reacting to Aleister Black WWE Raw Debut ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easywdw Carthay circle was also good but we had the slowest service known to mankind. We were there almost 2 hours… https://t.co/yhfx2OtIJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont like watching no nonsense shit , teach me sumn ; open my eyes , brainwash me positively]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightingWMyFam wow what a great movie! Definitely must see for everyone! Brought back so many memories #FightingWithMyFamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Omni56021917 @AP_Politics @AP That is good.  Did they frisk them all?  lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniaaaaB LMFAOOOO @nathaliexcruzz “Oh no they cleaned out all the bad ones” nonsense!   still the same bullshit i keep tellin you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about this makes this tweet sound like this is an ad for something taking place in a red-light district?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanthurmond So when you’re pointing out his teams lack of success it’s completely unrelated to his individual success?]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 February 2019  #Jesus  New  #PHOTOS   #Legendary #jeffdavisshow #Travel  #Twitter #Pinterest #Google #GooglePlus… https://t.co/kCh4hyr6z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealRogerLee @TheAtlantic @skornhaber I never subscribed. My mother did, but she was a deranged unrepentant “li… https://t.co/Iv6D990ZIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterhassett @markbonaKP82 Horrid giveaway in the neutral zone previous by 65 that don’t help either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocando @GenPenaloza @jguaido Casto ahora es que nos damos cuenta? Estaba clarito que el gobierno trata de desmovi… https://t.co/CpjiJgovDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunksOfHallmark @HallmarkHubby @HallmarkiesPod @anunderdogxo I was thinking that was from 4 yrs back.  What a sense of relief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahaha hahaha I agree with you. Please let me know if you figure it out. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Grabner on returning to the lineup: "It's been a while (41 games). I was sick of skating by myself out there."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @Birdseye1 @bourbonjon @ga18180 @intelligent50 @Muttonchap @Dimplewidget @swipecentral @MewllerRawr… https://t.co/eiFjrcnmxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveriggins @geteero I'm pretty pissed too. I held off for a long time with an Airport router, hoping Apple would… https://t.co/WU87MDYVns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all about tipping fairly, but I think it's an employer issue not a customer issue. Restaurant owners can pay a… https://t.co/X8xfyXdVE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@303FAN @Broncos @Chadkelly_6 If Hunt can get a second chance already, why not? I would have loved to see him play last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Parkeology I think I am missing the short hours badge from my run on 12/4/18. Can you please add that when you guy… https://t.co/iNzIOFARau]]></document></documents></author>