<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT And that has nothing to do with the quality of journalists there: the head rots first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sad I have to return my new converse 😩 they’re just so uncomfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr10 @Trump454545 @realDonaldTrump  I LOVE IT WHEN THE POTUS PUTS THIS FOOT UP THAT ASSHOLE ASS HIM IS A 🐴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharylAttkisson @KABBFOX29 @breannabarrs Yes I do.  Next time you come to San Antonio, the margaritas are on… https://t.co/U0GPUY4IHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmysdevs Agree. Honestly stoked they got a 3rd rounder for Lovejoy. I was expecting like a 5th rounder at best.… https://t.co/iepC7W8Gcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #WakeCounty on Garner Rd &amp; Creech Rd between New Rand Rd and Benson Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5Px0Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tinashe Hey I was wondering if you had any tracks you have produced to sell, I would love to make a song produced… https://t.co/3FPc8pd3cF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know this account had all of Lomachenko’s &amp; Davis’ finance record. Interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Vice Principals is relatively recent, but can Danny McBride go ahead and star in another HBO show  already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdoaleaP One person kept bringing up how they thought my previous profile pic made me look like a certain notorio… https://t.co/qb73rUXZI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateInVegas @PierreVLeBrun The Taylor Hall thing was a freak accident, haven’t see it since. The NHL has a lot big… https://t.co/1Z3eTqethK]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a player! Nordonia's Evan Wiehe had a outstanding year.  I watched so much tape on this kid. Whatever COLLEGE… https://t.co/pGGYHY1JMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccaballhaus @allahpundit What’s the point?   That’s not “collusion” with Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allan_cheapshot I guess Harley Race owes Batista 25,000 dollars. Adjusted for inflation, of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekapman your favorite place ever is mocking the Goodell! You love #NOLA right!! @WaddleandSilvy @CarmenDeFalco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread by @BethMooreLPM: "The whole shebang of social media culture is driven by drawing attention. Warning: whatev… https://t.co/rWyZJYev05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielaMarinov1 @FCKTWITR1 @ChucksWife1973 @MoatsShannon @DouglasDucote @IlhanMN @SpeakerPelosi @TeamPelosi… https://t.co/67IhEWitsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chest uploading. .abs still loading. .Lol posing while singing Dancing With A Stranger(LSS)haha daylight saving tim… https://t.co/dnZ0t1HI3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callie124C @Oil_Guns_Merica Especially that last episode of HIMYM.  Undermined everything before that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani You know and everyone knows Michael was telling the truth. The 1st time he lied to Congress it was at… https://t.co/c4Z7ihyknH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvman33wife @connorm60280099 @NinjettewhoopX2 https://t.co/yBid63Z7M0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeRavitch: Jackie Goldberg and the case for Ranked Choice Voting: Why hasn’t a system that amplifies the voice… https://t.co/atkP4P8BFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeThatStraw Okay then where did the big bang come from and how did it just come from nothing ? All of a sudden t… https://t.co/tiP7ypBoWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[erik spoelstra and quin snyder went through the same evil scientist program: https://t.co/o5PXjZDVYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ez4u2say_Janis #cdnpoli #onpoli #abpoli Hoodly surprising https://t.co/7RknWICLX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[**On Vacation till Friday, March 15th**  Will return all calls and emails when we get back. Thanks for your understanding 😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Beast Morphers was the most Power Rangers feeling episode of Power Rangers in years. I hope they can keep this up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Men manage money better than they manage themselves, that’s why prison and Wall Street are full of men”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we meet and talk about our angels that departed us ? @JheneAiko and talk about how precious life is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@argie2333 I felt better knowing that we were in the direction of tanking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @thelaurenicole ・・・ We are so excited about this line up for onefashioncruise @J_MrFantastic is one of our… https://t.co/AqKGGCY8CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC A VOTE FOR JOE BIDEN IS A VOTE FOR THE TOXIN BPA THAT KILLS WITH CAUSING CANCER THAT HIS BLACK BOSS FOR 8 YEARS PROMISED HE WOULD BAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP4Liberty @WalshFreedom I second this notion, Austin...Trump needs to hire Amash or Rand Paul as WH COS if he gets re-elected..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcjensen94 I don’t know. If you have Yoeli Childs, you’ve got to win your first round game in the WCC. They defini… https://t.co/GE6aO4QN70]]></document><document><![CDATA[So combine doesn't move the needle for me. Or make guys rise a lot. But it does make me take notice of guys I haven… https://t.co/dXrTHLiNYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrat Party Favorite Louis Farrakhan Spews More Anti-Gay Anti-Jewish Hatred: Anal Sex is Jewish Sex (VIDEO)… https://t.co/6NUAO9lMGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr A little late to the party with old and refuted propaganda! Orange jumpsuit boy is running scared!… https://t.co/WlaLD61BlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WshSportsDude Meh Shatty may have not worked out but we did get Copley back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a fantastic deal? Need the latest #demonfreska shirt?  If answered Yes, then check out @TeePublic ************… https://t.co/LW3grFG6VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Many do not think you are neutral. Good journalism. I think you are in the middle. Like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people follow unfollow isn’t that bad for your health? #thoughts #JustSaying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roizmangbn Редко с вами соглашаюсь, но тут поддерживаю на 100%. К слову, в США такой практики нет, все музеи платные.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corybarlog The Star Wars prequel trilogy, only this time it actually matches the tone and backstory laid out by th… https://t.co/ROhr6ij9zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GioWFAN @WFANmornings This kid definitely would not have been a fan of Johnny Damon leaving the Red Sox for the Yankees]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to never doing Valentine's dinner on the actual day @RIPLesley's@ https://t.co/9N3o8Rzhxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao what’s the pattern? Dumb people do dumb illegal shit and get arrested for it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSmallz92 @YohnDenise @ShirleyMArmenta @IGomezGuitar @Humanities201 @IlhanMN So far, the only proven instances of… https://t.co/7yZgy9TOiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWwaff You go east you’ll find some 300-400 year buildings, but not much more. They weren’t building w/ materials… https://t.co/7Joz09ebGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeltelling @ABCSharkTank @RealToyboxLabs Absolutely I do. Emily would have a great time trying it. Just got home… https://t.co/uEpV7VwtMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump You Libs have to admit that ISIS has  been pretty silent since DJT is PO… https://t.co/47XnmxGdAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins Oh, here we go again pretending to be a moderate until you actually have to vote and then veering s… https://t.co/qlWv253AYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSMBoysHockey I think Emma ran this almost all the time but as an alum and fan I want to thank her and whomever el… https://t.co/X5AoIvzsgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWildeGlobal @JustinLevineHBS And when I say "win" the lottery...I mean get one of the top three picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delighted to attend last night’s 35th Anniversary Celebration of Courage with MPP @lornecoe on the eve of #IWD. Thi… https://t.co/daX0M6bbEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is sticking to the roads in many places.   Oh and we have a Facebook live at 8am. https://t.co/FsYNOCseaf. https://t.co/CR8wzKGKTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @twilight19521 Big tough Macron policia  but cant go into a Muslim no go zone can you?? Shame on you, blind… https://t.co/W2V9LAyKwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawaiian Fajita. - man that was good. Green salsa was hot but great https://t.co/g7emdeA52A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertoVieiraP Lamentablemente, eso es los Peruanos, irracionales, envidiosos, Vengativos, crueles.Estamos una vez… https://t.co/SuXZpKfWfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lecciones de democracia y derechos humanos de EE.UU. https://t.co/NgOldRd9sE vía @YouTubelo dicho por un americano… https://t.co/u1JOOQSr4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaladandDarmok @WilliamShatner @EricMcNaughton1 Never been a fan. But Shatner ragged on him a little so it was worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajschreiver5 Phenomenal tweet. Couldn’t agree with you more. #win #besmart]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the Best DIY Garage Floor Coating Kits are not Epoxy | All Garage Floors https://t.co/X3054v8voq @StoreVibess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clapifyoulikeme Thanks Abby! I look forward to reading you for the ensuing one thousand years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde muy lejos rojo de mi vida 😭 Y cada día te amo masss ❤️❤️❤️  Esta noche cueste lo que cueste esta noche tenemo… https://t.co/r5Nm8IEhEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curry currying favor. Seven years is a lonnnnnng time on the beach, Ann Curry.  https://t.co/A3WGVvKSaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocuresident God help the man who tries White Palace. I played the game all the way through at once, was pretty so… https://t.co/3WgQa7MKNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Which comes first. Waters impeachment or Trumps .  Who has been in office longer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a visiting fan from Mayfield,the best part of the night. Much respect for Brecksville b-ball players and congrat… https://t.co/RaP0CFcDJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__RHJR your boys shot over Cook was only slightly less lucky.  He misses that shot 8 out of 10.  Smart decision on… https://t.co/k8Bz0TnKsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[AP World: hope you are enjoying the snow day. Reminder that Chap 19 is due tomorrow 3/5 and we will finish the WWI causes DBQ in class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bphogan pulled the trigger on your tmux 2 book. How do I get this signed? ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is working before 10am a form of TORTURE? One @UniofOxford scientist thinks so... 😴 #NationalNappingDay #12news… https://t.co/6l1B4zcD2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPOT THE ROLLEY ON MY WRIST #KINGACE 👑 #NEWJERSEYSKING 👑 #newmusic ▶️ #hiphop ☣ #rap ☣ #trapmusic ☣ #indiemusic… https://t.co/1O0MYs6qPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already sick of this ridiculous conversation...  If creating wealth was as simple as printing money, then wouldn’t… https://t.co/4zfMCtvP53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chakareyes63 @chris74_17 His retirement year he’s production was low. Why would he leave a 4 year broadcasting con… https://t.co/uojsoDCNR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Registered Nurse- ICU- Night shift - https://t.co/Wrh4oEm3Ps #hospitaljobs #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3: I have accepted a challenge from @Jeremy__Hill via @AnnaEpperly to post 7 books I love: just covers, no revi… https://t.co/K4vSvxvnCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn’t do than by the ones you did do. So th… https://t.co/1oZUDqkq1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraStemmer Amazing team this year Kara.  Enjoyed catching quite a few of their games. Future looks bright for Saline basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NomikiKonst @KyaeGunn Film incentives are still corporate welfare, even if the corporations' workforce is heavily… https://t.co/4bX9EmY3sZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[undoubtedly include Kaepernick’s past and future earning potential, both from  a team contract and potential endors… https://t.co/j1x0NfZXyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ajá ajá aquí ya con ustedes hermanos míos @RicardoEMontes @sotoleandro_ por la espectacular @990ESPNDeportes “Me En… https://t.co/kKnqC0Ol5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyyankeefanfore Stop.  He played third and other positions the last few years...on the cheap and he would be a spo… https://t.co/j49445w8MT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cherry Hill High School East in Cherry Hill, NJ https://t.co/gTOfboKQfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[As innovations in technology and ideas come forward, 2019 is sure to see its share of trends having an impact on… https://t.co/axhH0ZwIxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[which one? Fauxback or Oppo 🤔                                        Like for Fauxback / RT for Oppo  #RRExpress https://t.co/lPb2tdPDwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not Trump we have to worry about it's his boy Kushner! Guaranteed he's throwing us all under the bus for his own financial gain!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A helpful overview of how the #emergencydeclaration has been used...  Trump’s Emergency Declaration Is the First Si… https://t.co/RBG3FSQodu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broadcast crew for today! #ACCN #ACCFencing #ACC #Fencing #Boston #ChestnutHill #BC #BostonCollege #BCEagles @ Cont… https://t.co/c6Q0OlNFUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPEAKcipher #LiesHaveConsequences  4 Instance:  A Fake President  A Fake National Emergency  What’s Next?   A Fake… https://t.co/hrwWgejiXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1_focused_coach Nooooooooooo!  Nothing better than 4 corner offense to run out the last 3 minutes!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday and better to celebrate then two most important women in my life love y’all @FlosseeP… https://t.co/Z8z0GqbULt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoT_Truther I can't even imagine that the writers have come up with that. She will have an emotional scene where s… https://t.co/ignxakRJIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xxxneon @WillPresti @caroljsroth @ChristyRomano @sadieastanley @SusanSurfTone @DoveCameron Avengers and Peter Gunn… https://t.co/zfe2JtMvGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salamismash No I did, I have the best sheik recoveries in NorCal besides Zaid, but someone did think I was bm’ing… https://t.co/bpgaowdp1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly and that what this administration is attempting to allow to happen with Judge Neringa Venckiene if they all… https://t.co/i5UwgdeZSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si tienen todo militarizado desde hace años entonces son bien tontos e ineptos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarR49721088 @Imagine_V2 @KarmaBella82 @robbystarbuck @PrisonPlanet I agree, but your kid choosing to wear a Tr… https://t.co/Sm3vRnmEMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyitsmarcosv Your score on the main event was right on, IMO.  Job well done, sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's March people nothing is easy. Go Hoos! 🏀⚔️🔷🔶⚔️ ACC Regular Season Champs again. Now it's time for redemption.]]></document></documents></author>