<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am SORRY I am a UNEDUCATED REPUBLICAN It is AOC just verify I may have made a MISTAKE WHEN Referring to GOD AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broekisstime @victoriakonefal @Chrishell7 @MrRobertScott @billymflynn @KateMansi @greg_vaughan @linseygodfrey… https://t.co/1vF64fHkoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other than a very brief period in 2013, every manager I’ve had since early 2009 has been a woman. Guessing I’m an o… https://t.co/W3MevJfcF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Train......Wall? Don’t get what they have to do with one another?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowmuchfun2019 with #aquinnahriley #thisis3 #uwstoddler @ Upper West Side https://t.co/SqVCEWit3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dasBierSpiel @UrbanDecay He's got all the books, so I can totally read them!! AND THEY JUST DID IN THE LAST FEW DAYS!! &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Animohs @tamarakeithNPR Finished. Whew!  I thought I was going to need that second cup of coffee. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronc1011 @BlissTabitha Saitek Chakrabarti is her puppet master. Youtube brains behind AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Day Weekend at the falls @AliDidi09832555 #niagara #ourfavouritecity #familydaytradition https://t.co/eQVoqj7o7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursdays are a ... CLSQ ‍ ValentinesDay Chapel https://t.co/k1lF9ZDMUl https://t.co/e2WzcwXcfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[amazon has so many cute rose gold decorations i really can’t wait to start buying shit for my wedding😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear a broken heart are like broken ribs nobody can see it but it hurts to breathe💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCraftyCouture @MarzipanPiPlate @grendelsmumm I like sammich. Sandwiches deserve terms of affection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsKehoeGRES @jpgatesPE @GRESDragons @srburnham326 She’s one of the best!! 💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MichelleKhare is awesome. @MichelleKhare is a nominee in the #ShortyAwards. Vote for @MichelleKhare. Be like… https://t.co/qHLTbUBm8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't believe Mueller spent 18 months investigating this situation only to walk away with a suggestion of further… https://t.co/kZRDp4McgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[reminder that if your name is steady in other peoples mouths, they’re obsessed with you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerszi @SummerWinrotte @Catoutou99 @lieberrian @wakelet @Edulastic We shall talk.... soon. I have some ideas 💡💙🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppij @andrerucker51 @terry313401 @hey_butter @Grady10101 @SarahGould_SA @delgeo1 @MarilynHallett @RestlessNews… https://t.co/2rvzgGxrw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up now today’s #ValentineDay gift from me to you is a new #JuicyScoop I get into the #RHOBH #seekingsisterwives… https://t.co/mLpwzqPU5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[That just reminded me it’s time for another shipment. (Cons of living outside of the Carolina’s 😕) @kickerscorner_… https://t.co/PbSARNBPQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, very true! That’s why they complement each other! I was once with a Sagittarius for nearly 3 years and the onl… https://t.co/JbhI7G0AsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't enjoy burdening others with our issues. Yet, in our silence, we'd be comforted in knowing that not only do… https://t.co/8OwrD06iMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallasmavs @swish41 let the countdown begin! 9 home games and counting. #DirkNowitzki #dallasmavericks… https://t.co/ODRJDYiEJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickwtyler Good to see you this am. I will miss most of you! I will dvr. You are off to a good start. 🙂🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beaglefreedom this makes me so happy, brings tears to my eyes, thank you for giving these dogs the loving home they deserve!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping that More People start paying Attention to the Fact the Republican Party is Toxic!! The Whole Party is Corru… https://t.co/xsKzdFfaoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wonder what its like to have parents who actually care about you and your wellbeing 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouTheszXVX That’s a great point too... I like smashing pumpkins but not nearly $100 worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching the oscars on Hulu the day after cuz I am too poor for cable. So I know all the winners. But honestly… https://t.co/FYvEFFwuxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish me luck on this exam day. Hopefully I come out one license heavier lol. #examday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are 7 Tips for Positive Communication!✨💛 ⁣ ⁣ When we communicate with our loved ones in a positive way, we’re… https://t.co/tLvzuyatJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a3putter That’s my real face with hearts above it. My face has no filter. Are you saying my face is freaky?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh the weight off my shoulders now that I've finished my unit plan!! I have barely slept in a week from working on… https://t.co/8DgGtoQBKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pollsterdamus @FiveThirtyEight The biggest inconvenience for me is that it keeps me from having enough room to ope… https://t.co/586qlqX0ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deathgrippin420 R I G H T ??? Like it was my whole life how do people have no idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like an obstacle course to get here. Hope someone makes it worth my while. (at @DamascusBakery in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/qtk5xsnw48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule No one checked their exemptions at the beginning of the year. I knew this would happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coco crispies by the fire 🔥 ❤️🥣#sundaymorning @ Sweetwater Lake, Indiana https://t.co/T9llAt68iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I showed my mom a Burberry bag and she goes “why do you want a blueberry bag?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msrachelhollis will you support Corsicana and help us win! We made it to the top 6 out of 12,000 towns. The only t… https://t.co/g3tYoniSdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cbd dabs 🍃  Clear focused energy  Clarity  Inspired  Empathetic   #GoHigher my bongs rigs and pipes are from my fri… https://t.co/L4wOQmcexZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grimalkintalk @realDonaldTrump Girl, no typos. We know he didn’t post it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHOOT WHOOT 💃💃💃💃 #AllGreen day.  👍👍👍👍👍 #hearthealth #exercise #cardiacrehab #Fitbit #HeartMonth #GoRed… https://t.co/hZ50b897vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣hilarious .....they are everywhere and nowhere and those circus clowns that follow them around 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indoor swimming pool with gorgeous wood paneling and fully retractable doors that open to the outside and the guest… https://t.co/BaiJ01tHrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatdedesays I’m considering doing more plant based meals, however I need to find the time to prep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stone will do ANYTHING to get publicity. Best way to hurt him is to lock him up where he can’t get any publicity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris  @SenBooker @AOC  @SenSanders   Our country will never be a socialist nation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiffywild @JeffDye @JessimaePeluso @joshwolfcomedy A buffer or did you mean type butler?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had help again with my project lthis pair fit Zee! @ Olathe, Kansas https://t.co/f1WwVVJvdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m leaving school to Starbucks, and the barista and I are chatting but she points out my school laptop is hangi… https://t.co/FnbAsFgPvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vikkie Stepping toward the cockpit for your turn like... https://t.co/J11oNu3dPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will closed Instagram and immediately open it back up thinking I haven’t been on in a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKChilds @ShirleyIngmire @rgreenreid @OohShiny_Sarah @instagram @facebook @TpTdotcom @Pinterest We both know that answer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here I am watching season 9 of the #xfiles when I could’ve been watching weather-appropriate snowstorm horror movie… https://t.co/mTMpUMQEHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@________TMACK Because you stubborn and won’t soak them! We walked about 10/day x 5 days. Tamper your feet they not used to that💕💕💕👌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see #DOOLmoji app finally updated . They added 2 Valerie heads. They should have made a @ChristopherSean head . #days #dool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video 2: All Different Sections/Dance Sequences  New Dance Video: Today 3/7/19  Contemporary Dance   "La La La La"… https://t.co/xl5ABNfwIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s beat K-State @TexasWBB - #thisistexas #hookem #team 🏀 https://t.co/k9t5MS6T6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite worship service!  #worship #silence #Lent2019 #quietcommunion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaythird @2bumboclaat @merry123459 @Puglaas I'm not so sure. She would be better than Scheer, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, and he wants to take down Trump... that's good enough for us. Let's call it redemption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[undefined https://t.co/fcVjJ5Uc0d #biblestudytools #bst #bible Are there ET’s out there? If Earth is young then why… https://t.co/bAcaqb3MPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejassingh @BreakingNLive @POTUS Drawing The Swamp Is In Progress! #TrustThePlan  The #SealedIndictments Have Gro… https://t.co/SKWEMIbLzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimpledmoon I KNOW RIGHT?! like...i thought it was going somewhat well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1lngargsims @bridget_joy_ Seniority in the Senate. Not in hearts and minds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannity tells it like it is. The left and CNN, MSNBC are the propaganda machines fully bought and paid for by peopl… https://t.co/rQbWZ8eQHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMalysa @SurvivingGrady You sir are now excommunicated for this blasphemy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP  @HouseDemocrats   @SpeakerPelosi   America look at how many lives are affected by those who violated our… https://t.co/YD1tx9wu4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIndian8 I would disagree there.  Columbus didn't have that mentality, but he DID exploit, seize, ruin the… https://t.co/u9HoKkEwtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRockbeats @xzibit 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum… https://t.co/Nq36AOOwwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵 Break up with your boyfriend yeah, yeah,  'cause you’re prone to self-sabotage and paired with your inability to… https://t.co/pwRhusVHHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[smartphone apps cannot be trusted at all! sadly people don't read the privacy policy and accept all permissions whi… https://t.co/503kwgI3AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so sorry to hear this. Darryl was always an absolute pleasure to work with. Sending prayers to his friends and… https://t.co/yMNrS6pF59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cinder is getting all the snuggles she can while I recover #migrainessuck #hangoverwithouttheparty #ihateheadaches… https://t.co/QXxg5qCtEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris All good, you can just declare it a National Emergrncy. Much progress will follow.  #precedent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DlawrenceNYC @KIIB_ Haven’t seen it. Which season are you referring to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does @PressSec not just BURST into flames from all the HOT HELL LYING??🌩⛈⚡🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Book wasn’t a great movie...it felt super condensed and a little fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @kimguilfoyle @VOTEMAGA2020 Thats because he is one of us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no #clockin and #clockout When you are a #realestate agent you work day and night. Do what’s best for your… https://t.co/MoGRQlpWNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @SpeakerPelosi Maybe neither will come back because they know they will be indicted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @RhodesWest75 My guess is the dog wouldn’t feel so hot either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a video of a dog and showed it to Rodrigo and said “I NEED IT” in my spongebob voice and he gave me the DIRTIEST look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump For years, @realDonaldTrump said @MichaelCohen212 was a great guy with a great family. Only w… https://t.co/41nywmfVad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows NO. THAT’s WHAT YOU  ARE DOING RIGHT NOW &amp; EVERY FKG DAY! 🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was that time an assistant football coach from the visiting school reached inside my media vest, grabbed me W… https://t.co/Qz1b8Nk1ZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried, it’s fine. Jordan Morris scored a goal, scored a goal, scored a goal; Jordan Morris scored a goal and we w… https://t.co/e5jirpamir]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @NeelDesaiBA to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations, no reviews. 1 cover a day for a… https://t.co/eQFR3LrR50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that the STEEL wall you want?  So your Russian pals (and you) can capitalize on RUSSIAN owned steel companies ba… https://t.co/QLROgy9gPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth. It’s just that some people are asleep.  Fascism grows slowly so one barely notices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDubb1 @KamalaHarris You MAGA men are hateful and narrow-minded and don't give 2 shits about anyone but white… https://t.co/t9gqSQyCjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[we- first of all why are you ranking women who have no clue you exist based on their beauty  second..... i honestly… https://t.co/Z7wLSplslZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6 @DanikaJaster You inspire me with your plethora of tips and resources every week. I want to get to that point! I… https://t.co/lQayxjK0F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[La manera de medir que tan buena estuvo mi noche es depende de cuantos stories suba. Entre menos, más peligrosa. 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chicago_History @BDisgusting @JayBradleyPW @KeshaRose @TheMandyMoore @RealPaigeWWE @JoelEmbiid @VanLathan… https://t.co/Et9rZTTr0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnemcginty Otherwise we might have to talk about something that does matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it begins!! Only if I could start every morning this way. #ocean #coffee and #viewtodiefor  . .  #nascar #cars… https://t.co/gMexZGH0rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Seattle airport needs to warn passengers traveling out of the S gates that there’s no hot food or coffee BEFORE… https://t.co/9cFj8ZWrg9]]></document></documents></author>