<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My favorite comedians are @normmacdonald and @anthonyjeselnik . They were once on Last Comic Standing as judge and… https://t.co/Mju3LDGVdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Missouri Valley Conference Final makes me think that I could play basketball in the Missouri Valley Co… https://t.co/9fxXIzSmbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The office is better than How I met Your Mother.  But How I Met Your Mother is better than friends.   Disagree all… https://t.co/pXi7C8aNEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scratch my last tweet.. I’m corrected, my best friend postmated me coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we lose white folks, we lose America! That’s why I always tell white people to have truck loads of white babies.… https://t.co/1ehIrzojiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Dagoth Ur and his minions offer you a drink before battle. https://t.co/7AfGLvuJ0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JardinTaylor I mean that’s kinda racist also haha “White kids” automatically thinking all white people are bad and… https://t.co/bOsw6vqjgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcdjeong @BeingKrennic @Timcast @thatstarwarsgrl @SCReviewsmang @GeeksGamersCom @JJ66616 @Cyclone9650 @raulmares72… https://t.co/27SIC5IQOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald #Trump can't be a #racist because he has that one black friend is a thing that's on the Congressional reco… https://t.co/7Eo0tCShRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GavinNewsom on homelessness: “We have to have our mayors’ backs on homelessness. They cannot do it alone.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medicwife2006 For the love of God why are you people picking on a child? If you got a complant about K come talk t… https://t.co/my5XzSBduD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriba que se viene @FirmaEspn  junto a @EJerezESPN @vikingomartell @ESPNDRadio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddyBx15 @byrdiiie @boysru1ee What purpose does that serve? They have heard about the situation, they have met ab… https://t.co/HeIrhsqUXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF 9th Annual Echo Awards Spotlight February 15, 2019 TMP's Best Musicians Of 2018 Jerome Isma… https://t.co/A9ximozP11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ubercapper @GateToWire I would tend to believe you will see even stricter reforms adopted, especially here in Cali… https://t.co/VAsuR16sNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey @AmandiOnAir Sadly seems a given that he won’t and that they have :-/  @davidplotz was just saying… https://t.co/BBYqm7j4Ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! Hell yeah I do. Charlie Sheen has just started, and he had… https://t.co/sFFdnzqofu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love 2019. Simply telling the truth, stating facts, and quoting a person verbatim now constitutes “an attack.” Hi… https://t.co/V8y0o8FTqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom @GovPressOffice Why are we processing #tarsands from Canada in #Rodeo or California at all?!!… https://t.co/LmNDsPHIlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJBurghnett34 @nolanhall21 @billyyyy_boyyyy Cant wait to watch @nolanhall21 go through a table.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randygdub @iheartmindy @JacobAWohl That’s Minnesota in the summer time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djury827 The only thing I can agree on right now is that  @djury827  makes the most sense of all the @AB84 comments .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Franny Yes girl. I went one day and they made it that way for me by mistake. So I went back today and asked for… https://t.co/kfM7wR2BXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Using the American People, just like the rest of trump circus!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all our technology, why do mobile phone calls still sound like they’re being made with a potato?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@childofthewild7 I’ll be your warm breeze and definitely play with your hair...]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important lesson to build #socialjustice: Equality is not the same as equity  #sustainabledevelopment https://t.co/XMBWF8nprx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody looking for a room 2 rent out at an APT tap in my bro Mel looking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doomedparade @StankyLegMcgee Hahaha I was gonna blind guess that but was waiting for the initials. My fav Metallica!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankie82709556 @jayfonsecapr Gracias por probar mi teoría. Los españoles Rosselló haciéndose millonario y la “est… https://t.co/HPjo37pCc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#losangeles #lalaland #california #cali #usa #us #ernstandyoung #businessman @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/CATICh5r2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Date @Capitals History (Feb.14,2009):  #ALLCAPS Mike Green scored for the 8th consecutive game- a new record f… https://t.co/ycrJ5aqWX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to my boyfriend and his friends discuss Dragon Ball Z https://t.co/lR02a8qQ8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Did I just slander an entire profession?” My favorite line from the podcast 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to worry about telling my coworkers that I preferred to eat lunch alone. Now I only have to worry about tell… https://t.co/vIu7cQ7ZD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BkMidnight @nycnoname @NYCEMSwatch Come on! That is the same issue that goes on with ALS! You spend 2 yrs to send… https://t.co/Hh86EyXhSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re both parties that contain racist humans wtf are y’all talking about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastStand2019 @hustler_chitown @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Buy More guns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Elias interruption but this time, it's the #RiottSquad. Riott Squad vs @NatbyNature and @RondaRousey next! #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my mind start giving up and I remember who I am https://t.co/exheJu2Pxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t look now but #Creighton is in the First Four Out in this compilation of brackets. We’re ‘in’ on 10 brackets. https://t.co/4RezAf7tRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K24English @Kyruer Fwiw , I believe the statement of the SDF commander Firat carries more weight than SOHR on this… https://t.co/LlBgawwH0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to enjoy this... @ El Pueblo Mexican Restaurant https://t.co/mC7kps999T]]></document><document><![CDATA[so like is the planet that Westeros is on large and extremely nonspherical or just wobbly or what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael World according to garp and any other Irving book.   Odd Thomas by Koontz or anything else he’s written.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning 😃 #mondaymood #presidentsday #nodaysoff @ Blink Fitness https://t.co/8mILlfs2iS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlcantaraEdits @IlliniMBB @verdadero_andre @CoachUnderwood True definition of a ILLINI PITBULL ,  You rock ! GO ILLINI !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You really have to be some kind if sick ghoul to dream up a term like Pre Existing Conditions to allow people… https://t.co/xOeUPq78f3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mass attendance a bit lighter than normal.  Humbled and Awed that several parishioners made it a point to greet me… https://t.co/RqvPhw4BPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianTams @YogurtNutrition @NanciGuestRDPhD @LoriShemek @ESodicoffMD @DietitianOnline @Wendi_Irlbeck… https://t.co/g6PP1xHGjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was kid, I flipped burgers at McDonald’s for $3.35/hour and had to go in on my off days because half the adu… https://t.co/QdOIeNc3sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Have they told ur neck needs a fusion? I have a triple fusion in my neck from a car accident. It helped me. Need u back soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is proving Democrats wrong!  This Socialist Party is not prepared to deal with issues like NK. The… https://t.co/VNJsFI2Jiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump He knows not the meaning of  R-E-S-P-E-C-T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Research… https://t.co/bh9SeKEHxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh they the same people who think “funnyhoodvidz” on ig is the best memepage out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah you idiots learned after two years there’s no freaking collusion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriciakova You certainly know that I understand the process. 😉 So in sum, it sounds like this announcement is gr… https://t.co/UHBVUXZBGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilliesMike @AngeloCataldi @MikeTrout Mike’s going to go wherever who gives them the most money your theories delusional]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticias24 @jaarreaza no TRUMP no es como Uds. GENOCIDAS.. que bailan mientra matan a la gente de un tiro de hambr… https://t.co/WbmPvymL3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Outrage?  people cant be this stupid right, do they understand how it works when they take less out of pay, you get less back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlotReally @Killahbeez79 @pitbop @mtracey ‘I will put my record up against yours any day of the week’ Bernie Sande… https://t.co/bbWg0VHd2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itsyagirl_s Bethesda used to be adventurous, before they took an arrow to the knee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murraysmyname BUT i’m the same guy that doesn’t snoop or invade my partners  privacy.... my motto is be good OR be good at it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caiden drops a close one 3-2. Runner up! Congratulations! @AireaneCurtis @RocketAthletic1 https://t.co/jz5TTxydqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[They like you when you’re average &amp; hate you when you’re different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all think Abducted In Plain Sight is crazy then you need to watch The Innocent Man.... NUTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire neighborhood went down ... high winds in DC 🙈 We also learned that we need a backup generator for the in… https://t.co/CZpKo4E9Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like Anthony Bourdain at Quarters right now. I’m shootin’ the breeze with a cook and a server]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebLoVette_ @BarstoolTenn Nope I lived in a van. https://t.co/VExNcE9rJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elle_yess @WitchezGarden @LuCkYDaDDa666 Interesting and I'm uploading https://t.co/vLLJSdwQth]]></document><document><![CDATA[The deepest tragedy of the Jussie Smollett story is that a man felt it important enough to pay people to beat him a… https://t.co/7sQ5rkCrUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜🦋 Fighting for the #lupus cure starts with learning more about the #disease Raise your awareness 🙌💜📚💜 #educate you… https://t.co/8166YCZBMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[-we as DemocratsVotersNeedsCandidateWhoTRUMP Can'tSayHeHasMoreExperience Nthe HighestPosition of Gov,A CandidateWho… https://t.co/5zeSX37IxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBoschFF @Klazk That's true, but I almost made the playoffs with no QB, RB, or TE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say  “Everyone kn my family has had the flu, so I’ve been taking care of them”  What exactly does that… https://t.co/hiMnuay3JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd @MariaTCardona They believe he was sent from God ; his Presidency was a gift from God. If they believ… https://t.co/ACNhlGPEkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NDickerson15 @DGreenGiant @David_Crisp31 Love you like a brother forever Big Man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmarieeg I just hope he doesn't dive and gets impaled by the chain's crucifix, he's channeling his inner Mr. T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianoland @EdFrankovic @backstrom19 is one of the ten best pure passers in @NHL history #ALLCAPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aimes_sweethrt Looney Tunes and basically most of the regular Saturday morning lineup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @SecretaryAcosta @NACoTweets Leg Conference - talking about the importance of different career paths -… https://t.co/7Rj9GU69oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSUEsquire @TheAthleticMIA @Manny_Navarro Meanwhile, at the Nike Coaching Clinic...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristinafoxxx vs herself in #dreamselfbikiniboxingmatch👙🥊 #dingding🔔 #fight👊 #knockurselfout #youwin xoxo… https://t.co/JVSz0XGW0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veiled threats of assassination in NRA publications need to be scrutinized.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last Democrat Presidential candidate who loved America’s Constitution. https://t.co/BP9719B190]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junior_miller  @gordonkeith saw you guys were doing a Sunday night show... turns out muse is not musers... these g… https://t.co/riQpgJWISu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarcasimandsass @singleplaiddad @DuckingKissy @seanbaggett81 @TattedSoldier83 @Mr_Spikey_Head @Shamusroan13… https://t.co/uDiTFjRMlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not trying to brag, but Brandy thinks I’m pretty special. https://t.co/kwBDq5Zzsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 24th birthday to @ZachLaVine   Thank you for everything you do for the @chicagobulls on and off the court. You are appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethawilliams79 @DTutterrow @Gotitans333 @Titans I hAve a mock draft coming out soon for @PFN365. In it, I think y… https://t.co/Vr7sR6Yw2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeelTrigga @TheSportsHernia @mu5taffa Sorry I could’ve sworn you said recent history. But oh I get it now, we can… https://t.co/xUIPu4Q773]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell a the difference between a door you opened, and a door God opened]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do people still have like.... Actual clocks to set ahead tonight #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/15JNoLpCFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Lawrence Well Obama did say he was going to fundamentally change America. So how is that working out for you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is a #InternationalWomansDay?? Y’all gone stop making shit up to get our money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello ramen, my old friend.  Taking a quick break from packing. https://t.co/W8b9QVf3dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegate Daryl Cowles, R-Morgan, compares the bill to a pot of chili. He says some ingredients went in "that I thin… https://t.co/KXHpY586TG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lemmelyckyadyck @Lickmenow20 @NastyAndThick JUICY AND DELICIOUS SWEET CHEESECAKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @lagaviota521 @obrienmaggie17 @pppdreams @DUPONTBLUES @LuckycharmMw @helen19242686 @JenniferMlott… https://t.co/YDWZXguzVT]]></document></documents></author>