<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@newbegi20694568 @ReedwiththeRead @BravoTV She can dish it out but can’t take it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techcoachmama @AmyLSchumacher Great idea! Are they housed on a YouTube channel or does she send links out some oth… https://t.co/yJ9Cwlr8Z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished watching Episode 4 of @DoomPatrolDCU, and wow. This show is so quirky and strange and I am loving i… https://t.co/EH0gcQ5gZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a picture of apricot colored roses in a vase 💐and thought it was a bowl of caramel corn 🍿  Therefore the f… https://t.co/IGK7FSJQxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been proven women should go out, hang out with, socialize with their girlfriends to improve their happiness an… https://t.co/tpTAo6Empl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump So important !! New ideas give power and will build a nation even stronger!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayesha Curry is Making the World She Wants – GoDaddy Commercial https://t.co/ILB0CdGq55 via @YouTube #lovingit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusymomJen Seeing you all together made me totally wish I had gone!  Maybe next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesse joined others to honor @HillaryClinton. Bernie, not even pretend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnbreakableAT Fuck that guy. 1. He's a misogynist. 2. He's ugly. *reported and blocked*]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you trusted someone and find out they don’t like Star Wars. 💔🥴😔💔😔💔🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraysonDolan IM CRYING I’ve been really sick for the last 4 days and I couldn’t sleep cause I need to cough or vom… https://t.co/HHBNkLS2m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 I can't think of anything I would want to say to defend a girl who has used every resource to threaten… https://t.co/HgLAirYImW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy with the way my life is going 🥰 nothing but positivity in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i really looking forward to life and a future? bc i just want to sleep for the rest of my existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's true. He throws them under the bus and places all the blame on the players. When dook loses it's never becau… https://t.co/CxZxEmmOES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once my mouth heals once &amp; for all I will never take eating for granted again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super tempted to buy myself Pentatonix  tickets and Chainsmokers/5sos tickets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secutina I’ll come see you soon! Thanks for coming over! Psyched to watch your doggo 🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a crush on Tracy Tree as a child is this why I always want to go to rainforest cafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may have a crisis at the border but he's gonna keep on pissin Americas off he's gonna have a civil war this tim… https://t.co/2y4Y2eArzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LePetitNW @eddiebauer I want all my pants to be lined in flannel now. It’s been a life saver during our snow storm… https://t.co/EWpZbIpBMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing about coming from a poor background is thinking any raise is good. I remember my grandma insisting my mak… https://t.co/79l4WIBw6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shewitsch I am trying to talk myself into going to the Saturday cross fit for the first time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @juliettekayyem Good. Less Trump supporters on the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tragic. Oh, how I wish we could have do-overs in history!!  I can’t even imagine the depth of the hurt for these fa… https://t.co/AwQuCWkAf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day is complete.   #adventureswithNora #cutestassistantever https://t.co/DuGT3sNp3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics That's worse than everything manafort did, all 8 counts he was found guilty of? Oh wait, okay I se… https://t.co/qUZKL7P024]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only been waiting for #leopardlandsouth since spring break last year, and now we are down to hours.. #sunandsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianRep @DonaldJTrumpJr Pray you quit popping tide pods and killing your brain cells. #impeachtrump #FakeNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@55mmbae RIGHT. The building was historic, not luxury. That other hotel I stayed at was luxury from top to bottom-a… https://t.co/EwJ2dqzr7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Best Western Lake Buena Vista - Disney Springs Resort Area https://t.co/iIV3SW3E1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @RebeccaLegg5 Anyone have an answer?  We are waiting.  Still waiting...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had so many errands to run today with the girls and I got sick and had to pull over and throw up and then get bac… https://t.co/sPd2TEgcgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tilo423 Yeah it was a real bummer. I didn't know anything about it either. Kind of threw me to see them gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Obama wasn’t born in the United States. Wake up. He’s a fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buying cars online today... Got outbid on an A7, but he paid for it muuhaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@profeashley all these Season 3 teasers are killing me with suspense! #inspiredproficiency #nysaflt #lecny… https://t.co/FW1LqgfxCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how many times I see it, it doesn’t get any less Grand 😍 Happy anniversary to this national treasure! 🇺🇸… https://t.co/LzCmhSecI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not pushing for an interview person, I was responding to a Tweet.  Those of us in the US would prefer for the… https://t.co/ZCJYxezp5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lethrup @lorjayzee2 @FireGoddessB @ninampls @otter272 @Back_dafucup @BannedDc @FalResistsHate @CanuckSassy… https://t.co/CQDdrVrEkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I said...as long as this happens, I can continue seeing wicked_musical my ultimate favorite musical! 💚💚💚 @ WIC… https://t.co/NhS0oypron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnn @MSNBC @nytimes @AOC @SpeakerPelosi  I guess democrats are against people working because they can’t buy their… https://t.co/a6MQGp0Ven]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did i do to deserve being attracted to not just men but white men?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll trade your broken wings for mine, I’ve seen your scars and kissed your crime. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[my name is Jaimie  I was born the same day as you  My age is a different class of the day  I like to think about yo… https://t.co/7Xq3Ncgrzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheScorwin like many people even ones that are coupled and have babies, I just like having a companion animal and… https://t.co/VOaD6JhDxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley Trump operates on his 'gut' he claims. Where have the checks and balances been for 2 years? We have bee… https://t.co/VSrcEXORbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoureADandy And another way to say it is “he says he was attacked...” alleged is official talk. Cops and court peo… https://t.co/6oxpWQwcA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I wanna text the girl I fuck w gn but she W her boyfriend  😂  Thoughts of a side nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edtertaining honestly thank you, its 4am and I always have trouble sleeping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulpmx @_paigecraig That’s a stretch bro, and I can’t get that shit off my phone either]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn and Louis are both performing around the same time????? How am i going to do this????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m making that mac n cheese I tried to make last night. I’m awake this time. All is good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump To Ask Congress For Additional $8.6 Billion For Border Wall In New Budget https://t.co/lT9u6BpwP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday morning excitement...FSA LIVE! 🤩🤗 #FSA #BESBobcats @Bennett_ES @browardschools @BrowardOSPA https://t.co/IwAtURzPrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindsay_13 @ZachLaVine This was the WORST trade Wolves have ever made or will ever make! #shouldhavetradedwiggins]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤷🏻‍♂️why Club 96 1️⃣9️⃣9️⃣6️⃣ gurl amazing time for🧵 fashion 👚pastels shown in fall 🍁Paco Rabanne 👡 custom couture… https://t.co/WtJ3IdnS4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW IS IT that I feel like I’ll never be loved that way again but at the same time I know that in NO WAY was that love???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpringAyn @Chriskl70208387 @TH3R34LTRUTH @basedinfidel8 @Americanthatguy @AlexWY18 @fellspeaks @johnw299 @AJuM809… https://t.co/m4dwG3Aja0]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 23 Madagascar 🇲🇬  Republic of Madagascar is home to an abundance of animals and plants. Approximately 90%… https://t.co/hAmUr1tbXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Ann Salzer leave the BULL Facebook group? Delete her Twitter account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really sad when you get in bed at 12:30 and it’s “early” compared to when you’ve been going to sleep. 😭😭 7 o’c… https://t.co/aQ1K58C55p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so today is going to be a crazy day at with school and covering for peoples vacations! But I’m still going to ge… https://t.co/yfawmMunYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m looking for in life is someone to sing the Kid Rock part in Picture with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My juul is about to die during Valentines Day rush.. should I just quit now or what im not sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's funny. Funny Mom Confessions. Painfully true! Click for more. :D https://t.co/bOvTwU3XYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to a very special night with my forever Valentine... the stage! ✨💛 Hope you had a wonderful V-Day my love… https://t.co/lcl2fq7Kr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habits76 @PaulTherealpaul @PKSubban1 Carey tweeted it also you idiot does it make him less wonderful too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB Of course I’m listening getting ready for work! #HanginTough30 https://t.co/aETpiA0fXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[it doesn’t matter what’s put in front of me, I’m ALWAYS gonna pick my family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leslifoster @wusa9 This was my favorite part of the show! I smiled very bigly. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don’t just all Tennessee residents by this sorry excuse for a representative. #TrumpLies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enjoy_murph @ANCOM5600 @GMShivers Apparently we can't cause as soon as we do, we get called "white"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImKileyDavis @PatrickQuarter @leahcasciano Yea due to her lack in knowledge and experience as a coach. But she sti… https://t.co/Aw1upQd3cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocograce42 @CraigRSawyer @SenFeinstein He'll no sing from the rafters.  She has ethics problems but she's a democrat so she gets a pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuseumsWith @ErnieAnastos My pleasure Marisa.. loved your style of teaching!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to make my own You Got Served video dancing in the street pouring rain]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favourite clients is #socialenterprise foodworks_och - and they've announced a big change today-moving fr… https://t.co/zfzPPQgfPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #futureisfemale and it’s important to understand the past to build a strong tomorrow.  I thank ms_anaximenagp f… https://t.co/K6225HLN0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so thankful for my bed..one and only unofficial is enough for me👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruhhh I hate automatic flushing toilets, like you be walking out the restroom with a wet ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Javierito321 La ayuda humanitaria llegara a todos los Vzlanos, porque Dios va abrir puertas!!!!🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Data Center by Dynasty Brewing Company at @brewdynasty — https://t.co/hD0EH1VSSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t believe I’m one of the older guys now,” says 39-year-old Hackett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage to do great things comes from spending time with Jesus. https://t.co/le7wTPCAJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball @MSNBC Never seen a leader who never takes responsibility for any of his mistakes.  He’s like a 2 year old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed with applying lashes ❤️😘💋 #lovemylife #livingthedream #oc #newportbeach #lashes #joannayoungskin @ Joanna… https://t.co/9tMu1bDE2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWeepingAngel @DonaldJTrumpJr Why are women OK Killing babies in the womb..🤔??? https://t.co/1MG5pHdzcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have been saying for so long that you've been meaning to try it out or get back into yoga so now's the time!… https://t.co/ggkiKmiDI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How on God's earth did this idiot wind up in the White House? Oh, I forgot about the illiterate, red neck MAGA supp… https://t.co/yMr9jZesC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Trump hired Clinton people to his administration? Even they are good people like Heather Wilson - she is H girl… https://t.co/C8M8pv2sG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerrinnesmac @Jenny648144921 @pratoshnivedita @loveGoldenHeart @ChristiWalling @DerekPa56710094 @Adele47018578… https://t.co/ccuCfxBcBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the mountains, I will bow my life To the one who set me there—  In the valley, I will lift my eyes to the one who sees me there 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep telling people I’m an angel! See that halo?? #angel #halo #toldyouso @Christalina0809 christalinabeauty @ Ch… https://t.co/buOy6iDp2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oddly enough @FrankLuntz no one else will willingly point this out. Well I appreciate your #factchecks!!!!!!… https://t.co/vNLGVJkbUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Krieger_ You’re the second person I know with a telescope. I need to get me one now ✌🏾🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[But she didn’t respect him enough to let him know &amp; why isn’t her man aloud to the party with her?? No way 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so lucky that jonathan puts up with me. i literally do not know how he does it..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decades after Roe, black women are still denied reproductive justice | Opinion https://t.co/OMaptcgfAG via @phillydotcom]]></document></documents></author>