<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder @Timpanist I’ll send him my address so he can send my check.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as I expected, I’m rewatching Six Feet Under and I miss being a funeral director. I haven’t embalmed in almost a year 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lac_news @TracieMGardner @nycHealthy So well deserved! @TracieMGardner is amazing expert, advocate, leader and colleague! #teamwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just checked the weather for tomorrow and thought wow it’s going to be a nice day tomorrow, and then I realized i… https://t.co/hDlR1aRzWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FailShark @theshoetoo I was wondering if you were shooting shoe or Cohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trentpyles @ashleyburr @whitneyhammons @jdquinlan @tbhbth Can’t wait for #HurricaneSmashSZN to be here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your scheduled opened up to attend, let me know by 9 and we can add you in for lunch today! Or you can bring you… https://t.co/nBBb1M0QNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#polyglot #devcondetect @megaconference @LocalMediaAssoc  @EditorPublisher  #adfraud #cybersecurity @GlasswingVC… https://t.co/wuMBm7HRBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I'd buy a T-shirt or bumper sticker with this quote, wouldn’t you!🙌🙌@Lunascowboys @selenaozuna @1908Heslip… https://t.co/ak6iNPSGei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneaky card (Reverse pickpocket) i should start this.... https://t.co/j3QGnvNkb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is absolutely time to PANIC about climate change!! https://t.co/W76VDRiIM4 via @voxdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris @braveheartengr I apologize to Feinstein for my mistaken “take” on this video! Obviously, these kid… https://t.co/hi25WPaU8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zzbluebrass @Jeremy_Irons643 @Mad_In_America @dereksmall01 There's news about ketamine/ esketamine. It's not Rapas… https://t.co/ISHFaK3x2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OConnor4_5 @CampbellCounts @ThinkCampbell @mskleif @MsRoseTweets I’ve got a good book for stuff like this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you ladies didn’t start using eye cream and anti aging skin care till recently and it shows 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, I would KNOW these were empty, and hand them their flat ass soda through the drive thru just so I wouldn’t ha… https://t.co/vkExcr7NjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i should hold the world record for the most times a person has twisted their ankle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the new song on spotify / @itunesmusic “LAP” w @HeesunLee. 🎶Her album is #14 on itunes hip hop chart wtf… https://t.co/sbt0EJKrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I imagine that we’ll be treated to a massive oversell spectacular a la an actual dying snake in the wild like usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[One might think supposedly critical thinkers could have learned something.  Media waaay overboard. I checked the po… https://t.co/sidaZfi3AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can do it! #motivational #mindset #youcandoit @ Coeur d'Alene, Idaho https://t.co/FxlQJZvQMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Day of our February Finale Sale!  Select Statement Necklaces are 50% off!  Help me end #february with a ✨ and… https://t.co/mtFA07OREo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome time for Sammy at Sky Ranch!!! This girl melts my heart ❤ She's so beautiful inside and out ❤… https://t.co/zfZ4yf57QO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timjacobwise Tim, you are just a nasty piece of crap that is jealous of what Trump has accomplished]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peetz, CO Crook, CO Sterling, CO Yuma, CO Goodwell, OK Hooker, OK (yes, it's a town) Scott City, KS Ulysses, KS Kis… https://t.co/6Fq6XX2a42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Boss Wants Full Access To Your Cell Phone https://t.co/pjqCI42fjr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time at a NASCAR race watching the @TicketGuardian 500! https://t.co/lmCUx8qnSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami 9 mile festival was on fire. Mua nosworthycreations  hair @cr3ativ3styl3s @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/wyZpHJMCe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any of my startup venture friends trying to grow and interested in trying the venture design engine I've developed… https://t.co/sj0Eec3bFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is going so good right now no one and no negative energy will ruin it!! 🙅🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for the #AfterMovie!! This trailer is PERFECTION!!!! https://t.co/3Jk4UDG0sT @imaginator1d 🥰🥰 https://t.co/9MCmCQ06O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just came on here to post this fire ass picture of The Undertaker. The GOAT. Okay bye now. https://t.co/lt3kusvc0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smppdx66 @NBCThisisUs I feel like along with that poor Kevin is trying to make up for not being there during the f… https://t.co/gE9s7FO3oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#showtunes at @sidetrackbar for my #birthday @ Sidetrack The Video Bar https://t.co/P2uZC8Gydt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneKerns NKY School administrators ready to soak in the strategies to Unlock Student Talent  Experts are always a… https://t.co/zmJYskxqYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevewardpoli @Puglaas Wish I could hit the like button many times. She's the type of politics I want. Stop bowing… https://t.co/XypNNMmCjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo The fact that she grew up in an upper middle class household means nothing I suppose. Her mom made o… https://t.co/7KdWJwRsjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnBuell79 @JonahNRO Have you seen her face? And big brown eyes? How could you not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LpSavesUsAll I feel you. Life has been quite shitty for some time now. Very hard to stay positive when all you wan… https://t.co/2WZbhZnjiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨🏼‍💼 @BadIandsNatIPS  🙆🏽‍♀️ @VoyageursNPS   #findyourpark 🦌 https://t.co/zJRvLTrG2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emiliaclarke I absolutely adore you and I wish you lived next door!   I think you'd be fun to play board games with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ya can’t go through life expectin everyone to have the same heart as you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSFCFOTY13 @sonarriley I think he looks more like Dave Clark myself :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I think the Fed said different to day when he testified in front of congress.  Oh wait.  You weren’t their.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@posey_obriens Although i will argue that shameless remained good for more than 3 seasons lol. I will know the exact number soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[#funfact @WaltDisneyWorld apparently doesn’t sell burgers and fries but will serve hot dogs with chips instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But in the Kinder World, it ought not be. #TaraAnnMoons with @stpeteyontweety because He suffers. #PaganLove]]></document><document><![CDATA[La recompensa de madrugar; pinchis amaneceres bien chingones #queridodiario]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Coach Freeman makes you feel good about how you did , THATS A WHOLE DIFFERENT TYPA JOY 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[But by the time I leave it’ll be the Mangled Chestnut Smokehouse for sure https://t.co/h6CVwi0P1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to dumb n dumber🤓 legal mfs😈😤🤠 love u guys hope ur day was alright 💖💖 @CaitlinBraswell @colganallison https://t.co/tZUtm15Gjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_u_cy @winston53660 @ellenzelwell 1)I just got this email from Austin Indivisable -they are mobilizing efforts fo… https://t.co/6PprgKJ8XT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FOX29GoodDay ... National Pet Day .... Good morning from Jett ( right ) and my grand fur baby Kane ( left ) https://t.co/cdXDhyp3Dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's playful. This is so true!! Some one was talking to me about 3D and how it has... https://t.co/vwYXxxJg6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy I got to see a win, especially against the Pens! #BlueJackets @ Nationwide Arena https://t.co/99X6gFo2Kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nirishia1 @xhipee @jessicalbuxton @ChrisolytheN @Orpheus631 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump All of you drug addicts ar… https://t.co/VB4KrcXQoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really adore Sam and I feel like I don’t get to tell her that enough. I love you 🌸 https://t.co/n88QDX7QVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If it’s true that you are engaging in disrespect of an American while on foreign soil, you are a t… https://t.co/cPlKEItCeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenchungg Is it the one with Michael Hall? I need a new series to watch. Haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vast indeed with so much Hillary/Russia collusion that has been. Ericked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't wanna own just wanna drive 😊👌 #Luxury 👠 #LuxuryLiving ✈️  #Exotic 💎 #ExoticToys 🚁  #Founders😉🤜 #FemaleFounder… https://t.co/CmsjLIPk7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[People want you to do well • just not better than them #keepgoing #motivation #fridaymood @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/85midIxNBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissDahlELama I confess I feel I have missed something, but your sentiment is perennial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can plan for the future, we can remember the past, but every thing we have ever accomplished has been lived in t… https://t.co/UN4Sr5gwPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court is closed and I’m back at work... just for today 😊 #NoJuryDuty #PresidentsDay @nbcla @ NBC Universal https://t.co/2WnEenBvdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a window at home that has a crack in it. Can I have colored sand? Maybe it can make a design like the view f… https://t.co/r6RHNZqnpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devi_IbnLa_Ahad I meant to post this a while ago https://t.co/HQrBEulzk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson @realDonaldTrump I can’t wait I got the popcorn ready https://t.co/GdcEV7hDCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shrimp and cauliflower sauce with garlic over pasta. #yum #cookingathome @ Saint Louis Park, Minnesota https://t.co/PhMJaRNgzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreatheNewWinds @AllOnMedicare @cwillott @nytdavidbrooks I really wish Americans could walk through a universal he… https://t.co/Infeokvjrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFL @RapSheet Sorry Cowboys I am a New Orleans saints fan go drew Brees]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except Jr. always looks like he's trying to discreetly eek out a quiet fart, but it's louder than he thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moworldwide What Steve Harvey said, is the lie that MILLIONS of ppl tell themselves EVERYDAY, 2 jsutify not taking… https://t.co/u2Obcrh4Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I passed my test,I passed my test!!! That last minute Hail Mary is never without fail.  🙏🏻🙌🏻🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case you were wondering what they’d look like playing in your formal dining room! #mattnathanson #aarontap… https://t.co/X9TlqXoBOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was never the type to regret what i’ve done in life.. getting back to that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm extremely disappointed @ the authorities once again, when will they fucking realize how much harm this causes,… https://t.co/JxPh8jemK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA will conduct its first #allfemalespacewalk in March during #WomensHistoryMonth #WomenInSTEM .… https://t.co/uTrBqk6KZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blue_saphire5 Camilla, I understand now.  Some people never do sad to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in bed sick and Parker is the sweetest dog cuddling next to me.🤒❤️🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bandera Bandera de México . . . ❤️🇲🇽🙏 #banderademexico #24Feb #24deFebrero https://t.co/tUi0r7mHad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillymoe @DevinNunes Nunes is still waiting to see FBI reports against Trump, they won't give it to congress, beca… https://t.co/vrcrcfueZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSUBasketball @EmmittWilliams6 Emmitt MVP of this game! Geaux Tigers 🐅!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police want to know if anyone else in the neighborhood has had similar issues or problems.   Video makes me 🤬.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes, this is me being judgmental because you are negatively impacting the well being of a creature that has NO… https://t.co/IH19Y6hyIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Does anyone remember Foles at the start of the season when the team looked like shit? 2. Where was the Jags defe… https://t.co/b1bPshlUTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garages is the only one to make out on this deal. Jussie will probably go broke and see jail time. Lawyers will pro… https://t.co/bvSMrbk9t3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1/7 books I love with no comment. Tagged by @CleveArguelles, tagging @jasonmeanz and @M_A_Catalano https://t.co/AGSST2pNLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilvolo_Madrid @thess_efi The Princess Bride is by far one of the best movies out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Psyduck keeps appearing in the background and glitching this Gym lol https://t.co/eqttfzLFjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HankEpton @aliasvaughn There has to be an exception filed by Mueller to negate the guideline in this instance.  Ju… https://t.co/rpJi1GBtCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess being with someone younger than you is the way to go. Guys my age or older don’t want me, so..... 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tigermcg @NBCNews Not yo sista!!! But your opinion, it matters to someone, just not me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday couldn’t win!! 💪🏾 #movesomething @ 24 Hour Fitness - Glenarden Super-Sport https://t.co/clcrw2bYul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChewyHelp No problem! Hopefully I’ll get an email soon that it’s been officially sent out with the tracking number 🐾♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE HAVE TICKETS TO THOSE GAMES YOU PLAY IN APRIL!!!!!! #WontJinxIt #TakeWarning https://t.co/g4Zfu8NTQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs are the best. That’s all. Happy Saturday. #dogsoftwitter #savethemall #AdoptDontShop https://t.co/kQ4ga8Tsd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My morning stop. I love what they have done in here and can't wait to have some extra time on my hands to look thro… https://t.co/Qm40oi6vTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This face tho. 😍 • • #mysia #thisisfour #isiadavid #myboy #😍 #blueeyes #dimples #blondehair #heartbreaker… https://t.co/nPY0AGVva4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Region10Leaders Take time to work on your happiness. Serve instead of being Self-centered. #Thinklearnsucceed… https://t.co/12XugkXPDi]]></document></documents></author>