<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t you know @POTUS there are way more issues in the United States that are National Emergencies. Why can’t we fo… https://t.co/ahOMhQQ62e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanLRodrigue10 @BuxtonJulia @JasminaKelemen @jlynnmccoy @DPantoulas Ah, very important distinction. I appreciate the clarification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newton County Classic Update Revised Classic Schedule:  Thursday  4:00   Leake Central vs. Quitman 6:30   Newton Co… https://t.co/B76eUGx7Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Ryan on the call for the N2G3 State Champion game between West Morris Central vs Colonia! Give it a view… https://t.co/o5kaqOSckq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanortega3 @navarrowolff Además de que el proceso de chatarrizacion ha Sido un fracasó y se maneja a nivel nacion… https://t.co/aV3AXmYzNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@311Toronto @TorontosMayor is there a status update on this intersection? Fort York East bound is absolutely horren… https://t.co/CYbvjPnZR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yates says he communicated frequently with Dowless - "He was a needy person, he needed validation." Says they talked almost daily]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boy swaggy from top to bottom @coachfeld  #GoDucks 🦆 https://t.co/Ip7XMF9SZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oilngas007 @Swiftie01 A lot of the vile Twitter comments regarding Warnock just seem to prove his contention that… https://t.co/JUrUWikwoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @GeoffRBennett The Queens shyster is nearing his comeuppance. #ImpeachTrumpNow  #RussianAsset https://t.co/6ZfWMAtsmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone of the gym homies who are going through a heart break this Valentine’s day, here. You’re welcome and man… https://t.co/77keyKuHPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Jeremy Playing at Home.  Fired up at a loss against LSU.   They are Sweet sixteen and done.   Gonzaga, Tennes… https://t.co/D60QIlSzBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaep did the right thing. History will judge him well. Glad he got paid a fraction of what he is due]]></document><document><![CDATA[Illuminated in the darkness that we are surrounded by, beaconed by every thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IainCanUck @torontofc Curious to see what kind of spin TFC put on this. This is an absolute embarrassment. Can’t g… https://t.co/fer1aqlR2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelsNationLAX @Angels @Mooose_8 I totally agree. I would be happy with any or all of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great visit with Tyler @SenJoniErnst office talking about funding for libraries. Picture with the Senator is… https://t.co/YeGL41Wd2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[So considering #LukeCage and #UnbreakableKimmySchmidt are gone, I have no more need for #Netflix clearly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khyatt2876 @LianaBrackett Kris ... All you have to do is download..iTranslate... and every language in the world is at your fingertips...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Homecooked meal. Compliments to the Chef. My second Mother, Jess. #homecooking… https://t.co/ogCfGtcevB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most things take time before they are realized. #doverNY #psychology #WiliamJames  https://t.co/tLIZ0LYaHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What struck me is that in 1920 the KKK had 10,000 members in Long Beach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terribolin2 Terri you really don’t believe that reading is a parallel to what we have in office now? The metaphor… https://t.co/gpTBaePIOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyLodge No joke: I was listening to a pre-season baseball game on the radio yesterday, and one of the announcers… https://t.co/LFPS4EiM2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredhoutsma looks like @mnwild wenr with the shutout loss instead of the blown lead loss tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook should NOT be allowed to consolidate with Whats App &amp; Insta. Facebook should be broken up. Fuck Zuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be mushy but i made a playlist for a girl back home before i moved and i never sent it to her and i listen t… https://t.co/53eGki7OJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just putting together some more information on my dungeon crap for a video.  This is just one of my boxes, of set d… https://t.co/4zpD76SbZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys don’t ask girls on dates now days, they’ll respond with “are you kidding me” and leave you on read for a f… https://t.co/k7Qx6CLs1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Rep. @steveholland16 for visiting @millsapscollege tonight for the Second Annual Steve Holland Senior Pol… https://t.co/mCGuUXX6PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich Border Patrol agents’ deaths fighting illegal immigrants also manufactured because they can’t cover wide s… https://t.co/Icrjo0b907]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved this story by @GregJaklewicz on @CourtneyPenry! Hope she rocks it this week on @AmericanIdol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_SanRoman @gamify_i @Flipgrid @DoInkTweets @FCSVanguard @andre_elz @Mrs_ABoyd @RodriguezRockss @NiaBTeaching… https://t.co/ZLX6EPGYfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @trscoop Yes, she is a member of a religious cult who’s doctrine is violence...seems appropriate t… https://t.co/Tgtzlqk1Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_dow your seem to think the small amount of whack jobs in the church represent the average. good luck to you as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five suspects stole five motorcycles from Metro East Motorsports in O'Fallon, Il early this morning. They drove off… https://t.co/xCBtpdfteq]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRIPLE SHOOTING w/1 CRITICAL- 37th Pl at Ely Pl SE-DC near the Fort Dupont Ice Arena. 3 male victims shot; 1 is in… https://t.co/5gJz1kJpaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[As close as I’ve gotten to “LOVE” ... Happy Valentine’s Day #stillsingle #williamsburgva #valentines… https://t.co/TfWPAKovzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterBeinart @realDonaldTrump @CNN @RepAdamSchiff @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib God Bless the Jewish State of Israel.The… https://t.co/XtIKgv1Acc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bojan_222 @TwitchGainMore Followed #15 pls follow mine https://t.co/xRarkLFPuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican Evangelicals today are REALLY WEIRD, I was told in one tweet because I’m a Liberal Democrat I need to re… https://t.co/sOYD7GsPyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shatel: Scott Frost does more than tout mentoring — he stepped up as a foster parent in Oregon https://t.co/tuQa4F9jBw via @owhnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteWeatherBeat @CNYcentral @SyracuseAirport 6 inches. Italy Hill Yates. Near Penn Yan.  #keukalake #fingerlakes… https://t.co/l9QrdYrjxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Oliver North is a traitor who betrayed the U.S., Ronald Reagan, Americans being held hostage in Iran, and Law… https://t.co/UA1sOessy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and then he snapped the tip off my glue when he was trying to "fix" things. 💩💩😖  #stronglikeox… https://t.co/7L3VXVrfSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alita in IMAX 3D way better than I was expecting!! @ IMAX At Pacific Science Center https://t.co/xe3OZxwZ2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XStreamFisher @TrapperTackle @chewcoffeedip @bigbass217 @MarTeaseLures @bassfisher3k @jb_mchale Greg, it will rema… https://t.co/viavlq64Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UhKneeSeeYa I look forward to assisting you. Thank you. https://t.co/effpHqtiwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 #TrumpVsProzac President John Adams qualified for Prozac https://t.co/4teGUqKvER]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thanksjohn for being my next-door office neighbor! Appreciated all those talks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhoop_5 @hoopinsider @ihss_dfw @SportsDayHS @PrepHoopsTX @DesotoMbb @dfwhoops @dfwvarsity @HSwfaa @TexasHoopsGASO… https://t.co/Uu5H1M5XHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFR95 This was the story for me today. The sheer dedication to getting this car race ready was incredible to way. Well done!👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacSnyder @TwotimesJoey @JeffRisdon My man hasn't even heard combine weigh in discussion apparently, lol.  It's al… https://t.co/BKgiAqEZQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason you don’t see hot sexy #blackmen #model for #CalvinKlein #underwear is because he’s #racist, but serious… https://t.co/sQf1UIYLiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get some really cool requests for #freesketches at @cosmiccomicslv #comicjam sometimes! #narwhal #sketch… https://t.co/WHeV40Y66p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileyvassalli @Kevin_Agee In fact, I’ve never been so alive. https://t.co/z7G2JkpLpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a tremendous privilege for Cheryl and I to join Japanese Ambassador Ishikane and his wife, Kaoru, in discuss… https://t.co/VNiNf6gGXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey man I’ve got some bad news. Those aren’t the only dogs she is walking, know what I’m saying #woof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Public_Citizen not sure if I will follow your Twitter account but I will definitely look into who funds your reporting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professor just asked if I'm taking care of myself because it "looks like I haven't shaved in quite a while." She's not wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump are you just making thing up again you say he's manuscript that is before it is… https://t.co/k1HRubjn1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The AES on smartphone is set to automatically repeat and remind.  If yours continues to go off after you have ackno… https://t.co/ATWkJ5Elp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood I wonder if he'll speak about it... "The 4th of July is also known as Independence Day... a lotta peo… https://t.co/R4Z5MfSczI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having seen the care that @AHAhistorians put into the annual cocktail naming competition, I respectfully ask @TPUSA… https://t.co/aLX2pHuHN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisFunko @FunkoPOPsNews @funkofinderz @FunkoPopNerds @FunkoPopHunters @ThePopPros @popcurated @slaypreme… https://t.co/epabudbPEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelRome I’m so sorry for your fam’s loss! Animals are just like family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @JustWhatNowWhy I stand with my fellow Okie. https://t.co/ewOOZKe7ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[That look when you sign a long-term deal in Philly that can’t go wrong. https://t.co/ZDJSFOUy7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardonMyTake I’m pretty sure the conspiracy theory for you guys being in cahoots is real becuase that’s the only w… https://t.co/nRhiECazKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump We will be a poor country indeed if we let this charlatan get away… https://t.co/OqAivTd8b0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t like cheddar-broccoli soup in any of its forms (e.g. vegan) I don’t trust you. 😒😂😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchDaWoof @TheKendar @codexrau @RacthetMechanic Don’t forget “Who gives amazing snuggles.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most remarkable thing about this is that there are still schools out there that haven’t offered.… https://t.co/fmcro4kRu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lutheran East celebrates its fourth straight district crown, second straight here for @LEFalconsHoops. https://t.co/BXsOJL7Lz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Koppa171 @vaughtsviews @BobAllenMotrMal @WTDistillery @MeltonsDeli2 @DBParksandRec @MommaMc3 @kaylamoore @wpbktim… https://t.co/GyvNdjuuUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddtalk I worked on Miannis bridge after Remember those caught fishing getting state rate?I have better stories t… https://t.co/owTzuMM8gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley @realDonaldTrump 🤔 Didn’t Obama declare National Emergency over swine flu?  (Don’t think either of… https://t.co/RiwopSGecJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Het is 18:17 en ik heb al zoveel gelopen vandaag: https://t.co/M5aVSqDUBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGigger I won't tell anyone what to believe. If you feel that it was paraphrased wrong or edited in a certain way,… https://t.co/mrKVf7fIL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are wounds that never show on the body that are deeper and more hurtful than anything that bleeds...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merrillbro @mikiebarb @FoxNews @NPR @washingtonpost How much is that journalism a beard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenWillRock "Hammer To Fall" is the only correct answer. #therecanbeonlyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganWorld Were you required to get a clearance when your father was president?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish our "necessary evil" would work harder for the people and not for the corporations https://t.co/39YKCOyjsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @Kaepernick7 Nike stock is doing very well..  and its one big loss for the @NFL.  #ReHireKap or its a wrap!… https://t.co/mWq5NyOjE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexhill77x Might be because of that Sabre’s helmet.. #WishMillerWasStillInNet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Ryan, this country is in some deep trouble. The way forward is not clear. Waving a magic wand and re… https://t.co/JnE9kDiS3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it. Please. We need someone sane in the Senate opposite of Blackburn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paisleytears @Lady_Vi_2U Soros, Podesta, Alefantis and Brock. And @TeenVogue @Cosmopolitan @Allure_magazine… https://t.co/qUJVItIpPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaCroixInt @MassimoFaggioli “Refusing to be part of” the Sandinista government?  He was in the cabinet of a Commun… https://t.co/1VYlhxdnTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a supply teacher &amp; you cannot “handle” a class maybe you should be doing something else. Just saying 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight IF YOU SHOW UP YOU GO UP #showupgoup @showupgoupla @ The DoJo of Comedy https://t.co/IH2DQrvyqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight attendant explains to a man, “I can’t give you a complimentary water. If I give you one, I’ll have to give e… https://t.co/jGauLOaa1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Getting two Nigerians to help set up a hate crime hoax:  $3500. Bail for sniffling faker punk Jussie Smolle… https://t.co/064NFXkfGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter Maybe they should contribute to the conversation here on Twitter by saying that from their official account... oh, wait...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eva on valentines day @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/idKJdCcMx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure your tits are out today. Nobody has to see them but they gotta be out on gang.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/irgtNOaoLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElayneBoosler 2 1/2 years in office and still thinks the Oval Office was named for President Oval. At least for co… https://t.co/cGdcUjwpsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachFore @theekid13 @blastathletics I agree, Coach! James has been a tremendous help to our fundraising efforts… https://t.co/kn1Q0lN54H]]></document></documents></author>