<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Want to write me a ticket? Go to the police academy and graduate then you can write me a ticket.   Ouch.   #LivePD #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everythingloria @bryannamar0421 👏 As a Muslim, I feel this deeply - writing the sort of complex, multi-faceted, ke… https://t.co/o9qLLcTxYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Sold for hefty “adoption” fees, or incarcerated for equally large fees to the buddies of #DJT. Someone… https://t.co/D5TPGVrid1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The actor, seen in this video, reportedly apologized after being slammed by multiple groups and law enforcement inv… https://t.co/Vy57XSQapW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All famous people are aliens and we’ve been idolizing them since the start of human existence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aenergiebewust @davidhogg111 Not allowing nations to decide who gets to enter their borders. Not allowing reporter… https://t.co/QzU01oGSBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markondefense @JerryHendrixII @ConsWahoo Thanks! I hope there will be a debate, instead of Congress flat-out rejecting the proposal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWuori This is heartbreaking thank you for shedding light on the issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah new rule if you bring disappointing sex to the table, you have to buy her a bottle of wine it’s only fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanyGarciaCo I know! I’m sad too. He’s one of our strongest players and great with everyone on the team. What was the point of that trade?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogue_corq  Friends; I am a former Soviet attorney, please read my No. 92 -- Ripping the Mask off KGB Activity in… https://t.co/d4G6jfwQvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not sought out any information on the current Kardashian/Jenner drama, yet I know E V E R Y T H I N G. It’s… https://t.co/EjovsEjwrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 9am and I’ve already had 2 people tell me they want me to ruin their life..🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really want to talk about how emotional today’s Steve Irwin Google doodle made me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[we brought a fresh take on the mismatched chair concept. so often we see it done in a vintagey vibe. thought it wou… https://t.co/1WhiGEojhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember a couple years ago at trade deadline? IDK if it can get much worse than the Spring of Shattenkirk....… https://t.co/5HLRVJL1yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey this is your daily reminder that love is canceled and people are gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcelaFeudale Si fue demasiado la trataron muy mal ningún respeto ni consideración]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like Pina Coladas.... @ Bushwaller's Pub https://t.co/roRxC8zp9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this back exercise, give it a go! Returned early this morning from Miami. Got about a couple hours of sleep be… https://t.co/b5tIhGl016]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 years ago today I was gifted phil( my fish) so by default today was his birthday. I get overly attached to my ani… https://t.co/Nbc0D0rIHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Global Women’s Day!!! Let’s celebrate each other regardless of our differences,  race, social status or sexua… https://t.co/P778CrJfvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A word to House Democrats. Do not be afraid to take on Trump's advisors who happen to be his children. This is just… https://t.co/RQLBAoTiAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually I do a dress or T-shirt + jeans but decided to try jeans + a sweater today. I like it? Also picked up new 🎧 https://t.co/I8kyvD4wPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you guys got your #bookhaul yet?? Come on down to @BNMontclair and get some great titles up to 50% off maybe e… https://t.co/KXf71l62FW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca busques la aprobación y menos donde no te quieren. Si no te reciben bien, vete; La amistad no se comora, nace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could be dinner wine talking - but I'll say it.  We have a particular "climate" in America at this moment.  Rage is… https://t.co/aYBKdoTIGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primer dia de maestra en asesorias de español 😉 Te he enviado una ubicación: Estás aquí. Conduce hasta ahí usando W… https://t.co/rDOujScKKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer is the air that multiplication breathes! #churchmultiplicationcollective]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been there done that LEARN YOUR LESSON for the love of god y’all gotta do better if not for you, for your kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick and tired of this cold weather, I wanna wear sandals and tank tops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanblinder I just read a post anout that meeting.  My mouth hit the floor and its still there. This is just unreal. #SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Dirty Rotten Scoundrel is the most perfect movie ever made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @jonasbrothers - year 2019 ft. @JKCorden 🥰😍😍😂😂😂❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾   @kevinjonas… https://t.co/DtqHlJL5Xt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a #MidWeek Pick Me Up? #wednesday #WednesdayWisdon #DailyPrayer 6.45a EST 5156033171 access 381150#… https://t.co/vLFCGb0thy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @AnneMilgram Please take a few seconds and watch this ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a single bad thing written about Luke Perry. Sorry for my 10 followers. I’ll stop and tomorrow I’ll be back to… https://t.co/pWxPJ4azer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/AHVsMS8blN https://t.co/QTFEcLddwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are not just here for the food..... But we got hungry waiting for @duttypaul #mardigras #gumbo #catfishpoboy… https://t.co/A7WGJqULaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamFar @_Parker_O_ @chandler100995 @Eclipse_74 @MexiCould @Supreme_Owl_FTW @ACLU I adopted. I'm grateful the b… https://t.co/k3x0V5NhDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmprowell I attended @nbcc Project LEAD in 2017. It was an excellent intensive course on research advocacy, taught… https://t.co/c2t17QjPeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[guy at my bar today said “I bet you grew up with brothers, didn’t you”  I said “no, it’s just me” and he responded… https://t.co/Q2LtC4joAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammaciag @billycurrington Troy @SineadOconnorHQ Actually the whole album is so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how much Trick Master made me want to break something in Kingdom Hearts 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy show week, over next 7 days, 7 shows. Double dip today. "Inside Pitch" with Scott Braun on Sirius 209 XM 89 (2… https://t.co/mJbWabV0aL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyTumbleweeds I follow back !! VIP on #TeamMAGA #BackTheBlue #SaveTheBabies #KAG2020  #MAGAVET    It's follow for follow friends !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do men totally shirk responsibility and decisions of pregnancy?If u perform an act that leads 2a baby, u are re… https://t.co/2KHpEBMQLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So downtown Mpls. Showing this. So proud of our city. https://t.co/358mKCZHXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen concierto en @AguaCalienteCRS @broncojoseadan @broncolupe @Grupo_Bronco @broncoramiro @broncorene @broncojavo… https://t.co/1jApID6ff2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alilbrittoffun I gave it one full season and then I was like ok every one in this family can go jump off a cliff, I’m over this turmoil 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How easy it is to invent a humanity, for anyone at all. What an available temptation.”                The Handmaid… https://t.co/1uCXEvJhQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I imagine my bro’s gf be telling him when she’s mad, lol...  https://t.co/nv1hYO34Vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mstone0954 @Kybelle1957Liz @EnragedApostate @cspanwj @IndependentInst This is the Emergency...Not some made up Ill… https://t.co/zl1OYXpprn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Def lawyer-like. Better than 90% of the other lawyers who questioned him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunGalNews @tmj4 It’s 41 in Stockholm, Sweden, right now And a whopping -6 in Atockholm, Wisconsin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaRage @jeffieboy77 I mean, a good sweaty workout is pretty satisfying... 😏💦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaterDocs @Alex_Verbeek @tveitdal looking for to seeing Autumn Peltier receive her Water Warrior Award from… https://t.co/32n4G0GNY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was so thirsty in my sleep i kept dreaming about trying to find this bottle of juice i had lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kirpa better be the next Bachelorette, she knew what was up and I’d love to see another WOC as the Bachelorette. Sh… https://t.co/5O3kR86NOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro just saw you on @colbertlateshow - you were great! Respect you so much. I may not always agree with you… https://t.co/qsEiuhIdEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[More on #rkelly:  there’s no #doublejeopardy- prior prosecution was on #childpornography charges (jury couldn’t pos… https://t.co/pUYUs0HEgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[laughter is good medicine. #funniness #laugh #grin #playful https://t.co/sGJCgSFtCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[5-9 pm. Tonight. Support our Lac Boys!!! @ebhslacrosse https://t.co/oTB9PFps3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK @tribelaw WTF does he mean with “little bit”? His statement is as ridiculous as his justification]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrNickOFMConv Yes, I think it is. JMHO!  I would think you would have more time for priestly “stuff,” and for shar… https://t.co/dqP9ta4q6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easyecoach Yes.  People would be shocked at the amount some folks have on their school “tab”.  And so few folks un… https://t.co/J6KuI7hs5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no interest in being at work or typing/closing cases. I feel like shit and I just want to be laying in bed w… https://t.co/hJ1tMSw35h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:   Five year old me: I should marry my pony https://t.co/KR43WcKbU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[chuckle with me for a bit. Robert Doisneau (April 14, 1912 – April 1, 1994) was a French photographer noted for his… https://t.co/y7qvaAXzC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just entered for a chance to win tickets to #BayNites! https://t.co/i6Bo1OYnAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VoteBlueNoMatterWho but in the mean time I want my #GrandkidsToHaveGrandkids I want a survivable 🌎! #GreenNewDeal… https://t.co/WMGwtbncdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made some 420 pendants 😋✨ Round one is sold but other two are available! $8 shipped today. Can be made into a nec… https://t.co/7Y9sS66SPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoiled on Valentine's day!!  #SpoiledSampson #AdoptDontShop #RescuedIsMyFavoriteBreed #ValentinesDay2018… https://t.co/5jbczG4V6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaritanaVyrds I`m Professional crystal cup manufacturer、if you need pls contact me .all of my products are handmad… https://t.co/A9npUUNq2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard a bird chirping today and if that doesn’t give life to your cold winter heart idk what will]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy with AirPods judged me so hard for having regular headphones. I feel like a noob :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarincom Se eleva a juicio oral esta causa tan politizada, que sin testigos en contra, sin ninguna pericia en con… https://t.co/4ucUKZEB5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachWritesStuff @GimsonSusana wow, I used the patches (or tried to ) for months, my husband works for our state DO… https://t.co/hj70cUlcVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rice_And_Stew Smh u just gave me anxiety. I’ve yet to open the AirPods my brother got me because I’m scared I will… https://t.co/l1Mkabje7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 15th birthday to my lil baby!! hope your day is the most special, i love you day!!🥳💕@DayneyEaton https://t.co/wNZsOW0MiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOldPathTV Guest from North Los Angeles Locale Chapter #NorthAmBibleExpo   @mcgidotorg]]></document><document><![CDATA[FRAUDS EXPOSED: AOC found thru Casting Call! 5 Dems recruited-Political ... https://t.co/oUoyR63w2x via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraRanger @StephB617 @MenaGP1226 @stardust1006 @EByzio @mrjafri @_Cristian_Vlad_ @LauraMacDB @LeeLeeskeewee… https://t.co/QvWAxNGtnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creek Water Official After Party with Yelawolf https://t.co/tSJW4UC1VM Let’s Rage this Friday Night!!! Can’t wait!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peggyjane59 @SealsLax @nllwarriors That’s Captain Matt Beers for ya.. Such a class act move there. It’s such a sma… https://t.co/svA1acXLYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people deserve to get punished for the way they move cause they clearly need to learn a lesson or two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXNashville This is the best video I have seen all week!!  I love when kids do things for others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those trying to use the 25th Amendment should look in the mirror.  This is certainly a deflection from their own is… https://t.co/sRsjwXn5JE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Cendejas @SFBART It’s bc I was gonna get it through the dealership 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who’s son needs to hear this but clip your toenails before you go on spring break. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Shelby 💛🐶 and McQueen 🍫🐶 #NationalLoveYourPetDay #LoveYourPetDay #labradorretrievers https://t.co/uZvaa2tRaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beyabean I request the rest—you can’t just stop at a cliffhanger like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning orchestra rehearsal. @ First Baptist Church Opelousas, Louisiana https://t.co/z1ICJc5PZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only stage he lives for! #southsiderebellion #cwatrained #rebelyell @ Bankers Life Fieldhouse https://t.co/pAWY0Kthu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleeping with other people is one of the best rom coms ive ever seen like super relavent and relatable and hilarious but emo too :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joyous surprise seeing these lovely faces today! #brunch #family coconutroot @ Capitol Diner https://t.co/zejiUr6pA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the folks in the community tonight really spoke out. There chants were so powerful. We stood as one united… https://t.co/sG0wAzUWkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For me, the most impressive thing isn’t achieving balance but questioning it.” ~ @taniaisaac on Symmetry… https://t.co/Em0PoGeITX]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mans: i’m hungry  me happily getting him food even though i have no money]]></document></documents></author>