<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So much love felt this birthday week! Thanks for the surprise guys! Shout out to my beautiful other birthday girl f… https://t.co/nUvDPwTV05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittanyKOB can you please share a link to the story you did on the missing mini horse. I want to share it with my… https://t.co/wWDpYU8lnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I'm 15:13 into the video. I think I'll watch the whole thing. Duty-bound, it feels!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numbers never tell a lie  DM me on @instagram for promo https://t.co/oNlveC79OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was so fun got to high 5 @HawkeyeHuddle2 which doesn't happen as often as it should #SCtop10 #GoHawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the only time I would vote would be if the death penalty for harming dogs was being voted on to make legal was on the ballet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait hold uhhh ... lil cray just posted a track on SoundCloud !!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 points to @PhillyPolice for this tweet, slyly slipped in just after snow season, and never participating in… https://t.co/LRfw2fsMIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como no dejan entrar banderas grandes al estadio  en pro d generar un ambiente festivo,me gustaría proponer el q la… https://t.co/HYC7GZNJMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Band name idea: Deciduous Spleen   I’m just an idea guy, you’re going to have to run with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaBannister11 @RyanAFournier None of those arrests had anything to do with Russia. You people amaze me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter If you’re so much better... why don’t you run for office... if you really think you can do better. Go for it I will vote for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kateesackhoff As a sober male.  He is pretty damn awesome.   Buy the puppy treats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See this is such a reach. Admitting in the writing trump isn’t party to the collusion but still wanting liability.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey @viewfromE @JustinTrudeau That means if Quebec people believe it they are shit hole people who should go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi @washingtonpost @realDonaldTrump is interested in keeping one promise. The building of the… https://t.co/hiv6yxmIil]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PBPitch   JURASSIC MARK Mark’s a shy kid who copes with the stresses of school by imagining himself as various din… https://t.co/32vFmOwRCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlesteven_ug @officialslimjim @tifftiffanyvske good night steve little have great time all night long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao get you a wifey, your own crib, and duck off. Best thing I ever did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @WhiteHouse Wasn’t she supposed to quit or leave and why is she still there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[... not only was he not European (he was EXTREMELY American), he was arguing with someone on the phone about his st… https://t.co/g3nly4nCxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aydenmillar @NorthPoleHoops I had them on the bubble in our rankings the past 4 weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OddSpaServices a full body massage while they play William Hung music  https://t.co/x6WilyVMUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlutinoFoods Your new Multigrain bread isn’t as good as it was before. What happened? Not improved! https://t.co/7iq6siJzrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanwitopa @ClueHeywood @MelissaJPeltier It’s improper to refer to any elected official by their former title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller this sucks my device isn't compatible with the link up! Weei here were I live broadcast the bruins game!… https://t.co/icCMUItu1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport (SEA) in Seatac, WA https://t.co/fdxCQIOBHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraveForGaga95 I love when you sang shallow it's like you cried out! for help for the people with mental illness i… https://t.co/VBV9HsGKXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who pay regard to vain idols, forsake their hope to steadfast love - Jonah 2:8 ESV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvdvdguy @WarnerArchive @JulieAndrews A GP Rated classic. GP is my favorite MPAA rating before it was changed to P… https://t.co/12m1QEpsoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶"Baby, you don't have to rush. You can leave a toothbrush at my place."🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jlane_22 Did you think that last goal was a good goal in the shootout?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunsets from the lake. Nice to see you again old friend. The long days of summer will soon return.… https://t.co/nbYGamUeoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullTimeHoops1 @roygayhart @LAOKEITH @rj_rowan_42 So basically whoever the best player on the team who wins the op… https://t.co/lzCN7hJXe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized... 5 years later... That's so crazy to think about...  #LateNightThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gamerinthehive @RE_Games @samhughes88 Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian mus… https://t.co/tSi0O7qEJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So was the basic plan for Universe that roughly each season would be in a new galaxy, and each new galaxy would hav… https://t.co/XLAP2TBFpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganOrtagus Gotta have them before they get banned😂 https://t.co/G5Jh1c3zMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Connecticut Avenue &amp; Aspen Hill Road in Silver Spring, MD https://t.co/DesI4zBgzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boundy_Boy @matthewmercer They are currently at the point  where they could make it a six episode miniseries at th… https://t.co/OsNra0WRCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇲🇽En las encuestas de Twitter sucede lo mismo que las encuestas realizadas por el financiero. (Va a predominar la p… https://t.co/lkLzB31KLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t ever been handed anything..taste better when you make it yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[😢 Gutted by the loss of @BrodyismeFriend. First saw him @bridgetown and he quickly became my favorite comic. His po… https://t.co/UUb9VC8Fuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is as good a day as any to evaluate your mindset - keep your head down and focus on the task at hand!… https://t.co/yzbqfTBmSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight savings time made going to the gym less desirable this morning. But I went and had a good squat workout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake has found favorite game at @ChuckECheeses https://t.co/VTxlBe0pKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You were made to overcome and every misfortune will be to your benefit...@fulfillhiswill]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at A Second Chance Designer Resale Boutique in New York, NY https://t.co/ZSCHEMlC7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@subielifeluke @cohickb Shut up Lucas I didn’t get invited to the pool building :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump DHS SECRETARY OF STATE  FBI INTEL CIA  DOH OBAMA  CLINTON'S   THAT SWAMP ALL INTERTWIN… https://t.co/RUhGn11zqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @MobileTrakMike - JACKKNIFED SEMI on 270 East at US 23, North side.  Stay LEFT to get by.  #TrafficAlert… https://t.co/VhbujS02zD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicnewsfact @ArianaGrande Sis hit us w something in like 6 months we need to recuperate first 🧐💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vroncal @delpor1 Héctor “ porcelanato” es el capitán del equipo, lo mejor que tienen para mostrar, por algo perten… https://t.co/J1ZICeuxe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks:  OC to Chicago to OC to Hawaii to LAX to NYC to OC to Ind and back!  Both work and play, but not best pl… https://t.co/fSycHvyBnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow traffic in #Raleigh on I-440 WB between Hillsborough St - Exit 3 and Western Blvd - Exit 2, accident at Western Blvd - Exit 2 #traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs to shut her pie hole she don’t know what the hell she’s a dumb bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader.” - John Quinc… https://t.co/pes2pzuX27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human being is wicked and arrogant to fellow human being,forget that he was created from less value organism live a… https://t.co/aIytK09WeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A picture worth a thousands words. Evan meets Woody and Jessie. @ Toy Story Land https://t.co/LOBlCD2C8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning to belong...become through Education: "If you don't know who you are, how are you supposed to find your pl… https://t.co/uADu0S8pU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Kevin told us George Bernard Shaw started his career as a music critic, and I couldn’t stop picturing it https://t.co/1pplmR0oOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d say this disease has already made the jump over to Republicans, especially the orange one in the White House!… https://t.co/xrwrFPO4Am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa. Nothing makes you feel older than seeing a movie you've been meaning to get around to show up Next on TCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CabayeLovesHugs For all those hating on #CPFC especially during transfer windows, this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashSevereWx Thought we had really enormous dams for a moment, then I noticed the “NOT TO SCALE” bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering @biggiesmalls today! It’s been 22 years since he passed. #BiggieSmalls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @CPAC You are a joke, the epitome of fake christianity, you lock children in cages, you will burn in hell if th… https://t.co/JI5dlDjZfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bell_sms Sure you drink angry orchard and and party at medieval games.. but at home maintain montone with 60fps of fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamamin I’m with Aviral right now, he wants to know when we’re hanging next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate. Cole slaw at @GreenSpaceCafe1 Cabbage #cabbage.  Why so happy?  Because it is one of two vegetable types… https://t.co/PWOcZ4LWqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smb #Entrepreneurs #EmployeeEngagement #HumanResources #CTO #CFO Offering More Money to Your #Employees Isn't Enou… https://t.co/MJYb3zsGn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rescuegal @AuthorMBTosi @cselston @wbellauthor @Native_Shadows @CasamentoArrigo @CarolineMCook1 @wordrefiner… https://t.co/1V11b8Dy2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to celebrating 44 of the 45 Presidents today!  Still mad at James Buchanan. He knows why... #PresidentsDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever since melly got locked up everyone all of a sudden wanna be alllll on his shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami, FL - (AP) Friday March 8th, “Spring in the Garden | Overtown” Live Performance by Grammy Award Nominee… https://t.co/Iur8fdvgNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler4510 @_SJPeace_ Well yeah. Water does rile up the tRump base like a Wall does.  They are all racists and hateful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneFallenAngelM @AllVape3 @samrulestheworl @NeilSamra1 @franic420 @Pastabowl2 @StephaniedeJag3 @Smokette_… https://t.co/g24UqBrGmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery Hmm 🤔 socialist list like another list from times past? This is a sign of leftist evil in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJMcKean Spielberg: Schindler’s List, Raiders of the Lost Ark, Jaws, Saving Private Ryan, ET  Drama Action Horror War Family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ablem61 @xvzla2009 @Jhonatanro @LocaLuzCaraball @_Gabbyta_ @GiuseppeNoc @iam_pretender @JusticiaDorada @Sibadongo… https://t.co/Chyk5jjkWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayBlake20 Same af! If I have kids they ain’t going at 15 tho that’s for sure 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll see where we’re all at by the time we hit between the ages of 24-26 though 🧐💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC WELL THAT STINKING JUDGE AND THAT F"ED UP OLD MAN WHO CALLED HIMSELF A FATHER I HOPE ARE BOTH ROTTING IN HEL… https://t.co/GQmAs8vb1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[joanne was good, i dont give a fuck what u fags say joanne was an EXCELLENT ALBUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tac1991 @AlexaGreenNews Plus the E logs made the market tighter this last year, causing drivers to get paid more. Don’t understand this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ava @PeteButtigieg has impressed me more than any candidate thus far. Articulate, thoughtful, brilliant progressiv… https://t.co/gffS4BKjcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshJepson @GrandPOOBear I mean... there are USB / USB-C ports. It’s not the craziest idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Cena in @JCLayfield defense Orlando Jordan wasn't large or oilly #SmackDown298]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett just some friendly advice from a true #MAGA2020 believer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ted's Cafe Escondido - Broken Arrow - @tedsbrokenarrow in Broken Arrow, OK https://t.co/GnMZK08CqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InterroTalks That’s extremely disappointing for our community. Despicable behavior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great day talking football with some of the best high school coaches in Michigan and Indiana. Thanks to the… https://t.co/P9oDg2Y2yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squeaky was all over the kitchen as I cooked #okonomiyaki for the first time. All those new and delicious smells! I… https://t.co/ZNVMJT12l1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncohen1995 I have a value for each team's Home Court that is added in when comparing to their opponent.  I simply… https://t.co/7237Uj10Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[THAT is, and has been my concern, American/Mom. We're Really not much smarter than were the Rwandans in 1994, when… https://t.co/KWwnwQSmZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire planet is fuckin melting, animal species are dying at an alarming rate, Muslims in China are literally l… https://t.co/6WtHufmFsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BELATED BORN DAY TO WILLIAM CLEMENT FRAWLEY AKA FRED MERTZ OF "I LOVE LUCY! (R.I.P)  William Clement Frawley … https://t.co/nRTcpaUKcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaBoiTonio_ https://t.co/XkttuwMuDK hmu we can do playmaking slasher vids we to raw out here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haddonfield opens with back to back dunks and a 3 ....Haddonfield 10 Barnegat 2 with 3:46 left in 1st quarter]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡‼️New On The Market‼️  -  💰197,500  -  3 Bed 🛏️ | 2 Bath 🚿 | 2,384 SqFt 📐 | El Dorado High School🎓  -  📥Inbox me f… https://t.co/ho3A0ky3pS]]></document></documents></author>