<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@island__lion @iamahawk5083 @johnpavlovitz @AOC @guardian I'm fine with adoption as an option. HOWEVER, that still… https://t.co/3JxEO0c38k]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To be a Christian without prayer is no more possible than to be alive without breathing.” - Dr. Martin Luther King… https://t.co/gJ5VJ9YMgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a cold 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🥶 🏖 blustery day out on the pier at https://t.co/JlxQyPt8u4 and the beach / board… https://t.co/FRIF0jmKqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If #GoBolts win tonight AND any of these happen:  #GoHabsGo lose in regulation #CBJ lose in regulation BOTH lose in… https://t.co/wrP3tIygPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scrumhalf1 @_SJPeace_ @AOC You also forgot that he called less fortunate or “poor country’s” sh*tholes too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grove City Christian starters   Lukas Hamilton  Brayden Holbrook  Taylor Stauffer  Timothy Sullivan  Garrett Baker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texastigerpaw @GamecockBasebll When I was in Clemson the other day, beautiful day, now they are saying we won’t ha… https://t.co/R4SBe0EiGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Is the Democratic Party primary becoming like the Kentucky Derby? Every candidate great but were dealing… https://t.co/tERzqKkWYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Trumpster!!  Please tweet the President and ask him NOT to sign the GARBAGE being sent to him. It is full of… https://t.co/I5ghY0aX2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's obvious they don't want fame or credit for their cowardly and racist attack. I thought they would be 'proud' o… https://t.co/cG1sXNeqtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew preordering this phone would be a bitch on @TMobile   One thing I loved about Sprint, (Which was a LOT) was… https://t.co/1Vb1PH3A8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fuckin this money n I don’t wanna pull out, I fell in love w the racks 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nightfall #yul #photographer #giglife #waiting @ Maple Leaf Lounge https://t.co/JwD9DMRXGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting back my strength little by little ⚡️ #humpday https://t.co/cFX4IwaiAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it me or is it more uncomfortable dancing at parties when there’s hella people there that ain’t from your school?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Arizona defeats UMASS-Lowell 20-5 to sweep the four game series.  Quinn Flanagan gets the victory for the Wi… https://t.co/UOkMe00DXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[from [zen], 2019 ... . . . . . . . #contemporaryphotography #fineart #architecturephotography #zen #wood #nature… https://t.co/RyjDuYL3YG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YANiROxUrWORLd Nah, cause then you get some clowns mix tape instead of the song you want]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapNegative @Giants2019 @Giants True, but what kind of product are you selling to the customers. At least a new QB… https://t.co/jxsS0GJfGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[MJ Hegar lost her bid for U.S. Congress in 2018.  Wendy Davis lost her bid for Texas Governor in 2014.   Yet both a… https://t.co/hgyYUnPJmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiniebeany And ALWAYS the need to BOAST about his own role. Stopping just short of saying ‘Obama couldn’t do it but I did it...’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in the back row with a Gatorade bottle: Hey dudes! Look at us just wizzing thru Fort Worth! Them: 🦗🦗🦗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senarosalie I would’ve Literally Donated to them. Your loss. Way to be the bigger person.  Donated 118$ to Candida… https://t.co/rTx4EPTh1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get 3 Amigos graphic to see if they can make me a t shirt 👕 like my cup. Still waiting!! @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/Vyak7mMmSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:4 2 Thessalonians And we have confidence in the Lord about you, that you are doing and will do the things that we… https://t.co/ANOzibQVSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep  Greer at Podium talking about the money he has paid to repair two family automobiles as a result of hitting po… https://t.co/otk9kyrW0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel You, David and Jacob Wohl make a nice threesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDebATL Well it was told to me by the ranger who talked to him so they told story in detail but he said it was a nice experience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Beautiful morning floating over Sutro tower @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/NciaSujXwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is the kind of argument that needs to lead the discussions on this subject.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna go to parties on the weekend, I don’t want to drink. Let’s go to the zoo. Let’s go to museums 😍🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 It’s worth our while to assume that Trump is always performing for his father and Roy Cohn. Always. His… https://t.co/QMu9esJpOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Unidad 🌉 #mtycity #mx #atirantado #bridge #atirantadobridge #invertedbob #oldpicturesinmyphone @ Puente Atiranta… https://t.co/gWK4pGMCL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: more people have left but I am going to stay. This is my penance for my sins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I discovered I’m down to fight when I’m drunk if you disrespect my squad idc if you talk bout me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JameyGoodman @Dawgsfan34 @Deblg1G @ALiferGaDawg @abparrish083 @Betweenthehedge Same here]]></document><document><![CDATA[How was Mathew Brady influenced by portrait painting? What role did inventor Samuel Morse play in his life? How man… https://t.co/9wFcCk8MQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Division II Quarters - Glastonbury 74, Bunnell 69 https://t.co/Pwl7BOy8ev #ctbb via @ciacsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmarch63 's 2nd assist of the game (Grzelcyk's tying goal) set a new career-high (52) for him. 60+ seems within re… https://t.co/6O2YI4voyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of your @BF_District team is out recruiting today. We do ❤️ @northerniowa teachers! https://t.co/gYRsjc1dlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court documents say Bushkin has prior weapons charges and is suicidal. His family allegedly had his cleaning lady c… https://t.co/lqSFimxklh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimePinkynm Drove all the way from Santa Teresa, NM to New Braunfels,Texas and my Grandkids ask me why I didn’t b… https://t.co/x5URsPDI2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastiankurz @IvankaTrump @usembvienna What a sad bunch of stupid shameless ignorant criminals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Head Sketch #Commissions are open! Available in 5.5” x 8.5” or 8.5” x 11”: $60 plus S&amp;H. Pick Up available for… https://t.co/7HR4PjurH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioSportsNet @Make_YourCase Do it. Old guys can't sustain success and are more prone to injury. I'm not sure why… https://t.co/DXj89Rmv0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your friend takes a whole handful of takis out of your medium sized bag https://t.co/kDom33JmcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @RachaelCavalli @dreamofkylie_  @nastynatxxx @Emily_Balfour @dakota_skyexxx 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/uh4ZDWkTeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcgilh @DeeShor47114331 Just hang out at Starbucks with a soy latte - wear headphones and just text. You’ll fit right in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magagary687 @ord3001 @Rainbow_Whisper @KimberlyMrsRR1 @cjdtwit @evewhite5500 @LizLiz_Di @KatTheHammer1 @MissILmom… https://t.co/ikV9xCB60u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me feel a little better that Penn State is making every 3 they put up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson I took my kids there years ago, once and never again. That place really puts the ‘chuck’ in chucky cheese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[02:56 Temp. 48.7°F, Hum. 65%, Dewp. 35.4°F, Bar. 30.22 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 186° 1.6 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump But...but...it’s a 🚨 NATIONAL FREAKING EMERGENCY 🚨... or nah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a dope and really cool day overall! But here's a highlight.  Been waiting over a year to get back in with… https://t.co/485kytfiYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathowie I have repeatedly asked Apple to stop trying to autocorrect proper names]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm No Superhero: Encapsulating My Placenta for Postpartum Healing. Lots of great sources #mirth #tee-hee #smile… https://t.co/MEddNupKQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perezreverte Joder Arturo, me quito el cráneo😳😳😳😳.....no obstante éste mitinero del tres al cuarto va a probar su… https://t.co/90OPijRRoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[We pursued this story because many progressive voters and candidates have told us that the moment to elect a populi… https://t.co/wDj0zrLHkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madonna @ladygaga @JRart You were born this way, and you are proud to say, I know everybody has their own way to say "I Was Born This Way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesKhanTV @DanikaXIX or you could just put it somewhere else in the star wars galaxy, unconnected to known  ch… https://t.co/PlFqZgvsCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie These right-wing radio talkists toss around terms they barely understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lovely and beautiful @Bluebunny_03 is online. Stop by to say hello and follow at https://t.co/92KDayJ5QR Don’t… https://t.co/m7rSnyPIrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbears51 @CraigMeyerPG Ok. I think ur son hung in there with the new coach.  I praise him for that.  My conversa… https://t.co/KqYXgc2gyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul_Casey @genesisopen @peterjkostis @NickFaldo006 Matthew... you’ve been playing some very nice courses! Need a caddie? 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Venice Beach - Venice Boulevard https://t.co/XGtf7rFFJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna start reading books. Business books specifically. To expand my knowledge in general + gaining knowledge in my field of study🤓🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNC +9 was the easiest bet of the month. Even if Zion isn’t hurt there’s no way Duke covers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @PxlJedi Jus how much monies have you or your companies received from UAE, Qatar, Saudi’s Arabia or t… https://t.co/YtljnoWtKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it seems obvious but I’m always shocked to learn how much baseball writers fucking love baseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldyvolsftbalfan @micahhhh @benfrey12 @vols80419 @MMercer21 They just said it but only 2 right handed hitters again… https://t.co/2Aj8Or9gAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lower Antelope Canyon ✅ @ Lower Antelope Canyon https://t.co/U1FWmQZGnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocean County St. Patrick’s Day Parade 2019 #wobm #radio #seasideheights #stpatricksday  _knights_of_columbus_… https://t.co/sOmC6Gf3gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Found Your Banana Republic Gift Card (Denver): Your the lady who lost her Banana Republic gift card aren't you? I… https://t.co/tVjmHU8a05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beave10 @woolford6624 Did you have your bare orifice skin on the phone or what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJane2019 @deolebear @Jessicasquared9 @KnowSmallParts @pismoeyedoc Lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bones5390 That’s because we drafted the right QB. If we drafted the wrong one and tried to correct a mistake I don… https://t.co/gXyADGLCLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi son las Fake News: "El Parlamento autoriza que Guaidó se ausente de Venezuela por más de 5 días". Parlamento?… https://t.co/PvFfIJcqlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all i just found out charlotte russe is closing forever and my heart has been broken]]></document><document><![CDATA[$20 to the couples who don’t post about how much they “love” each other all over social media today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to go to the bathroom.  Checks phone before laying back down...  😳  Well, looks like I’m wide awake now!  W… https://t.co/XjVi0o0G1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“chris said goodnight kissy face, what did kyle say?”  “he said wtf happened to the bathroom?” 💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NgSerinah Excuse me, I was poppin. You on the other hand though https://t.co/SQ5JuH1qFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thumbelulu So to clarify, “white” males lack empathy when creating stories about “POC” and females. And hierarchy is a bad thing. Correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning and Happy Monday from Grace and I. #gracelinette #happymonday @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/DwOVgPdRhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henrydicarlo Is the atmospheric river similar to the Pineapple Express that forecasters used to mention? How are t… https://t.co/UalEYHIkxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a paycheck from one job and direct deposit for the other is hitting tonight sooo yea this is the best Valentine’s Day I ever had]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XianJaneway @BlkCarmenSDiego @CybertronGuy98 @mmfa I'm so sorry for you! Shows you are a strong and smart person t… https://t.co/4ZudFzTkYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl What is a “ campaign surrogate” for DontheCon Trump as you call yourself?Dies that mean you are Trump’s surrogate mother?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idalia_ga En definitiva, fue el cansancio el culpable, realmente no fue tan mal día, mis 5 min de drama jajajaja p… https://t.co/EqmgpaRqRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icywinemixer Lot of body builders just tan the body and not the face but thats besides the point because it’s a co… https://t.co/gN5IcUHrrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clayshewey Just submitted a starting 5 of myself, Kyle Kuzma, Karl Malone, Rick Fox and of course, Gallagher. Good chance to win, IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s weird that short people got angrier at Randy Newman than rednecks did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Trump’s electoral college victory over a scandal ridden Hillary Clinton, those seeking a realignment narrativ… https://t.co/x0LeX2b7hD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind. Calm. Reasonable. That can't be TOO tough, can it? #Stoicism #Virtue #Happiness @ Plano, Texas https://t.co/OAecPBVnV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like silly ass Horror movies with great gore and a lot of laughs, I can't recommend Cherokee Creek enough. B… https://t.co/nuTfBAkSYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[As far as rest areas and welcome centers go, eastern Tennessee is one of the best.   Rocking chairs are always a go… https://t.co/MW9tBcgjLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blayne_Voorhees Son you would always come in talking wreckless to the o-line and ole dad would have to come in wit… https://t.co/XzTT4D2nYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 🌴😎☮️ Hey #CadetSluggoBoneSpurs #FatDonnie At least #SenatorBlumenthal… https://t.co/BSSXRWdIgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[INFJ Live in two versions WORLD of Deja-Vu and lucid dreams, withdraw in difficult periods of they life! Peace of v… https://t.co/jqQLwKrelh]]></document></documents></author>