<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[nope you was suppose to start college when you started! it’s YOUR path 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking immersive theatre sandwiches...or layer cakes... or maybe it's a multi-deck sandwich... with… https://t.co/ErFgnauK6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Model_Felly no! drinking or smoking might distract u from focusing on ur breathing and ur gonna want to be able to… https://t.co/ejn0xfVdg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[chuckle with me for a bit. homages to: braveheart. matrix. unforgiven. matt damon? american psycho. minority report… https://t.co/9Qmghllrnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domyboo @CCdiTitan @skipfrombk @belleneg Ticketmaster blocked me on my work computer. I just sent a request for th… https://t.co/Nmaxj0zmEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad i stopped to the store for sinus medicine i feel so much better😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_w_84 Because we NEED healthcare and fully funded schools and body autonomy and clean water and sick days and soc… https://t.co/nXnF7HGQLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waldemarkowal Niech się zboczeńcy i "geje" gejują w swoich sypialniach ile wlezie. Nikogo to nie obchodzi co tam r… https://t.co/purONaJHBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something We're Working on... #SayLess Produced by: @blackboi813  #BlackRaine is Coming Soon...  #NDVID #DarkStar… https://t.co/ozL7uLGl6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nowadays all I do is shine, take a breath and ease my mind, and She don't cry no more She tell me that I get her hi… https://t.co/GbNhsOY1sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a personal chauffeur so I won't have to drive long distances out of state. It will take me at least two days… https://t.co/a74nJLGDwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickiBarbolak Well somebody's happy about losin that hour. #DaylightSavingTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lathan was served his arrest warrants earlier today and he will be going though bond court tonight at 6:30 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Elisha Cash take home the title of Miss Jetset 2018 and be featured on the cover of Jetset Magazine! https://t.co/leOKWpu1su]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBO #WontYouBeMyNeighborPBS Was a great rendition to my friend Mr. Rogers. I did not grow up (in continental US) w… https://t.co/YT2vPUF8VL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hwmnylx69 @simms3710 @mhtexyankee @maydaymindy9 @leslievermeulen @ShineSalty @LuLuRoche @fransau30608291… https://t.co/FesbHCKYQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a beautiful home is everyone's dream. This dream can become a reality if you let me assist in the home buyin… https://t.co/RacUIeZVFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell My late husband was black. So my father had a black son-in-law. Doesn't mean my dad wasn't a flamin… https://t.co/wTMWK9WnRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCOTUS unanimously rules to limit state and local government's abilities to impose fines &amp; seize property. https://t.co/RCeZhm0c9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello @AmazonHelp I got the @hbo one month trial with prime yesterday and today I cannot watch anything. It keeps b… https://t.co/9Hdxz9CU58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTKNet If you took History in high school- you know all these things are BAD! We watched films of Hitler ordering… https://t.co/EqbI32Z3AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotelsdotcom #WinterSwearJar Nothing feels better in the dead of winter than cursing the f*#*ing cold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Tuesday: Got a late start and ran out of time so only 3.1 instead of 4.5 today. #rebuildhealthplexfitness … https://t.co/4Q0LwS91tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2 days I’ll be on my way to Massachusetts to go skiing with my Dad for a couple of days and I'm super excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovStitt I hope you shook the hands of some little girls and children of color too. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the end, every feminism ends up being a machismo with a skirt.  — @Pontifex, February 22nd, 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmPenn32 @brisdaleps You are so gorgeous there is no such thing as a terrible pic of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktwolf Ah ok. Yes @IlhanMN nailed him good when she had him in front of her committee]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk how you want me to act like and i just wanna be perfect for you. and i know me alone isn’t good enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collaborative teams meet weekly. They set their own agendas and use data from summative and CFAs to guide their dis… https://t.co/O7AJvKlrLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[First business meeting at the most beautiful place 😍 @ Miss Priss https://t.co/cOQCZOfDZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy cansada de esperar, debo reír, debo llorar. ¿Debo de amar? #buenasnoches]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notice the dirt streets.  I think this was when they were leveling off hills in early Seattle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Thankfully by the time 2020 comes around, @realDonaldTrump will have solved this problem... and you wont be President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol we do something similar to this in Workington. Uppies and Downies, and play every Easter with proceeds going to… https://t.co/BrP6dGt7Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the phrase “glamping on Navajo land” isn’t the epitome of whiteness idk what is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittyBhagat @IvokainKrieg @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @bunkybun @ChrisFDonahue @buell003 @Dennis_Lintz @KatG4… https://t.co/W0AQGK028K]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you in the guy friend zone please stay there until decided otherwise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpatt70 @Distinct_Words @TraciIrving1 I worked NICU. They do wonderful work on premies from 24wks. It’s exhaustive… https://t.co/R00cQzvZuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balance versus Harmony #choosetobehappy #visualize #chooseharmony #wagepeace #asabovesobelow #massagetherapylife ke… https://t.co/ZJsjD7PVuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting around at the apple store is such a bummer, says Lily.  @SantaMonicaPaws @AnneRoyy @AnimalBehaviorC… https://t.co/rH1gI1zNVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftyGlenn @Daylate10 @MoleskiA @iheartmindy @AOC Sadly, when presented with evidence, certain trumpettes and othe… https://t.co/cmS6uXNBh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5sos_military I'm already subscribe to your YouTube channel and I would love the treat people with kindness  hoodi… https://t.co/LkzHzsIYUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[CVH @EvensiFeatured is preparing to celebrate @JoAnnPDX @departures@7pm@drcynthialive JoAnn's friends say Congrats… https://t.co/V2ZfaPVSts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since tomorrow is International Women's Day I wanted to share this amazing female author and new @contodopress chil… https://t.co/4K7VYyE3MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the amazing staff and crew at The Warehouse and to photographer Scott Vincent for always capturing the… https://t.co/IVrbdfMj7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/k3qY329kb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-DC dinner with the parental unit... @acarlson1018 @PCOSGurl #whatsnext https://t.co/pFnaYMHrQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muaz_asperger42 @GBSection @GrandBlancHoops So many awesome kids in this photo!! @gbhtv 🖤❤️🖤❤️’s you all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Yes he does. Then someone needs to teach him what respect means]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycarmack1 @krassenstein @WendyDawe8 What is this gif? I’m trying to find the video but I don’t have the info to google it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three of my favorite photos from @mvhsjackets trip to the Woodward Opera House @mrC_MVHS @Jsan0900 @MVCSD_Supt https://t.co/QClgm1b3jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UnionSeminary is giving me hope for Christianity when I didn’t think I could find that today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mastery-based Learning has to be at the foundation of a 21st C Education and today can be made possible by technolo… https://t.co/KIxKwXls5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking into auto parts store Dad:just stand there and look Pretty Me:ok  auto parts guy asks a question i definite… https://t.co/EAMXeBfXWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bergerfromcali @Fbk1Kasey @TheEllenShow @3for3burpee @HilinskisHope 👍🏼👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/mDLD8eBAW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @RepRatcliffe @DevinNunes @RepGoodlatte @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @SenateGOP @FoxNews And you believe… https://t.co/Wilo6qR5sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Herbivore_18 @_AnimalAdvocate Im sick. This is just gruesome. People are horrible. If you eat veal, you are skum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Valentine ❤️🥰 Love my Westerville Sunrise Rotary mornings! westervillesunriserotary #valentinesday… https://t.co/PxBUlqneE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeckertRyan @penelope8226 @zeebranation I don't run with the "firm but fair thing." If she's fair then she doesn't… https://t.co/5n06FAc5ZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCEMSwatch But no increase of paramedics to assist?  I do not want to be in a disaster like the hurricane that hi… https://t.co/chvmpYCqeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IGotAPatentFor my soap box rants and made up words I use instead of cursing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 I know a few Republicans who aren't Racists but I don't know any Racists who aren't Republican.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar I thought of you when I saw this beautiful house! I do k ow there is one in LA also. M👑ch L💓ve❣ Hue an… https://t.co/iasHeTACmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[well this was an inopportune time to discover our satellite is covered in ice and can’t pick up the RPDR premiere 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tosca3333 @PeachesPomPom1 @Lamb123V @Free2BeeMee @Rosie_fluffybun @VitCza @Susansm70570449 @honeybun667 @Royboy24… https://t.co/EPhxYBfrpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOberg I'm abs shocked + distraught. Why isn't a single motorist stopping 2 help. Disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me the sparkle! This #DiamondNecklace from @kayjewelers is perfect for #ValentinesDay. https://t.co/OcFD6n8j0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t tease you, then we’re not really friends 🤷🏽‍♀️😂 https://t.co/SqqjOqdmHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mel23s @sharroyn @Ar_NKOTBfan4L @DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB @jordanknight Luke is coming to hershey in June! Cant wait… https://t.co/5NT7vaPcnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girlfriends are the best...Love you 🥂 @ Rosewood Sand Hill https://t.co/OmBsyMud6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cureisidaiamond CARIÑO QUE NO QUE ESTOY HABLANDO DE OTRA PERSONA JOE NO TENÍA NADA QUE VER CONTIGO SI TU SIEMPRE ME ABRAZAS 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfcookiemom got #GerritCole to sign his #ASG2017 jersey with @amazinggreis' help. #AgsWin #Astros #TakeItBack #MLB… https://t.co/agCxEhyf2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[French Mood-       ❤️❤ ️ Sunday in PARIS practically everything is closed. So what do you do?  👉 schedule visits to… https://t.co/RDYu7ibqry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Evidently they do.  What CBC consequences have they suffered before?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote vote vote! @alaysiashunice’s drive is unmatched! https://t.co/0xRQ3FH5Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the Rockets hang on? Catch the last :18 seconds now on #abc15 #nailbiter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news for @nreal_MR! I met them last Spring at an #AR Conference, tried &amp; super impressed w/their… https://t.co/Jg6fe9iivG]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUNDAY DINNER #SOLO @ Ena's Caribbean Kitchen, Inc https://t.co/I8c48euKD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s ok to seek professional help aside from the church(doctors, therapists...) don’t let the saints tell you other… https://t.co/Dj9b1XzGf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DETAILS: @AACOPD say last night's shooting at Arundel Mills Mall stemmed from a verbal altercation between two gro… https://t.co/vLzQHh4z1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[QUARTER OF A CENTURY 🌻  Year 25 is gonna be one for the books and it’s already happening. As I look back over 24, I… https://t.co/F8DL7q73Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cute if I was pretty so I can make tiktoks n become famous and make millions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estaba en México, sin un centavo  Me sentí un hombre de éxito  México uh oh, México uh oh  El destino me pintó el c… https://t.co/SMhoopBor8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megan Cottage completed the Princess Half Marathon! Time 03:06:17 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/KiD1At7FOk #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @JamesAGagliano Willi Cicci   “When the boss says push the button on a guy - I push the button, see,… https://t.co/TVWifoOK1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Valentine party of elementary school, ❤️🍎❤️🍎 https://t.co/RQdKZoLJCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick reminder to all, don’t forget to thank god tonight and every other for another day of life! Every day is a gi… https://t.co/83vBCYbcsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ishepherdducks @FrankFigliuzzi1 @mayawiley Same here. I seriously hope our electeds who received NRA money are inv… https://t.co/CqHgJYXEHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArielEpstein @ECUPiratesFB @SouthCentralHS @wcti12 Yes indeed! I have seen him bounce back time and time again! #sportsmom #falconmom]]></document><document><![CDATA[And right to be deported. Raise your concerns in FOREIGN country,  not in the country you belong to! Try Canada, Au… https://t.co/i3HGoDsPFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[my english professor for this semester is cool and everything but her assignments are so confusing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share to Facebook  Share to Facebook  New Jersey - I am a New Jersey girl and I used to be proud of it. I imagine t… https://t.co/21ESsn6seo]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THE BEAUTIFUL SOUL THAT IS @MissPrimaDonnaa MAY YOUR DAY SHINE AS BRIGHT AS YOU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en New York, New York https://t.co/xtGOxdhzUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orionpower2001 @Frankly_Emily @jessicaverdi @LaurieMichelleJ @AlizaPearl @Hyper_RPG Yayyy!!!! I can't wait for next week!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenTrulyLuLuu @micaylahtweets @norvina1 We support each other in this community girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #US. I put Pompeo and Bolton on mute. No more tweeting them to you guys. #Tatiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love love love ❤️ Soooo proud of you both and the years you guys have spent working together @jburris27… https://t.co/U0EcKwFrT0]]></document></documents></author>