<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TOwolfpack @TOXIII This could be @yeahdamav 50th game for the @TOwolfpack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babchik @EvCoRadio that one is on Tim. Everyone knows Babs is a dirtbag, so I don’t know why he expected anything… https://t.co/vYuBtCyggy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoffmanDavid6 @ngatten48 Im sorry, but that is one of the most fun things I have gotten to do in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the time* how black always end up worship our oppression god. That gave the ok to enslave us smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the Post-First-Coffee Pooptime Show presented by MasterCard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently read that Jackie Chan doesn’t like the rush hour movies and it hurt me the exact same way as when I foun… https://t.co/oqkwGb3qTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder This is total BS but it's the same all over the country. We the people need to stop this crap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ate A5 Wagyu and then watched Dario Cecchini’s Chef’s Table. Beef Saturday like whoa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting up at 4am isn’t too bad when you get bumped up to the exit row #businesstravel https://t.co/SCeuiw8WLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBloom34 @witzigdg 400 is far and away the most no other coach even has 200. You can also check ihsa season summar… https://t.co/pggyVXtCvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarkmo12 @realDonaldTrump That makes you a lot better a spelling than me. I think I made the point. Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Who Do You Trust? by Papa Roach. https://t.co/oTON8cV73m  This song kicks so much ass....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson I saw your ridiculous hit piece on the new vomiting/screaming mania that you think cannabis apparent… https://t.co/CxS34Fz4wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Beautiful Heart” by Laura McDonald. Happy Valentine’s Day everyone! https://t.co/S192pqBY5R We help you live an ab… https://t.co/X0XSnuO4GE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only drama left here: Peyton Jaquis has NOT hit a 3-pointer yet in this game. She has at least one in all 28 games… https://t.co/xa1Wqq6NrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Silverado 4WD Custom Crew 5.3L V8 @ Vaden Chevrolet Pooler https://t.co/oy0Sj4b4D6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKONOHIO @EJ_Atwood You know the Demonicrats from California are on top of the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un compa del brete le gustan los cómics y compró uno buenísimo...  My money is on #TheGreatest   #AliBumaye https://t.co/QzbELy8ZZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Oh true authoritarian socialist , she lives like a queen paying her lover illegally, Everyone gets paid e… https://t.co/s3agXVkm4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump won legitimately. Does Matt Viser think he’s smarter than the Founding Fathers who gave us a Republ… https://t.co/NhkyUcpwb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally agree with you President Trump! I am sick of all the Fake News that is constantly pushed out every day! Non… https://t.co/stEwNnO8Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moofasajmk @VanessaMerrell @veronicamerrell @MerrellTwins Yes, my family is disgusted when I told them about that video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like @TheAcademy is being run by #MoviePass. Get a grip! Televise all the categories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majomalnis Combinado con visita de @dmoisset debacle económica super anunciada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldKerry He wasn't terrible. And consider this: When they traded him, the Browns eventually got Johnny Football in return.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaveWahoo not sure about when but @OfficialMLBShop has removed all chief wahoo hats from their online offerings. T… https://t.co/bLQtx8ACGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrinwanderson @njymca @njhealthykids @YHealthyU @ymca @NealDenton Great event]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Takes up Case of One Cross that Could Decide the Fate of Many https://t.co/r0QsX0oyDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krystallromero_ @ashhleyirene Happy birthday! 🎊🎂 we will celebrate with you soon! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameTeachDad No (own it, recommended by someone I trust implicitly) and yes (fucking outstanding).]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how dust particles “glow” in the night vision camera in the nursery, creepy as f#ck. https://t.co/zTkqXhDLUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was the last day of my class of entrepreneurship for architects @ELA_MX . A great opportunity to learn and te… https://t.co/3Hh8nle1ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael @LarryBlaze6 Those very officers use marijuana and Other Drugs on their off time. They have a no dr… https://t.co/XRkMOmZqeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MckeeLincoln @jakephelps2 @SportsCenter Beta Kentucky and jumped 4 spots, lost to Florida at home and beat UT in O… https://t.co/gNc9dmC1NM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveTheHRCzar Great to be with y'all today. Thank you for the opportunity to brag about @ISUSHRM and the state stu… https://t.co/JznTkq3eEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sash is back baby! #sacramentorepublicfc #urbsindomita @ Sacramento Republic FC HQ and Team Store https://t.co/YYQBDhgXO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling Would apply for asylum if you are safe in your home country]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKHouseofLords @UKParliament @SusanBaroness If you'll pardon, as pertinent, I always felt upon witness the interio… https://t.co/vEqVZdfCym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoxocruzting 😕🤮🤢 bruh don’t nobody eat jack in the crack! After the club mash like fuk them tacos does hit but nah… https://t.co/PTVgCDDofw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSThakral @rsehji @mrkempnz @HostBrian @ocpalloneword2 @Doctor_Harves @VipulaSharma1 @nzvh @DCSG_Senior @kevbartle… https://t.co/oO53SMNeYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ain't leaving till we're heaving..gotta love St James entertainment....Stay Tanned My Friends...#… https://t.co/UnlgQlO8Tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlevanchuk @OriginalFunko @HilaryLGray @ash_anderson24 @CSSully @camerondeuel Yea I didn’t think so. I just want y… https://t.co/O3BZHXbKpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST MET THE HEAD OF NASA, @JimBridenstine, I am in shock right now. This #NASASocial just went to a whole new leve… https://t.co/WAuPajNiDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @disturbed #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/dkAf5rJGz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaradoSheny Muy buenas tardes Sheny y provecho con tu café cuídate mucho saludos cordiales hasta Guatemala 🇬🇹,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PercivalPenman @iamredfoxx Riccardo Tischi who's the creative director at Burberry currently was one of the first… https://t.co/CqEzzbpKjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump caught lying recently about issued security clearance might be harder than🤔 Being Trump's Daughter Is… https://t.co/nxIrtv2fvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quincyooo @moderated_mike @chucktodd @AsaHutchinson I have a very good index fund. Most months it appreciates enou… https://t.co/NAaJAhmW3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilbulli1031 @Hodag66LEE It will never happen. If she does that ...there will be civil war and the ppl will use th… https://t.co/OcgXbB8ApN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y que es la verga ps si lleva 5 y de esas dos se las ha quitado a ellos!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Profile of a  #FridaysForFuture Campaigner. "I am no longer accepting the things I cannot change. I am changing the… https://t.co/xX7dUY9COj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Panama City Beach - Public Access #18 https://t.co/3VeI8GeYde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FedExGround  #safetynotfirst  #youdriveforaliving https://t.co/4bfjnr1LW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My apathy has seized control again.  The fear of feeling inadequate has rendered my spiritual efficiency invalid. I… https://t.co/TqdoHeX1EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 21: Garrett A. Morgan. With only an elementary school education, he went on to patent several inventions, inclu… https://t.co/neyuXYLK8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate being short lol  T why can't u make me grow!!! Big tall strong boy!!!! No more being butt height walking up… https://t.co/3BFjBwiKEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickdece Definitely Arby’s but I don’t blame anyone, we’re rebuilding. It’s part of the process]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRLOVEMX @luis_gj Pinches batos que se quieren vengar de lo que les hicieron a ellos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down the lazy river in Laos, a dreamy diversion from the modern world: As most of Southeast Asia rushes into the fu… https://t.co/Fx41vQ7YCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Senior Project Manager" in #Austin, TX. Go on informational interviews. The best… https://t.co/51UhIUc8DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[FEBRUARY 25TH METAL MONDAYS AT HOOTS PUB AMARILLO,TEXAS $5 AGES 21+ $10 AGES 18+ https://t.co/lJShC18Y5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheWalkingDead The Whisperers believe in tough love child-rearing. They never pick up a crying baby. #TWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carigi12 @sec1968 @SenSanders Energy? What Energy? https://t.co/QzgNqgoO4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahoy Drivetimers! Happy back-to-work for this Tuesday-is-a-Monday commute. For February 19 your quiz topics are: To… https://t.co/m3EUjREqvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahershala Ali- best supporting actor nod for a movie he totally dominated?? Some mistake??]]></document><document><![CDATA[grateful to have been able to share my work at this year’s @emory_urology research retreat! great afternoon learnin… https://t.co/VEshmuLAJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[See, @LJthaFiasc0? People do come to baseball games. Sorry to *rain* on your parade 🌧]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe how bad Provorov and Sanheim have been with the puck in their own end today. #Flyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build The Wall: Construction Progress https://t.co/DXEZe2gJfW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FliederAmanda @mims_words I'm telling a secret even my best friends don't know.  (I can finger knit, sew and croch… https://t.co/8jr2Ochbo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the @GtownCollege hoops team blowing out Adishian shoes. To act like this is the first time ever is anot… https://t.co/qEATBORWVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinJ_Vogt @Skersvikesfan06 Lol this is probably why the Lakers are ranked 27th in the league for fast break points allowed. #GetBackonD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more home runs today for @CalBaseball's Andrew Vaughn in a 9-3 win at Saint Mary's.  The senior All-American's… https://t.co/CMPFqks5tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is important to point out that in 85% of the historical cases, $AAPL goes on to retrace HALF the losses immediat… https://t.co/2hP1nZYZGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyRockstar333 @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @SpeakerPelosi What possible business is it of hers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a monster of an SUV!  The Mercedes Benz AMG GLE 63 S Coupe is coming! Please click the link in my bio and S… https://t.co/JztyMRPcu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurpleS1urp every time I see this it harder and harder and just reminds me of how much I love the boys nights we a… https://t.co/dSVLkQy17m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPGeek @Wingster26 @JiCLajoie J'ai hâte de voir le prochain épisode. Moi je suis certain que Marie-Eve joue juste… https://t.co/H1mPPgEHqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The main event is on early. The Shield is not the main event here. This crowd is there to see @BeckyLynchWWE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiembouvier We really enjoyed it. I knew it would be good, but much better than I had anticipated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention to who is and isn't freaking out about it on Twitter 👀   (Hint: the only meteorology people pulling f… https://t.co/Iot1TP4tiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPGSite I was seriously worried there was going to be a Fire Emblem branded Switch after buying the Diablo bundle in Nov.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through some old Esquire mags (Nov 2003) and found a multi page ad for Nokia. Love the keyboard on the 3300.… https://t.co/0mJrqCYKqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittPettibone Saw this while on Instagram.. This needs 2 go viral!! #MAGA!!! #1STAMENDMENTRIGHTS!!! #AMERICANS1ST… https://t.co/b15o0MlF9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Happy Birthday to one of our countries greatest leaders, George Washington!🇺🇸  "Happiness depends more upon the i… https://t.co/hzzi1eJz4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @smellydeuce757 givin off Maynor-esque vibes to anyone else? @VCU_Hoops #LetsGoVCU #VCUPointGawds https://t.co/btS7s78Yjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work right next to chick-fil-a and I’m hoping I don’t end up hating it, also had the breakfast today. Didn’t feel nothn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dicen los asesores de morena que ni la gaceta parlamentaria les quieren dar por transparencia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxsleuthUSA @waconia3 Like the rug...                   .... ON TRUMPS HEAD! https://t.co/DQDVWm6959]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember wgen @ThePistilPacker would drink this on stream....  https://t.co/5vQbwx4cTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, a prerequisite to drum corps media is that your first camera was a Canon t3i.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a time traveler now. Fix your future regrets by working today. #fridaymotivation #timetravel #endgame https://t.co/ULRSFvcshz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A comfort zone is a beautiful place. But nothing grows there.  photo credits to: mendailyclassy @ North Las Vegas,… https://t.co/AiQdSxV4oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting out before the rain returns - Drinking a ...From Here To Gardena by @statebrewingco at @bottlecraft  — https://t.co/LkeB31oIQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APEastRegion @AP Did an editor actually read this? There are two big errors in the story. Hint: One spelling, one repetitive syntax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say this out loud:  I have chosen to believe (for as long as I can) that God thinks the WORLD of me and that I am m… https://t.co/kr35Vuh031]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend got to watch my little brother beat the  number 1 team in the state on Friday!  Then the cats beat nu… https://t.co/poRmaizl6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @DineshDSouza Now you know who you do not want for president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hermanntertsch @cayetanaAT @GaetanoLoHace @cristiancrespoj @CristinaSegui_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteTallon @ChipNoir @EdKrassen @AOC Have a great day. That’s for commenting.]]></document></documents></author>