<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Feeling lonely in a foreign land is some other type of shit. I can't just be all, "hey wanna go out and do somethin… https://t.co/kYf45xkLdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alezander @AmandaReis429 @AmandaReis429 me on my way to pick you up after sleeping through first period]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be seeing Blueface w @narroubi17 in FoCo 🤪 I don’t even listen to him like that but I’ll take any reason… https://t.co/iONpLxvz5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCMontreal The problem is Canadians forget all of this in 6 months because he will be handing out candies😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[blame it on my juice  #juice #lizzo #anchormanclapback #bts #musicvideos #barlubitsch #vintage #vibes #red… https://t.co/glHzOzfONO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tri-colored Heron... @ Arthur R. Marshall Loxahatchee National Wildlife Refuge https://t.co/AdmvZoprbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new collection of soaps have landed! #slsfree #handmade #naturalbodycare @ Sonia Masocco Phytotherapy https://t.co/M8osiJcLkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enews Right up there with Whitney Houston's and Jussie Smollett's interviews.... Except at least Whitney was belie… https://t.co/w8T6lvECIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are invited to our  “Go Red Dinner” -  to raise awareness of women's heart health within our Community in San A… https://t.co/LQT3aXbXV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got two tropical candles burning in the apartment right now because this cold rain is killing my vibe today. #bringonsummer 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/3bSrHZdZ7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is all about sweet surprises... I love my friends! 🧁🍸🥂#HappyBirthdayToMoi #NoCellphones #DoriChronicles… https://t.co/NZZuThMwFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markasaurus I wonder what the other side looks like. I hope it's an equally as lovely mud room. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evil cat has resorted to biting to wake me up. I guess my "no animals in the bedroom" rule doesn't apply to cats wh… https://t.co/xkHwX9AyiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cleversea23 @TheTimmyCat @TheRightMelissa @sdebbieharris @charliekirk11 Says you.  I guess you have to suffer to see the light.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why the gibberish? OH..........the MANY briefcases that #MichaelCohen brought to the hearing yesterday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RohenSharrma Not bad busy at work and got in trouble for spending to much time on my phone lol 😂 can’t wait for Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix get on board!!! You’d have a million more people hopping on to stream whatever @shanedawson and… https://t.co/HwOQev1YY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLairport  Can you help with info about Ethiopia flight? Looking for passenger confirmation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras! Tune into @CBS4Local #Daybreak to start your Fat Tuesday with me @AmandaKFOX_CBS @SalinaKFOX_CBS… https://t.co/hwQnMpLSwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Cavey The Cave Boy caved. That is what you elected him for?  Hahahahaha! If he does declare a nation… https://t.co/dyW40To7eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RUE8jUfzmC  How Dayton, Ohio, Reduced Opioid Deaths By 50%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day @ldeprey17 @matthewlaporte https://t.co/oVcZqYKYiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday wisdom is so powerful! #caring #caringpeople #whohasmadethebiggestdifferenceinyourlife @ Knoxville, Tenne… https://t.co/TViOsd3dtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InnocentSinful @DXRacer Haha seriously! you didn’t take this picture...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday. Getting ready to slay the day @ Santa Clara, California https://t.co/yGDoFIfF3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dianne Feinstein scolds schoolkids who demand the Green New Deal https://t.co/hcAcGeo3v7 via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ira Ira thank you for recommending A Simple Plan. A thoroughly satisfying film]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve told this story before but one night i was at CC Club pre Touchtunes and someone played All my Life by KC and… https://t.co/LG9ilL5a0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! We are open 10-5 today here in #ptbo ... what are your plans? 😊💕 📸: julialuymesart  . . . . .… https://t.co/VZpKU5J0I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[She protected her rapist’s baby. #Pregnantfromrape  - Extended interview with Jennifer https://t.co/wxUM6qmk6i via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am telling you if you are looking for quality products PLEASE hit that link https://t.co/8tJprwE48O Help aid in y… https://t.co/NBfpDUmvzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que este nuevo día sea inolvidable! Buenos días! 😘😘 #ElChiquilínTodasLasMañanas en La Grande 107.5 https://t.co/jhpce83GHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy winds today blew out huge windows at my office in Florence today! #NonotuckMills @WMassNews @WWLP22News https://t.co/XT9jfrFkem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotlandGirl123 It’s usually when I’ve also had too much wine so I really appreciate them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rollapaluza @philipglowinski I think you may have tagged the wrong person...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheIceGarden @NWHL Three blocked shots by @ThunderCWHL to hold on against MPP, Montreal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/VmTs9KdRUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me with the bj’s app for free pizookies😂😭🤤 @keely_fester @ stacia (can’t find the @😂)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angles are EVERYWHERE! #mathliterature #mathematicalmindsets  #4Rhappydreamers https://t.co/dtDDn2ZYFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥 away! 💨 Congratulations to the connections of Flameaway🤗 you just won the Challenger Stakes at Tampa Bay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6: Get educated. Remind our community that all kids are our kids.  #falconslearn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact when I drink things, my pinky automatically comes up. I don’t know why but it’s such a stupid weird thing… https://t.co/cfnRsRgseO]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had to stop 3 different students from telling me spoilers about HTTYD 3 today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalHatred @John_R_Berna People better be looking for a strong Country! Not hand outs, or they will lose out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficeSmallBiz Definitely. One of my blog articles expresses how it affected me:  https://t.co/FFnBAM8HkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t got fucked up, fucked up since my 18th birthday &amp; it’s SHOWS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOMORROW 11 AM🍑 Let’s Goooo❗️ @ Millennium Dance Complex https://t.co/XcLoWeDnmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rejectedjokes @DuckTales @DisneyXD @Disneyland You are too damn good looking all of the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re on sale online today!!! 10AM! https://t.co/0zqZ6lK1F8 https://t.co/O4sIQtcArv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Calling 🙏⠀ #jesuscalling #march3 #reading #dailydevotional #inspirationalwords   #20likes #repost… https://t.co/WAu1w18npe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcsosazpurua @Marysioux @NTN24 @YouTube Excelente!!!! Más claro imposible. El mundo desde la comodidad de un tv en… https://t.co/TqEz058SIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when the path is daunting! ♥️🙏🏼✝️ @ Oconto Falls, Wisconsin https://t.co/Mnd1AWTfIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st TD of the season...Somerset vs. JAX🏈🏈🔰🔰🔰🏈🏈🏈 #flagfootball🔰 @FlaHSFootball https://t.co/3aaNL9OuhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A la verdad es que ustedes son bien llorones lo de el $$ lo dije por esto !! Porque aha te “robo” pero a los que ro… https://t.co/MqEaFU5Mi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaLillja thank you for your help at the senior center Valentine’s Day party and for this awesome photo!… https://t.co/VHm2HynJZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe i have to bleed every month. This is blasphemy. I am pissed https://t.co/t3vfINYPcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino I’m afraid my brain cells evaporate when I see her pics on here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your feet are so sore that you start falling over when you walk. Great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today just kept getting progressively worse, but you know what it’s fine I’m gonna just go to sleep now and try again tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckRybak He's trying so hard to pretend all that ugly never happened. Hey, @SykesCharlie, #YouBuiltThatYouOwnIt.… https://t.co/kbJbkjniPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing forum on The Futute of Labor Policy and Work with @jasonfurman @marylgray @daeaves @profsheena as Jason men… https://t.co/LXVPWtAYTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe my volcels bought me roses :( the cinematic parallels  i love them so much https://t.co/Xq1jXh4fR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shheelbylynn I’m so confused as to why it bothered him if you wanted to be naked ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pope Benedict points out that forgiveness is a theme that pervades the entire Gospel. We meet it at the very beginn… https://t.co/yJGm9ayHuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was in snacks? Parents fearful to send kids back to school after eating tainted candy: https://t.co/BRUxTuszAc https://t.co/ece6a5RVVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing snapchat memories of ex-friends hurts but what hurts more is seeing snapchat memories of me with clear skin 😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What?   Grow a pair and stop whining about things that don't matter.  How about doing some governa… https://t.co/QlKy31mBc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up I was lucky enough to experience caring for a large range of different animals (various birds, insects,… https://t.co/eJyliWQAWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[These laws/loopholes r sooooo conducive to an evil potus, we might never see the end of this family/tentacles, esp… https://t.co/Qzkc5YPS1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHowe Thank you for this thread. It points the conversation and where it went into perspective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak Peek at the look for tonight!  Natural Face in an almost instant! @ South Carolina https://t.co/JE13RxTmIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamentablemente la #intervenciónmilitar va más allá de que Guaidó la solicite, o más allá incluso de las intencione… https://t.co/T4YoG7GXG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iancharris @SuzanneEvans1 @business So soy or something for the substance? Tofu🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just start over a song because you weren’t appreciating it enough? Because SAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmCly73 @IWasAtTheGame @Jesserose33 This is Leah Burris’s youngest son!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump SHUT THE FUCK UP - YOU ARE THE ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE #TimeForYouToBeLockedUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your body shifts into recovery mode after a workout, it needs a nutrient-heavy meal. Enter chicken: The lean p… https://t.co/tqWLB0zJCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I moved into the city 28 hours ago. I've signed up to do 3 social things already. #typicaltonya]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're born with skills it shows! I didn't see this coming. I am shocked he made the basket backwards. #Talent… https://t.co/apoygZ1x1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prudinx I've don't that too..and Autistic Children. Cranial Facial Charities too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@des_vargass3 @woahhitslitlen Ok bubba so we’re lying now huh? 😏 alright bet]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we try to include more adult voices that reflect the student populations we serve, we should look to representat… https://t.co/RmeMEr4naa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this kind of just proved their point, Cardi? 😅 I personally think this is impressive, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the drive home from losing my v card... shit was storming and my bestie said it was god crying 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Magic School Bus   Ms. Frizzle poisons her class with Psilocybin mushrooms and takes them on TRIPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s still time to tune into #GoodMorningAlabama on @abc3340! Can you spot the bags under my eyes?! 🙈 https://t.co/YfZs6wlUqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadfelixg Damn that’s a big lost for him.  My bet he goes to rehab like others....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning @UnionCollege alumni!  It’s #ADAY4U and time to make history!  Our goal for today - 2,500 donors in 24… https://t.co/AjhWqIsYrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MveLibrary for inviting us to read to MVE’s awesome roadrunners! I always enjoy sharing my favorite book… https://t.co/UXUXd4NW0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[No need to take offense at what is happening around you. Just go with the flow and take a leadership role. This is… https://t.co/JRCXFNx2zV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThisIsAmerica #ThisIsTrumpsAmerica #BlackLivesMatter #OleMissBasketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being silly with my sis on her Birthday 🎂 🎈🍾🎁 @ The Grove https://t.co/hMEKxBUVqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao we brought Jerry to my house tonight😂 and I’m getting briel pajamas and Jerry is like i need some. And i thre… https://t.co/kkixvvXWEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayleyyyymariee @TMohlfeld Wow.....some little girl is telling ME what to do....😅😂 Thats almost funny. Please do u… https://t.co/omHtEfyhqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about we #TWUG it out on this #Valentines Thursday, @DonnieWahlberg? We can trade #Twugs for hugs on June 4! 😉🤗 https://t.co/a3AdwEfjJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women working longer hours more likely to be depressed – study https://t.co/dg4u8HeG7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s sprinkle: Be enthusiastic and thankful about the blessings coming your way today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSBrenner @HillaryClinton @chefjoseandres I didn’t vote for her either!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotRickHahn The sad face is because now I have to clean ravioli off the window]]></document></documents></author>