<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NickW2389 @ProFootballTalk It’s not worth it, Thielen will want a bigger contract soon anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeeBear HA HA @VeeBear this had me giggling a bit lady , Is this also @ArpCreative Valentine's Day card to ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwebb55 @joerexrode It happens all the time free throw numbers don't always equal each other ,sore losers lil orange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kilmeade You dam skippy i am, there isn't much choice if you want honesty! Great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyfeofchristian Sir I’m gonna have to ask you to step out of the vehicle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHanleyRI Belgian Scientists Announce New Solar Panel That Makes Hydrogen https://t.co/2UgnI9e4in via… https://t.co/zViQGtfJ5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polysymptomatic @BrentAWilliams2 @jbez85 @clairlemon It was Chernobyl that led me to change my mind about nuclear.… https://t.co/8nSJaxhCU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5foottraveler Perhaps he should carry a mirror in case he gets lost? 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steinhauserNH1 @KamalaHarris @BernieSanders @foxnewspolitics Pushing for no private healthcare at all, she is not… https://t.co/WZJlZ61Djd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradleydevlin @DonaldJTrumpJr Someone find this piece of crap !    When you do, Roger Stone him at 6am.   Don’t wo… https://t.co/NislPqms6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pinball machine clearly needs to be in my house. https://t.co/7CsJBytPH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[See what happens when I have too much free time on my hand michelobultra 🍺 🤷🏾‍♂️😬🤦🏾‍♂️🤣KMSL......... @ Baton Rouge,… https://t.co/pAeeiOFaeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the perfect life and i'm literally miserable - what do you call that]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here to argue that if Elton John 1968–72 that it would be regarded as an iconic track—likely his best ever.   T… https://t.co/DNfD50Nrtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silly_starfish @JohnTAllen @mapmansethn @UnrepentantWino If you ever come to Austin we will make it 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielKennedyDK For the record when I was first watching Solo I  didn't know how badass she was gonna be. Then I w… https://t.co/HIzVxVVpIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dr. Seuss! 📚 🇺🇸 #readacrossamerica @NolaKWilson https://t.co/ac5Ie81XUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic @matthewjdowd @Timwill04765 Jesus must be an angry, armed hate driven spirit, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnip2020 My celery girlfriend is like, block him, he's a tuber, I'm like he is doing a service,, Somewhere remote, like Wal Marty produce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blue_eyedmolly Think we could run this through Workforce Alignment? 💁‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ongoing “debate” between Kruse and D’Souza is like a car wreck. I want to look away but I can’t. D’Souza is th… https://t.co/abRlY9B1lJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the first time I was introduced to this 11:11 lol now I can’t get it out of my head I swear smh. Everyti… https://t.co/sQW91BHkcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol @ me next time 😅 good thing I’m learning about this thing called communication 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you admire someone, you should go ahead and tell them. People never get the flowers while they can still smell them.” – Kanye West]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just hope we don’t have a preseason game that night @squidbilly929 ....uugggghhhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic win @McMasterSports. Great tenacity, clutch shooting and rebounding. My wife, a 2-time Mac grad is pretty… https://t.co/Y6MThu159q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 Jim Jordan has replaced Mitch McConnell as my pick for biggest pos in government today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly.  Plus, in my experience, the “binder throwing” bosses are actually people who aren’t really that effective… https://t.co/aUCWgkirkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exeter Celtics 7th grader with a strong attack in the middle leading to the lay in ⚡️🏀💪 https://t.co/kT19ot2Ref]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celtics have lost 5 of their last 7, Kyrie had just 7 points last night in a prime match up against the Raptors.… https://t.co/C10zIlEB7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChattaSports Prep Score Updates: Brainerd 49, York 46 (Final); Cleveland 49, Blackman 42 (Final); Oakland 31, East Hamilton 24 (Half)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EasyMoneyDRob dog i got a whole ass gym membership and all i gotta do is drive there and i just can’t pull myself… https://t.co/oxoXa8qDtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Online Flute Lesson available through Skype, FaceTime and Kakaotalk - Be sure to get in touch with me for more info… https://t.co/zT7OmKruDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_notcatherine Are you still watching? When he corrected Jim Jordan about the 1.38 million I spat my cofeee out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjtoplin I just rewatched the first ep of rock of love because it got put on Hulu is that what happened to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeremy Lin is the most overrated player in NBA history. Had 3 great weeks, every team since the Knicks got rid of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DETECTIVE4LIFE I'm waiting for Abe Foxman to say that "Because they have shown themselves to be anti-Semites, Jews… https://t.co/sBZRDYJkV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman Here is the only difference that matters, Paul On the right anti-Jew bigots are called strange outlier… https://t.co/qGrjZu2w5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judyjetson209 @AryaResists @miblogestublog @Mikel_Jollett @Clara_Resists @Augustus709 @StormResist @Cyde_Dish… https://t.co/XPwDVOVYBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, the Rocky Mountains were rocky en Rocky Mountain National Park https://t.co/9mZKf2nXtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Shaw started the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! https://t.co/Zg4DTsnF0K #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any of the other candidates had been elected, I think it would have been altogether becoming and proper for all… https://t.co/bmkLZKMTq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVToronto Probably armed to the teeth now too what with constant shootings and what not ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan is a total badass. If you dont listen to his podcast Deconstructed, you should really check it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hand celebrates after beating Windsor 33-27 in Class L semifinals #ctgb https://t.co/FbKoYFuzKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I believe a hypothesis I had about captain marvel waa just spoiled smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhnizo i feel you and i agree it’s not rocket science but the people in this country don’t get that and won’t vote… https://t.co/tllfJVfBzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lakeland Regional Medical Center in Lakeland, FL https://t.co/3JTwKdub56]]></document><document><![CDATA[anadirm1877 not only is an amazing mentor for the Ollie Life Program but he stay repping the brand. #OllieLife… https://t.co/qTf0NCKyZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenescullion @martydoyle100 @empireofthekop It’s a good point well made Eugene]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsTalkMock I’d love it if she were name-dropped although I don’t think it’ll happen. *sigh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deray Just like most Democrats. They portray themselves as perfect, yet they are far from it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I copied your cadence, I mirrored your style I studied the greats, I'm the greatest right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even believe I associated myself with her.  I unblock her for literally two days then she talk mad crazy on… https://t.co/vdURT8nyQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤ #TheOne by #thewatcher33 #poetry #poem #author #poetrylovers #poetrycorner #poetryislife https://t.co/WyZo7wy129]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AprueboElGobiernodeAMLO  #AprueboElGobiernodeAMLO  #AprueboElGobiernodeAMLO  #AprueboElGobiernodeAMLO… https://t.co/MthEj4UXyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So maybe it was an obvious point, but if any one is asking, I’ll be happy to translate any of my hot takes for a Gu… https://t.co/E834nqCdN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this... writing prompts inside Newsela pair nicely with this, and also Lucy Caulkins. Stop by booth 306 to lea… https://t.co/jS1mjCk737]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonrmcintyre Check out these sources before you do that. Both of these guys testified he never touched them unti… https://t.co/J6zvLMrXKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rahafharfoush Not shameful, just making sure you understand what you will be doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to @TkeyahBennett for her successful business trip in LA earlier this week &amp; accomplishing a huge milestone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dodd loves her new mybenebone! If you have a super chewer I highly recommend this bone 🦴 #dodd #benebone #pitbull… https://t.co/DwB75xlOs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So land owners again are losing their voice and being told what to do with this government. This will not help farm… https://t.co/OqmH10x8Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlcat06 @starwarsromance When you grow up watching TMNT and see them never put ranch on a pizza.... do you put ran… https://t.co/qBSxl2Pkxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pumped for the Daytona 500 today! Will be cheering my newest favorite driver, @austindillon3 for the victory! Alway… https://t.co/RGwEIvhwXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_steeler You know what this actually is? This is the total absence of hatred, racism, and bigotry they need to s… https://t.co/NhWKdUJTPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilmoreGlenda @KevinMKruse My father was told"You don't need advanced math and art classes in Highschool! You're a… https://t.co/egTEXe7GDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie it’ll make me happy if #BlackPanther wins best picture and all the pretentious people have a cow over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMauraA Thank you so very much for your kind words Ema! I really do appreciate it! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I discovered that anything in my diet can be replaced with an iced coffee. I’m swapping bad eating habits for caffeine addiction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Lap 43, time for another Aftershokz Giveaway!  To enter, simply retweet and follow @AfterShokz.  A winner will… https://t.co/rwpeL9QgAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My home few the next few days. @maggiejones_5 @emo52980 @tselitevb @triplecrownspts https://t.co/mA5Dq8WItr]]></document><document><![CDATA[spring break has been good to me so far #lastvideoisntme #iwalkedthatrapid #mfwasscary #yeeeew @ Highlands, North C… https://t.co/Fdn6YmMfNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg There are conservatives who are of your Jewish heritage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t think it was possible for the headlight bulb on my car to be more expensive then an oil change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oakland43 PepsiCo doesn’t have the greatest track record either, but I agree their stuff tastes much better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaturner when will your candidate release his last 10 years of tax returns?  You must realize this question will… https://t.co/v7oErbuMgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[People trying to get me to go to Lucky Strikes already...I'm just an Aqua guy. Something about BYB in Gallery Place dont feel right lls]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1) The lack of standards bears both risk and barriers. Are you going to invest in edge devices and customizing alg… https://t.co/6uJSbDkPSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanKruegel Blue Pan👌🏼... try Cart Driver! fun place and they serve @MTKYColdSnacks 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSenturion @Don_inFarrhaven @j_w_613 @TomSENS *Sold* Gretzky for $15 million. 💰💰💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ser emprededor no es tarea facil, Porque es pelear por tus sueños en contra de la negatividad de muchos, talvez pag… https://t.co/CHSLTsc3tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sometimes the best thing you can do is not think. Not wonder. Not imagine. Not obsess. The only only you can reall… https://t.co/keXmGDGcwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AidLiveVenezuela #23Feb #AmarEsParaSiempre #BuenSábado https://t.co/YgyFf0cA0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad. President Trump would have crushed her much worse then he did in 16. And she knows it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a mere 24 hours from now, it will be @UpperDeckHockey National Hockey Card Day highlighted by  @hoosierjm26 meet… https://t.co/Kg9aIHotv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Just Means More.  @AuburnSoftball hosts Tiger Invitational this weekend with DHs on Friday/Saturday/Sunday. https://t.co/GAf7qZjN6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe this isn't standard practice. Amazing how few basketball people actually understand shooting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @foxandfriends @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Roseannes New Blessing! @therealroseanne love All The Way!… https://t.co/Uj3s7tbZoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barrel aged double stack pickup - Drinking a DDH Plump by @GreatNotionPDX @ Great Notion Brewing Northwest  — https://t.co/p9v9m48orJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlasfeldReports @joncoopertweets @jkbjournalist The corruption in this Admin and Cabinet are literally unbelievable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaytonRG40 Idk who’s wearing wires around my man but they bout to be snatched.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lanz_edward @MarkLazerus @Suntimes @ByScottPowers We did that a couple of years ago with @BrianHedger and… https://t.co/ltIiJRycKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best #lasagna we have ever tried. #thevenetian #trattoriareggiano #lasvegas #birthday #birthdayboy… https://t.co/51AgFgssc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a bar guest ask for my deadname repeatedly, but leave me $20.  Am I bitter? Immensely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3b) It was a tool used extensively during the CR to take out SBC leaders and unwanted convention employees. P.P. ex… https://t.co/azU7w2srSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racer86r @USAIDMarkGreen @VP So if a lot of Iranians like Americans then I guess you should go help them to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdeebocane Good morning Dee and Happy Monday from my alternative music station ☕️☕️☕️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol boss man quits on the spot, 2 guys left last week. Bout to be 3 more tomorrow. Where the hell am I working]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Xjj5uSmPKZ stokz mcabe page all antifa gay mrdia theres no statute in 25th ammendment that applies to… https://t.co/Q5rRj2GWiD]]></document></documents></author>