<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[District 10 Wrestling Class 2A Individual Championships (2-23-19)  https://t.co/dm1xcnA98H  (Via YourErie 2Go)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Houston of Cooper with a huge three out of the TO with 16 sec. remaining to tie the score at 39.  #dagger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin It's too space epic fantasy w/ pseudo gritty realism. I love space fantasy but it bounces off me too?… https://t.co/lB0OxGOgfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristyMontilla @KulcsarBarnabas @trish_regan @CLewandowski_ @RepGosar @nedryun @DougWead @kayleighmcenany May the… https://t.co/aeZOSq9oTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyGarcia07 Y eso, que se han otorgado contratos pésimos a lo largo de la historia, como el de Chris Davis, Carl… https://t.co/rfU5ao8kZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsatiablyChevy I watched my mom rip almost entire sweaters after spotting a dropped stitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nolab123 I was born in that hospital, my grandma ran the Sugar Bowl, and we had 2 gas stations on Scottsdale Road.… https://t.co/LLsXX4FSTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berkmerkz Ima keep trying bro, but I take offense to our pizza is wack]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sign of that good life coming to Uniontown on this cold and dreary day 🍗 #bigshotbobshouseofwings @ Walmart Union… https://t.co/pM0CDBM5K9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come Check us out at the Stars VS Rangers game @AACenter!!! @ the AT&amp;T Rotunda near section 121!! #POWERCentral… https://t.co/8Z462GKrIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeAndersonFF @FFAaroneous I hear he ties the laces on his left shoe first.  His left!  Doomed to fail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMCTalkingDead Beta needs to get into professional wrestling! This could be a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Connecticut Avenue &amp; East-West Highway in Montgomery County, MD, MD https://t.co/OOaQ554w2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can be the most honest, real, down to earth person and people will still fuck you over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo IN MEASUREMENTS WE            TRUST IN GOD WE TRUST  MEAS.UREM.ENTS  THIS.            .… https://t.co/hPMRs1DwuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_eleanorina @paulg This conversation won’t go anywhere. I agree that buffalo roaming the prairie is why US soil is… https://t.co/zLIDW3mi4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLightPours And let’s not forget that the welfare state is one of the biggest things attracting illegal immigrat… https://t.co/YReNCpKDS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t enough dads take the paid paternity leave they have? @alexisohanian is trying to break the social stigma… https://t.co/w0awuRjYQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JlspzSpitz @thebrittanyxoxo Ha. Who wouldn't be? Ass-tonishing. 💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥👅👅👅👅👅👅👅👅👅😘😘😘😘😘😍😍😍😍😍💦💦💦🌷🌷🌷🌹🌹🌹🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarsmileSteve Hey! Thanks for reaching out. Yeah, I'm far from knowledgeable when it comes to DM but Tomb Mould wa… https://t.co/tB6qDS94Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it *really* not possible to run later hours without any changes that upend commuters' early commutes?  And can… https://t.co/g2w5zmVXEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonViola This might have been one of the hardest things I’ve ever watched]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what was the worst news of the last 24 hours - Bruce Bochy announcing he’s retiring or B*rnie S*anders ann… https://t.co/ztOegb8Rpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜African American History Month💜  Robert E. Morrison (Buster), born December 28, 1959 ------------------------. Jus… https://t.co/Y9Oj6Ehd1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAR WARS: The Force Awakens with a live score performed by the National Symphony Orchestra! The Force was with the… https://t.co/PfVJMSEMLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend and I are texting about dating apps and she accidentally replied to my text to the guy she's been talking… https://t.co/xTYhkZK8v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agustdaze Once their company lets them change their image to this, I’mma die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us March 12 at the Detroit Public Library to celebrate "Detroit's Abolitionist Moment." https://t.co/EbkSs9CXRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is also a good idea for an interdisciplinary MYP Unit Planner @Techieteach11 @jesgarrigan @SDoLSTEM… https://t.co/TD92wunJL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any day that ends with these two things s a good day! #RaganDIsney https://t.co/cO0eERe7zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we need to distinguish between equal pay and parity. The women are suing for access to business records and… https://t.co/CPwLbwZec3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 1/3 of college presidents say more than 10 colleges will close in 2019 - 10% say more than 20. 1 in 7 presid… https://t.co/ZI3kelyHQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justblamelaurel @nchan A favorite of @LadyDangerFloof and mine! “No, they’re trying to fly that tank.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LumberKings @MiLB @toneill21 @MiLBPromos @ClintonHerald @CHerald_Sports @mwlarchives @MWLtraveler @bensbiz… https://t.co/eagCLdfVRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard what's so sad is there are probably a majority of people in congress who couldn't 'ace' those 3 questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Summer Management Trainee Intern Arlington" at Enterprise Holdings? Applicant tracking sys… https://t.co/cT4LMitKVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marketingmolly_ @_BigMatt @TurfSpartanLord @andrewmuntz @rtdemayturf @BPolimer @JamieMehringer @gndkpr… https://t.co/wDSNYQKCl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wisdom of Malcolm X: He was Warning Us about These Bourgeois Hustlers ~ The Ghion Journal https://t.co/ik1X1Eknid via]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Victory937FM @TheCoachWilkins @gchspioneers @JSWriterMichael @WBBJ7Alex @rcude93 WeAreReady !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Whitlock after hearing Kaepernick's  settlement is anywhere from 60-80 million https://t.co/RxciplurZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKasser @IAmTreasure117 @FeitsBarstool @iamLegend22 I’ve seen four in my life. #98yanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all really just gonna announce you support VR on my BIRTHDAY like it's nothing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat That's every answer he gives.  A word salad ramble that sucks the oxygen from the room until the next question is asked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a small boy, I would trail behind my Maman, irritating her with incessant questions.  Rather than squelc… https://t.co/bR0pF9PpaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailYou72514463 @lisaponyexpress @galvan_naomi @GarDolphin733 @JasonCowboysMan @Tinanicole96 @a1_spurs… https://t.co/VgTl0kxJXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Veronica Congrats and I am happy for you. I hope your Father is proud of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @Mitumba10 Did #LooneyLaura say said she had dinner with @KatrinaPierson last night. Didn’t even know… https://t.co/emvPs4lZZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made my appointment to finish my sleeve and I couldn’t be more excited !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to a podcast about turbulence while on a flight is very on brand for me, isn’t it? @ San Diego Internatio… https://t.co/aHyZzR5JBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanVanSciver Best way to beat them is doing what you do best!   Wonder how many people would buy an SJW parody c… https://t.co/GLxNWIn8ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m sorry but I’m just really into Fit White boys. I thought I didn’t have a type but my bestie pointed out the… https://t.co/gur9rKpAK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouGiveMeFever7 @TessatTys I agree with her statements, however the way she presents is the problem. I think that… https://t.co/sXvLWVfZIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve memorized the British version of Miranda rights. Thanks Broadchurch! https://t.co/VHpUNR8ZmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 9 - Daily Yahoo!:     Surprising new battleground for Trump, Clinton voters;    Ranking the Top Demo… https://t.co/l3FQLJ13FJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an In Bloom by @FieldworkBrewCo @ Jacobs Center for Neighborhood Innovation — https://t.co/C21TST97dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are starting the Hype train up early. Mark your calenders as @abridges79 Q's Bunker Hill on the 27th for the Sui… https://t.co/WJ2vdnIgUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnlyFans #JustForFans 🔞🎬❗️🎥  join my pages to see hot ass #AmatuerContent that’s #Hotter than the boy next door.… https://t.co/XFtVUR2axL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bryce Harper couldve made $45 million a year” blah blah blah. He’s going to make $330 million, staying in one plac… https://t.co/sYqDq7C0oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siento que Mauricio Fernández ha creado un nuevo nivel en la pirámide de Maslow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twinkiejiggles Stardog Champion - Mother Love Bone   Runner up: Bob - Weird Al  https://t.co/TQExWMO1n6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyG211 @JayBehrens1 @IntegrityFound1 @JimHealthpub @StarTribune You’ve not nothing. Bye!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I think it’s fantastic that you have the power to give your staff a raise. A raise to the living wage! Colorado public]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol America is such a wonderful place that very stupid people can be elected public office! Communism and… https://t.co/qPBUw3fXSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryan_kantor I remember that game.  Their fan support is good enough when they are good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMontieth My God Collison, DO NOT PASS toward your opponent's basket when you get trapped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Stocker" at ResourceMFG? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. You might be under… https://t.co/lYzyU5Vhx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEchrisHOKE I watched the whole 2nd half ha.  And yes I noticed same thing, I hate they tourney seed rankings]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really telling me that since I’m not a first generation college student, I don’t understand the college stru… https://t.co/Ndd5kGJKZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've had a French Press for years, and I really liked the coffee. Then I bought an Aeropress and now I am deeply c… https://t.co/KAGujKygcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’ve slept maybe a total of 5 hours all week anybody have any good ways to knock my big ass out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I actually hungry or am I just telling myself I’m hungry because I’m bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just one of those days where the depression and self loathing hits hard man...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliceLfc4 I hate to make judgments based on isolated videos, but there are a lot of things in that video, I would… https://t.co/GNj5N3HPUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Martina Yep.  XY against XX only hurts women.  Nothing like having your 16 year old daughter pinne… https://t.co/NMpiiAY9xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bocachica70 @ctsvrunner @nbcsnl @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/t8WpGeCYVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcapsalin @thisisinsider Also, ya know, it’s a MOVIE. Let’s all take a deep knee bend and relax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶As in the Days of Noah⚓️~Misty Edwards.🎵 Watch on https://t.co/SaFl0WtY1L https://t.co/SpiJ8JGJjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyonndon Honestly. Same. I only leave Mina in cus her fighting skills are really raw lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfitzmorris64 @swensoncr @MacBulldogsMBB @kcacsports Thank you @dfitzmorris64!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either make the tree good and its fruit good, or make the tree bad and its fruit bad; for the tree is known by its fruit. (Matthew 12:33)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabrielaLeskur sounds great though then you'd be - camping...? 🌿🌱🌴🌳⛺️🌱🌲🌵🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuses are for the weak. Either you is or you ain’t. PERIOD! Let’s GROW! 🙌🏿✅💪🏿🆙 Another homeowner IS firing her fo… https://t.co/XHrCERu6J9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC says WE should be excited about automation??  I honestly think this person gets S T U P I D E R everyday! I wi… https://t.co/eNzw5hg9Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @yorkulions WHKY Erin Locke who put up 6🍏 this past weekend #whanau 🦁🐾🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prageru @LordSangOne @RealCandaceO @therealroseanne This girl is a star!🌠🌠🌠  God bless you Candace! 🙏🌹🌸🌿🌼🌺🍃🌻  #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget about tax returns, @DanielBiss . Candidates for President ought to have to file a declaration from a certifi… https://t.co/MGXExd1xHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allegiant Help! My TSA KTN#  is missing from my itinerary for this weekend’s trip.   Would someone be so kind to a… https://t.co/IGdVlp8p6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoseOfficial Can you help me out by signing this petition? https://t.co/qWMiY1JRJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfcdjalmasantos @opropriolavo Ninguém é obrigado a doar dinheiro, doa quem quer. Já doou  o dinheiro para Haddad fecha a conta ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Current situation is “the small picture”. Your FUTURE is “the big picture”   -Jesus de Nazareth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LFwede @AmiiboKing313 So true: mentality is half of what it takes to be a pro player.   Find a really good player… https://t.co/13ybvQEx3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep so I’m stuck looking at weather models at 430 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I hadn’t made it through my accident, please know this what is what I would’ve wanted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetterOfficial We want to see you do what YOU want. You’ve had a huge journey to become what you are and seeing yo… https://t.co/c0hVpQQrxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch, what’s it like being a flyers fan?  Well... https://t.co/DO0Dfm1OMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nashville 36, Althoff 25, end third. Hornettes close quarter on a 12-0 run. #stlpreps #618hoops #WeAreSTLToday]]></document><document><![CDATA[My HS classmate, teammate, and friend's granddaughter. Really a good player. #CollegeLadyMule]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habermetrics Why? Because it would not have been 9.5 it would’ve been max. Then the price of Dobson, a first and a… https://t.co/NANELFxy6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kodele_mua @JsinDark The velvet cars, the corn with caps/grills, the lady-dog tattoo, the Captain Morgan moustache… https://t.co/Mryk06Ag7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Oscar goes to...Green Book.  Me:  #Oscars https://t.co/qRGShdQ9qz]]></document></documents></author>