<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ms_carbone 🎁Aww thx sweets! Beware this is what happens as you get older...Memory Gaps 🤓#AppleEDUchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Pelosi us extremely stupid when it comes to the Sumit with President Trump and Kim, she doesn't kn… https://t.co/SAtmZPCsfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oversize Sunglasses...for these or other TAP on the link in Bio  #sunglasses😎 #fashionsunglasses… https://t.co/cT3v1JhToM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Paul Manafort sentence is a slap in the face to the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was seriously thinking the same thing in the midst of the manhunt. @TommieClarkKCCI telepathy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is playful. #laughter #tee-hee #grin #amusing https://t.co/7rUZ59JS04]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Goodmorning from my cruise 🚢 . #Tatiana is sailing ⛵️ today all day at sea 👍. On her way to #Charleston… https://t.co/lKN1WXxXUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @shayne571 @GayleKing @rkelly Exactly my thought as I watched this morning. And she never stopped asking r… https://t.co/rCXE90KIw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Waywardaughter0 @ :49 in the clip, it sounds like she starts to say her shoulder hurts! 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adapt and overcome!   Citizenship students are using our office to start today's lesson. (We have an online class o… https://t.co/Ypc92kv3av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner Ok.  So he's got problems.  He should get help.  But WE should not make the mistake of over generalization from this either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i dont make the president’s list this semester, mark my words, i will cry about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[But after the three and a half days a breath of life from God entered them, and they stood up on their feet, and gr… https://t.co/crwJAcCufu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to go on reserve in April!! I need to see places other than Korea and Japan for once]]></document><document><![CDATA[i started driving my car just yesterday in sport mode and this is exactly how i feel driving it now https://t.co/WC3qdrT9lE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad thinks it’s genetic that both of our phone batteries don’t hold power]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cool with paying a pet deposit but not a non-refundable pet deposit on top of pet rent like wtf! Especially whe… https://t.co/sxzJLWYF04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady’s little page 😭 I still can’t believe she’s in a book about shih tzus. She’s been the little loml for 6 years… https://t.co/apaoharqmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big congrats to dear friends @mattsgorman and @LoganDobson on joining @TargetedVictory team. What a great group of… https://t.co/s1AeYsbvSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We GET to make a difference! It’s all in the mindset. ❤️ #JoyfulLeaders https://t.co/T9HWxRJN3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sulcusandjirehs I'm so glad it won for costume design, because those costumes were genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prsarahevans The @CF_Foundation (my 3-year old has the disease). @Cisco is a great supporter of the cause also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a difference from praying sitting up, than praying on your knees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pienso en el estres de mi día y nets no manches, soy una bebé como para que me sometan a este tipo de cosas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEALYumballoon lol SAME or when I watch @LifeandNothing with someone. That movie is so beautiful and it's even in… https://t.co/fAoW0oQjft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made the mistake of getting my car washed at dusk and I am now officially in a horror movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Goldberg Tax Services Satellite Office https://t.co/CJCjdfeoFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who's learning a new trick! @ Corvallis, Oregon https://t.co/ZRyaohggkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashpay123 I’m actually crying right now. you are beautiful inside and out, and I’m so lucky to have met you ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd love to see the 77 year old billionaire do jail time. Kraft knew these females were sex slaves, maybe even owns… https://t.co/RmkiDQTUVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 23rd Birthday to my beautiful baby @hopesaboss I cannot tell you the joy you have given me and your daddy, by… https://t.co/eTC2GV8WCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: tell me your honest opinion   Friend: *gives honest opinion*   Me: HoW dArE yOu https://t.co/Rv2XSJBSUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else thinks that judge Ellis might be a trumptard?  Show of hands....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahead of today’s @USLChampionship slate, I want to acknowledge how grateful I am to be a part of such a brilliant t… https://t.co/gPgAREcvgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My excellent daycare provider has a spot. Low ratio (only 2 kids!), Downtown (on the bike path and near the bus!),… https://t.co/Nq8kzgoAHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo I have 5 interviews within the next 4 days two I’m one day...when you put your faith in GOD he will never let you down]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 7114 HAMILTON PARK BOULEVARD #Tampa #FL  #realestate https://t.co/vE59bwEMsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you must #takethebus match the seats. #bigbluebus My car is still being serviced so I had to put all my teaching… https://t.co/X7VEvl3R6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle and Barack Obama assemble Higher Ground Productions leadership team  https://t.co/SYKJM3Keet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @TheMERL,  Found this unit in the central admin building of my campus. Apparently, we grow them smaller over h… https://t.co/3g5lOmyaoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cakedaddy4ever @KamalaHarris I do not understand the hysteria over this. The woman thought she had some Native Ame… https://t.co/nhrNKF9ZyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch mad at me because SHE was talking shit about me to a stranger?? Yeaaah I don’t understand Portland bitches. We are not the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen I thought my dad was the only person who said “who’s on first” 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @tomselliott It can be true that a black gay man fabricated a story about being a victim of a hate cr… https://t.co/zuCWzkNnpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to #Win @GeorgeStrait tickets. You should too! https://t.co/VMZFDUnFki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToniHargis @BuzzFeed Lol I’d be the type that still tools around town in my pre-owned Volkswagen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanbpeterson I am currently reading, "OUR CULTURE: WHAT'S LEFT OF IT.  This is such a good reading list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurawonderswhy @TrueFactsStated Yes. Yes. Yes, but his mental illness, drug use and  dementia should be his famil… https://t.co/dQTJXH3SUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that part of your drivers test when they ask you to turn on the left then right blinker??   Someone tell m… https://t.co/NyBlm9N4WW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a boy I made out with when I was 14 tonight and that was..... a time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing App Uses Your Smartphone’s Camera and Flashlight to Detect Diabetes  https://t.co/hMbh1Scvhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart before I saw the Talk music video: 💔 my heart now: ❤️  @thegreatkhalid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein Norman, you will know this legal question's answer. What is it called when it can be ordered that a p… https://t.co/DNGyO1YIM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaCardsPack Earlier he said Shaq was the most dominant center of all time....SMH....he did the same retweet thin… https://t.co/bLbE45L8st]]></document><document><![CDATA[On garbage days you identify as a female and leave it for a man. It a subway, you identify as a female, so someone… https://t.co/HPmBNG6IEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoicePremiere   Wow you missed out on the trio. Better luck next time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am proud of who I am, and the journey I am on. Nothing can stop me. #proudmuslim #TransformationTuesday https://t.co/uLD3xT62kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rawstarr @Thattinyassgirl @bri_sacks Unemployment is low.  If you have to move to find a job that beats going to j… https://t.co/UXO0ttZCwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents gifted us a weekend to Blue Harbor instead of things for Christmas. Second year in a row. Such a great p… https://t.co/3BGGz1gFch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayneC37 @Raluca_Florea @Leahlangleben @pctwood_74 @JamesCraigmyle @KIMBERL10021594 @k9_max @ChicagosFines19… https://t.co/781EGEY0uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TV914 After seeing a tweet with the guy dressed in a ball gown... https://t.co/MygrUMceZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight our @HHStigerhoops team plays at 7pm!  The winner goes to state!   I love watching this team play with each… https://t.co/gfIZZ9Oyo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ayo_X_ Chiiilllll i only throw up peace signs. Also not pictured is you with a corona with 🤙🏽. Thank u, next]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is a full moon. I’ve always loved full moons. Before I knew my late husband I used to belong to a group that… https://t.co/6bwZzGghZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nat_in_thehat @HaleyChapp @NikitaDragun But it is that deep lol medical professionals need to know if you’re trans… https://t.co/SOyZKkuQ59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exclusive behind the scenes video from the set of “I Spit on Your Grave: Deja Vu” just came out!  This had me crack… https://t.co/zS4b76XBmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASaunders_PGH You don’t know Andy Isabella ! Great player, very determined, dedicated and love of his family &amp; football 🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissJazzDaFunk Eh, it's not TOO unpopular an opinion. I'm alright with it at most, and I mostly like the animation… https://t.co/NG7H2GqYRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Valentine’s Day. I always have. What’s better than celebrating love? All kind of love. These two make my hea… https://t.co/IXcu6Mg10h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniek_p Thankful for your focus on these things Annie, and the time you took to wrestle with your own voice, past and present.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helloimadde dude i remember one time it happened to me at work and Lucy was super worried and made me go to the do… https://t.co/bisAP2H87M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, this has aged SUPER well. Episode two, and it’s totally cool that a dude films himself having sex with women wi… https://t.co/YkiY9uMKTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a v good day™ and now I’m up thinking about all the reasons it was a v good day™ and finishing it wit… https://t.co/ZhxHg6ReC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful downtown Los Angeles tonight. @ Downtown LA https://t.co/wFXvLmATch]]></document><document><![CDATA[KR says I remind him of Winona. But feelings are a lot more powerful. Like a tsunami.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hows the day treating you  #MIAMIHeat #chicas #danidaniels   #miakhalifa   #brazil #brazildating #sexy #biggass… https://t.co/d264LmyIrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tony_BATtista @American_Heart Keep going Vinny!! We need more kids that keep believing in the magic of the world!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pickerington North Clarinet Choir pictured with organizer and director, Tom Shook https://t.co/qkxr5ZniVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept pretty much all evening, and now I’m wide awake but too lazy to do anything....]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY MOTHERRRRR like chill mama all u ever order is customized crocs and dog food how do you not remember]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get started with the basics and learn how to add in more beneficial foods to gain more health and energy. I d… https://t.co/ofnopCWxfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just lily and I enjoying #NationalMargaritaDay on friday...🍸 and to answer your question...yes tequila got the best… https://t.co/KiMILEp1GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mookyluv3 @IAMBATMANakaBr1 I don't know either but please let me know. Love you Miss Mooky❤️😊 https://t.co/JPl7dOg5EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of our most-requested #dermbff fixes is for addressing the thin, crepey skin under the eyes 👀 . As we age, our… https://t.co/0cIxhejE1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ian telling no nigga how to treat me. Ima get YOU before I let you get me 🗣💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day treats from my co-workers! *Except for the donut holes from #KCDonuts. I bought those. 😉 https://t.co/gdg3WuTTud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grief can be a real struggle following a loss in your family. If you are not able to attend our class starting in A… https://t.co/uy3GJUpwIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let my neighbors continue to leave nasty note on my car and when I need to use the handicap spot #multiplesclerosis… https://t.co/q9OGMGud41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing trip to Naples! TY Shannon Reilly Hanna - our incredible “hostess!” https://t.co/EC3vszomcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The brilliant @iamjohnoliver RT: Brexit III: Last Week Tonight with John Oliver (HBO) https://t.co/iyXW1ChKh5 @LastWeekTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[how would she know everyone was gonna call her a crackhead for laughing at a feather]]></document><document><![CDATA[BAD BAD accident on 232. Deputies said it will be a while before anyone can get through. Avoid that road if you can and be safe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Never heard of that museum. I did do @VikingCruises on the Danube and was impressed with their tours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diamonds are a girls best friend. 💎💕 #nikkimarieapparel @ Tiffany &amp; Co. https://t.co/TiP80DZjXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris You realize that ERs will just raise prices. Go after the arbitrary ER Trauma 1 fees that are a cash… https://t.co/Uagy1KNvtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s known in history, God asked cats to rule the world first. They said no thanks, they had better things to do 😹 https://t.co/8mmzQZ342a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggkrupa Why don’t they ever play Witkowski?  And I wonder where Osgood has been too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally ran out of social media to check this morning so now I’m looking at the universal feed in Venmo..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Cover Girl by @NKOTB on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/4jdgXE0q5h https://t.co/PAMPbHa8YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next witness is Nikka Powell. She is the sister of Riley Powell. After prompting from the prosecuting attorney,… https://t.co/bdKtPdjDaM]]></document></documents></author>