<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@corey_snow @SFDOPartners @SalesforceOrg @SalesforceDevs @SalesforceAdmns @trailhead @salesforce https://t.co/WqAJH56h0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day out in Venice. Visiting my cousin from New York. #california #croatian #croat #selfie #beach #actor… https://t.co/GrNy41kUvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the “leader of our country” gracefully and respectfully answering a reporter’s question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Just keep throwing shit at the wall to see what sticks. You are a disgrace to the office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you finally let God guide your life; things shift at the speed of light, according to his will... Trust me, I… https://t.co/CZ4c3jyUOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @itsyvejr! And apologies for getting it wrong earlier! Check out @WebAuthenticity (Authentic Web Solution… https://t.co/KVr4k7NTxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gearing up to host an incredibly talented group of #nextgen leaders this evening at R-Labs where we'll take a deep… https://t.co/VIFwozLD3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamirezClaudia_ @valenciam07 @GloriaAlvarez85 @GarcesLaureano Que fue lo que más le gustó Srita.Ramires?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elkins_sam hey it’s sam from the youtube comment. lets shoot soon? https://t.co/ly7Y96rNRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbenzie @OntarioPCParty @LisaThompsonMPP I agree with the courts. The curriculum was too much too soon for li… https://t.co/fEs3HhES5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hidden leaf villa- i mean the music industry will thank itach- i mean kanye later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merryshoebell @KymFrank @WVUSWG @TheHubbyDaddy @road_av @Control4 @tweet_daniellek @MarsAVIT @TierPM @vacajun Let'… https://t.co/DZJdYSMqwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I'll personally admit that @MittRomney is right: 🇷🇺 is the enemy to 🇺🇸 democracy: https://t.co/6VnOd1WFSX (vi… https://t.co/fAbpWeIJaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went to the World Cup in Montreal. These women (Germany too) took time to stop and talk to kids in the hotel. Th… https://t.co/HaXRTyxx38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Life is WAY to short. #rip #lukeperry :(   https://t.co/bYCicH05JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChemicalAT SC struggled horribly down the stretch. Broken team. But, Trojans have guys that can get hot and help w… https://t.co/gzt58aFFGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[grateful for the friends who are always there...not the ones who are they there when they need me🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via Original Photo Copyright @StevieStone09 ©) @StevieStone09 + @MadChild57 #StrangeNoizeTour2019 w/Special Guest:… https://t.co/dSGsYvaizm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revolucion3_0 COMPARMEX  ANDA  QUERIENDO TRANZAR  AL PRESIDENTE..COPARMEX  ANTIMEXICO SON CORRUPTOS PRESTANOMBRES.… https://t.co/xKoRxYJW4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Sorry to say, they will not remove her from that committee, nor will she be removed from congress! T… https://t.co/XmKFcQsZ5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendonWoodsPD the Commission terminating the Executive Director of the Investigative Agency after he told commiss… https://t.co/yPYQkDhqCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just the other day the looked as though Christ could arrive any second. I was filled with joy at the thought. Then.… https://t.co/lCSj7FprkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump He seems nice... https://t.co/OhEE1AQD60]]></document><document><![CDATA[This, here, now 😊  #ViennaPhilharmonicOrchestra #ÁdámFischer #CarnegieHall #NewYorkCity #VPOTour https://t.co/V2dVrKAbHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little man thoroughly enjoyed his first Mardi Gras parade...and that hamburger! https://t.co/dBeqEpLwkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[W O M A N   U P  bijouindochine : ......because every day should be #internationalwomensday 💥  Sending mad love and… https://t.co/OqyQwe1Etj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKONOHIO @Oscars2019Live_ @buzzman888 @pinkk9lover @Trump454545 @AppSame @LVNancy @heyitsCarolyn @baalter… https://t.co/yFFCMx4RFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you watching #TheBachelor? If you’re curious if I’ll be talking about it tomorrow on #GoodMorningLubbock.....… https://t.co/EwXmSt1chC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to move out of my apartment because the people above me got a puppy, and I swear everytime I go to bed… https://t.co/t5E0FI8V2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walter Ostanek - Clarinet Polka (instrumentaal) https://t.co/0EI5ILtshS via @YouTube. Happy Fat Tues!  Enjoy some Paczki😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sampioofficial @Flapdoodles 1st answer would not be an appropriate response to a child's question on Twitter. Howe… https://t.co/jEZLL2F5NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMuze_ I know. She was a great person. She was just such a normal person then she could turn on the actress of coarse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyEricRI @LPMisesCaucus @ThomasEWoods Maybe you missed that those are things Tom said about Nick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realStephenK62 @AndiePG @TheRickyDavila This makes a great point! That kid was such a coward. His gripe was with t… https://t.co/m5MrO2nIH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#trhss Sheridan gets a big 3 from golfer Costa Coconis and two tough runners from Ethan Heller and extends its lead… https://t.co/xmfCfVcQBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to go to my next local Smash Ultimate tournament wearing this 😂 https://t.co/hatrKswHOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Maple Hill Restaurant in Maple Shade, NJ https://t.co/8MTr9PzLKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Traditional Lager by @Yuengling_Beer @ Patrick's Beer Haven — https://t.co/w9jUDfW9YA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buchanan FD R26 at Peekskill St. Patrick’s Day parade https://t.co/6SUIQkTQeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berryaldridge21 Wait, people get out of college in 5 years? 😂 4.5 here - but latest stats show a great deal of stu… https://t.co/A6d18yT9Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm glad I got the whole me being a dickhead p.o.s out of the way already i really feel better bahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my Dad being installed as a minister in church yesterday, I am so thankful to see God working in… https://t.co/C5QpnMPat6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Day 2! #ochmrashow2019 #ocean98 @ Roland E. Powell Convention Center https://t.co/Ege9oBFF9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorCaffery It has a Bond villan sound for sure. This is no way to run a post-industrial megastate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xCepterK @Renee6878217 @MegaManZero88 Exactly I think he’s a great character no matter what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChuckBush @stoolpresidente @chaseelliott @kimmiecoon @Blaney @StreamlineHotel Was there not a show last week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real, the people in the crowd that night might have experienced the best show of the decade in hip-hop. This wa… https://t.co/EPNO1NoSTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before I leave for a long vacation/trip, I always leave Future Ben things to do and ways to come down and chill for… https://t.co/oY7cPJMEuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MossbergCorp @MossbergCorp still waiting on a dealerto get one in Northern Virginia...hopefully soon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike35033639 @davereaboi @DonaldJTrumpJr Own properties. Disregarding intelligence briefings. Using Fox News as a… https://t.co/609YiIoh0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might get behind this Birmingham Iron thing. Their defense is solid, I love Trent Richardson, and the uniforms lo… https://t.co/4T20iteb6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOregonRA @TR0771N @Carterdsc @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/WsQXn6lxQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielleqquinn good morning Danielle happy Monday to you beautiful lady enjoy your day from John in Manhattan New York💓💓💓💓💓💓👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen 👂 do you get it yet? Everything is connected.  It’s all part of the long term goal and vision. . . Have you… https://t.co/btXubyNLPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kurt_BSH It’s not the record we want, but it’s the record we need right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rightytighti @GoboMontaco @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Love it, Roger is Awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdberdMolina claro que nooooo yo lo elegiría aunque nos quede mal de los males el menor]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you tell a girl “age is just a number” well your prison sentence is just a number too ig 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearNotesApp I was wondering if there were any plans to allow for editable drawings from within Bear. I use Bear o… https://t.co/1LZOFrIw1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @MainStreetIowa #MSIawards were so inspirational.  The message is always “this is a self-help program and it ta… https://t.co/H2dFHJrFrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They are losing their shorts due to you!  You are not well liked by them at all.  Bye bye farm votes]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎵🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼🎼"GO GET A BAG"BRAND NEW MUSIC BY RICK GARLEY FT.  AN-G-LUST.  AN ARCHI… https://t.co/4fw12Uj8l5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for him. False accusations needs to be addressed as well. Somebody loses valuable time in their life when they… https://t.co/9w6cmfUGhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to Miami. (@ Northwest Florida Regional Airport (VPS) - @flyvps in Eglin AFB, FL) https://t.co/pyAKW2XfdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you leave a manifesto, or sex questions, or blue waffle picks I don't care. I have a goal,and not many seem to b… https://t.co/pSzbSpuy0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like things would have been different had they split this weekend but I appreciate the Blackhawks not making… https://t.co/R3H3Gr9pcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinoluna I present to clients on this topic slot, let’s chat over a 🍺 sometime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianmele great job reporting on Fox and friends on a sad story-Alabama-and you look great in red, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blaydz520 @LunarMeow @ThomasKlineMD Avoid that shit like the plague too. https://t.co/QKSBaRcydB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepugdc I don’t think this is working out the way Boras thought it would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Santa Margarita 76, Foothills Christian 66.   Max Agbonkpolo finishes with 28 points, Jake Kyman had 22.  DJ… https://t.co/bHBBn8P7La]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissLilyDoodle A crisp bar!  Mom makes cheesecake that way.  Lets the eater choose the topping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day ash_patino !!! Crazy in love with this beauty!! . . . . . #fujifilm #x100f #blackandwhite… https://t.co/4rW6CAZeWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few of our engines.  Day two at the ARA Rental Show.  #deutz #poweredbydeutz #deutzxchange #ararentalshow @… https://t.co/EIMvVk4WkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The freedom lovers over on @foxandfriends didnt talk about Parkland at all this morning but they did have Dana Lose… https://t.co/tNkAQCwCBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH MY GOD MY LAST RT HAS ME SO DEAD I CANT STOP LAUGING I WOKE UP MY MOMS LAUGING 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[You folks in Beaver County, check this Twitter Page out! https://t.co/EofDAkEUvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The almighty Real Madrid got washed by a bunch of YMCA saturday players??? Lmaooooo https://t.co/SuET64m8bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what @Eminem  should  do  while on tour... bring  out @BustaRhymes  to perform  one of their classic  trac… https://t.co/hBmhaEl5vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[if lebron doesnt win the lakers atleast one ring, he wont even be a lakers legend 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of like the Texas version of the Yard of Ale (just on steroids) (at @YardHouse in San Antonio, TX) https://t.co/25Q30Twdyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to our Toronto innovation center to lead some exciting technical solutions workshops all week for customers… https://t.co/XOd4TQIgKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewT61830774 @WoodsfordMartin @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow “The Nonbeliever’s Favorite Verse”… https://t.co/E3dE1RyevU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just unlocked Chief Chirpa! #starwarsgalaxyofheroes #starwars #ewoks #starwarsewoks #ewoksofinstagram… https://t.co/VoRiw9YQA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insanity:  China is not benevolent. Sending student to study there is not a very good idea at the moment. Encouragi… https://t.co/BInaVVKRGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinman905 Tell him that Leafs paid refs tonight !! 2 borderline calls I hate the refs !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American Legion sponsored monument erected by mothers in 1925 should not be torn down, it celebrates sacrifices… https://t.co/19DJCDXgvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tagruber @AlohaHa59067534 @EinsteinMaga @GodFirstGina @BundyGP @BellaInxs2 @ARedPillReport @krunalley… https://t.co/v0oveNSCJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linda_lballis @FlyingMonkeys @DrunkPolkaroo @Paul__G__ @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist @ottawahockey… https://t.co/jSi0LLuoKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I don't know why you even dignify the cringeworthy @dc_spotlight with a reply. Since when does… https://t.co/n8AbMJw4Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Way harder than it looked 💀” #Crossfit games open 14.5  21, 18, 15, 12, 9, 6, 3  Thrusters | Bar facing burpees… https://t.co/OSpnkAzNib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quimdomenech Te digo traes al @realmadriden clavado tanto que tienes sueños húmedos con cada jugador,recuerda el que ríe al último...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigkstone Have you seen his dating app photo?    😂😂😂🏀🏀 https://t.co/2vZ0k4IKQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EarnhardtKelley They keep talking about the 12 car I'm going to lose it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehicklife Can someone please help this person receive a triple-tummy-tuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeepinUpWitRai_ Jason still listens to his mom. Michael kills his family. ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naijadailyfeed I thought this was commonplace in Naij - if you don’t travel with security/military escort or Naira then nawa for you oh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bierdeutsches @gifdsports @Cnyari Now, someway, somehow he needs to work with veteran players and younger ones ali… https://t.co/EjJwnPx1Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Lippert23 @poweredbytacos2 @Hugeshow Look at record, look at rosters, look at your best win, then look at UM’s.… https://t.co/Fe2UXdwPcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentines Day vibes.. 😍.. best move I ever made! #valentinesday #love #wifey https://t.co/EwsG9PXWul]]></document></documents></author>