<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Um, it felt great reuniting with muh sister this weekend. Although, we regret sleeping in and not going to church t… https://t.co/mS6d14CJi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMSEarlyCareer Last Saturday was the first time I’ve been that close to a tornado. I was honestly a little bit sca… https://t.co/8RO3rTfErm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we made @fuelrl tonight. Got into the top 10 and wrecked. Then I got penalized for a lane infraction and then… https://t.co/JmHWfG9n7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[(5/6) Bonus question: Is there an easy way to see, in each case, what the AVERAGE number of vertices-of-tiling-#2 p… https://t.co/pjHEH1x7QS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyNolanArt Oh - um - it may be different for me specifically because I’m a speaker. I bought a ticket that I li… https://t.co/Vs6LAzgsAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Fire-Era Mansions In River North Saved Again From Demolition — For Now https://t.co/1JagnoPHY2  #Monday… https://t.co/ZhTjvm1y1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forabogey @MisterVegas1957 Let’s just say if James dropping ~30 points in a game was Menzies biggest problem, Rebe… https://t.co/bQ0Ko3iDLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to a con and picked up two new "kitty" heroes from tomkellyart . I love these things, I have quite a few I h… https://t.co/Ohz7zsp9tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsmon77 @SweetEmmyCat I don't think so. He was a live wire. This gang is cool cats. He was just in the wrong place… https://t.co/r5TYw7IlQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matracaberg Just the Orbison stuff would be enough, but then the rest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lawrenceville/Grayson, Ga.  Home https://t.co/4E27EQ5gQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a Russian blue named Beaker for a long time. She was super smart, loved playing “build a nest” and walking ar… https://t.co/HRcsGQClkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always nice coming out this way on a day off and doing a little adventuring. This preserve is one of the state's mo… https://t.co/dlManMULmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scoopclemons If you can get a cheap flight, it might be worth it for this. Otherwise, meh. https://t.co/2NQFmhzFFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnywrenn @ggreenwald Actually, no.  Wrong on just about every count.  In fact: https://t.co/1MjUaNMgHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshallCohen @jaketapper He worked for Trump 3 months. Try not to fake this up to much for your dummy viewers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroIinalot @bretmanrock Them: "Just let him go, girl. He'll come back if he really wants you." Me: https://t.co/iwR4KAP0aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGertz Two criminals represented by Cohen who have as much credibility as their criminal lawyer.  Even less bec… https://t.co/4CSj61ooYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MySluttyCams @absoluteukbabes @robertgiguere59 @stu007gots @bazooka_tubes @constance_in Mmmmmhmmmm 🔥🔥🔥😍😍😍🔥🔥🔥💯💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Good can come from Hypocrisy? Unfortunately, a whole lot. See https://t.co/44CJlRj9N1 https://t.co/gYHd84rGR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek His brain is incapable of FOCUSING!!! https://t.co/0Bv1N8x8ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamario44 @CALLMEMRTIBBSS @JustRyCole @DekuSaiz No at what point last year were we a playoff caliber team?  We had… https://t.co/HgL2hGtaDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunhausTeam you keep setting off my Google and telling it to play mother's be aware....... I couldn't be more happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockyohio thank you for following...check out our new 10 minute #horror short written by @brown_brantley and direc… https://t.co/IbjotEuDSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sidenote: @OfficialEGO looking a bit trimmer these days.  Nothing really to say about it. Just noting.… https://t.co/Uh7Il86llG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SulomeAnderson @JustWhatNowWhy Rwandan genocide had transistor radios 1 hand urging to kill w/machete other hand.… https://t.co/cGNS0S5Hvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@streamsong how long have the eagle coins existed for? Can I pay to have one shipped to Boston??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Ocala #FL  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/OtMkzi67ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Booming Rollers (2019) by @ModernTimesBeer at @McGregorsCBW — https://t.co/dwSYsGUYzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Wait I thought the Republicans won the senate.. Sit down chuckles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belle Vernon smelling upset. Larry Callaway with a bucket as he draws a foul. Leopards leading Highlands, 44-39, wi… https://t.co/BmhZmebBC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork Cali AG Xavier Becerra drafting miltary families ... 'the troops' into his face time on cable news]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is important to support anthem through their launch issues and to not allow the ratings to deter you permanently… https://t.co/mpaKPvqogV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six JSO officers at one scene and it wasn’t a Curry commercial? Jacksonville police shoot and kill armed rape suspe… https://t.co/WVZwX2b5V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colts outscore EEA 16-15 in second quarter, but still trail Raptors 33-22 at halftime of D11 Class 2A quarterfinal… https://t.co/vfFn7G9rYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Morning Snowfall near @BallState ❄️ @matt_mccutcheon @WTHRcom  #WTHRSunrise https://t.co/L422cwl8Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mayor achievement of ICARE that has been pushing this for years after the current admin closed the last daily hom… https://t.co/xNjnlFRGg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Of late  Democrats are driven by hate and envy, not by love and  compassion as they want us to believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocBoiP @jaggerhype The girls won’t let me put a plate down especially when Tron is in the kitchen]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just have to say that I still don’t like Paul George.... 😕 #TeamIsEverything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melo is like Cam'Ron to the Knicks' Dipset. It was never about numbers or accolades. It was about pure attitude and… https://t.co/0VTKiYLZOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DozaEric @IHboog @thebirdfarmer @JenSchweigert @HedrickJessica @FarmChicJodi @BootscootinGMaw @AtlantaAgCurt… https://t.co/ah3Gp4mCHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slamming is so offensive to black parents and nobody ever explained it 😂😂😂😂 they didn't have to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamDEMRICK You mean, you ain't bleed out yet!!🤣 https://t.co/qYKx80Xx4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northrop26 @Dubt0wn @davesnorthrop @davidnavarra18 Bring me all the Lox and Bagels in the land!! 🥯]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Flooding—It’s happen this week up north &amp; today is a perfect day to prepare since it’s #FloodAwareness day of… https://t.co/kj89Kdcr2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nao, Miguel, Allesia Cara, Sam Smith, Halsey, Ariana, Gallant, Mabel, Lorde, Dvsn, Paramore, Sampha some of my favo… https://t.co/pTuR4tjarA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Walker crossed 25K. Time 01:55:36, pace 07:40 min/mile, est. finish 10:15 am https://t.co/1qbZM4QRys #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You and Putie overturned a legitimate election 2016. Therefore turn-around is fair play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s electric time 2night at @RockwoodNYC , a monthly feature of my (usually bluegrass) weekly residency. Partly to… https://t.co/icSpNaOJdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceMcAlister I don’t even think the “good business” argument is really accurate. It’s not good business imo to t… https://t.co/dR0UccNoIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this happens, then Mueller is going to need to testify under oath as to whether he was rushed. Because we had he… https://t.co/P5Rp5xNmzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta get that #keto dinner!!! #ketomealprep #mealprep #dukecityguy https://t.co/piEch8MeiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SHSFLAGSHIP 💪 reminds ALL our Bulldogs to put in 100% effort into every assignment, test and Re-do work to have a… https://t.co/ealyLs46q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryGraff tweeted this 33 minutes ago. @nbc29 #iLoveCVille #iLoveVa https://t.co/Uu6BiNjotv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nisleecita @Asoprofasil @Asodepa @sosanimalvzla @fundaproba @ZuleikaMN ¿de que raza es?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey ikeausa it’s Saturday you want to open more than 5 checkouts out of 13??? @ IKEA https://t.co/J2aik6hITL]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@YaleLawSch @YaleLawNSG Introducing @EricHolder and Professor Cristina Rodriguez @cmrodriguez95 for a conversation… https://t.co/mEX25tm3gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bomborisimo Con un corte de Picaña y asado de Tira, salsa molcajeteada, te digo una cosa si ganan, pierden o empat… https://t.co/rWgoY6VMcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ He’s a dipshit. That’s why SNL makes fun of him. He just wants to be recognized as important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker still think this was a Modern Day Lynching? Maybe @JussieSmollett should be charged with a hate crime? https://t.co/ejfeNSC4rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Robin is to “gourmet burgers” as  @luhrsman is to “working comedian.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is art spiritual? Is theater? We explore this in the Washington Heights Arts Salon, Fri. March 8! We'll hear from M… https://t.co/93rEmzywHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReckoningComing @o_marianne @WomenForTrump4 @SaraCarterDC You can’t trust the news, do your own thinking and resea… https://t.co/HUYqKsRrTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orlando Fringe loves ya! Happy Valentine’s Day! https://t.co/0PR7wqLQNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinbennett18 @caymiendavis @AdamSchefter Great comeback. Really intuitive contribution to the discussion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatRetro Problem was that it was trying too hard to be Ren &amp; Stimpy without forming its own identity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BreitbartNews #Democrats can not find anything good to do. ( 0 ) Why? you ask ? Because, The Donald,… https://t.co/Z6mEx63DJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @w_terrence @lyft @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse T, man I saw the photo of the Lyft car.  Prays are w… https://t.co/b2UQtnPLqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxEmandBetEm @rogueclown @SeaBass912 @PicksByDynasty @theyreoff @thedailygallop @pinfante97 @Amateurcapper Look at you Vinny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kebabFromGenos @MarkBullockNFL @ChadwikoRCC @CraigHoffman Keenum and McCoy are on one year deals. Both can be trad… https://t.co/5gtIRg4qzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSeth1107 @LAFC @Tymiller01 @LAGalaxy @LampStrong  @KevinEHartman @orangecountysc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/mgnAw5tAAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh, Oh! Guess what day it is? Huh? Anybody? Its Ash Wednesday! 🕊🙌🏾🐫 Currently,  it's 10° under Clear skies.  Sunris… https://t.co/FD8uH1ImA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony is Ren/Daniel disappears and comes back but I change completely]]></document><document><![CDATA[@38O9127469 @Stop_Trump20 Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Bar Number is 48962. He violated 18 U.S… https://t.co/0nuZvP4sLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMileskiKFAN @RadioFalness what do you think about a trade along the kind of Jason Zucker for Mats Zuccarello? #WildFanLine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comedy tonight at @ASTLComics , new cocktails and a bunch of weird ****. Open mic starts at 7:30, show at 8pm. https://t.co/HdrSNA3i1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rund00m @elenakoshkaxoxo even with a moustache she is still sexy. Great now I can't look at them w/o thinking of her now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachergoals Late work, like tardiness, is a detriment to the flow of learning and to those who chose to achieve.… https://t.co/MLAQGWBcPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe WWE made this Alexa Bliss shirt exclusively for me https://t.co/v7Vw26Z8Mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planned targets included several high-profile journalists from MSNBC and CNN. https://t.co/p0YrQ9xpkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyP16 @st_anger_snare @muchmor1 @AlexGuijarro10 @GNDorBust @NateSilver538 So would I! Because if we don't do i… https://t.co/vAFI857Cfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyBraves @bradleyumbb  At the Carver Arena https://t.co/HLI7QVCFOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love speaking with people. You never know what you can learn from others. There’s a lesson to be learned with everyone you meet ✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Witness???? Ok I’m sure he’ll testify.... but..... I bet a they won’t call him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of giving up a specific thing for Lent, I am being generous and just, giving up for Lent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a great visit and conversation with Coach Fabish today, I’m excited and honored to say that I’ve received my… https://t.co/RuHt3tHebq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philritz1 @Paul_Davidsen Not shocking at all. I live in a city were public transportation is common place. Train,… https://t.co/1ejYTyoORX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acmecatalyst @samirose817 @VarshPrakash @sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein She could have done a lot of things. And YOU ca… https://t.co/puFjkkKTDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolte: Never Trump CPAC Coverage Mocks Cancer, Christians, and Baby Murder https://t.co/1qAekLyRfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angcould @Evansgirl12 @BenMastersxxx I know that did not come out right. Didn't check it before hitting the reply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck-It Ralph character visit #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #epcot #werehome #Disney #wreckitralph @ Ima… https://t.co/0xz127rS7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMR09 @starck_patrick And another one gone and another one gone and another one bites the dust!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This raggaeton playlist sucks..... whoever made this one was in their feelings...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 No the school system is not. It’s an terrible disservice to the country not to teach the citizens what the USA is all about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Gordon GIF grade for Hamidou Diallo’s second dunk https://t.co/TPlqkLcsnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only cause they the same height she looks uncomfortable but being choked is lit so overall nah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamonMC3 Did you know Kamala Harris lives in a  *house*, with wait for it - fucking walls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpkiser He is most certainly NOT “a little Jesus” aka not a Christian. He must be shunned]]></document></documents></author>