<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s funny that this POS now expects the presumption of innocence but didn’t think Kavanaugh did! For the record, w… https://t.co/LncuUAvMDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had so much fun tonight. Thanks for the dance party @emoraleigh 🖤 https://t.co/2DFpkSHZQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALNMGN18 @LuisaBarrantes5 @WorldsBestCBS @dimash_official #TWBDimash #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFittXXX @DJChiChiLaRue @HunterSmithXXX @xxx_blanco @TheWesleyWoods @CadeMaddoxxx @LincolnTunnelXX @Brendanpatxxx 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went to bed at 11am yesterday. woke up around 2pm. went back to bed at 10pm. and just now woke up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn't it make sense to ensure your #nervoussystem is working properly? If you've never had #chiropractic, it can… https://t.co/EukiTLo34A]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you just can’t bear to get up, but you know if you steal on more moment in bed, you’ll be late. Ye… https://t.co/j35DwYhNtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grease 2 is kinda wack there’s nothing better than the first Grease movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krysalislu @mixellemedina @Ludvick6 @Daniel_S181 @Greg_MPCS @metroCDMX_QA Omg that’s it’s sooo cool, can I enjoy l… https://t.co/yCK53tprlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Diesel Mechanic"? What did you like most about that job? #Automotive #Hopewell, VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo Beautiful story.  So glad Vulcan survived and was found by such a loving family.💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[After GRR 15k guess who took a nap.  #meandmysonDavid. #hesstillzonked. #buthedidit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evettexo when u announced it i thought boy cause I also see u being a mom of boys 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_moonshoes The layered necklaces were a good choice to contrast with the plunging neckline 10/10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodNotesApp It’s not updating when I manually click on the update icon in my App Store (updates section).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland My TEXAS Governor is trying to fight AOC for Capitalism and is against Socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clint_geiler @bedolcaroline Can we reserve a month for you Clint? Ya know, the month that celebrates douchebags. S… https://t.co/z2ZxF8uV4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently accepting suggestions for where we should go next year ✈️🗻⛷🏂 @ Killington, Vermont https://t.co/uKLTzQicZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday’s are for forgetting you have a meeting until you literally walk past the meeting you’re supposed to be in a… https://t.co/rWnhRsD2zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a spiritual experience 💙@robynkonichiwa https://t.co/ODB0KWsfE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncommonUnivers I think Dresden's Chicago. Crazy scary, but also so much fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne Happy 🎂 Mom...you did a wonderful job raising Mr. Payne.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know? IT’s NATIONAL NUTRITION MONTH!!! Have you been wanting to bite into a healthy lifestyle? Well, let me… https://t.co/KN5Vb7YZzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent about five hours today listening to that podcast with Alex Jones today. So, that’s how my maternity leave is going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My forever Valentine! Counting down to March 30! #ValentinesDay2019 Send is your Valentine pic for #MorningRushATL 🥰 https://t.co/oXtTDHhJI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dylanlovesdogs I’d come swingin. Nobody touches my dog. Horrible people]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomansDay &amp; today's Friday book talk to students was Scythe by @NealShusterman. Great book showcasing strong women! 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InvestorsPool @thedailybeast Look Aid drinker.  #SHAME #IMPEACHTRUMP and lock up his minions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy much? 😊Thank you Canadian Music, East Coast Style! thedardsnl 📷 @jefferystraker #faimontreal @ Montreal, Queb… https://t.co/aW2I2jHew2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsGAGirl #Pedophilia is RAMPANT in our World! It's s heinous crime &amp; needs to be stopped. If you know of a… https://t.co/4hRaSy24rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[the difference in photo quality with an #iPhone7Plus vs #iPhoneXSMax 🥰🥰🥰🥰 https://t.co/5Zss7hjTaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a sanctimonious prick. @JeffBezos will do whatever he wants with his company. Go pound sand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today begins a week which includes SIX OPPORTUNITIES FOR METAFIT AT FUSION FITNESS downtown Mt. Pleasant. Sunday 5:… https://t.co/E2dVnxpLZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Wouldn't it be nice to see her get taken down real hard. She give women a bad name...]]></document><document><![CDATA[aye yo chill, my tweets ain’t about you. they’re literally song lyrics, fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the #leadership @Microsoft appreciate all the work you are doing to include our #community. @500Valuable… https://t.co/1hgC78kQEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayThoughts #positivethinking #March2019 #March1st #ThinkSpring https://t.co/96uOM7RzWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirleyb4433 @SallyAlbright Forget thinking about it, let’s get the press to find out this time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels Hey, sometimes you gotta do what you gotta do. You gotta go through it to get to it, you feel me. It… https://t.co/pZCOwSC6rW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don’t believe a word of that.  You’ve separated innocent children from their parents. Your adm… https://t.co/GTRlfqqsUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bugsoton About to get in my car to drive home, but I'll continue tuning  in to you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over a dozen dogs have been seized from a New Hampshire couple who were considered top breeders.  @wgme  https://t.co/JU6wvh0Ipt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenWolfe @fishlimit598 Oh, please. It's just a primary. You know, with opponents and things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaCollins11 I'm sure. But I'm speaking specifically about the Pope and COMPLICIT Vatican officials and priests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if emotional pain continues to get worse or if it levels off. How extreme can that feeling become before you go numb?]]></document><document><![CDATA[there are 4 cops just watching another cop search a car right outside our motel room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women's Day!! It's our day ladies!  Shine brighter than ever!! @ John L. Scott KMS Kent North https://t.co/WotYmLcFt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ford government recommends #Ontario #school boards freeze hiring ahead of upcoming budget | CBC News https://t.co/jmnt7pT6ZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attacking Apathy at today’s @whitmancollege #powerandprivilegesymosium My commitment from session one: when I ask s… https://t.co/yqA4aIU6ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiernannn “We didn’t know what a pedophile was in the 70s”  But you didn’t think it was a little odd that a grown… https://t.co/0z9e1m9B1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join 5KPlayer 4th birthday Sweepstakes to win Home Theater Gadget Pack X 10 (HD Projector, Roku Ultra, Popcorn Make… https://t.co/78OMG38kyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asia_tasanee DO NOT GO HIGH !! ... hope you like pain , good luck doll 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[More horrible news from #SCOTUS: Supreme Court will consider letting groundwater pollution escape regulation under… https://t.co/0dov9ehxyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling docu, chilling piece.   “A Night at the Garden” is the most terrifying movie you can watch this Halloween… https://t.co/5J2OCBrVIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramzpaul Congresswoman Omar moves the needle 🔥 https://t.co/rVLg1gHC2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNL might be closed, but @NU_PPC road warriors are still on the job! @NDESchoolSafety @MarioJScalora https://t.co/FFzvOlyaE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bendecida por Dios por la vida .!!! SIMPLEMENTE SIEMPRE  “ YO “ 💕😘💕😘💕😘 @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/GhMC3zGGMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaEdwards_1 @plastiquetiara HAPPY INTERNATIONAL WOMAN'S DAY, LADIES!  💗☺☺💗💗🦄🦄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristinrssmith Wow. Glad I went last night. It was busy, but not packed &amp; no line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axidentaliberal @MatthewWolfff @realDonaldTrump May God have mercy, but may what is right, true, &amp; good prevail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer The will of the people was to put the person with the most votes in that would’ve be… https://t.co/HfdqIbdWmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @cherokeesher2 Sanders had to sign NDA. That might explain all the lies.  But, she’s still a cockroach in my eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Platforms not cleared, be careful. Note to Septa: I managed to get up early and clean my sidewalks. 🙄 https://t.co/b8RtYws09U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to be in your pyramid scheme Facebook group. Pls stop asking me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SVLeadershipLab @UChicagoSoc @SSNScholars @UWSoc @UTAustinSoc @osusoc @UMassSociology  thanks for RT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things really do just work out, even if they seem like they won’t at the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[taking (girl and boy)friend applications ♥ #LGBTQoftwitter https://t.co/deCK6Aql0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this song😇#Jodeci #HairbyEdie😇😇😇🙏🏿🙏🏿🙏🏿 @ Rancho Vista, California https://t.co/WTqz9MDPyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollybackes @anne_theriault I’ve had that one! Or the dash or too high and I can’t see over it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BmoreDoc Yes! We need community land trusts to ensure that land remains in hands of residents and permanently affordable]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️😎 #winterisleaving #snowbunny #iwannabeoutside #stircrazy #cabinfever #sunnies #selfie #goddess #loveandlight @ U… https://t.co/uAR1BgV9ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a crime is committed, committiees,  DOJ, authorities get involved. However, I have never seen committees,DOJ,… https://t.co/CU28ac11ZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a weekend. Always good to visit Hogsmeade. I love this place. Back to the grind with a cutie tomorrow!!! https://t.co/DBhvMeUlyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentStephen @NealRoys So angry!  😠 😡 absolutely disgraceful.   Unbelievably tone deaf!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reasons why I’m not spending money on dumb stuff #100,000,000 https://t.co/gbAhbfRVrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 Bears studied abroad this past winter! Will you? #MorganOnSocial is more than sure today's weather has you dream… https://t.co/swgJVk7oXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 60th Birthday to Barbie! In honor, recommending this awesome @hulu documentary "Tiny Shoulders: Rethinking Ba… https://t.co/9gjY3bb3xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you see the small baby hairs growing? PRP hair growth stimulation works for almost everyone (male and female); i… https://t.co/3rO4MAHEbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Jr. seems to have forgotten that teachers have died attempting to protect their students from gun violence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImabitcSumtimes @9975Ts They are traitors and should be in Gitmo for life or get the death penalty, especially Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chazlouaz @cynthiamckinney I was pointing out the FACT that July 1993 the NIGHT #VinceFoster was murdered  Out of… https://t.co/pkgqoakVma]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone apologized for being drunk at the indoor game tonight I’m fucking dead bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to @allinwithchris for pointing out the absurdity of Paul Manafort getting a lighter sentence than Reality Wi… https://t.co/ohlRvvUMaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaNotJuliet *sips my moonshine like a grizzled old man* Back in the good ole days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_xoyazzz one of my closest friends and i can trust her with mostly anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenSecondSongs Billy Idol, David Bowie, Rod Stewart, Tina Turner, Tom Petty, Bob Dylan, Heart, Johnny Winter, Alice Cooper, Gregg Allman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day #solidarity #IWD2019 #sisterhood #WomensDay https://t.co/vo6caJLDe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timurmeyster @Career_Karma @nanamaia_ I really appreciate this this is honestly the best gift anyone has given to… https://t.co/U79xbe3uno]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love #Dateline, unconditionally. But tonight’s story is making me sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m almost to $300 on my 300 follower day! Get me there, slaves 💸💸💸 #findom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pussykake @RoseGirlSweet I've gave a few bad ones but the 👅🍑 was awful so....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs It's not real money anyway. Let's replace this satanic fake money with honorable true-valued money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to launch my website tomorrow, here’s some portrait previews thanks to @goodbrand0 • 🖤 https://t.co/SZi6nfSwFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Yellowjackets are your undefeated Super Bowl champs! What a fun season watching these future Highlanders! ❤️🏈💚… https://t.co/203NBsAjQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #TheBachelor Women Tell All is so extra and ridiculous AND I GOD DAMN LOVE IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld They are a disgrace to the natural world. Heartless and despicable beings should have consequences. Horrible people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Besides, we all know that the Jews and the Blacks are the only ones with a decent sense of humor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They came out with a few movies on Lifetime network I think? My fav books when I was a teen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impossible to measure with the drifting. @WernerPark North shore https://t.co/ONutL5dXRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 - I have accepted the challenge from @LeahNeas to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews —… https://t.co/TxHUlqnjhJ]]></document></documents></author>