<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So the Dems compromise their funding bill and Trump still says “fuck it, I’m declaring emergency and still getting… https://t.co/pXVPuiC3ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insane the killers in our unsigned seniors event this year! Book your flights coaches, Mark your calendar i… https://t.co/2ZAv3Kv8gA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyeoftheStormZ @PittPenguin44 I don’t think he lies in any way.  He tells what he sees happening in a play.  In fa… https://t.co/ksyklnASP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prof. SI Strong: “The Court loves to give the #arbitration case to the baby justices. It’s interesting because they… https://t.co/Bos1xf52Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayfonsecapr @thonyo1 El Dijo Estate Tax...Nunca  menciono el Sale Tax...Jay Reacciona mijo 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @Aric_Almirola @SmithfieldBrand @StewartHaasRcng @SmithfieldBrand Good Morning staff, crew, team,… https://t.co/OHaxTKciyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irving Quintero completed the Washington Heights 5K! Time 00:18:01 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/Plxi4agKIH #WashHeights5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BudKennedy @JohnCornyn You project well, JC. Here's fellow Texan who knows Constitution. Cspan:… https://t.co/jc4AZ7Bv5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por q AN no discute causas dl apagon casi general q sta ocurriendo n l Pais? a)Por q la Fraccion Gorrin no quiere b… https://t.co/Fyk1z7ojUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[El de la Izquierda Freddy Solorzano se fue con la cabuya en la pata de Aragua. Hay que estar vigilantes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another penalty on Hunwick. Interference this time. Sabres still lead 2-1 with 6:22 left in the second period]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt slow and unfit in my game today. I guess it's time to get more serious about training]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chico1640101 I met Roberto numerous times. He and my Dad were close. He was the best all around ballplayer ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our winner Corrie from yesterday's #WaybackWednesday picked up her cash today! Thanks @PrimeWayFCU… https://t.co/tdFCE9yoKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Your link referred to working conditions in the UK.  Do you represent British citizens now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[was he also feeling losing to the worst franchise and team in sports, and a team that ought to be contracted and di… https://t.co/gMO0L8khxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lapagapeo She turned lunatic. Tell that to any animal https://t.co/NCsjSvGJyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan begins with bullshit pontificating to give the ignorant base a name to resonate. Meh. The adults are sp… https://t.co/FJfShSEYII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the regular season is done.  Whose dunk was the best? @uahhoopsdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[My downstairs neighbor is blasting Sting, and not even his good stuff.... this is s choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew everyone  @sdeebocane  @ilovemusic_76  @LauraScyrkels  @TomKochABC13  @TJParkerABC13… https://t.co/opbAzWuuJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulWiebens @Bravesfan1010a Except that you could never swing like that for MLB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 304 Marina Way #NorthTopsailBeach #NC  #realestate https://t.co/axPPuSXaGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also think it’s important to voice the White, Middle American Man (and Woman) because of the fact that this inter… https://t.co/bNPu5B1Onk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erininnashville @tracey_f @saraclark Yes, all of that. I’m nice about it too…I think all the recruiters understand… https://t.co/S6I8Ib6JvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fashoo_ Yes you are look gorgeous and sexy in a yellow bikini  Yes ur Tatyana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkruesi It’s an optical illusion Or something. I may be standing on the edge of my feet though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go-  where are you at now? C- I am healing and teaching Go-  what are you healing? C- life was being horrible to ea… https://t.co/9QmUC0m5kT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recap of the end of the madness at Silverado last night. Marquael Wright’s 3 sends the game to OT, Jalen Hartwill g… https://t.co/ESqX2NUqGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I apologize to any Christian family members when I criticized your relationship with Christ when you did not formal… https://t.co/DGOSdY6NBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop it Wayne.  Right now.  You are stealing from the vaunted Washington Post.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBB:  The @OgallalaHighBB team leads Scotus 40-37 at halftime.  The Shamrocks trimmed a 14-point double-digit India… https://t.co/XuD9NV1X78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LostInCatLand @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/kPG8xIwT7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2luv4eva1 The easiest way to rent a car! https://t.co/5YRoxmXZoE #CarRental #Like &amp; #Share https://t.co/REN7fe5s3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are ALL victims of procrastination. Start whatever it is you want to change or do TODAY. Time waits for NOBODY! #JustDoIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zepol7 I think it was partially polished bare concrete? Like they sanded it down to a particular level, but not as… https://t.co/PZnPjwdB5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers I feel like I win when the person I vote for has the higher percentage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussellBriar @J11Garner @MeridianBSB That’s you brotha! Proud of you and this #ComeBackSZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump thinks less of his supporters/base than Muslims and minorities. He plays them for fools.  @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/z5IqrPKpEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter was shouting some of these same things this past weekend- #fail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sights at work! The part I love about the ramp... @ Gate C21, Terminal C, Logan International Airport https://t.co/SRWNAhoCYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I definitely have a speeding ticket in NYC that I am determined to fight! I’m so sick 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Graceman66 @RevChuckCurrie @realDonaldTrump What an idiotic reply!  How do you prove a negative?  Prove it’s true troll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤🎸🎶 Something worth remembering... #MedixKickOff2019 #PositivelyImpactingLives @ Lacuna Lofts https://t.co/XJG7oBX9F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee Who the hell cares? Apparently not our own government. Think about how dangerous that is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeMatha, Paul VI, Gonzaga, St. John’s, and O’Connell all receive 1st Round Byes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@by_aoc @MikeroHonky @CynChamplin @HamLibertarian @TheEliza2 @gypsyglutton @bigolfoot @Merica_Media Why you scaring the shit outta me. 😅😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like that I cheated on my diet on my first day lol.  Someone made me a belated birthday cheesecake so I just h… https://t.co/4qRGyU1Xqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames please go visit him lol 😂 he just set a record of creativity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the challenge from @khussey11 to post covers of 10 albums that represent the music of my life: no explan… https://t.co/9O4AZD1ADS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnriquePenalosa Pero hoy! Mientras que en cinco y diez años los sistemas europeos será eléctricos nosotros tendrem… https://t.co/MtljiABCwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FearThePegasus @jwarner15 Come on..He had shoulder surgery and that has affected his shooting motion. He gets offi… https://t.co/nTaFVt4Pv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO COMMENT: Cory Booker REFUSES to Answer Questions about Omar, Abruptly Cancels Briefing | Sean Hannity https://t.co/JtELxwdRTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don’t let it be the ACL Please don’t let it be the ACL   Please don’t let it be the ACL   Please don’t let i… https://t.co/NxbEcm2YHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanduke81 @TommyBeer When you have a very select few that can score, and create their own shots you have to live… https://t.co/IZxpTRni7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABuckvold @mngop It's sad how some people don't even consider this life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude in front of me is confused that the Jersey Mike’s doesn’t sell breakfast sandwiches in muffins.   5 minutes la… https://t.co/aYdPdiJggH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel review: Ben Mendelsohn steals it. Jude Law is still Jude Law. Feel incredibly safe with the MCU in B… https://t.co/uGSdICbXeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I’ll be switching back and forth between #CapsFlyers and #WizMavs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DhaniHarrison @tompetty @lukasnelson @jakobdylan @WillieNelson Interesting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Que descarado este tipo!   ¿Entonces que ha pasado durante los últimos 15 años? ¡Ladrones! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlad_zhukovskiy Так это же напротив американского посольства! Ходящие за грантами всю плитку вытоптали!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NCDOT and Turnpike Authority get federal approval for Mid-Currituck Bridge https://t.co/zcsdVbeHXn via @mark_sentinel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/woLQFvVnhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmataconis Well I mean being sycophants and intimidating witnesses and all https://t.co/mWoCEiwsJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Facebook co-founder’s company Asana signs lease for new SF headquarters - San Francisco Chronicle:… https://t.co/3HXoowhJxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidthe3rd   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)  https://t.co/j0aZbvB0ii… https://t.co/oJpY8ZL9ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. That way my favorite thing. Having someone to let go with and share your daily life with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real disappointed that @CJAD800 thinks a man urinating is news. Ever think that inside his office (truck) that he d… https://t.co/cSqCl4Nbub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamuelSimonis 😃😃😃😃 men nonm nan yo di ki reprezante nou an nan komisyon dyalòg la. https://t.co/qHQdiqXkEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Floats 10% Middle Class Tax Cut With Election Looming. The Only Problem: Congress Isn’t in Session https://t.co/r2WcPfwZHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would sell my soul for someone to bring me some Biofreeze right now #imold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExplrUpstate @GeneseeCountyNY @IGersBuffalo @I_LOVE_NY @promoteWNY Thank you so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my pal A-Rod at the park today ⚾️ @ Madison Square Park https://t.co/6L2qbrr93K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fernanda_strada Mami...le hubieras mandado saludos al penal del estado...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chances for rain don’t drop below 50% until midnight tonight. I’m not optimistic this game gets played]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani Hey put a gag on it already! Dude! Another one of trumps lawyers telling the truth Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw @BraunStrowman on his Instagram account post a throwback pic to his time in NXT with the caption reading “fro… https://t.co/loaJLozZqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could never live in San Antonio.. I’d be a 400 lb alcoholic without question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moshoosho Big ups to all the Asempa Sports crew. I hope Ajax wins today with a huge margin so they can qualify. Kw… https://t.co/sLKasHzUbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rounding3rdSB @CoachJenSewell @FloSoftball I don't believe you need to be a professional necessarily, but be able… https://t.co/KDtu2u34GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twithersAP @AP Easier to tell us what was true than point out all the lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TripleHTheIII @benbruns @apiecebyguy @77cyko However, he’s practicing with what appears to be a wakizashi, not a katana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gothatfunk @AgentOfDoubt @Kizzume @CehBeachActual @xxxild @theantibright @JordieWeeds @JJTalkz @haeriasmind… https://t.co/rTPDqtt7ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@areynarivarola Please do what is best FOR YOU! Muchísimas gracias for constantly being an amazing mentor to me and… https://t.co/59rZxWTFhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely heartbroken at the news of the passing of Brody Stevens. Such a funny guy and a good dude. He had some o… https://t.co/UA93FhmfL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dump A Day Funny Picture Dump Of The Day - 55 Pics #laughter #giggle #smile #amusing https://t.co/AUcqsorjMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kusku72 @williammn27 He seems similar to Julio. But I'd be a little Leary with lack of production]]></document><document><![CDATA[It also will have a downward effect on middle income wages. That level of high paying jobs would have meant that ot… https://t.co/9q9g3nI3KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicassimon @SarahDysart @OfficialHIMYM I can work with that! https://t.co/W0sHYKJspA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacGyverCBS poor choice tonight.   Who really cares about R Kelly....   what's next a Kevin Spacey interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OtsoDiretso @GaryAlejano @SamiraGutoc @fthilbay You should talk about what a liar can do as a national leader and… https://t.co/T9PNn2EksD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittenstop1 we are the factory of ceramic mug in china… https://t.co/dKx0QYXEf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yyyyyep... Leave it to the pp to give all the momentum to the Habs. #CutTheCord #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett used a check to pay these brothers!!! https://t.co/wGexJUtjOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt  I hope that the discussion expands a bit to the connected issues of our drowning in plastic, consumer… https://t.co/9FRnjVEXFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy charter day to ZT 💪🏾💪🏾💪🏾 @Djhoze_ @ForeverSwelly_ @khalon40 @DaBeardedApe @RoTheGoat @SkyRocket_DG @Commerce_Alphas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get some rest, because tomorrow you will receive the good news you been waiting for!]]></document><document><![CDATA[El PRIAN quiso ELIMINAR este VÍDEO. https://t.co/3m01p5TbSA vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal budgets are a reflection of our values. This proposal in it's current form may not exemplify a commitment t… https://t.co/FmjmCmESuT]]></document></documents></author>