<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just found out today that ratatouille IS NOT the name of the rat, it’s the name of the meal. Remmy is the name of t… https://t.co/ewU3ZQMlLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDaydodge @ECMcLaughlin @RepKatiePorter Approximately 30% of bankruptcies in the US are filed because of medical bills.  Disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if king taco don’t have these tamales when i get there i’m causing a scene idc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well.  I can’t say it surprises me. A friend of Trump’s.  And well, New England patriots??   Need I say anymore??]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. District Judge Susan Ritchie Bolton subsequently said the pardon didn’t erase the underlying facts or his conv… https://t.co/3eMz7ZWBu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellylushious LMAO!!!! I think she’s beyond beautiful and I love her products but I’m not here trying to say she’s… https://t.co/hSBVHjE6oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj has helped so many, so many lives, and I want to thank her from the bottom of my heart for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenanderson @paminthelab Thank you! That’s great. See you on Sunday - looking forward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[u gotta do some shit in private so no one can form an opinion or judge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone replies to my pics complaining about me hunting or fishing while wearing makeup https://t.co/xBVq5CkUnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKathrynRoss @DrTiffanyCarson Same...I had a paper accepted with no revisions requested once. It was rejected by… https://t.co/raDXvYKyEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that’s a tongue!!! 💋😛  . . . . #giraffe #crazy #tounge #texas #kissme #fortworthzoo #feedingtime #biggerintexas… https://t.co/iIjeha9Ld4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarafinaas Nah. People who are big know they’re big. They knew they were big before they left the house. At that p… https://t.co/FPmwIXIrM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be encouraged, 21 Days Hope Ladder Journal Dr. Frances Harris the tools you need to reconnect to God and yourself. https://t.co/UvbqhTQTo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol if you have an attitude you might as well keep it to yourself. Because I do not and never will care about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ik Victoria Secret better send off my packages before i lie when they arrive and say ian receive them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NewsieNerd is gracing us with her “lovely” singing voice 🙉.  Tune into @KNWAnews NOW for #GoodDayNWA… https://t.co/QO97NwufpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @KING5Seattle This is kind of sad, he is not an old white dude so they are sure to throw the book at him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've seen so many rainbows (and crows) recently that I'm taking it as a sign from the universe... death + rebirth... the tower + the star]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop using LGBT people as your goddamn shield to try to gain moral high ground on totally unrelated policy. It's fucking ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC The sword símbolo of powerful influence in tweets yeah and ripping the gold and treasury all around the world!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t put restrictions or limits on what God can do for us.  Open up the windows of your prayer life and expand who… https://t.co/8K2igFkNBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milam_i It is. The fact that she thinks she’s about to use up all of the vows really got to me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[These non-ending mega-expensive investigations done with TaxPayer dollars.  Everyone knew media protected HC and Ob… https://t.co/kawUtlmDuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. Such mixed feelings about this. I've deleted many angry tweets over the past week. As much as I'd like everyon… https://t.co/xfGe5o3Ala]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it disgusting that a mother to be endangered her unborn baby to come here illegally. How about the 1000's of… https://t.co/Uo6k4QnSeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorFrank56 @ananjigie @seriousdrexxiv @waterlishi @lillalila @_pureedestinyy_ @gngo909 @pederopdl… https://t.co/y2XQxyymrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claire_Disney @CentrefrancoT @abelmaxwell @FNgenzebuhoro @ReneCViau @choqfmtoronto @LExpressToronto @blogTO… https://t.co/q0DUPAo3Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes! I’m not a morning person and this clock might be oddly motivating. Days’ a-wastin’ indeed! 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dateline Four family members charged with murder.  Now that's a close family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_wellmanr4 @BellScience Too late! I’ve been challenged by @AlynthiaCurtis! I’m on Day 2!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boredmonkey Yes absolutely! We should believe our own eyes the Republicans have sunk so low we shouldn't overlook… https://t.co/PB4cp9SeP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gac_well @DailyMail Wow nearly $2000? Manafort just got convicted of $50million I don’t hear your outrage? Trump i… https://t.co/afnz618hy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pal_fairfield @gofairfieldhigh Congrats!!! Fairfield is proud of you. #KindnessAlwaysWins]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate when my “friends”judge me, without looking or knowing the whole situation ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone who hears these words of Mine and puts them into practice is like a wise man who built his house on the rock. Matthew 7:24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg @nbcsnl @idriselba I want this character to return to SNL!!! Love love love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media favors minority folks, white people at a disadvantage, over time it may take the Muslims to topple aborti… https://t.co/fz3xXpNika]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealLilRizz The fact that it said NBA and not MLB should’ve clued you in 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making sure my kids dont forget how to read and write in their mother tongue, even though they live in Chicago now… https://t.co/9lqJVwb8vA]]></document><document><![CDATA[ordered my bfs Valentine’s Day gift back in January and it just came in today... real life sad 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screaming Happy Birthday to my bffff🎉 So so thankful for you😘 Love you forever💘 @13kmccarty https://t.co/hPqJUNsi3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Mommie Dearest” was just an answer on Jeopardy and I think I technically won $600.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#prettyflyforawhiteguy #Flylikeabutterflystinglikeabee https://t.co/2Ka1izejD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning Amanda 💫  She is so inspiring! Such a hardworking lovely gal that motivated me to work harder in the gym… https://t.co/zxNyPLY331]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 3 completely for profit entities including consulting small businesses, diversity and inclusion workshops an… https://t.co/QtwUqKbpQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best socks! Use this link for 25% off! You will love them! https://t.co/vtWxAlCtc2 @BOMBAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[At a party with like a bunch of trust fund or well off people and I cannot relate at all. Never been to Ibiza, sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#marchmeetthemaker2019 #marchmeetthemaker day #4 #toolsandmaterials @joannehawker I use a lot of tools to do my art… https://t.co/JG4p7xxY67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicboxtheatre @MojitoMamasita this is the movie I told you about!!!! Let’s go]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of stuff is disgusting. So much to legitimately criticise her for, so why resort to lies that also play u… https://t.co/6ud0n8r8DH]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. my dog filter phase, I really felt like ThAT bitch https://t.co/p2zK7lssFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[boys psa... DONT SEND A GIRL WEINER PICS WHEN YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHO SHE IS. It’s weird. Stop. Bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be a Point of Discussion  Regardless if this is CNN or Fox Reporting...SMH at the Imbalance of News Reportin… https://t.co/oel2U9tkuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on this mess to get here at least the pups will have some fun https://t.co/Dt2ga0gOxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckModi1 Pls reach out to us!  We have such aligned goals!   This!  https://t.co/vUtpzGrDOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My VALENTINE'S Bear! Isn't it CUTE?!! @ Byrd Park https://t.co/nJajOoIPDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftdflowers no delivery today, ordered a week ago. Terrible, awful customer service. Massive disappointment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were best friends at first &amp; this came by surprise, but I’m glad we’re so much more than that now💛 https://t.co/wogzcJU1o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[incredible line-up of #WOMEN killing it as #authors #publishers #editors #graphicdesigners #marketers. Get your fre… https://t.co/B78r92kACg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wrong. It’s been done on every President. They were not as publicized but there were requests for… https://t.co/JlSgyBxans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Washington, DC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/FQMBHnAL20 #aviation #WomenSTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had money to splurge to go in a spontaneous trip to Julian while its snowing :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this mini bar 🍻 The half-circle shape with radiating stripes shows its original colors- blue and gold. Th… https://t.co/WbsiPR3jDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omggg why is he like this??? @chelseyhaay come get ur man https://t.co/STh67AsSGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s love day &amp;&amp; i wouldn’t wanna be lovin’ anyone else 💛 https://t.co/xBhwQhGuZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOGCLOTHINGCO13 @MAGA2ARIGHTS @grindingdude @MichaelMAGAUSN @bedevilme666 @Stephen57036680 @KathaleenHarpe9… https://t.co/KZiNqT4gln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @Patri56 @routh_l @Jdv74D @jonz970 @Naviiah1 @LoriKorn1 @jebeess34 @jdp021189 @OLDFLACO @MAGAgirly… https://t.co/hfwdcXlSA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @VrainWaves for another amazing and inspiring podcast! So many different ways that the interview with Gir… https://t.co/HD0ZiGoOQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[namoral dividir quarto c gente, ainda mais c peruano folgado, NAO DA Não vejo a hora de ter meu quarto de volta]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would not want to be in the Duke locker room with Krzyzewski right about now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Too old too white too male  time for new young blood oh and a person of color or a women from the Midwest]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way I can get my brother to do me a favor is to remind him of the 5,000 favors I just did for him 🤷🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/iGgqsQjEww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump America has seen what Democrats/ liberals do,  look at California (where I was born… https://t.co/RqYVJQWXve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robflee23 @Dee_Wexler That’s like all I’ve been playing lately!! I’ve been playing on my switch though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we just do what we did the second half all the time...forever? #letsgohoos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Yes and when we get back in we need to make appointing judges a priority! Mitch McConnell blocks Obama… https://t.co/6BNB3k6Z1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we say God don’t like ugly...@TheKMAC1 shouldn’t of been talking bout Childress so badly this morning @TheSportsShop1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoiceofBP Listening at Little Newton Lake! Let’s do this Pirates! Chris, our Granddaughter, Emma, placed 3rd at th… https://t.co/2BJqN2ck1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fly #fame #figureti #youtuber #influencer #influencerswanted #influencermarketing #influencers #youtuberewind… https://t.co/Zeq7coM2DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vinipizzetta11 @krassenstein Wasting court time and money!  But we can’t afford food stamps or provide school lunc… https://t.co/6wk9Wz7vpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamsesVidente Muchas gracias bendiciones llegando de una boda en domingo 😍buenas noches Ramses 😍😘🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cailsx This is a close survey I’m looking forward to the final but I vote hoop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donnie_Rock69 @xoMackenzieMoss There's a rwason your on my "no list" now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipPope Thanks for tolerating my enigmatic surface persona! Now can you put me in touch with the Ha-Fucking-Ha gu… https://t.co/cpz12JGqNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d ❤️ Your Help, But If Not, It’s Still Gonna Get Done, Now Even Better‼️ ✅ With God As My Partner, Even When I Lo… https://t.co/HZXBgadzX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that I sobered up, I’m actually really tired and lowkey don’t want to be on our way to the Grand Canyon 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: clips toenails to do a home pedicure  Also me: stubs toe hard enough it bleeds  #twodaystiltaipei #still10toes #fornow]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy anniversary adrien 🍻 @ Stephen's on Court https://t.co/cCJlUz1MWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my brother, who eats DiGornio frozen pizzas 3 meals a day, just told me that he won’t eat McDonald’s because it’s “… https://t.co/xdShN7A3OJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@untipsyteacher @katiejmoric @hdbigjourney @snifflesnack I’m telling you! There’s a book of terlet stories waiting to be written!]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND MEN DO IT!!! Like why’s it okay for men to rap about bitches and pussy ALL THE TIME but when a woman do it it’s wrong?? Get outta here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[once I asked for Horlicks instead of Milo in front of my grandfather and the look he gave me still gives me chills.… https://t.co/V7lKMMlavt]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of scoliosis related tweets I get sent is actually really funny, considering I don’t even have scoliosis… https://t.co/0QMFqWCaIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even Democrats See President Trump’s Wisdom in Walking From North Korea Negotiations https://t.co/p4B5fy4nM1  wow common ground]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeTV @Bionic_Tweets YOU GOI G TO STATR AIRING THE BIONIC  MAN .THAT SHOW WAS FANTASTIC  BABY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Women are all the qualities the world has not deemed us as we indeed are #sexy #goddesses #funny #creative… https://t.co/6D9u888FIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siegekurt Guess we don’t have to worry about that extra pint taking time off our life with this beer. 🤮💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually, this tweet is giving me the motivation to wash the small pile of stockings that has accumulated next to t… https://t.co/L8vRW50gOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annehelen He seems to hate the state he represents, so he could always go back to where his family farm is...in Io… https://t.co/9dwSWVezw5]]></document></documents></author>