<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[People had like 8 years to see Mac Miller live talking about “man if only I could have seen him just once 😔” smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[this dog shows more emotion in 1 min 52 sec than any man i’ve ever encountered]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @GHSEmergencyMed PGY2 @theEDabides, after assessing ABCs, determine if AV an block or dissociation is… https://t.co/52M0DZBvEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squirrels                  @KortemeyeRyan                          🤝  working super hard to get their nut]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and @ayanna_rose_h when we decided to go to the park last semester iykyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWaxHeaven @WatchTheBreaks Thank god she never did, got out before she did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sassyredhead20 @RavensAnnabel Thanks sassy wish it was mine that one is my sons]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ass is going to be right on SoBe letting the sun bake me more than an Alaska]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hilarymilnes goes right to @nilamg (Instacart) at #shoptalk2019 about new Amazon Grocery rumors.  Nils believes co… https://t.co/Yy9mfnFVHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always argue that if chess and card games can be viewed as a sport, why cant a games also be labeled as a sp… https://t.co/o3nD32J6lK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeple...Gus mawnin...hope y’all have a blessed day..mine finna be stupit long....but great and blessed...what’s h… https://t.co/ia4LbVRCsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥍 Boys Lacrosse, Late-night edition. The @DNHSNighthawks hosting @PowayLacrosse. A battle of 2 first-year coaches (… https://t.co/GaZ5kIpfTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no. logic...slipping...away...reverting... back to comfort and what I want to believe in...to bring me...happine… https://t.co/l645YL1ClZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marvinlwilliams Prayers sent!  What a great collection.  Wishing you all the best in your journey @marvinlwilliams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OBraveOne Yeah I know, just really liked the setting of the Chaos maps and was just becoming invested only to be blue balled already 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmTheWarax @mitchprothero ROFL! I know those feels! https://t.co/MtoigC6tEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y éste fallo no puede lograr que se cambien los buses por los eléctricos? Sería lo ideal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tmasterxtreme @RealMyUsername @badimo I can already see your garbage/trash talking while your probably the worst o… https://t.co/WCBl3jzLyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YohannaLoucheur @Mark_Brough @andylolz @timdavies @IATI_aid When we had this discussion on discuss and the on/off… https://t.co/i1g3SeDiQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyStars27 @TGFBI Agreed. Love the 20/20 potential. And if he can somehow hit .250 even better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackmanResults Oh Jeff, I didn’t know.  Di and I both give you and your sister our condolences.  He was a great m… https://t.co/A2YSMYwTCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammynickalls I have no idea how you do it, but no matter what you do with your hair it looks amazing. A style icon. 💁‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amymarie315 has a witch doctor oils book and she’s not afraid to use it....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alton timeout with 4:31 to go in first half, up 22-16 on Belleville West. @AltonAthletics #AdVsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the cold front has hit austin because that wind is picking up &amp; it’s getting colder #atxwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find someone who looks at you like I look at this candy apple balloon from Alinea https://t.co/WhjAB4ziN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteadyRiot Imagine thinking all liberals lean as far left as the party is trending. I think lack of centrist voice… https://t.co/cNFxGPyBCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Gov. Gavin Newsom's prepared remarks for his first State of the State address: Here are the full prepared rema… https://t.co/C4KHZxP5q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @AmericaNewsroom Keep up the good work on @FoxBusiness @FoxNews and have… https://t.co/eQJaLTrSgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala’s pitch seems to be playing up this prosecutor thing on the debate stage w/ Trump has all the makings of a p… https://t.co/McPcqM9RAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadAssBowlegz They mad comfortable. No bullshit. And ( I move like a ninja.). Chill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWarRoomNZ @AndiBeeeee I spoke to my friend overnight and I respect her wishes about whether or not she wants to… https://t.co/YgSpibT7Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many young people tonite are mourning the death of SLUH 2018 alum Will Smit—I had the honor of teaching Will—He was… https://t.co/80GcyRtOFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta push harder on the days you don’t feel like it. This a lifestyle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody wants to take your spot...until they see what it takes to play your position! 👑🏆 • • • 📸: @SayCheese https://t.co/0tvYdOjD0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[We won’t support a wall, but we need a barrier.   Let’s raise the price of meat to save animals.   Ban air travel.… https://t.co/BLzVk2LQWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about you but I’d much rather be mowing the lawn than snowblowing the driveway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:56.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob_sheridan Just wondering, did you ever consider putting a big gaudy presidential signature on the bible in the… https://t.co/LulBYK4JFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackRus44698878 @chrisbflix @SeanMcD_CrimZoo my review of Alien Domicile https://t.co/0jfeeRcJvR https://t.co/72pqpPR1nG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that @ABCNetwork doesn’t allow a streaming option for live tv? No wonder the oscars has low viewership. Get with the times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think all proud residents of Tampa Bay can agree that Googling ‘Bubba the Love Sponge’ is very amusing right now.… https://t.co/RxiMA7X7CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrsulaV @Myrmecos @ChuckWendig I mean, it feels pretty on-brand for them. If I was to read that in a reputable new… https://t.co/s96WPhYhIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHIntel @JamesFourM I didn’t say you shouldn’t make the argument, bud. I said you shouldn’t use the term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iubb love the game plan of feeding Davis and letting offense going around him. Wish we would of seen this earlier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson I despise that ridiculous assertion 😖 They should support you for being bright and informed; a true leader 👏🏾👍🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad- “I had a lady run her fingers through my hair today.” My mom - “omg you whore.” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mejor pelicula que eh visto en los últimos 5 años: Spiderman into the spider verse 😍😍🎥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just casually listening to the Hamilton soundtrack at 8:38 p.m. on a Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you #teamciraflexion ??Contestant #2 Cira Flexion is Hosting Fabulous Friday inside The Legendary MotherHouse… https://t.co/w7oTEJ6T4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me till the last day of February to break out the hot hands. #amnewsers #mewx #maine https://t.co/VxZ5mthMzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottliebShow You need to get aggressive next month when coaching vacancies start popping up. You’d be a great fit in Fayetteville. Go HAWGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ireland0828 @jonathanjewel @abutler04 @DanteB4u @physguy2 @iRhysTay @dwaynecobb @JGRIDLOCK @jason4e @emarblack… https://t.co/z7jdxVI5Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mercy Health &amp; Fitness Center in Clive, IA https://t.co/v8ZJ3umIdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrettMcPher10 Take your “stand”😂 Coach B has a lot of years to come to match Izzo, idk how you can talk shit abo… https://t.co/rqfJiMeBDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broncos__London @WolfPackPackTO @SherAndLil @SherAndLil are two of the most honest fans you will ever come across]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so thankful for your support. I’m working hard to join these amazing Members of Parliament in Ottawa… https://t.co/t3ceGCtZPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DustinGouker How much do you think this is all a long set-up to justify ESPN launching a book/getting paid an insa… https://t.co/15IfI4VrHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Region 2 BBB: Thompson leads Hatton-Northwood 17-16 at the end of Q1 #NDpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we don’t have a wall let everyone in we can go to Mexico City when we want but get rid of thugs we can go into C… https://t.co/oIucfqxTp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Port of Tampa . @ Holland America Rotterdam https://t.co/VRXYaNt9Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Goldman happens to be the one prosecutor that Trump didn't want on Mueller's team to begin with. Now… https://t.co/5bphOEriE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always wanted to see the face of the person who slams down the seat of a toilet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going thru my Jackie Chan blindspots and MY LUCKY STARS has an insane structure. *First 15 mins = Jackie versus nin… https://t.co/DFWlbenU15]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUMP YOU CAN KISS YOUR ASS GOOD BYE NEW YORK INVESTIGATING YOU,NOW YOUR EMPIRE WILL FALL TO IT'S KNEES, YOUR FIRED… https://t.co/kWUFrZneuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a hunch we will see a lot more headlines like this over the next few years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tony_Patron @alexvancini @raychilIl @Evan__Gates @vic_moser Gang shiiii https://t.co/JZcySGlTL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome meeting and talking to @ZERTZ_86 Great and humble guy! #FlyEaglesFly https://t.co/N9HlJ0ZWup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, a domestic terrorist in the military had a hit list of democrats that INCLUDED her. Meanwhile, a domesti… https://t.co/QNDhO9uyeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsBrizz No. Like if they changed daylight savings time to just be regular time all throughout the year that’d be… https://t.co/ZBhmkDOa5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that think the AAF is better than the NFL are probably Jets fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattAnders17 @AOC She’s the deviant of congress. She’s filth and basura. Mari macha, que feo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lMc2GVVzEG Il faut écouter à la jeunesse mondiale! Notre planète en dépend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The midterm elections were a step in the right direction, but we need to keep going ... do the right thing protect… https://t.co/noavEMYoYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlousM can you drop a single or sum! You rap better than half these niggas out right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Alpine Weiss by Trap Rock Restaurant and Brewery @ Trap Rock Restaurant &amp; Brewery — https://t.co/iHhE91Wi0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to eat healthy today! #churropoutine #tasty #healthy #amazing #diabetes #churros #salad @ Chichi Café https://t.co/E4fJulvWlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trigger_st @20HoF00 @RealMattCouch @KatTheHammer1 Not sure anyone was talking to you, child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close win. Now let’s get ready to play that dark blue team from Durham on Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easily the roughest year of my life but cheers to muthafucking 25 yooo ! 🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATENCION. RECOMIENDO A TODOS LOS NORTEAMERICANOS CATIRES, NO LATINOS, QUE HUYAN DE VENEZUELA DE INMEDIATO. Al retir… https://t.co/4ZfuVx8JZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@left_too @digitaltrader @DavefromTO @ezraklein The hell it isn’t. These people keep winning primaries for a reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 @penguins @Pitt_MBB  @PittIMGSports @DuqMBB  @RMUMBasketball @PennStateMBB… https://t.co/wXG9CpSAoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youngsters don’t never let certain people hold you down for what you did in your past. Judgmental people do a great… https://t.co/aJAr8IeKvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building new #MacMini hard drive after the last new one bricked in 4 weeks. And my #TimeMachine bricked 2 nights ag… https://t.co/9Ukg8KUI7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dank_think @LMac_1326 Well as long as there’s water underneath I’ll try it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardesSeleh Doesn't everybody use them for the bathroom trash can liners?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DStonerookMusic @SabSilv @WJACTV Obvipusly. But these kids are gonna  think they can just roll a joint like a cigarette.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why u asking that nigga what color u should get ur nails if he ain’t pay 4 it]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not his daughter or granddaughter on his lap that would be even more disgusting @GovRonDeSantis]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Steelers need more men of character like James Conner and Aaron Donald.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Standing with you President Donald Trump....MAGA... continue forward don't get side track with DEM… https://t.co/cFxfmresgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[For everything that was written in the past was written to teach us, so that through the endurance…… https://t.co/Irmgzk0c8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenesisMako @jpmir @EpicGamesES @NicolasMaduro Si pero las dos idiomas mas habladas son el espanol e ingles. Las i… https://t.co/3ktXBqHi1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n8vbell Being super rich has perks.. I just finished leaving Neverland.. that shit was fucked up.. MJ was one sick little fucker..]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ in 1862 @ the age of [15] Alonzo “Lonnie” Clayton was the youngest. Jockey to win the Kentucky Derby”… https://t.co/EG7QX5dhdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[work! itscheekychiko  @kakuberry  @ShiningRaeMusic  @AudraTheRapper   #teamwork #newmusic #letsgo @ Hollywood https://t.co/E30MvYfgwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[[ARTISTS NURTURING ARTISTS]   Thank you Another Sentiment!  #anothersentiment #nurtureyourfellowartists… https://t.co/uhXx08ujQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@web @MrKingJD Dang. And I bet that’s just all up in one half of the city, too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A kind soul wants nothing more than to resolve and not repel. @ The Dils Center https://t.co/evSJSuwMSH]]></document></documents></author>