<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Cryptopia_NZ 2FA not texting me or emailing me now. Used to work fine. Please advise?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kentindell @Tweetermeyer That article is BRUTAL lmao. Screencap for those who are blocked https://t.co/OjUjSmkCiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprise I'm going Live 🔴 Right Now  on @WatchMixer Channel @RuffOnezTV_ playing @SaintsRow 2  a @Xbox… https://t.co/AnPJC2PHie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting out doors a lil bit spending daddy daughter time together @ Anderson, Indiana https://t.co/5gF56580Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopularCC1 @CarlOrkmansen @LightfootForChi @ToniPreckwinkle Went from him making $50k a year to $600 a month . Dec… https://t.co/HjsOzT61wP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entre Le Glacier des oscars et puis Le glacier Malaga de bietry qui djassai que son Ami ? Pour moi c'est bietry ...… https://t.co/F3PqgAXnos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaterCrunchy @RoArquette @JuddLegum Obviously. Some of these people have a rod up their ass that has a rod up it's ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Addy has been sick all weekend, so I’ve seen 34 episodes of “Sheriff Callie’s Wild West”  Send help and ibuprofen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZubaZ21 Hi, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, then Give us… https://t.co/2VgfpnpCE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[People from South County are like “what the hell is Florissant?” People from North County are like “what the hell is Affton?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my oldest son @zachotoole10 hope all is well in CA.. keep doing great, we’re all proud of you!! https://t.co/zbbgtU5QHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theme_park @NanoGotchi @phantazmick25 @WDWToday @WDWToday is sempai for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to take a Facebook break so twitters gonna see me all up in this bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst part abt losing someone is not being able to send them funny tweets no more :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at DSCC Cafeteria - @dsccmwr in Columbus, OH https://t.co/2aOjpBitZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly there’s nothin like a big ole house centipede to remind u that ur rlly in this bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feykabahlodvg Yeah the latter, but could you imagine if she snapped and wanted WW]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that need to go to jail for betraying their country: @realDonaldTrump  @senatemajldr  @LindseyGrahamSC… https://t.co/HdQ2pS7XPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[bringing this back bc this WILL be my senior quote speakijngit into existence @JIDsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocked to have heard the news about TJ Cunningham. Over a parking space too? My goodness this world...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tweaked some of the values this morning to tone down the greens and bring out the red. https://t.co/bnicS53gGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a lot of sound in this picture!! #fortinamps #saw #zuul #guitarnerd #tonechaser @ Power Up Fostoria https://t.co/eQivbfTF06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manafort was convicted of being a massive tax cheat (not rendering unto Caesar), Trump will likely pardon him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For instance, if I set a precedence of pronouncing forgiveness anytime an injustice is committed, there will be tim… https://t.co/hMDOKR49ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView So now that Meghan McCain's parties coming out with legislation is hate legislation and anti-Semitic look… https://t.co/B0TFsyefy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how many people listen to rock? Drake might be the biggest rapper to ever do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottfranse @DiGardRacing @DCopeRacing I mailed this photo sheet from my Charlotte office in January 1989 to newsp… https://t.co/KEqFeGvmNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyjay24 I wouldn’t be surprised if Bron comes out with the “uh yea me too”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 @AOC @errollouis People should be called out for lying.   The press used to be respected for doing just that,… https://t.co/qHxFGP5Qgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[o so edgy!! to have a strong opinion about a holiday! remember to let people have a good time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cincyfella @shanebible @justme2andu @rfmmoran @nancylees @Ehukai411 @KirstenPowers @LLinWood Educate me on that fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 2) "And is even trying to make ( pedophiles) acceptable"? That's...a unusual idea to push.  Remember whe… https://t.co/EG1T2jljsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capital Hill Day postscript: I visited with the staffs of 6 Congressional Offices, and all were supportive and seem… https://t.co/d8476Xenhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emotwink666 they'd get a lot more attention if they used their cocks :^\]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Nifemi Two questions: 1. how did they get up there? 2. What exactly is there problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time I’ve seen Naimi acknowledge the health benefits of moderate drinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyMiller823 @NASCARONFOX @Team_Penske @RustyWallace @keselowski @KurtBusch https://t.co/7QWAODB3dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marshwood timeout 1:14 left trailing Brunswick 47-45, Dragons' Emily Larochelle shooting 1-1 at FL. #VarsityMaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edsbs It's a brain and nerve tonic, full of proteins and electromagnetic juices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And she gave an @IntlWD shout out to her inspiration and mentor @onehealthconrad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anddrewmichael @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker Sorry guys but I was blocked after he sent this tweet. Also I meant to no… https://t.co/AOrjFPQ4UH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbkdragoon Lol. I'll say....fine. I learned I'm completely out of shape for Enduro riding. All that downhill and n… https://t.co/tw9Pw8AhWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lancers starters: Trenten Scott, Jalen Duff, Jacob Kasbaum, Zachary Clayborne and Rodriguez Gayle. @LewPortBball]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Francesa rant about the Mets having Keon Broxton and not Harper will be epic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mel_the_geek @Observer2541 @deelane @synredae @PATRICIAMEEHA17 @Elinor27652146 @Trixie883low @Hiveaclue… https://t.co/thGFvj9Ron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolan Arenado got paid big!! 8 years $260 million, $32.5 million per year goddamn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted Rall for February 18, 2019 | https://t.co/eSMqRsQRgf https://t.co/idEPhFBeEY via @GoComics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump Such a stupid statement. I know where your head is &amp; its certainly stained brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on Feb Goals:  Followers: 180⭐️/180 Views: 2,382⭐️/2,365 Subs: 2/4  Come join the revolt at… https://t.co/Cpt1J2sULl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is 100% accurate according to my Mexican wife - who still laughs at the way we white people roll up a burrito… https://t.co/hUxi2ALpkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas_Dexter @DogginTrump Or nipped up cat day! https://t.co/tHIU37KNBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Why are all of these people attacking you?  Your reporting seems honest, accurate and fair. I’m a Democrat… https://t.co/GKu8VU4aV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you call a niggas phone and he don’t answer for you that mean that Nigga never gave af about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to make 4 drawings today.... if y'all see me on here being a dumbass before I've said I'm done PLEASE yell at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Friday night when you’re looking for a win, and Saturday morning when you found one. @bellaspara3… https://t.co/2hDPsslQ9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimrome maybe the padres should send Manny to Greenbow, Alabama for spring training to learn how to run. Signed Forest Gump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcogrimaldo felicidades paquito  Muchos días de estos, te mando un fuerte abrazo y que todos tus deseos se cumplan… https://t.co/uImoCnaeYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder This is why @ChrisChristie is wrong when he says we must find ways to get along and meet in the middle… https://t.co/0qWbWc0Egk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanquiller That’s a fact no one brings more energy to the table than @trvisXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight 🌙⏰💤💤 &amp; God Bless @ Southport, Florida https://t.co/BEZk9uAvNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bald_Calvinist @BCDyer @NatePickowicz Shh!! We don't want them to catch on!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE Lawyer up? Haha The Man has you triggered 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC announced Flyers-Penguins game drew 1.9 million TV viewers, the most for a regular-season game (excluding Winte… https://t.co/aehtFxasIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtomsksSanakan @camstreet1 @david_hanselman @SteveSGoddard @MatthewHavicon @InTimeLiving @MLBinWA @realPitBullDog… https://t.co/Q8gPaOR804]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a joy to meet up with friends in Fargo. #NMSI @ Fargo Hector International Airport https://t.co/VsMQABZBrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[UDATED INFORMATION:  All @NorthernLehigh schools and the administration building are now closed today, 2/13/19. The… https://t.co/JyLS1vXYhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsTHINK same way with Trump haters...magical thinking https://t.co/bIahkIcsK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little heavy on the piney! - Drinking a Voodoo Ranger Imperial IPA by @newbelgium @ Lakeview Brewery  — https://t.co/pa1LyD5RFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the most amazing girlfriend, hands down. We're going to do big things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPDRMemes @VanessaVanjie Tiene cuerpo de qué me encargaron una manualidad en la primaria y le eche todo lo que tenía encima 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoBelaunde Alberto, ya hay normativa sobre la NO obligatoriedad del uniforme; por tanto al no ser obligatorio… https://t.co/rKbykVFlsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egratto @ImpossibleFoods And now I see that I misspelled Steak-Umm. My piss-poor snark effort is more of a mess th… https://t.co/lo2Zfzpb3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatdresby @90sWWE @TheRealXPac Nah everyone except hhh got that work more than anything lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been thinking.  I have 13 followers on Twitter.  I have 120 Facebook friends.  My twitter followers like weird people best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@971theticketxyt damn Jamie you’re arguing every thing Stoney says today.  Beyond annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiderCody_ @ProFootballTalk F!ck bleacher report bro AND they're stank ass no vote for Tom Flores https://t.co/l4oVLvb2rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 14 - Business Insider Select:     The president of one of the world's happiest countries says it'… https://t.co/EucDqQsWN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said it on a recent show on @PGHSportsLive via @PghSteelersNow, and it’s becoming more and more evident now, find… https://t.co/8YwfSICgv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covington lawsuit against the Washington Post I hope they win 2 they need to it's time the left in this country pay… https://t.co/87MotLttdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snywalker @reneritchie I was being lazy when I asked him. I just went and looked and it will do two at the resolut… https://t.co/dJL9gluW1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do shoes have to do with Networking? Attendees at @SIRVAWorldwide #2019PSAPRO Sales Conference are about to fi… https://t.co/r4VtMagNLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in class reading Season 8 patch notes, don’t have the slightest urge to go home and play this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Destin Florida. Caty and I are here for the Tribe Mastermind Combat Business Success conference. Yesterday was full… https://t.co/WsYe2PBmlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EternalHokageYT @deathcrank Who is this ugly thing? He don't deserve to live]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playoff atmosphere tonight in STL! Love the tenacity this team has been playing with. #Blues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miamidadetpo @GoMiamiDade @MyFDOT_Miami @GoCITT @MDXway What does the miles axis represent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[With SPECIAL APPEARANCES BY BARRY “BAMS” OBAMA, HILLARY “CONSTANTLY LOSES THEN WRITES ABOUT IT” CLINTON, GEORGE “GE… https://t.co/urA56nqUUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyaThompson_98 @Ianncaab @Evlyn3__ @Mashyahamurphy @Suckmy_beautyy @DrayaPinckney She got exposed for this same thing like a year ago too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 19: @RedheadfromMars!  Michelle Swope is dedicated to spreading the word of the creators who bring the horror g… https://t.co/UAhP0CdKLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me thinking about May 11th when i inevitably take an L to bots/resellers on Bred IVs and then have to stress over c… https://t.co/xQTzad4sJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIRST OFF MAJOR SALUTE TO THE ONES WHO BACK UP THAT TALK WITH ACTION WE APPRECIATE YALL ! ANOTHER BORDERLESS AP DON… https://t.co/ra9z52mQDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Valentine’s in a very long time that I am fortunate enough to enjoy being in #love... #valentinesday2019 @ La… https://t.co/Hl65U2fCNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenKairy @WearyHeathen @McconneyMichael @Idonthaveanick2 I am sure he doesn’t mind your support  of infanticide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing for my friend, @providenceghost: Seeking new stories for our collection! Especially from the East Side; Col… https://t.co/PCYL4mv4Bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actual sun beginning to threaten the skies over Riviera....Mickelson, Spieth and Schauffele playing in front of a handful of humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyButler hope you see your value to the Sixers.  Take the max and play the role only you can. Don’t worry about… https://t.co/GgCC3mLzr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back at how Congresses attempt to allow a line-item veto was declared unconstitutional, I have to wonder if… https://t.co/XbEVMsgHSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheistBigfoot @stejwill @iamAtheistGirl Why are you continuing to ask me to do something in 150 characters ?Belie… https://t.co/QjVEZItyh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[god i fucking love that me and my best friends can sing anime openings in Japanese together m]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 yrs ago today I took this picture of #PinkFloyd airship for promotion of #TheDivisionBell album over Center City… https://t.co/edpVXCCjTV]]></document></documents></author>