<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My best friend thinks soap and water is considered a skin routine. I am making an itemized list for him as we speak… https://t.co/2RMn2QAoWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattzollerseitz Pete Hamill got himself fired by The Daily News for writing a scathing column about him a day or t… https://t.co/so7A4Ozwjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders If Senator you run independent &amp; not as a Democrat you will give that psychopath 45 another 4 years!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband sent me a sweet text and I started balling my eyes out. I need a hot fudge sundae and a nap. Pls and thx.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "1968 The Year the World Changed Parenting Hosted by Parents Engaging Parents" https://t.co/boNaCfAEyC @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brief stop in the Capital to say hi to Justin and fam! @ Jaques Cartier Park https://t.co/j2zOAPx6zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OurRevolution10 @cinemaven @maddox_pj @jaketapper Ya wanna bet? You're young, so you still have a chance to grow,… https://t.co/hOF4pVJegz]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i’m under the influence i start telling everybody how much i love my boyfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on my way to the scene to get more info. @cbs46 #news #weather #rain #storm]]></document><document><![CDATA[He missed the #music #Cat and so did I 😊 silly cat swiped me off 😆😂 #Carpenters #LP and #Video #JakeCrew 😘 on… https://t.co/74RlgyTiQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 500th beer is a good one - Drinking a Concentrate 101 by @LandGrantBeer at @landgrantbeer  — https://t.co/SwcsCr56Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sensiblecit @JohnFromCranber You never trumpers just talk shit with zero to back up your big mouths.  You should be ashamed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the jump master could stop landing in the bunker every round that would be fantastic 🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressive SF Sups banned live/work lofts in SOMA, SF’s only affordable housing, bc progressive activists mistaken… https://t.co/BnSegXvcKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisaj_2190 My friend @ohericarose might be able to help, she’s super knowledgeable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s have your favourite fruit or veggie photos folks! 🇨🇦 Canadians are looking for #halfyourplate inspiration.… https://t.co/bhMlGadtDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierre SO pathetic. The man feels like a complete loser (and does everything he can to try and counter that lack o… https://t.co/H60pWNkeh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[these falsies helped me fulfill my abg fantasy  (i have all the requirements to be an abg except i'm not cute or in… https://t.co/TXye3rMDis]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is such a load of bullshit! If immigrant children are raped I can guarantee you it’s by another immigrant in c… https://t.co/Pb7Kas33AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton Thanks you for one of the best concert I have ever been to. In Pittsburgh Pa https://t.co/4XNUflBuA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlitterNStuds @WDWRAH I mean, most of the costumes at Disney fail with that lol. I look at some and I can’t even imagine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Brooks, Dan Porterfield, &amp; More on Weaving America's Social Fabric... https://t.co/jD1oZJ0gEA via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The K cup screams metal lol. #deathwishcoffee @ Sterling, Virginia https://t.co/CE4RXIKN5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at T-Mobile &amp; BlackBerry @ College of DuPage (SRC/SCC Foyer) in Glen Ellyn, IL https://t.co/MUrJvpGQg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oyster Shells and Favorite Blue Bowl is at Grand Bohemian Gallery, St. Augustine. - #artgallery #exhibiting… https://t.co/lam2fMaZJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hombre de palabra y acción, nuevo liderazgo, importante muy importante nueva cara de cómo debe ser la nueva forma d… https://t.co/g1DiuNA7Dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Aluminum was once thought to be rare 😳 #BRITEconf @Xandr76 https://t.co/AulWJYNA81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlpcs @SnoHo_Al @bedevilme666 @John_R_Berna @apb_ap @paul_lomonaco @RayRaybrown57 @ncar999 @RodHillis1… https://t.co/nk2grkh38I]]></document><document><![CDATA[This boy is from Great Bend and goes to Kansas State University. Not a lot of information but I need to know his na… https://t.co/4MsVzJJgsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun with @SteveSmithFDN bowling event and the @roaringriot peeps I got to play with!! Thank you for cho… https://t.co/lsVrH33IX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChildishColin @Bas I feel you, when you gotta be up at 4am so you can’t go &lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing they can get me for is running a funeral parlor without a license]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbybrieanne @wiffanytood15 @matt_bang22 @syd_vicous @emohleee @kaylafacedd @Lane8music Ma’am please quiet down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank God! Are they really immigrants? Doesn't the law refer to them as aliens [illegal aliens]?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbennettpost @realDonaldTrump @gbennettpost @MarcACaputo @PatriciaMazzei @browardpolitics @MitchEPerry… https://t.co/xc0r2Kb4PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS @TheTalkCBS Thank you for continuing to talk about @SelmaBlair and her courageous journey. I am 46 and… https://t.co/mpgBus6AFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida tiene tantas maneras de decirte eyyyyy wake up la esta ultraaaaaaaaa regando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidTh94535989 @maziehirono @realDonaldTrump U really have a thing against smart strong women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you replenish, restore and reset? Do you take time to fill your cup? ❤️💫 Invitation: connect to nature this… https://t.co/YHATNDGlW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GDClearedToLand My flight attendant said I should *call* them. On what? A rotary phone? As if.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel is my favorite yet!! I want to be her when I grow up. Also loved all the tech components]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many “Little Rain” reference jokes Morgan Wallen has received since yesterday lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Trump ordered top adviser Cohn to block AT https://t.co/zRwQqvKxQ9 via @NBCNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whilst the rest of the world is out on the town partying the night away, I stayed in for a little me time...somethi… https://t.co/0feer42tCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some mean ass tweets in my drafts, I can be such an angry girl sometimes smh https://t.co/3c6cAobPkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all!! #FridayNightLights is no joke! After 12 days of binging this show, I am FULL of emotions! Thanks @RadioAmy… https://t.co/xDam0HkYSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marc_lotter @realDonaldTrump I don’t see this in my neighborhood another trump lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OversightDems Crybaby dems needs a liar to distract from NK peace talks.. America sees all of you… https://t.co/ZrD7Pq6PYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #DeadFiles “The Devil’s Bidding and am literally in tears during the Reveal. Thanks @stevedischiavi &amp;… https://t.co/WyEAeCxJXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I don’t feel so bad about asking @TMobile to contribute to my campaign to help make up for wages lost by them b… https://t.co/P2mrvuZooJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elliot Abrams is a war criminal. He belongs in jail not leading US policy in Venezuela. This administration continues to be crazy-making.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see some friends again tonight at AIW #AllHailTheKing @KingdomKarrie @Tlieso @mrs25159 @djones360 @KVR216 a… https://t.co/wvPPW4snPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eww everything about this is gross. Lmao ladies if a man doesn’t think ur attractive bcuz u want to dress comfortab… https://t.co/T5mYCbip54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjfree Be embarrassed by Trump, but never for the idea of the type of country we have long striven to be, even whe… https://t.co/E4lWJo6f4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT... Things I've been thinkin' about, today...   #THIS  #rome #ancienthistory  #ancientwisdom @ Mexico, Misso… https://t.co/ErbPToW5F2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what I said they ain’t equally at fault, he’s the man whore plain and simple he’s the one who f up]]></document><document><![CDATA[We thought we could make acapella look like a baseball movie, and it worked, @ElizabethBanks on Pitch Perfect… https://t.co/TFgR56FiYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is The Day our little actress is coming Home!!!!! @cperrymaddog  @lexirae26 #actress #singer #talented… https://t.co/OxA07p6qni]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: SATCS,(Air Traffic Manager),(MSS-4,Level 5), AT-2152-FL -… https://t.co/6SV3e7Kegv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I SAW A DUDE INSIDE THE VENUE AND MY STOMACH DROPPED CAUSE I THOUGHT IT WAS ZECH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bungarsargon @GOPLeader Get me @MaxRose4NY to call some bullshit on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advice when buying tickets: stay calm and have your card and information ready, or have someone read it to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff @PascoSheriff  @Kimberl38218406  no sir absolutely not trying to get me back I sorry 😐 I hate this st… https://t.co/odLcR12SPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[me drunk at 2am: i need to go to sleep now and be productive when i wake up  me drunk at 2am: now is an excellent t… https://t.co/f20SX1nvgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdnginger @ehme @chrissyteigen Would you like her to use her celebrity status to get you a tutor so you can use th… https://t.co/0v7HILsNRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you forget Puerto Rico and California?  Or Flint, MI??  Oh, that's right - you're only preside… https://t.co/egpCxWY77J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost 2) And who cares if the country who flew planes on New York, causing the death of thousands, gets n… https://t.co/SiTOtfQLQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧡 How can past life memories help you get the most from THIS life? Find out!   Susanne has a limited number of past… https://t.co/NyG24g1c1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatesfoundation Some of those scientists live in countries that still don’t have many toilets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jilliemary @Peeperpea29 @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @roads2 @Jimmysimmonds1 @Iluvinspireu @ClockworkHamma… https://t.co/iq11gsEiJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yalitza aparicio en suiza https://t.co/GvfBGFNj58 #RedAMLO https://t.co/au7otXvI8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour Wow!  Brian! You have, by far, the best guests ever!  Jeremy Bash!  Matthew Miller!  My #1, Chuck Rosenbe… https://t.co/iNoILvZKpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Be like whenever possible. It is always possible.” https://t.co/YeQlBQZvRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuestoLoco @maddow It infuriates me how people now deem criticism as hating. I hate it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTrentkemp1 @RNRKentucky Can you-all in KY do something about Mitch? I blame this lack of support for @POTUS/borde… https://t.co/kvjk9GdOyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I do want to go back home for the summer but the only way I can see Ariana grande live is if I stay in New Yor… https://t.co/EeK4r01Ojy]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I worked a job last year my return would b extra fat. Like ah 5 piece type. 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpOrBust2020 @Jamierodr10 Amen. It’s such a shame that all of the violence in Chicago goes unnoticed for the mo… https://t.co/PmFNofnJET]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Must See Temples in Egypt #egypt #egyptian #temples https://t.co/TWAaeGxLTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeverDotard @Bastard_Of_1967 @tedcruz When the D’s take the executive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah! Beautiful afternoon at Spring Training watching Ernie’s beloved Dodgers.#loveAZ #baseballlove @ Los Angeles D… https://t.co/rCtN6div40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr we should give Trump the money for his personal WALL  ! LOL https://t.co/ZJCFfIGoQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate change is real. We need to wake up for  future generations.  https://t.co/7jiA98uuLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBOUCHER10 @michaelschweitz @BuddySchweitz My daschund has chewed all the wood in my home he could reach.  He has… https://t.co/UoxTLMx7Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subtle transformation.   #workinprogressart #lakeplacegallery #art #artistatwork #arttransformation #mooseart… https://t.co/BGj2DYSH7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I talked with the VP of resorts about the bachelor and @colton jumping the fence. Tell me one more time that this show is stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously just need to get out of here. This place is just toxic on so many levels. Peace is just so much more im… https://t.co/AxEg5SdbDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValleyBoysBBall @pv_vikingfb @pv_student_sect @perkvalleycheer Congrats to our senior girls on their way to their… https://t.co/1RI54rlkQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long work week there is nothing better than treating yourself to some sleep and a good breakfast.… https://t.co/2xgLxBXNmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another extraordinary Super Moon. #fullmoonritual #highvibrations #fullmoonenergy🌕#lettinggo @ Isle Of Normandy Mia… https://t.co/sdG0vl3Npi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @jduke0407!! So proud of you! Still using all those character building quotes you made us memorize… https://t.co/r3obTVrGES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmiketaylor The closest I'll get to a mountaintop finish is cheering on the riders as they finish the Assault on M… https://t.co/nse2oh0uUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@carsin_Johnson starts the home half of the 6th by drawing a four pitch walk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincengi @FaceTheNation ..to me, and to lots of other people, it’s worth holding off on building a school. Do the… https://t.co/vjN0yqjNUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone to change my car stereo ASAP. I need prices and pictures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This movie was totally snubbed. Sam Elliott and Bradley Cooper deserved way more than just a nomination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorCristina2 @HarrisGracyn Thank you @TaylorCristina2 It truly is so nice to have someone be nice to you. ❤ Muc… https://t.co/PIZErZI3qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@obligatraveler @The_Endless_A @obligatraveler I ❤️❤️ your sloth profile pic! Tres cute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal judge finds ex-Trump campaign chairman Manafort lied to Mueller probe about contacts with Russian aide https://t.co/91emsqw2dF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurkhamerLinds Well true! Usually meal prep but I was stupid and did that all yesterday 😂]]></document></documents></author>