<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Literally like the perfect first episode and I’m getting everything I didn’t know I needed on today... Thanks LB @ksgraham_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers After listening to you on @davidaxelrod podcast self reflection is your greatest strength.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinifolius 😡🧞‍♀️😡we will stick with our founding fathers who knew this would happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SullyKSNT @CoachDoty @ESUSports @Coach_Tucek 1/2 Cant relate to the medical hardships, dont know @CoachDoty or… https://t.co/2Up4KsNOAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The role model of puppeteering for Jessie. Now we know where he got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tower Mobile Home &amp; RV Park https://t.co/o5naY2TYji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I had Trader Joe’s employees come to MY restaurant to eat burritos! Okay the burrito thing isn’t true, they ha… https://t.co/zSjBrFFj9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[First CTO session of the new cohort! (at @Boomtown Accelerator in Boulder, CO) https://t.co/yOv4lbQurT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josalw NICE #Faggot PIC "Sloppy" JOE. How is @taylorswift13? Ya fucked her proper yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbychiukitmei Well I am impressed by a half dozen+ things in this pic https://t.co/ePVmdW77hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bacon_Is_King Oh how I wish that Twitter had emojis vs. a simple like option...  😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 2019 and people still don’t know what to do in a two lane drive thru. 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinkin bout how Trump probably tweets from the bathroom like everyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here come the Warriors. An 11-3 makes it 24-23, Parkside lead, 2:30 left in the first half.  #DelmarvaSportsInsider #ShoreHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Ms. Alexandria could educate the the #trumpprincess 🤔with a gold spoon it would probably go over her head. 🙄 I… https://t.co/yQvazRZgGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took 5 sets vs. Corona, but Boys Varsity Volleyball finishes off opening day with all wins for the Pumas!!!  Set… https://t.co/Nj2Jxftddi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao that awkward moment when you see someone you used to talk to at the club 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I quit vaping, quit smoking weed, and quit frequent drinking. Gonna be substituting all that with protein sha… https://t.co/TTXnm6uDsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Depends on what the definition of "one" is, to use Clintonese  speech!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elsoado49439204 Non mais si le défoulement que le net procure peut empêcher des zélé des passer à l’acte!! C’est t… https://t.co/pHNXMY5YqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anti #Reylos don't seem to understand the mythological nature of Star Wars.   “The people who Rey meets are the dec… https://t.co/vQdV4gDmfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSamBrand Great job Coach! Great seeing you last night as well...#keepgrinding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pearl4Leah Happy Valentine’s Day Leah! Hope you have sweet dreams!!❤️😘😍😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CYO tourney round four.  Go Gaels! Go Chad! 🏀 #EliteEight (@ Detroit Catholic Central High School in Novi, MI)… https://t.co/zhxRRVRywi]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAKEWOOD RANCH #LITTLELEAGUE TUESDAY NIGHT UNDER THE LIGHTS💡   #PEOPLESUMPIRE 🥰  #GLOVEISGLOVE ♥️®️⚾️©️©️⚾️♥️😘 @ La… https://t.co/ytUn90J8P0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elfazi31 @anghunt26 @jenlyell @baptistpress And - your comments are inappropriate.  Potentially damaging for a vic… https://t.co/AioAgEO5Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[a little more info amd perhaps some perspective... not that anyone out there who’ve never had an argument and consi… https://t.co/9N7T24Jnxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did my Xbox just turn on by itself while I’m in my bathroom taking a shit 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuosoPizza23 @dreamsunwind0 @SpartanJessica Haha! Enjoy Vegas. I'll stop in when you guys get back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is my saturday morning. @ Jubilee Services https://t.co/8pCoWAFJTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KetoDocCLT Or chasing ketosis over just feeling good and mental well being]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pizzapower my guys at Giovannis Pizza on Saron Hooked me up!! https://t.co/AIWZPAKp04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for @artpapers auction, More than 200 art pieces for your bidding pleasure, this Saturday, 2019-3-2 @… https://t.co/CPuLUfSyfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 7 of 14 matches, Mo. Valley leads Lo-Ma 21-18. Lange &amp; Haynes, 2 of MV’s 4 rated wrestlers, did not compete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bored_in_jersey THIS is a rant I can support. Not like @JoeNBC's bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HomerGlick @debbiewfleck George Orwell? I mean, the polls show him starting off six feet under.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump knew it was false, Don Jr knew it was false, Ivanka new it was false, did all these Trump’s lie to their atto… https://t.co/5LyJn8BmeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a great parking space w/ @ParkWhiz. Here's a $5 credit so you can give it a try https://t.co/FSP9VBEo3T  https://t.co/CThIK2tO8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lex_Lutheran @llcoolj Just watched the Kevin Hart black history special. It was a lot of fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[#usa #travel #travellover #healthy #love #igers #bestoftheday #instagood #goodlife #likesplease #follow #lifestyle… https://t.co/sjNn1JbOB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀GBB 3A Reg QtrFinal Update🏀 George West 18 ~ Odem 18 at the HALF @CallerSports @ChrisThomasson7 @mysoutex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to see some folks so blinded by hate, they expel any and all rationale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl in a red skirt makes me hella weak!#ThrowbackThursday #TBT #MinnieMouse #Disneyland #Me #Valentines… https://t.co/fePXwPyy8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EqualRightsInst @StoneBridgeCLT @JoshBrahm @cities4life It was a great discussion too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyeased just installed one of your wallpapers, pretty cool stuff. How often do you release new ones?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stadium stairs.  San Diego, CA (5/9/18)  #california #sandiego #padres #petcopark #baseball #baseballstadium #mlb https://t.co/AxqGuu1UBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte - Day-party today at Queen Park Social!!! 1pm-7pm Fun Games Drinks Music!!! @poplifeclt lk_rrproduction… https://t.co/SifcCJzi9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Warrior’s Peace.” It’s Sunday! Tome to get to work. I’m mapping a road plan for projects today. Also working on so… https://t.co/H7ViGsvLV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#morningjoe I wish someone will do a story on @CNN and @MSNBC anti @sensanders bias Either they ignore him entirely… https://t.co/kIzDoVHFcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[this week I’m challenged by the #Word I heard on Sunday morning from #matthew15 and I am embarking on breaking some… https://t.co/HgM6RaPQkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Reflexions On Life blog today... “In Search of Eagles.” #hudsonriver #hudsonvalley #eagles #CanonUSA… https://t.co/lI0jy9ltGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wavesandmeans @mgabrieladfc Échale una miradita a este video, hermano https://t.co/o2zE9LwuqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The game was 3 days ago and you wait until 7 hours before the next game to make an announcement?! Pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to use Instagram to follow friends, now I just use it to follow parkour people and animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um.... how is someone going to bitch about 3rd party voters and then say that they would write in Hillary's name if… https://t.co/RiYGzhDapq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting stills of Paczki Run (@ Downtown Hamtramck in Hamtramck, MI) https://t.co/kS3yBhV0TZ https://t.co/WhqrSK0Lwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normally I would agree that @TWooodley deserves a Immediate rematch but after]]></document><document><![CDATA[These types of things show up in the office. #treecrew #fungalfruitingbody https://t.co/Iow9ZXsKcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime Stats:  FG: Coho 9/34, CCA 7/26 3FG: Coho 3/6, CCA 3/9 TOs: Coho 4, CCA 11 Rebounds: Coho 16, CCA 18 @GlobeSchools]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_rybot_ @NikkiComma And I don't want your dad to get rid of that primo stache!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders, the #socialist,  discussed the failed states of #Venezuela and #NorthKorea with @wolfblitzer on… https://t.co/G4DmQHGxPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew we’d win! I told you in spring training that we’d win!!! @NHLFlyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochieWBZ Don’t get used to it. There’s no reason to think this was nothing but an aberration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePTPROPhet It’s certainly a theme. I can understand Billy letting the fastest guy in the nba go to the rim, but… https://t.co/Z5khpk3VMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo en la prepa de portero pero el delantero corriendo y el vergazo fue en la nuca. También tengo la cicatriz de col… https://t.co/coxe8xng34]]></document><document><![CDATA[bobs burgers ass so is king of the hill, american dad better than family guy, cleveland show not that bad, rick and morty not that deep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricktjoker @rynshe17 @DynastyTradesHQ @FFDynastyTrades @MyFantasyLeague Yes. Gordon would be the best of the bunch… https://t.co/PkDZfrWNbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Frye Regional Medical Center Rehab in Hickory, NC https://t.co/BJmbadtBAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dynamic Underwater Photos Look Like Dramatic Baroque Paintings https://t.co/eLu22FmQ3G via @mymodernmet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate and support but focus on heart health, the number 1 killer of women age 30 on.  Here are 10 tips.… https://t.co/WDuiUxDJSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/L8r3sxQbVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday(s) to these two! @ Hillman City, Seattle https://t.co/dLmKOTdiYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump   So...fellas, they have tons of DNA from the Jupiter human trafficking… https://t.co/RYt4LMm1u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I think they scared of us.” @ Youfit Health Clubs https://t.co/vXlhghUeyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesselheninger check me out coach I play DT #53 in game film https://t.co/TrRq1K8xUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesleytodd @matteocollina then maybe node should focus on the mechanisms that create leaks, not on symptoms of the… https://t.co/mEKlIdLFdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/i0Zcf462xj Internet Explorer Help is effective and reliable to connect with 1-855-479-3999… https://t.co/EbdfkKh8UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take: lil Aaron and Juice Wrld are the future of rap music. @JuiceWorlddd @lilaaron911]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bucks Guard George Hill has a left adductor strain and will not return to tonight's game vs. #Timberwolves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyBlueDevil7 here we go!!!! We could meet again. #Wahoowa #gohoos #giddyup 🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🔷⚔️🔶💙⚔️🧡 https://t.co/gbJrzujbSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead @PhillyGOP mayoral candidate Daphne Goggins cites her status as a recovering cocaine addict, 13 years sober… https://t.co/3msd89Tfja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hank_green5 Unfortunately haven’t been one since the first Michigan State loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abella_Danger Cani try babi am ur biggest fan and ihad a cruch on u since i first saw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's season change not climate change please stop scaring the children of America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerfederer Just do bike. Run loose sand...weight. and the most natural tennis player I seen in my life. jokovick… https://t.co/FQVSIuY03W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorxyoung 13 seconds into the first available track and I’m sold. Whips ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manfightdragon I stopped bothering with Kotaku for anything, long ago. And I just get my kpop and news from Arirang]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzanier468 @billyrunaway @SmoncureW @garycdavison I'm terrified to find out how that thought creeps into anyone's… https://t.co/rUcyVyyBWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic thread from @adamscrabble on China economic stress points — pollution is significant economic suppressor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorseTourneys That's why I'd rather play a live tournament. Less likely to happen in live tournament if they're wa… https://t.co/bgcMxlkKuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annendil @wdrohrer @Madt44491145 @jlwesterfield @KJackottawa We just love towns with suggestive names. 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DizFoley Pokémon could do with a set of goo variants to popular/all existing mon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you knew my Mom, then you know she saved everything. Though she has been gone since July 2015, I am still findin… https://t.co/ySDTgdVe5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski He came here When Pleasant Ca was destroyed he called it Pleasure on National TV, the Governor had to quietly correct him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brother’s Discover channel performs well for Vertical Networks. In February it received 23 million unique viewers a… https://t.co/IwEhpOeOAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I moved out before graduating high school at 17. All it takes is some fucken hard work. Not everyone is willing to… https://t.co/ErwRXBzVOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherry25793049 @HLAurora63 I was rooting for Ricky Williams to win on Celebrity Big Brother...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audavidb @LAPC Legit don’t know if you can draw 5 and if so, have you ever witnessed it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends is the #1 morning show and Ainsley is an angel from God!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brake caliper rebuild day with the season rapidly approaching #HardWork #Determination #Perseverance #43ToTheFront https://t.co/2TzQBcaWKp]]></document></documents></author>