<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I love this pic of a girl and her toad...because i had a toad, too...but mine... https://t.co/aVelrtVfwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The temptations in your life are no different from what others experience. And God is faithful. H…… https://t.co/rxIrCls565]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ people who say my technology doesn’t listen to me... how is this recommended??? All I know is I want a shirt for… https://t.co/7oxmqVcXnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a sectional? Retail $3000 for $1199 Come see me today to get this super comfy gel memory cushion sectio… https://t.co/GrP4Nc6VSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/OmQYRPG3gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vidman Lol... not just for pregnancy.  That gel is cold!  They used it to check if I have 2 kidneys. Apparently my… https://t.co/GCMbLnt96c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_jenxx Agreed. I just think she's too set in her ways and he shuts down when she starts being extra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motherdaughter Career day at @CelinaISD. Loved telling kids about the Army! #Veterans #Military #Pilot #learning… https://t.co/9wnAQYqa1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AalyaDE @TaranWasson @jan_ssh @ColleenTiernan @tmwy_emav 😂 Absolutely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Authenticity is better than perfection ⭐️☀️💕 Love this list of things to remember. Have an amazing day! https://t.co/djTFckErJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__nicoke Lol true that happened to me on the hwy a few weeks back when it was raining and i had natalie in the car… https://t.co/pg2w5znKSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for showing me how love feels, thanks for showing me how loss feels too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@staceyabrams will be governor and Brian Kemp will be in prison! Hallelujah!!! Refer Kemp to DOJ! #ArrestBrianKemp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metromorning Got ice melt yesterday. Last storm’s casualties are in air boots from casts. Saw 6 ppl in them yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mostrador @Aeromexico_com in Reynosa, Tamaulipas https://t.co/ztZomqgJlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family .... period....love all 3 of these beauties 😍🤩💕 https://t.co/O1okelxi8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marjory Stoneman Douglas students reflect on the past year  https://t.co/G3YCz2ytpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[still don’t understand how tf I got played 🙂🙂 if it’s not your TRUE intention, don’t act like it is ??!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold @a_cormier_ Isn't March 14th the same day of Roger Stone hearing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need some workout ideas for the weekend @BrickellAcademy ? Why not try one of the staff workouts from this week 😊… https://t.co/kOyEPZ8FL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCMLXXXI_ME @hkmccorkle @LindseyGrahamSC @BetoORourke @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You wouldn’t have heard about it. It… https://t.co/UXUmLUrwdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mis amigos militantes, simpatizantes y familia priísta; quiero agradecer por los momentos, reflexiones y abrazos… https://t.co/5EkQX7SAb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Pacifica at the Sanchez Art Center to view the artwork of Maija Peeples-Bright. Amazing colors, vivid animal mot… https://t.co/hthHG2KkJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK BUT I SERIOUSLY CANNOT WAIT TO RECEIVE MY @daisymarquez_ PALETTE 😩😍💖💖💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this isn’t the most 2010 post I ever saw idk what is. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/Zf9Hl7zm1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eathbound420 @tetsuki @canadiandaws83 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4… https://t.co/6OVkyslSPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooo today at lakeland: • some girls fight over a dumbass boy. (one gets their hair ripped out by the other) • the… https://t.co/nRtI7p3uIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @Unfreakin @Jim_Jordan @realDonaldTrump .@Jim_Jordan’s rhetoric shows he DOES NOT CARE about Donald Trum… https://t.co/vk6igCiUOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Maybe you should ask and if he says yes find a doctor who helps you instead of saying negative things… https://t.co/9cHux851OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Policies and practices, manager’s mindsets and unconscious biases, as well as women’s doubt of their own readiness… https://t.co/DrFurnW1ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever it takes! No excuses! This is what strong women do for their sisters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[aaannnddd the other day my manager told me I was a boss ass bitch and truly... i need to start reminding myself that. thanks for tuning in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys.. I have another snow day! I’ll just be here sleeping with my cat! 🤗🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rfighterer Please get that thought out of your mind. I live to see him in Miami.  Best part of my year. It was awf… https://t.co/8UXhTIH6fS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AMITAhealth, are you aware of that patients are receiving telemarketing calls on internal hospital phones in t… https://t.co/lCk8mxuMbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mortgage rates fall to 12-month low – 30-year at 4.37% https://t.co/MbTng5WsEa #mortgagerates #realestate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to S.O.S. by @rihanna on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/MeKVvtMCyf https://t.co/x1CXxhIMbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[drake is the  score to our lives the past  10 yrs  everything we went through  there’s a drake song for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for some #fun #BabyCanes #content? Follow @JrCanesQuebec as they take on the world in this year's… https://t.co/XxUFMsb8Zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnSmithReads Lol they aren’t that savvy with it, it’s real. He’s doing these videos on his Instagram. There’s ot… https://t.co/UT79UY0V1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for #writerscommunity: is there a hashtag for advertising/talking about stories with queer characters wher… https://t.co/TS60HCrt2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAMIU PEEPS! Go support TAMIU Ballet Folklorico in our Valentine’s Day Bake sale! ❤️🧁🍰🥧🍪🍩 https://t.co/tINHH26z9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The start of my @Spencermusic1 wall of fame! ❤❤❤ pictures will be added in the next week! https://t.co/6MFH3u1aYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just left work and my cab driver commented on how I look like I’ve had a long day, ye think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t know i could love someone so much until you blessed me with a niece ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does kid me kinda look like that girl from that vine https://t.co/Se9dFsDuP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dylan performed with Katya and honestly as 1 out of 2 of his momagers I can almost die happy now, he’s almost made it😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StripeysRiposte @SnowyOwlGoddess @manlogic2 @diva_ex_machina @LamentMyIcarus @JackLam42356343 @FikeMartin… https://t.co/SZB7e9TuB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DutchBros another weekend and another tweet and no response from the coffee place I  love so much. Really wish we… https://t.co/Fs7hq8p7Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano Mmm, @hockeygirl41 , I think your right, I don't think this is sal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bright_kolleen @JGreenblattADL @IlhanMN Jews speaking really bothers you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why parents/educators are starting to feel like their voices are not being heard is killing me! Keep fighting, keep… https://t.co/jYSAromLqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend 10 years trying to justify buying a $20 sweater but I don’t blink when I spend $4 on my daily coffee 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[we are listening to i bet on losing dogs at this here 3:30am during lit issue layout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanquetino Haha that’s super funny actually! The homeward bound part mDe me chuckle.. ☺️  She was already named Ma… https://t.co/ia4IA6XLRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[this one time a kid walked up to our car and shi thead rolled down my window and the kid leaned in and hugged me an… https://t.co/bFByS06GoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 And that's why Florida is investigating you.  #FireKushner  #FireIvanka  #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #ResignNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piratechristian , I was just listening to the 1/24/19 episode, &amp; I have 2 questions:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I entered my first weight lifting competition. We had 15mins total to Squat, Strict press, and deadlift.… https://t.co/ODZWdj6mf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAXES TAKING FOREVER I BEEN CLAIMING THE SAME DEPENDENT FOR 23 YEARS NEVER SOLD MY KID'S SO WTF? MY W2'S BEEN OUT S… https://t.co/zzXy87lEo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[also i wanna do someone’s makeup who isn’t my sister. so dani it’s probably gonna be u js]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ahora corran y no lloren los que hicieron de mi confianza un folclore”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ChanceGuest very well deserved!!!!!  Tough kid and competitor!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love them so much! ❤️ #2yrs4mths #6monthsold @ Tierrasanta, San Diego https://t.co/dMLuJzs38x]]></document><document><![CDATA[You didn’t win, Dumbo, Russia made you win and we have put up with your lies long enough.#Trumpresign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeBestest @realDonaldTrump Really! Yuck, hearing him once hurts my head, twice, I want to stick something in my 👂… https://t.co/c6iSajQ3ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tahoequeen21 @skelechiwatson Yes, my father passed when I was 23 and that line explains my life since then. Tears flowing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravo_Karma_ @VanderVVtm @lisarinna @KimRichards11 @KyleRichards So her behavior is typical and no one finds this… https://t.co/ydIhSYGUar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicRegistr @CatholicNewsSvc Oh, ok, it’s just coincidental that the PA study found that about 80% of pedofile… https://t.co/bCIem4xwzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smitty52_ @jamescharles I will be soon! My youngest boys are starting school!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And dance by the light of the moon... @ The Amber Rose Bridal https://t.co/0O7HjUWbTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen I call them pizza bones &amp; either hubby eats them or the dogs do! Lol! Judge away. 🇺🇸💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Workout mientras, escucho #MiedoBebanaRadio  Napoleón Zzzzzzzz https://t.co/VNq8bwbJkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 #RotarySunshine is the recent one @vicky_git  @Gathua_Muhia https://t.co/8S9sKXTPsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum It is just because when it comes to someone like him, there is no way of knowing what is truth &amp; what is bull.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenateDems so basically Cali is gonna pay for our wall 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kreilly65 Also she’s a high school student- she’s learning how to employ different approaches at a young age to ho… https://t.co/gK20LS73QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to know Howard. Why else would we send out the reveal of top 16! Wanted to make sure people were talking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[trauma surgeons sharing #gunshot wombs while ignoring OBGYNs killing women in #childbirth with #substandard care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brizmv21 @babyjane8673 @Lifesab5138 @Dr_O_inFL @dwdemom @2020_kari @karap214 @TinaKonvalinka @mrw523 I’m on Instag… https://t.co/4EyLMiidoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLS 2.0  La citation marquante de la première journée @mls.   #MLSisBack #OnniaisePlus https://t.co/7rgIz63s9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[:: since 2019 is my year of learning and practicing #selflove and #selfcare, i’m totally feeling being my own… https://t.co/KnSbTFna0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este Lunes 25 de Febrero en #EL_CANAL_DE_MIS_ESTRELLAS  ⭐ vikybaltazar  Denle like, comenten peronlo mas importante… https://t.co/xsw2Q1SeKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life gives you lemons. Throw them away because ewe. You don’t need those in your life sweetie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @myserenity69 @SpeakerPelosi IF!!! That's the operative word here! We have no, idea what Mueller is doing… https://t.co/J6w7nLYB1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two rays of light and the best leadership examples any woman would be honored to have!  Thank you for sharing your… https://t.co/WBCZj9ggT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie Where are you all coming up with these dumb ass questions??? You all look so stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welikekittens Prayer and Blessings to you and your Dear Kitty. Please keep us posted on the health of your Dear One.A]]></document><document><![CDATA[first question- could i make a snapchat story for “close friends” but only put one person on it and Second question… https://t.co/kV9DNikQ36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brokenmouth7525 Maybe I can sneak in, rebel lounge is like 5 min away from my house lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just drank like a litre of arizona green tea are my organs going to shut down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nando_aze MIDNIGHTPEARL thinks since it's on a military type base it should have bunks, just like real bases. I have to agree her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what America is going to have to put up with if we let these immigrants into our country! It’s not fair to… https://t.co/pRThm5S3pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm... I need to make more time to read books. #2019goals #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/3lZ1UrmZlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Does @realDonaldTrump’s appeasement’s to #TheEnemy ever end❓❓❓  @marklevinshow @marcorubio… https://t.co/QZLmPXjWE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I thought I’d introduce myself more so for IG than FB but I’ll post it to both as there may be something peop… https://t.co/8T5KXz2Td2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! Don’t miss us doing a uniquely poignant and Space Invader-friendly performance @sevengrandsd in #NorthPark… https://t.co/GQnJbNkg7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[DID YOU KNOW: You can get free rides to cultural sites for #BlackHistoryMonth⁠ ⁠ - https://t.co/0HfihN8E4C https://t.co/ODi17uhcxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Talesh @brentwpeterson Brent and Susan train in MN which is basically Canada. If they can run in the desert you c… https://t.co/HdGXxMS233]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classes: 18 hours Soccer: 7 hours Work Study: 12 hours Work: 20 hours Homework: ??? Socializing: ??? Me: https://t.co/O2YmcE34aB]]></document></documents></author>