<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KelseyNews3LV @News3LV Tanning in Vegas on a snow day. Good call, CCSD. https://t.co/Zvlggkn7w3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DataInforms Thanks, I *hate* looking things up. https://t.co/hVrOJ2Zobu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLeopold I need some advice from you my wife is a victim of her employer they file the I-9 form checked box sa… https://t.co/nYmTnK3O5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know youre getting old when you think, “you know what? I’m gonna sleep in tomorrow.” And set your alarm to 6:45 insteat of 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertFGoings Hahaha. There in lies the difference. Wofford = PE (that included chardonay and cheeses?)  The Citad… https://t.co/mUgREPfG9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a life time NRA member however I have got to were I hate the NRA. They support all these mass shootings that A… https://t.co/G0liI6DG58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kj_fetishmodel Katrina, do u know who I am!! There r a lot of people out there pretending to be u!! One tried to s… https://t.co/Q0FPMFrAVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigtanktv Coach I’ve had a few coaches hit me about those too good athletes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OsirisLunaMeza @nayibbukele @LaHuellaSV @RCuchillla @_ElUta @DiarioTIMES @anliker1980 @SanSalvadorGANA… https://t.co/qgfk0GuOAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeByrne6 @jonnybowles731 @Beefboat15 @NateHoot @theofficenbc https://t.co/O3pQNZL9Ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaltyCorpse When you know you're right but people won't accept it and just agree with you. It's not difficult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arroyo de La Pasión, al fondo se trasladó la misión jesuita de Los Dolores Tañuetiá en 1741. El religioso Clemente… https://t.co/AHwSsHgpe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost javierhalamadrid with get_repost ・・・ Y así es como el demonio de Chavez terminó conduciendo hacia lo que él… https://t.co/fFGD4jrpqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[After scoring his first #NHL goal, #NYR rookie defenseman Libor Hajek heads to the locker room for what appears to… https://t.co/4W0SlVBzZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJITAD @Drnancyskaplan Great win - well deserved - never underestimate the power of a little extra sugar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizabethMay Squamish used to be a nuclear weapons free zone, now it will be a LNG zone, I told Catherine that it was a bad idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcox64 @RealJamesWoods @JWWins I refuse to give even one click to any site associated with Bill Kristol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theotropho @TimelessNuggets I know I can be wrong. It's happened many times before. I enjoy conversing with people… https://t.co/InBOsfP2sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickyeatsbeats I can’t believe we were little hoodlums tattooing/piercing out of her house lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@76ersProcessing @DerekBodnerNBA Those 4 minutes are nearly a fireable offense. I’m serious. Game was within reach… https://t.co/sw3VUOc29e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Only democrats see color. They use it to get votes and as a weapon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m doing keto, and everywhere I go, I see pizza.  Literally in my face. https://t.co/lOu5ezpIvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Tierney Aldredge and @denveragency for taking the journey with me to support the Adopt The Arts Founda… https://t.co/hsTrRiRBSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If his grandfather is Kent Hance and Kent is from my hometown, I’m sure Andrew spent some time hooping there. There… https://t.co/9YHvsmAHdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREP BASEBALL: County Line 17, Magazine 0, FINAL  Caleb Robberson WP; Pacyn Reames 3-for-3; Tyler Dugger 3-for-4 @ClhsIndians @TimesRecord]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely another #ImpeachableOffense and supported by the corrupt @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[In #Tennessee a child born to unmarried parents is legally in the custody of the mother until a court orders visita… https://t.co/x8Y0RGvKmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power Item of the Day - Lady Spider's steampunk style powered by invention and used as one of the Web Warriors. @ R… https://t.co/ipOL2wj4LT]]></document><document><![CDATA[5am vibes in the East Bottoms. #kc #electricpark https://t.co/vfBjSJQf81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRickScott @orlandosentinel If you can’t drink the water or farm the earth, and get cancer from by products.If y… https://t.co/ytB6cLQWEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winniesun A2:  Make sure to create a great summary, check your spelling and grammar, use a current headshot and an… https://t.co/kpXCePswRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's with me retweet Charles Payne is filling in for Neil Cavuto on the fox and I love him I wish they would keep… https://t.co/abHxsp3tDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZimmersEars @JimJaxMedia @gmfb @heykayadams @nateburleson I feel the same way. We could be wrong. Maybe neck s… https://t.co/EszRnvjJaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two constipated faces of Mika &amp; Joe in the morning. They both need to drink a gallon of prune juice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching Tarasenkos Instagram stories of him at a children’s hospital signing autographs and hugging everyone... https://t.co/ulTiDLrvuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments Isn't it great that we're in league with the worst people on the planet now that we have Trump boy… https://t.co/ziFHhMIa2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear friends. I don’t do this very often, but if you could help us out and follow @SBCWines on instagram, you’ll be… https://t.co/ldrBCqrM5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s Jared Bednar after #Avs blow leads of 2-0 and 3-1 and fall to 1-12 OT https://t.co/t5HEzyTvnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherBM @FPGarvin @realDonaldTrump Again, we’ll have to wait and see what the report finally says - it’s not supp… https://t.co/5y80HtLD76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @BillKristol Seek treatment please...so much wasted energy and intelligence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid day of baseball with 22 hits and 27 RBIs - pitching and defense did a great job and the boys went 1-0 twice t… https://t.co/JwIuTQOfx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“95 percent” isn’t too shabby for a QB with serious drop foot concerns just a few months ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcgloves This really is a million dollar idea. I would honestly delete this lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip Shows how idiotic trump is. Painted steel would be a maintenance nightmare. Continuous and expensive.… https://t.co/dVubtmwzyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesDurham Also great to see one of the ACC ‘legends’ working the game in Dick Paparo. You knew the drama was coming when Paparo was there 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[God grant me the courage not to give up what I know is right when the world presses me to accept it’s godless values.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ St. Peter's Church &amp; World Outreach Center https://t.co/Wz964J9Rhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Do all the protestors create enough of a reason to declare  marshall Law ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aetiology, have you seen this?  I am shaking my head.   https://t.co/qDQy41CEzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[De hecho hoy se vislumbra un amoroso, cómico, musical #oigoxeda No se lo pueden perder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithxblack You just have to master the art of meditation. I think only like super monks are capable of this tho gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun on the runway!! Always a crowd pleaser!! (I filmed the audience during one of my walks on Facebook Live!) 😜😜 Th… https://t.co/lnZz6Uxh0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Kevin is a racist POS and so is @TuckerCarlson with his lying views spewed by the fakest media of all the daily caller]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a feeling the Vanderbilt v Tennessee game tomorrow night isn’t going to be pretty... Go Dores anyways!! #AnchorDown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally bought two floor tickets and I’m riding solo... one for sell hmu NOW #travis #astroworld #houston… https://t.co/s4lwhIK7jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida governor calls for grand jury probe of school safety ahead of Parkland shooting anniversary - CNN https://t.co/mA36DdT2PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatadorCalderon @BachesEsAMLOver En la práctica, a toda señal, comentario o insinuación del ejecutivo, habrá una r… https://t.co/VUdnG2U6aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiltonWolfMD One thing good comes from this. People must listen to factual reporting to get to the truth. Many peo… https://t.co/MoasQ51HVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColonelGirth A drop in the bucket for a one year deal that the #colts aren't tied to. If you don't know how this w… https://t.co/3GZrmtpsSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher Good news Sunday:  came across a dad this AM panicked because a pickup had side swiped his car, disabl… https://t.co/obEJ3jhNQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews https://t.co/VNDRgl1lcj wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJostworth Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve just spent five hours editing the by-laws and covenants for our homeowner’s association. They haven’t been… https://t.co/5xm0mcJRqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should add, I don’t think the situation in the US is anything like that in the UK. In the US, the Democrats gener… https://t.co/xJ5eIgbfCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonyxperiamx Pregunta...cuándo traeran a México el recien anunciado Sony Xperia X1 ?  Muchas gracias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tompkins: “What’s the problem? The news cycle is moving so fast. We started when the news cycle starts instead of g… https://t.co/SgaChigUz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could you imagine going on vacation to escape everyday life and enjoy the world you just stepped into only to have… https://t.co/NHXthqs0WY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ I’m the KING of talk s*** now I’m back it up” - Pardi https://t.co/KYtBWC8UYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out fellas! Now my gaydar is rusty I admit but this dude looks like he is SOOOO in the closet! Not that th… https://t.co/R2nmRXEBLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamthe1110 @NBCNews They should be held responsible for any harm their irresponsibility causes others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentleyGC Tiger’s the best. He has also declined post round comments at times throughout the years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirTrafficAJ @RealFansProgram The structure is to protect during the lockout.  2019-20: $3M + $9M SB 2020-21: $1M… https://t.co/782XaGwjqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MozingoBaseball @keithlaw @_JeremyBooth Come on now, you know which delivery is more efficient for Command.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clnbrns @AmericanAir Ha! I was thinking the same. But then a hero named Renee at the ORD Admirals Club got me on t… https://t.co/54D7s86Otr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBozzella Thank You Coach. I was at the game yesterday and wanted to thank you for letting Grace take the tap f… https://t.co/N3i9DDaK1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am feeling HEATED about religion this morning these morons will really make jokes about liberals thinking climate… https://t.co/vBjEt6lExO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JP_MotherOfPug That Is My Moms Name Jennifer Palmer and I Love Weather So Weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina Ale House 2618 Weston Rd. Weston, FL. 33331 March 28th 2019, 6:00pm to 9:00pm Register Today Limited Seats… https://t.co/NVEGDCfw9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, would you look at the time…              12       11           1   10                  2 9          ⊙… https://t.co/NADvjt5lhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlukacs exacto quien a hierro mata alli esta lo que busco o es correcto el senor???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it wrong that I keep repeating, "Nobody puts baby in a corner"??? 😂😂😂 #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanHilferty @PressHerald @DavidLarter @thisdog @KevinMillerPPH Do you often defend grifters? Perhaps it would pr… https://t.co/tvGMkdodxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dem Whip Clyburn: Rep. Ilhan Omar Has a ‘Tremendous Future in Politics’ https://t.co/Nal33vxuql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceyb65 All I’ve ever done is love Chinese food! https://t.co/rAvnkkVtU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your music sucks mate. Lmaoooo! Can’t even say it with a straight face. Just kidding boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know im ugly so if I bump into money no woman finna tell me otherwise.  I know my league lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MrSteven had 2 arms attached 1st sight 10AM Feb22 @PortCanaveral-after campickup #pad40 @SpaceX #NusantaraSatu… https://t.co/moFt6Th2hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeGoodberry @JayMorrisonATH Is this some "I can fix him" bravado from Turner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theforrestblack @RachelSlur That’s what I’ve been referring to her as 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never too small to dream big. Photography by: David Loeb for Edward Fox Photography &amp; Video . . . #flowergirl… https://t.co/nht153ohX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCOttawa Its been pothole season since the roads were clearer in late January]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxnewsgal Good morning, Lisa! Have a Happy Valentines Day! @foxnewsgal will always rock! https://t.co/tUWcUt3CEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Hey don’t you dare try to get us to go on record supporting this total bs idea. Says every democrat on the hill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this tweet I went and read em and all I can say is Melly gone bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting things ready for the #RedlandsClassic #shimanoroad #shimanomultiservice #thatsagoodblue https://t.co/ogb6Hzqh6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/BvXwPgxG51]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @OnTheBorder Mexican Grill &amp; Cantina in Exton, PA https://t.co/ZatMkMVayM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Marlins team leader in stolen bases is certainly an interesting graph to look at.  In 2017, Dee Gordon led the… https://t.co/wIOnS5ncdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CleanJab Do you think Dana White knows anything about promotion that he didn't learn from Vince McMahon? I sure don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConceptualJames Also why safety issues like wearing a safety belt or motorcycle helmet are appropriate areas of le… https://t.co/B8qxCJElkn]]></document></documents></author>