<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MartinHeinrich @WSJ You may convince me. I’m just asking for the true P/L of one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahVienhage How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/oeFM9nwXYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m Game of Thrones the only thing that could be better would be more thematically engaging cinematography.… https://t.co/UR2i2qAo6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukedabbelt2514 This is why college is so important!  Think about this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cureari 6. Sexual abuse which caused depression, an ED and self harm. 14 when my schizophrenia started. Lived with… https://t.co/7lnmz6DrTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s goooo Maryland 🐢🏀⚫️🔴 close this season out with a W #FTT #Terps100]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step and Repeat Banner.... In need of graphic design services? Contact us at info@minorproduction.com or order at… https://t.co/FRJgAcyL5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself I understand the puppy, Boiled eggs are good, more so in a salad. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Questions to Ask Before You Buy Your Dream Home https://t.co/HSbZd0swV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofShawneeKS as of 30 min ago Shawnee Mission Parkway and Monticello was very very slick. If it's not too much… https://t.co/ByemIxCoGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it !!    Aline ? wise sayings..... #laughter #snicker #grin #merry https://t.co/la8zSaQZ3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treated myself today while at Roosevelt Field mall for work. 🤩 #doughlife doughliferoosevelt • • • • • #dessert… https://t.co/cotQVcfmRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread really show how blatantly flawed the #justice system is... #justicereform #wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMQ1030 @RadioEmmet @nytimes @eoinweldon Not a bot but no profile pic. Good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricArnoldTN @VMI_Basketball Shooting 50% from deep on 29 3’s is going to be hard to maintain. Better bring some #defense to round 2!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to I Can't Be Satisfied by @muddyofficial on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/K9vEcmxlHk https://t.co/hvQljBq2VH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mardigras was a blast! 🤢🤮 @kevinfowler @ Louis Armstrong New Orleans International Airport https://t.co/VvIkFpSaP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karynbaum Certainly. Thankfully this tweet is getting me some good recommendations. Watching doctors go on and on… https://t.co/Y9QLALpf7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyGavin I accepted the challenge from @coachballard to post the cover of 7 books I love; no explanations or… https://t.co/n4NdZweTfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just going to put this video out there from @rickmercer. All @JustinTrudeau had to do was do his best at what he pr… https://t.co/eGelQ6abtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zac Ervin is an Example of being raised in SWVA by a Great Family and Living in an AWESOME Community like Gate City and SCOTT CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Look at me, I'm Ben Shapiro and anything you say that doesn't agree with my beliefs on Israel makes you anti-semitic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein why the flip flop? You seemed to care for American citizens then, why not now? #BuildTheWall 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mans said he would rather listen to a podcast lmaoooooo i’m dead 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know the difference between sleeping with someone and sleeping with someone you love. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackLamsonCBS6 Did you see the kick? It wasn’t good. And shouldn’t you be sleeping now? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist This is what PRIMARY ELECTIONS are for. https://t.co/wlXwQlxn9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could argue it’s the Bulls best win of the year. LaVine (42) and Markkanen (35) with career-highs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump According to a recent prophecy she is being used by the left because she is a femal… https://t.co/2v0JSL1fUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[delete your Valentine’s Day tweet or just delete your Valentine, Zach has THE ONE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna miss @Mathieu_Era so much!! So upset w/ my Texans for not trying harder. But can’t wait to watch him ball… https://t.co/bQZPljut7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrandonMorse I saw the people who asked questions.  They certainly weren't stacked against Bernie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends make fun of me because I have a very obvious type ... sad, short, baby face tattooed girls next door]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why but every time Juston feels sick he comes &amp; ask me to diagnose him 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abroadunderhood У нас в супермаркетах пиво, вино, шампанское, слабоалкогольные коктейли, всё что крепче в специальных магазинах.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Rutherford @Nashville_MMA He did have a good junior year. We still think he’s a good player. But he was rated b… https://t.co/oVHKfvdAxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe she doesn’t have valid point she can stand behind to defend socialism and reason @AOC won’t do live interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhirlpoolCorp What are you going to show your remote features don't work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the day with our favorite two characters at Magic Kingdom @WaltDisneyWorld https://t.co/ELeyNcXi8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I saw and heard you talk about the stand you made at Standing Rock protest.  Question What did you and everyon… https://t.co/r1306cYVQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We keep up our Power Tower work all the way to the conference meet, tapering the yardage as though any other form o… https://t.co/pfHxcAVgRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASBO past presidents (plus Pat 😁)#PASBO2019 #asbo https://t.co/Xff2KNSWXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn’t planning on working out at 4:30am this morning, but it happened.   Thankful for this Herbalife 24 Brownie… https://t.co/JMtu7NLZW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cops show up to roll call the next day after their biggest arrest! #NYPD #BackTheBlue #kids #rt https://t.co/5VgFgIFdpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCreamer @ProductHunt Nice! Shoot us a link when it’s up. cc @jakecrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freesrt8 @your__grace @tevgates_ I tell everybody keep that emergency pallet on hand for the boy never know when ima pop up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleWeezley You established you aren’t a baseball guy, I definitely am and also have lived in the northeast sever… https://t.co/8DH2hqMrQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Friday13thGame is there any chance you can add Rob as a playable counselor you guys have the model in the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoPRENSA @Pontifex_es me pregunto si Bergoglio piensa un poco las cosas antes de salir en Prensa ??? NO sera… https://t.co/myfQIwtGaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #FortWorth, TX? View our latest opening: https://t.co/xF4SA6yF2P #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoviePass I want to make sure that this stupid thing is canceled and you won’t let me! PLEASE VERIFY THAT IM OFF Y… https://t.co/1HIuFxg7xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arky got screwed on the road. Now, I’ll say they missed some key FTs down the stretch, but the refs screwed em. Eit… https://t.co/iCQ42yV98m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YMA_GirlsHoops @Donnied926 @RcollinsJudon @YMAPRINCIPAL @YonkersSchools @quezada1229 Great job coach and ladies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this jolly there's something wrong with you. Grumpy cat funny, grumpy cat humor, grumpy cat meme,… https://t.co/FFBVPKlyWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The line, "...predominantly French-speaking Outremont neighbourhood." Blew my mind. "In other news I'm standing her… https://t.co/ziGMgjveDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes ... and the fewer straws you have, the more socialister it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes indeed Clifford mommy took care of my wellness Bath but I see that your Unicorn Spirit is telling me that we ar… https://t.co/KmU9IuUJrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow coming down! #winter #tree #Boise #NorthEndBoiseIdaho @ Hyde Park, Boise, Idaho https://t.co/tXdCD57I6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capitalweather coming down in Ashburn, sticking to sidewalks, grass, and infrequently used roads already. https://t.co/MDpu8OtPgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieV @BeverlyWilshire @chancetherapper I took the dog out in the rain for his nightly movement then I came in a… https://t.co/3FudsGVwp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier Fair and Balanced? About as Fair and Balanced as Sputnik. https://t.co/jc31FBo3PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#acrylic and #ink on panel #abstract #abstrakt #abstracto #arteabstracto #pintura #painting #pittira #peonture… https://t.co/mXl5RZohZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good start once again for Trimble, which leads Glenwood 6-0 in the opening minutes. Glenwood has 6-7 Tyler Caldwell… https://t.co/AQwhNcxqqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little pocket on jeans is designed specifically for guitar picks, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGr78574965 The similarities between the words of POTUS and those in their final months in memory care hospice… https://t.co/DeEnhJrbFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Principal @mssimley showing off her dance moves!! #BlackHistoryMonth #JaguarPRIDE #WilliamWirtStrong… https://t.co/HXPLanfQN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBorgal @ladybugspicnic @daveyslimmon Lack of attention by #ottcity and silence is probably the best thing to give… https://t.co/WVRO6FNfhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When two of your favorite people write a book you get excited!! Congratulations @csloughrige and Uncle Scott ❤️ thi… https://t.co/SudtUUFahR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta look up the facts before reacting. No drunk driving, no speeding, night time and the people weren’t using a c… https://t.co/pCxchsRub1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakewirick12 Yea I wouldn’t hate a 3rd rounder. Maybe he needs a change of scenery. They need someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Here’s to hoping your day goes better than Kharitonov’s night went last night. Sorry @mattmitrione bu… https://t.co/hBPosj5T0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDirtyTCo I appreciate your advocacy, but do you have a particular policy change that you think would help? Wond… https://t.co/vUhTZI64Zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having ones skin crawl doesn’t really matter, because nothing will be done.  Need more doers not talkers.  Not talk… https://t.co/SeCo0Dx7DK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mayor_Steinberg @sacsheriff @FBI @CIA @TheJusticeDept @dhs @thegrupeco ...Grupe, please have your lawyers contact… https://t.co/nDxr8Z0rIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to present today at the Vaping and Our Youth conference put on by @MPY_Inc! https://t.co/dOicWA6I3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina-Duke is a little less than 48 hours away and, even in Wilmington, I can sense it in the air]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy’s a capitalist. But he also knows you have to win the Democratic nomination before you can win the general.… https://t.co/kiGI9vPasX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dark money is what happened and made it easy to stop the one person one vote to be made for big money. That is why… https://t.co/VtqXARroyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Stay positive in every situation and everything you do, never stop trying, have faith don’t stop due to failure.”… https://t.co/DcTtWUS2Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scope the MS metric reference tool in the back of this 1486 Boethius @NewberryLibrary! I have no expertise in datin… https://t.co/7GckLh6tRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignOfApril and expired mayo but that ain’t nunna my bidniss 🐸☕️🤣 https://t.co/u6TmitXDDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope that the UND men’s hockey team can deliver a big win over UNO as]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Edelen follows the orders of the “blue Bloods” of Louisville who have tried to take over city govt., tried thr… https://t.co/x9LOWyCpna]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is sad. This is a guy that used to promote himself as a righteous Christian. Wonder if the train accident chan… https://t.co/vPbhoMPjU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently streaming on #twitch. Come hang out, drop a follow. Give me some pointers in the chat. #ApexLegends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast for champions! Roast beef with chimichurri sauce, one of many new options at @ToyotaStadiumTX. Chef Rex T… https://t.co/vXV9sEw41J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harlan Loves me Donald “F’n” Trump.  America first. Constitutional return.  Death to the Democrat Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichGrisham I can't believe this is Xbox's answer to all the award winning exclusives on @PlayStation  Also: Can't… https://t.co/UQWcHeVXy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So barbecue Becky getting 75 years too? #tuskegee_rys19 #SouthernU_RYS19 #wiley_rys19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmoPhilips I’m here for you. I even waited 6 seconds before tweeting this. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryCallahan Won’t be long before Al Sharpton is sitting alongside Kraft in his box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rachels_Ratchet thanks Rachel. Have a great weekend. https://t.co/WpxGitJVys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@housewifeswag You can buy extra icing, the best thing about @Publix cakes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPLGLocal10 @BrandonOrrWx @NekiMohanWPLG @TTongenWPLG @JulieDurdaWPLG @alexfinnieWPLG @BettyDavisWPLG… https://t.co/PycJVMoTiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two week update....poor Vandy has to go to Knoxville after UT’s beatdown. Hide the women and children for that one.… https://t.co/K7Z38MYC3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendonbouzard @NicolePauline17 @CarriWeatherwax @DJaye @Rachel_McRea So I'm guessing you missed the memo that the… https://t.co/2TmfAPHeH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irish_Atheist well, two. they're either jaguars or leopards. a black lion isnt a black panther :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow for @FootyTalksLive’s #ElClasico panel!  🕰 Noon 📍 @TheRecRoomCa  🍻 Drinks, snacks and prize raffle… https://t.co/XPCfgntUEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at I-90 Exit 145 - OH-57 Lorain Elyria in Elyria, OH https://t.co/ONB7PRCDky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta remind yourself the type of lifestyle you’re working hard for https://t.co/kS2km8JnwI]]></document></documents></author>