<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I don't understand how the sport of Judas Priest, Motley Crue, and Guns n' Roses gets Keith Urban to play its prime… https://t.co/02nHV1Kuhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manriquehector Con perdón de los Idiotas en sus momentos Porque Éstos los Sobrepasan en Su Anacronismo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJOpinion_ @reviewjournal But it sure shows how little the 'middle class' actually benefited from Trump's 'huge' t… https://t.co/Bhs3iAJwLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no good reason why all of y’all have American cheese in your house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Viewed crosses, autographed Bibles, and then went back to looting and pillaging the presidency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[what kills me is when i email a professor and they don’t respond for DAYS and i ask them about it in class and they… https://t.co/6NbHhpUXJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This look is called “I was too cold without a jacket so I threw one on and this is what happened” 😂🤷🏼‍♀️  White lin… https://t.co/ls9Oan0IgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishes a happy #ChocolateDay to the online friends.  I just had a dark chocolate ganache to accentuate that point.  ^_^  #Valentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day To ALL Educators. Hahahahaha!!!  Keep those kids focused today. #belltobell https://t.co/YFK8BpP5lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t know it by 3, I’m going to bed. It’s 3:04. I’m going to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New highlights and  color for this soon to be "MiMi or GG"... she doesn't even look old enough to be preparing to h… https://t.co/xaCAymyvGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @BECCAcosmetics @ForeverMalika @Sephora @ultabeauty @Nordstrom @Bloomingdales @QVC @cultbeauty If my 💋 would only]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I flew from NYC to LA just to end up on a bus that’s NYC bound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glynn_Watson30 Your very welcome! What a great day to celebrate!! ❤️💪🏾🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Providence Hospital Emergency Room in Portland, OR https://t.co/H14271ks2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctausigford Apparently people all over town are lined up to take pictures with the #FortErieIceWall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What made Iris think that Madize would go back with her is beyond me #Shadowhunters #ShadowhuntersChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Toronto: I never liked you anyway. Especially after you put @mattymarts17 in the minors.  So blow leafs, blow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mepoclassroom Culinary Encounters Ss are exploring popular eating patterns and product development careers.  Evalu… https://t.co/LNyr2papob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally @DamnD4hlia and I fallout every now and then but she’s is one of the realest bitches to have my back]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, I was so tired, I put toothpaste on my burn instead of first aid cream. It felt great 😕 #monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fideoking @OddJoey joc was ready!! this pisces szn has her like: https://t.co/0FaYIyPoKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AEProjectLit is meeting on March 15th after school to discuss @justinaireland’s book #DreadNation. Community membe… https://t.co/jIvA8ZsjfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful brides! L❤️VE Pics to finish off February! I❤️ 👰 photo by Lupita Ramorez #azweddings #azflorist… https://t.co/X3QKparqaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[A hate group that should be banned or in the very least it’s non profit tax status 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck canvas for crashing while I TYPED an assignment on canvas and not saving it anywhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWENXTGuy @NinaxMouse @KaRaRacn75 @BoakyeCherry @ikeroy82_roy @AlfredoReyes24 @Yungraf1988 @cnationmaverick… https://t.co/iC1oveFSaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I meant to tag @vanessabayer in this tweet but I can never correct it because @jennylewis liked it so I’ll just let… https://t.co/NahNmp1n43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special wildlife visitor today at #nobleES #NGSS We learned a lot about adaptations. Thanks NoblePTA https://t.co/SgRY0AfqVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EscherNYC #goal #motivation #magic #miracle #crystalball #absurd #nycYogateacher #yogainstructor #impossible… https://t.co/3LKjo98Swb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who were the girls hoops stat champs in 2018-19? https://t.co/walysXghmU via @MansfieldNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7273234054 #forrent #stpetersburgflorida @ South, St. Pete https://t.co/5u4VSEy9fG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol the Grizzlies I get since they started in Vancouver ... I have no clue about the pelicans tho lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writing about the Cat in the Hat. #FLALEADS #risdace https://t.co/kFCU1J4QfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prettyHANSOM @wetwhyofcourse I mean if Megz cough up the 500k maybe Nicki will have a warmer heart https://t.co/1eJxsNn767]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg!!!!!!!!!!!!!! This be me in the car for sure!!!!@ChipperChels hittin Thoes high notes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliDa22369986 @jade78052492 @BruinsSandi @gemcos12 @BodtonBears @djglidden @GillyWillyWoo25 @saraturner19… https://t.co/979BkPppew]]></document><document><![CDATA[um me trying to incorporate jonas brothers and irl into one @ is stressful pls ignore my many stages]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend fell asleep while we’re FaceTiming and I miss him so I kept retweeting stuff because he has my post no… https://t.co/eDP59VEgtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 7/11 by my job with have hot Cheeto asteroids tomorrow https://t.co/pAa52VCqQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm  ready!!!  Let's GO!!!! Women are again under systematic attack...... NEVER AGAIN in our lives!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrmngandr Who has always been at the head of the most widespread mass destruction/loss of life historically? Men i… https://t.co/roNfHgUFM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you shall love the Lord your God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your mind and with all… https://t.co/tytIVFwKQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has been too much so I finally got to start watching this season of #SurvivorEdgeofExtinction   SO EXCITED tha… https://t.co/mi6ajMlnIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever grateful for the man who really ignited my passion for public policy, so much so that I went back to school… https://t.co/0Vps5jtgCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyThriller69 Suicide is more common than people realize. I had the pills and the water at my bedside.  I thought… https://t.co/QKi7gqs8Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss being so shocked the first time  you got pissed at me and put me head first into the laundry hamper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EduTurn @BarackObama @NASA @MarsRovers I wish it could be but the flip side of the coin is Trump could, in theory,… https://t.co/cElFyXLaXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: CREAM CHEESE SHOULD NOT BE USED FOR ANY DESSERT aka cheesecake, cream cheese icing....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some spots in #Detroit before the #DBCPitchFest2019 by @detroit_bcc + @eosiodetroit   #Fintech… https://t.co/J6t3kYox0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Petrypsique Claro, te invitan a cenar y no llevas nada?,jamas se debe hacer eso,por lo menos flores, chocolates deberías llevar!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for an informative session at #ATD_DREAM! As part of a team @Starfish360 that helps Higher Ed leaders to lin… https://t.co/rEt92bj4Xy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilsimsie Kayla listen to my voice " it's time to turn your ears in a new direction " Did that help?😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to reconnect with my former boss and mentor @Felixwortiz at the @SOMOSNEWYORK Welcome Reception! Thankful for… https://t.co/881BrJvzZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated @Lawrence has put the spotlight on @RepKatiePorter she is not here to play 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 What’s better than flowers and chocolates? 🏃🏽‍♀️ @brooksrunning eGift Card!!Thank you @1mahoneyelectri love you❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlrichJvV @JHBWestdene @visitgauteng @CityofJoburgZA @GtStevenson @MeetMyMzansi Thanks for sharing. I looked him u… https://t.co/fOyuHs6BuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colbycombel The only good boy that has my heart 😂🥰 Damon is scrumptious too though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeNurseRN @matthewdowd No but he snorts Adderall and is a racist misogynist. You're a mean lying weirdo lady. Just like your Messiah 45.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take away from the 2 late-breaking abstracts: Less is more. #SMFM19  #1 Cord milking harmful in extremely preterm b… https://t.co/rTo6LIUyZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally have the hangover I deserve and Carrie wants to listen to circle takes the square 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[do not watch the handmaids tail on hulu if you have sexual violence triggers. wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rich complaining about needing to be more healthy.   Kayla: You know what it’s called exercising and dieting  Rich:… https://t.co/ASkPbZuiCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[if nick doesn’t perform “nick j is off the chain” on their reunion tour what’s even the point?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are literally drowning and going to blow away! Good grief I’m DONE with the rain! #rainraingoaway @ Tullahoma, T… https://t.co/pB5ETFlLUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetTropiques @GrassrootsSpeak Pence is dirty too,we just haven't searched his wrongdoing enough,He knows what tr… https://t.co/JvZeyNALCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowineco @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @joneill55 @Julianna_glass… https://t.co/jk0u2oRPMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Truthspeaker57 @DineshDSouza @jjauthor That is exactly what their culture and religion believe. We are infidels if… https://t.co/A2Acn5dVvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayasesh @tpatt220 @pattyskim For a second i thought you guys got matching leather jackets and i was about to be l… https://t.co/1pvF3UhNkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth I never thought of it that way before, but you are exactly right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the mental health services at @cnu Christopher Newport University. Her voice teacher fell in love with the song (as… https://t.co/KnOwARLmUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this humorous there's something wrong with you. 11 Confessions Of An Underachieving Parent. This… https://t.co/wMJmE7V8WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y'all don't have moms who yelled at you for chewing with your mouth closed and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why wait to show yourself the compassion you already deserve? 🌟  💖A much needed reminder from angieknightyoga.… https://t.co/brA4Tq7R64]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but she looks really tired just look at her eyes. come on baby girl you GOTTA take care of yourself. Besos! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women's International Day is now a week long ♀️👠👯‍♀️ #zontaoakville https://t.co/3lHdkQZv9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went through my moms blog last night and over 14 years she only mentioned me three times..... the most she said w… https://t.co/2vmvGRRAUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Thoughts on whether we think the weird orange babysitter will pardon him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Black Sheep Burritos &amp; Brews - @blacksheepwv in Huntington, WV https://t.co/N57wDglgzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy I was able to be there to cheer for you!! So very proud and honored.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SnowVegas it started snowing since 7:30p The Lakes! https://t.co/gFaGQ7dg5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never get tired of shutting down restaurants with you❣️ @ New York, New York https://t.co/FYUqjO8uVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikacostell You are my #WomanCrushWednesday because you inspire so many people everyday, including me to keep goi… https://t.co/B5u4I6saX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is all this talk about them switching Drew and Jason again? Please don’t play with my emotions #GH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only if DJT learns how to really pray...and walk humbly with his God. Otherwise, wishful thinking by Trump delusion… https://t.co/ezGipAmdAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Newsom tell the truth the 💰 for the train is gone. Ask Brown where it has gone? California’s underpa… https://t.co/H3iKrIHuKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warmups are underway here in Willmar!!  #BlizzShow https://t.co/fiSY2ZVtuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did @IndraNooyi become #CEO? She has no idea! An inspirational and honest morning at the 18th Annual… https://t.co/z5JQCdgk1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Oscar moments for me: -Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper singing Shallow -Regina King, thanking her momma and ‘God i… https://t.co/pEKSq35tzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I signed up for two classes at the gym starting at 6pm. There is a $15 charge if you cancel without 24hr notice. I’… https://t.co/hv2xZPbeOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caturday night... goodnight! Where’s my spot? 😻😻😻 #stevensclan #gingercats #teamginger #polydactyl #alexstevens… https://t.co/3I3en9kBIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presenting the POTUS...disgusting, shameful and bordering on pedophilia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you eat @ChipotleTweets and don’t have a guacamole mark in your shirt at the end of it, did you actually have Ch… https://t.co/9dw4fUkOQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsoJudi I don’t use my gmail account anymore! And I really don’t know why!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some hilarity. Mustache Photo bomb Contest teen program---lots of good event ideas at this library! #hilarity… https://t.co/3dLj4d5jnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to my handsome honeybadger ❤️💋  @jaycoc  #bemine #honeybadgerdontgiveashit #happyvalentinesday… https://t.co/MmNCHztR74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I like it.  It expresses how I feel these days. You can always return to current photo if we survive… https://t.co/xPynNGymXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blckriflecoffee On the balcony of my room in that hotel. #LakeLouise #Canada https://t.co/PlXQvGV3V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't watch any more... But I hold a firm belief that sunlight on faux mafiso and collusion is painful and necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally shook and speechless!! Cold in La is such a new and great sound!! Everyone go stream #ColdInLA right now!… https://t.co/h8EjUMG33d]]></document></documents></author>