<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BooksBrews I'm sorry. The correct answer is... 😉😁 https://t.co/eVrJuY4Dma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta waisted no time to get me sick. 😩. Haven’t been sick in YEARS. IM SUCH A BABY WHEN IM SICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10centBeerNite My point was he really wasn't THAT good, yet people liked him anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next person who posts on Facebook, “Please pray for our class, we got a huge test today”   I’m gonna comment “I pra… https://t.co/jmhF5P0fUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @SecPompeo united states sanctions are what has crushed venezuela. we bury them in sanctions, freeze the… https://t.co/S1laKGzD3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candle optimization. We are so progressive yet so regressive. Modern paradox.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mecall55 @JussieSmollett It will be a slap in all of our faces. Something never repairable and he will never work… https://t.co/qomRXpUgHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets I still dont, and never will understand how or why people follow and believe this arrogant, bragga… https://t.co/2N4SSACDnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The downhill approach on the tenth hole meadowcreekgolf, a short par five that’s often reachable in two. #vsga… https://t.co/p3wSN7exi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calbahrsd31  You will pay dearly for letting your filthy hatefilled insides be seen streaming out your classless m… https://t.co/jDQxnHPqT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteeIerNation This is almost as good as him going to the Bucs. But Buffalo has better weather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is hard to believe there are people in this world trying to paint this human inialation as a lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this new listing in Norwell, MA. Welcome to 4,600+ SF of wonderful! $1.095. Call/text me for a private sh… https://t.co/1EBTVnMqv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlitteredGoth Yeah right sanders, your getting as frantic and desperate as your boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5-4 Barrie final and they get all 3 stars... *sigh*.. No, damn it, I’m going rogue! Sorry Aidan Brown , you’re out.… https://t.co/4g7DktdgC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Radar Irish wbcc lounge &amp; porch in Rochester Hills, MI https://t.co/dcNj2EBUVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eeareeyein Hmm. When did you stop watching? The current season has been consistently good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:49.1°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @waltshaub.....I think you just caught Gaetz threatening a Federal witness with violence. Witness intimid… https://t.co/2ojMXqlANE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_LoveShack @pcont97 It’s definitely a fan favorite, that’s for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kazweida @realDonaldTrump Then move to Syria, why don’t start having respect for American voters. Your a sore lose… https://t.co/3630PjtApk]]></document><document><![CDATA[keeping it chill stevenspassparks  . . . . . . . . . . #snow #snowboard #snowboarding #snowboards #mountains… https://t.co/0kW6F3QEU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLAST OFF!!! What an incredible sight. What an incredible memory! Seeing this historic launch first hand is somethi… https://t.co/eOPfFbwxz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diamoneceee If you decide you want a LA Fitness membership you may want to let me know cause I’ll hook it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coin toss between Brayden Schnur and Reilly Opelka as they play for the New York Open title. https://t.co/YXRIHStR29]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget highschool with Kari she was SO lit.. we used to be cracking up all the time.. in the same class… https://t.co/GpYWgybQFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Construction Progress 🏗 #villageatlangtree #lakenorman #langtreegroup #mooresvillenc #langtree… https://t.co/dNqcjToeJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful not to drag yesterday's trash into today's beauty!  #newday #beginwithprayer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it - simple and makes sense. Employers and companies can and should do more to provide vision, set example a… https://t.co/ihqnEzIO51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxSportsRadio patiently waiting for @TheNoeShow &amp; @AndyFurmanFSR !!!!! https://t.co/59OFQ0dxjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The infrastructure is there, the demand is there. We should lift the density restrictions to better take advantage… https://t.co/s7SOeLT35W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_reymenn @GODZMusic96 Also just saw the second question, I stream it on Google Play Music, but I have sneak added… https://t.co/CKKw7jVLEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Residents of Richmond Hilo remember @NYPDnews Detective #BrianSimonsen #1010WINS https://t.co/993XkRYLsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila if he hadn’t thought that dinner, he has now.  Great play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s what Mike Pence had to say about Tim Scott, SC’s Opportunity Zone Project https://t.co/yosxkr88zD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday March 6 - POLITICO Playbook:    Democrats are enmeshed in a messy, divisive internecine food fight over s… https://t.co/YFhRL1thjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:39.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueKofi faith journey not over bro. Boom boom boom https://t.co/ctj9m9IF7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fatherless child , listen how I got this knowledge is wild. Streets taught me speak softly and watch from the crowd… https://t.co/Lf6i6JdbYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go and Tell evangelism seminar is an easy way to equip you to share the gospel. Go and Tell is free online at… https://t.co/EszPwtNPer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Hollywood does it too. They are called seat savers...except @TheDemocrats in Hollywood don't pay them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the bestest mom ever. She made @jbellecake waynehead088 @brooklyn12209 (2 missing) into some fine… https://t.co/ecqNLTbz6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, pretty much everyone’s over the ❄️. @ Bend, Oregon https://t.co/KI3qiGqow7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baileyangle don’t know if you knew but preseason games while not competitive are cheap on stub hub. I got two tick… https://t.co/opoTe048wN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ALL CAPS? OK! YOU ARE A FRAUD! ILLEGITIMATE PRESIDENT! FAKE BILLIONAIRE! THIN SKINNED! SORE LOSER!… https://t.co/ROT0gwk4w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fritchee @DragonCalf @peterdaou It's there in black and white. Republicans are notorious in sticking crap into bil… https://t.co/4KOABtyDuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter GET EVERYONE+Food/Drinks &amp; watch the G.O.A.T. Movie Trivia match YOU'LL EVER SEE! The #Schmoedown… https://t.co/GCPQdcdiy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chase Jeter took it easy during Friday’s practice but went through shootaround today and will play tonight w bruise… https://t.co/pOQQ5SvqhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TadhgBranagan17 @TheDavidGaul @ITB_SMCO @TUDublin_BN It'd take me a lot longer lol 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash At least he’s not going there to have sex with teenage girls on taxpayer dollars being from NJ feel he… https://t.co/HqntBoDjSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuing with Writer’s Zone #swjxn @InnovateMS  #startupWeekend #startup #tech #work #learn #grow #share… https://t.co/HX56nTeUcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Party 🎉 Tonight @thesapphirelv treasuresvegas @hustlervegas therhinolv with Me 2/3 @Letzgitit at #stripclub N… https://t.co/9JhFh6wGLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what they’re suggesting is that some pilots are smart enough to fly a 737 but aren’t smart enough to fly the Max… https://t.co/HpEbvsjKyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toffleresque I thought they kept their membership private? That was the whole reason they stuck out and got ridicu… https://t.co/QSVTAy6nbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ginning up his unregulated militia for civil war against truth tellers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDLehman3 You funny!   Gallows humor my man!  With Flacco and a couple of stud o-linemen, the Rocky Mountain footb… https://t.co/9e7b3bos17]]></document><document><![CDATA[North shore v. Duncanville for a state title in basketball?!? Duncanville wins on a half court buzzer beater?… https://t.co/YltWBXoenM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiskyLiberal This is not the @NCGOP first rodeo, we need to keep digging deep, there’s more to this story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Islandswamp Like WTF? And sorry for long rant, I'm with you in it pissing me off. It's arrogant, prideful, and tox… https://t.co/HKovmOp826]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity The worst part of the “green deal” is all the people who actually believe that 💩 would work...not only… https://t.co/zJ7n1FeOtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yancy’s fresh fruit tarte, the crust is amazing you can cut into with plastic spoon limited time at West… https://t.co/YzJFF6Vl6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeathMayes @SuperWinterGirl @lokicaps @NicolaScottArt What did you not like about it? Did you not like the Ultron character?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was uber fun. Don't care what the critics say that was a damn fun movie.   Also that #StanLee cameo. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dicklund1 Because you can never have enough guys who will see eye to eye with Rocco Grimaldi.  #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpLiesMatter #TrumpRussiaConspiracy h/t @KatyTurNBC  this doesn't read like a joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its true....almost separated from my woman...she threatened to kill me and anyone I dated. I stuck with her for lif… https://t.co/KgjKLYAsZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Where is the republican senate still cowering from the want to be dictator?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum He was rude and non compliant in the opening with mr Jordan, he's a racist who hates white people… https://t.co/ACy407t4Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlatinumCat @DonaldJTrumpJr California is the perfect example of the stupidity of the Left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello educators:  John Maxwell once said, “Nobody cares how much you know, until they know how much you care...”… https://t.co/bTXxLzvni9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/QAlD7JTQ0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drknstormynite @JacobAWohl @ali Terminal Stupidity 2: Electric Boogaloo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another clue for the #SEO celebs to help with the counter troll offensive https://t.co/bjllVoFc3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Zoom Info and a pending Forbes profile... @ New York, New York https://t.co/3999eCiXZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHAUFFAGE. Andrew Scheer vient de promettre (je sais avec la CAQ on n'y croit plus) que s'il est élu en octobre, il… https://t.co/aUTw0xNRx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me walking into my boss’s office: Alright man just get it over with I know I’m fired, you fucking hate me and yes I… https://t.co/TT0QZ7uK0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alivia Hamric picks up 4th foul for @CFBlackTigers. Mika Dalton 2 FTs. @auroraathletics up 76-30. #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how you don’t see an issue with LeBron’s comments about the team when the team hasn’t been his priority all season long. C’mon now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Libralady13 Bernie can bugger off. Same as Trump, but on the other side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring practice starts March 19 and my spring primer series rolls on with a breakdown of Troy’s offense.  https://t.co/K5knmsGYZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't get why people complain about the #AmbertAlert so much? A little girl died. Her mom won't sleep peacefully… https://t.co/lvQ3ub3pz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@equitymatters77 @cspanwj @alaynatreene @axios @JonathanTamari @PhillyInquirer Good point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even remember the last time that I’ve had such horrible like the one that I had today]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you call a combination of lack of sleep, early onset dementia, willfull ignorance, narcissistic personality… https://t.co/yFOjZNnKuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREP BASEBALL: County Line 10, Hackett 2, FINAL  Pacyn Reames WP; Indians are off and rolling @ClhsIndians]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope James sniffed his fingers after sticking his hand in that haunted silent hill toilet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbombard2 @rudykyle @3BidLeaguePod Haha they have a lot of work to do in my own opinion but good luck to your team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gilead scores key HIV data as Descovy proves non-inferior to Truvada https://t.co/NEChGILpDR via @BioPharmaDive]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've taken my phone out of silent for the first time in about 10 years, that's how you know something isn't right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iBleedPhilly @RealMamaEagle @cj_wentz @DeSeanJackson11 This website is just too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Mayer - I Guess I Just Feel Like (Lyric Video) https://t.co/9edwz1Yqvb via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninepintcoggie Yes. He did what he did with his life. He lived, died, rose. It happened and continues to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great morning @COJOFlatbush Breakfast honoring @NYPDONeill  with commissioner Ganley @NYPDDCA , Councilman Deutsch… https://t.co/HUQZolCHgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteelSeries has there been a permanent fix for the adhesive problem on the Rival 650? I’ve seen a lot of comments… https://t.co/1fvMZsdKn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening @RyanBretonWX temp in Topsham 36 raining total rain of .44" we picked up 1" of snow and have had a wind gust of 19 mph.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisconradi Colleague pointed out - “given the color scheme, isn’t putting Google on the side a bit redundant?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigh (@ Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/NXDxNqAopm]]></document><document><![CDATA[other day just a li warm up for deadlift 🥶 #225lbs https://t.co/EvBotcmlO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to last summer and what miiiiight be my single favorite photo of all time:  Charlotte's reaction when we told… https://t.co/2gy0EOl0A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the madness of yesterday's @PaniniAmerica Doninion and Select hitting, I neglected to share that the new… https://t.co/r4KQ46T0h0]]></document></documents></author>