<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[two weeks came on while I was driving and wow I miss @shannnyhanson so much I could cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great photos and reporting by @TheAspenTimes reporter @SCondonATimes on the "landscape changing" mile-wide avalanch… https://t.co/tLRtSyrnLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellybell__9 It depends on homework and if I get my packing done. My apartment is a mess an I have to deep clean it before Tuesday.😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the Cortez and Omar going to say it was not bribe money as well and the fact Obama had more @DHSgov than a… https://t.co/QfLW3LGIF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you work with your pet? Happy #loveyourpetday from Dania Micala Group in #DTLA https://t.co/dmAJfdgQUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddyMayer32 All these festivals that were cheap are tryna go for $100 and up now smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I want a stuffed fried avocado... but like I don’t want it fried”  -Britt]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - Save UK's 'dwindling' language skills, say MPs and peers https://t.co/DfBN2fFOEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[FANTASTIC performance by Jeremy Woolstenhulme and the Hyde Park Middle School Orchestra! Great energy! #Rigor… https://t.co/js8tJQi3nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault Chasing dreams, where someone or something is chasing me and no matter how far ahead I get or how c… https://t.co/8koUAjuCV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went from having a regular cold/ sinus infection to almost not having a voice at all for no reason ... SICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy super VIP tickets for Firefly or pay off a credit card? https://t.co/MmKdFrBuHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOLLOW NOW 👣 🗣@24kmixtapes  DM FOR PROMO!!! Or email 24kmixtapes@gmail.com  24K Mixtapes Services: - Spotify Playli… https://t.co/uVM2dK5yFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju @SunlenSerfaty Yeah right. @MarkMeadows is one of the original birthers so no racism there. Such bullshit. He’s racist AF!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a minute or 17 years since I’ve gotten mail from them 😮 #firstjoboutofcollege #englishdegreemeanssecretary https://t.co/EGOOSCuJ1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 How about we start with making Amazon and other uber wealthy companies JUST like it, pay some taxes?… https://t.co/WmUISJx3ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze You have enough EYE problems becareful you don't stick that pencil in your good eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchMeRawr i think it was andy's account but not 100% sure - i still followed all of the accounts but andy hadnt… https://t.co/HxKpkdGbYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSLisson @TheEllenShow @LisaSLisson you inspire every day!  And you always ride in style! See you @TheEllenShow #bekindtooneanother]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finplan I think this is also one of the reasons why young women are not pursuing careers in financial planning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam_253 I kinda wanna follow this tweet bc I just moved to the area and wanna know all the fun stuff to do 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now my heart awakes to the sound of silence and it beats to the sound of silence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all not rey flood my timeline hollering about PUSSY &amp; MIMOSA’S when yall shit more like Catfish &amp; Can Sodas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blackwatch IPA by Vermont Pub &amp; Brewery @ Vermont Pub &amp; Brewery — https://t.co/2h7sMTQZGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowToGetAwayABC #HTGAWM why Gabriel lying to his mama bout spending time with Michaela! Bonnie takes her prego tes… https://t.co/vxlXceJnOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[💍💍#WhereFashionMeets5DollarJewlery🔥🔥 🔥🔥#ThisDivaIsOnFire🔥🔥 #PaparazziAccessories 🔥🔥📿📿#PreOrdained🔥🔥… https://t.co/2r5P0KZAvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@banannerbread They own it because nobody else wants to; the best residents are temporary for a building like that… https://t.co/9UvfIa7S4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatWokeAuntie @InBrokenCountry @RobElgasABC7 @ABC 1/2 They’ll just arrest him.   They have plenty of probable cau… https://t.co/8JEnJUERze]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/L7cbQTyqlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarahA30 You’re pregnant? Well that certainly makes sense! Congratulations!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of shitty toys i hate-watch videos for  If there was any doubt that poopsie was designed by fetish furry a… https://t.co/49sJCIhzYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scv74980610 @snackystacky @SethAbramson From what I’ve read from lawyers, he should resign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on 3 hours of sleep is going to SUCK tonight #sendhelp #sendcoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishsumerlin I don't trust anything uber biased Andrea Mitchell or CNNs Jake Tapper report. They don't even try t… https://t.co/peOirczvQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proxénétisme: quand le recruteur peut être votre voisin #JDQ #villequebec @QubRadio https://t.co/oOkxMZj98K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. My Lord. I got to the first section was so embarrassed i just had to turn away. My Eyes! My Eyes! #yikes… https://t.co/Cv0LxH5HYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once that demon gets you. It is hard for it to loosing it's grip on you. Get better soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE—The Wake County Sheriff’s Office is confirming Stephen Denning, 60, accused of shooting 2 Walgreens employee… https://t.co/QTWDzQz4eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanaRagsdale @Twitter I consider it time well spent.  When I advise my husband what was said on #Twitter and who… https://t.co/yQQPLRhwr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is by far my first relationship where some one actually and truly loves me to the core 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronhuertas Thanks for sharing, @aaronhuertas   Arizona can be the 38th and final state to ratify the… https://t.co/0S7u0R5eNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patta47cake @samstein @mschlapp Suspect. That was really a dumb thing to tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro @vladimirpadrino Ustedes son una verdadera vergüenza para el estado de Venezuela 🇻🇪 ojalá y trump les corté las alas pronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[my skin is dry all the heckin time and I’m getting frequent nosebleeds and 45 degrees feels like -20 to me AND MY B… https://t.co/yHeWwIJSZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Sha Sha! Still churning out dem crafty club killerz to this day. -  @Swedger_ YESSSSSS😍🏁🏁🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenkimball @HRchupp Hats off to you (MN Insider phrase). Raised in Chicago. Found my way here after grad scho… https://t.co/08a1zKJHcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCrawford247 @nikproffitt Actually not a Marty Smith fan. A Marty Smith co-worker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i slept through all 5 of my alarms for 2 hours straight and missed by bus for skiing... WHY DOES MY WEEK SUCK SO BAD UGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What?   This is so wrong @CathULaw My communication law professor Irwin I bet would be furious about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get free trial off your first order at Curology https://t.co/DwjXA8cNWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys. I got to thank and talk to my tiny, badass Governor today. Maybe one of my favorite parts of today, and today… https://t.co/Q7fBWDnT8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t forget to water your own plant today and get some water and sun ☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieStith @Corderoknows Kids had to sit and think of someone to say to respond to that ridiculous question. You… https://t.co/aBOJsSmfvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oma81307 @voicefanatic36 @Cabecki68 @psiangelic @SmallcageGG @HandyRed @deedawson66 @automotor16 @Khristel54… https://t.co/UYUdFch3mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Augura @LantagneS Bon a rien pour ces appels, ils changent de numéros continuellement les numéros n'existent  même pas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than Nitro Sweet Josie to keep warm.  Well, maybe this awesome cap. #alesforoutlaws @ Lonerider https://t.co/ph0AQvWQLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just paid my credit card off so hopefully my credit goes up. Plus I got one more payment for my loan before that’s paid off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ HAPPY VALENTINES DAY ♥️ WILL YOU BE MINE - Poor King has now been… https://t.co/hYKt0J8eL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA That’s stupid why pretend to care when you would just as soon butcher them]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday to when Ms. Lily had LOTS of style! 😂🙌  #MyGymTucson #MyGymFun #LearnPlayGrowAndBeHappy… https://t.co/p9ggBhpYR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyraej1979 @DonnieWahlberg You are amazing and so handsome and talented.   @JennyMcCarthy is the luckiest woman… https://t.co/WbDpDbc03n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know most of you haven’t donated to my @RileyChildrens Dance Marathon page, but...  https://t.co/A4jCd1niRp https://t.co/mLTUmtWpwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iaminfamous @Clover1292 @BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump You know now. Sometimes it takes 1 person to stand up. L… https://t.co/wx9atOiZFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentRK @IMFmyeloma @BrianDurieMD @mtmdphd @NorthTxMSG @MyelomaTeacher My verteboplasties were literally a lifes… https://t.co/uHKAXofUCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what time I fell asleep but I feel like I done slept 8hrs already 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fdbedout @NetflixLAT Como esto es negocio, van a poner brasileños y mexicanos. Los extras serán colombianos. No se hagan ilusiones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carloshsiso @HLaverdiereNPD #NotYourRA here is one freebie https://t.co/DMAIod7QF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattFinnFNC I’m so glad the @Chicago_Police are being diligent on this one and not backing down or letting his “ce… https://t.co/FX5p5J0MJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Carol Stream: light rain, 34°F 86% humidity, wind 21mph, pressure 1016mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[...happiness is a #supermuch Sunday brunch talking #allthethings w @peerlessgreen @CateTolnai and #BabyRachel… https://t.co/gHJZzaPICr]]></document><document><![CDATA[24* Mamaaaaaa donde están mis pósters de POR TI!!! https://t.co/82LhdHp5uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[And don’t forget that bonus revenue you get for all the meetings at Mar-a-Lago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a blessed day everyone @ The Auditorium at The Douglass https://t.co/e5a31dZqbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi my name is Joshua Marc Vincent I work for the Us government I want to tell u about my life I’m a cia agent I spy… https://t.co/zkFxF9dPd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Korean-Canadian seniors need your help now! - sign the petition today! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/neSEYVf4vf via @CdnChange]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look just like my mom so everytime I say I wish I looked like someone else I feel bad because my mom is so pretty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheyAreWeAlso @qanon691 @ChristineWagam6 @SebGorka @charliekirk11 @TPUSA Honey he’s a bot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayomariuhh Seriously 😒. The whole time I kept pausing it and saying to myself wtf wtf !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJ_Baumann No I don’t actually care. I was just setting you up for that response.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How RUDE of my professors to not schedule our midterm exams around Colton jumping the fence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water spilled under laptop. Won’t turn on. Will be writhing in desperation for next 24-48 hours to see if drying he… https://t.co/9JgyNOEfbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemWrite Ivanka is a conduit between trump and Kushner.  She's involved in everything.  Trump knows she will be th… https://t.co/DKxVDECjVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLehmann @ppobroker @brithume I think it was about women-owned businesses, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RenCarothers @MattCTVG Oh Ren..... feel better mama, could’ve been worse, yikes 😳 you were lucky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActorKavanagh @grahammctavish @BadHusky1 @Outlander_STARZ @OutlanderOnline @WetaWorkshop @BrophyJed… https://t.co/Ws1E99vAYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amylourose @FakeMikeMiseph @CaliforniaGram @OhNoSheTwitnt Yo kids, I’m commenting on our healthcare system and tha… https://t.co/bMTEipl6IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ that my HS alma mater not only allows its students into all its regular season games for free but is now payin… https://t.co/CyF1omkWcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Wow. I was in the army for 7 years and never that brave.....or idiotic...not sure which. One thing… https://t.co/HpnKsDYuXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uprise49 @Austin_Police I've been seeing signage from the city calling it that this year, for some reason. At leas… https://t.co/fwxRESqbxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKuhnerReport @POTUS That should not have been in the bill. I hope President Trump will be able to take care of that somehow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesmiglehart @freestylelove @WayneBrady @Lin_Manuel James, Why Up So Early...????  Are You A Card-Carrying Membe… https://t.co/VILJk5M4sS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another piece of my childhood gone.  PS @EW he was a huge part of Days Of Our Lives too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlottefitzny @EmiliaArlotta Oh god you’re not alone there 😭 I need to be in a bikini somewhere STAT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow my sister is awesome! Look what she has researched and created! Congrats @theatrevicki 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@93XRT while my guitar gently weeps, got my mind set on you, love this song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazarLaw I defaulted to variants.  Tracy Morgan and Ice-T (T is for Tracy). They could both defeat me with little… https://t.co/6vcruimwlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can never find parking at COD and it really makes me not wanna go to class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill @shanedawson That’s why I love @shanedawson. some of my favorite people are cancers! Most of them actually]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting that none of the republicans are asking about Trump. Not one question about Trump on that side. #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joycemillman He’s totally letting out his inner diva. He looked fabulous.]]></document></documents></author>