<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann Because its working so well for Communist China...  The fastest way to kill a nation is to stop having children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sagesteele @StephenCurry30 Yes he will. You have to love him. He a ball player, a dad, a husband, “a girlfriend, “… https://t.co/kxUqvDGqdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ideal match is someone who just paints all day and gives me each finished piece like it’s a gift]]></document><document><![CDATA[this trader joe's is across the street from equinox https://t.co/w1NBl6834w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k1d2 Although I rarely saw my uncle, I always knew that I could find him in New Mexico if I wanted to.  Makes me w… https://t.co/wZYcQ0eHPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bz4Christ Thank you so much...yes all is well on my end. Your prayers has been answered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that sometimes I wake up only 10 min before my alarm so i’m too scared to go back to sleeep 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich She is opening eyes. Hope people are smart enough to listen and see her danger]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a leader it’s important to take the time to pause and learn - excited to spend today to learn about the successe… https://t.co/4AVHUWvhne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keith Richards would be a good choice for this position.  You usually choose someone who is the an… https://t.co/RSF6vRfVAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I want to grow my hair down almost to my waist again and some days I want to chop it up to my chin like w… https://t.co/WV3aqsJMVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toland_sam Mine would never believe it. One of mine (the biggest character in the family) looks just like your sleeping beauty here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Beer, Bourbon &amp; Bacon Festival is so much fun!!! @ Atlantic Station https://t.co/5g62od2ghQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Fifth Grade PBL project is taking off...”Oh the Places You’ll Go” Colleges have started sending stuff and they… https://t.co/jEqMQpQq7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole Homeroom wanted to pledge $3 each.... so.... then my whole Homeroom could ALSO listen to iPods..... EHHHHH… https://t.co/YBYp755UZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to take a minute and show everyone how smoking hot my baby momma is. 🤤 https://t.co/A4bxg1eG2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please Help #SaveEndangeredWhales from Being SLAUGHTERED by the #Icelandic Government!!  https://t.co/Hi3pd328jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back now, I realize I was close to not really being able to secure up my future.   https://t.co/hy4NyG66G1]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Just Friends (feat. Phem) by @G_Eazy on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/8eywfwRzHO  we’ll either be in love or we’ll b… https://t.co/lR2AVLtDS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is everything for #BlackHistoryMonth &amp; all year long. Brava, @nhannahjones !]]></document><document><![CDATA[too bad I subscribe to the domain-general theory of brain architecture, otherwise I'd lobotomize all my romantic desires]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day is tomorrow, but we were just so excited a blessed beyond belief to share our growing love with you… https://t.co/1twhfxcRdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotsFyre @ajenable @MrAndyNgo Because being a victim gets you political power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNgolf So no-one stopped to think this was inappropriate and downright awful?? Editor? Asst. Editor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Share:  Found this DVD  and recently began practicing  "Simply YOGA" Yolanda Pettinto That's what I'm giving myse… https://t.co/nTvYu0jpww]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're waiting for your co workers slow asses for post shift drinks so, I started w/o them with some… https://t.co/ASIjAus4Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sana kasi nagTagalog ka na lang. Ay, wait. Di nga pala ikaw gumawa non. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went from zero co pay with Obama to $31 three times a week with Trump. And that doesnt include specialist we see about 3 times a month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grounder761 @Seamustoo @TheRyanSupreme @pokerpami71 @Andrea_S76 @odd_bat @rae_lila @jlparizeau @AmyInJetsLand… https://t.co/BSB9kMdeED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebasAHerrera @evanasmith Interesting! So is the Whole Foods going into Plaza Saltillo going to be just a regular Whole Foods?]]></document><document><![CDATA[She cheer me on pom poms She good for the soul, she good for the mind She help me get found, TomTom She help me eat… https://t.co/AguOwClVek]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you passionate about?  ~ ¿Qué te apasiona?   #SpiritualAwakening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMPDogs What type of Shepherd dog is she?  Absolutely stunning.  How old is she?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still reeling that I’ve been working 3 jobs since 2016 and my dad tried to lecture me about “a thing called work”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this on https://t.co/QAgZGmzacI with the link to our local affiliate WFLA. What happened to editors?! @ Palm… https://t.co/z4mREZeV9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[my twin flame, @_chanelgrace. visually, we’re the best opposites. spiritually, our souls are the same. i love you f… https://t.co/iqIWt6atsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah we know, the roads are slick and it's cold outside but we have you covered. @KRLDWeatherDan  has the latest on… https://t.co/scH7eUjQyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneGodOneJihyo @missmayn You’re entitled to your opinion of course but nothing in his record suggests he’ll have a… https://t.co/EUBB2BuGie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippeCorbe Of course she aligns herself with the world’s most hated and corrupt, she was sired by the third stooge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i discovered this song thanks to my coworker + now it’s my fav one of this month lol https://t.co/yfYYeoxF8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[For St Patrick’s Day can some football media account ask everyone who have been biggest snakes in football?  I’d pr… https://t.co/T1nEdTdoVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a joy learning from each other! #thisisheartwork @burgess_shelley @jodi_mahoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son las casi 3 de la mañana y este canción me llego muchísimo. https://t.co/JAAlvRlYzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically all my friends have the hots for either my dad or my brother. Or both. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing gay is the nigga asking. Interaction between a male and female is not gay it’s sexual exploration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could just sleep around like before. Now I gotta know a person 🙄🙄 I didn't sign up for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningJournal Glad Hardy took back about rehiring teachers!! He is a piece of work!! There are good and bad stude… https://t.co/tuIWmyad87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam Man I was with Bernie Sanders until I seen this b******* he's dodging damn questions No black Agenda no vote for me sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocket came to snuggle on the couch with the patient. Poor thing. Temp got up to 103+. Administering meds now.… https://t.co/cMrLI6UZV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember his work, how much of a shining star he was, and please don't dwell on the tragedies that overtook him. Th… https://t.co/Jelo0zM9br]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MXYZ_ @cnalive @matthewschmitz "Melbourne, Australia, Feb 25, 2019 / 06:21 pm (CNA).- Prosecutors have abandoned a… https://t.co/hsaDH74Ksp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBuxtonBooks @DanielDydek I’ve made Turkish Delight (for a Narnia themed birthday party). I think it’s good, but i… https://t.co/BLE9jn4Lmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump DEFY the damn Judge. YOU are the President and a damn FEDERAL JUDGE can not over RULE YOU. IS Just… https://t.co/JmsaLRIBWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my old residents just got hired as an RA and I’ve never been more proud ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I have a lot of Jewish friends who were raised the same way.  They are awesome people!  I however was ra… https://t.co/wopFln2JRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @TuckerCarlson @JennyCraig @SamsungUS @Bayer They've all taken leave of their senses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BgBengals2019 Mr Bengal contestants —your BABY pictures must be sent to Bengal Buzz by Friday 2/22 also senior pic… https://t.co/EHJb5WqCbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton FFS, she is more than entitled to her opinions.  So she feels about 45 like most of the country.  B… https://t.co/qUPAkRbnuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t hang with people who hate oatmeal raisin cookies (Sorry @BizNasty2point0)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pittsburghbuz @robertdunlap947 @MissILmom @kaci150 @Serremmy @ChrisBragdon @Lnr57 @Briteeye777 @LionelMedia… https://t.co/sL9lvsUSgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @IvankaTrump So, @IvankaTrump please, explain how a rich, spoiled child of a rich, spoiled criminal, w… https://t.co/7EZCHFOTCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[and today, i wear another shade of i slept like shit so don’t piss me off]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family loves my boyfriend so much I remember them telling me if we ever broke up they would still invite him over 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u take your dog out three times and he still gives u the sharp exhale/sign. What am I doing wrong? Is this what motherhood is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez never looked better  she always get the red carpet right #Oscar2019 #theculturekeeper #JenniferLopez]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to start having kids or something bcuz I always owe taxes. Even if it’s a small amount I still owe money 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[With @jaxaman1 Fernando and Janell. #3N118 went to #4N118 tonight! @SanAntonioFC @MissionCity_118 https://t.co/dfJY6mBD1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I have rough starts to my morning. It throws everything off for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course Chris Harrison has multiple phones #TheBachelor https://t.co/8f0FAahSJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from office  https://t.co/heaUGcguhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Merseyside Derby is on Sunday! Can’t wait! 🔴 #LFC https://t.co/lH5EPCvCt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How bout a NY show added to the list this summer....!your not boycotting us my friend are you,#cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzieBURR_ yes ma’am. Me and my homie sliding. S/o to the payment plan 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino And they don’t care. Look at Chuck Todd if you can stand it for 5 minutes. You will get nausea]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s great Debbie but, that should have been the law ages ago. We have a problem in that we don’t have any laws p… https://t.co/FGz9bTgQ7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should not be surprised that an episode of @nbcsnl hosted by @mulaney contained so many sketch gems, but “Bodega… https://t.co/PXSpFfRwWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third stop on the Pay it Forward Tour: Jackson, MS! #springbreak #pift #capitol @ Jackson, Mississippi https://t.co/TCdaySQx45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Doesn't this sound like u and ur father? Except in your case,the lies have been going on for years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marked her head with tape...just like everything else for moving day! @ Broken Arrow, Oklahoma https://t.co/hL6gtJqTPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peek-a-boo Moon  . . . #peekaboo #peekaboomoon #astoriany #queens #nycphotographer  #justwalkingaroundthecity… https://t.co/HBxi04ee4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@67jewelCDH @ladyinlksd We need to reach as far as we can see!  GOP has been relentless in the past and now it is t… https://t.co/kiB4uwzjQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must want to be different before you can change yourself.   #nofilter #army #changeiscoming #newme #love #life… https://t.co/g4cQJQs6aS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recycle the beer bottles trophy style. When someone wins, whip this out! Lol. Need to keep... #comedy #chuckle… https://t.co/PoIP4IpYOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewSantoro You're going to love it if you haven't read it already! Happy reading!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to the grind! 💙⚾️ #GoBigBlue @ Bud Bender Park https://t.co/t3rh2B3msr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just got an iPhone. To give you an idea of how insane this is, here is a glimpse into how the set-up process… https://t.co/PtQONJTU0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but seriously it’s embarrassing how obsessed I am with this Kardashian drama]]></document><document><![CDATA[the saddest thing about betrayal it never comes from your enemies. it comes from the people that mean the most to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFA_Rocket @AstrosAngel10 @HouAstroholic I thank men who open doors for me. It’s polite! I wouldn’t say that in da… https://t.co/JX6yDT6ndb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC No chance lady robot..... he is the subject because he is destroying the America you so claim to love...shut u… https://t.co/mjdqqWpcWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So period cramps feel the same as contractions (except like 700x less intense) so does that mean my vag dialates to… https://t.co/HTpASY59jM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Dear Jesus, I ask that you please be w/our friend Terrence.  Grant that his body will heal, neck, back,… https://t.co/Bu5OBFrJVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earthquake M3.9 - OFFSHORE NORTHERN CALIFORNIA (USA) - Sat, 2 Mar 2019 05:55:56 UTC (00:55 EST) - 1 hour ago more i… https://t.co/1PA50mNjUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SemaCiel0101 @loveGoldenHeart @helensmomma @ZoieFanAnna2 @gottogetoutof @coop_chaetolae @Lizwiz275 @Vaeltaja5… https://t.co/OrmznIb4Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[And no I don't have to take up the reasons why either the fact of hardness of heart has been well understood and no… https://t.co/XnRrl3MAFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet @realDonaldTrump hired him as his personal attorney who worked for him for over 10yrs...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I  fired my kicker for poor performance, I am not sure I would replace him with a guy named "Blewitt". But that's just me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pinche_Pi Sarah from Alaska? What services is she offering her? Pedicures maybe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @senatemajldr The country deserve this new bill with the wall funding to be read before being voted on.… https://t.co/jwPw3Dop3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[me when my husband’s/then-boyfriend’s roommate stole my packed lunch from the fridge and took it up to his room but… https://t.co/weP2RWMpt9]]></document></documents></author>