<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[dierksbentley   #DierksBentley #DrunkonAPlane #BurningMan #UpOnTheRidge #SomewhereOnABeach #BurningManTour… https://t.co/KNpeUP0PvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JunDishes If I lost half an ass, I'd still have more ass than most people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[$27 is a pretty good price to pay for some financial education on the stock market...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe  hey joe how much money did you take from aipac??  Bet it was tons. You disgust me. Keep shilling for Israel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There used to be another style of track that has been gone away from. It used to be superspeedways, intermediate, s… https://t.co/YrYBRJShCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeNotes2323 @PlayBoiPatt I’m not taking this as an insult. That guy is actually funny lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/wt8wwYyAWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hardball The RW Show must go on only bc ppl have closed minds to the Dreams of others- Sounds pretty Selfish to me… https://t.co/WLyQSRc8RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimdunaway @JOXRoundtable @TheLanceTaylor any idea of what Johnny Football did to have his contract terminated in CFL ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajrowe98 Takes a sick person to claim that someone was lying about their treatment]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Disagreements in relationships do not get solved, they just get managed. Once you decide that convincing your part… https://t.co/IB7R2bRnAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spectator @afneil Who would believe that @brendononeal24 is funded by the Brexit loving and Climate change denying… https://t.co/FIJaEC7wqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptnJackass_YT We don’t have to shoot 3s, when you go 0-10 you can move the ball and create a good mid range look or drive to the basket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevilsA40599657 @rand0m @renato_mariotti @realDonaldTrump And his declarations of national emergency’s did very li… https://t.co/GV0mCTQzON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop it cus yes I saw may moon of shinning bright tonight y'all I didn't want to go n do all for brother Joshua tho… https://t.co/J94tuAgAnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryJordan_KTT @amsupdates Ironically, both penalties were assessed for the exact same speed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving back the unused money would be the right thing to do. That’s why it will never happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Views on this beautifulday #FortLauderdale #fortlauderdalebeach #ftlbch #ft #beachlife #views #rp #rwtweet #sfs #f4f https://t.co/mukLSkJ74y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrainwreckJerry @GlenCasada @brotherjones_ @joelebert29 @natalie_allison @Tennessean ... advancement of those ends… https://t.co/FLfUHqIMAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brooooo I can’t wait until My Hero Academia season 4 come out! I’m so hyped 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaterboysORG @Eagles @JOEL9ONE @Beau_Allen @JasonKelce @Haloti_Ngata92 Just did the climb last week.  Altitude is… https://t.co/d1Cu3jFin8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quito_caretas Su fuerza y su salto impresionan para ser un freshman y es un top 5 prospect de seguro pero a su jue… https://t.co/gY9SBcA5Hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSterkel Congratulations!  Exciting news that God has blessed you !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarySmed @1776Stonewall @borntoraisehogs @BreitbartNews That’s what Paul Manafort said. So did Flynn. Didn’t work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donT_mESSAround Definitely expected more from the ending. I kinda wanted a bit more drama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattkusek @Tim_Heinis @Jason1Goff @SarahSpain Exactly in my money clip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember the lives taken one year ago. Never forget #MarchForOurLives @davidhogg111 @Emma4Change @ALactivist57]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Trudy Farnell and Chris Bradshaw @SSS_Spartans Crystal Apple and Perfect Attendance winners this mo… https://t.co/SySH6PvMcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sickest southpaw in the land.  Wouldn’t worry about any shoulder issues, according to the @bostonherald Red Sox… https://t.co/drbdSSZVI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HotChoc1217 I'll never understand why people just can't LET GO of a relationship and find happiness why someone else! SMDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came across this the other day when I was  cleaning out my closet... Been at it since I could hold a crayon 🖍 😜💪🏾… https://t.co/0aYFdoTlG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chawks_92 Say it with me. I will not believe the hype. I will not believe the hype. I will not believe the hype.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AAFHotshots, will that full Granite Mountain Hotshots video played at Halftime be available online? I'd love t… https://t.co/46IQ8rMe7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[like why am i so mad? my mind is going at like a million miles an hour and i can’t focus what is happening to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/qrKEKZF72Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[*uses chopsticks for the first time and immediately turns myself into a walrus*  @CassieKay27 staring at me from ac… https://t.co/X3L6llJ9ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Elitehairtrapper #menshair #menhairstyles #mobileal #menshairstyles #barbers #kidcuts #mensfashion #hairmodel… https://t.co/rCig6NVVwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine your parents having 150,000 just laying around for you to ask for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chad Ryan served as coach, mentor, driver, counselor, prankster, and friend. Wore all the hats well.   Good job, Co… https://t.co/NO8ZvS6fOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zachattack_zrs People on a shortlist for keeping their jobs.  Luke Walton @Zachattack_zrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[1110-1142 La Cienega Blvd 1110-1142 La Cienega Blvd, West Hollywood, CA 90069 https://t.co/dcpQxxLJXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albroost What are you disagreeing with because it sounds like your agreeing. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloMegLou @Oneiorosgrip @anlrBrad @JustLaurenB @sasha_author @mycoolbagel @Sydney_Sceptics @roguesquadkat They hap… https://t.co/3coJXbSAJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure she could wouldn’t have to work another day in her life if she chose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megan Smith singles and brings in two runs to give the Lady Panthers a 5-4 lead in the 4th. 🥎]]></document><document><![CDATA[184, round of 32, @NJCAAWrestling : Marcus Placide (Iowa Lakes) pinned Alex Kauffman, 6:44 @NEONorsemen @CoachP_NEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 23rd St Metro Station - @metrolosangeles in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/OmxhKTCjSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBuble nice playing football with you yesterday. I think our team could win a few games! Great show btw! Almost as tight as my spiral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8lyse You start wearing a different jacket every day to class as well. You’ll both stand out and one day walk up t… https://t.co/VshmNVB8UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ramblewood1304 @JimCarrey Jim Carrey's career  is still very active, his career isn't over. It may be to you, but… https://t.co/95JCl7CX4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hopsecutioner by @TerrapinBeerCo at @aviatormke — https://t.co/P7DHV53Ts0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imperiaband  this is such a limited edition and I know I am one the few people that have it,   besides the band th… https://t.co/xWtwQRHmVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keyboard warriors are best at creating a controversy that was never there. Literally no prominent  conservative was… https://t.co/rWOR7dHnjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUfan107 @wrestlingnomad Possibly Phillippi as the 4 and DeSanto the 5,  not much difference between a 4 and a 5 seed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenmulvaney @grantr44 @JeffFrancoeur You are the one that discussed it. He shared an opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx QUE SE LO CREA SU CHINGADA MADRE. Y TODO EL SAQUEO A SU  ESTADO DONDE LO TIENE? DE DONDE ESTA OBTE… https://t.co/LorxP2qD0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finessekidDev @JordanEmeterio It’s the math teacher tho.... Never been called a lockdown defender.... get tf outta… https://t.co/skmC7TX4ZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodilyn96789228 @rlmtaiji @ExProducer1 @Shelley19581958 @MRollins83 @Samuel26230516 @shoe4842 @melshy09… https://t.co/YaD2ikoXDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially going to my 13th #Brickyard400 @IMS alongside @gwells_24, hoping it goes better than last year’s was unt… https://t.co/PYUyy52Lqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewisrevilla and me back when we would try and make some YouTube videos lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:58.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilysears @BumpinFresh @terrycrews U know this is Twitter right? Do u actually know the man?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Dwyer Still miss long gone friends. Where’s Jay Leggett when you need him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ZION has to come back!!!! IF we do beat them I don’t want to hear the excuses.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m3lixir It is reassuring (in a way) to know that my lectures are not at the top of your most horribly taught list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTFern @Enes_Kanter @Dame_Lillard #inclusiveleadership cc @TRILLBLAZIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left. #DST (@ MTA Subway - 34th St/Herald Sq (B/D/F/M/N/Q/R/W) - @nyctsubway in New York, NY) https://t.co/JCM0VtHFV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[370LBS/168kg 3x4 80% 1RM. Felt really good so you know I had to record this set. Next week will be the deload week… https://t.co/IS3V6VyImF]]></document><document><![CDATA[got caught cheating on a state test at school, went home thinking it was over for me, my punishment was i had to go… https://t.co/thaSFYMQQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to see an eye doctor for an exam as soon as we get tax retirn money. America's Best gives free eye exams… https://t.co/YLA0ryEFb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The red sun rises. Blood has been she'd on this night. tianner @ North Carolina https://t.co/iOkBQZc2uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THIS BIG BOY OVER HERE!  🥳   Wow, it’s insane to look back at the pictures and see how much we ha… https://t.co/PrPvrIfVQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid The only silver lining for me is that the MAGA people are feeling the pain and embarrassment from votin… https://t.co/Osrqu53Snh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllCharisma @AmyAcker @EW Can’t believe it’s been so long! I love both shows respectfully! Truly my turn to as a t… https://t.co/RdZ3dtOqKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[ugh I missed out on my birthday drink because the starbucks in my resort doesn't accept them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBrennan where is the collusion on Russia and Trump.  Eating some crow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you!! Can’t wait for you to come home and tell me all about your trip💛🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting in with this company and met hefe today. Was told no more paydays. Asked for account n was told I stay take… https://t.co/QdGUFslnch]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet dates for tonight watching Captain Marvel!!! Love y'all @TobySmithSC and racho_13 @ AMC Classic Harbison 14 https://t.co/EkLrAB7s2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModeledBehavior @tylercowen Of course participation drop doesn’t matter if robots put us out of work. That said yo… https://t.co/iNgKIaOgj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica @KellyannePolls has been rode hard and put up wet. And, she’s going to burn in Hell for her part in… https://t.co/I5Prci7oqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to weekends and the balcony for @MetOpera’s 2019-20 season. Really appreciate the addition of Sunday matinées.… https://t.co/GUmd1VZWIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Local governments can veto the wall which are controlled by democrats. What a disgrace if you sign this bill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotMoscona Sad, but undoubtedly true.  Can’t imagine what your potty training was like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samuelgoff7 Hahahaha can't stop, won't stop 😎 (but dammit I'm ready for better grilling weather 😂)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultra what are the odds I can get a free ticket?! I went last year and want to go again this year 😭🙌🏻 https://t.co/ocxFzjRzJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarylParkerJR1 @FortWorth1949 @7_damum @PlayBookAthlete @_mikkio3 @247Sports @NPNGfitpro Don't believe a fake fan… https://t.co/JGe7sM7o26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGMacN @ncordle @AllieMartin143 It’s one of the pivotal books (besides the Bible, of course) that I use when I… https://t.co/UCsEiE9q41]]></document><document><![CDATA[mirth is good for the soul. Lesson Plan – Teen Finance – Student loans, paying for college and what Jay Z has...… https://t.co/fjNGlxNfN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patscap @tomecurran Donta, idc about his salary, I’m talking cap hit and savings if he does get cut.. my understan… https://t.co/C1LERlIR80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LundinEA @MamieLouJ @greta The easy access the enticement from the school ads.. the hope for a better future]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vesgcRk5n1 How play #BraveLittleWomen became #Chicago; the #musical or jusy watch @drunkhistory https://t.co/5BHOlXVF8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think one of the worst feelings about being in a relationship that no longer works is that you eventually become… https://t.co/ad5bOcLs8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#meditationmusic #houstonrican @Rico_3MINDZ 🔥💥💯 @ Crowne Plaza Houston River Oaks https://t.co/Hp6Srwfxfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grazitransex Yes I Will Suck Your Yummy Cock Absolutely Mommy Anytime My Goddess!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You find out Gods plan is for you to drop out of school and be a SoundCloud rapper]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las day of the week bitches! (@ Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/8Lgj2pReEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would explain why @VP is such an obsequious lapdog to @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone is having a good start to the weekend:-) https://t.co/fU0NvxsLTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonesher It wasnt that @Bonesher but that dint help I know, but guys have weiner concerns]]></document></documents></author>