<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TimothyDeLaG Always wear a face mask on flights.. You might look hella stupid but you'll never get sick 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was sitting down sharing cookies with my grandma and it left me in awe realizing it really is the simple things tha… https://t.co/fMqO6HE0Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beers300 @Shawn172510 @volrob33 That's just really not something to brag about honey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @HARRISFAULKNER @thehill @FoxNews @TheDemocrats They are scared they are going to be ask hard hitting questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are the white ppl who file false police reports getting in trouble? I need something more than them just going… https://t.co/NxwT8X7Hol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling the need to redecorate but don’t have a fortune to spend? Pillows/pillow covers are always a good start and… https://t.co/FNZ32fEERT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let them stay busy slandering your name and doing everything they can to frustrate you...karma is a mother.💜💜💜 @ Sa… https://t.co/g9elbEuKNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveAstrologer @sfreynolds @supersmashcache @bythebookpod There are many ways to die period. Was this a study done… https://t.co/ubaXA2DyBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here for Kate’s friend on married on first sight !!! Yes!!! Tell her she deserves better than Luke !!! #mafs #MarriedAtFirstSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah0s I haven’t, actually. I started writing about it on my blog, but kind of petered out. It would be nice to s… https://t.co/RPU8Ovs63P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jail time forthcoming .  He's in huge federal legal trouble .  Did he apologize  to Chicago  and President Trump  s… https://t.co/w3BpIo8RBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jriley8832 @chayesmatthew @ziptron John, I think you’re looking at this really narrowly. Hundreds of thousands of… https://t.co/2zojcO8QZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a bitch move. Doesn't have the balls to make a move so he retires.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re emotionally at your break when you start crying at the Humira commercial where she gets to watch he… https://t.co/4GpUOIkZu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is going to increase ridership on trains ... and increase tourism in Toronto” - @JeffYurekMPP on giving kids… https://t.co/eqn1QFVf7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 17289 VAUGHN LN #Dumfries #VA  #realestate https://t.co/iuAEAVGzDp  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will orange or red haired Jimin make a comeback? @BTS_twt #Jimin https://t.co/TN1kysrMUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TwoOfUs #KingLou👑 #LouGirl😜 @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson @Louis_Tomlinson… https://t.co/d74N7WFMBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiefullerfree @Fowlkes82 @Fowlkes82 @katiefullerfree I literally just laughed so loud! I can’t believe he thinks that. You’re beautiful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaRaveica Umm even if they can’t do it in their head...do they not have a smart phone? Lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d3vanlee @TSwift_Spotify Ah I’m getting all the posts mixed up lol. But you know what i mean 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[RJ Barrett’s reaction to the rumor that Barack Obama will attend tomorrow’s Duke vs UNC game was classic. 🎥:… https://t.co/DC49XDYHbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NucksNBirds I blocked POTUS and a few weeks later his tweets were showing up in my feed and I was following him...… https://t.co/JVGMDYGFpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet Baby Rae- you will always hold a special place in our hearts! Congrats on your accomplishments - well deserve… https://t.co/84tQRHgdEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDugudichi NO... as long as one uses their wealth to help others as well. Greed and gluttony are sins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @DebraMMason1 This Bayhard broad is really looking rough. Poor thing 😀😀😀😀😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely absurd. Dance Moms Quotes dance-moms-hunger-games https://t.co/9K92e7hT6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagnumPICBS Sending a hearty “well done” to writers, cast and crew! Thoroughly enjoyed tonight’s episode!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve come way to far to accept below bare minimum. if it makes you second guess your worth it’s not worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a clue and now we’re screwed 💔 ⠀ 🎶 *l I n k I n b I o* 🎶⠀ Lmk in the comments how you feel⠀ 🌬🌊⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀… https://t.co/bkZCoxawWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stripes on my 🍑 so he call this 🐱 Tigger 🤪 #actupchallenge #citygirls https://t.co/QLB0KN6mDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smirk for you. Southern women know how to say what comes AFTER "no offense" without saying "no offense" firs… https://t.co/1DqHkVW2oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up dreaming about which kind of ham to buy  not seeking explanations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avoiding @BachelorABC spoilers with @KatieWGME like... https://t.co/IXyD4Xu3H3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skelechiwatson @NBCThisisUs A couple heavy hitters played Beth’s folks! Wow!  #PhyliciaRashad #CarlLumbly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandon7nettles @chefrocky413 @strom_annette @MisleaderC @esadah @MelissaFunGurl @Cha51brolll19 @Barb81146… https://t.co/dBp45IRXVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi friends! 👩🏻‍🦰👋It’s freezing and I am baking! I added lots of veggies on top! 🎉🙌👩‍🍳I lacked mushrooms, but added… https://t.co/SXjNnl2cXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeautyChickee @PlaylistLive sigh i didn’t get to meet you :( i couldn’t find you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashvilleSC @Nashville_ABC @NashvilleScene @TVAnews SOMEONE PLEASE TAKE CARE OF THIS  FOR THE LOVE OF GOD -… https://t.co/jDieOpGGIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jus wanna know why I have spring break in April when everyone else has it this week/next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Fox News is actually registered as an entertainment company #FakeNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water policy your expertise? Apply now!   Posting open until 2/20  https://t.co/uI1ceG6JdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spring_Harbinge @DebTownsend16 @AOC You are disgusting....you should be in jail because you were hired under false pretenses...dumb dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think about the guy I shared my hotdog with at the Drake concert and I haven’t forgiven myself for not gett… https://t.co/qoUY8YZBYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Price! 1791 SW 24th Ter Miami, FL 33135 SqFt: 2,062 List Price: $749,000 Lovely, Old Spanish corner home in the… https://t.co/DdYdJPnCi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillySchnabel @Judithmboyd @kathybestburge1 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Jesus loves you, he touched your heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just ur daily reminder that @merylwalker is a gem of a person and a friend and I love her sm and she deserves the w… https://t.co/xQFjXh9wY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had sooo much fun doing a PSA for wellbeingtrust  Wanna volunteer?  Check them out! #wellbeingtrust #giveback… https://t.co/ncnSFvSbls]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello, @charlieputh is a blessing sent from above. that is all. carry on :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USArmy @GoArmy some of a back tooth chipped off. i can wait to be seen for that but you need to be aware that my m… https://t.co/ZXdcW4Xspe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyGovan THE MESSAGE FOR YOU IS THE BEST OMG save that, FOREVER  Like awwkakakakakak-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pardon Me @cspanwj What Socialist Thing Do You Want To Eliminate? https://t.co/fEISkiOpaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constantly and consistently inspired by the people around me. Friends, family, colleagues.   I think the secret is… https://t.co/f4cBtlIq2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damyantiwrites @andrewpyper Thank you so much for taking the time to share my post. Wishing you a wonderful day/evening!☺]]></document><document><![CDATA[$VYST there were many large trades excecuted in the 045 area (Company? Insiders? EMA who may be shaking in their bo… https://t.co/WPhCcfjjdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[security clearance over claims experts said he should not have been given access to nation's secrets  Two Democrati… https://t.co/k3S5ZZiHJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epilepsy_parent @SeizingLifePod Thanks for listening and for the love! ❤️💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t get over how I checked in a little girl named “Wolfgang” today. That’s so badass lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happycustomer 😁 taking home his New 2019 Yamaha YFZ-450R SE!  Enjoy the new ride, have fun, &amp; welcome to our… https://t.co/ZtjruFvm5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too stressing of a weekend!! @ Meadville, Pennsylvania https://t.co/RgvCiaCU6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCBS12 @moodysally1 @chortletown @SandraQuirnbach @Rhonda777 @Stacey5899 @iwd12 @irishfox1949 @Bwagg4… https://t.co/4zBDU61ytm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Raising Our Sons in America - ROSA https://t.co/QTDca93XsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Feinstein exchange reminds me of my mom’s 2nd husband who often tried to win our arguments (I was a teen) by sa… https://t.co/tmQjfDHv8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I brought the hoops out today .. it’s been a minute yallllll https://t.co/wg6Ola5WlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought I was schedualed to come in at 3. Turns out I'm schedualed for 4:30. Its employee appreciation week and the… https://t.co/k07rosocm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dunno what I would do if I went to a wedding and the groom punched her in front of everybody...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHarris707 @CatholicPierogi @ArleneKowalczyk @Jj051301 @d_ast777 @JudyMcAferty @TheBread_OfLife… https://t.co/9xrsTWkiTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must intentional teach, allow students to practice, and improve in these essential skills! It doesn’t matter wha… https://t.co/XpXuHnyZ7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCREMilton @HoneyBadgerUSA1 I wish Elie Wiesel was still with us, he spoke a power message.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWDay2019 ladies always remember the wise words of Queens Marie.  There's a media in social media.  Be kind to one… https://t.co/woAv8E7bJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want to do right now is go back to the Wizarding World ⚡️🖤 https://t.co/i77g2DF4ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonoredValor @SEALofHonor @op_hawkeye @bigdawgjdub @GenDonBolduc @mjgranger1 @Joeydonofriosr @SRex41563921… https://t.co/D5nDXpoRpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Faydee About a American tour in Chicago. !!!❤️❤️❤️ I'm waiting my Super Star 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community policing at work - look who we saw at the Chestnut Hill Mall yesterday afternoon! @newtonpolice held a “C… https://t.co/ZihjaXQbHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Feliz Día del amoy y la amistad!  Happy Valentine’s Day! 💕#LoveisQueer #LoveOurWay #aNuestraManera    Photo credit… https://t.co/L5TL5td6Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little TBT baby Shay lol Ive always been the wild child 🤪 I was gloria trevi she used to be my favorite artist. I… https://t.co/dWrV32q1ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivCountySports @hartlandbball @hartlandsports @KLAASports You go, girl! Way to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A city job you can really dive into: Philadelphia seeks summer lifeguards https://t.co/JtUykmKNwF #PHLCityJobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[いろんな影響もあってイギリス英語がなぜか好きなんだけど、キーラナイトレイの喋り方はなぜか好きになれない https://t.co/fS6vdX7MSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strategema @SenatorDurbin @repmarkpocan Send em all back.  Columbia would be good place as they are bragging how it has been cleaned up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to squeeze in a hair appointment while working 7 days a week and having school 5 days a week is stressful lm… https://t.co/LircPbSZo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues yo si me tome foto en el show de @franco_esca #nomeacuerdoqueeraloquehabiaqueescribirjajaja buenísimo en serio… https://t.co/32PPoUiAPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PierrePoilievre I’ve said this many times. If SNC-LAVALIN cannot sustain itself without corruption then they shoul… https://t.co/MDWxx9N7jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to that time 22 years ago, when my daughter was born, and the whole world shifted. I adore you my sweet, funny… https://t.co/GlRdIWJkoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/yQ8bCb4r3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[1507 N Surrey St, Medical Lake, WA.  Secluded yet close to everything! Fantastic home sold w/ additional lot adding… https://t.co/V4h1U1UTWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @XfinityRacing for providing an awesome race weekend at @ISMRaceway for @chloe_victoria and I! Thank y… https://t.co/OiXORiQUbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheila413Sheila @JaimeRKOFan @Ruth_A_Day @naturenohurry91 @DDUBGIRL69 @CncBhDdubminion @Asure76 @tammywalker2334… https://t.co/neniWUTXXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow as if I didn’t love this account enough   (The answer is obviously chocolate duh)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Do This! #MondayMotivation (@ 24 Hour Fitness in Houston, TX) https://t.co/4IKNqhygIT https://t.co/tgulmMR3oJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost What a joke. Is that the best that the Washington post can come up with?  You are a bunch of fools!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a limited time only @gerardcosmetics has come out with 3 mystery boxes. My discount code won’t work in this cas… https://t.co/s4itbQzM68]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Uppers whoever thought a #FauxNews #Fox broadcaster could replace @NikkiHaley is as nuts as #Hannity #Ingraham and… https://t.co/4k3amKMJoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr @POTUS , I am happy with you most of the time with the exception of the following,  I am outraged as well as man… https://t.co/6sOUr1X0An]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a week jam packed with soccer, Andrew wanted to sneak in one more training session with his good friend Ben.… https://t.co/1rDHQtTGvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three movies, 5 tags, no explanations @CassandraDBoyd @byMorganWright @debnance @thelaceylondon @seeorsea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvgeniMaIkinEgo Has nothing to do with Murray. You need to outscore your opponent every night. You need to score 3… https://t.co/TOWBXpglhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love doesn't just happen to you. Love is a choice and it represents a commitment.” #dailydevotional #loveisachoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump Yeah seeing citizens being stepped on is one big facto in my heart I loo… https://t.co/HeuRIficaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hochstriess @Rimmael1 TVPiS nie "uświadamia"prawaków, wiec z niczego nie zdają sprawy! Nic im kurwizja nie mówi...… https://t.co/kANyriZrfG]]></document></documents></author>