<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dronelaws @Diana_M_Cooper Ah yes, here we are: Remote ID in action! https://t.co/WuCtd1YyBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirPhillipEsq The other is a power outage of ~15% of a country for two days, a country that was otherwise relatively well off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the funniest thing is I don’t know who this is or was. Like did he go to knightdale? https://t.co/tl4ZY3jcz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabilas @placardabuse @JimmyVanBramer @NYCSpeakerCoJo @LICwalkers @NYCMayor @QueensNative1 @FabianBuchheim… https://t.co/zUcJ9PvLNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This how I wake up to warm weather and sunny days https://t.co/PbfPIiIKLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[SpaceX Crew Dragon capsule successfully docks with space station in test mission - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/higRhwUpOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norwegian Escape heading into Port Canaveral at Jetty Park after a rough time at sea...  and passengers injured. Se… https://t.co/srSJdbxxt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softly_sighing2 Was actually just making a joke.  You might very well be correct. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calimerog11 @bbusa617 @georgesoros I could care less about Barry.  I think he makes an ass out of himself every time he opens his mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Born-Alive Infants Protection Act of 2002, signed into law by Pres. George W Bush still exists. This bill is du… https://t.co/OhcxMby379]]></document><document><![CDATA['What a Crock!': GOP Rep. Stewart Slams 'Liar' McCabe's Claims About Russia Investigation https://t.co/LXyt3SPXAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeoplezPen Wow! That’s pretty aggressive. What would be a draft number where you start thinking about drafting him? 140?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano @jamessmurray @Joe_Gatto @BQQuinn @truTVjokers Eternalized on the back of my buds phone… https://t.co/k9cVdh3We4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquelynGill Yeah this is why I’m much more open to GND-style issue harmonization than a lot of people. Addressin… https://t.co/bwBc9FOrtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that’s “REAL TALK” send them both to prison lock them RUSSIAN backed TRAITORS up!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekDeedok That’s why the world will always be ahead in soccer but the Men’s team can’t even beat teams on this s… https://t.co/KZ0ckrmYVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I swear Shiva sunbaths like she didn't have cancer 3 months ago..smh what is you doing girly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElyangelicaNews El que a hierro mata, que no pretenda morir a sombrerazos]]></document><document><![CDATA[They bettr be fuckin because this was cute and her tortillas mad perky i love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[WARNING ⚠️ All day I will be retweeting stuff about DM-1 and Dragon 2 capsule because today is a big deal on return… https://t.co/AAjatk6euR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Trump's a guy who would struggle with the assistant manager job at a Queens Best Buy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Get this, Canelo. ESPN is stating Bryce Harper’s 13-year, $330 million contract is the richest in sports today.’… https://t.co/v9POxn375e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisondeck Nothing says “pro-life” like cutting off access to cancer screenings and STI testing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Coronado Cafe - @southpointlv in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/EqcLMPuWCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nightly pics of @VanessaBorneWWE and @WWE_Aliyah in a desperate attempt to get new followers. #NXTCrystalRiver https://t.co/Cd0sl6tEW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themikeypick I hit under once news of Duchene officially sitting broke.... staying hopeful 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsIzzyMania Congrats on your win. I’d say you could be the next Ronda BUT you’re going to be the only Izzy! Good… https://t.co/i0qBSrUNKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enrriqu25692593 @CasoCerradoTV @Telemundo @GlitzTV https://t.co/jmFQEYQms2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tennagersex Definitely beautiful! All of you defiantly are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepKarenBass U have no idea what you are talking about, background checks do not stop people who what to kill fro… https://t.co/SQRrUwM5RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iammgeezy let me hold Sumtin 💯💯👀👀🔥🔥🔥Hit Maker from Duval we ain't playing round Here move to ATL for what #DUVAL y… https://t.co/Frzf6fwYwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mc_bless @davidz67 👍❤️💯Morning Bro “Looking Good”  In NYC Just got up Can’t really See  Straight hope (Spell Check… https://t.co/VzvOgJjMVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Tries to Bully Kirstjen Nielsen then Kirstjen Gets Fed Up And Fights Back! https://t.co/ho2Z2KK77u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week of Swipe Right[eous] this Sunday! Married folk- you should be dating, too! #dating #single… https://t.co/RiykJHxPkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbusa617  THANKS SO MUCH 🙏! U S A   FIRST!! Build the wall!!  Mr TRUMP 2020 MAGA👍🇺🇸👍🇺🇸👍🇺🇸👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been saying for a while that @ZO2_ is the second most valuable #LakeShow player, because he brings smart defense, b… https://t.co/oi4gWNCpH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reinamodificada Have you ever heard k McCarthy dead dogs eyeball ? She sings his songs. This album came out in 90s… https://t.co/p7s8FobLjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we are underway here with a three from Evan Skeary @MetroWestSports @DSRaidersSports @DSRaiderHoops https://t.co/gGUq1y4eZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcary333 @Con_Chron I disagree. It's just that Klay doesn't shoot the deep deep 3s often. Only when he's having a… https://t.co/qFbpjddmDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewColler Not sure if u included the Steve Sabol one, that was great too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDaware @sassistheword @footyDoc @ChrisCarrollMD @iamyourgasman @PharmDuprey @aartisarwal @virenkaul @SapnaKmd… https://t.co/LXDW5VEWih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandywwills A: ?? Although Dickinson's death certificate Bright's disease (a common kidney ailment), recent resea… https://t.co/TtjErIMjty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putemupcdukes @MikeBellATL @hbonow No. It’s HBO’s stand alone streaming service. Just like Netflix you download th… https://t.co/jArbFi2kG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPassanisi @DanielSmith1022 True, especially from the press. Just pointing out there are plenty of haters here in the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support the Little Guys Monday!!!! Fall threw and Show Sum Love, I'm Live 🔴 Playing @CallofDuty #BlackOps4 chasing… https://t.co/RjCmeBzvr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comenzando bien el día con Cesar Miguel Rondon, para mi la mejor voz que nunca oí en la radio de Venezuela @cmrondon]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you've wandered onto the wrong side of the internet if you see this...Come to the Sabbath...… https://t.co/JxbPyWAn40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who knew or had a lot of love for bunny pls donate if you can the only thing we can do for him rn is to watc… https://t.co/KPhn2ee8v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisbenflanagan Repping T-Town🙌🏽 and covering my Roma parody!! @alfonsocuaron is the capital T, Truth, winning eno… https://t.co/GuxAhRYCSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesss this a fact. The white people who helped black people were also killed. They should be praised as heros too .… https://t.co/yZTfalIR0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest regret of last night was not getting this girl’s number! She was so nice and we had soo soo much fun!… https://t.co/7MpjcJVYdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvrobison @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/seKYXCHfCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[just grin a while. From Lesbian Affairs To Swapping Spit, Here Are Last Night’s Best ‘Girl Code’ Quips As Memes!...… https://t.co/7PgM1mLM8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ndymium6 @DylanSAYSS @dilemmv He’s supported by more democratic black women than any other demographic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's as usual, is not what anyone else is saying, the North Koreans say there is no point in fur… https://t.co/wgLHbpUKlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking into #1stteachchat with one eye on the @UHCougarMBK game! #GoCoogs https://t.co/z3fJ5Rw2Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks for Timbers Army supporters who donated. Thank you for showing up for our community once more. #RipCity… https://t.co/320xqe9puM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharkBoyNet @itsjerrylynn That’s funny AF! 🤣  I feel bad 😢 now...sort of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PST: I HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF THESE ROBOTS CALLING MY GODDAMN CELL. IF YOU AREN’T GOING TO TAKE THE TIME TO CALL ME THEN DONT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In life, you’re either Harry Styles or a Jonas brother. Or you’re *NSYNC. Or Backstreet Boys. Or, God willing, Mr.… https://t.co/PMFqqKnzfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN More Dem B S, The only reason that the shooter had a GUN, was because Government Workers  FAILED to do their j… https://t.co/3qNxTEslPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For to be free is not merely to cast off one's chains, but to live in a way that respects and enhances the freedom… https://t.co/UGUOSRhADC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress Gruden is Mr. Know It All.  Could never stand him, and that stupid, eternal grin, he has on his fac… https://t.co/gMiXBNl1El]]></document><document><![CDATA[We, Venezuelans, are better alone or choosing those to support us than having your blind “support” for failed revol… https://t.co/GtNTvp83yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinchXXX @drewdixxxon Yeah, don't know what part of him to French kiss first, his pouty lips, or his pouty perfect hole. 😚🍑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ray_lyn @journeyprokc I looked it up last night and the MO rules are super restrictive and expensive. I get why… https://t.co/AXOzkAiyVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rob Ray great hands great goal.What game is he watching? Weak Goaltending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madfriarskevin @KrissySD His tweets kept getting RT'd into my timeline so often that I finally muted him (do not follow)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar predictions: Times critics pick who will and who should win this year: After a notably dramatic awards season… https://t.co/sD4TIY4u3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notjustahooker @OPPoliceDept @FHPJacksonville Yes it is, but CCSO always wins. 😆☕️☕️☕️🤜🏼🤛🏽 https://t.co/49wlF9potN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiesnider I considered it. I think Durant’s personality and the fact that he’s on the Warriors tend to make peop… https://t.co/6XB7Bqc7Mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You still wrong! You don’t win against Go. Earth &amp; Heaven will be destroyed. Save that money to save people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carr says this until the first time Antonio goes off on him for not throwing him the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a former CNNer, I resent the fact that this Is ... entirely spot on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Ellis: these were just everyday felonies that would not have even come before this court except for the 2016… https://t.co/AcvawtNk5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full disclosure I did write 3 musicals in preparation for shows, but no scripts. the jokes are just what happens wh… https://t.co/M7qCPhAiPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[At NCCC, Alden senior wrestler Danielle Stanley came in 2nd in the first ever Section VI girls wrestling invitation… https://t.co/dJEoJtmugk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just posted on Instagram let’s see how many people will unfollow me this time]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a great team, it’s easy to spoil them. Thanks y’all for being you! Today’s National Employee Apprecia… https://t.co/xqeQ6JvMmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POB_CBB Lunardi has them as a 10, before that win over Iowa State  Not locked up, but it’d take the wheels to comp… https://t.co/oVaG9Gri7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youn_ht, eske nou ka fè yon kèt pou #Manzè svp pou peye lekòl pititanl? @BoukmanEKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kaburi_ @ghirapurigears Agreed. Though trading posts may be a fourth reason too..]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Ray's Collard Greens by Steve Turre, from #SoundHound https://t.co/QmGR7WhxQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, and just so you know, I'm a size 52. And my one arm is slightly longer than the other. https://t.co/p7Hnuriaqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Just like the song said, I see your true colors shining through]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again it’s #snowing ❄️ so much #round3 the kids next door started building an igloo, oh-my! #SnowMageddon2019… https://t.co/aSK1dWBmxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miisssliz @elchivo1112 @DimeloANG damnnnn can my boy defend himself tho 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never would’ve thought that a quiz would make me this nervous 😂 i hate anatomy 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still need to figure out the #KanaiCube in #Diablo3. It’s obvious that I’ve been away from the #Game too long. I al… https://t.co/lvh2McrzEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[3-0, We Got it done once again.. nothing like the high energy environment @mohegansun arena.. this is only the begi… https://t.co/Tnr9WFyJN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @Margerey3 @realDonaldTrump To Stand by the truth and for all that is good One suffers.! "If you find… https://t.co/jvtMiXACE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump For those of you who thought Trump would be "more Presidential" after he was elected...… https://t.co/KJQJrI98aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Putin and Kim a perfect lover's triangle. You have so much in common. You all suck, especially...I'm sure you a… https://t.co/CqNrEzDkz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time hearing him, what a motivator. Having no issues having players playing for a coach like Coach Chesney… https://t.co/8hWfrBusV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeGrinnell_ should get a @spittinchiclets live show on deadline day next year. I’m sure the #Insiderrrrr would be a great guest to have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jazmynbliss Don’t remember the last time i played fortnite with a girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The crazy thing is that I actually feel pretty damn good. Tired, but good. I probably bought way too much food just… https://t.co/BB9RwJX05S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/JQBpVAaJJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricSpyrosNBA Would you rather have Russell and mozgov or rondo/Beasley/chandler/Stevenson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @cade_bertrand hope you got good “Practice” in for today and the rest of the week😂😂. In all seriousn… https://t.co/wmgqSEAPho]]></document></documents></author>