<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We don't need to change our #SCOTUS because we have had a few years of noise.  The court has served us fine for hun… https://t.co/PG7eBEgdQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jay_the_raven finds a way to bully me no matter what he’s doing https://t.co/7OAHEXVeiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davependrys Of course there is but you are only one man with limited resources and no one seems to want to pay so!… https://t.co/beJqpkAD4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[#colbyexposingsecrets I had sex with my cousin’s husband, it was before they married, they had broken up and he was… https://t.co/ncg4mVA5gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisVuittonYon Facts! The simple ugly truth is that our society, our system is broken. Shattered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone: been there, done that Me Peacock’s voice in my head: GOT THE TSHIRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko I just drew a #rickandmorty 12.5x10  #pencil #drawing that I'm selling on my #etsy #shop at… https://t.co/HHYjRb6GTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just blasted through the last 7 miles of my 30+ miles in our relay on no sleep and sore legs. My secret? RICKY MARTIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has she ever gone on record with an explanation of what changed her position?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“it’s been really frustrating to see the business model for the industry begin to transition from creating and sell… https://t.co/hyPQZfjTqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guardian The people depend on tourism for survival. Staying away punishes them for what's not their fault. One way of looking at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JilldarWu That’s Thomas Alva EDISON! I know, I attended an elementary and junior high school named after him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dane doesn't have twitter, but I love him so much 😭❤️ https://t.co/3ZzE89ho0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReginaMagOnline I signed. I knew it was futile because I live in LA...did it anyway...I continue to pray for our b… https://t.co/xG8BB0e3Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lukifer47 To bad it’s in Washington state... like the furthest possible state lmao this would be a sick show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenSchaus @DirectLivestock Love that your voicing this!!  Pet peeve of mine!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my day off and i’m still up at a coffee shop at 7am like i’m supposed to be working or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to a work training/ staff meeting, so I swiped from a backpack to my purse and put everything in my purse… https://t.co/153m1S15BN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear .@HillaryClinton Our @POTUS is going to take care of that for us!  No worries.  Well-at least no worries for m… https://t.co/ornfty5yMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working up the courage to unpack from my month in #Thailand, and face any 🕷stowaways.  #MondayMotivaton #travelblogger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started watching sailor moon because I’m just done with tv shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooooo proud of these grls @LadyPurpleHoops !!They are the 14th district champions!Congrats to our favorite Coach… https://t.co/SKGhNmy2iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neal_katyal @PersuasivePR @andersoncooper @CNN Stone knew this would be picked up so his apology means nothing. La… https://t.co/53bX4VOn3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was soo lit after getting off work lol definitely was much needed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyAndCo @ladygaga @RecordingAcad Beautiful!! The jewelry too! 😉😍🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NargishAnsari3 Yes,store room me Manik felt something,something he never felt before❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything’s bigger in Texas! This is an actual wax warmer I have ! You place a cube or two of wax on the top dish… https://t.co/IY3M7Mqhq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on a mission to find a KS dani opal earring and I will not REST UNTIL I DO SO @KendraScott]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janine with her fajitas burrito. #NachoDaddy #LasVegas #Nevada #USA @ Nacho Daddy https://t.co/VRCnwqo5qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnStokes55 @ScreenCaffeen @sabine_durden @Acosta The legal status of the drunk driver who killed Sabine's son (il… https://t.co/IPgjv1SJnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatsyandEdds Thank you for sharing your videos. Love them (and your voice).]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK for my classic GHerss. Just found fatal attraction as/LW/Duke, Anna and Olivia Jerome. Is Olivia faking this pre… https://t.co/cMjXcptsUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you delete tweets from two days ago? Alright then. This page is to help your pockets, don’t be so rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to align your department with the mission of the instuition. How are you addressing the crises in the city… https://t.co/P0aLg0FZcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been writing this article for like a few months now and I finally finished it today and I think it’s my favour… https://t.co/BDGRYO58qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg..if you ant got a gun or a knife you ant even going to try a .....tag them just scared... seems like they need… https://t.co/g9UmxcfuFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[During this season of Lent, reflect on how much Jesus loves YOU.  . . . I have shared this many times, but one of m… https://t.co/x3QxnfMK0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATS MICHELLE! I’m so proud to be your teammate!! Can’t wait to watch the amazing things you’ll do at Elmhurst💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniachocron Los expertos en Venezuela, son aquellos que jamás han vivido y padecido en ella, a todos los expertos… https://t.co/aDurUrgAUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myblanket #picsart picsart #lhatese #sleepy #blanket #yawning #naptime #dog #canine @ Cypress, California https://t.co/572nUkv0Xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol American Idol suck, Lionel Richie is the only judge that has a clue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, remember when the Goverment Accountant resigned because they didn’t want to lie about the numbers for Doug? Ag… https://t.co/JcobPjfQr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson  Please bring some warmer weather with you next Tuesday .. @parisangel_1  and @CaldwellCarey  will appreciate it 😁😎🌻👍🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmshaf @FitCoachBruce @JohnHookfox10 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USMAN84kg #Congrats that was an amazing dominate fight. Thank you #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are just 3 days away from the conference! Some of the Conference Chairs met with @JharnaMadan from… https://t.co/cqVAvpQsqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters dear Maxine all I hear is your voice that shows your racism. In my area we are just people stop blaming others]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five ways male-dominated industries can attract more female talent /via @globeandmail https://t.co/W4O07BcoY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Adams is an utmost professional and model physician. So humbled too to be able to call him a colleague.… https://t.co/VONuk6x3H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband has a twin who cleans the exact same as he does. Well, my husband uses a purple head wrap but still... p… https://t.co/ON89N9qsTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdtips Did you see my earlier tweets about the shots fired into a building? Take a look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yehme2music I’ll lie to my husband and tell him whatever he gets me is my favorite gift when really the flip will be]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥The Return of Pooler 1st Saturday 🔥 Grown and Sexy Affair  March 2,2019 Doors open 9pm  For Tables and Bottles Ser… https://t.co/86FHaUZbLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfX_x1 @OceanicSquadGG @N3rdStGamers @underwatchgg https://t.co/Q8ngUovCVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisShort I could see parts of it in the distance when I was in Disneyland with my son last year. Can't wait to see this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand80760480 @LilianaSnchez9 @mainzina @szalacain1 @jobragag @Cantero9Vega @angsala67 @JSaintPastour Feliz sába… https://t.co/CfcgcQijEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[New addition to my studio, African violets.  #flowers #violet #africanviolet #houseplants #artiststudio #purple @ C… https://t.co/cD1c01SCae]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite go to dinner  The salad, the tips, the combo  #healthyfood #healthylifestyle #turkeytips @ Dracut, Mass… https://t.co/rR7PAh05ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Sylvia, Writing Coach / Reading Teacher @BrandonHSEagles  ... feeling better this morning! Also, the… https://t.co/omjKDF1bfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans Oh woah, in my neighborhood, it melted the second it hit the ground. It stuck on tge cars, but it was thick slushy snow]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was newly bereaved and 8 months had gone by I thought there was something wrong with me because I still miss… https://t.co/mGORe8mXTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help my drag mom find her black louboutin heels  #theroseroom #s4 #drag #dragqueen #shoes #louboutin… https://t.co/Zr1wpIpt21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiceAthletics @RiceWBB @ricealumni @RiceRallyClub @RiceUniversity @ThresherSports 🎩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don’t control the stock market and only the well off are in it. How ignorant you are of the average American.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sparkle That makes sense just like my birthstone!💎 https://t.co/fyWrLhTszO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you do things from your souls, you feel a river moving in you, a joy. ~Rumi https://t.co/uLsbEjItz8… https://t.co/iG6xcHcQSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek Don’t want to hurt someone’s feelings crowd has brought this upon themselves. Very dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, history friends, who is this Max person and why is he saying ridiculous things?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣Come out and Celebrate Black History with ASU’s ASPIRE Progam !!#myasu https://t.co/EdavOWCKfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is 💣🔥 Unbreaking America: A NEW Short Film about Solving the Corruption Crisis https://t.co/imo9v3dOXk via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMalorzo @medpepper @A_Badassunicorn @moinanderson @witchofgric @AlwaysChica @stevie76 @gany760 @ewannaC… https://t.co/rfe9geCW4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoTV RHOBH Reruns: I’m amazed how childish Kyle was to Kathryn Edwards during the OJ scandal discussion. Kyle w… https://t.co/8WaSvo7WTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I discovered that mixing ranch and Italian dressing on my salad is actually awesome but probably negates… https://t.co/e2CcEgC8au]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly wanted to go shooting when i was like 10 but TO THIS DAY no one has taken me 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump U have said, how strong U are as a leader. It looks like the "young" representative… https://t.co/3eamAk1pCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to announce that I no longer have to pretend I’ve ever listened to a Ryan Adams song]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope ppl knows my plus 1 or i have to bring a date....will be my Bestfriend’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[mis amigas y yo empeñadas en resolver todo este misterio de la jordyssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn @lulu81507 @JupiterFl123 Those photos are as sickening as the crimes themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcaitlinboon @JuliaWagemann I had the same question. 😂🤔#ImNotLivingUpToMyTwitterPotential]]></document><document><![CDATA[Menciones Honorificas: Malcom el del medio, La casa de Papel, The Office, La maldicion de Hill House, La ley y el orden UVM, Hannah Montana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya’ll know how hard you gotta hit someone to knock their tooth out WITH a mouth guard in...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some comedy. Why does Batman slap Robin and say "my parents are dead" so often? #mirth #snicker #smile #amusing https://t.co/6zr3KRNGOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[couldn’t relate to when it rains it pours by luke combs anymore than i do right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening night @toirishfilmfest 2019 looking forward Under The Clock. https://t.co/RsI284Z8o9 https://t.co/D7851R2va8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing performance by this beautiful talented young actors  @vytphoenix 🎭🎟 #edwardtulane📕… https://t.co/VEs8p1L8Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottColbert @RandolphLaw @Rick5342x @atrupar Yes, it is excusing it. He was Ok with hurting millions of his fello… https://t.co/9LGoG0ceL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol @ bird twitter drama  can’t we all just share binoculars and love birds, together, from a respectful distance o… https://t.co/o8OJ7oBQUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I went to return my rental car and it was the same guy who gave me his # way earlier in the summer when I went… https://t.co/uQoh56tqZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraysonDolan we love you :( he's still here with you and will never leave your side 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WheelerpretPat @realDonaldTrump TBF he really doesn't think about anything often, except maybe Ivanka and #hamberders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbymalala That policeman should never have treated that child like that! Rapping in the mall and selling cds was… https://t.co/bJwLzDnzwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mannyfornh @nadia_perl @elistone123 Thank you!! Fun night in Chicago :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toppjj @ggreenwald Why does that bitch even have a platform? Oh, right—because being one of John McCain’s sperm th… https://t.co/m7YKv2qy7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[email from the nurse said: "[your daughter] was playing conjoined twins with a friend, fell and bumped her forehead… https://t.co/Nv3JviSk3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a nightmare all of my friends from high school were at an Excision concert. I woke up horrified and appalled at… https://t.co/W5JJkAk3CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt being all kinds of adorable today and as always, I am here for it. 🥰❤️🙌🏻 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets for Aladdin JR will go on sale this Friday, March 1st! Be one of the first to secure your tickets to a whol… https://t.co/ZHPV1rHMFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones Weird, bc my dad grew up in a similar situation and he would be the first to tell you that discrimina… https://t.co/lyKez3oblc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scharmach_s @star_indie @networkindie @kelly_kintner @TamanieDove @thesouthernfall @JessieLynnJL @winstonc_music Thanks Stefan]]></document></documents></author>