<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kowenmoffor @TheRealEazy32 That’s what I love about it, you really make that bowl fit how you are feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all know Illhan Omar is anti-semantic.....but I go a step further and claim she is also anti Christian, then of… https://t.co/dRm1rXbFqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard Idiots! I’m not even sure the 18yr old vote was a good idea as many don’t even know what our government is supposed to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thread. It’s more about defining the capitalism we have (see the new deal, new frontier, great society) than the s… https://t.co/bvWaFIObd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witstudioco Pocket Monsters sun and moon and almost over can please secure a deal with the company and studio behi… https://t.co/LatXQNXz1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregoryRanches1 @KtGibbs49 @IceCreamJudas I understand but she was older at the time. Listen to solange’s new reco… https://t.co/TModn8iq1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump You're reaching sir,  or have you already sold your soul so it doesn't matter.  I… https://t.co/WejSPB1NI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go home Bernie Sanders, you're drunk. You are the reason Trump is president anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikschlitt @mcannon_10 @throwjimmy @erikschlitt let me know if you need help with this buddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @PetLevrieri @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/ywVKFigojL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris This is why the dems need to be removed from power from control of our schools and shamed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ritual de Domingo, café da manhã e @pedroandradetv 🎳 🎳 https://t.co/hCTWNqIve9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you really believe what you write? In what world can they be scary with that pitching staff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGreeneIV Sweet gesture. I wouldn’t expect anything less from the Greene family. #firstclass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennethafisher @StaphCdbusters @IP4PI @AAPSonline @jorient @kksheld @janehughesmd 👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lunavarion I really think will do awesome man, I think we have a very similar writing style, and I think we will really do a great job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #Classic 🏈 Thanks for the #Memories @NazarethAlum @NazBCast #Winners https://t.co/hD1jHp5uLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[But also there’s such a potent patina of exhaustion and sadness over everything that it’s kinda mesmerizing. It’s l… https://t.co/GjMro2mRFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel was a film filled with mediocrities and was completely average. Spotty, boring at times, and less than charming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidgolferman @Jali_Cat Only the 'The Best and Brightest'.   Just look at who's vying for the top of the Dem ticket… https://t.co/OZqJNAK23u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to Lamarcus Joyner and the Oakland Raiders. Always a Ram !! #rams #nfl #freeagency #raiders… https://t.co/xQI36IHVIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is Hyperbole. Look it up in the dictionary,  it’s in there with Tantamount.  So is Traitor an… https://t.co/OvXM7OJyfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry SOMETHING SHE KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT SACRIFICING FOR DOING WHAT IS RIGHT FOR YOUR COUNTRY, SHE DOES KNOW AB… https://t.co/tYUl2Zc5wY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonVorthos I'm not sure you understand how Markets actually work if you think "Hoarders" are the problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Through gospel and Spirit, God is now putting people right so that they can be both examples of what the gospel do… https://t.co/ZrPMWpCBlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It needs to stop raining. We’re not in a drought anymore. I’m sick of it 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know - you know.  . . . #frankocean #boysdontcry #boysdontcrymagazine #001 @ Maricopa, Arizona https://t.co/Rdv4j4d7zt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flutterfli007 @RBReich You could be right, but i hope not. he's doing the right thing now. And deserves a chance w… https://t.co/wx6ST5uofq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a hand getting out and walking more?  #WALKING #exercise #fitness #health #hand #helpinghand #helpinghands… https://t.co/Gk6V27IFMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane Sounds like they'll be rotating announcers. So he won't be working as many games. It's a foot back… https://t.co/0z15jHafo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsServant 💖 And they heard the voice of the Lord God walking in the garden in the cool of the day: Genesis 3:8,a… https://t.co/CiVdpLx0DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how this will save so many on installing solar. California - the new energy state. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #Solar$]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was slid on a wand while at Olivanders. SHE SAID YES!!!! @ Olivander's Wand Shop. Diagon Alley https://t.co/qtfrOxjYlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to be invited by the Ambassador of the Republic of the Philippines to this special reception at the Pinoys… https://t.co/V2NwNeyCNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[you just can't make this stuff up. @PUBG @PUBG_Support @PUBGpartners @jasmaxwell @JohnTRourke]]></document><document><![CDATA[POLL: Would you give this guy a THIRD date ? #selftape #sake #chopstick #comedy #improv #sweetbutpsycho #amypoelher… https://t.co/R9tlv9ZLbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCH_LCO @MarysPlace1919 @StephaneOCH_LCO @cmckenney @JimWatsonOttawa @ScottMoffatt21 @tm_kavanagh @MathieuFleury @ottawacity Amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strategist_62 @FrayJosepho Juasjuasjuas 😝😝 ayayayyyyy que llegaron los buenos😝😝😝😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[La insólita decisión de frenar una carrera de mujeres porque estaban alcanzando a los hombres https://t.co/bjlcv9lhi3 vía @El_Universal_Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[After getting plowed out at loves, here picking up (@ Westvaco Trailer Yard in Covington, VA) https://t.co/MqiPPoq89R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Arsenal’s toughest bits of the schedule upcoming — the lower rungs of the table.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamabogadaok1 Muy buen! Todos los días yo hago un "shake de protein" (no sé como se dice) con muchas fruta!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you comfortable, in New Hampshire, with the title of front runner?  @KamalaHarris: "No! Not at all. I am used… https://t.co/7CTvZvPGiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@love2laugh4ever Community impact is best served when a company enters a community through the planning commission,… https://t.co/qPg4RheZOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NulaTweets actually the tariffs for Pharmaceutical products is 0.0% between the UK and EU in a no-deal situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to avoid campaigners on the Concourse like.... https://t.co/PjS4d1gPeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin @AOC @SenSanders @SenWarren The deer 🦌 kicking the guys butt was really good. I have deer 🦌 on my prope… https://t.co/PcqjlGwEXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you imagine what it would’ve been like, if drumpf were in office during Saddam Hussein‘s reign?Saddam would’ve… https://t.co/BcziFtdiWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Landmark's Midtown Art Cinema https://t.co/4lHWL0FOsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conscience - follow your intuition or at least do what is right.  Get aid to these people now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayKarioca @MarceloM12 Dude, 95% of the time you only rate Brasilian ballers. I watch Madrid games (hoping that th… https://t.co/EPkrvnRNxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaAdlerr The guy has MAGA in his bio. Im truly not surprises by this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @JohnJHarwood Do you ever do any real journalism or are you just limited to Democrat propaganda?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who says you can't have a little fun during an afternoon brainstorm meeting? My first virtual reality experience ✅… https://t.co/3YRrOPgvor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedeejjj only scenario I care about....blue team doesn’t win in basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the nicest young men you’ll ever meet....and that lockdown vs. Springfield 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithsnyi @91Butch @cwotd Hahaha, I love how it’s that’s a text impression of someone else (Fred) doing an actual… https://t.co/MAEl9ZRJE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY https://t.co/C5m2umOFsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiorioKate @jillian_damon @PupilServ_SGASD @DHEPrincipal After school programs and summer programs provide student… https://t.co/8JNa23zBvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLMiller9 @my3monkees They don’t act on illegals breaking the law, Taxpayers sure, fleece is. Illegals are allowed… https://t.co/toDma3wStM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KodakBlack1k Recruiting Video!!🔥🙌🏾 #WeNeedKodak https://t.co/XYV374gNup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyTeethB @ggreenwald Marco Rubjo is the one pushing for war in Venz if HD doesn't know then he shouldn't make su… https://t.co/VUo6lXt7Oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Analyst_G Well said, shorting the mkt isn’t working, being long w declining impl vola isn’t very palatable, time to sit/wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heroinebook @erinbiba @JSTOR_Daily Not to be too picky but I must quibble with your use of tense. “...has descende… https://t.co/TUTO7gSj0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenChuckYeager Salutations and much respect as you celebrate your birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca ignores a una persona que te quiere y te lo demuestra por que un día te darás cuenta que probablemente perdis… https://t.co/A1EJqEHuIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should take coach off your name if you don't understand this simple concept 😂 😂 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have watched three films this week that have a moment in a scene where the main character goes to light up a ciga… https://t.co/Rozb9ScQPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_FisherKing Oh the stans were happy as a pig in shit about this poll over at Bernie Central—er, I mean Daily Kos.… https://t.co/vQZjRQNSp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't do any just watched the mj show waiting for my phone to charge 🤪👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s something about Robert Englund’s chuckle in the first nightmare that I love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug’s Filet Roll... yes please. Steak makes sushi great again! (@ The Cowfish Sushi Burger Bar - @thecowfishsbb in… https://t.co/4uRGyVnBus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some tunes at #Winterfolk before my last set of the festival at dorakeoghpub. That's my #publicist Beverly… https://t.co/FLkOD2TPoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when our trials and messes are self inflicted, He still comes through for us. #HisGrace God is for you! Rom. 8… https://t.co/VTZ9ie0s7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrtoastyman But that would mean turning around, not seeing you, and more time. Gee, don't you even care? :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[We turned up without our best player... and y’all dancing? Couldn’t be me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phoxilady @realDonaldTrump Thre only joke here is the traitor in the WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDPomp Nothing would be more entertaining than seeing AB and John Gruden on the same sideline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrginganinja @readetome This is getting too deep https://t.co/mkZv4L9i3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[No es justo que dejen así a tremendos atletas @Rommel_Pacheco @jahir_ochampion mucho ánimo, son unos gerreros y Dio… https://t.co/FkPEiLJUOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyDinniman Dear Mr. Dinniman, before I involve my media contacts at Fox News and ABC News, I want to give you an… https://t.co/5eKj5alU8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOverGreggy @albinokid How does he have the time for a Bloodborne plat trophy?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlastispherePod Perhaps @machadoaas has some resources? Here’s a cool study on MP transport by earthworms: https://t.co/7ilqnfoEMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryelder @LevequeThots @Twitter I heard of someone else having the same issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Juan Capistrano, California https://t.co/JvGVIrZR04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModellingWorld 2019. Can you afford to miss it? And do you know someone who deserves to be put forward as Master o… https://t.co/vbk433FTu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend last second chair turn earns @lisarameymusic a second chance on #VoicePremiere @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buddyhield As they say. - and you follow this philosophy it seems ...    good.  Better.     Best.    Never. Let it… https://t.co/qSZkn23Cdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading back to NYC with all the right supplies from a successful trip south. https://t.co/VKRo9IeCN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickygumbel I am about to finish your one year Bible reading plan on YouVersion. It was a blessing to read somethi… https://t.co/wUO7y6Kv9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an honor to be on the House floor with Supreme Court Justice P. Scott Neville, Secretary of State Jesse White… https://t.co/CkJcpZYPnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Directly or indirectly, all three are aided by the Far Left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be clear about your intentions when you are trying something new.  It makes the end result more fulfilling]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 Days!!  Senior C/RHP Danny Livoti is all smiles knowing the Vikings get to work a week from tomorrow!… https://t.co/QsED1v7EWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tv in the bathroom? Yeah kinda. #houseofthefuture @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/pWFbVCGSiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwinSenior @SkighKing @ItsSeanBroleson @GrahamAllen_1 @AOC @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump I bet you have no cre… https://t.co/6IJGrLuzys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nourishedcloud It’s like getting glasses for the first time when you never knew you needed them, except even more… https://t.co/a0Jdvep9nK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing you have to be up for work in the morning and not being able to fall asleep sucks :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a Bernie Cinematic Universe, Tony Stark would be taxed so hard, he’d have to build a tin suit and Spider-Man cou… https://t.co/vGn776Nb7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_4moso Cut those people outta your life, you don’t need that negative energy👸           Sarah,” gehehehegehehhehhe”]]></document></documents></author>