<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MattLorchQ13Fox Matt, have you heard about the crazy plan to fill Gold Creek Pond with dirt in the name of water m… https://t.co/fUVn5D59j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamaubobb @UMBC @FreemanH1963 Two speakers, a single breath, a common thread — altogether fitting and proper.  I m… https://t.co/k00YT1LeOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fragments of Vision series now has its home at the UT College of Natural Sciences! I'm particularly honored, gi… https://t.co/cN7OoSqkMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Weather Girl tells me it’s Bitter Cold in Canada and the Upper U.S. , So you Bullriders make plans to attend one… https://t.co/g4LddEky1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say it’s my Birthday! Off to Vegas! 48 will be a great year! https://t.co/e2H95fxX7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[6:14 3Q🏀: ORR 19, Falmouth 16 | Bulldogs on 4-0 run to start the half and Clippers call TO to regroup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AggrotheClown @WrestlingWWUK @rasslinblogs @smarktodeath @AmazingNerdShow @TheBroKast @ViewFromTopRope… https://t.co/1FSrSJJZQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabethacantu @TimCoeUK @10xMIllennial The yellow is good so is the blue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abhinary @_BeanEnthusiast @chuckmcatee @mitchellvii Oct 28 2015, so what you think that building a Trump Tower in Moscow is illegal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[📹 Filmed 1/1/19 via thewoodsskateco 📹 I had the pleasure of bringing in the new year with my sponsor thewoodsskatec… https://t.co/tGxmZH4rca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out one of our Soccer Alumni @FeistRobbie  in this Awesome shot. Glad you are ok!!He is currently going to sc… https://t.co/D6qKVzSQ8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Russssyyy @Adam_Jacobi Local officials can declare emergencies, but a Blizzard Warning is the highest winter weath… https://t.co/72JuR7IYdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My T_C levels were way down it’s good to back back https://t.co/Fq97KoPzqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Begin”? What the hell has it been doing all morning?!? https://t.co/sAaYdoOZeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Springing forward to #DaylightSavingTime is a great idea; evening daylight is so less depressive than early darknes… https://t.co/y9ZTc6bbnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @JuliusGoat @realDonaldTrump I don’t think you’ve ever even read the Gospel then, Jerry, especially… https://t.co/Ap8x5rMHrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait🙌🏻 tune in Sf and beyond.  @KGO810 @ryanscottshow @SF_Dragon #ryanscott2gocatering]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/eUg2KSK4cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addy_pez @RCSD @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @WomenPatrol Congrats Addy! H… https://t.co/SJ40NeXclt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully more and more blacks and Hispanics come to realize the truth about democrat history, democrats still have… https://t.co/5kofTN6wjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least my backup plan of going to Humber is solidified , Carleton where u at????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just know....😂😂😂😂 #TearsFloweth #DailyLaugh #LMFAO #Funny #Comedy #Hilarious #Jokes #Flatlined #LOL #DigThat @ Atla… https://t.co/aR0Of2DVG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC who was Jim Crow? Also do you consider Mexicans to be indigenous to the United States? #rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagnumPICBS what's the problem with the show tonight? My #comcast DVR won't let me pause, back up, or record the s… https://t.co/wIJvD7D0ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CaptMarvelNews let’s spread the joy found these mobile wallpapers on the Disney Singapore site https://t.co/AvHEfX90x2]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to the homie @raginblazian rocking his FM “Motiv8” Dri Fit T-Shirt Hoodie.  Thank you for your continued patron… https://t.co/RjbwUW2IFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band Bed Of Roses performs at Blackthorn 51. @ Blackthorn 51 https://t.co/jXPL8FGCY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cub Scout Winter Adventure Camp! (@ Camp Pouch in Staten Island, NY) https://t.co/loCSlnHxEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrollCougsBBB Enjoyed my many conversations and interactions with Greg over the past 25 years.  He will be truly missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, a week ago this was my Friday!!! 😔 (@ UPS Orlando Hub in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/xq0yCl6PAr https://t.co/88yCDKabuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zmcartor @armadsen I definitely agree re the death of the indie scene. Seems to be the same on #macOS as well. I’d… https://t.co/dVQUkG5K0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a morning of dueling performances of "Rhapsody on a Theme by Paganini," beginning with Sergei #Rachmaninoff at… https://t.co/CfXTbdvGIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indeed ouch when the @potus is an obvious Russian agent taking orders from Putin and out of control putting our nat… https://t.co/clFQNFKDrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the @ccwrangler_ftbl Cisco College wrangler nation  @Gipson22X https://t.co/5te3HauWCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Og Supreme x Clark's desert boots for sell https://t.co/jeYhQ8XTjx https://t.co/R6LIYBKWgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Divine Right of the Elite AI Obsession https://t.co/ZRQEi2JTU7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is wonderfully complex. This issue isn’t as simple as black and white. Discuss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are we doing another phish song bracket when we know what's going to win]]></document><document><![CDATA[hm....why talk shit about something you know your friends like when it costs $0 to not do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael20270505 Yep whether or not she was bad at her job,she was.. most Male pundits had to bite their tongues so… https://t.co/O42J71LWtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amywilson This is still the one from yesterday! I'm trying to 'milk it for laughs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for some #MarchMadness? Tonight at 7pm, I have the call for @WCUAthletics women's basketball as they host… https://t.co/YKjey9GZx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twtmpodcast @ToddlerOfTerror Keep it up guys... we will see you at MK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deojr1965 @FearlessGirl24 @pianopsycho2 @Swainwalker @AOC That's not how collective bargaining works]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue is it real what I see on Facebook. Share to get 2 free tickets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how irrational Jordan fans are. Half of them prove the point that they’re arguing against 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @PaulLeeTicks Yea because they wished he was no longer with us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking Kentucky’s ass even though the refs are really tryna help them out 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanted to share this cause i thought it was so cool 🥺 this guy randomly sent me this vid of a routine he mad… https://t.co/b8Ex7Jbr3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[So jameson wasnt kidding and he’s actually leaving for spring break. And to top it off he’s leaving TODAY and not t… https://t.co/hpdqBb1e8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will pumping this a lot over the next 24 hours.  The @McMasterSports Women's basketball team faces… https://t.co/2DFtxIRLp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unified Police say they have arrested 37-year-old Tyler James Vernon for investigation of aggravated murder. They h… https://t.co/wnYGWhaRjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmSteveHarvey Starbucks...Nacho Steak... spacedust( 🍺) ... she gone so u answered for her ... ok 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Angelenos! I highly recommend "For The Love Of (or, The Roller Derby Play)" at the #kirkdouglastheatre, especia… https://t.co/ONRAX1c4d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IzaTabaro Mainstream Jewish Democrats were the driving force in the Soviet Jewish movement, it was only the far le… https://t.co/OPe3z0Q5EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[only thing I'm upset about yesterdays all-star game is we didn't get to see Lebron play alongside Davis once]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLong2099 People are going to hate me. Thin Mints is taking the walk of shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PIAA Wrestling State Championships @PIAASports #GIANTCenter https://t.co/1ll8PINyfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me enjoying to see my dude Tommy Wright III get his just do. #nashville #tennessee #thirdman #thirdmanrecords… https://t.co/CKfC2zQVBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle  Iwish the freaking familyseparation with the children would stop so we can get on already to start… https://t.co/FYEAELXJXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great info here for kids wanting to get recruited!   When you like something the world can see it on Twitter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peach Crown is a 10/10 and @CrownRoyal continues to show why they are god tier]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because this ISN’T identity politics? Right! Got it. Excuse me while I go and LMAO 😂 @jemelehill @CapehartJ… https://t.co/Z56wLHEF9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @MarsRovers Really amazing but in the end kind of sad that this journey came to an end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan the other commentator needs to let u speak more!! #fuckthatguy #letroganspeak #BONESJONES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demarious👏🏻Randall👏🏻tweeted👏🏻about👏🏻Dorsey👏🏻trading👏🏻Kizer👏🏻for👏🏻him👏🏻stop👏🏻RTing👏🏻him👏🏻with👏🏻alarm👏🏻emojis👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome new profile pic beautiful lady from John in Manhattan NY 💙💙💙💙💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPost_Schwartz Attention all those writers who think  they're the shit:  Landon Collins just bodied you.   Repeat… https://t.co/Hm1gNymy5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Government has failed us, Liberals have failed us!” Malcolm X's Legendary Speech: "The Ballot or the Bullet" 1964… https://t.co/d5GxJXpooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks good. Looks like you got Christmas early the Redskins acquire Case Keenum congratulations 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Gen Korean BBQ House Fremont https://t.co/R1zXn0rLsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 3 pointer by @danniwill3 Danni Williams gives @TexasWBB its largest lead, 38-28, 6:24 in third @statesman #OneMore]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to buy a body suit instores gahdamn. Not no longsleeve either it’s fucking hot. Shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to the Derrick Favors locker room interview and NO NOT FOR THAT REASON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta, Nashville, Austin and Dallas literally can not build condos and apartments fast enough due to people reloc… https://t.co/LDgNgzm4bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lou_farrakhan I thought it was gonna be something cool cool lol but I don’t even got the watch 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mane Jussie was mdine went and gave MAGA hat wearers a great victory in Black History Month. Bruh why you do is like this? #why]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfiessssssssss ❤️🎉🎊💯 #bigj #nofilter #newyork  #31  #like #share #comment  #lit #smiles #positivevibes #happiness… https://t.co/rwoecdSxEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AverageJoeArt You just have the one 1990’s style turtle movie one right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason I want to add a duck to my household. They can eat all the nasty ass peas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But now that I see that in print I am reminded that the Trudeau government is a collection of shocking weakness! Do… https://t.co/6J56d2jGPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/UyXzmM2hlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clairmore2 @dazlendazle @thebestof2018s @robert_sicario @RamosEdson1 @Larryputt @KeecoWang5 @KLHirst1 @broady981… https://t.co/0kDdIoqV89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two really good takeaways for every golfer that are being displayed by Tiger 1) club is constantly being released t… https://t.co/pw4md7UQBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philhester I had tsp many great responses to this, but I think I’ll quit while I’m ahead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phimher Glad you got back safe. And Ditto on the reunion but them cards will tell you how it ends! They know it all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[195: Lincoln Shinn, W, maj dec Peter Moen 8-0.  Bemidji 33, Willmar 17.   @WillmarWrestlin @cardsathletics @BemidjiSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameful craft strip mall prostitution ring free 1000 g-strings opening game next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr You're a liar and a partisan enemy of the country. Stop blaming the Democrats for your wrong doings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Haenchen @RealJerryP @natesportsguy @Ballgame_9 I don't think that is a challenge at all. If you include the… https://t.co/GuJLg2RwMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on https://t.co/92BYRH3zF0 has been hard work. Seeing it come together has been the most rewarding time in… https://t.co/Xqt3GOszJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman It would be nice if people read the background on the shooting before reacting. Does anyone care t… https://t.co/0DZVshW39l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyelliottmcm @gmbutts @Puglaas As if to say they knew better than her]]></document><document><![CDATA[To everyone complaining that Travis Scott was like an hour late last night, just know that when Kanye came to Indy,… https://t.co/sXIYlfHlPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@87astro @JohnTerek They just did the pettiest trade in sports history! Me Big Chest can’t be happy about that! 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goose2448 @adamrobin84 @MackTrucks I love that they group that all in front of you. Easy to see and lit up nicely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay annoyed I told my crush I like him cuz now I can’t dramatically subtweet him and that’s the tea hi bb 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gurbeans @richardzussman @AJWVictoriaBC @Rob_Fleming So proud that you've moved this forward! Great work. #sd61 cu… https://t.co/L0yOs7GIQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvspharmacy I hope I got her name right, Fanny, who works behind the pharm counter on 18th/65th Brooklyn did an ou… https://t.co/sjNoclqQkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mon_ique @CTSNOWman1 @John_Jamason @SnowballManny @oxlamb @omdohmydog1 @SkiPow7 @PGadoury @ParisParamus… https://t.co/bv7EENxAB6]]></document></documents></author>