<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Try this poll: Vote for the Fan Player of the Game now to earn an extra 5 bonus reward points in your account! https://t.co/93tLCXJqmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Open Houses in Shaker Heights, Solon, and Chagrin Falls https://t.co/CXNzTgcYu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope - not twins. Ram lamb on the right; crazy cat, William, on the left. He really was trying. William follows us… https://t.co/lHL4Ez6E1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadie just informed me that @KaceyMusgraves is her current favorite singer 💗 (tweet stylized by the 5 year old herself)]]></document><document><![CDATA[12/10 I don’t wanna come back to school bc that just means 8 weeks left of college... 8 weeks left to be with my fr… https://t.co/hZfu6pJSKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day later, but here are some snippets of the #RedVelvet #redmareinusa concert yesterday; all credit goes to emurs… https://t.co/uojT3R0gv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaekDique_ @Zelina_VegaWWE You’re just mad that @CarmellaWWE beat you at your own game!! When you’ve done what she… https://t.co/zqPHWRbC8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanCloe @OrenIShiKiddo @Chrisstto12 Lol!! Are you reading Breitbart?  Indictments? Trump gives Putin pedicures… https://t.co/cxIYIYJSZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Punkyval @MarzGurl Yeah, but that's just a Marvel films thing. The only unanimously liked villain is Loki, everyon… https://t.co/sWL6R4JUIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgia242011 @laura24fan @DaleJr88FanNate @JLee418 @Chrisracefan1 @chevychevelle48 @ToddTPrice24 @nation_myers… https://t.co/s3uDS7abX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[hmmmmm is dis a trap? am I being set up ... lmao SOMEBODY JUST LMKKKKK SOMETHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[In class today: “Primary sources help us connect to real people of the past!” @DrLizi  We talked about how importan… https://t.co/qWKS8JmrFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnamaeKElliott @jlparizeau I do want to see that, but I'm betting it will be all over social media tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkInEarnest Fact: Patriots have Something that Libtards will NEVER Have: Common Sense! Or As My Grandpa Called: Horse 🐎 Sense🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a monumental moment for science.   H.I.V. Is Reported Cured in a Second Patient, a Milestone in the Global… https://t.co/CzLWj4kOzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gilbert made me strawberries and I want to eat them at work but I don’t want share...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rfagoaga Y es un gobierno de “izquierda” si fuera de derecha que haría? Lo mismo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maniacmiler @GovWhitmer #FixTheDamnMDE I supported this governor. In her first 2-months and 3 days I’ve lost all h… https://t.co/UWTJ2XXiT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satansafadi can you explain to the fan club what exactly full moon mode means]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaabAlex @madds_12 @SummerStoewer @kathy_pinnock @Abby24Coates @MarquittaEasley Love this...the hugs, high 5s, an… https://t.co/vpQJelwdAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetoMetroDos Tbh I cannot decide if AG Barr will be a hero or a villain. Really hope he’s on America’s side. #TRMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikegriffinFL @PeterSchorschFL @michelletodd @michelletodd, how do we not have parts?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! @CrashingHBO @peteholmes @TheJamieLee have been wanting you to get back together since you split up 💕📺💕 https://t.co/ASPyECvyBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #CustomerService job in #Johnstown, PA? Click the link in our bio to see it and m… https://t.co/3WAg8quGGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bank Leumi Le-Israel BM, Bank Hapoalim BM, and billionaire Sheldon Adelson must defend U.S. lawsuit accusing them o… https://t.co/Hh35lgA8jC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carloshsiso @HLaverdiereNPD the situation is deeply complex, I encourage folks to listen to this interview Scahill… https://t.co/DTNzG9vTNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rewatching the #FredRodgers documentary ‘Would You Be My Neighbor’ and feeling all the feels. Happy Sunday. Please… https://t.co/tO0jrR5iTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look guys, I don’t blame folks for trending #FakeMelania. Melania trolls Trump. Now she is being trolled. Hey Melan… https://t.co/UqvedLj3fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friends signed off on their first apartment the other day. A group of us helped them move in. So, so happy… https://t.co/Ci7Dk8G44j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Williamscanlon6 @DevonB324 Hey you how do you idiots possibly know if I have a man or not and I am definitely smarter than either of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianaComm @pablohidalgo Hi, I'm Christiana and I'm entirely reasonable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you elinkizumi for videotaping my swim yesterday and giving me suggestions to improve.  I know what good swim… https://t.co/fe2GkIeaxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBCHS_Broncos @SDPBCChoiceCTE #engineering academy students finding out how @SWAPBC processes recyclables in… https://t.co/c6X4y4Y47g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so much laundry to do. Normally I’d say I’d pay someone to do it for me but I don’t even have the money to do so 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I leave a mark on people, everyone who’s gotten close to me and no longer with me, still wish the best for me, they… https://t.co/6zkzHWzye6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Grayson!  He was only 14 days new when he came to visit our studio! #frisconewbornphotographer… https://t.co/d7I3Xm1rqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un muy feliz, productivo y bendecido Miércoles con el favor de Dios, cariños y bendiciones!!!            😘🤗🙏🏻❤🙋🏻‍♀🌹… https://t.co/MT4j2qZDIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) We need to lift the sanctions on them that are crippling their economy. 2) I thought someone from the UN already… https://t.co/zdWYZSugkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Libra_Scale1982 @WisdomisNow @TalibKweli @RealBlackMedia @AbeAbbott4 @dacw10 @nurse_divine @BlackKyleFraz… https://t.co/HKCWolwhgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITGeekCT I don't think your last sentence adds to your post. The rest of what you had to say was very clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArenBuchholz @ChrisMcNally_ @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome Good addition❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeriLeighMerrit @KateDahls @luvbourbon @jmjafrx @sejr_historian @JuliaGaffield @PhdRachel @ProvAtlantic… https://t.co/iVxhtvJBwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a notification for a cheap flight to Hawaii and Miami same week...I need to choose one and get out of a Vegas for a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughter. Sisters. And yes, the summer. Spring is on its way. Promise!!  Cannot wait for spring sessions!!  . . . .… https://t.co/G895wEPWmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGoldfarb @facebook @instagram @kerwinsp8 I was more surprised to learn that journalists leverage finstas for their work 😱😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got done w chapter 7 of Becoming and I did not know Michelle was Obama’s mentor during his summer internship. Cuteness overload🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Sr. Associate Logistics" at Harbor Freight Tools by asking for referrals. It's a gr… https://t.co/82E4ibPFSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[These notes from the students in Ms. Jackson’s class were the highlight of my week! #LHWolfNation https://t.co/KgHxawQ8Ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troyprevails Troy don’t give up keep going and remember why you started the band! See you in Cali:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyAnnia You’re not just stare at that picture of @ShawnMendes in his #Calvins it’ll be worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama woman who went to Syria, joined ISIS cannot return to US: https://t.co/SDbmp5sTrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @aupotterton for sharing this cautionary article about the impact of tax credits in AZ: “[AZ] tax credit… https://t.co/ysIDOWaZeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you about my favorite thing in life....being a mother 😍 https://t.co/F1gQiGbV8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch really got Hellen Keller and Anne Frank mixed @han__uh I’m screaming]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s about to go down!   Temecula Rod Run 2019!!! Come on by to our storefront location for some giveaways!  28475… https://t.co/eqGsy4hoR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Easter bunny hid gifts around the house. To find the gifts, we had to solve riddles. #MyEasterBunnyWillBe https://t.co/GSeoc4rtna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, this is why Melania has stepped forward again with her bullshit #BeBest campaign!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 1/2 price, no roots Amaryllis Rilona is blooming beautifully. 4 fully open and 4 more coming!  An orange beauty.… https://t.co/RzqWkQI2BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Housemedic181 He’s a Virgo. We r perfectionists. He takes great pride in what he does.  Nobody wants to learn that… https://t.co/vO9yfZ325J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to spend my night? Watching @FOX5Atlanta w/ @russfox5 @CYNNEFOX5 @jaclynFOX5ATL @DChandleyFOX5… https://t.co/CPd4jvQC9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyVeevo @AppleSupport This is happening to me too! Can you please let me know if you get a fix? Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo happy @tyhenrymedium is back on! Best show ever! https://t.co/kbwU8RquXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m “shook” as the kids would say. @WhatTheHelicon has never heard I’m Blue by Eiffel 65 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my baggy eyes could talk they’d tell you stories of joy, pain and self discovery 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro You look gorgeous. Congrats and wishes for much happiness forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[En la vida nos vamos a encontrar con personas que se aprovechan de la buena voluntad, la solidaridad y eso no debe… https://t.co/TQ5hz692UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join our fundraising campaign for Arele's Healing Fund at  https://t.co/D5goQXv2wZ via @wearecharidy]]></document><document><![CDATA[move over, mom jeans—bringing back the #momtattoo in Hebrew daintyaf fineline for this all you can eat sushi birthd… https://t.co/9I5BwzzEhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studio vibes with jeremy_l_carver thanks for stopping by + New merch dropping soon 💎⭐️🔮🙏🏽🔥 #Diamonddistrict… https://t.co/KDQzoG5phV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My break has been full of happiness and criminal minds , I’m so sad I have to go back to school tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[instagram got @kyliejenner &amp; her @kyliecosmetics #💰#👌 #😉 - #Entrepreneurs #Kardashians #KylieJenner -… https://t.co/uBkeh2aLHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelesteKellogg can't wait for Celeste posted a new show on @StageIt 😀 maybe anti-love songs???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch I finna went to jail fucking with his bad ass 😂😂😂 hyper ass just like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @PhillyMayor has proposed to make permanent the Office of Immigrant Affairs which assists undocumented immigran… https://t.co/8oxgNOLr7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga you leave me speechless. Your humbleness and beauty are breathtaking and I admire you beyond...❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hugest thank you to the #WallStreetJournal for featuring my bag in their March Fashion issue! I'm beyond honored th… https://t.co/RRbrHUos95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadoutnumbered3 @hummingbirddab @CNN And yeah... Considering you are an abusive conservative Christian, your paren… https://t.co/dpG0cYno3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, after the Cohen testimony, the Jonas Brothers have reunited, Miley is a guest judge on #DragRace, and there’s p… https://t.co/ICzxc9wOgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun add to the iconic @Bellagio Fountains #WelcomeToTheShow @ladygaga @parkmgm #vegas #BadRomance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoCoHowie @ThankYouKeyzus this is literally the second time the gin blossoms have come up in 24 hours. prior to th… https://t.co/4OO2u4Yqnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was this shirt made for me or was this shirt made for me? Stripes AND a grosgrain bow 🎀 (on my blog today!) @ Hobok… https://t.co/l2VS73aB4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher You always hit the nail on the head bring today’s women’s situations into common language and reality that ev… https://t.co/1mRbwUSPQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonmarie40 I’m going to Shask for brunch, meet up with me later maybe??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnip2020 #Truth. You’d have to be an avacado. Sayin’ https://t.co/dbRlYjhVmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The inside-the-restroom-stall info sheets in the women’s restrooms at my church are called the “porcelain post” so… https://t.co/vsDJA7H3oU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concernant les fusions des territoires de taxis à Québec, les taxis doivent garder à l'esprit que Uber et les servi… https://t.co/JYLxonKd0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my husband asks if I want froyo, I don’t ask questions! I just book it to the car 🙃 Happy Sunday y’all!  — Lik… https://t.co/Be65IYCkkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sloanybear @jonasbrothers I’m comin with, I’m coming with!!!! 🙋🏻‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lelllteee Igual mucha gente termina súper mal con sus exes y se entiende completamente, pero a veces se termina po… https://t.co/ckbVqUSZsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to get comfy!  #Princess #Hypnodog #Hypnosis @ Loews Hollywood Hotel https://t.co/vwFob7PzP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the actual CRAP. In what world is 15 years for killing a little old lady LENGTHY? Are they just taking a year… https://t.co/587ShBvhJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftchina @sdonnan Kind of funny from the folks who insisted on milk export restraints.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Away rotation for her 4th year of medical school.  Working in a women’s health/pediatrics clinic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fundapmom I ditched mine and just keep a note on my desk. I talk to the kids about their behavior and how to fix i… https://t.co/n7YGzKpn4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frithamarie @murphdogg29 @DissentingMind @TheRickWilson Thank you for that! It's a lonely road. Taking it one day at a time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntunicorn Open up your eyes shut your mouth and see , I'm still the only one who's been in love with me ....  😇👼… https://t.co/IPQuKH2joV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex-boyfriend told me his on &amp; off again ex-girlfriend would stalk my social media pages! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus is all the world to me,  My life, my joy, my all. He is my strength from day to day, without Him I would fall… https://t.co/1uCvlq0xNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Critical Care Physician" at Sparrow Health System? Applicant tracking systems look for spe… https://t.co/Bt1NTORHD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnsBible @DrDenaGrayson He’s such a liar; he is Epstein’s lawyer. He tweeted today he was only involved in th… https://t.co/lCzAmKBRBq]]></document></documents></author>