<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[TERAPIA DE MEDICINA CHINA *VENTOSAS* CITAS AL 6621329423  En qué nos puede ayudar las ventosas? La terapia de aplic… https://t.co/X8U9ziYGri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @thatsVeryKari @Starofthesea007 @FionaMorgan79 @CaththeWineLady @SteveKubota @joneill55 @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/mOnxM0hKHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of track is tomorrow! Can’t wait to get the season started on our new track! https://t.co/5QRSJxDS8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @FielderElem for having us this morning! #FielderPride https://t.co/h2ZvqWn3HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[After having completed the 200 mile distance I have to say it’s my favorite. I’m blown away. I didn’t want it to en… https://t.co/w1CEkISCt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t see the snow moon for the snow clouds. 🌨 But we talked to the moon anyway. 💁🏻‍♀️🐶🌝 #FullSnowSuperMoon ❄️🌕✨ https://t.co/MCjn4ydyW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t believe I get to marry this man 🤤 https://t.co/7bcFVreges]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rainbow Spring State Park in Dunnellon, FL https://t.co/6rUyMbC2A9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant wait to move into the apartment downstairs once it is nice and renovated to take bubble baths while listenin… https://t.co/o9n0xKmICO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taymakeusadrink Don’t even get me started on if they don’t perform Nick J is Off the Chain!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden and @BarackObama apparently agreed not to critique @realDonaldTrump when he first became president in 201… https://t.co/o0XnoWYesb]]></document><document><![CDATA[BecomeBetty Gives Thanks Giveaway- One winner will get a $50 Gift Card to Trader Joe's #giveaway #win https://t.co/XWbqnhjgS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing to ever happen to me #peporinigreasehole https://t.co/B08jJsiXHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards @lisarinna @TeddiMellencamp @doritkemsley1 admit what happen to the puppy was fucked up.Doesnt matter… https://t.co/FSwPHAU2Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this Valentine’s Day I’m playing myself the best album about love ever made: #TheDivineFeminine by @MacMiller. D… https://t.co/u4RtERFbJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen puts Jim Jordan in his place with brutal scolding https://t.co/bWOUSgT3he via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jetemetet @dazzlecarol @cas_33 @allyemmerson @lucretialive @lusciousvixen @feromoon @jaguarlogdrum Morning 🥶🥶🥶going back to sleep 💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I'm missing spring training by mere days, I'm still showing my @BlueJays pride! https://t.co/hMTGtOV1Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWalkingDead You mean “Should have GONE after Lydia”? No; not alone and not without a plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is up is down...what’s right is left.  Nothing makes sense anymore thanks to the left...#MAGA #KAG2020… https://t.co/9z6Z61cs47]]></document><document><![CDATA[growth and deepening the faith that has begun in us. We do not come to faith all at once. Indeed, a typical example… https://t.co/iJmfBdIbaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Got my MAGA hat today...wear it proudly. I am so scared the demos are so demonizing our… https://t.co/QJVtI5YNEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PACRadioShow @midlanderos @mirandalambert @ladyantebellum @KeithUrban @joshturnermusic @MidlandOfficial… https://t.co/kqhVKJ1cBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that move! Many are “not gonna’ take it any more” w/ TRUMP talking thru his hat! Rambling, even sing-song nons… https://t.co/xFbBdGeVXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué cosa más linda me llegó en el correo hoy, recetario dieciochesco de un fraile franciscano aragonés, editado por… https://t.co/vQVIMnVYAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst Love this show! Reem was the best to go first but, I did go to sleep worried about her. She inspires me… https://t.co/ohdh0DaLpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the visit @NUFBFamily Bad weather and all, thank you for the opportunity. @c2powell_]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trains, planes, and automobiles! (@ Santa Rosa - SMART Station in Santa Rosa, CA) https://t.co/69LwSlyL1y https://t.co/m8M8T5XeA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillLiedy @thehill He didn’t go there respecting the office. He went there insulting it, and what it stood for sim… https://t.co/VhmGgZDpIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariadorosario Que nao falem. Que imprimam e colem em todos os postes muros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieMcqueen11 @NELLY822 @OldCatLady57 @miamimama40 @morwennajh @hesterdiva @Shannon34625862 @Marylaw55555… https://t.co/hqXvkeL40Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kids are worth how much? These are the special tax breaks for parents https://t.co/nsIaz7YqjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what our country must stand up against. If we are wanting DJT to be held accountable, then any congressiona… https://t.co/Su1XREurv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[this kid is telling me that i’m so lucky bc it’s my TA period, and i’m sitting here rushing this letter for a schol… https://t.co/SybLlPJNQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think a 20 year old would be mature enough to walk her store keys into a store she worked at... not have… https://t.co/83csE3BQUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailBenzler @AkronWineGuru @chelelife @CaththeWineLady @TheSavvyChef1 @LoriMoreno @pietrosd @suziday123… https://t.co/SXimasdkSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed visiting @WaukeshaSTEM  Randall to see the @waukeshaschools FAB LAB and seeing Matt use the Top 2018  grant… https://t.co/h2qKxtRE0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our parents never approved of us when we were young,” he adds. But some things change. At Jolene’s grand opening i… https://t.co/gXSwDsPU0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBMorgan They should leave but no deals for them like using Canadian Passports, Currency  or Separation Payout… https://t.co/wfew1HTnzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TsarKastik Add substantive law and rules of procedure. The problem is multifaceted, as you say, formal rules and t… https://t.co/U9fGXOFdsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I dislike disrespectful people.  If I am showing respect I do expect it in return and can get crazy if… https://t.co/eRJeiAc8Sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live Free 🌷as a 🦋 Background art by @lucinda_aia @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/P43V5tdlBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it today with 2️⃣ matches!!   ⏰ 1pm vs Aurora ⏰ 3pm vs Loras 📍 Thornton Gymnasium, Aurora, IL 📺… https://t.co/vMBwWRzJkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué pedo con la gente que no ah visto RuPaul’s Drag Race ósea mi novio le encanta @JavyAgundez https://t.co/0ixP5WLX9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Internationalwomensday! Here’s a drawing I did to celebrate women and their strength 💪 #balanceforbetter https://t.co/7yZOq5h8kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching knife skills and making vegetarian sushi  #organic #farmtotable #chef #personalchef #cooking #classes… https://t.co/Sf6nT1gHyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great read! ❤️that this speaks to the role of social and emotional learning in all aspects of learning, student age… https://t.co/0h3sBmOYZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#INPhys2019 poster judging time.   @heidirgardner’s @ScienceOnA #Scientist pin took on a new meaning for my co-judg… https://t.co/8wXv2E2MDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovInslee @BillGates @BradSmi @amcauce @UW Sure I have a lot of questions from the American People why I support T… https://t.co/Sx8EC9nFcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardRod34 lolol I’m actually probably visiting Houston and/or San Antonio at some point this summer — dunno how… https://t.co/IdWiaMfR1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Curious about how many abortions YOU sponsored? Maybe we’ll find out in the Cohen hearings. #Hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shortsalewhiz @callmemrssachs There is The Creamery at Alkalai Flats (Downtown) https://t.co/VLR8F3uaZo There was… https://t.co/m8bAwtIC1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChrissyTeigen #JohnLegend @LisaVanderpump's #TomTomWeHoWeHo https://t.co/mSyF08A64n https://t.co/e6Wg7uL06F]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pessoa aproveitaaa e depois vem me mandar 1000 mensagens e ainda quer que eu respondo??? vsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bardach Team - BHHS New Jersey Properties https://t.co/pv6E8kbEQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Sports Center and just saw Dwyane Wade’s buzzer beater recap. Honestly made me really happy. Love the Kobe… https://t.co/2S8km20Xjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever they say #Mixologist on #vanderpumprules I remind myself that was what the #bartenders at the… https://t.co/BEbUUvjF8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's Datz It,Datz All schedule this week. #210foodies #foodtrucklife #foodtruckstalkers #foodporn https://t.co/hr80rwwRQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @maggieNYT 2 bad you don’t care so much 4 women-Rockstar “Drankin Henny, bad b*****s jumping in the pool/A… https://t.co/mQ7t3TxKnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Plus, an innocent man would know an investigation could clear him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbarann @KwikWarren Always gonna be that fool who brings up Taco Tuesday..on a Monday. 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my two favorite guys. ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/FdR5YilGtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to start making plans for a trip this summer, because I need a break from setx soon. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@power0879 Still developing their prefrontal cortex! One of the things I have to remember when working with kids wh… https://t.co/Hs1YnxgVUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikefarb1 @jack @Twitter I just Twittered them both about this problem! Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fun thing about Tyce and I’s wedding anniversary is that it’s Leap Day! So we can celebrate it, not celebrate i… https://t.co/FiEqOCviBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah won several races but ultimately didn’t place in the District Derby today. Proud of her for all her work desi… https://t.co/UmLqaUYyZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will not regret adding this video to your porn roster💪🏼💦   #Manyvids @ManyVids  https://t.co/RWydp4cuDD 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSWPrincess I’m a Tx Native.  Almost 65 yrs. There is no crisis. This is a total lie. THERE IS NO CRISIS. A wast… https://t.co/bY2k05GJHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHD2009 @JasonReynolds83 I quote RSB all the time, and recommend Jason's books regularly. Two of the best!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indy Boxer Malcolm "Unmerciful" Jones and Michigan's Emmanuel Sanchez announce at the weigh-in on Friday, February… https://t.co/U0AAC4YfrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday - At lunch time slowing down with some of my Anthem colleagues from our “SOMOS ARG” that for the past… https://t.co/S5aqIM3EWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics @CNN You make me sick, Mitch. Literally, you’re disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Using the Constitution to act = unconstitutional.   Yet more evidence that everyone… https://t.co/T1CyjdNza1]]></document><document><![CDATA[the moment i shat myself. @SamandColby @SamGolbach @ColbyBrock https://t.co/LPBdGY9r5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Trump_Train @realDonaldTrump @nytimes 5) corporate tax rates and maintain the tax rate for pass-through income… https://t.co/7rvKBG0SPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an article that appeared @crainsdetroit @OUWB medical school names interim dean https://t.co/AFtLVa4qCl via @crainsdetroit]]></document><document><![CDATA[RED RIGHT RETURN radio is on the air from 6a to 9a... tune in 91.3/92.1/womr.org @ WOMR https://t.co/kMUwR7TZbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ice picks and chill @ The Royal Cinema - Toronto https://t.co/WYxm4VNtAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coffeecrew @malahatdrive Did you at least stay in the right? #leftlane4passing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys! I’ve re-branded and spruced up the website! Head over to https://t.co/YSE4m7F7Mg and take a look around!… https://t.co/8KxIJMILt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Physics GIFs  https://t.co/XH47WELpiJ @coachwilsonHMS @AJScienceTeach https://t.co/PjVcStHPCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MRSROMYROM @BLACKGIRLSROCK @kencen @BlackGirlsCode @volunteerBGCDC Awesome! 💜 #blackgirlscode]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're a fine one to talk about cost overruns! How much have your Florida vacations cost the taxpayers so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewStimso16 @stradagangelica @AAvallones @DerekPa56710094 @RobRobbie7477 @BrownieJohnston @AintitMarvelous… https://t.co/0mTzxeuGHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Villain: *pointing sword at ventus, who's locked up in a cell* WHO ARE YOU Ventus: I'm ventus! But you can call me ven!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @johnbcrist last night. I didn't understand the bible stuff, but the rest was hilarious. If you are not religio… https://t.co/4gO80KCoAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh the #mnwild traded Charlie Coyle and it’s giving me hockey depression 😞 first Nino, now Coyle, me no likey. Who… https://t.co/juGtNpNC6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got your cookies! Come see us at Epps Bridge Walmart tonight until 8:15! #gshg #cookietime #girlscouts @ Walm… https://t.co/oD316AtOiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s doing the work? In Shared Reading, readers are supported by an experienced reader, their teacher!… https://t.co/CO0qq8Wlgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Though thy beginning was small, yet thy latter end should greatly increase.  -Job 8:7 #God’sgotthis #trustGod]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm guessing im guessing fat after all @ Lakewood, Ohio https://t.co/Uw39yHMVEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to get into nursing school and be too focused and stressed to think of anything else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I need to go to bed but really wish tommy was here I could use his arms around me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clarknt67 @maggieNYT Not true at all. Millions of her supporters would be thrilled if she ran again. But, we respect her decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TOMORROW ~ Just a reminder that our next 'No Uniform Day' will be tomorrow Wednesday, February 20th. If you have n… https://t.co/3dqT32DG5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to see you there!!! #austintexas #sxsw2019 #ledzeppelin #filmfestival @ Don Don Express https://t.co/JtslF4eFgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airport Limo Service (703) 459-9666 Call us https://t.co/ZHllVy7okX https://t.co/xn9gjcJO7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuppetofaMiscia @satinephoenix @deathbybadger @zacnaoum @vampiresnvino @DNDElise @Farore_DnD @ShimmerwindIsle… https://t.co/Yw2QGAfrJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sparkly, fluffy new snow ❄ Clear blue skies and crisp bright sunshine ☀ Perfect winter day!! #winter #snow… https://t.co/3YZJH4ZAz9]]></document></documents></author>