<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Two Thai days . Good things (@ Bangkok Square in Gainesville, FL) https://t.co/11EX4HphE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸… https://t.co/bmPXI49lLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all of these losers cheer at #TrumpFail to strike a deal with North Korea. If POTUS would’ve signed a bad d… https://t.co/3siwzWURl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to @NashCC's WNIA 89.1 FM for spinning tracks off Where You Know Yourself! Much appreciated 👍 #radio #newmusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_krames @AngelBigmac3039 @bsmith134758483 @Ravens You look dumb as hell commenting 6 times on a post about your e… https://t.co/pXZJbURY2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite game is an understatement: SimCity2000 was practically the only game I played, growing up. #Robinson4Phx8… https://t.co/85xIZsnKeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKaufmanGolf @jeffygolf @chambleebrandel @JeffRudeGolf @GOLF_com @GolfDigest @McLeanGolf @eamonlync @GolfWorld… https://t.co/azaD9tpuB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kausmickey But the basic trouble is caused by putting people out of work by automation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset lagoon views! . . . #spaceshipearthsunday #spaceshipearth #earth #futureworld #artfulepcot #epcot #epcot36… https://t.co/PWYvcdOjb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie_Masters29 I wish I knew how to use patreon, but that does sound like a good line-up]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tell my JH team this constantly.  They are 30-0 in last two seasons. “Do not settle for the level your at.  If yo… https://t.co/UevwALHONQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Belgian_Girl17 I'm still waiting on a good sale for it I'll get it then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_giggz I actually responded to the McCabe not standing up, but don't see it. In a nutshell, I said that it's amaz… https://t.co/iWqwdsOmRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRF_News @wendyknowler And if you’re a #mining engineer, you know what kind of #geologist you’ll want to be calling...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump Can we still "dumbass shame" or "infidelity shame" or "hypocrite shame" or....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Good for Tucker. Real Americans are tired of the freak’n left always getting away with using inappropri… https://t.co/7artx1Wiua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juankyAG CDLM ... que ladilla que digan que son tres y no digan quienes son ... 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing keynote to what has been an incredible, inspiring experience at #SBM2019! As a new SBM member and first tim… https://t.co/R8reV4gmhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mturyn I'm not criticising her plan. I'm just saying it's a bold stance that your first policy statement is to dis… https://t.co/7DwsyUEI6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty. …… https://t.co/CycTXK1bv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes. Couples struggling with infertility put A LOT of their time and energy into trying to have a kid - IVF takes… https://t.co/MLhzjIUpqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are here and checked in at New Balance Nationals. It’s a Business Trip  @lildashhhh @LkwdSchools  @LHS_ABOOSTERS… https://t.co/qxcDTc74wZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoJuice 🚱 sponsored kickback tonight 🗣 Good people and good vibes, invite only. DM a #NoJuice member for the addy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach O’Neil is a great man !! Blessed to have been around him since I was a youngster !! #goat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMZimmerman @DPRK_News all I'm saying is you would think it would be satire jokes about North Korea, which it u… https://t.co/OBZzDnTcX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman I hope; Once the #WallyFence is done, we will find a way as @HouseGOP to help @mexico with Humanitar… https://t.co/QXMegRvDlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching THE MEG and Rainn Wilson playing an Elon Musk type billionaire funding an undersea rescue operation REALLY… https://t.co/D9msJCuCeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this news hitting at once! 😩🙌🏽 I wasn’t expecting the stickers to drop today as well, still shaking you guys. T… https://t.co/qS8aE561ZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ctgjb with a career-high 20 points tonight. He’s 5-of-9 from three. Bulls lead 65-52. #USF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for @freizeartfair (@ New York Street Backlot: Paramount Studios - @paramountpics in Hollywood, CA)… https://t.co/cne65zvE1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drayyf Buying a keyboard and mouse for my PS4. Obviously the only way to adapt fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Being an Adult by Kim Na Young. So catchy! #kpop #singersongwriter https://t.co/i4CLG0VSay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Jumpman by Drake &amp; Future on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/bL2ed0yQsw https://t.co/UByAHe1JBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoughboyFresshh @Arvindparmar08 @Giants2019 @Patricia_Traina @cagiantsfan Exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr It wasn't a failure. It was a conspiracy! They totally succeeded in spreading the leftist lies that… https://t.co/ZXG7cAjj42]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible documentary by Dan Reed. #LeavingNeverland we always “knew” things went on at the “ranch” but di… https://t.co/EN2cxluWHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LillyTellez Tienes razón, no es cuestión de religión, de leyes ni menos de partidos políticos, es cuestión de conc… https://t.co/Za9hjqEwEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Heritage for hosting a great briefing with interns and coalition partners about @PepPublicPolicy’s… https://t.co/skJKczIDF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is what the ASSU petitioning form be looking like: https://t.co/AoHlZw6TvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sayomgwtf I actually love the original's aesthetics but I always found the resolution to be overly claustrophobic… https://t.co/oTfkdnbTVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is going to point to a surge on the border in the last few months to declare a crisis -- and then propose a w… https://t.co/Lb9KDJzrXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna be in this room alone anymore bro 🙄 this why I need a girlfriend so the ghost can kill her and not me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marwinGF9 win miss you Marwin. All the best to you and your family   We’ll all — @etaylordvm @HelenFrink… https://t.co/GG1UWR6wjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little bit later than I normally do this, but I’ve finally finished my Top 10 favorite films list of 2018. Prepare to be spammed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Bella Vista AZ at the Grind Session in Bowling Green.  They are LOADED!!!  Dominated 1st half over team from NY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time @RedbirdFB Junior Day.  Thank you @Coach_Spack and @CoachK_Stew for the invite. @DeepDishFB… https://t.co/0pdUchh9Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods James, You are the best! Never back down especially, when you’re right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion Williamson leaves Duke-UNC game with a knee injury  https://t.co/jvVWOi1Uor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 #1 Pink Floyd  The Wall   #2 Van Morrison No Method, No Teacher, No Guru  #3 @Neilyoung Live Rust #… https://t.co/5ZqtxZfW5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodSunday #JasonBirthdayLunch #At #OliveGarden @ Olive Garden https://t.co/bNoddGZyhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet @HFritzB was having chest pain the entire 10 minutes. https://t.co/vXaK1z3Pnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not joking, nor being a stubborn Thunder fan when I say this but this team is the BEST team in the league right… https://t.co/De11Dttxv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samuraihonor U so mad I’m win more tonight than ur whole tiny, miserable, Jap bank rolls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinaspirit1 @Shannon14220774 @stareagle @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Who’s doing your taxes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bearloga @marc_data Shout-out to my early datageek compadres who also had to do their own devops and data engineer… https://t.co/SBSl1HNn56]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂to me it’s just a game but to others idk. @Castro1021 @JamieODoherty this game ended up a tie. He was pissed. https://t.co/QolfPBOjvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette Yes. By refusing to report. I know hindsight is 20/20 but the #Steelers should have listed to… https://t.co/EYs2ng2TN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@straczynski If he traveled back to our time to get a job, that would explain a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valsthewoman @realDonaldTrump How about talking about how many children , now adults are affected? #MAGA… https://t.co/3rrnPaD6vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBTimes_Rays Worry about your Astros and stop crying about our Cy guy, better luck this year,  not!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theskrypclub_ @SteveFrenchInc @PeteBlackburn Probably the obvious trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexqgb “Situational awareness”. Where do people think HMDs came from ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lemmie guess if it was obama dude would have been executed publicly. https://t.co/6xQrXgm0Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_Eazy Lol. Can you like this post since I don't like Trump neither? Fuck him, he's Orange lol 😂 https://t.co/n8dJdfzqm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a real psychopath to watch a 45 minute highlight reel of the 2016 World Series of Cubs Indians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In memory of Uncle Frank @ Universal Chung Wah Funeral Directors https://t.co/keKxikMtiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤠Let’s raise the roof inside the Hoop Dee Doo 💃🏻 Had an absolute great time at the Hoop Dee Doo Musical Revue with… https://t.co/4IXnk7L8TQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @rayfineburg1 She should take the oath of office in a different country.  Far away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox @IAmSteveHarvey You'll always be GUN PORN BARBIE to me. The #HeresWhoToHateMedia audition girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning today we are watching mre reviews again https://t.co/wMePbDLglR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dahlin takes a flying elbow to the head. Philly announcer “yeah that’s a perfectly clean hit” #what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rolex7Michael @bukolasaraki You have fought a good fight. @OfficialPDPNig will still be in control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverInvests Which city and state? Need to start looking in that area for similar deals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[भजन संहिता 122:6-7   Awadhi Bible:     6 तू यरूसलेम मँ सान्ति हेतु बिनती करा।     “अइसे लोग जउन तोहसे पिरेम राखत… https://t.co/Itkfwxbcl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamKingLos That sounds like that's ALL on you!!! https://t.co/Mu0ZZdoo4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buildings continue to change hands downtown with the sale of Oracle Centre/International Centre for $74M… https://t.co/H16D2NpUuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we talk about how damn beautiful the new iPad pro’s are?! Ugh the squared edges are fucking H O T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey les Flyers game as started. Fighting for there lives with a start like that wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbucky24 @SuchockiJason @tahececlayborn @Onsomethin @CigarChairman @Investnoir @keepmovin2019 @NathanCaliendo… https://t.co/JCC7KFQJMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HafdisHuld Looked like you were having fun.  Just gotta love that girl in the middle wearing coveralls.  Hope you… https://t.co/woBMa7VLBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAFFleet This was a tale of 2 halves. SD looked like a completely different team in the 2nd 1/2. Bad play calls, p… https://t.co/o65UDiPMuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppcorp Good morning and happy Monday buddy! I'm wrapping up another overnight so off to bed for me soon. 😁☀️👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YungPicante The pain is gonna be what the pain is. She’ll go through this like everyone else. Nothing you can do b… https://t.co/kw6AEj0afD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure the girl I liked a year ago got plowed fourteen times by now... good for her lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I can't decide what I'm looking forward to seeing more, the unique architecture or that spicy tasty food in fr… https://t.co/WNm43b2yHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a Boston Uprising fan but the silver lining is your team remains the only one to ever have a perfect stage… https://t.co/NjEdKao6D6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I say I want to be a musician I don't mean the colloquial "performing in front of people, recording songs, and… https://t.co/SNzNEFgZiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran 7 miles, then immediately after I ate a 482 gram sweet potato as a side for dinner &amp; that bitch fucked me up in a real good way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/mYN7l1EaQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah another run. @ Shannon Brewing Company https://t.co/6KmomLYcL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two have great chemistry together. I hope they make more videos. Maybe I’ll start to watch Unbox again.   Sho… https://t.co/d1jVuDOEw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storing energy as hydrogen gas. Could this be the ultimate solution? https://t.co/aqeiIN02HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get in line to loose, we don’t want you back, our jails are too full also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana es un gran día! Estamos emocionados por ver lo qué está pasando en casa.   Te esperamos a las 12pm para escu… https://t.co/drGHD7T2Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_Cwood Biased Sports Opinion: I want yo mans. https://t.co/1gVfHVnx4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonMooreENT @AmberRoseRevah @benbarnes @jonnybernthal @giorgia_whigham @J0SHSTEWART and all the writers thank yo… https://t.co/zWk87T7gTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s boss,Vladimir Putin, is currently advising #Trump, his dictator in training, not to step down if he isn’t r… https://t.co/eXdTApfUor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinkedIn - I don’t really know what a “soft skill” is but I’m 100% certain I don’t care. Stop making me watch your… https://t.co/Xygv7rX0uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelendezTMZ Not sure why ... it wasn't even close. Dodgers won one game and needed 18 innings to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisIsPissed  I try to predict what color dress Stephanie RUHLE on MSNBC is going to wear every day. About 3 hours… https://t.co/2hkWP2sPZM]]></document></documents></author>