<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DeeboF22 @JudgeTorre @Babchik @EvCoRadio @AGBerg12 @UCONNAl @hereslauren @dannykanell @BdalFal @CMarq23… https://t.co/lIhfBoEIEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKBHD Yo man you seen this ish? This is my home town btw.   https://t.co/Hc71BoIKvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrianfallon what do artists receive for their songs being streamed thru Apple or Spotify. Don’t need exact numb… https://t.co/hdxlrIDGsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 8 my uncle gave me a tape of monkees episodes that he recorded off of MTV. It was one of my favorite thi… https://t.co/ckb9MKSqqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[A better pic of Rick Travis, 66. He’s been missing from his home in Spencer since around 2:30 pm on Monday. If you… https://t.co/KAqtde9QAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Wow CBS! Your “news” reporting has become as desperate as the pathetic journalistic integrity you are clin… https://t.co/IysRuGDOq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[YelaWolf "Mtn Dew Mouth" Freestyle | TM3 Coming Soon https://t.co/PLx2roYIGT via @YouTube @Yelawolf 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[My awesome salad 💯💯💯✅✅☝🏻☝🏻☝🏻☝🏻😋😋😋😋 @ Alexandria, Virginia https://t.co/h9j35rzHyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davejsports @glennconsor I'm loving the way #Wizards are executing the game especially the 2nd unit showing up als… https://t.co/VzoS8PTkDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure there’s a better teacher of the game than @JohnBeilein. What a great interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our students at district speech today at Lincoln Southwest!  #rollstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmandoGarciaC @GonzalezAcido @rocionahle @JimenezEspriu Claro, aquí los esperamos en lo que los alcanza la 4T. 😁🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWVerret @dcEmerald @TokyoWoods What problem do you have with consumers who have been abused by the financial syst… https://t.co/ApPtBtMXnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC like it’s basically scientifically proven. 😂😂😂😂😂😂 Giddyup horseface get THOH with your nonsense. Go on and spe… https://t.co/DmvPfOvRBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a strange coincidence, there was a power outage at the city hall mall today and then this should occur tonight 🤨… https://t.co/h29hcPFAUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “Alexa, play Baby Shark.” Alexa: “playing Baby Shark...” Then Mom and I def just did the ‘Baby Shark’ song and… https://t.co/YGVHn4ipUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumphreyBookIt @Gator_Alum When you penetrate that deep, you should be rewarded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayr8r @ScooterMagruder Jerry’s got plenty under the table cash for that ... ain’t worried bout nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waxmonkey @washingtonpost Go research how hard it is to get here through asylum. That's what the f it has to do wi… https://t.co/o6rotCaChP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwinMadrigal You need to see the threads @KenJac puts out. It’s terrifying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great episode! Thank you for sharing what has become a way of life at Grayslake North!@GrayslakeNorth… https://t.co/mhwiFAcmgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyxtopher @SenFeinstein @NBCNews Saying "It won't pass" isn't engaging on substance and she doesn't offer her a… https://t.co/PCHQgb3erx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS 😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬 #TMobileTuesdays + #Contest 😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬😬… https://t.co/eo5C4A5EMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinadesalvoA @ddale8 @matracaberg The Dreaming Fields is still one of my favorite albums.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ourtastytravels Q4.) I’d start with some chocolate covered strawberries and then a nice steak. #FoodTravelChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[So to deal in deception Is for these so called Representatives of are nation to give free range on babies that live… https://t.co/RckHp7k7Zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[A monument to celebrate #SiliconValley will signify to the world where application of #tech was combined, marketed,… https://t.co/Cd2bQPpM9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to ask the Senators to create a committee that works together with FBI to investigate the theft of the mone… https://t.co/kmGbtECDZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ki_daNymFo Try it out and let me know how many minutes you could go before the tap out 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gangsterhealth @philosophrob Winning by millions of votes is “rigging” now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK Hahaha.....The ear joke was a give!🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 Lend me your ears! https://t.co/E3Fa8F82kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess @RideRTD was late on paying this months electric bill for its light rails...Never fails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucken cop flashed his bright ass lights at me so I can turn on my lights 😑 like why you trippin diiickkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this news to you? Stay current with all the news from ASU and earn Pitchforks toward great rewards! https://t.co/0vAzFXolmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christofow @nadinetkat @citizen_truth Need dis. (Going out past 9 pm) #coffeeposse https://t.co/YNBmSv9AxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the second to last upgrade. Soon I will slide my X51 R2 aside for my first custom PC Build. NVIDIA.. #1060… https://t.co/4q3u7hKYsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunattwood How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/jfSw0XH62t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Antonio Brown era in Buffalo was short lived, which is a shame. The Bills are literally the most spiteful place… https://t.co/5d38bsJqzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treeman0703 @Bharper3407 Yes Phil's dropped the Ball could have clinched the deal last Sat....Phil's came up small in Free Agency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melaleuca @US_FDA @SenFeinstein @IdahoStatesman @TruthinAd @RBReich @FTC @dsa @Forbes @POTUS44 @RollingStone… https://t.co/SA2pThEbHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitch Livestream | Metro Last Light Redux – Part 3 – Finale | Xbox One. Watch Chris (MrRevaN7) return to post-apoc… https://t.co/tskqi57nrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to do some 1:1s out of the office today. Maybe our most productive yet. https://t.co/gx3N79QcGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sorymadridista @tildegm @roberantolin @realmadrid @AlvaroBenitoV @QUINTERORADIO @Quijote_cuerdo @WOSfanatic… https://t.co/gKwhJhSisw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a fan of writing out actions for users within an interface. Design should provide enough context and inform… https://t.co/2ye1X5RVPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solangeknowles will never be @Beyonce  and that is the best thing ever. #WhenIGetHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re to come I made a choice to strive for a look of pride in my best friend’s eyes. I made a choice to heal my br… https://t.co/KbrsDd2twG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics so what Trump really meant when he said you'll get the best people to work for him what he meant to sa… https://t.co/oRRCmrpeS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writeorama @JacquiDelaney @storybywill @l_stone @JustinTrudeau @anitavandenbeld @LapointeLinda @liberal_party The… https://t.co/zIjMJpeLfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Sabino and Pusch Ridge Christian Academy, who are located 22 miles apart, won last night, yet the AIA is still m… https://t.co/yfmLCCdjOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[इब्रानियों 9:27-28  Hindi Bible:     27 जैसे एक बार मरना और उसके बाद न्याय का सामना करना मनुष्य की नियति है।]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not Charlie’s bed!! #aunt🐝sbed #aunt🐝 #sleepy #naptime #😴 #fatso #ownsthehouse #spoiled @ Pomona, California https://t.co/KlZaAuFtdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night's incredible sunset!  #texas #sunset #texassunset #txsunset #texassky #sky #txsky #clouds #photography… https://t.co/j0616ErjhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealtblake Meaning the input given will taken seriously and taken as direction moving forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexanBasketball lead Palo Duro 31-26 at the half!! LETS GO TEXANS!! @WCMSports @hoopinsider @Gosset41 @ihss_dfw… https://t.co/w5BVroAqEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical liberal nonsense! They can't beat President Trump , His policies are succeeding so the Liberal left must us… https://t.co/Sjir3ELVD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great students!  Great athletes!  These are the student athletes we want representing @SJCPrep! Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[After hearing these stories, @azcentral then compiled data from the state Charter Board. It showed regulators who a… https://t.co/Da6c6ANlAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal never know? Trout might be right in front of the phils face in 2020 &amp; we might not even  know it? https://t.co/qJzbIUfJTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdchambers25 @LindaEMc @OCSD1 @AuthorPaulHsu @mattgaetz @PublicSchoolSup @Mel_Ponder @SenatorGainer Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Since this is OBVIOUSLY coming to Florida next, what about poor people with PTSD who use medicinal marijua… https://t.co/f4MbdTKTQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in 2005 I shot the photos for the @tocfest DVD. This photo of @gerardway of my.chemicalromance and Bert McCrac… https://t.co/y8BKy477w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm old enough to remember when Republicans would have been pissed if a President sided with and defended  Dictator… https://t.co/51cNk9PV7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump force is probobly one of the worse games I have EVER played. Wow. Terrible terrible design and the gameplay is… https://t.co/TjD5voXCop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Rutherford What no Jordan Bone he should be on their he is the bast Point Guard in the SEC 🏀 GBO 🏀💨🍊]]></document><document><![CDATA[BB-8 zaps people. You can’t zap that many people and not be punished in the final episode. I can’t see how he gets… https://t.co/2TYdnH9vnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Raiders could upgrade defense in free agency - San Francisco Chronicle: Raiders could upgrade defe… https://t.co/StF7J4pwdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst I want to see @sbledsoe that dude went to the end twice give him another shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edsblogtw1tter @TRHLofficial I can't... because hate those as well. 😂   Solidarity high five ✋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregQuinnFCO @alissa_784 @CommonwealthRow To the natives he appeared to be a God.. as fire blazed from his hands...😂😂🇬🇾👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how now all i see is Voodoo type set up s on Jason video . Low green days hugging moving average after remount s .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna live in a world where a moment can exist to where I write my number on a stranger’s arm who just oh-so-sexily hit on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[The absolute cutest dog ever , besides my dog of course! https://t.co/D5IipqHenB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabino ends half on a 12-0 run to take a 49-27 lead to the locker room. #AZPreps365]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamuppl @JamilSmith Yes, there is a serious book about this triangle, which had replaced the British. Trade, finan… https://t.co/IapYixStnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Raleigh: moderate rain, 47°F 100% humidity, wind 6mph, pressure 1019mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanamStyle @JohnBrownlow @Stig_Ofthedump I’ve only done that once or twice. Feels weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Introduce a little anarchy. Upset the established order, and everything becomes chaos. I'm an agent of chaos. Oh,… https://t.co/kQtolk1Wis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christi196155 @SecPompeo The troubles began in the absence of sanctions. I don’t think they helped things but this… https://t.co/MheDtZhh9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Gavriels1: “Happy #InternationalWomensDay!Thank you to all the women in my life who... cleared the path for me.Ch… https://t.co/TWf7J0NBgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosalynTravels @kerbieaddis @MagpieLibrarian @erinroseglass Why such limited hours?  (As others have said, there's… https://t.co/TpT147B8x3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex @djrothkopf Interesting. Can you list countries producing the most pollution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimRocks @ersle @Barbi_Twins @PeterAskin1 @catsrangels2 @Mybabykitties @straysneedlove @MeowMiya88 @BrendaPerrott… https://t.co/hZlV7PgmoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMcKenna53 @lesbianweisz @missbriehaven I have to say im not familiar with the men. If men are in anything i watch they are bottoms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dynamo defense played well first half, fell apart around 70’ and allowed two goals in five minutes   Still love y’all @HoustonDynamo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwmangum @BigBoyVol Probably went to have coffee with Anthony Wiener who was released from prison yesterday. https://t.co/IqHWVz8XYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCarlsonShow Seems I'm the top Google result.  Hard to imagine ever being able to measure it for certain, though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youngseebi Wherethetreesmeetthefreeway Didntyouhearroadsareclosed Goldenchevrolet Rocks/keepawayfromkeyboard Calci… https://t.co/qpFtLkejsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuandoerapavo @Edurodriguezg Trabajaba con mi amigo Vicente D Alessandro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thing I've noticed was that when I made my ADR on the MDE app, despite the phone number field already being o… https://t.co/w6jxeGaOke]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shiraz #thepundit #loveowls @ Total Wine &amp; More https://t.co/JCuqapPHgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jokacolaclassic I’ll be your ex husband. I’ve already got one ex wife, might as well collect more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to get rid of @realDonaldTrump ASAP!! This POS is dangerous to America!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my birthday. Check out this amazing wool blanket my wife gave me! I didn’t know this existed. So cool! Ooh… https://t.co/2NORUPwCXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 🚨 #NextFriday 🚨 🚨  Join me and my #hysterical #comedian friends for a night of #NoHoldsBarred #VerbalAbuse!  Link… https://t.co/5lld9r7qr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HowieCarrShow @TheJusticeDept  @realDonaldTrump @VP Too bad we don’t have an Attorney General]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerronEShort I have been following you for quite sometime. I listened. Check this out....  https://t.co/HBbCRt62IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllAboutWills @HuffPostEnt @yashar If you can think that after watching that doc you really must like defending ch… https://t.co/KNTq9biup8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I'm doing another #openmic in #astoria. Show is free so u have no excuses! Come lol with me or at me, just… https://t.co/vAOr50BJup]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do u have a dream and someone from ur past like 15 years ago is in it? What does that even mean?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i always tweet modymay things but then i realize my cousin follows me and im lashov so i delete them]]></document></documents></author>