<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[From this morning's @VNewsUV: Thetford girls hold of Oxbow's Cinderella magic in Saturday's D3 championship game wi… https://t.co/QPs2KBpAMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it the Republicans always seem to think they know what God wants and how is it that it's so often the aligns… https://t.co/QwyQBx5xAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trendon Watford beats the 1st qtr buzzer with a 3 and its 21-4 @mtnbrookhoops over Vestavia @AHSAAUpdates @abc3340]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a bar with amazing food, service and music near by @ Pioneertown, California https://t.co/au3efecNYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#parents #glamshot #palmies #cuties #vacationmode @ Palm Springs, California https://t.co/dYcSdegVId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robertfritz33 @WassmannBill @Bassin_Away @cauzin_trouble @LowellMiller17 Whoops😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuba Rushford is closed today Monday, February 25 due to lack of visibility. @crscienceteach @deisel68 @RalstonK… https://t.co/mn6EjnbMXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because, sadly, it’s not news. We’ve been watching this crap for three years. It may be getting worse but it’s not… https://t.co/pa1UphS46R]]></document><document><![CDATA[steven hitting the hand sanitizer after someone questionable buys items with cash https://t.co/Iz4ZIaoz9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀19-6A Academic All-District🏀 ▪️Henley Beisert 🔹Sarah Holson ◾️Chelsea Huynh 🔹Domo Lombard ◾️Kailee Mann 🔹Katie Mas… https://t.co/0I6H4fTLoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read and see in order how Trump and family friends conspired to break the law. What he has done thru out his life.E… https://t.co/Nm7YI2x5A0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbiRatchford Yes, this may sound crazy but it works. Fill up a cup of water about 75 percent full. Then drink from… https://t.co/ddBDGKHX55]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the time I took the stage tonight, it was after 9:30. I was sure everyone would be gone or asleep. That was not… https://t.co/7FfjKlBaxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listos en CUAUHTÉMOC 👍🏻 nos vemos con OMEV A.C. https://t.co/iGW23kJg8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg I am looking for a job in the computer science field.  Do you have any recommendations?  Thank you, pal. --Phillip :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klemmett_r @allisonpearson @christopherburd sorry twitter typos can't correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official the best month in sports. March Madness can’t get here fast enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_Thompson @AirFranceFR The fuq is wrong with him..lol! I know flights get warm... that's why I fly in shorts… https://t.co/B7U7amnBgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We like to give back!   #AtlantaCommunityFoodBank #PaternityCourt #CouplesCourt https://t.co/ZR0oerKLD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really... 🤷🏼‍♂️  Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/LJcyxSJP2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shortest Way Home is officially a New York Times Top 10 Bestseller!  South Bend’s story is speaking to people. Well… https://t.co/icDB3FswUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bandeauxx i mean rugby the same thing its a team sport and a HARD TEAM SPORT like so team  theres a stupid kind of… https://t.co/jBJyGjT64l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamoniJones414 So was the one with his sacking cabin in the wilderness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t DX getting inducted to the HOF make HBK and Rick Rude two time Hall of Famers? #WWEHallOfFame #2ringsforrude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeySweetTweetz I think the joke was missed lol, but yeah, you should be good]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LeavingNeverland will be the first film to win an academy award for a robot. That drone put in more work than anyo… https://t.co/dd1fcP3kdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building community during play rehearsals this week🎶 https://t.co/gxcqRmAdse]]></document><document><![CDATA[PC fans heading for the exits with more than 4 minutes left! Ouch and yikes. #heartandsoul #charactercounts #pcbb… https://t.co/apqnxaxMK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMichaelKay  looks like Will Ferrell from the movie step brothers. @TMKSESPN @TMKSonYES  @Rosenbergradio  @DonLagreca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethBehrs @TheNeighborhood @cbstv @hank_greenspan Loved, loved, LOVED watching this episode!!!! Thanks for what you do, Miss @BethBehrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There can b Airstrikes, Drone Strikes and Tomahawk Cruise Missiles in Syria. #Syria]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lady was on the phone rn talking about how her kids not vaccinated should I be scared]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhhhhh, Melisandre what gives you the right to utter those words??? How???? Dare??? You???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastWord @Lawrence @Hickenlooper Hick was not ready for this interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win tix to see Metric this Thursday at the Crystal Ballroom! @monqui Enter here ---&gt; https://t.co/0M4H0q6yvw /]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerbums @jasonintoronto @QueensberryW1J @frenchnneed4 @PozitiveVizion @markneefuzz @Kentfitness01 @3two1life… https://t.co/8GDJNxaOCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#letmemotivateyou got that run in tonight. I'm getting better, health wise...but I rolled my ankle. Slowed me down,… https://t.co/FycOllduIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsLyndee_LPS asked me to clean out my cooking equipment from her classroom (I use her space on Tuesdays) As she w… https://t.co/tIiJ6re22F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of 3 with @BernerChiefs. Nothing like smiling faces and smart questions to jump-start the week! Thx… https://t.co/NPoCbDnnCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottParkCO @Austen Why would a woman not be most qualified?  The two goals are NOT mutually exclusive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect line:   “the dickheaded solipsism that emerges when you are sixteen, restless, and convinced that you shoul… https://t.co/eVih5bmAVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow Night’s #CONCACAFCL quarterfinal for the @HoustonDynamo is a huge one! Get your tickets and go support the… https://t.co/cQH7aoM9yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianwordenBW I did not see any man hating in the movie, infact she work with Nick Fury.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVED hanging out with the @Peach_Rays tonight!! Y’all are amazing!🍑❤️ #SundayFunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add a trust fund baby and you’ve got my worst Hell’s Kitchen nightmare!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerpGrad01 @WTA @Naomi_Osaka_ Kyrgios has been asked that many times. I don’t have a dog in the fight but it has definitely happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoicePremiere great night last night how’s your mouth hole?? LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rashida Tlaib another trump hater fishing for things.  They don’t care about Americans, their constituency. How sad!  She can’t even speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jS1IsKHYPO  @SenatorRounds is just #OBTUSE as the idiot criminal @realDonaldTrump. Really? Paid off po… https://t.co/jiBkK20cXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi sobrinita de un año va a cada rato a buscarme a mi cuarto en Houston:( jajaja ya la extraño]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing day on set, of the Black Grove feature length film. For the other place productions. Here is my costume and… https://t.co/XCwHG4QGNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FootballVines @nachopla95 That was a better attack than anything Los Blanco's produced]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun little trip to the @GeorgiaAquarium today 🦈🐢🐳🐠🐡🦐🦀🐟🐋 https://t.co/UPhaavOHly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDonScouting @DFF_RyanB @DFF_Lukas @tonycars10s @AtillaTheHuhn_ If Penny shows up fluffy again this year, or even… https://t.co/Ca9QfqcnXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chopper11Pilot @WPXITraffic Rt 28 in your picture looks like a river of Lava]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan360Smith @TheBish75 Lol but I like my profile pic better than @TheBish75 too bad the “free chicken for everyone” didn’t fit :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is ridiculous! No version of A Star Is Born can exist in multiple cuts! I won’t hear of it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If so, then why is my account lower than it was? You December shenanigans took 19% off the market.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmorfina Equivale a cortarle de un lado para pegarle del otro... ¿me equivoco?]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Any time it’s hot in Pittsburgh* Pittsburgher: “It wouldn’t be that bad it weren’t so damn humid”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah hell, here is an update. Still a fair trade off https://t.co/hACJ8yb2OE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making mistakes is the inevitable result of going outside of your comfort zone. They are a sign of progress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeepingFlag @hottubhouse @Alyssa_Milano I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presid… https://t.co/lX6h1pGmB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was one of those folks who got MASS EFFECT: ANDROMEDA and quickly gave up due to all the glitches. Anyway, I s… https://t.co/PFEOWBx3oK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaMaier3 Yes, that’s a good point about age and it’s effect on metabolism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paxton walks 2 and gives up a hard hit out to Yankee killer Kevin Pillar in his first inning as a Yankee...Squirms… https://t.co/cVmMgYNxHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like Greya Van Vleet go ahead and favorite this so I can unfollow you]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What’s my question” from the @UNITEDA1RLINES gate agent?   Why am I still flying you?   @JetBlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay here's something i'm mad about before I go to bed: Bishops United Against Gun Violence has a project where the… https://t.co/YFnTaweSNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ancomrade Oatmeal chocolate chip is the way!  .... will not touch an oatmeal raisin cookie ... looking at it hurts my stomach]]></document><document><![CDATA[The red head and I are kicking it at the Pink concert tonight. Our last hoorah in NC!!! @ Time Warner Cable Charlot… https://t.co/mMdTQkHL4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryce_Cluff Ride or die...   Seriously though, you coulda taken a sick day....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ The Original Thunderbird Steakhouse and Catering https://t.co/LvyMNKzCF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjhickman @Bucktailes @1MonsterMission @D_David89 @historyinmoment Night C.J.  HAGN ✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never heard a bitch say “reciprocate” until 2019. You trendy grammar hoes probably don’t even know what that means smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😯 Jason Witten is coming out of retirement to return to the Cowboys  https://t.co/VKpk1ICXeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to our four shooters in the 3 point contest tonight at Glenbard West at 5:30: JB Baptista, Jonny Bey, Sam… https://t.co/C2Udgrq7aH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianelyssa @AOC @IlhanMN No. Anyone, regardless of their immutable characteristics (such as race) is capable of ra… https://t.co/JpYdkDY9si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luego pienso qué habrá un día donde tengamos qué ir al estadio sin ti y la verdad no quiero qué llegue ese día]]></document><document><![CDATA[.....the (14 year old) victim had been living with her for two weeks....The victim's mother told investigators she… https://t.co/D3mfo3ePO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottkubie How else can young people have exactly the same experience I had watching Donnie Darko?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elguapo64 @shylohg @BreitbartNews We don't care what you put in your mouth, but watch what comes comes out of it bitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[on in the world and some of it through the porous Southern border so to be fair let's treat everybody as you sugges… https://t.co/0KESun47m3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieSimoni @Ash_Baylor @WTNH Good Morning 🌞 from Wooster Square where it's Winter wonderland! #woostersquare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachGelb Notice Kenny Rosenthal isn't engaging much in this Harper Rumor Mill like Heyman, Nightingale and Olney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We created a catapult” is the best thing I heard about airplane design this morning.  #aeroeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehorrordork @Jessica_R1993 Maybe I should reply to Michaels messages?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBandJacque The legal parts of it. And raising a 142 LSAT to a 179 with a 20 second study montage]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's funny to see female's posting all these love things, and how they want this and that. But yet you look at the… https://t.co/OfGujhOWHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[HMU if interested in a Bonnaroo ticket for only $250, that’s roughly $100 off the current price!  #bonnaroo #sale… https://t.co/mwm464LKYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost time for the sparks!!! @ Dr. P. Phillips House https://t.co/La46DJHXiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secndnture you guys better #run. @KylieJenner is going to put that 1B to work. @jordynwoods is not even a speed bump in her $$ game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyD1070 @JMV1070 Is the back row shootout going to be just 1 lap runs or 4?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielr62049568 @danielr62049568 the Pistons are the hottest team in basketball right now @ESPNNBA. I would not co… https://t.co/kmLJAnhEco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeleneStJames Had Hope's for him but never worked out. No goals until the last game of the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outfox20 @NYPost_Mets No you just make foolish statements and expect people not to think you are a moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[A los 10  años en España ,Argentina y Brasil les dan solo el balon.Los entrenamientos se basan con el balon.Mientra… https://t.co/S0zTAGMaQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please do not rename Yankee Stadium to Amazon Prime Stadium. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro the thought of me turning 20 in two days blows my mind. Like how in the hell am I already 20 life is crazy that’s all I got to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @SainzSainzz @xaidrafox @emilymenaxo @MsKimberLeeXXX @slutsaucekhloe @AlexisMonroexxx @thetanalea… https://t.co/mtnkztIlf6]]></document></documents></author>