<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@anylaurie16 @StormyDaniels @warriormama1019 Laurie, this whole thing is on you, but you should take the trump vaca… https://t.co/rlEUmh0s1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Trump Supporters: “HAH you heard Mark Cuban is gonna run for President ? What a joke.”   Me: https://t.co/UF5YMzxV2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[If hangings would just come back into law,we would see a change, in the criminal Society..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarioDiBattista He didn't stupid his secretary dose it.  If you had a life you wouldn't be wasting your time typing your.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FanMorningShow Carr is getting up there, in terms of being a QB.They don't have much of a running game.  Question:… https://t.co/KJxA8I0Tya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @WhiteHouse @greggutfeld @IngrahamAngle @michellemalkin The words of a traitor? Turncoat? Conv… https://t.co/TTYZZ5ffbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austin_walker18 @brodyadavis He called that ridiculous tech on Joel Berry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoneWith45 @Villane39221507 @PatrickRandall @psychdr100 @crooksandliars Our Buddy says yo https://t.co/1okgEwN3aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sailboat Spritzer by @purebrewing/@gunwhaleales at @TheBeermongers — https://t.co/eUol2Muj2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston Cosmo, Luxor &amp; NYNY keep the best air quality. Only 3 places I stay now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsBoyTony bruh, you sound like you dont give a damn at work today Haha.  It's how I'm spending my last day at work, today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shonduras I love that I can watch these cool peeps axe throwing while I’m feeding a baby. #gottalovetwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to the most wonderful woman I know . My rock , my soulmate , my wife and my best friend , I l… https://t.co/M0TnrF31dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rough country 4 inch x series lift. Life is good! https://t.co/U1uoLBdldv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does my boy have the nastiest Euro under the age of five? My goodness. Already got 6 offers and he ain’t in Pre… https://t.co/0GXP7bQ8Qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You lie!.  You are a racist! Why do you hate brown people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilverGaray18 @LuisMondragon24 You mad cause arsenal are below our teams in the epl and isn’t in UCL 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sama_Gautham Kaallu nokkamantara enti Asalu fielding cheyakunda Aaaadikem pani akkada Lazy fellow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClimateAus The Joint Chiefs of Staff declared Climate Change a national security threat years ago. U may find this… https://t.co/M8x8iytTmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #blockchain #technology made a real revolution in the IT industry and in other important fields as healthcare,… https://t.co/1LKR0FtAZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this kid can stay outta trouble and keep his head on straight, he will be a DJax type deep threat. Hopefully tha… https://t.co/ywH1AhG48n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabbyFFXIV @YshtolaCat @HealinIsYoko Both of y’all empty your bags into mine https://t.co/1QYBOMxPuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Westminstergold Have y’all ever done a version of it is Well with my soul ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about some milk with your whale tails? 🐮 🐳 #cream #twotone #white #mixedmedia #modern #metal #epoxy #resin… https://t.co/nXON8hEj1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Race and class are intersecting. Thanks for the good thread @briebriejoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBaileyVO @KariWahlgren @GreyDeLisle @tarastrong @AbbyTrott @RachelKimsey @kimberlydbrooks @Julie_Nathanson… https://t.co/jSs1E2cQj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to wish our son good luck today as he plays his first real high school game of his freshmen season. We wish… https://t.co/W9tIFVFBFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yas! This is a good move for her. So excited for her comeback and another Demi tour!!! ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sactown_Rise @TeamJuJu HAAAA!!!!!!!............STEELERS GO 3-13 next year, Ben suks and just lost his #1 wr nuff said!!😁👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little did she know what was awaiting for her today #chigi #spaday https://t.co/fNEdFNec6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man works tirelessly to make everyone happy regardless of self. In the end no one is happy including self]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mvanolli não sei até que ponto pode ser besteira, mas sobre a parte do chico xavier é verdade, já li isso tem pelo menos 1 ano e meio, 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dillard 2020 WR Raphael Williams @Poppi1k has earned an offer to #The UNIVERSITY OF PIKEVILLE! @247recruiting… https://t.co/5ljSPGR7Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilikeridebike @cspanwj You need to go back to school.   The Preopolicies are anti fascist.  Socialism and fascism… https://t.co/hYkvplws5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCoopJR27 @theaceofspaeder   true shooting % LeBron 58.7% MJ 56.9%  eFG% LeBron 54.1% MJ 50.9%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why aren’t there more themed anthologies containing 4 or 5 short novellas? I think those would be really popular. I… https://t.co/IJzNibuMit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Hey @josh_smith8 with the walk-off  2rbi knock... @LSUbaseball stays undefeated at #TheBox! #WalkOff #Tigers https://t.co/QaO75GwJ91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Banana?  I am very tired.. I never had a chance to sleep too much but I'm tired.. and obviously you are not gonna t… https://t.co/8s1X7imyOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcook793 @arieljatib @tim_mecklem Okay. You’re not that far away. Stop by and have some. There are a couple of peo… https://t.co/lLD8VDYVB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDouglas21 @YaBoyJUMP So is Russ... why are his triple doubles not weighed as much as scoring 40+? I’d give it… https://t.co/C5KZz7aJMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Points to MSNBC for using Sherrod Brown’s pic twice, more points cuz he’s a white dude with putative black name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabresProspects Two words for you when you’re in Denver, Bakes: Westfax Brewery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spicy Fried 🐔 Sanny..... That's all   Lunch with @lovedvancouver popinavancouver  killin it !!  @hamidsalimian… https://t.co/7tQIgxrQiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeTwtsTennis @TennisProfits Add more W’s to that. Pretty sure I’m good. Have you followed this idiot? He cries… https://t.co/hSNdKk2z7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[And most of that money 💰 is salary and benefits for Socialist Professors! That teach hate of America!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can find me at the Fry Bread Stand. #SheSaid @ Melrose on 7th Avenue https://t.co/Esj334x8hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSnyderCBS Yeah hopefully that was the reason he was not nearly as good offensively but 2017 might have been a career season too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaRosePeters I can understand why you’re not a fan, HOWEVER, I do appreciate noticeably smaller, artsy, sentime… https://t.co/AvWUMWEi6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @PennyHicks13 this is bad news for people who say we need the wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first sensible solution to the problem of SBC power abuse I have read yet. Instead of seizing greater a… https://t.co/eAudCIQg2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Daytona Day!   @mikejoy500 @AllWaltrip @JeffGordon @LarryMac28 @NASCARONFOX https://t.co/ZYqaHe7sKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to start the day. 4.78 mile hike. Greenway and the Coves @ London, Ontario https://t.co/tOUrSht14E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canon’s new EOS RP is peaking my interest but damn a full frame for only $1299? 😳🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk Maybe because he is a cancer in the locker room and they are better off without him even with him being a huge talent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsZombies1 #Phillies and then #Padres in that order would be my bet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see one of my all-time favorite @WWE superstars, Shelton Benjamin, on #Raw tonight! 👏🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnarae_ @kailah_casillas But thanks for stopping by.   They do appreciate positive people here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jose Alvarado (GT) carves through the Wolfpack defense and scores out of the timeout.  31-28 NC State, 17 seconds t… https://t.co/O0n8D9x6E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthGroudon What?? It’s visually beautiful and emotionally complex and funny af!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EntheosShines This unknown truth is much more real than most readers will realize.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissaykim @JakeKocoB5Q I drank maybe 3 ounces, which is 3 ounces more than I would drink of your green concoctions. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home from another wonderful concert by the @WaterburySymph. An informative musical history lesson and a great job by the musicians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serves him right. This guy was slated to make millions in the next few years, but that kid was making more than him… https://t.co/LszZEUm7Jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbrowniepoints Is doc emrick stopping by this spring? his love of the game is infectious. I love hearing folks fro… https://t.co/XSJD3vdhY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#elarroyoatxquotes #valentinesday2019 #socks #underwear #singleamdlooking #funny #lol #dryhumor #humor #funnymemes… https://t.co/48rx0X1LwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud moment for the Haub School and for our Food Marketing Program. Our student team came in FIRST at the NGA nati… https://t.co/QyzTa3TOTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Adventure may hurt you but monotony will kill you.” @ Aeropuerto Internacional De Monterrey https://t.co/U1SBCr2eRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samim I see people have mentioned @NotionHQ - have you explored @milanoteapp or @coda_hq ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The small little overlap of college basketball season and the beginning of baseball season is the absolute best time of the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in @KatieMcGrawx’s forecast for later this morning and crews are about to head out to start salting the roads… https://t.co/GJWlJTlTid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriTexan China customs just a small sample of the chaos.  not the big issue here...   enjoy your day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDSlider Yes and probably 3 of the 20 years has "worked". Feels like iu is a good program and not elite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody at my job be so excited to say good morning n shit... I just try to go past with my head down so I don’t gotta speak lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not far from where Buddy Holly and Ritchie went down in their small engine plane after playing the Surf Ballroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lankywitch @A_Peterson1995 What good do you see in the church that is unique to the church? I am not challenging y… https://t.co/u51DdZruoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYKCattle We will be doing the bulls tomorrow with de-lice product, always lots of scratching once the sun starts… https://t.co/ZGmLpq1j2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I got a little tipsey tonightvand made out with this really good looking girl and I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/EPTBlZeEqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 House Democrats took $60,000 trip to South Africa for Beyoncé concert, records show  So thats OK because its the… https://t.co/jdOysFkvFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@580CFRA More craziness about the United we Roll protest. They have no money to get home!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaidelozano hola que tengas un.lindo fin de semana a continuacion los detalles del clima https://t.co/hgfOVj9jMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more! Maybe I should get food, not! (at @Hooters in Madison, WI) https://t.co/0OYAwoKpgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mf gonna get a B on his report card and Mom’s gonna be like “I was in the hospital studying less than 24 hours afte… https://t.co/Y0AFYoY7ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[J.D. day at JetBlue versus Orioles. Hernández, G. LF, Betts RF, Bradley Jr. CF, Martinez DH, Bogaerts SS, Holt 2B,… https://t.co/JnRzCMLg1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris So, Ms Harris, you are again proven that you care nothing for justice.  Smollet just charged with a f… https://t.co/WPzJeK1KRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cl4ptheist First, that’s your opinion and you’ve made your choice. Second, you don’t have quality of life at top o… https://t.co/OtW2j6q0TJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the lack of fall anhydrous in many areas, planning alternative Nitrogen sources and rates will be key before… https://t.co/rox7Kb0xXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤯 When you realize #Strawberries are not in season on #valentinesday so we're paying a premium on a premium day!! 💰… https://t.co/bN2LGDlfqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henry, you lose it the second you open the rubber door. No mercy for her, no mercy for you.  #TURNTHEANIMAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toniforchicago VERY turned off by this hack job ad. Preckwinkle shot herself in the foot.  Poor start to the runoff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cobber_bobber @ChrisLDunham @charliekirk11 @RtisticOne Illegals cost taxpayers 130 BILLION a year, so which is wor… https://t.co/NTWnYGG0ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does the gym do for you? 💥 Most of the time the gym isn’t about about training only but so much more. Some som… https://t.co/4zwvsModHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguin with the empty net goal to put this game to rest! Stars win 5-2 and snap the Blues 11-game won streak! #GoStars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, @neverquitkid and I recorded a Small Talks episode on the word "IDENTITY". And honestly, exploring this… https://t.co/jQofhOZtJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BOBESTILLZ We’re moving to Pop Century. It’s $300 for two nights, which is way cheaper than Wilderness Lodge for one night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump You spelled “Donald J Trump” wrong. #CohenTestimony #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danagould I think what’s needed is the power of puppies!  Come on out Dana! https://t.co/S8f2PmLk08]]></document><document><![CDATA[love you the most. thank you for all your inspiration. #KarlLagerfeld https://t.co/QFmLH0mDfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aerosmith, Las Vegas and my September 21st birthday... hmm. Looking like a road trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadingWPassion I can No More Calm a STORM as Stop the SUN from SHINNING! So take your Bussiness Inside!]]></document></documents></author>