<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Independent was the first long word I ever knew how to spell all because of Webbie]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Netflix wasn’t around Blockbuster and Hollywood Video would still be in business. I sure do miss going to the vi… https://t.co/JkABAlTGIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon from Binnie Media Events (as produced by me!). #epic Keep May 4th clear on your calendar! https://t.co/4GQnpKkeYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Inslee on TRMS. I'm liking what I'm seeing. His record in WA includes a 12 $ minimum wage; public option o… https://t.co/uzb83YZ15D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitweeting @jakerobison1 @sreednak @Billie_Jean00 @SukkaCockatoo @Eminem11684 @clark_gasm @heyidgaf69… https://t.co/LzEojTATKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wintergloves @Google Who's Sully's love interest? Roz? WE NEED TO KNOW, @DISNEYPIXAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will have far reaching implications and impact @tycely - thanks for the heads up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came out on top to win the SIAA PG State Championship!! What a blast coaching these dudes was this season. Grateful… https://t.co/tIjxwFHoWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelenReynoldsTH @Shelly032014 @Cali_J_ @ChristopherOPS @a_porter2005 @airbornliz “T Y !”  R o s a l i n d ! https://t.co/pEH1nbD5KI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a Dirty and Sneaky games played by CIA and Pentagon,by sabotaging the Electric Power Dam ,which is one of t… https://t.co/NZMpb6oBEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they love to mimic and copy. Spell check is sensitive on new devices, as it does not know your speech patterns yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was not gonna be going to this game but with the news Stanley is going to be there, I’ll be there! Great marketing… https://t.co/ek88oQWp9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t need a friend who changes when I change and who nods when I nod; my shadow does that much better.”  #Plutarch]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now this is happening...#BiggieTributeMix #LiveFromTheKitchen #RIPBig🙏🏽  . . . 📀📀: @DJSlick310  . 🗣🎙:… https://t.co/gu84aV82Ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tart! - Drinking a Razz N’ Berry by @palmcitybrewing @ Palm City Brewing  — https://t.co/U6AGNgZWly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link and my bio and grab tickets to check @CallHimLambo @moneycarsin onlyjahmez along with myself and man… https://t.co/OSbOY1VhzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.I.P King Kong Bundy  Did a show together 23 years ago and he was very nice and pretty damn big.  He was the only… https://t.co/0Ni7fbIUQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Taraska @ChipWile @DISupdates Took very many minutes to upload a picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way I said it was: "We find wisdom at the frontiers of what we don't know." Or "We find knowledge at the fronti… https://t.co/XJvlXTqqpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anaban_Cr Con la mini te puedo ayudar, ya que el matchmaking cambio justo la última actualización https://t.co/hr6hWgsR8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that one of the #NATO5 protesters remains in maximum security hell—almost SEVEN YEARS later? Drop him… https://t.co/69CszPTwUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: are you going to wear a red shirt to work today? Me: nah, I'm going to wear this black one, matches my soul better #valentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early jolt bitches! (@ Starbucks in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/fCozuVOwtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow wow wow!! Cannot even say how proud and excited I am to be an #Iowa fan!! Thank you @IowaHoops @TheIowaHawkeyes… https://t.co/xafb5LDN66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardFosterr I think I’ve said “the parents deserved this” in my head about 8 times an episode]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY SHOW SOY SHATOMIX MUSIC Y ESCUCHA ESTO: – ♫La Última Batalla por Grupo Rebeldia, de #SoundHound https://t.co/iDYNcDoxcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went with pathetic as my “p” word, with patronizing (to his goofy followers) coming in second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTGabe There are a ton of NFL QBs who never sniffed SB, so I'm gonna say yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[En su afán de dejarle bien cromado el escroto a su caudillo, a veces se dicen pendejadas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet the pile of shit is still the president of the United States due to the defense playing of traitorous repub… https://t.co/jgyVoSxxfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a good thing I'm on nights because I couldn't sleep right now if I wanted to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laron Bishop Ft. Ben Grimm &amp; Royale Swerve https://t.co/fmYMyVW8Ts via @YouTube @LaRonBishop @benGrimm_CRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHC_76 I mean we have no idea what’s been offered. It’s premature to kill the Phillies for not “getting it done”.… https://t.co/2rE3xwtVBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like her or not, she definitely knew something. His lashing out with “you’re the puppet” comment is clearly his tal… https://t.co/8wtUC8TtJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone down on Lonzo take a look at @Lakers defensive numbers since he got hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmaddening I have a crappy folding one but it does have green felt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that we are both alive and for the fact that we are all alive and hopefully no one is being murdered, kidn… https://t.co/CRCBMkTzN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was running in the snow last night like I ain’t got a bad knee and asthma lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positivity and negativity is a choice. Theres ALWAYS a positive in a negative situation even if it hasnt materialized yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Obby_Oss I bought it with when El Tigre was green lit so it has lots of sentimental value.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accomplishments can lead to arrogance but the reverse is seldom, if ever true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selfcarepapi You’re discovering these gays. You need to set up an agency https://t.co/vfcRxc7Qk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day baby!! We took a fat L on Friday but we’re still enjoying home cookin.. Let’s go rip some goals against th… https://t.co/hA9dwHJHTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdaisey Fair enough. I think a multi-million dollar company (DPC) diverting a revenue stream from Harper Lee and h… https://t.co/FV2LrEAWss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that @BernieSanders has announced he’s in, watch all the other candidates slide even farther to the left.… https://t.co/7I3OLdcjVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtconners @YoungCultureNY @StephVaughan19 and i have been trying to for a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachPPeterson @leebdial @BYUfootball @CoachPPeterson congrats on moving up to FCS. This is a great game for both… https://t.co/JG2TGWOljF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivien2112 @RushFamTourneys Are we the only two working today?😂   Make the best of you day!✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry Is this a reference to “grabbing her by the p***y” or to one of the many rape allegations against you?🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be fun. So it is incumbent upon the callers to bring their A game; whatever the hell that means.… https://t.co/dfpVh1Ld0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#alfredoriverajazz #sem #ethnomusicology #conference #paper #theworldstage #research #losangeles #jazz #leimertpark… https://t.co/MeWjVKUphY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seal at Head of the Meadow Beach Truro November 2017 #seal #seals #sealsofinstagram #mammals #mammalsofinstagram… https://t.co/SdUJ2aLpmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmawhorter thanks, Peter! your tutelage was critical to the development of this work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor Janet mills Maine  Just created 12 new jobs Handing out welfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong Cartels having some Democrats on payroll is the only logical explanation.  Always deflect back to t… https://t.co/gsLTyEFOTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrath_of_Comm @nancyjeanbird @NancyWallaceGA @nereid_niobi @Nevada_Dem @Nikki_WVU_49ers @ninampls @nmalexander1… https://t.co/Z2Z0zd2Rst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipfranklin @Eaglefly124 If you asked the average Senator to explain the difference between Socialism,  Communism… https://t.co/5FB6cR1ffw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Everyone!!!   Words are the second most powerful thing, second only to thoughts…but without words ther… https://t.co/HLn79yZVxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulietHuddyTV This story will refute you NASA theory. Is The Global Temperature Record Credible? https://t.co/fFWjXVOApR via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy reading (and learning) how others are using the #HighImpactPractice of ePortfolios in their classrooms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryjonas @IvankaTrump you have to be Jewish To understand What jewish soul food is,believe me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God,who has called you into fellowship with his Son Jesus Christ our Lord,is faithful.1 Corinthians 1:9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielDiMartino @DraCanterville @Caspwus @garciabanchs @jguaido @NicolasMaduro Diste en el clavo mi pana, describi… https://t.co/GAeMILk07q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Some love him simply because he upsets “Liberals “. Some love him because he says he’s against abortion… https://t.co/5XVob1VO5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goodness do I love @Giannis_An34 pure joy and fun. I hope he stays in #MKE forever. @bucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPhilosophy_ I’m glad to that hear man. I’m sure you’ll figure things out. Besides trying to stay afloat in all of… https://t.co/o5AUe6Fp7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on a recommendation...threw this new XCaliber this week. It’ll be in the bag by Azalea AM.  #flippindiscs… https://t.co/CdyvSeTUgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cowmigos @ArmaOrientalis yes these are interesting reads, gentlemen, aware of cleopatras history being embroidered… https://t.co/EhZP32YuSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[He harvests the injury energy of other superstars to be able to shoot from anywhere on the court. Like how the mons… https://t.co/shjKBbbeAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[We lost an hour last night, which means seasonal depression is almost over!!! Now it just needs to be warm again!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/txeB9GdkOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Hastily conceived concepts to push an envelope untethered to any reality that could exist in 2020, 2030 or… https://t.co/3iUkHt6Hq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizwomannshorts I'm glad that I didn't watch the game because I went to bed sleep anyway, that's why, #6 - Eric Bl… https://t.co/JubUub3n8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ion mess with no type of water... no rain, getting in the pool, nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are correct. The Clinton corruption is beyond the laws of our country. What can one expect with corrupt FBI and… https://t.co/jgHyQ5wwUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Galesburg @tracy_lillard @wcisports @IHSAState @ILStatePolice @gregorywbennett @ILStatePolice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh em gee... this popped up in a video I was watching today! I have to share it. https://t.co/dgYcQpDbr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was literally listening to my PSP yesterday and “Remind me” by @royksopp made me str8 think @GEICO #Caveman]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve done a fine job of celebrating the 4th long before trump came along. Injecting his brand of Nationalism is un… https://t.co/0bHBSOVTWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone knows that @Ninja is the gaming god and changed gaming culture in every way possible.....butttttt; the joy… https://t.co/mE6UF0MC2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why yah proudly be throwing yah flags everywhere. Yah embarrassing  your whole nation with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget being at Fenway this summer where they needed to play a video during the game (twice!) telling th… https://t.co/I6i5IdggjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa is windy right now. I just watched a startled crow get thrown off his planned trajectory by a gust, and he was… https://t.co/nBxqHknQ12]]></document><document><![CDATA[1878-1854 Crenshaw Blvd 1878-1854 Crenshaw Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90019 https://t.co/8sHukZs1A2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ash__hill @KyleeMiller_WX GM Ashlyn you two need to team up more often 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ange_Amene @tnisha_soaps Talcum X has not had a good rollout with POCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLAMonline @NBA Lets not make a big deal about this video. He crossed up Kelly Olynk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan I know your shows here are sold out but a live show with you and Alex Jones in Austin would be hilarious!… https://t.co/bjhGF7Qkaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the body kit on this Corvette.  It's outrageous. @ American Airlines Center https://t.co/2lL1M2v6L7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollieB @ObvItsAmy @KelseYouLater these are chocolates right? I'm just going to assume they are chocolates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBilbert You don't want to assume my life. No, no sir, no way, no how.]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Phoenix is the new South Phoenix with all it's shitty drivers and roads. Smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryMcCormick Thanks so much for your pointers tonight! I’ll be in touch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time is right and the dollars are right. Solar full steam ahead. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quantum computing takes advantage of the laws of quantum mechanics found in nature and represents a fundamental cha… https://t.co/W1j6sFUvnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Welcome Party for @bradleyumbb! Tonight in the Main Atrium of Renaissance Coliseum. Doors open at 7:30… https://t.co/gnOthBzKct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time @genesisopen today. Spent most the day at #1 tee and got some great shots of the @PGATOUR finest 🏌🏻⛳️… https://t.co/zfnNhmtmOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysonoffense @cc_fla @Alicia_Smith19 He’s being modest. Ryan stays at Clooney’s Airbnb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy respondiendo todo tipo de preguntas, confesiones, etc. Sean sexuales o no. #Freerol #Sexrol   https://t.co/HT6xNkhqsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it is strange. Like they are doow fiend aliens from another planet.]]></document></documents></author>