<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[3 years ago Tony @mrtonylewisjr had the opportunity to interview his Father Tony Lewis Sr in Federal Prison in orde… https://t.co/hK4F671GTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevadamrjones What about Mike Jones, the rapper? He's got your first AND last name!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MystikGunn I'm really digging Apex Legends right now. But it is new, so we'll see. I haven't given Blackout a soli… https://t.co/abUayR0CIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavy band of sleet/rain mix moving through the area. Temperatures are above freezing so no issues expected. #ncwx #wncwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I live in sinful Pennsylvania. Where you can breathe air in God’s Country in Lancaster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naima True but I believe he feel he is the victim him... I don’t believe all of it. But I believe enough of it. He… https://t.co/5gvDQebRsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the many reasons why @TeamCoachBuzz is one of the absolute best in the business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to be the first subscriber to @donnellrawlings’ new podcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clutchcurryback @Blake340_ yea our offense, with CP3 at point, is why he’s good :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montanertwiter @jguaido Why is the international news focusing more on Maduro than Guaido?  Why is Maduro controll… https://t.co/3bf6s1OoRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the same bday as Rihanna so I like to go into her hashtag and pretend everyones wishing me a happy bday]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3) Tech teams have to learn the business and meet customers. They should should put their solutions through a “rea… https://t.co/h05htQmhpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma make beats and my finna b “ lil erection “ my beat tag finna b like “ lil erection ya u hard “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustenBundyDC @shure_joshua @Nationals You guys make me laugh. 🤣 The @Mets are CLEARLY the superior team in the NL… https://t.co/wcxjTRBbVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mricet1005 @southladyeagles @holmdelcntap @MiddsouthNation @MTPSpride You’re very welcome sir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityzensMke @Cityanapolis @takesonlyone @SportClubMKE I concur. May have to travel up that way to snag a sticker for the laptop...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A disfrutar del Sábado y que mejor con “Sabor a Mi” con mucho ritmo 🎉 https://t.co/stRFBkW3c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@refinedmess @RealJamesWoods @benshapiro Ahhh! Another triggered liberal when confronted with facts.....find a safe place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sachems are 2019 Newburyport Bank Classic Gulazian Division Champs! https://t.co/vwlVyXl2kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mryannagy @micky_larnen You’re responding to the wrong thread. I was saying Ryan was being rude. But every single… https://t.co/r1aqOMfaGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC HEY ITS CALLED A JOB  THAT PAYS YOU. HELLO we don’t want hand outs or bread lines. Bull shit America is fine.… https://t.co/6CEfgUNVvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiattenberg @JasonAChristian I started with Stories of Your Life and it worked for me 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe16283648 Because some council members were using that time to make political speeches and grandstand, rather th… https://t.co/UKXKoCHw6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maria_Tureaud @SamSykesSwears And then they say "I bet you get that a lot." Then wtf did you say it?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can say is that art is important.⁣ ⁣ Now I’m on a mission to acquire makeup remover, because I could not for… https://t.co/vIoVLWscQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberPatriot @SteveHyde13 @MikeStuchbery_ @PGMcast @Tenbit That is what I believe as well. But I'm willing to deba… https://t.co/jzhE5mISnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullPup2A @Itsme81977221 Arrest Pelosi immediately Clinton JOHNSON stearns Bush ROMNEY beekman probst lobato sanch… https://t.co/twIGiiWdTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time out @StaytonEagles 3:15 in 3rd tied at 40. Henley was down 20-9 after 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 I believe what women decide to do with their pregnancy is none of your business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealGlenMacnow What precipitated that question? The Harper inclusion? And yes. I agree. An unfair question at this stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNickyWaters @joeysofficial @Ashleydidwhatt I mean I just want an invite]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m rewatching the overtime because I don’t believe what I just witnessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Former DCCC executive director Sena launches consulting firm: House Democrats’ top political strat… https://t.co/oTcGo3FEv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout if that’s who Tristian hit I don’t even feel bad for whatever tf her name is....life is a competition “surv… https://t.co/spHRupBlyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[More funny memes and videos on our website!   https://t.co/hZPnGokf4P  #meme #funnyvideo #catvideo #memes… https://t.co/3tYQq7OArK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHHSTars @trabucobaseball @LesLukach @PBR_California @ocvarsity @stbchallenge @ByDCP @DailyPilotSport @SoCalSteve9… https://t.co/5BoU7uOEb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hawaiian Lion Coconut &amp; Coffee Porter by Big Top Brewing Company @ Tipsy Taco Cantina — https://t.co/XMDYmWrqvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excalibur5 @GOPChairwoman @LindseyGraham @realDonaldTrump Really McCabe: apprehended them ? police had nothing to… https://t.co/EWcOB4Qt5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dopedaneille @ZeffToke @khyatt2876 @UNDEADANGEL6 @PeggyPotHead @Carreenv1 @woodeg81 @LARRYIRBY6 @Amznfrknaz… https://t.co/BguZZIuWtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[ive been using night mode since i found out about it and never gone back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manipulate the girls               Indoctrinate the boys   @poppy https://t.co/vxNw3eAxzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurSchwartz @KatrinaPierson You idiots with “ no ideas” is why America is behind the World now, Cons suck the oxygen out of science]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewchristian @TomChristianCB My goodness look at the head, if only my mouth could reach through this android.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about the Democrat Party... https://t.co/cqLC1JiQE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mississippi State wins the #SECWBB Championship over Arkansas, 101-70. https://t.co/HnF2gWhisd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me a fair weather fan all you want. I have little interest in watching ISU until they start playing like the t… https://t.co/GhpQw1DIUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to my severe lack of sleep, I may be checking myself into the psychiatric hospital that I’m working at today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cannondaltx That’s my personal pick.. but if I was a betting man Roma by Netflix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelFFlorio That works, do not let us down or your east coast privileges will be revoked. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Facebook keep texting me?! What makes you think I’ll text you back I don’t even text my stylist back smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meditationsndz @NBCNews @KenDilanianNBC It is their money because the system is rigged in their favor. They buy th… https://t.co/LG3L74ASxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piaadistrict3 playoffs tonight for @LLhoops #berksbeat.  In game reports and highlights @mhsboysbasketb1 and… https://t.co/22CYiVTj5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve met great people in my life wether they are still in it or not I’m grateful for every single person that I come across]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump It really doesn’t take much to make you and daddy look bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this was like 2 years ago when I built this PC literally piece by piece..  Ran all the UEFI updates and all… https://t.co/ehU2Mf56tQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccerhof @MSRushSoccer @MCJagSoc @CentralMSSoccer @MC_BIGBLUE @MACoaches @nhsaca @mcsinfo @JFCsoccer1 @MaxPrepsTT… https://t.co/1riR7DLzGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicktotin @swaggie_hunter Oh wow I thought they were banned from America]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been back at #syracuse for just over a month now and I'll tell you...  the whole time's been one weird incident after another.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit the 20 minute mark in this @ChipotleTweets line #Yikes #AssemblyLineInefficiencies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you love wolves???? 🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺🐺https://t.co/TeJdSIHvcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Paint By Numbers Morning Sky by @Worksale at @madmexrobinson — https://t.co/abWic6YrxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jav95_ @49ersHive Am I’m wrong for thinking Tank Carradine when Burns is mentioned?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidshuman @gamespite @jamesmielke @retronauts @greenlitcontent Do you have one, Sid??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourmandaniel @mickey_norah Ironically his name is Mickey, but not this one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Th3Franchise You’re not playing no tears in your beer bullshit or I’m losing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champwebdotnet @IndyCar @juncosracing Apologies on any misunderstanding, I thoroughly appreciate your retro video… https://t.co/xp2GruIlmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention to the slut-shaming gays.  They are THE filthiest whores behind closed doors. https://t.co/4TZw099rPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que gustazo coincidir contigo después de tanto tiempo querido @AaronDiazMX  como los buenos vinos jejeje   #actor… https://t.co/i2X9qdPfvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[These migraines are NO JOKE!!! Headed to get acupuncture therapy...never done this before. First time for everythin… https://t.co/0u35R39jEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best game to date: 278 scratch for 305 total. First time breaking 300 with handicap. #bowling @ West Covina, Califo… https://t.co/jPwrpXz0y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#judischekulturbund features #massfortheoppressed https://t.co/LDVN0tlFlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[No.....not sucking her soul and vitality via the Dark Arts at all.... https://t.co/uGN6QXV8o4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheabooskyy Yell if you’re coming to Keeneland!  I’ll give you the horse farm tour and show you part of the Bourbon Trail!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bourbon maple goodness, so smooth and delicious. - Drinking a Genetic Erosion (2018) by @SpeciationAles @ Funky Bar… https://t.co/B0LFxmMX29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last I checked. Per the Supreme Court, this is a violation of their First Amendment Rights https://t.co/O52WkuWdmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope they convict on every  count. It's not that I dislike him. But conviction could act as a deterrent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I at least do my taxes before you take my shit for the wall @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[i see twitter went through and deleted all the tweets from every girl in the world where they said I was “very hand… https://t.co/Fpn1Frm81L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #vinyl record calendar sounds a lot like #FrankSinatra, but it’s actually @JoePiscopoShow #Comedy https://t.co/2SmEvnTIf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are gearing up for #HungerFreeKYDay! Join is for breakfast in the cafeteria and then please join @KyFoodBanks in… https://t.co/wrmRPr3hyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill there has been NO missiles or rockets fired in the last 20 months. does that not constitute moving forward?]]></document><document><![CDATA[just convinced our professor to cancel our 7-10 night class within 5 minutes of sitting down... that’s gotta be a new record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if Facebook/Instagram/WhatsApp delivers perfectly on that promise, it can still observe your behavior; combine… https://t.co/nD9lQ4VoYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryandarmstrong You’ll have to pry that dry aged steak from my cold dead hands!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elite 4-Star WR Jalen McMillan (@jalenmcmillan20) talks recent #USC Visit, probable return, Spring/Summer Visit pla… https://t.co/iP37qI8vBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UEFAComPiotrK Nigdy nie spotkałem, ale twarz nie do zapomnienia, kiedy jeszcze grał podejrzewałem go o makijaż :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeirJourdan @SportsBooger @_brothermesoft @TheSteinLine Your crazy dude..stay off the drugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is the story of anyone who is working through depression issues.  Like, people like me. People enjoy m… https://t.co/mbw9z3Do6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation 3/10 - 3/16: Live With Others In Mind - Rms 15:1-6 KJV https://t.co/HRwwakZV04 #arcamax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whale watching at breakfast. Whale playing about 1000 feet off shore. 🐳🐳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dallas 2016 with #MelissaSantos @ThisIsMelSantos https://t.co/Kc9HjC196S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaaizzy I missed the Wednesday's Child segment it seems like they would have a show that shows the best Wednesday… https://t.co/hBULvSYyvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayblossom27 TY Judy H. I have heard the name before, but didn't really know what it was. The shrew is another sma… https://t.co/Y3pHLwCdDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HashtagGriswold @benshapiro It’s almost like there is no longer a standard and any idiot can get elected.  There is no hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden That summit turned out to be a nothingburger on taxpayer dime...I don't think he realizes how bad thin… https://t.co/ALC4OvJUg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferris__MUELLER @TheOracleACHNJ Id rather die. I wouldnt let Dakich coach youth basketball. Hes a trash human.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBenchCapon @SteveCooke @berggruenInst The guy at Johns Hopkins seems to have done it out of gratitude, which is nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time I thought she a love me for me? = What's me if I ain't got what somebody a love?Soul=Human Even… https://t.co/Th8fOa4hTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahatum Aca me vine a asegurar que siguiera todo en orden profe, no la vi a Battle vagando por estos pagos... el li… https://t.co/1CQgLraULN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a preference for masculine men is TOTALLY fine. HOWEVER, if that preference is based on INTERNALIZED HOMOPHO… https://t.co/nuSI0TmHFH]]></document></documents></author>