<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VivziePop @AshNicholsArt @EdBoscoVA  It's 1:30 am, radio daddy why- been practicing Alastor #HazbinHotelFanart… https://t.co/qJ1UkdD5oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craving Ritz crackers and spray cheese in a can....???  😳Not sure where that's coming from 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to learn from @jaywilk about strategies to engage donors in more meaningful ways #poweredbypurpose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Style Consultants are here to help you find that perfect fit with our new brands #T2124 🎀💗 https://t.co/ISZZlHz4oE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyjaffe "Romeo and Jules" from @Degrassi! And I loved all the music from the fictional bands within the show, as well. 🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RV30B @dbongino Your great Republicans defunded Security for Embassy’s.That is the core nature of your party.Fuck… https://t.co/RO2RC2oBNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like subway tile is going to be the orange and green paisley couch of 2050. Also...I’m sick of f$@cking subway tile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Dad: "NOT STILL BEEN WALLOWING IN CIVIL WAR CRIMES AND TAKEN A HORRIBLE STUPID DIRECTION. HUG THAT FLAG AS A CLO… https://t.co/Gw1pyCYEth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Donald, We're Letting You Go: America's Final Letter to Trump | Opinion - Newsweek https://t.co/MTLr9C9aLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did no one tell me about this daylight savings bs? I’m going back to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t figure out what the issue is.. what “consideration “@FOXTV @EmpireFOX #JussieSmolettHoax https://t.co/EGqlHRSUDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Free market do it’s thing! The only thing government can do is try to catch up, regulate, then tax. A… https://t.co/vVbYi1gcvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@birge14 @andrewmcmahon Happy Birthday Jeff! Hope our buddy here sets you up with exactly what you need. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[My two valentines / forever boyfriends huntergett + @ShannonKirsten ❤️ Love my boos💕 | (wedding sneak peek 📸… https://t.co/En45FvOabs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is reform for them to serve longer. NO to this election-reform. Just stop allowing illegals and dead people to… https://t.co/s1BXrNU1nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was @TGowdySC on the Gang of Eight? If not then how does he know what they thought!  If he was then..WHY ..didn’t h… https://t.co/8LWhhIlNYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Hint Hint* I would LOVE this #GemstoneHeart necklace from @kayjewelers for Valentine's Day! https://t.co/t9HcTzR47s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyKStewart From an outside perspective, it appears they have or are very close to rigging your elections so GO… https://t.co/U12it8rnlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[(my poem "Intuition", copyright © by #jasminekang)  #poets #writers #writing #creativewriting #prose #poems #poetry… https://t.co/DfQQdowTLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS I voted for you. I support you. I am hearing stories about people’s taxes and to be honest it is frightening… https://t.co/nhxgZXqPOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JussieSmollett  Numbers 32:23 “...be sure your sin will find you out.” #youcanrunbutyoucanthide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Beverage Distributor That the Iditarod Is an Arctic Nightmare for Dogs https://t.co/NTztHEW3zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know how people manage all social sites. I hoped back on Twitter, but still need to catch up on Instagram a… https://t.co/URJIvCqffc]]></document><document><![CDATA[They look like men/are attractive and can probably use a strap better than any real dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAaronBolduc @JFreischlag is incredibly cool!! This doesn’t surprise me at all :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stayed up late enough to play DMC for an hour, which means I stayed up later than I should have, which means oh g… https://t.co/wcQRZaRuQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamás había tenido tanta paz en una relación, como en la que estoy ahorita y que bien se siente 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elle_316 @BrotherNature It ate a large portion of cheese. That like feeding a dog a bar of chocolate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 100 years ago, on June 4, 1919, Congress passed the 19th Amendment to the US Constitution, acknowledging the… https://t.co/Ss5Tm3DFjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in running a shortened #Daytona500 on @704NASCARHeat on @Xbox?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atDavidHoffman I sure more people do! With Obama the period of complete joy! https://t.co/Zv9PsTJIZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you beauty vloggers that promted Invisalign: screw you. I ended up w/ braces AGAIN because the 6 month evalu… https://t.co/FccgiRqJME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shuffle really hit it with playing k , the only exception and song #3 right after the other what are you trying to tell me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chairman Huebert closes the hearing on HB 2233. Hearings Wednesday and Thursday. View KASB’s Weekly Capitol Calenda… https://t.co/uikiykMZnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treat yourself!💕 Enjoy a free #ValentinesDay coffee on us at @Balzacs in #LibertyVillage! https://t.co/sYSlsYl95r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VyNguyennnnnn @LadyLawyerDiary Your first gig may not be exactly what you envision. Keep the faith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscardismore Taking that for granted. Mostly commenting on his description of the desert around there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump I hope people hear and follow your sound advice. Didn’t do this in 2016!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you guys all get the Presidential Alert yesterday? I musta missed that text! #SaturdayThoughts #FakeTrump… https://t.co/flHyV01bYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a petition: Don’t let Mitch McConnell kill democracy reform. Sign here: https://t.co/htsklHimzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanBrayboy Thanks for sharing, @BryanBrayboy. Can’t wait to watch, and imagine I’ll start showing in class!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work paid off today! Way to stay tough, 6th Grade North Hoops! @ Manitowoc, Wisconsin https://t.co/EYkGLE06qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty. … https://t.co/mQnA9QCXSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanTheBeepMan This better be another one of your funnies. https://t.co/9tCIaz6lKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we sell again! #colonialcreek is nestled in the back of #colonialcharters.  This sweet 2 bed condo has plenty… https://t.co/zKsXC3c4nK]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great collaboration opportunity for non profits in the area!  #inspired 👍 Thank you @jacksonhlthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Gordon and Zack Levine had the best dunks ever in a slam dunk contest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those skilled in warfare move the enemy, and are not moved by the enemy.  #SunTzu https://t.co/yQ3BU5VydE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam It could've been worse.  Some men will kill when cheated on.  A little shame in public won't hurt. #scarletletter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @CaththeWineLady @DivaVinophile @joneill55 @SideHustleWino @thatsVeryKari @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123… https://t.co/UgJVh98DbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjteacher @Kaepernick7 I have actually been creating mosaics as part of my #digitaldetox weekly! Fun to see ho… https://t.co/r6Fup8KmGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[but when hannah b said, “i will not allow myself to not feel chosen every single day” i FELT that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almaldo2 Está bien para empezar. Con el tiempo llegarás a 3mil pero es mejor poco a poco porque yo me lastime los hombros por intensa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokyburnout @jeff_gluck That was ridiculous 🤦🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/qOSC2T5ful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit this hearing is a shitshow. Cummings can not manage this committee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abducted in plain sight has to be the dumbest documentary ever bro💀🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovebakedgoods I don't really like myself very much, but I'll give it a go. 1) My sense of humor 2) My loyalty 3)… https://t.co/bZof15D06M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the night with the Phantom @ Marcus Performing Arts Center https://t.co/ej4sJPyHIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oliver making a new friend and instantly regretting being social : relatable. https://t.co/tabshy2K0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[You like my bow? Gee, thanks, just bought it! 🎀 It’s no secret I love my bows and wear them on a regular basis. I c… https://t.co/H3bOn9Cumo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just watched this 5 times thinking he was throwing them different ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanJodoin @Kevin__Wald @_waleedshahid @sunrisemvmt You don’t know me. My son was an environmental science major… https://t.co/dWXjqnti2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGraylin @htcvive Hi Alan! Educator in Kentucky, been trying to get this exact thing started on my own. Reached ou… https://t.co/aQVbqjVbPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyGraw6 It has been great weather!  Sunny, warm and snowy all in the same day 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stick to the things you really love.  An honest room is always up to date. - Billy Baldwin - . #kitchenenvy… https://t.co/mE0sdb3o1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 people are living in sanctuary in Philadelphia, more than any other major city in the U.S. https://t.co/vz1VSywPFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot7231 @jjjlaughter @bmxmom156 @lisastoi @DineshDSouza He wants to be a Dictator.  That is all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many people try to reject needed modifications to the death penalty by labeling reform as abolition. The 2 thin… https://t.co/93A5Vvb1W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolecadwalla Why do you think McCain had a problem with it..with the Aldridge deal...he hated Putin as much as I do]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true! Proud of these leaders @ChadHertzog @JohnFaulkenberr @JMeis @DmitchelDavid @JeffScalfaro @JanetteMillerPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TSPRA19 #campcommunication is not #keto 4 sure! Oh well, bring on the #Smoresbar @ASanchezTweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got tagged by @heymisterOC  to post one of my favorite books, with no explanation, for each of the next 7 days, a… https://t.co/kHveBYs1JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodeLovee I felt bad for the kid .... but I still laughed ... people are so childish 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottkfoley The commercials for your new show r so creative and bada$$. I can’t wait for the first episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chamas, perdón por exhibirnos en nuestra depresión por el final de la novela💔, ustedes ya saben quienes son.    TE… https://t.co/O3tgak9Rhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @VABVOX @damemagazine Ugh I'm so sorry to hear. 😥  I was just thinking today (after arguing on why mi… https://t.co/LotJL5bmKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are dealing with more of a narcissist, manipulator, and abuser than we know. He is convinced his damn self. And… https://t.co/ZqB06wi5ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinallyMommy19 @theleahgirl1 @LogicalLiz @sarahsimmons179 Except Sarah just said Megan was told by the producers w… https://t.co/dQUmgVfr2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need: a lazy day with Cameron &amp; Starbucks  What I’m getting: a 13 hour day at work with Folgers 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[My good friend Lillian. Unfiltered 100%! Planning our new Women’s Bible Study! Make the most of yourself, by fannin… https://t.co/yD7ANSTRnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haiku   Bernie is running In the best shape of his life "Unprecedented."  👓😎 https://t.co/AEzYunqfir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah he did get it right Malik He was a bi-sexual man not gay. Study more and double ✔ your bio #FreddieMercury liv… https://t.co/fAxVRnFYl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home and getting to read this amazing gem! My goodness, I’m lucky!   #girlstopapologizing #strongerasone… https://t.co/hLVlbmKnOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheMerryWriter Day 18  Oh wow! Umm, I guess a fancy dinner? I dunno, I'd probably just freak out and do nothing. I… https://t.co/a64EgpExVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 @trump_brett And CNN would have the ratings of a #1 cable news station...alas and then you woke up from your dream...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrysler ...and out front of the pack #Chrysler300   #Chrysler300Nation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaBrowning I know this sounds stupid but What is subtweet? Sorry I don't know the term Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mediumship Certification Program | Carefree Medium https://t.co/hj7tdSvNkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissSchmidtNCSP @jacksheard @GIPublicSchools @StarrElementary When @jacksheard reads, kids listen ❤️ Thanks for sh… https://t.co/wnmtk1SjMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[dude that 2nd to last shade is me in the summer.....tfoh givenchy??? do fucking better this is absolute trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leilanilozoya Aww.! You’re so sweet! I love you and your family! I’d do anything for u guys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes having morals isn’t easy. louie just lost all his friends and his job, but he’s beyond grateful and proud… https://t.co/js8qrAcl0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chasemadgamer @KitKatBrothel @BunnyRanchNetwk @MadamSuzette @Dianneassistant @sagebrushranch @LoveRanchNorth… https://t.co/xxQvfox0Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graham and Rob with their Pasta Transporter @bbyarstis @SteeleThoughts @sumitch16 https://t.co/LRNvyXWVgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never front on those that have helped Me/that choose to help Me,I think that’s some wack ass shit when people… https://t.co/9RLuYaUU5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Sen Nunez for great investigative work.  I for one will always remember you uncovering a false allegation… https://t.co/JtxxtiW6Qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrimfulofNasha @TeenageFanclub Mystery solved! 😂😂 Thanks goodness there’s options for small now or I’d never wear my band tees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jus’ touching Bass...🌖✨ . . . 📸: Michael McGrath 🥁: jmincerock #bass #drums #reggae #onedrop #mix #graciebassie… https://t.co/QO78HFJyys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinyanStaz @raducom @DoingRight1 @pjbowles4 @Razorsmack1 @GeanineC @Serremmy @RevKeithBritt @cali_curmudgeon… https://t.co/7xrRN4ZcKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emtothea @WynonnaEarpPod A big thank you for the pep talk.  Will keep the words "It's a marathon not a sprint" clo… https://t.co/L86avIpnRv]]></document></documents></author>