<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@romens99 @TampaBayTre @DoubleHFantasy1 Meh. @Nick55WATO can do the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great evening with such great people. All proud endorsers of @marlowstavern enjoying the chef inspired dishe… https://t.co/Qey5cVYw7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlliesOutlet just visited the store in sterling it’s awesome found stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JESnowden Mark me safe. Marvel movie came out today. I'm at the movies, all day, just like I am for every other Ma… https://t.co/fA108FOssJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live now! Tune into https://t.co/eyN1inuAGg now! Old school vibes and smooth electro coming at ya til the sun comes… https://t.co/6SJJ5fVZXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dondiegopaz @TurbaMX @michperezof Hicieron que les pesara por el drama que armaron pero , no niego que era un buen… https://t.co/L1G0qTfAp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix  #Unsolved was fucking great Screen play ramp ekkincahdu real story ni kuda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MixonMason @MarkdKelly2 @mschlapp Stop tweeting me. You post but do not provide where you get my your information.… https://t.co/8WJebmIq65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueeyescooking @KTHopkins I have no inside knowledge but it takes two for there to be a dysfunctional relationshi… https://t.co/Qp7PDRKTkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bwoodknows #nike art DEPT deconstructed #vintage track suits + #techfleece  #vintagemashups  #AIR #3m… https://t.co/FI5VaF3C1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 67% of registered voters are Dems or Independents. Congrats on your minority, asshat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📣📣📣 Public Open house 🏠 today 📍1 Bell Drive Westfield! Doors 🚪 open at 🕐!  Beautifully maintained Split Level home… https://t.co/IXrlmclGGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mWilstory @Evan_P_Grant Evan you are the BEST!! Congratulations, again. Mr. Baseball ⚾️⚾️⚾️👏👏👏👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sooners now leading 3-1 through four innings. Get one run out of a bases loaded situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshgre @zshahan3 Start walking it back. Really slowly. https://t.co/rQWJ6cEzVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[makes me so happy to see less and less Detroit fans here every time we play them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayelzSantana Really hope the rumors of them remastering MW2 are true. My favorite CoD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Read the laws you guys passed in the 70s about declaring a national emergency for immigration. Political hack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatpeterfox @QueenMab87 @MeghanMcCain She cares about daddy’s friend Joe. She doesn’t give a fuck that a lot of u… https://t.co/MgCSukwxR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buys apple music subscription to hear 1 album then cancel when it releases on spotify @LilSkies https://t.co/Z6DcZAKgHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedemptionBrew @Gatwick_Airport Thanks, have a good weekend guys! @Fly_Norwegian , thanks for free WiFi on board!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molttedduck No worries, I guard MY own boarders and I will shoot ANY suspicious DUCKS on sight !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilleduffy @lindydonna @alovedalongthe If someone looks at you funny when you correct them and they’re not a nativ… https://t.co/5GmGNIXrWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#czarface #ghostface #instrumentals #clearvinyl 🎶🎶🎶 #ENJOYVINYL   🎶👍🎶🎵🎶🎵👍🎶🎵👍🎶🎵  #vinyljunkie #nowplaying… https://t.co/VCiAmotl9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three things will last forever—faith, hope, and love—and the greatest of these is love. https://t.co/bvcJlboNwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great mashup by @OX_VT and reflects @espn coverage of @HokiesMBB with split screen showing game with Zion r… https://t.co/PpgwYdt67c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalesFrmTheStrp 🙋🏻‍♂️  *any game with a decent team playing*  💰O2.5 -160 bol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vwvan #vwbus #westfalia @ Oceanside, California https://t.co/6Jqb9c5sgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[follow me on instagram to see these in a cooler way @ jacobshootsphotos i’m gonna do a giveaway at 1k https://t.co/zvnlQsmc7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting set up for the bluegrasstrust antique and garden show!! Come see us at booth number #5!   #bluegrasstrust… https://t.co/AaUhdoN2hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[really good picking night for both nhl and nba. nhl 8 right 4 wrong. nba 6 right 0 wrong. and i seriously do not kn… https://t.co/J1SWJDkoWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJoeBrownTV Why are them Democrats always trying to pull the wool over our eyes always the deception]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce Weber isn’t sure if Dean will play Monday. He seems more sure about him being back in a week. It’s a soft tis… https://t.co/TTofr4ePLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m quoted in this @CTVNews piece: « Liberal MP apologizes for suggesting Wilson-Raybould was shuffled for not spea… https://t.co/sAy8fIqKg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltzingMtilda How's your evening darling? Can we get a pic of the big dogs or what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @syblades I fine when you're young you don't think that you're going to get old but when you do yo… https://t.co/66g1IeaJnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun read, but the differences in picks between the 3 writers was the most interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked our Senior Articles Editor if we can get a race and gender breakdown of who we publish in the Iowa Law Revi… https://t.co/4QcGsI3HoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejito_mendoza @drew141414 I mean if you don't know that 40 of the players won't make team then just get out and… https://t.co/LetgbBdoUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The King wishes too play, The dept of Human resources and the FBI again , Economics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanbar17000022 It was . It is a must go @VegasToyCon . You will not be disappointed 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listened to a coach tell his players they sucked and the only way for them to be successful was as a part of his “s… https://t.co/v216p32mZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast bar (at @FrischsBigBoy in Chillicothe, OH) https://t.co/LrEpXlzAnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimJatras @TakeThatEpi @NuckChorris16 @RosaRubicon When you are ready to debate evolution, I am ready. If you want… https://t.co/9HhuKx5njw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theonly_phil_j 😂 I don't know about that. It's just because it was my facts vs her feelings made it sound smarter than I actually am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe this is the first and only time that I ever agreed with Ann Coulter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneknottsports Yeah he is every small business in STL  Thinking yay March is here no more snow  And yeah she’s Wi… https://t.co/9IbCkVv1nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a meet-and-greet yesterday (Sunday) and while the event itself was a success, what happened afterward was ano… https://t.co/t0hpy2o6Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mindwbw POSTED TO MY SITE- CHINESE INTERNET  WEEKLY    20 billion interactions on cctv about the spring festival… https://t.co/JAQJh6MNnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[On assignment at Paris Hotel and Casino unveiling the new Eiffel Tower light show on the Las Vegas Strip!!! @ Paris… https://t.co/EB03Zncvum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooklynFitChik A daughter? Whatever do you mean? #fthismoviefest #TheatricalCutHumor]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels good to be lost in the right direction. @ Rainbow Springs Head Springs https://t.co/l4n8zpX3VS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wealth_Theory @OrlandoinNYC @iancassel @SJosephBurns @AsennaWealth @naval @dmuthuk Thanks! Honored to make that li… https://t.co/GppFwM4Vx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jontlewis I think there are two seasons shown and don’t forget there are many positions held indoors as well. They’ll be fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitino did a great job in the first half getting Gabe some clean looks, specifically out of TO’s. Great to see.  Ga… https://t.co/6iXdiPg7HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT I’d do anything for that @jstaley74 #TeamMVPs card. ANYTHING! #MyFavoritePlayer @49ers #Faithful https://t.co/CAUJw1XA2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[People comparing pain like bank accounts , I'm tryna see how wide that smile get]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lee: "The state of our state is hopeful and prosperous and strong."  #TNSOS #wmc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLatinos4US @MarcoGutierrez @realannapaulina @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews We need leaders all across the bo… https://t.co/WFrDIPbleR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skycaptain25 You know he hurt himself more on the flop than the actual minor bump from Scott]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Your Business Can Say 'I Do' to Millennial-Targeted Wedding Trends https://t.co/YVBb3QT3kw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about cord-cutting? I did it — here’s what I found out https://t.co/sh5fYjZqnO via @BostonGlobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surfing is amazingly free sport. It's just me and the waves and the ocean treats everyone the same. So when I see t… https://t.co/ACtENVOsHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoryCakes1 @spanmoustache @TweettopVillage @blog_micro Cops are pussies who blow everything out of proportion thou… https://t.co/djIm4JfbKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thmsftz Bruh. We can both agree. Gerrymandering gives government a lot of power. Ending it is perhaps the most bip… https://t.co/EzsSSTdYKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CiBVS4jlPj Get reliable help at our Verizon Customer Service Phone Number 1-855-431-6111… https://t.co/YbasCBcIms]]></document><document><![CDATA[nice day for a long walk @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/avMmAHJbgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yurifucker Damn that's worse than when I was trying to put Jotaro's face on and I cut my finger open  How old is t… https://t.co/DplDNlV2PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The feeling when you wake up in Houston and realise the U.S. moved overnight into summer time https://t.co/lpmKpy8WLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out and Thank you for your support dernishia76 i appreciate you ...    🔥🍹🔥#fiya_flava #drinks #colorful… https://t.co/NZhFL3BNlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJ90803 @RealJamesWoods And George Zimmerman’s family isn’t having to visit a vegetative George left to die on tha… https://t.co/YiK9tbmnLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfa Really?? Is this guy for real?? Good grief! That’s like saying where would we be if the caveman hadn’t invent… https://t.co/l1PyLWAmGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really be bashing servers lmao god forbid somebody you care about become one so y’all can really understand how shit works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked one of @AnnCoulter's tweets. This truly is personal emergency.   #NotesFromNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LumLotus Until ppl start winning in court due to these whispernet allegations, rumors will have no consequences. I… https://t.co/6JMarmMd9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rockprincess818 @Lonestar357 Gee look at this pig whore slut https://t.co/83Vmcq4YvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Insanity_Toy When you’re teeth are like this after a bite don’t be complaining 😂 https://t.co/qoVq6RHtkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think you read the over all ratings wrong the 52% is your disapproval rating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mizzou could easily burst a bubble down the stretch, and I’m totally here for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost @AAFFleet tailgating time in Section C3! Come out and meet the many San Diego fans!!! #AllHandsOnDeck… https://t.co/jtKyLf2pYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul I understand our principals and that is great if your opponents share them. For the past two years our op… https://t.co/surFDJvYNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be successful in any financial market, as an investor, your mindset matters. I have three(3) watchwords for gene… https://t.co/gVXUHXkaaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Stubbs @HockeyHallFame And Eddie Giacomin without a mask down and beaten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cillakilla1995 Finally someone else appreciates Lady Gaga as I do in the Berben household 😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mannyfuckyeah Megalodon es una película de cine B con el budget de avengers. Dátela.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short Show today for OOB, Hog Baseball today at 2:30pm.. we will have: 2pm @DannyWest1  Hogs Hoops Lose 6th Straigh… https://t.co/fMLS2gnO0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing better than waking up at 3am still drunk and having COLD bottle of water ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[To add insult to injury @amazon pulled their bid to build their new HQ due to concerns that their employees might c… https://t.co/bipV67qeU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_p84 damn thats awful. north bay area? im 6 hours south but i put it out on my TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trouble_R4 coming to CFL this weekend, if you make it down to St. Cloud I got a Blizzard at DA with your name on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[kyle: *rips wax pen and coughs for 13 minutes*  five seconds later  also kyle: “and then he rose in 3 days”  i actu… https://t.co/boNIwDgLL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meg_onthe_News @kaylathomasoma @ShaneEwing @AlysonAcklin @KAKEnews Thanks Megs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson yea pretty much the whole ball game..I assume you include Castro?...he could win nevada az and texas]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's No Such Thing As an 'Ideal' Engineer, Male or Female https://t.co/aaiNk8acVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeezusKhrist He’s gotta take after the chip roots can’t stray too far...]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WHTribe girls lead @BBAthletics 11-8 after 1 period in Somerset County (NJ) Tournament @AmitBatraHS… https://t.co/RKM1XupYSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IStandWithIlhan.  Because I have grown tired of republican lite same lousy taste just a different bottle #IStandWithIlhan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianSimsPA @RhondaJonesLevy shes jealous because the vein on her face,caused by her pettiness, is not as big as the kids 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted: my @townhallcom column on yesterday's ridiculous "anti-hate" resolution:  https://t.co/bUfChx4hBu… https://t.co/3D5blUEcMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Dartman #1 is available on digital at https://t.co/1QepIUYpiN https://t.co/zdWYGShI0S]]></document></documents></author>