<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[“I just found out that the time my dad had me drive him to a colonoscopy he was really getting snipped”]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco public defender Jeff Adachi dies at 59  https://t.co/L48BxhPXM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can also type out a tweet saying i talked to ticketmaster and they told me there’s going to be a vip ticket that… https://t.co/6GjYEG1fYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone ever wants to send me cute postcards or doodles to add to my wall please do🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte We need to do an.Ethics complaint any one can do it will u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevAdamHamilton @TheCall_Holston Wow.. Had a feeling that was coming.  Alum from two UMC colleges.  @millsapscollege @emoryandhenry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet @ZzzQuil is targeting journalists. I need a good night’s sleep. #TwitterAds #KnowingYourAudience https://t.co/E0NyDzMzAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very impressive. All the names they called him..He kept his head and faith..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you work best in a team environment? 👭Looking for open minded individuals with great work ethic and a desire to… https://t.co/chzZrD86vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations hamiltonchargerscheer for earning 1st Place in Varsity Medium at Sun Prairie Cardinal Classic today… https://t.co/ktG19XBLfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend a women asked me and parker if we were mother and daughter. I really just wanna know which one of us s… https://t.co/5V90HNqgj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze They should change the name of his show to Mourning Joe!  Such a sour, negative, woe is me kind of guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the asian man in the background is exactly how my dad acts anytime i do anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random acts of kindness are doing. God’s will. Let’s all try to do something kind for someone today. Love happens o… https://t.co/3ALu4uP70I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CounselorMegan Congrats!!  Well deserved!  Both of you work very well together!! Thank you for all you do for the kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemma🐶♥️ #easylikesundaymorning #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #lovethemback #petsofcanidae… https://t.co/mAMOrDnh2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna be so mad if the girls loose to a one direction member agian#BRITVIDLITTLEMIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberDick @mmlanz333 Lol ! Talking about illegals taking American jobs away !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to @ConnistonMiddle on this huge recognition! @BankofAmerica is proud to support this awesome… https://t.co/QeSYirg9j1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlumRemson @NancyBarto So parents should be able to place their children in danger because they want to take a sta… https://t.co/198rYIQil0]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in my class group me really be trying to squeeze everybody for all the answers. I’ve already had two people… https://t.co/9p5VFEPItM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn! @k8bischHRLaw your posts are 🔥 this morning! It's all I need in my feed! #HappyFriday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapsindepthcbs @YandR_CBS @JessicaCollins @DollyParton @YRInsider Congratulations! Can’t wait to see you on the screen again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GirlScouts Sunday at Fredonia First United Methodist Church.  We also had a tray of Girl Scout Cookies in the back… https://t.co/w23l42zn8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an editor, I found my time spent editing hundreds of articles and actively championing Herb as a leading voice o… https://t.co/4vs49rzd9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching my usual @WGNMorningNews @WGNNews. @seanlewiswgn needs to work on his puns. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to chuckle. Grumpy kitty's just gotta wear shades! https://t.co/D5rnbRsr00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Demonrats are fine with abortion period, at any stage. Maybe they don't use birth control for religi… https://t.co/y3IYG1dq0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would and will murder right now for “ex-pat living in Germany” style falafel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[KNIGHTS WIN AGAIN! Over D2 Charleston 6-1! HUGE way to finish the day 2-0 going into a HUGE match tomorrow vs. a to… https://t.co/qf1ximEbxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just know when halsey releases her new album im either gonna be in love or heartbroken tbh most likely both]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big thank you to Western Trial Lawyers Association for inviting me to moderate a great panel, speak about physica… https://t.co/0fqdzMDPtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my birthday and I’m crying cause I’m an emotional wreck and I feel loved and I don’t know what to do with myself ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you find your peace? Do you find yourself veering off track too? https://t.co/XpqsmbheYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your days are numbered what you going to do when they come for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@downey @DrewBMcIntyre Why yes. The one he chose not to share even when asked ahead of time! #gcumc #gc2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge @docrocktex26 There’s something he doesn’t want to show until he’s the nominee and we can’t do anythi… https://t.co/oHZ6daAxQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamwhrbrf But Donna isn’t a lawyer, privilege doesn’t apply to her. But I can see her saying something along those… https://t.co/N9ZVQVOdP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime Inaccuratsies! WTF? The bar is set below sea level. The truth is now a mild suggestion. Say whateve… https://t.co/MDy7MaaJkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed with this song i swear @iamcardib @BrunoMars #pleaseme https://t.co/R49jV4YFWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrackett316 @JakeSnakeDDT @SCOTTHALLNWO Yes get out DDPYogaNOW goto user guide then click on the LIST @DDPYoga DDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a magical day making this EP at @sound_emporium a few weeks back. Thank you for making this possible. 💛 Feelin… https://t.co/I7K4fEMAlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorothyDalton @AvidCareerist @CareerTrend Sending a thank you after an used to be expected...but few did it. Handw… https://t.co/PNKG9eAo7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @peetscoffee do we have to discontinue the coconut whip cream? Some of us non dairy folks would LOVE to have it stay on the menu!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what she enjoyed most - Disney or the manatees❤️ https://t.co/csJspu1d0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[pianists, violinist, drummers and sax players hold a very special place in my heart. cause whew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I was in Jacksonville to run the #GateRiverRun15k with my fam. But even in frozen NJ I’m still supporting… https://t.co/8W0re6rIAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS Wow, @realDonaldTrump has really turned a new leaf since the ‘70s when he and his old man were i… https://t.co/d9JJjNJqeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's essentials for going to the grocery store, coming home and reading the rest of the day. 🙆🏼‍♀️ @ Nashville,… https://t.co/oq2Ch07OGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[California’s excessive use of force law has not been updated since 1800’s, #AB392 is CA’s opportunity for meaningfu… https://t.co/LXay4EEf2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeptofDefense @USArmy I’d like to know what book-pg. that is and what it says!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lastnight after we finished dinner at our fancy ass restaurant, the waitress said the bill was taken care of and… https://t.co/knVrsTG1II]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeddraASmith @BuzzFeed Hahahaha!!!  This is the one I was dying about! 😂😂😂😂😂😂   Don't forget about the darker hair!!  #BeautyPagentAnswer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trynagetlikeyou A worthy man has to have 34D breast https://t.co/ItPvuZJB8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Yet Trump is a billion times a better person then you Bette]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rape is a serious offense. Rape is a nonconsenting forceful act of sexual penetration. Thursday night, 2/28/2019 wa… https://t.co/lHKfNg5x9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebookviking @boulderpolice We'll be watching this very closely and so will a lot of others]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week 34: contemplating my first @amazonnow order for ice cream....too bad I’m not sure I’ll still be up at 9:00 when it could be delivered 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @realDonaldTrump Couldn’t agree more! It’s a travesty of truth, lack of temerity and total treachery on… https://t.co/wkyA1d58jR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraysonDolan i love you more than anything else in the world with all my heart ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No politician should be in the middle of this difficult decision. A woman should be free to make all her own health… https://t.co/UlCfirkfna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laker622 @realDonaldTrump It was a real travesty  Postponing Cohen hearing to coincide with N. Korea nuclear summi… https://t.co/nk1yAMRhkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddFitchette Great photo! Does WeatherNation have your permission to share this on all platforms with full credit to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final-MSC Magnifica @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/742CBEArzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a nice time hanging out at the #beach . It is so wonderful that even thru #LakeJackson and sand, we can conn… https://t.co/kI9jSvsHNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hair salon time with my favorite girl! #mommydaughterfun #momlife #girltime #hangingwiththemini #beautysalon #laughs]]></document><document><![CDATA[US only unless willing to pay shipping. I'll also do a trade for books! DM me if interested! https://t.co/TDLfnEKK5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRBballCoach This was a hard watch...again!!  Great half time talk coach!  Everything I was thinking in the stands....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIZ_JJC @marissatweeting Nothing could have made those songs good except not singing them]]></document><document><![CDATA[some guy told me he was gonna be my money slave and send me $200 every sunday but he hasn’t followed through ugh men are trash :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[You still have  1 1/2 hours to catch @artistprojectto at The Better Living Centre in toronto.ontario.canada .  Grea… https://t.co/oLqJ4hStV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @maddow @sarahkendzior #StandOnEveryCorner #KremlinAnnex #Resist 💥Definitely This✨👉🏼✨⏩|A Nation of Weavers https://t.co/OEXjtVE2CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diannamorgan44 Honey, it is sad but you are above that!  You’ve always been good to him and his family...just rise… https://t.co/zDEXptcJz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyHinkler and @ElizabeeHinkler both have my heart and make it full of happiness and love everyday because they… https://t.co/gWTcltJ2uB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiegossage @MikeLeslieWFAA @wfaa @MikeDoocyFox4 @KDFWsports @DISupdates Great weekend @TXMotorSpeedway for the D… https://t.co/QTPqvBpj37]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌 OMG YES! Mind power is where it all begins! Trust me I struggle  I am struggling but I have goals in mind and I C… https://t.co/L45KjumNSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Everything in moderation.  2. Never turn your back on the ocean.  🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tokidoki!!! (@ Books Kinokuniya in New York, NY) https://t.co/62vp55zrxH https://t.co/L1lP5C3Zwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Making a horses ass out of himself daily. He’s great at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueBitesUK i have a question for you! ... should you start doing donuts!? 👀🍩 #donut #bacondonut #destinationdonut https://t.co/7GDXkONdFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump  Sir,  This made me cry, see name below and you'll know why‼️  Did McCabe Consider Trump As… https://t.co/LQW1CpgMzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, have faith. Look at polls about how people view socialism. Millennials will be the largest voting block next… https://t.co/lJ4KEW4b1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo más puntos en mi tarjeta de Benavides que en la del cine. #Quetriste]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh please, we’re all floundering through this life together. No one *actually* has their shit together 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[#A Lion Is Born #oilpainting #oiloncanvas #36x36 #sanfrancisco #cityscape I titled this piece “a lion is born” beca… https://t.co/8r9YGp0iOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mteague I agree. Two of my great Uncle’s  were  survivors of Pearl Harbor, one on the Oklahoma and one on the Arizona. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to my awesome team taking home the awards last pm!! @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/1MFw2bSmGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you still live with your baby daddy and want to be taken seriously as someone to date/build with?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinningWordsPro @Sparblack1213 @MsMollyRachael Is this with no insurance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevibooo my advice is to let it wash over you while in a state of ambivalence and then later tonight scream at the moon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zopo82 @fras99 Maybe they’re going to take Jesus of the cross n put his Jesus n his God since they both have a sol… https://t.co/pJm8q2E5Wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any word on coach k's back problems? I just saw reddish on the floor and wondered if k might have to go in for emer… https://t.co/gmoS3yAELB]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Maryland, a tax accountant told one of my teacher colleagues she’d have to make $300,000 a year not to be materi… https://t.co/TOlGmhTiGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing this Amazing program Day One with New Hires!! 100% is Phenomenal!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This could be a really fun "first picture" to send to people. Hilarious. HAHAHAHA https://t.co/osND74s4Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[H.D. is one of like, I dunno, four people I’d actually trust with Artemis’ voice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my @OrigamiOwl charms in the mail today! For my angel in heaven. 💖 #breastcancerawareness #pink #angelwings https://t.co/LJf2P8ngG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to pick a fight with Digo for 1000 Cookies and lost... https://t.co/PBimmyfhbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to John Somosi for sharing his talent and knowledge with the students attending the Northern Spirit Games… https://t.co/MI2QuGwPFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll tell you why... bcuz it does not fit the entire Mockingbird Media’s narrative on who President Trump is and th… https://t.co/FiMRbRl6Bj]]></document></documents></author>