<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[To be fair, she's only spewing out the political vomit that liberal educators have brain washed her with. She has b… https://t.co/vWEKIcj1sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to screenwriters: Please no more references to scorpions and frogs. It’s been done. Over and over. Come up wit… https://t.co/JQVhcPSfWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @Comey He is as crooked as they come he belong in jail now not making millions on his lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Round1🏋🏽 #Good Afternoon My Beautiful Family 😘😍and Friends/People #NewGoals💪🏽🏋🏽‍♂️ #YouSeeMyGrowth💪🏽🏋🏽‍♂️… https://t.co/yZbyRKAjlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CATERINAV si lo detienen el grupo de Lima dirá hay q dialogar para q lo suelten NO JODAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@todaysbird I have tremendous respect for your agency and its mission. The entertainment industry routinely depicts… https://t.co/p3tCQiaT2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to be on my radio show tonight? Text 813-602-2715 between the hours of 7 PM to 9 PM Eastern time, and you’ll b… https://t.co/EAeIBi5LmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Randy_Couture thank you Legend! #ttmsuccess #autograph #collection #hobby @ Waukesha, Wisconsin https://t.co/YWWS6Qealz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump #OurRealFoundingFathers https://t.co/hCGQsYqKFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiPolar28201476 @Falcongod082 @thiagogpires @CNN Says the guy on Twitter, using a smartphone or tablet created by… https://t.co/DnV2ISQUCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Middleton , a photon camera release 5/8 full power , 64 percent sir , The beautiful year I was born, At your com… https://t.co/OnIje5DJlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insanity. Purposefully misleading your viewers is so disgusting. When their viewers average age is mid-70s… https://t.co/Rzp8b1Q77F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it again with the #CapozziWeeklyMonologue - this time I only gave myself a true hour to memorize and film i… https://t.co/au2VMSDs3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's not drag this out any MORE!  REMOVE TRUMP by MOST  expedient law. - - #25thAmendmentNOW!  America, even the P… https://t.co/lNZQJn20BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when folks like @Jim_Jordan said how authoritarian Obama acted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Samuel Adams Bavarian Lager by @SamuelAdamsBeer @ North Hampton, NH — https://t.co/C9ddYYHJPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurbedLA Easy, put a 99 cents store on every other corner. Next question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[purdue's actions have at best just led to restarting the offense in neutral and then starting a new action, but usu… https://t.co/n9PptAG37Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports And "honorably discharged" sounds like a quote from a male porn star's obit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMGGaryde @ArizonaKayte I heard she wanted to donate her BRAIN to science and was rejected, but Peta has shown much interest. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coraisiordia me quedo con tu análisis del partido y sobre todo poniendo en su lugar a @vichernandezm que solo se la pasa cargando al tuca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieCarvin @MAAWLAW @AaronWherry And if I said Canada had a problem with terrorism financing ... ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerbRider It's clear after Fallen Kingdom they are trying to take it in a planet of the Apes route but let's face… https://t.co/rLOx8pDdhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxduchaine Again agenda, I was at the game when he hurt his wrist. Yes when he first went down people were being… https://t.co/K1IlAFPT3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort is now asking for a reduced sentence.  NO https://t.co/oRsogVaDxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwallinga @torontomusicsvc @mschoendorff Is it bad that my gut is to put Twitter notoriety above being a composer… https://t.co/DTrfiI4mw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[From that 1st step on stage, until the last step one getting off, I promise you that I am in a whole other world. I… https://t.co/HIfwDLqsnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ya shorty knows what these are for you deserve better https://t.co/CIfADbw6Hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senile dementia afflicted old White Collar crime forgiving judge certainly not of sound judgement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hweetener @MattEdw12312749 @herdiningtable @KetoHiking @esnythirls @cfahey14 @paulwesley @Edival @Cynwel73… https://t.co/5kDwrOWi8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen Dia Raza Que Pasen No Solo Un #FelizDomingo Sino Un Feliz #DiaDeLaBandera Y De Los #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeBearison Who is arming kids? What tweets are you reading? And guess what, all of the warnings were there, an… https://t.co/tjb3gFePD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serge Przedborski, MD, PhD, told Neurology Today that as in other neurodegenerative disorders such as ALS, the stud… https://t.co/4iqZrzqmnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackKingston Jack don’t make yourself look smaller and non relevant then you already are by trying to jest Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it take to create a magazine cover look!?? Lots of intricate details about the editorial vision, colors,… https://t.co/nrPpSxwFA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one tooth that hurts when I deadlift. Anyone every experience this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mathewsinc Vertix  In Sub-alpine, flatline bars w/ #shrewd Atlas mount, Nock-on Elevate 2.0 rest, Accent Assault V… https://t.co/isBAtPNHJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 Suffering though it, because I refuse to dump Dragon’s Milk down the drain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwingmanBrown practicing the routine for the @OntarioBlueJays pro day on Monday https://t.co/qPt9MlxB8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kendallmm I will ABSOLUTLEYYYY be going 💓💓 gabs said you guys had v much fun so I’m so esssiiiited 🤸🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks and sounds like a war zone outside with the barrage of flashes and explosions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuraPuffs In Splinter Cell Double Agent you have the choice to double cross someone. Gameplay wise it’s one of the… https://t.co/5TAAUmEbAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! Great addition! Fletch and Jackson side by side in 2019....scary!  #FlyEaglesFly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in line for groceries talking to a friend on the phone about places to take portraits in Berkeley and I said… https://t.co/A2AnooOLxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FtBraggNC fort Bragg let me keep my Brigadier rank but were really happy that a general walked into the PC buying… https://t.co/y1LV5gbUKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottKCMO @BrianHartleyKC Not sure about all of that — didn’t ask — but a sustainable source of revenue is needed… https://t.co/5mwZiKTLZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @libertyflames @LibertyU for making the big dance. @ASUNMBB conference champs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuerpo entambado en Colonia Federal. Al parecer del sexo masculino https://t.co/SnHACbMhPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The U.S. sent a B-52 bomber through the South China Sea for the first time in months https://t.co/FGn0Hv8YWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee Doesn't look broken but definitely inflammation. Possibly torn tendon. Let us know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're at Bar, go buy some merch from these fine folks. Or maybe even an 8x10 shot by yours truly 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KernelKelly Me too...me too. True proof of the amazing things small businesses do... hope there are some left tomorrow. #friedapplepies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sereen2011 @TakinBackAshley @ChevRoss100 I am not a father, nor will I look like one anytime soon. I’ll shave my b… https://t.co/iQtzGVxpmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chinmay2000fore @billboardcharts @billboard @Madonna @MariahCarey @JanetJackson @rihanna @olivianj @ArethaFranklin… https://t.co/LqoqCvFoNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I had a quarter for every Valentine’s Day snap I skipped... I’d buy Cuba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_C_Campbell Yeah so the children of people who use drugs won't eat either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TransitGeekJoe @trimet Those who "input" rail aren't the ones who NEED transit - those who NEED transit are busy a… https://t.co/GajGlXrAHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthShoreRalph Not gonna make that. But I’m hopeful MU gets sent to Hartford for the NCAAs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whomartyp I’m looking for a safer alternative but I might just have to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivmonk Hi Viv! Yes, we always stay here too..I actually didn't bring good shoes! Might have to go shopping 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse I love this picture❣️ It shows President Trump’s love for the American Flag and for the people in America❣️🙏🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetEmDot @EdgarrC__ Nigga said I’m open minded but don’t talk to me lmaoooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correct me if I’m wrong, but aren’t the only appropriate people to autograph a bible the ones who have been dead fo… https://t.co/AtmPkHHGWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottCo53391272 Created a national emergency for a wall. Yet fires and tornadoes killing people is just another da… https://t.co/OOuwh2U9h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday morning training...here we go! #chaseyourbetter @ Exceed Physical Culture https://t.co/UyBC5cM471]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @HardballChris THEY ARE FOOLING AROUND WITH TRUMPS LAWYER AND THIS ANT-SEMETIC THAT TRUMP SAYS AND THEY ARE… https://t.co/F4WN9UaX4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about you, but I’ve had enough of this “lay flat to dry” bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy Your decision to do #cinematography and #editing categories during commercials is shameful. You don’t h… https://t.co/wFx3HXmzkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Vancouver, WA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/Okd484kv9r #diversity #highered]]></document><document><![CDATA[When was the last time I had cfa? Thinks for two seconds, oh yeah Saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllDayAllGay @goodkindalex this is the most untrue statement i have ever heard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Need To Hear This Marine Vet&amp;#8217;s Response To Dixie Chicks&amp;#8217; War Controversy https://t.co/5TPovfwHXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we skip the next 10 years to where I’m happily running my vegan cafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do anything to not fall - #defydetroit #defy #tumbling #gymnastics #gymnast #cheer #cheerleading #flipping… https://t.co/P9nilwNHTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chesleydohl I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770 Boston massacre Soldiers were… https://t.co/TIPpCQJvTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyWischmann @cspanwj No because I don’t let tragedy control my emotions. I can still think logically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All aboard the wine train! Thank you for the wedding gift pollyknowles aworlledge gruvmw besto00004 @jstardan 🍇🥂🚂 @… https://t.co/deSieQOuWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck #DirkNowitzki⁠ ⁠ in @NBAAllStar @swish41 @dallasmavs #dirkhashtagemojishouldbea 🐐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am starting to journal my successes (and failures) as I push for a two-hour or less half marathon time. Started m… https://t.co/O7i6N4XWdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just scared myself half to death because this is what was on my screen when I unlocked my laptop  @MatPatGT… https://t.co/GG1h06rKEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for my favorite frequent flyer program at https://t.co/mgqMqUQmYC Join me @freddieawards #VoteFreddies… https://t.co/YH7tQWXxHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is shining, things are about to 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥up!  #happysaturday @ Fort Collins, Colorado https://t.co/ai1YiLqzNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[running on ZERO sleep but ya girl is FEELIN herself https://t.co/YHVrphLk1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustAskLizz @LesMarvelous @AMHotFlash I get that. I lived through Nixon's impeachment hearings that the house had,… https://t.co/V5oX3I8uoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FireBrownell The SEC is and always will be the best football and baseball conference.  The financial support and d… https://t.co/FYaztLJVUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dragonkick #iwannakickitlikebruce #belikewater @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/p4fSG5A8NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few laps around the Loop with some Marvin’s Room sounds nice but gas is espensive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz I worked in sales for a company that provided FX services to small and medium businesses.  I set up a m… https://t.co/THxV2zG8dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Model Y public presentation and leases on Model 3 now available 🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennweintraub @realDonaldTrump Complete lack of couth and it’s his Club!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaSveta amazing cover! Your voice is amazing I cannot wait for your next cd release! #Queen #Cover #Amelchenko https://t.co/0VHVvclGue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Thanks for that primer. I have a daughter that was diagnosed with ADHD in her early 20’s. What you describe fits her to a T.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Caturday  Thanks for flying SouthWest Airlines we will be around shortly with beverage and snacks. thank you. https://t.co/ISuSw8RVhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aniddda @DantonKHilton @UMSLAthletics @UMSLMBB @CoachJesseShaw Get it Coach!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chill_GOD__ The fact that they’re are actually married annoys me I hate seeing people live out my dreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lotuspapi Best friends can be cute and all...until..... https://t.co/qRpiKca19j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son and me got to meet the one and only #actionbronson #themanthemyththelegend @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/TRVIAfULiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to do your taxes? I used @creditkarmatax. Check it out! It was super easy, totally free and 100% awesome. Swee… https://t.co/Dy1oUN7PnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBardTalks The core risk of severe storms is north and west of Birmingham]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started editing the video from our trip to Guadeloupe today! Little rusty but I'm getting back into the swing of th… https://t.co/mT7sEjffkS]]></document></documents></author>