<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TejDhaliwal87 He’s skilled.  That has nothing to do with Captaincy.  Captaincy is dealing with offficials, media,… https://t.co/tprgyODpIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[20,000 jobs added, unemployment rate down to 3.8%. Looks like the partial government shutdown and a slowdown in con… https://t.co/gXlWo3KXio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VernMcKinley @nomiprins And a super-important stakeholder who could make his life vey miserable is Maxine Waters.… https://t.co/3Ix4q3i9gS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tides of Galway Irish Red by @FrothyBeard @ Grateful Brew — https://t.co/XkON9eRQmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blunted2themax_ that’s what i did &amp; dead ass best thing i ever did for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSportsnet @thetender1987 @stephgonzz 8ans / 9million et plus pour stone fait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottch81 Please close your eyes and let you see exactly what Trump got  compared to what Obama got]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aterkel @grumpybirdieS ......which proves that most people don't give a shit that "he's not a democrat" He's not d… https://t.co/oW8dkchY27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapgamequaZmoto @Pabl0GRIN @SpeaveGRIN @JesusEverest Dude that fucking sucks!! Weirdest/best show ever. Lehi legend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trapqueenleah Awesome. To keep it real with you, Chief, my room is kinda messy, so I can't judge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher ❤from Louisville, Ky @cher. You are  indeed a priceless Diva!🧜‍♀️♥️🌎⏰⏳🎵🎶🎤#Herewegoagain #cher2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting on the brakes!  Tomorrow - Spring Season Begins - My ABs Thread. Enjoy 😎 https://t.co/PgEpKHdvB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier @SpecialReport Hey Risky lib ,please do some follow up on the Words of Democratic party, i find 87% what… https://t.co/BQ7u36UCZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinObs i am updating to build 18863 20H1 and its going rather smoothly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLGranucci @NRafter @NYCAviation @HAbbott4 @PhilDernerJr And only when the @FAANews truly doesn't care about  the… https://t.co/qYnphRJqD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper And they can all plead the 5th @jaketapper. After witnessing that charade yesterday, I beg… https://t.co/JQthucTGsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del Rosa CA Tue Mar 5th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Rain Lo 49 WEDNESDAY Chance Of T-Storm Hi 61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karyncupcakes @JimmyFromPhilly @DickToledo @HMSon98 They should be pissed at themselves, but rather  today most us… https://t.co/AS6pq5sQdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update the parents just told their kids they can’t go to Disney world for vacation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elarue2323 Dude let’s out a grunt louder than my headphones so I laugh my ass off, they give me the death stare the whole time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Please read @dwallacewells book, "The Uninhabitable Earth." Time is ticking and #GlobalWarming is acc… https://t.co/2cntA22sxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Juicy Jay by @LegionBrewing at @harrysclt — https://t.co/VuV8EwEpEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got out of 2.5 hour meeting with a teenage Olympic hopeful about building her Instagram ahead of the 2020 Toky… https://t.co/cEbwAqjzUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuelans removing road blocks to humanitarian aid &gt; #FreeVenezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Prayers, love and hugs.  I hoping you get through this mess soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriving Tomorrow #craftbeer #beer #ipa #dipa #beer #draftbeer #growlerfill #beerlover #newenglandipa #hazyipa… https://t.co/QxmLoCTll2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conservatives who decry Justin Trudeau's role in #lavscam should be equally upset about Doug Ford's blatantly nepot… https://t.co/nAqXIjQPzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerrythornton1 Two giant jackasses although Mazz has been right about this Kyrie issue with #Celtics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hanstaekwondo #taekwondobakersfield good luck Gian! @ Las Vegas Convention Center https://t.co/0gTqyKrGRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@temterune You look a wee bit different than when we met at Kay n Dave's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And gosh, just imagine all the folks who don’t speak at all because they need time to form their opinions or gather… https://t.co/TbCBLNwFJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mastercharls @TigresOficial No se llenaba ese estadio desde la final regia .. ningún equipo este torneo logro llenarlo hasta ahora]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hawthorne’s Cave. 90’ sheer underwater cliff under the snowmobile. Glaciers carved out this granite spot 14,000+ ye… https://t.co/53aIQnxBVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio Congressman Jim Jordan made a complete fool of himself. #CohenCongressionalTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes, we camped in my tent in the altitude! yes, we had a great day skiing Vail. #CO https://t.co/bFPuC7QTSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brad_frost @tbrodbeck Does that make dryer sheets just some extra seasoning? I’m liking this logic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Beth’s boss Robert for getting us Fleetwood Mac tickets tonight. Great show. No Lindsey Buckingham, but N… https://t.co/D33LfudIdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/EledPQAiDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayharding11 Lowkey one of cleanest step backs at I’ve seen . Skip to 0:50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you prefer the mountain top view? @ Desert Foothills Park https://t.co/CC0UeTYmdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGeschwind @NHLhistorygirl @n8sager @FisherJillian @SteveMcLean888 Cap era killed him. Blind loyalty to vets and b… https://t.co/fmp5uLjZP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRCaputo @PressSec I think what you meant to say is “ Crooked Donald Trump has committed so many crimes, why… https://t.co/LQO9yULDvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsJunkie80 @JoeLoAndDibs @957thegame What’s the Super Bowl count Singleton? Who has more upside? Is Santa Clara in California ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because fat never sleeps. (at @AnytimeFitness in Wauwatosa, WI) https://t.co/LwJgZtP5ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 22nd 8:00 p.m.  Santa Barbara, Ca  click the link in my bio for tickets…  Tickets are limited!… https://t.co/G78XtoGLJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse WTF are YOU Morons ON? Everyday Deflect, Try To Change The Truth For Your Own Narrative BS. Typical Far… https://t.co/XKeVucwj9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAGAt Senator Mike Rounds just said that tRump’s payouts toto Cohen was him “handling some family issues.” Is the E… https://t.co/1CtMqdJ07U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsungMobile whats the difference other than the in the year it was made A5, S9 Galaxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LastWeekTonight future of #jobs = “A series of non routine tasks that require social intelligence, complex critic… https://t.co/kYcciFIeke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___JesusFreak Until he gets caught in a public bathroom somewhere. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[PHOTO GALLERY: @goghosts defeat @RedRaidersHoops in overtime for DIstrict Championship https://t.co/VjCjTWiolD… https://t.co/vRYstff9Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realksuz It's a cool thing to watch, but I'm still rooting for that blond girl in red who was with them at the end!  🙂 @katreceveur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasperBeaumont Puppylupagus called Puppy and J.D. for John Doe because he was a lost Pup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2019 Gander RV Duel at Daytona winners, Kevin Harvick and Joey Logano. 🏁🏆 #nascar #daytona #speedweeks… https://t.co/j7wVKDqccN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobtwells01 Honestly, can’t decide if I’m feelin Fat Albert or Einstein #tossup #albert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyOtt3r Please don't respond to my political tweets. I'd like to keep any interactions with you to poker/sports.… https://t.co/y9QLMkWzq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dansolomonza @NBCNewsTHINK @realDonaldTrump The whole piece is about Justice Thomas’s opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man rollo was the OG of your parents “that one friend they never liked “‼️r.i.p. Mr. Taylor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the new Oregon’s Elite Twitter, the old one got locked on accident so go give it a follow! @theoregonselite]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a younger coach I am truly #blessed to be surrounded everyday by such great coaches, mentors and human beings. T… https://t.co/aQEamgpA3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobSantarelli No no no, I’ve just been taking that “u like it u buy it” this a bit too seriously]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciative of yesterday’s discussion with @naacpyouthffx on delivering more affordable housing in NOVA https://t.co/xFrh99nced]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year for lent I’m giving up even more of my free time to serving my customers. If you’re not seeing success in… https://t.co/Isl7vrm0uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A thing happened when I try to upload a video it didn’t went out in what I completely the editing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NgahuiaHarold You said it sweetie, you got some good stuff, keep it coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to thank the_shelf_life for the inspiration to make this absolutely delicious bowl for this mornings breakfa… https://t.co/cghTpdwnio]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not apologizing for being busy anymore. Either you understand or you don’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSchwenke @GovEvers How about this for a change of topic https://t.co/jIXqGtozTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never said I had all my ducks in a row, but they're all in the same pond so at least I have that going for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally Race Day!!!!  Time for some Daytona 500 racing!!!  #Nascar #ChaseElliott https://t.co/2KHi2Q6x5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔊 sound on. Priveleged to share my "Open Rant" with Heather @BoxProMag . The @crossfitgames Open is a blast for mem… https://t.co/TP5x4A3Mcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SleekLarryKE @SSIIIIUUUU I believe Zaha would be better up front for United than Icardi to be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 @SinghPooja98525 The pathetical liars I'm the one that hides her panties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScrumRyanRadio @tjcm200 Get wild and crazy, Tom! https://t.co/TunovOQr0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending @balletwest1 ‘s production of “Swan Lake,” with @saramkelly and #TeamDiVa2011.… https://t.co/5hK3UyRLm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brigitte_youman  Hi! Stick with the Right of center Conservatives. (Read your bio)  Without any affiliation you ar… https://t.co/VGRGHYnUuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejoertr @RealSaavedra @TheBodySays And don’t forget Al Franken also...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Tell me again who doesn’t except the results of elections]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shots from @TerrierWBB going up against @RamblersWBB last night at The Roof https://t.co/dZAPACqUou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historylvrsclub For what it is worth, I was around 14-years-old and read that Charlotte Rampling was "nubile" in a… https://t.co/YgcdPQ7n3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody gets a little dumber every time they listen to Ocasio Cortez. I’ll never understand how someone so stupid… https://t.co/wUyCWsYlx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods DTL Iron - P7.5 In-line release @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/7GnBKBuiMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @AOC #MAGA #Trump2020 #Donaltrumpjunior for governor and #Ericktrump major of #Newyork]]></document><document><![CDATA[had a whole ass crime scene at my house, my mom's live here y'all needa quit playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHENDEREAOW @zackgreenwx @NBC10 Little squall in EP came &amp; went quickly at 4:30am!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesireeNavarro @DiazBeatri No. Tenemos los necesarios, no hacen falta mas. Todos están colocados en el gobierno me… https://t.co/g5qhzqWl8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distinct_Words I block about 3% of my followers due to solicitation or wanting to get married to the perfect man... LOL 🇺🇸🇮🇱🇨🇦🇬🇧🦁⚖️🙏🏽😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I get a @TeddiMellencamp accountably coach?! I need someone to tell me to put the pizza down. https://t.co/CKLyMKPG0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turki_AlOwerde @sicat222 @ceasere @kbsalsaud @etidalorg @FBI @Smiity646 @SamuelQPrescott @305local @bonmarche946… https://t.co/Man0GQPYlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekandSundry @DeborahAnnWoll Chaotic anything. I’ve also actually had a lot of fun with Lawful Good because it se… https://t.co/7NylGS0XPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSechrist22 Maybe he knows trout will be in Philly in a couple years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROLEX Ya know whoever came up with this concept with Directors came up an Academy Winner ...Best commercials both… https://t.co/VxkDpCikJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding all 22 college film is the hardest thing ever omg lol #MissionImpossible @nfldraftscout]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Guard against the impostures of pretended patriotism.”                    -George Washington. Have a great day, friends! ❤️✌🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's WTF is up! You go girl!!! I'll always love u. @ Moss Point Riverfront https://t.co/uLu4Pu9DVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[These last couple years have made it very difficult to stay away from politics, but man...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pork butt is in the smoker. Hoping my attempt at dinner resembles some of my favs. @adamssmokehouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeoliberalShill @CourtneyHagle Oh no. What would we do without progressive hero Bill Maher. We are truly lost with… https://t.co/K8QpxVyZAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatseflatss @ryanjjvance @ultimatesanvers Omfg. Also that fire was already big. Wtf was he doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random Led Zeppelin #foundrecord #notmine #randomvinyl #ledzeppelin #inthroughtheoutdoor #swansong #vinyl #record… https://t.co/uoTq9WXB2I]]></document></documents></author>