<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not a great end to the season @ MOCs with a dropped baton but a great season with the 4 x400m relay team running 4… https://t.co/93oWxLoV7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_Van_Damn Hi ladies i send my kisses happy cupids day let start a kissing booth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will upload the vids today. Both 6-7  minutes long. Itll prob be late in the night cause i wont be home all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to model for parents what we do each and every day with our amazing 3rd grade readers and writers!… https://t.co/CqvaSY4csb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scyian @Megan__Cutler @DKTaylorLane @jennyrglover @winter_cecily I guess my issue is that when the story is moving… https://t.co/2ndvIWGSlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Time4U2Know @VincentCrypt46 Me too. Who knows where we will all end up? The Lord bless you and keep you, brothers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want him out badly.  But I don’t want him to escape prosecution as he’s done for far too long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3DXXP_CEO19 @kaylynnjoi Someone that’s not gonna switch up and play trap music]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all #SamsungLovers!! Come check us out @BestBuy and get set up with the latest S10 with @Sprint!!… https://t.co/YXR4VUusKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DabsJk @FakeHoppe @etanthomas36 Dude you can live anywhere and still believe black people. And if you think Texas… https://t.co/SLzvXaHp9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiffordsCourage @SenatorMenendez @RepTedDeutch Thank you for introducing this bill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southernams @BillKristol Please enlighten me. Which scandals do you refer to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The confederate monument is gone. But there is no consensus on what should go in its place. I like this idea of thi… https://t.co/Q1s2LTvj1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Twitter: my soon to be 90 years old Nana has Instagram. And knows how to comment! https://t.co/d7zxsSq1xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeromeAdamsMD So @JeromeAdamsMD I would assume your somewhat intelligent?What are the true deadly effects of nicot… https://t.co/0lQjbYCfXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live like a rockstar athlete! @SHAQ’s shack can now be yours! Recently reduced. Inquire within. @TheAgencyRE… https://t.co/mr4P8WuzcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgnieszkaNR @StefanTompson @gazeta_wyborcza Prowadzenie badań nad przyczynami wzrostu antysemityzmu w Europie to antysemityzm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audiojoe13 @NeddraASmith  ..... this is a rant.....   It's time for the Black History Month performance. Again, we… https://t.co/HLRttDNPZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi does anyone wanna go to the mall with me soon and just try on clothes all day cuz I’m in the MOOD for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems Who lied for Trump and knows all his dirty little secrets. Bring it on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @carol08156 @eepeters_ep @Peeperpea29 @MarieSoapFan 🥰😘❤️😍😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost carriehodgkissfit #freedom #LiveYourBestLife  •  #soberaf #sobrietyrocks #justdoit #nofear #noshame… https://t.co/yys4qrcWNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheresaLucas3 @GenieFrancis Wow!!! When ????  Have loved her from the time she began on #GH over 40 years ago!  Sh… https://t.co/G2hMQ5LjcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Facilities Maintenance Technician" at Hobby Lobby by asking for referrals. It's a g… https://t.co/rluEDr16am]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOULD POLITICAL ATTIRE BE BANNED FROM PUBLIC SCHOOLS? I voted ABSOLUTELY on KPNX. What's your vote? https://t.co/mvuzwDM8pP    Absolutely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatManGeno @tpinsonn @tatefrazier A road game is a road game, this is the ACC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Schmutzler You are an awesome picture person- capture the moment 💕love it and thank you for being the eyes, ears… https://t.co/M7GCcITk6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanBrowne looking forward to meeting you at @YorkUedPL #PQP1 next week. @mirella_rossi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman They need discipline. I’d make them all clean bus station toilets throughout the state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReElectMW2019 if you want my vote, stop me from having to wake up EVERY MORNING hearing about all the murders arou… https://t.co/IvDn0EO7g7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland He took a "boring and lonely" job as a railway ticket clerk, which left him feeling isolated. And desp… https://t.co/1qr0TCE5pM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone giving Robert Kraft a pass on this please unfollow me immediately this is a horrible story involving human t… https://t.co/n1u89LD4OB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrWhoTimenspace The Day Of The Doctor  😀  #DoctorWho https://t.co/of6ZHwMtr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section V Boys Basketball: C.G. Finney defeats Marcus Whitman for Class C1 title https://t.co/puqa4czlx9 via @DandC… https://t.co/Ac7HfwYK0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[“that what I once did to them, out loud and without much thought, I now do in writing, with a bit more thought, to… https://t.co/lA9yGm1I4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @HillBeverlyhill You are right, but Manafort won't serve even 4 yrs. He has already served 7 months… https://t.co/nfmDLRObAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowBack #SleekSkinette With dcdivasfootball Our Female Football League Champions!!! #WhoseReady4SumFootball… https://t.co/6ooux0FtYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ieatpeas Can you imagine your mother telling you she was going on a trip, hoping to hook up with a married man, mu… https://t.co/FzuIcK1B95]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tl is made up of Animal cruelty videos, police brutality, and water pollution. I need positivity]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you start losing all  8 followers you have https://t.co/1B3zdie1eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just want everyone to know that i have $14 in my bank account right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMJoy A $400 unexpected expense? Ha. My budget is to the penny. Literally any unexpected expense, I don't even know what I'd do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know Jim Jordan read this to himself, out loud in front if the mirror this morning. #CohenTestimony https://t.co/iuqemUKw9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you entered Asmodus &amp; Sourcemore Giveaway https://t.co/KKezWVvVCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieLChaffee @Center4Fiction @katherinebhowe @jsantlofer So terrific to see you and celebrate ALL your good news. Baci, ragazzamica!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my homie Issac Chappa, the man who causes the most laughta!! 🍰🎂🍨🍧🍦 @ Havre, Montana https://t.co/qkhZRWoxHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should evaluate at the level of the Bishops' Conference whether the individual bishops are working properly and… https://t.co/wClyNfhbF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney Cat sleeps in the sun on top of the Winnie the Pooh ride. @ Disneyland https://t.co/TovXRCojTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PedritoT Yo también nene, algo desubicada come so que tenemos varias terminales 🤷🏻‍♀️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always : Why are you texting me  It’s never : come over and cuddle 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay safe my doll. #TrayvonMartin #SayHisName #GunControlNow https://t.co/Kmg5z6F2Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POzzur @trump_enemy So is winter...and the wall...the wall is collapsing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@archwaylawncare @ny_landscaper @SEA_labor @realDonaldTrump We left all we had on the table.  I know I gave every p… https://t.co/H7rFIhUqFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Amazement awaits us at every corner.” #JamesBroughton • • • Charm is a complete understatement when talking about… https://t.co/kMz0BtdJLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loraj5162014 @brycetache I know many of us have had our suspicions, but that speech sealed it, for me. He's a lunatic, and he scares me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the word of the LORD one of the company of the prophets said to his companion, "Strike me with your weapon," but… https://t.co/8o7IRUDzZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyDanceJMorg Thank you my sweet sweet friend ♥️ Always feel blessed by my career, students, grad program, and l… https://t.co/UhTLBTZq9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is who I am, this is who the fuck I am. Thank you Gaga for making me feel inspired, artistic, comforted and… https://t.co/buO24OzfIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angiecthomas This is amazing!! I love watching spiders and snakes molt. It’s so cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todo por gastarme mi dinero el viernes y ayer hoy no pude ir a disfrutar de boneless 😂😭😭 https://t.co/VvWP8VXXzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlmDMR @AysemOzleyis @agnessilence @DokuzOlmaz @PatiliCanlar @CanlaraYuva @pambikpiremses_ @sohaykodernegi… https://t.co/F4MWVMQpb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylesellers @davidscottjaffe @notaxation Not amazed. At all. I know someone who has been on these missions. Amazin… https://t.co/byn9g0mWJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanasking Oh em gee!!! I heard they bought it!!! Oh good I'm glad they are keeping it a  coffee shop/cafe now I… https://t.co/9eIvoWsOXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t stop eating. i want all the snacks. and a fooot massage cos my shit swoll😫 send help!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlutocracyToday @KyleKulinski True. She just called out a liar. A lie that was pardoned by Bush a long time ago. B… https://t.co/YsnKOzQswm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Free Children's Book Narrated by Lily Cole Helps Parents Explain Climate Change https://t.co/I9zWsWNkcx #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Native SON https://t.co/effQor3iAf https://t.co/bI3a33PmzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great! @FollowCSA @uft #inserviceofchildren #futurecollegestudents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesNGilmore Thank you for posting this, I almost posted a similar tweet, but hesitated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black History Month Speech Contest.....#GloryFitness  Don't Get Upset, Get Healthy.... #gotthatgodjuice praisefitto… https://t.co/YqPjZUhzV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTimers @billmaher @RepAdamSchiff @clairecmc @TheRickWilson @donnabrazile @BHL @HBO Your an ugly little man Mah… https://t.co/KfuHTcPpyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went on a magnetic hunt! Love hear my 1st graders use their science words and deeper level questioning with each… https://t.co/brYLJz63Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuctupMike Prostitution should be legal. Porn starts get paid to have sex. What’s the damn difference?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never saw this! @Bungie @DestinyTheGame you guys finally dropped Activision! This second paragraph sums up EXACTL… https://t.co/fLIsfLH3Jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonAnderson310 @MiaStJohnBoxer @TheStJohnFamily @Julian4Justice Iyou have my Condolences for the loss of your friend kristoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @AOC Exactly what crime did President Trump commit o getting elected look at Hillary Clinton Bill Clinto… https://t.co/Bg0d4Mt2q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why do you always protect criminals, pedophiles, white supremacist, Nazi lovers, the list goes on.… https://t.co/lgjppyyywi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekpentenburg @EndoGains I mean I guess I could be a bitch and post the Wisconsin bowl game scores for the last… https://t.co/0cBUuvPl6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The__Squealer Sounds like me when I finally go shopping for clothes/shoes. They have every size but the one I need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But people clearly don’t take you serious when you talking, until you start taking action. Word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting for spring break to be here like.... https://t.co/ym37DF9zcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SomeBigFace @SpeakerPelosi She’s been in office for decades she’s never fought the good fight. Never accomplishing anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also mentions a new approach to training this new class of urban leaders, i.e. Master of Urban Strategy 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re overcharged. Told you are getting an adjustment then hear nothing for a month...you reach out and then… https://t.co/5251pjU3eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister and my #youngwarrior nephew #CHDawareness #CHD #Heartmonth #HeartEffect #zipperclubmember… https://t.co/DjAeEZzn2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 14 minutes left to write this and I have no clue what I’m doin https://t.co/aRJdkDjcjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland A statement released by Toyota says the company believes “no private employee or customer data has bee… https://t.co/daVDGk0E3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow #GoOpenNC for the latest updates on OER! @JillDarrough @pambatchelor @ncdpiDTL @NCHomeBase https://t.co/EAh2z17dbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current condition - not bad for 11 weeks #postpartum https://t.co/5IhEMaAqQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Blandford Stud Sales Graduate! Congrats to Team Asmussen and all of the connections @PadraigCampion… https://t.co/zRiNDhWsHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potterhead1207 @yehetsongomo Lol I did the hand movement in my head too 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcgraue #session day! @vanessasolidvo #videogame #animation  #comingsoon #voiceactor #actorlife @ The Legendary… https://t.co/HbkH52SH51]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are watching @tanamongeau  and you're phone freezes. https://t.co/QMrH7Ir84N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#debbieharry #stephensprouse #1990 @ New York, New York https://t.co/4pjCPA6R61]]></document><document><![CDATA[your ass doesn’t go from super flat to stupid fat .. ain’t no baby in the works of no gaining weight in the world t… https://t.co/aaUfsJeDPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I don't even have to see Mueller's Report to give it a good title:  "Mutiny on the Bounty"]]></document><document><![CDATA[spike lee is getting so much hate for his reaction to green book winning best picture last night and it’s sad becau… https://t.co/DZOZN9nhpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Visionsofimages @ImAnthonyRay @JordanE33 @Mathieu_Era y’all can carry on w/ this shit. You said Mike garbage that’… https://t.co/qxMYs3IHNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM Beloved @KathyDutton16 @KimelPenny @thelastmilehome @joyce92009250 @ElkeHansen7 @EliCann1 @DKNE4Sure @Mopor777… https://t.co/pxejcFXEuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drnelk I agree. There should be a separation between  depression and melancholy, but they do seem to interact most… https://t.co/h4hnywS1E8]]></document></documents></author>