<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Veltins Pilsener by Brauerei VELTINS at @derwolfskopf — https://t.co/Exs6vNUSPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougRobersonAJC I live in Savannah but I haven't been there yet. So many restaurants to try. Haven't even made a dent in my 8 months here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Encouragement from God’s Word: There’s joy in following Jesus. @ Oakfield-Alabama Baptist Church https://t.co/TcARP0FJLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActualAero btw remember when  we got that leak in 2018 with the 3 starters i knew that was real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSteveCox @EmmaSegasture @thenation @johncusack @BernieSanders @BarackObama Again, I make no excuses but tweeti… https://t.co/Jljer8WcWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevermorelit Ditto. This is the article we all needed to see on both sides.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessLiptzin Not even close bro why is Shaq on every commercial? Why is Barkley even on that show to begin with? MO… https://t.co/4d5eQeDzOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @AlanDersh  https://t.co/9rYcpd39p0  Seems you can't hide. Now what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nailed it! This is all I got from the hearing. The rest was yea we know. #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpKimPlayDate https://t.co/bEiWKbOjQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah the lakers will make the playoffs. But that puts them ahead of the second seed in the west? Fucking pathetic.… https://t.co/loeHJJ9nx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ron ‘Bumblefoot’ Thal and Steve Mack @ The Empire Hotel https://t.co/N6qs2sBbXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaWSOC9 @wsoctv @TrafficTeam9 Was this the same driver who drove that bus into the townhouse on Statesville Rd?… https://t.co/Ne6NtF7nYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge to remind the @NRA #NRAPoliticians everyday that they are putting $ over lives We shoulda stop it after Co… https://t.co/Gy1hZBFGP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[find someone who can tolerate your dipshit reason, kalerks ka mars! also i’m not interested doing OT on weekends! m… https://t.co/AARxWioqZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta run!..cardio day joke. (at @PlanetFitness in Reisterstown, MD) https://t.co/jczO6w3V7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or did my MP @lraitt and the integrity solid @Puglaas just prove today it’s about time this country b… https://t.co/2u7Vk2RLM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[EEUU aseguró que la cúpula militar chavista "está negociando con la oposición" la salida de Nicolás Maduro https://t.co/IPU3pFoNJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLore No. It is an absolute mark of shame against our education system and makes me want to puke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G4pNVTo0Jt Verizon Customer Service Phone Number 1-855-431-6111 is toll-free for its users… https://t.co/T4IpN6enGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not happy with this jumbled @ESPNU feed for Columbia- Brown game @BrownBasketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LADAOffice When are you going to do something about all the #Scientology victims DA LACEY?  #cultnotchurch @AftermathFdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a How Now Brown Cow w/ Coffee &amp; Coconut by @Aslin_BeerCo at @MohawkTaproom — https://t.co/Jlp8NSbK5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC That is such a standard and full answer. Tell the truth about socialism. You first. Oh that's right you do not… https://t.co/63YJBb9Dmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falling Stars - Feat. Dallas Owen, Smokey, John Michael, a song by Philly2000 on… https://t.co/IXhkkbNTQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PA_reSISTER @RepSmucker I'm confused, didn't Democrat law makers tell us that they wanted to pass the affordable c… https://t.co/NwbLOx2tVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlgaKhmylev Gotta love this little girl knows her hockey and she's adorable!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanHan @DGlaucomflecken @teenytinydino22 @rheum_cat We have consensus. I Love Samoas even more than oatmeal raisin… https://t.co/p7K7HBR2Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! @diepthought and @RobKendt ive been having deep and important conversations about the theatre’s relationship t… https://t.co/tDnjQ4FxeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We lost 2 of our best players and our backline is shakey. But yea let's celebrate losing 2 of our best players a we… https://t.co/5CKLsn0J5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 @universidad_uci @CubaMES @jsaborido50 @AuroraFdez19 @WalterBG_uci @marthadelcmv https://t.co/Ubf8KwUMmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really cant explain how thankful I am for this person in my life. She has seriously been a main reason for who I’… https://t.co/7GqeHUaoto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presentcorrect I started collecting security envelopes a few years ago. This is awesome. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seangentille No the new one coming out on HBO has already been teased into my brain. After that though we can shut it down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I jus want to thank everyone for all the shoutouts 🥰🥰 I love you all I really don’t know where to start...you all k… https://t.co/u4vqtpzO51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the @SECNetwork called the refs and said please make this a game and make Auburn the 4 seed...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cloud Catcher by @OdellBrewing @ The Burlington Apartments — https://t.co/Pj87ID6Pr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is true because I’ve seen. It was first “dude you’re crazy, then people were pissed, then it was like, ok.. yo… https://t.co/1Zn0wh7FoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelseyummm @kahzooehh Omg Marie Kondo looks stunning!! They all do but I was shaken looking at her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL Roy really thinks he won that fight. Got eat some meatballs you fat fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulDeCristofo4 hahaha. well, you've got at least another two decades before the gran torino stage. https://t.co/Ew9B2nqEvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SprotsFan @edoz10 @McBainsGoggles @BartsNewGlasses @MikeyFarrar I’m still blocked by him :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timreckmeyer Hey Tim. I have two Specialized eBikes. A 2015 Turbo X and 2017 Turbo Levo Comp Fat HT. Got them from… https://t.co/1eR8bMDzaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeplrbleRzistr @sherry25793049 There is no such thing as trans anything. Trans is another word for cross dresser.… https://t.co/RUOpuxQSxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about that... @F_Molinari makes a bomb on 18 to win the @ArnoldPalmer Invitational with the Flag In!  Never thought I would see the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morrison says candidates like Cohen, Turanchik, and Castor saying not much mayor can do, is lack of leadership.  Sa… https://t.co/YZGXVA1Npo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCAlerts @OfficerMooken Yeah but they knew where she was it's saddening yes but they need to revise amber alerts… https://t.co/SmJT5GLiz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool @OtoDalakishvili. Hopefully soon we will see each other in #Washington or #Europe 🙇🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing a bit of #golfinstructor this am. #recruitingforthefuture @ Fremont Park Golf Club https://t.co/xcCtlJbmO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Ken Starr is a shameless self-preservationist. He's the goddam scum of the earth. I never want to see… https://t.co/DQybJQViOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USA_Anne711 @learning2fly6 @RobChristie11 @MassKURoyal Love my g'night one too https://t.co/3Y9sq17ocv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simon just turned 1 on February 6th and his future is bright!!  @DKPghSports @penguins @SidneyCrosbyEgo… https://t.co/0EjjBnLvTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDforkm Don’t get it twisted folks..... still one of the largest public schools in the Country!  Pretty sure #1 on… https://t.co/RyVKyDnzXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendrickF0ster @mjp360 @CFL @calstampeders I     -     L     -     L      🧡💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oh_So_Chronic @Steel_Curtain4 You don’t have to like him as a reporter. But if you’re gonna say he is a bad report… https://t.co/PGpkbKSlw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started watching @TheSimpsons as a kid and now I'm about to be Homer's age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- you hand make books? C- yes Sari- how many? C- I don't know, 2 dozen or so Sari- what are they? C- why do you… https://t.co/efQ8Ep8zVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want something fun to do before spring break? Don’t miss a night full of poetry with Kate Rushin! See image for det… https://t.co/tYBCA0ZtGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iRobot Ya’ll sell parts for Roombas? Ours has seen some better days. https://t.co/6Xs6Clcuxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[temperature down 70°F -&gt; 58°F humidity up 37% -&gt; 76% wind 5mph -&gt; 8mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that PSG dominated the last 30 minutes of the match makes their collapse even worse. They showed absolutel… https://t.co/2MA1tWlDak]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXTENDED 24 HOURS!!!!!! #prowrestling #Wrestling #WWE #RAW #SMACKDOWN #wrestlemania #motivationalvideos #pullups… https://t.co/STXWpGNznu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah. This brings back memories, especially tonight.  Thankfully, they're no longer vivid, and I think I've forgive… https://t.co/itVfCPOFes]]></document><document><![CDATA[POTUS has made it very hard for the Liberals to continue in their corrupt money making schemes. It’s obvious to me… https://t.co/D5hgqLM8fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The official playlist of Point Blank pretending to write https://t.co/MXUWkoQHdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight B.S.. @2deep4someBlkPl @2UrbanGirls @southLAwatchers @SharisRhodes @JanPerry @florencefiresto… https://t.co/DGFL3e4ERL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyft AWS spend in context. When people use the internet, AWS gets paid. Like google, stripe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@page88 But who has seen him throw a baseball? Maybe he sucks? His greatest fear in life is ridicule; he probably t… https://t.co/2UCxDIans6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton amazing show last night. Was exhausted from so much fun.  Great to see John Anderson &amp;… https://t.co/ev6A0hUUUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after talking to a new girl and not getting a reply within 10 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih @suzjdean Interesting! So, how do you prep the pineapple? Cut off the green leaves and grab the sections??]]></document><document><![CDATA[European leaders not even willing to feign approval of the bullshit Trump &amp; Pence are selling. Good on them. 🇪🇺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicamillertv Omg those were my favs too. And the stripped version of colors.... I said hello]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FailedMusician @Roger_Roeper @ShatTheMovies @ShatOnTV It was the best part for me too! I’ll miss our weekly sessions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lazy researchers conduct lazy research and produce lazy, tired results!  Continue to set @Forbes  straight… https://t.co/7MiRZP9aoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[TTW boarding announcements for gates you aren't at are 13 times louder than for the gate you are at. #techfail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dummy, I don’t want her anyway that bitch ugly. Cuz all she good for is suckin’ n fuckin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Caturday #drawing - the Baxter in repose. Archival felt-tip on paper, 5.5 x 8.5 in. #CaturdayRTC @ Fairmount, Fort… https://t.co/NsmMdOqxZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvredlegs @Mike_Ferrin The best view among the stadiums I’ve been to in Arizona. Highly suggest taking in a game there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Complaints are being filed by citizens across WA against @BobFergusonAG , accusing him of multiple misde… https://t.co/ou9ASxN7D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliGreenKFrog @ladygaga @KelliGreenKFrog oh to see you doing Karaoke to Shallow would be Devine 😂 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jae_tree @teapaahty This is my best friend Tess and she is a force of nature that I fear more than tornadoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a show! Whether it was covers or original music @jadenovah and her band @bandofbrothas were amazing 🔥🔥🔥 @ Beat… https://t.co/LqH3nHE0O4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN LMAO WHAT ABOUT HILLARY WITH HER UNSECURED SERVER IN HER CLOSET CONDUCTING OFFICIAL GOVERNMENT BUSSINESS ON IT… https://t.co/4Rn2Nd3oe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls hoops- @friargirlsbball half stats vs Nazareth (trailing 21-18)- Team shooting: 19% (6-31, 2-12 3PT). Scoring… https://t.co/LVuaTVrS9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @EOLeinberger @realDonaldTrump They will be pounding him until the opening of the Presidential library ceremony in 2025.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MirandaDuffy @JimByersTravel There is some good value. Mainly when you save up enough points for a business class flight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/QGc6MrS0CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freddurben @OHXC_OHTF @SportsCenter @JeffDarlington Oh he went there 😳😳😂 wouldn’t wanna be at Sunday family dinner tomorrow 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comeseedrew @vincefabra and Evan Pittfield are going to be bringing the heat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marioxantonelli have you ever watched the docufilm In search of greatness ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very blessed to spend time with my parents. The man I am today is because of these two strong and supportive souls.… https://t.co/hVRwDfQ82o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Don’t stop at leaving food and water at the border.  Take them to your home and give them room and board on yo… https://t.co/5ERxSlHqco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only the pets and I are awake this cold Saturday morning. George Szell conducting @CleveOrchestra on the Richard St… https://t.co/Sg3aheM8pE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awprokop Great idea to piss off older voters, who reliably vote, in a Presidential election year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime i see this ad, I think about @senatorshoshana and her Tina Belcher worship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[530PM TONIGHT @ Avon High School | Families with students who have special needs can attend a free transition fair… https://t.co/r1bPsCCIse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamagedDenny  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump PRE-DESIGNED AS             PDA             ONE The politics of DoZen in America 🇺🇸 an… https://t.co/Mv4g7sapJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be a Horrible strict Shark on @ABCSharkTank . The Corny pitches people use are a huge turn off to me. They make me cringe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadRowdyRacing I know he is. He was even garbage in the NBA as a player and announcer]]></document></documents></author>