<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@blkumathurman My question is who would  want to come play second fiddle to football]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec To be fair we entered the social media age in the 90’s. As soon as guys In fedoras knew they could se… https://t.co/Ax9WsIJdBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjasonw74 @Alyssa_Milano Probably more concerned when every intelligence agency said Russia interference in our la… https://t.co/T3AqivoJ7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReformedBroker I’ll be choosing not to fly 737Max until further notice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @jguaido  https://t.co/Z5Dx8UzDcf ‘No tentarás al Señor tu Dios’ (Lc 4,1-13)  .  #venezuela… https://t.co/zyZfoXZGA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow these Hi profile accounts  Real people , no bots , friendly, interactive,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramonashelburne @TSA But u gotta understand that these dudes have seen some crazy things and are doing thier jobs. @TSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's back. It's really back. - Drinking a Boing by @larkbrewing @ Lark Brewing  — https://t.co/pUIUJYv8AA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillParchman @delshaffer You’ll learn to keep subtitles on all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading a paper naked in the public sauna with the lights on....this state is something out of a national Enquirer… https://t.co/8DZUWkvIFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeslaArmy @stromerleben For sure - no translate option. But I agree with the “😍”!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Millions more spent on BULLSHIT gotcha politics and what do we get? MORE NOTHING BURGERS! The Dems are over the top; sore losers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FretzCrystal That's all I have/had since this afternoon. Are you thinking vertigo by any chance? That comes with t… https://t.co/4OWsR8r60b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  after Putin is Gandhi.. as in dead// there will be much to do.. Xi has already assembled a List of contacts t… https://t.co/U3EJpzSobh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_grammar_ you are a real asshole. really. is this all you have to do is fix peoples grammer? this is twitter, we a… https://t.co/HeoywFLCoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/iKVegsIpcM @ambarnes8 @Adam_Marez7 #loveastro #teachSDGs #cowboysunite We support goal… https://t.co/IOrcy2Awu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[why cause y’all can’t make music that makes you money like this whether it sucks or not? lmao don’t hate the hustle… https://t.co/CS2HltKgKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing 🙌🏽 . . . #Repost @laurabenanti with get_repost ・・・ This. Is. Amazing. @ Our Home https://t.co/skuZknLJfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday To Me Y'all Know It's A Real Niggaz Glock #21 🎉😈🍾 https://t.co/eBYOnZYhqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwww, River is cute when she's not clawing into your skin https://t.co/JLhPx42U9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News is literally white nationalist propaganda so spare me the hot takes on the vile stuff spewed by their talking heads]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching the budding rivalry between these brands and so should you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimiuorio Since I’m a new found socialist 2 ( cause I like free stuff) thought (I expected) that means I get free… https://t.co/YnUuN81vze]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have nothing nice to say about some people children baby pictures so I don’t say anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicia45KAG @sxdoc @SuicideSeattle @senatemajldr Absolutely unconscionable Alicia! Hope Valentines was Good Sister… https://t.co/YDLfUGugkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #rehabtime with @trentshelton. Exactly what I needed. Thank you!! @ Marriott Marquis San Diego Marina https://t.co/8TXbEOeRZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pink soap looks like pepto bismol. It looks hella good, I guess that's how things like the tide pod challenge get started]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Caribbean Queen” Sketched out, outlined with ink, water colored and Digitally Enhanced.   #caribbean #queen… https://t.co/vLLED1fQUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndhapple @nahmias It’s Nomiki, not “Nokimi” - just noting bc you did it twice in a row]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/NJJB3yC0BV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaTtKs So if players are OK with 1-2 quits, we can let things get a little looser, which lets more people play. Bu… https://t.co/iFp9hNtc3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Flowers and Garden Festival! #epcot #freshEpcot https://t.co/GLwLta8Bka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to join @CMMathieuEugene, @NYCSpeakerCoJo and our @NYCCouncil as we honored and recognized Yeon Hwan Park and… https://t.co/6ku1W3uPeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He makes millions, what would he know? And why bring the race card into it?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@branmoorhead @Jess_D_Ripper Look. you saw me last night,  I was drinking a lot of whiskey. I do NOT remember getti… https://t.co/uWEBaE7Ojl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna go all weekend without drinking but then I remembered life sucks so I’m gonna get slammed rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker @Reince @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @VP @mike_pence Is Putin paying you also? Are you another… https://t.co/toTmT3xuWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltingInMarana @Paul0451 @OLDFLACO @GeanineC @trumpshappygirl @rkline56 @rdrhwke @KevinMFerrara @ZeeZeeandMe… https://t.co/rfQBg3ujAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it’s pretty easy to understand. POTUS and calling them FAKE NEWS so often they are “over correcting” for non e… https://t.co/XF9t4jxfph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killercankles @benshapiro @SethAMandel The funny thing is that they called him a liberal, not that they attacked him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mark_Baden What if we compromised and shifted the International dateline by 7.5 degrees of longitude?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot my toothbrush, so now I’ve learned that complimentary hotel toothbrushes are designed solely to insure you… https://t.co/UKnu25N68h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickwallace7 @CodyMullins34 We’re a better program than LSU &amp; Penn State.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAIequipment @OhioStateWGYM Whoever is a buckeye deserves it that’s just how it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @facebook has built out the digital equivalent of the town square and they feel the digital living room is missi… https://t.co/npS64m6P1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaineCarosin Ok thanks for follow my twitter and g plus. Hope u like my new music im fento drop]]></document><document><![CDATA[#80YearsOfBatmanTaughtMe There is a repellent spray for Sharks. https://t.co/TWwhQI1cDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I travel for Bliss. I entered the #ITravelFor Sweepstakes for a chance to win an unforgettable trip to Great Britai… https://t.co/DUwZ0dtOl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acnewsitics @cryindonnie Yeah, all image, no substance. Ask the good people of Ukraine, Libya, Egypt think of your Titan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You wouldn’t do it because I could wipe you away. You don’t have the brain 🧠 of a worm 🐛.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Get rid of this pile of garbage. She is worthless for this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son and I built a little portable greenhouse. Hoping this will allow 1-2 recoto chile peppers to over winter. Or… https://t.co/k6AGB9dqng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vacaciones nathaniel 😍2019 en Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/Z2UVlkmTG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darylatenas Excelente  Ojalá Roma Gane Como La Mejor Película Extranjera Y @YalitzaAparicio  Como Mejor Actriz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He is not just unprepared – he is temperamentally unfit to hold an office that requires knowledge, stability and i… https://t.co/QWOVVCcbwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris First...totally support you for POTUS.  But with all this Tweeting when do you have time to do "the people's work ".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman There are times when I could almost absolutely ❤️you this Osone of the most level headed things you ever said...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to show you how to take a person who has no net worth at all and within minutes, elevate their net financ… https://t.co/vKbrZw8xpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff And does what? Shake its finger and tells the president how naughty he is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, those aren't decorations...I ate those peppers 👍 @ Red Robin Gourmet Burgers https://t.co/EDCtzkGxrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDemko I'll stop you now. You're not going to win this. They just deleted a video they had posted of the scu… https://t.co/A8dhiAkSSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do hope we make Earth a better place before we try to colonize Mars. Well I guess before rich people jump… https://t.co/nNb9j0HK0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennife58305610 Hi Jennifer, I follow Jesus &amp; have been following u, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikkiharper @viralbirdflu @IncmpltMadnss I feel lucky to have him too. Funny thing is, at 6 months he's only half… https://t.co/k9klMTMqOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t mess with A Colorado girl visiting Texas....#claysnomore @ Cordillera Ranch https://t.co/8nWMLOPpdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowl For Kids Sake event for @BBBSNF last evening. Thank you Team Peak Realty for having me. Over 15k raised!… https://t.co/ANROS8w3MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbyron @Quillette It feels like you’re not actually responding to my article....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egoltz @diegojuarezs12 @MikeZimmersEars @ReddHead_13 @lno09281978 @GregTompsett @Notkiba62 @celestealbone… https://t.co/ppXnmgs2nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What will it take for Gym to acknowledge that russia instslled Trump as president? How many boys will it take to ac… https://t.co/rLtkfeoxLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAdamsJustin @Jamieblog @baseball_ref @Reds I’m not saying he’s necessarily worth 9 million never did I say that… https://t.co/OHM6c5dxAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope, traitors need to feel the Justice to match the harm they have caused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so fucking cold like shiiit I'm frozen wtf pinchie weather. I hate winter season I hope it's cause we're in Mar… https://t.co/cFxrnwzk4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was attacked by Bush Airport was the way you were closer to the moment and I didn’t have to take my kids out for… https://t.co/bYxnhib3Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best Oscars in so long. They’re flying through these and I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Farmstead Ale by GoodLot Farmstead Brewing Co. @ The Lanai — https://t.co/0QuJYGqXAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe I painted this a year ago already,  doesn't time go by faster when you're doing what you love?   .… https://t.co/9g1mLNUWfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no paro de reírme con @juanluiscano es un crack.  Hoy están emitiendo en un barco desde el Canal de Castilla (Pa… https://t.co/dLJLreb5VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 7:30 on Monday morning and I’ve already told multiple people they are going to have to wait to talk to me 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[you have to be kidding  build the wall now or place a row of army tanks on the border we must stop the aliens from… https://t.co/uDcXlOhhho]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Gerrie Sylaidos plays up to his potential with South don't be surprised to see him back in the #ALeague system.… https://t.co/mEQo2rL1OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichNChrist57  Appreciate the RT and likes  Lord your Righteousness has no end;  It's everlasting. And your rules are perfectly fair✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The country/ world would be a better place if there was more of this.... a lot more]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF - The perfect Friday night Letterboard!  #fridaynightdinner #fridayvibes✨ #fridaymoods #tgifmarket #spirits… https://t.co/70Z83fyOWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Conference tournaments are underway, 4 days remaining in the regular season, 11 Days until Selection Sunday. THIS… https://t.co/IHdau5R7VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sport #2 on the day...please hold off rain! @ Anderson High School, Austin Texas https://t.co/jGI9MO69TW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling out the #Birther and member of the #KremlinCaucus, #MarkMeadows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freepsports @umichbball @MSU_Basketball Even as an MSU alumnus, @Hope_Basketball v @CalvinKnights beats them all o… https://t.co/hwCnRQxsmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpuckl I think so too, quite likely. But so is programming.  Those that offend tend to create a vicious cycle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sketch1984 Even though I'm not into snakes, we can agree on everything else😎 https://t.co/4UkNVs2fv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so angry right now..this piece of dung needs to face hate crime charges as it fits the statute to the tee. He… https://t.co/qIL5WaKeF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abandoned body shop across from the Kill Bill Church in Alta Vista California! Way… https://t.co/cbL8EjXFkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sloppy morning run, with ridiculously thick humidity. And it got worst on the rowing machine. Brutal - but it got d… https://t.co/NuHSd8Vekw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @bigb3145 @JussieSmollett why aren't you talking about this https://t.co/Ds5aChmKZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp @kmartin120469 @joncoopertweets @realDonaldTrump @GOP Amen to that!! https://t.co/5HVpmWeN6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we can’t bounce back and beat the Suns tonight in Phoenix we don’t deserve a playoff spot plain and simple. #LakeShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys it was my fault we lost to the Sabres... I wore the wrong shirsey.  For our victories against LA and TOR I had… https://t.co/UcVluwZ0Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen! Travel with minimal planning (identify the must sees),  engage with the community and let life happen. Best t… https://t.co/b3vMDXF2Gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah bc every player knows that every pitch during a game is going to be in the exact same spot....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united extremely frustrated!!! Your podium agent ask people to get on the phone to rebook, phone line can’t help,… https://t.co/bJlMKoSlsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to work on a Saturday night, have just discovered Tetris 99 and Fortnite, and have some time to kill. https://t.co/eaKboMMjH3]]></document></documents></author>