<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why I Donate Blood CW: self-harm, suicide, blood I started cutting myself in 2011. It became an addiction that I su… https://t.co/ar7W5mKyFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your student says you remind her of Leslie Knope from @parksandrecnbc #ICanSeeIt #Yep https://t.co/k36nb01wng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our own @BurrellTyjean  gets 1st team all league- so well deserved! We will miss you Ty!!! Always proud to be 🅰️Tit… https://t.co/PMXjzzjeil]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I am around you...I am afraid to breath regular. I shake sometimes because I’m nervous. You give me goose bump… https://t.co/a7ZbvaEwV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The differences that protect us (white people) are unseen” -Elizabeth Warren at #SXSW2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[💒Con Sue Photography and Design💒  ⛪️Like our photos...Follow our IG ⛪️  💒This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/lTokQdJMWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fri-YAY!!!!! In love with my new align pant from lululemon ..... #weightlifting #GirlsWhoLift @ Princeton, New Jers… https://t.co/d5PKLGn6k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DvKHzvZVmV HAPPY BIRTHDAY 2 MY  LOVELY FRIEND PANKAJ!! IN FARAWAY EXOTIC INDIA! LOYALITY  IS NOT  DIFF… https://t.co/iOQ1BzrbY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re addicted to murder shows and single on Valentine’s day https://t.co/PISSfoTpvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnimalsAsia I have to say, how proud I am of you to save this moonbear. You are very special to help an animal liv… https://t.co/A6YnMOANHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good fuckin morning people ☀ Here’s a song for you… Florida Kilos by Lana Del Rey https://t.co/Fojeuxanst]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwback to a few weeks ago at the @globies game.  . The kids had the BEST time! It was their first time at the S… https://t.co/WlKQWfMEXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garway95 @kfisme @gneely17 @Gracieluf @Mooster22 @stripedbanana3 @trumpAngel45 @Priya4Trump @okWessler5 @Sekusa1… https://t.co/ruWjKQfNP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belleoz1 I am a Capricorn for y’all to come home and I will have time for ya tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xcxrxnx @iamsexier_ Nothing against them as long as they don’t force you to change just like religion. We all have… https://t.co/MbKIRflGQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter I only follow those that follow me...you're 200 behind in my total.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a student “You would be surprised at all the kids you thought were going to drop out that actually have the mo… https://t.co/6KeUd1SVck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen Mike! Publishing this dribble as news is so utterly sad and anticlimactic. Mike Pence is one of the kindest pe… https://t.co/Y7LYB8WkQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even at the age of 19 this still  holds true. I will always put my daughter first that’s what being a mom is about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha. Britney Spears might need two umbrellas 🌂.   But I’d hope we could sip on some Pinot Noir after the scuffle and… https://t.co/6RvQYkLknw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @MaroWardak, on Monday at @AJStream, we discuss if achieving peace with the Taliban will come at the expense of… https://t.co/LJvCnaZEoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drniallmc @AllisonKeating1 @psyclingqueen @ClaraCorless @WinningMindsIRL @dr_em_mardlin @sharongrimes1… https://t.co/9kJ50GGzLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacticalDogLive @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD Boop doggy dogs! Rocking the night away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 7 year old sister snapped me “please don’t disturb on Snapchat anymore tonight I’m watching videos” 😔 when will she love me again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuniculaTv I don't think we needed Brazile to tell us Hillary owned the DNC. They BEHAVED like she owned them. FFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaycelv_ I’m fuckin busy if you didn’t see my Snapchat???? https://t.co/7U17dRYBDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because we never prosecute the Johns and demonize the women. Women are sex throw always in our society and not valu… https://t.co/8aLgOvWShS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Elote is life!! 🌽🌽🌽🌽🌽🌽  #sxsw #latina #yummy #highheels #legs #legsfordays @ Elotes fanny https://t.co/mso3UfWLbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking my feet up for the entire weekend .. for a nice change!! #NOLA #vacation #homeiswhereyouparkit… https://t.co/ZofeZ1xz8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camryngrimes it was very nice meeting you! Thanks for the pictures and autographs!! #yrfestivalcbus https://t.co/luSgYpOULe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you looking for some fun gift ideas for a pre-teen boy in your family? Here... https://t.co/Yg3FPhBGVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to share the morning with my co-workers at the @mercycareaz ReMEMBER Kate Aurelius Award and RISE Awards. We… https://t.co/LbZGinO1m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[No YOU’RE sitting on the floor eating a king cake at 6:30 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanhill171 I’m not ab to argue w someone that never even played real basketball before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunny’s Banana Bread is all done ✅ Now just have to wait for it to cool and we can see how I did. #nalacooks… https://t.co/H2kdtrgomL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump Your son is a freak. Good job Dad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFrankthecat @MollieM75164454 @Turtlecat9 Hai Fwank, wans to be fwends wif us? 😸😸]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one:   Co worker: you only get big tips because you’re pretty.   Me: ?¿?¿:/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @LindseyGrahamSC Well Lindsay we know for a fact that you and the trump adm always lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pampisford @1madwoman1962 @karenslinn43 @Shirley82829043 @11syoung @leonalombaerts @fiftyminus2 @FRISEEMYRIAM… https://t.co/KVxKDoiZKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesKosur Enough with scolding Cohen actually it was smart to tape Trump given Trumps erratic behavior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanEGregoire LOL Yes Seperate traits but she would have been a HORRIBLE doctor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump More fake news or at least edited news.  You are pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to think guys going after their best friends’ ex gf is like a part of the whole friendship deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg This is so dam funny trump has to go to the bottom of the rung to get someone to speak for him. TH… https://t.co/8nseDXq7J5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just lost two things that were in my possession the whole time already this morning.. how is this day about to go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[this week has been one of the shittest weeks. so glad today is my friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might feel a little too at home at Kelley Rink https://t.co/KhOmvYNkgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took the @bradenmccurdy to my company convention... this is what he texted me.  Hubs: This place has the be the b… https://t.co/aTLL4X6n0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexanInOz @BlueMountainsBG @GregBourke3 This is such a wonderful plant. I have had great success w it in NE Kansas… https://t.co/7F888X4qCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microwave beeps:   Katie: “oh my Mac and cheese”  @KatieAylett https://t.co/d81ZvdeW2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @Tanya_Vogel7 to post 7 covers of books I’ve read - no explanations - no review - ju… https://t.co/GYSfrcfbD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christina_Roof @workingdogmag @K9Mattis @tkeleiott @bulletgifts @judes_chan @TracyTharp4 @Love4PoliceDogs… https://t.co/gPf1qkaKlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watch monday night raw sear ronnie (ronda) Uhhhh…putting the title down in the middle of the ring is vacating… https://t.co/4Y2hO4oVRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG THAT'S A FINAL OMG @focorollerderby #brewvictory #cantstopwontstop #DerbyTwitter https://t.co/JvPluraJ3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Maddness Continues! Limited time exclusive for the month of March! #marchmadness #thursday #packages… https://t.co/lXaNhpnreN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pabu begged for a twitter account, so here it is! Go follow him if you want extra cuteness in your life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeachforGA No to school Vouchers. These take tax $$ paid to ensure high quality and graduating educated workers an… https://t.co/A9jJUzn2qN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the exact scene I had playing in my mind when I read that page from your book!! ❤️ this movie! 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommahenof3 Had a bill once that was $8.95. Gave them $9.05. Blew their mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Thomson, GA, check out this job: https://t.co/sTFlsmK0Fe #Automotive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @MitchellMeeks11 No Donald, YOU ARE THE TRUE ENEMY OF THE UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigmylesMob @thehicklife @BackTheLEOs @LivePdBlueLine @IndependenceGr1 @DonnaJamesRye68 @TrueLivePDFans… https://t.co/Uavuku9Ght]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioSQ @spicyquesoman @CoachPaulSilva I do t know. It’s a question I ask as I’m going thru school. It’s kinda wher… https://t.co/OxnxWxSjnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my two loves in my life #throwbackthursday #cantstopwontstop #selflove #ilovealcohol @ Chicago, Illino… https://t.co/dnvXJjZ3jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realized some people really are strong. They have every right to press quit and they don’t. They keep fighting. That person is me rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[- Sailor Moon - YYH - Mobile Fighter G Gundam - Card Captor - Tenchi Muyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, all lanes closed on the highway to the gym ... guess I can’t go 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaKAlston Being Revealed ! I’m so very happy Girls everywhere will begin to feel safer and living in her power… https://t.co/ozGo9pjugQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay hold on.. so let’s just get this straight. If someone wants to post all over their social media that they’re w… https://t.co/BSFr1Of1BJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightOnIt1 Yes, I work for a German company and some of the people over there were/are very resentful of the E Ger… https://t.co/U1i4Tx1Vff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyKemper @BriversWHL @pdxwinterhawks That is shocking to me.  You know it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch don’t let me fucc fucc it I’m going home &amp; jacking off 😂😂😂😂 niggas that rape is weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitchh I hate when dudes try to play me!! That’s why I play my cards right y no me hago la pendeja for anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERYONE on #TeamPatriot must actively stymie people who sew discord on our Team. NOT by slinging hate BACK AT THEM… https://t.co/Zn476Lav7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racconconnoisse My dad definitely had books like those. I don’t think quite the same series, but in the same vein.… https://t.co/iIg5fZdX2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Thank you so much for the support. It's beyond appreciated.. 💚💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonKittay That is true, but in the end we had to deal with percentages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omfg @trianglejs shirts have arrived in time for Triangle #devfest! @ZeroToCoder @JakeDohm @robocell @MariaLamardo… https://t.co/MSFQYh5gIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CW_CrazyXGF I am dying at your La La Land send up. As someone who has had to do multiple dances to La La Land, thi… https://t.co/RBy7y4yxgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLenkov @lucastill @jay_hernandez @MeaghanRath @Trizzio @MerEaton @ZachKnighton @StephenHillActs @tokyobound I am!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can it get any more California that this?!?! I’ll be there. Respect to all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s welcome them out of our country, how did they get here in the first place. What the hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods They are so stupid. Don’t they think ppl can see what they are up to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @Centristchowdah @cspanwj @RepDarrenSoto They can vote. If you are not on the registrars there is l… https://t.co/pHVDJvwKVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of you haven’t yet read some of the fantastic books #CopyPasteCris straight up stole from, this thread has links to… https://t.co/uruo8hdBh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjrowland68 @TheLastRefuge2 @BreakfastNews @abcnews Even they hate msm 😂😂😂🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonCailleach @JeannaLarson @that1mum @witchywhimsy @jeweleaves @_thatMDgirl ❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since discovering this technique, it truly has become my favourite. Simply because you just leave it. There is no f… https://t.co/FYugDfDDY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Mary! Thanks gor inviting me! @ Club Paragon https://t.co/kAbHggUTLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar Just can't tell the truth. The hate will make you sick. Ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback! Jameson’s first Valentines Day. Shirt still applies - five years later he’s still an eligible bachelor.… https://t.co/G3izRusxhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I love you and you’re doing so so good. V proud. 💕 I don’t know the boy who hurt you but he’s garbage Bc you’re… https://t.co/lswF9jQTJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[EE teachers love learning! #plcsummit @ Phoenix Convention Center https://t.co/YtUhhWNPzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump How about some facts !!! Bun brother’s . The bun brother’s How are delusional https://t.co/kd6Q6j2ECd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok this not having an immune system is getting old. At urgent care to see if it’s the flu or just a cold. Been figh… https://t.co/X8fLABoMCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcgoLC @MonteDCantu @OdysseusOfWinds @CharismaMolotov @MrsGoodoz @CNS15141 @DogsBCool @Punkin682 @mcgregorgirl1… https://t.co/tTek9biCWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my group members would just straight up tell me they are not going to do anything instead of ignoring my  te… https://t.co/UQPXMkSQU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IgorM97487117 @fernandezmaris_ @saojanuario @VascodaGama Olha isso qui @EwersonLeon 😂😂Piada né?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, can’t even put into words how much I love @XNICK30   Thanks for everything baby 💕]]></document></documents></author>