<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@livebloordale @RyanGosling @BloordaleCIA @digital_mainst @anabailaoTO @maritstiles @JulieDzerowicz @bloordaleblog The Jim?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone get me an American Burger no tomato from PDR before they close please? 🙏🏾 #FAMU 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwbackthursday Because I miss my Partner In Crime minerdee88 🐨🧐 @ The Discovery Center of the Southern Tier https://t.co/mXoR9LxmoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been eating so healthy that I honestly could throw up everywhere right now from eating a cookie🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke with a potential client today and they ACTUALLY had an understanding of what they wanted for their brand. I w… https://t.co/04Hg5sIETX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pat_MercadoC Una felicitacion Senadora Li. Paty Mercado una Excelente Dama y a las chicas del partido Naranja!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[-understand, though, that as long as i’m doing positive things for my body, at the end of the day, what i look like… https://t.co/gnI8Jk0wjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s is supposed to be all about love, right? All sorts of love... well I love this image and it’s one of my… https://t.co/knM9TcqOxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was tagged for #7books #BookCoverChallenge by @LiteracyLadybug - 7 days, 7 covers, no comments, no reviews. Day 4… https://t.co/xF4poGI0FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Riddance!! could it be #indictHillary for crimes against children @TheJusticeDept @FBI  @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my students spits when he’s talking and I’m always like https://t.co/Y9fYdCv8ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated score and tinder just fouled out @jflick1215 https://t.co/YkJfK2lmC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait until Saturday when we’re finally done working on our house and moved in so that my back can stop feeling like a 90 year old’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve already dealt with just words enough to put you through some real mental distress especially when you’re going… https://t.co/cke6Tx5N6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9quW5ceC41  Lower Booting Age To 16?  Dems are for it, GOP against.  Gee, I wonder why. 🙄 https://t.co/G8KpHaOK22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras #maneklady #manektravels @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/vdbfEIGEbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rapplerdotcom Yan ang mensahe ni @mariaressa sa nga taong sinisiraan nya. Manahimik kayo at wag ng lumaban pa dahi… https://t.co/qFW7UGOE4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gm world, 43 yrs ago my mom gave birth to me👋🏽👋🏽, man im so glad to see another yr of life, off to work now but whe… https://t.co/oFnYV7TjSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chick_in_kiev You dont understand the US budget and prove you are ignorant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 10 more days until queer eye season 3 look alive folks!!! @QueerEye 🌈🌈😭🌈🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Jorge at MK guest relations helped us out and shared Disney Magic! #CastCompliment]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect @draperjames Sailor Stripes are over on https://t.co/zBZBuxu1DD today! Talking a little about why I ado… https://t.co/tmNc2FeM1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cupcake baking with my aunt and cousins!!! We made dozens to share at local fire houses ... but mostly we just want… https://t.co/Gr1KmFR5Oj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCPDX Jeez, I think “TheoTypes” needs to rethink his career. I was shocked when I saw what he does and where he works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevcol12 @Rschooley Covered extensively, Kevin — as it should have been. And the Coast Guard guy’s intended mayhem… https://t.co/RwUAiJRxoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart hurts, but I will always be a @Simmonds17 fan no matter where he goes. ❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was on hell of a week!  Sunday, I walked the runway for @anaonointimates #nyfw2019 show.  I sat for hours whil… https://t.co/P118VmKWAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apinick Me every day: “I wish I had my shit that together when I was that age”  So many fantastic humans in the wo… https://t.co/WXO8wx9fx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[princess mononoke came out 22 years ago and you're still capitalist? grow up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of pictures of the Jonas Brothers that is showing up on my feed right now is truly incredible 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein He continued to step in shit like every time he opens his mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMichaelMosley I am very much the “out of sight, out of mind” person when it comes to my food weaknesses; however… https://t.co/dSypXoHLRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado store that quit selling Nike products over Kaepernick ad goes out of business  https://t.co/bddOvWhD6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrBobbyBones @ProducerEddie I just heard the eggplant line for the first time and it is hysterical!  😂😂😂 #NailedIt #HeyYouUp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonikaBauerlein A new Recharge tagline if I ever saw one, haha.   Happy birthday, MB!🎉☀️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know the value of our water until our wells runs dry. Let’s not let that happen. #AZLD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whaaaa 😳                yup, true @ Party Eve Place https://t.co/QmaKRSE62U]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is laughable. #laughter #chuckle #smile #merry https://t.co/y6Q7EwYRGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came out to have a good time and I’m honestly feeling so attacked right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC I will never forgive .@StephenAtHome Colbert for taking a hiatus this week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I’m glad that woman was charged!! You are not a victim if you are in this country legally!! MAGA!! Go TRUMP! 🇺🇸🇺🇸❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We keep getting better everyday. The glass is only half full. https://t.co/5yCR11xosP]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁣ The liver has been associated with over 500 metabolic functions; it's main being to filter the blood coming from… https://t.co/Mu1LkfJ716]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhxPDChief Thank you for coming out to read to our students, families, and community @JustineSpitalny it was an ho… https://t.co/N7L3pbHdwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only someone could have warned @realDonaldTrump and the @WhiteHouse that Kim Jong Un would do this very thing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Beer Festival https://t.co/AuflAbFwcI @Brewgaloo #ncbeer #craftbeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my girl @edith10vargas mf BIRTHDAY 🎉🎉🎉 zapo verde coma gracias por todo, en las buenas en las malas y en las p… https://t.co/XvKXcMpPVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Bolton is NOT @CIA . I've been informed, "Mom, he's Narcissistic, educated but No one who's Narcissistic or Bi… https://t.co/dXHBcq79Q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here everyone, you can observe a Republican who minds his own business when it comes to a woman’s reproductive… https://t.co/jyr5Nubeei]]></document><document><![CDATA[My skin is so ungrateful!!! How can you have acne after all I’ve done for you??? All this money I’ve spent on you????]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Simple a Liberal get's it  @joeblow745 @smfehir https://t.co/cnfb29nFD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Against our rights and constitution, tired of double standards. Our voices want to be heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this is annoying to 98% of people but come ONNNNNN LMFAO this shit matches up ok I’m crying 😂 https://t.co/7cGU4Qx5HB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PBS Learning Media site is AMAZING!! So many resources for Ts and Ss. @pbsteachers]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really cool to see how this fire video turned out! It was supposed to capture a tunnel, but my camera wasnt fa… https://t.co/eaBghxinnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Stand up and speak the truth, stand up and speak your truth even if your voice shakes” #wil2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want if for @ShawnMendes to follow me!! Like is that to much to ask for lol 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@people I’ll never understand why it takes years for these women to come out and say something and then all of a su… https://t.co/rFWAhH6hJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some laughter. #humor #laugh #smirk #playful https://t.co/86y4GuDWtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The  good thing about a 5:30am MRI appointment is that I get to sleep in a little bit. 😂 #earlybirdsleepsin]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe the the people I started elementary school with don’t even know me anymore and people I’ve kno… https://t.co/p10lKAEAHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are already divided. There is a huge divide. Unless this POTUS is impeached or resigns, it will be an even great… https://t.co/RXI7eLqKya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ali_Davis She is being an asshat. No need to subordinate your choices because she jumped the gun. Caucus as you we… https://t.co/KiesqUIabi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ScottHawkes @TIME Yeah... or not. We can pursue much more green energy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That opening, complete with the #FyreFestival Cheese Sandwich reference. 💯  #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjgodush @HogStats @RazorbackMBB Agree😡. Grow up people. Get a life. I am a season ticket holder. Back your team.… https://t.co/HrmFhIAC3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go to the #southernwomensshow in #Raleigh in five weeks! #tysonbeckford will be there! Come have some #fun wi… https://t.co/8QaxUK3LZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m glad im up at 12 am to hear this song. you did it again @whydontwemusic :)) #ColdinLA https://t.co/O9ZyfsQ4J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jazmin_sanjose @LittleMissLizz Are you asking the murderer to be your sugar daddy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#releasethevisas #saveh2b @realDonaldTrump @SecretaryAcosta @SecNielsen @IvankaTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilosParrots @WesIiames @barngrl @cliett_eric Probably. When you’re that inbred, the animals start to look like a… https://t.co/h3Nu7Iy1AS]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s my lil mans 3rd birthday. Follow him on Instagram #bozie_the_cat #TavaresDayTO #TavaresDayTO #TavaresDayTO… https://t.co/VENkHZRG3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n73u5RV2CY  Well deserved! What a win...what a year for this team! ⚫️🔴]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Sasquatch is a @u2 fan! ❤️😎😂 #maytheforestbewithyou #MtHood #snow #xcski #xcskiing #forest #Oregon #U2… https://t.co/489RN558UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien The patriarchy is old white men still using the lie that reparations mean cash payouts to decendants… https://t.co/zxiF8R2FHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@underwhelmed04 @Steelerschic85 @sassyteapot63 @lilsun83 @DemTeaParty2020 @FreshPhunky @Kovie1961 @BlueBeeInDaBoot… https://t.co/9pEW2SEm2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUSPHTMOnline @Tulane @TulaneAdmission @TUFitts @tulanealumni @NOLACityPark @KeohaneHannah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started the day with a little self care BarreFusion then Barbell Strength for the 1st time #KirkSelfie #KirkROAR https://t.co/MyWV53Q8fO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ike_Irby You are my smartest friend and I brag about you all the time. You got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi donald, once again you get an F- in Tweeter. Your "work" today has been horrible, are you even paying a… https://t.co/lGQwEdnerX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drtonyevans I really enjoyed listening to you we’ve even listen to you in Bible study we have a small group of wom… https://t.co/B60rt8jmBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol I’m going back to to eating whatever I want whenever I want and it’s such an bad habit because I’m getting chunkyyyy . 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustorino @SonjaNi41294318 @APeijer @ClanOutlandish @bk79 @AGuirado5 @Nakary_Baptista @JuliK317… https://t.co/jlOr0bl5l8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to avail Wordpress #Web Development Services in New York? Get in touch with Openwave! Our professionals pro… https://t.co/iNxx4vANyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think about the time in Vegas where we didn’t even make it in more than 10 min the second club of the club… https://t.co/DeNlOA1Df9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeldebritoOk AGUANTE LA JEFA !!!!✌🏼✌🏼✌🏼.....ah no para ,que paso ??😁🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heya Reilly &amp; Stone!  (catching up here) #VegasBorn 💛🖤⚔️🏒🥅🗿 #StoneAge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep training is heartbreaking for momma! Thank God daddy is patient and loving 😫❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lachlan @cmclymer So they make the post again, without the picture this time, after it's been pointed out it's factually incorrect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NPPC delegate session underway at #porkforum19 @brownfield #ontheground https://t.co/GFW5YkGfkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rucker stated last week she wasn’t comfortable voting on something she didn’t have time to read yet just said on th… https://t.co/m73ZB8klVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk every once in a while i like to spice it up and say the absolute stupidest thing that i can verbally form in a… https://t.co/h9MUvH3OnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlaDems @CharlieCrist @TedDeutch @LoisFrankel @KathyCastorFL @DarrenSoto @SMurphyCongress @DWStweets Meanwhile in… https://t.co/a4klfVYyiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[La #UE espera que #Venezuela “reconsidere” decisión de expulsar embajador alemán #DanielKriener https://t.co/p2p459pJXz vía @elheraldoco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashhessel i can’t believe people actually think like this i’m so sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson A misogynistic jerk that has never gone to bat for women. Not for sensible gun laws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning. I woke up unprompted at 4:30 am. I’m trying to go back to sleep with the knowledge that the caps won in LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate staying in hotels I ALWAYS forget something, I left my JA earrings that I’ve had for over 7 years literally… https://t.co/H8HdL0YXpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooooo we gonna pretend that khloe and jordyn probably didn’t set this up so kylie could have all his assets that k… https://t.co/HdoNaPsjPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be tryna play cancers Ike crybabies when in reality it’s y’all who can’t control y’all emotions.]]></document></documents></author>