<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@OzmaSommers @DeborahJ242017 @speechboy71 As I used to tell my Glaswegian father, that’s not an accent. It’s a speech impediment]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dayoutwiththomas 🚂☀️   . . . . . 2 march 2019 @ Gold Coast Railroad Museum https://t.co/hRgEKlhpak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Montreal Canadiens goalie Carey Price is an incredibly classy guy after videos of his nice gesture with a young fan went viral. #NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi-litez of the week!  Nice week of workouts! Great group of people!  #bodybysid #fitness #behealthy #exercise… https://t.co/BTYeC2YhKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corona Motorcycle helmets at https://t.co/fVmCY1PV0i #corona #coronadobeach #coronabeer @ Stead Air Attack Base https://t.co/IFhuh3PQRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenWolfe @RitaThaQueen Out of that list, I think the only thing that will honestly bother him is seeing other pe… https://t.co/DvOKR73aDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juice_Spur @FBI @realDonaldTrump @bibinetanyaho @ButchOtter just there to give the ILLUSION of safety and justice.… https://t.co/fcNOmWMMYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heychristofur @samoosterhoff Don’t say that on twitter he’ll SWAT you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonStall2009 Hey @NightlyPolitics “Resistance” https://t.co/OXprUJc642]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Church Residences is hiring in #Hilliard, OH! Click the link in our bio to apply: Life Enrichment Assistant #HealthWelfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodHillis1 @Littlleome @stlpcs @RL9631 @ctanner3 @AW95NJ @BundyGP @raducom @MAGAGirl8 @arkiegal411 @Serremmy… https://t.co/JUhNzcY2OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lo mejor no he llegado todavía, pero estoy más cerca que ayer.💪🏼💪🏼 @ Mostro Fitness https://t.co/bE7KggvVeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a big wave coming and I will need only those I trust with basically my life to be in the inner circle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryTay @SanchezLaCuenta How about the 2 years he won back to back MVP lmao?]]></document><document><![CDATA[VHSL Championship Games - Pool A - GW Danville def. Louisa 55-44 #STATVALIVE @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinBade Man... had to do the same thing w “Ott” when I first started covering PJM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little iron, a dash of wood, and many teaspoons of resin. Recipe for an excellent build. Invest in an Artist.… https://t.co/g3eu28nXGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I live in a different world than some. Asked someone about Zion Williams and they never heard of them. Like what???😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blambo34 @Patriots @REDSOXNATI0N @stevemjr Doesn’t matter he’s already denying it just like tommy boy he should ke… https://t.co/s6hx42ANPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My most embarrassing moments is ice skating, ballroom dancing, roller skating, and my daughter laughing sucks to be… https://t.co/NCKjyXsCrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoldMyBluntt 😘 This is the sexiest fucking thing I ever saw. I would marry this amazingly hot girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFalsettoMan I really hope TT vs Iowa state decides conference. For sure gameday would come]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hoje na @andrevaladao culto Vision Night com os queridos brunaomorada e @andrempaquino ... Vms juntos buscar, clam… https://t.co/TZFR32OQsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I only one who doesnt give a flying fuck what an OL runs the 40 at the #NFLcombine ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IFact82 @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump @POTUS It’s called resistance, Iggy.  Get used to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know places like this still existed. #daveandbusters @ Dave &amp; Buster's https://t.co/TaXY7wDc81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrociousLaffer1 Only if it is what you wanted to hear.  The story was ridiculous from the jump]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @ymca honored several #YAdvocate Congressional Champs for support of #HealthyLiving #YouthDevelopment and… https://t.co/yiJkrXkoCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Hmmm, not self appointed, plenty of opposition and certainly doesn't control the media. What "markings of a… https://t.co/H5j63gt0Jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlendishRhuland @AOCpress @speculatore Her hot air is not methane like those cows so that might work however there… https://t.co/Eynu6rhdAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Via @WRAL: Wake judge strikes down voter ID, tax cap amendments  https://t.co/VbrqAP6p94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jer_ I know that as men, we need to be voices of “don’t do this,” but I am so continuously amazed at the shit othe… https://t.co/FH4uCrLpow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pres Birther. @realDonaldTrump There is something seriously wrong with you. Please don’t mess this up with N Korea.… https://t.co/edASkh4ppC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A&amp;M’s arena looks to be about as dead as Coleman Coliseum normally is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizunyan @BryanDraws That’s me with the prospect of buying Jump Force right now lol. We really don’t have enough H… https://t.co/5LyVf0SBgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull @IlhanMN Check it out y’all, the War Criminal Defender has logged on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck it i see alot of girls complaining they aren't gonna have sex today , so i volunteer lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good idea, I'm headin to Louisiana there smarter down there, constitutional carry state, no state tax jobs out the… https://t.co/swu3qEyzz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to receive a offer from Johnson university 📚⚽️@JohnsonRoyals https://t.co/3G7tckf726]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigirules7 @WhoopiesMind @WKatCrook @SeanMODonnell1 @clark_gasm @PammyJC @okaatta @eminem11683 Great photo. She'll… https://t.co/NSrJGrf3jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moslemi_fatima @Zwei_Augen You will be so proud. Most of you had ancestors that were forcefully converted to Islam. Chew on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watchmeteevee Word! I wanna hang out w you guys again I had toooo much fun at the Christmas party him and his brother had me dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told myself I’d study today... instead, I slept in, went to run errands, cleaned the kitchen, and I’ve got a pot of… https://t.co/TkF07ozsi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viajar por muchos sitios buscando entre la gente a ver si en una de esas de apareces por ahí https://t.co/LF6IJHMl7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dinner 🍔 buddy! #BubbaAu - Rarely see my grand-nephew Austin Casey Smith from San Angelo, but I sure love ❤️ thi… https://t.co/FUeOgoUw53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a better feeling then being back in your city! INDY I MISSED YOU! #317]]></document><document><![CDATA[My anxiety levels shoot way up at the salad bar when there are people in line behind me. I feel like I can never ch… https://t.co/lZA2KZmpS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaAlreadyNole @BassNicoh That thing looks like a 🧱, don’t tell me your a medium well/well done steak orderer .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Omar has decided that nobody is off limits, Did she actually take a shot at Obama wow now that gangster, oh sh… https://t.co/1jvMFZIU4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[What? @realDonaldTrump The largest cocaine seizure in a quarter century found in New York and not #Mexico? Can we b… https://t.co/ZGGXcp8zML]]></document><document><![CDATA[At it again with the wrestling universe who's next https://t.co/SYOwjozxOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody ain’t good for you.. move different and create your own wave !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaoKho1 I’m on my way to Boracay Island. . . save a spot for me under the 🏝☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great,  ballsy move.  Love the product,  first time digging the company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet He is souless &amp; ruthless &amp; doesn’t deserve a platform to try &amp; fool the American people ! https://t.co/d199xbtyIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Good. No one wants to see your lyin ass anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still covering @Atlantic_Hockey from Chicago! I profiled @USHL legend Dan Willett, who has been powering… https://t.co/5bDsNZZafR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the JLo movie: 6 hrs was not enough. Not even halfway. If only I were a handbuilder instead of a thrower, it wo… https://t.co/mg34Nq4o4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_al_wiseley To be fair, I did try to get at least one out of office in 2018 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@federalreserve reports need to inject more skepticism into their coverage, writes @Johntamny:… https://t.co/FX0VruLh5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnblud I gave up on the GCW stream a couple hours ago for that reason.  I’ll watch the VOD later today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a party going on at the pool but I have to study for two midterms tomorrow 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mallorymphoto I had a friend die in a car crash with a drunk driver.  He had just finished law school and was prep… https://t.co/XKjpReUxkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I have seen some funny stuff on here today. I seen someone tell a coach to put the phone down and teach your ki… https://t.co/ELWk3s0uoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students benefit every day from the hard work of our school board. It's School Board Recognition Week, so take the… https://t.co/VCBkrlFnLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Gee83 @ScottAdamsSays Whaaaaaah' Whaaaaah' Whaaaaaah' feed me burp me whipe my @$$ this stupid person as you… https://t.co/0bjlbBpMBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbeaulieu But I just mean that I read YOUR content fast and more is better 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed South, 14×11″, collage and mixed media. 2/16/19 #headedsouth #sillouette #map . . .. ... #handmadecollage… https://t.co/z4zbEWzEhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deleted a tweet that criticized Michael Avenatti; I didn’t get that it was a joke. Rather than have that out there,  I deleted it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@green_astrid @MrLuisRamos @NotiUno @eramosnavarro @ricardorossello @irisiri8 @HablaGuillo @EndColonial1sm… https://t.co/ctGerjgXQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your tax cuts are a joke for the average American, they were a payoff for your rich buddies and yo… https://t.co/A4UHkxMzD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob_sine @jbarbarito I like your point, Rob, but have serious doubts that Miami is the right market for that strategy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JVegas01 @by_JBH @ArtOfTheFu @RapSheet Lololol huge vote of confidence there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HumpDayHope #MidweekMotivation   Fact: Our God Has The Final Word!!!  #ThatPart My, my, my!!! #wipethetears… https://t.co/wxjAGA0Y8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @AmyFox43 @HeatherFox43 @Mel_Orlins @JaimeFox43 @MaryEllenFox43 @KaraDuffyCBS12 @LeahMKirstein… https://t.co/IshKaUmnBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dickenson County Public Schools are on a 3 hour delay today, Friday, March 8, 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatsyResists @B52Malmet Delanian has sold out. He hasn't been right for a while now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Maybe you should run back Into the Woods and stay there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @HBO @HBOGOhelp, the new UI for #HBOGO is terrible. Please change back to the old one. Sincerely, Everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[The One Where They Celebrate Lindsay’s Birthday At D•I•S•N•E•Y. Starring: My Beautiful Wife @LindsayMikrut  Guest A… https://t.co/1l5XssQ5OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were going to, well, like, say declare marshal law and suspend all sorts of freedoms, and say take over the… https://t.co/2rJapccOB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DFFS 💥🍒🥴 #BWOODKNOWS chadtepper @bam__margera @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/DoQwzoIlAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Art_Donovan @Siennagold @NSRasta @NHRA @JohnForce_FC @TeamChevy Aye Doc!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little back glass motivation for all my @ncstatemba cohorts, and nc.state @ncstatepoolemgt noobs during midterms.… https://t.co/ngWToVL0Mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ready for snowbowl, and the Fonz approves. #rctid #snowbowl #orangeball #denveraway @ Denver, Colorado https://t.co/EF2OIax0hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dreaded 4th quarter for the #twolves . Got to get this win at home. No collapse aight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fight over. Eubank absolutely battered DeGale around the ring. Cue up the split decision in three, two, one... #DegaleEubank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump no one is accusing the president of a crime. no they are accusing the president of multiple crimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  "The @packers need to start making some damn moves!"  *Looks to see which teams are handing out big contracts… https://t.co/b4Fc0kAqzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffShac @JamesHahnPGA @greg_kraft Played with Nicklaus at Doral in 90 as a rookie. Over 50, past his prime, woul… https://t.co/zavFWCq9vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And STILL your Raw Tag Team Champions! The Revival! At least it wasn't Ricochet or Aliester Black who were pinned.… https://t.co/O22Slg6ZKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyarnoldcincy @votePASTOR @pricehillchili @HamCoGOP @jimkiefer1952 @JoshDuckBurton @Dannoacton @CincinnatiCRs… https://t.co/vMM8CZAw4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troubledhubble Yes @Uber drivers that waste our time and cancel after we wait should get penalized and we should b… https://t.co/Fqa3n1v5Ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlamTalk22 @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse How could anyone let alone over 500 like this tweet? That says it’s all about this moronic crowd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD You need to interview that woman in Slidell, LA every night. https://t.co/kRD1OY8QAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @PFT_Live Kiss my ass with this crap,,, defense wins,,, as the PATRIOTS proved. Stop them or shut the ***k up !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some great food and big laughs with Michael D Marino at Visani Theater thank you! #standup #panzecacomedy… https://t.co/2CSvLL0nUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaG2772 Ewwwwwwwwwww😫 it must have been eye-opening experience LOL 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Because most of the time staffers are your age or younger and 30-40k is a normal starting first career salary.… https://t.co/sCwP68l0UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A winter tree with the mist from Niagara Falls hiding the Casino in the background. Shot outside of Queen Victoria… https://t.co/FfkdK6z6Gv]]></document></documents></author>