<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Mr Chair, for advocating for pay equity for all certified educators in FY20! Our students need highly qu… https://t.co/IpgucheNjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for charter to show up #boatdogchloe shows off her princess pose! @GeigerKeyMarina #kneedeepcharters… https://t.co/DUu9SQwXpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @NiallOfficial   #CryingInTheClub #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards   Retweet to vote. Good luck Nialler! 🌹 https://t.co/6pjNCRPULP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10ECGIRL1975 @TNMelissa Gotcha.   Well, I am glad you found out before you spent money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wilfrid Gordon Mcdonald Partridge  by Mem Fox  Paperback 9.3 x 9.3 inches Gently used rough corners (see images) Au… https://t.co/CngPLmRFv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garrettelliott @LimestoneDSB Thank you Garrett - I am incredibly honoured to be recognized by the #QUAA, and delig… https://t.co/ZphXgXNRws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC If u mean good u don’t have to flaunt them so what . U got a black staff. One of my best supervisors I ever ha… https://t.co/Jw5HZNJSXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce has been playing NF for the past few days, and I have been hooked ever since]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is much clearer wording than in the past. Re: structured data manual action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakeowen Much deserved! Wish you would come back to Syracuse for another show. #jakeownshouldwin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #BusinessMgmt job in #FortOglethorpe, GA? Click the link in our bio to see it and… https://t.co/NWvYsIk9aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key to life is to keep going and find the love within, even on the darkest and coldest day. Loving yourself mea… https://t.co/oFB06EswzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo In conclusion, healthcare is a fraud. Knees dictate health. Muscles reign supreme. Both… https://t.co/PpLhDrXGHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is fucking sick, I deep it at the most random times, I’m so happy and grateful for the life I’ve made for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever just rearrange your entire existence so that you don’t wake up your sleeping cat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@durbrow @realDonaldTrump He wouldn’t be the first! Think Nixon! Also brought down by the head of the FBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saint_anything7 @punkydory80 @SallyPort863 @MarkAgee @traecrowder Bull crap!  If abortions became illegal, the ult… https://t.co/XTXlJpxjZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the next two days I will be in @googleanalytics mode at @BrainStationTO 🤓 It’s important to always keep learni… https://t.co/exE6U8DvQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intentionality in housing policies and education policies are vital to battling school segregation #DiversityEquityAccess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle Female erasure ? War on women? So trans people want to replace women?! I’ve never met a trans person th… https://t.co/VVAwrbm4LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #snow! How’s your view this morning? #OHwx https://t.co/rZIIvEwVwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kstand40 @JoseCanseco @JLo I know I shouldn’t be laughing but damn. 😂😂😂 Bless you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment alone, immediately after you become husband and wife! ❤💖 Photography by Douglas Benedict Photography… https://t.co/oSMWjXFGD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t put your baggage at the entry way of your door and expect someone to climb over it to get to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadedDragonMMA @gunav8r64d @AOC She never worked ... what she did barely qualifies .. she has zero idea how corporate structure works]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwfulSer @barstooltweetss I was sure Cody was going to get it but damn lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You are an ass who obviously doesn’t have A life other than tweeting anti-Trump tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lanaroske1 @weemin21 @DrPyo @dudehowru @hanwooabi .@Thank you.@DrPyo  We are with you. LET'S END THIS BARBARIC DOG… https://t.co/ICoGV4pHaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 13 is starting on the quiet side. The electricians are here, but can't move the panel today :-(   Yesterday was… https://t.co/TZ5YCRXU9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicevilleTrack congrats to Jaylin Mills (High jump) and Kobe Babin (pole vault) for setting new school records today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Fauth completed the RnR Washington DC Marathon! Time 04:42:45 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/wMKrYu8IiN #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntvnyr173 @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs Well, Wray didn't do crap to restore faith in the FBI, that's for damn sure.… https://t.co/A881fmuADw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lindell gr. level meetings focused on  @JSerravallo’s structures for sm group instruction! I asked Ts, “What are s… https://t.co/1yBz2SGsES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Marsteller is so sweet I hope no girl ever breaks his heart again ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Powell89 @trey33wills Fortnite is having a skirmish lmao I’d hope they’d have more viewers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahstwits @cmclymer Even moreso as a woman exiting the service.   I went and signed my DD214, and was escorted… https://t.co/TJZ82kZq0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everly_bliss @mopage19 @roddrickjr @mevocreatives @mevostore @ColeSauceAdams @novoa_laz @Iivid @Benjamixn @CWDaly… https://t.co/Wo2YZclKK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dean_Bradley13 @MikeGrimala Noah said there was a miscommunication on the last two plays of the game. Meaning they… https://t.co/oatH2pJGkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost Friday 🙌 goodnight my lovely hooligans and @BrunoMars luv chus 😘 hi Bruno, thank you. Luv and miss chu 💋… https://t.co/JfUKeCfXrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Caturday from Jeezy cat who’s literally hanging out 😹He’s my handsome boy, my gorgeous, green-eyed mini panth… https://t.co/Yy3lAE7McA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazingly Proud of @careecodes , @JustAskClaire , @Tiffalwaysfly , @Johanna_Klay , @jennplusplus , and Jordan B for… https://t.co/4eEsJnS9rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning this women not only take our order but she hyped us up and prayed for us. Chick-fil-A have some of the… https://t.co/Csj0b4lcEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @realDonaldTrump @DineshDSouza @DonaldJTrumpJr @charliekirk11 @LouDobbs @TheDemocrats They're also a b… https://t.co/i2wVbjLKYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truest analysis ever! Same could be said of most things tRump has done! Would elicit the same response!  Just think… https://t.co/jUqs02k2Hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are they still allowing Cops to get away with killing unarmed Black Men. Why do they Hate us so damn much? We a… https://t.co/xtGssohVHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time there’s a semi sentimental moment in Game of Thrones, I just assume one of the people involved is going to die]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuestra verdad posible tiene que ser invención, es decir, escritura, literatura, pintura, escultura, agricultura, p… https://t.co/qKdrb3zUkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crookcreative Staying up north is always better with a #candle. Enjoy a free woodbecute Candle when you book your… https://t.co/gOTVaksCLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico How sweet of his new bestie to show him the way #TrumpKimSummit  #BFFS #commielover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechWarriorKES @Super2ndsMrsJ @JoyannDrumm @AWatsonKES @TechTeachVB @PintoBeanz11 @jlabar2me @iluvteaching72… https://t.co/2x80weEeZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Britney set the STANDARD and everyone artist that’s come after has just completely MISSED THE STANDARD - change my… https://t.co/siVBqVQ5I5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold onto your wigs, #WeHo! #DragQueenStoryHour is back with fun and fierceness for the whole family!   Find out mo… https://t.co/G9KfjPc4Rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Find a group of people who challenge and inspire you; spend a lot of time with them and it will change your life.’… https://t.co/hRsNIeH7aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If one thing defines me, it’s what God thinks about me” wow I love him😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sleep routine includes my Alexa playing rain sounds to block out the noises of #apartmentlife however tonight, i… https://t.co/cVbm9Eizb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexarharp My first semester of college I studied abroad in Italy and took several courses in fashion where my tea… https://t.co/3mR8IYS5MY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holooooo 😍😍 #houstonnailtech #coffinnails #swarovskicrystals #nailsofinstagram #chrome #holographicnails https://t.co/m90asZOC4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannaIngber @nytimes @michelledozois I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed bac… https://t.co/uZ7ThAu1HU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you  🌈Life Colors 🌈 @RainbowOfMySoul for liking my post and words! Happy day!💙💦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliapazdu Yo odiaba cuando estaba en cualquier consulta y ponian el mega y salía la vieja hablando de su vida...]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever get so irritated you just wanna go off on somebody that deserves it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I work with some of the most independent women I know and they inspire me every day. It's tough to work i… https://t.co/lXRUosKUaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting all of the NASCAR truck haulers we see as we head south through SC has become our favorite little roadtrip game this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[My perfect #ValentinesDay? I’m at home, three cell phones in front of me, fielding desperate calls from people who… https://t.co/uJSOz2NkRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OohShiny_Sarah @DrKChilds @instagram @facebook @TpTdotcom Don’t go chasing waterfalls lol!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got kicked out of a vegetarian and vegans group on fb because I commented “you guys are the reason people hate ve… https://t.co/Isz6kQwrOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s kick off St. Patrick’s Day weekend the RIGHT WAY!! Such fun party for a really great cause! You don’t want to… https://t.co/iu2fZicgCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reepRN @DRJOLT A hamburger is better than an incompetent healthcare provider, but NPs are good in many situations… https://t.co/9P0KSdtTyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi And for the first time in history it is legal to kill a newborn baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bowers217 7th graders...getting an early start on Spring Break reading tomorrow! https://t.co/34bMUfuavP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBryanOnline @AmericanIdol yes!! It's always alright to cry the #goodtears. The first time I saw you in concert… https://t.co/fstnZFU2lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalickUmair6 Wow! Surprised you could tell. I decided to put cashews because I’m in love with them! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently waiting for an unmarked mini van to pick me up at a subway station for work and this literally goes a… https://t.co/GMgv5DvHJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fried chicken report: the Damn Hot is ACTUALLY making @AdamMBrady sweat. Color me impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraTXAS Better yet let's bug their phones raid their houses and their lawyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StalkingKyle @79Aspen I see you in one of the city’s in Washington for sure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swohtz @redheadsupermod @jimgeraghty @ClintonFdn @ChelseaClinton I didn’t confuse anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[O twitter do Carlos Bolsonaro parece aquelas brincadeiras "escreva tal coisa e deixa o teclado completar". Ele não… https://t.co/p1Q7lCidIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broadwaysted LOVING @aaronjalbano ‘s report on the Stanley Martin episode from Hamilton Philip Co. with… https://t.co/OBAQgYzDq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much the most excited person in the house right now https://t.co/pvZBU9mc3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvnSosa18 La historia de Latinoamérica! Tan manipulada! Tan incompleta! Ninguno de nuestros países reconoce q nues… https://t.co/WaoCS7hcHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 @BravoTV So sick of Katie playing victim. Every single one of them have done some messed up stuff! Why… https://t.co/eKMMaeDydr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the castle ... about to see Mickey welcome everyone @ Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/Ap0aVJZkfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo... Penn Badgely. Like I’m watching Easy A rn but I can’t stop thinking about You???? But also... he’s always… https://t.co/Gh66C7Bv3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump around!! 😁 anniebug09 @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/oxtmY7T46s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiskeyRiff Coming soon ... @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ... https://t.co/FE8BI4aU9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es increíble como “sexy bitch” de Akon sigue prendiendo a la gente en el antro hoy en dia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #PinkShirtDay2019 message at work! Proud to be part of such a genuinely caring team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Mrs Trump, you are the most beautiful, gracious, and elegant First Lady Ever in my lifetime.  I would love to meet you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHamsClassroom I'll be driving from Statesboro so probably won't get there until 6:30 or so. But y'all get the party started.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlecole @shakeshack If this is correct, then it truly is a glorious day for Indy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to strong women.  May we know them.  May we be them. May we raise them. -unknown… https://t.co/iuq910cOqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you've never seen Show Dogs you must! It's hysterical! And has a little to do with a K9. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[New opinion alert! I would die for the owner of the club that booked Stormy Daniels. (She’s also responding to ever… https://t.co/ROr7y9m78v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gateway4Paws' days old Cav baby has spent 2 nights in the hospital in an oxgen tank. Our 10wk old Bichon baby is in… https://t.co/w5O03GVrJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCartelMatt @realBradStaggs @RantsOfIzzo @RealRonPhillips @j It smells like flowers and tastes like piss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blankslate2017 @panininef @bravenak I don't think it helped when some of his bros said PoC didn't vote for him bec… https://t.co/t3Lm1yWxMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianArthurReed @DrJenGunter Mary Dague is just one such woman.   https://t.co/LI9jmykghP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubenGallego Personally I’m sick &amp; tired of these attacks ads.  Our children learn these bullying tactics.  Stick to your Platforms!]]></document></documents></author>