<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There are as many active QBs on NFL rosters from the 2004 Draft right now as there are from the 2011 Draft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE OF THE GREATEST HTOWN AREA PREP BOYS BASKETBALL TEAMS OF ALL-TIME 1994 FORT BEND WILLOWRIDGE  THANKS FOR ALL TH… https://t.co/qV17xN7AMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Warner Brothers, you idiots. And I told you. Warner Brothers has a deal with the Pentagon and the CIA. -Math Powerland WHAT?!?!?!???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye delete this shit! You have the goat @CharlesWoodson fucked up. Better put Reggie Nelson in here or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@highhopespod did you guys here Bryce mention “a certain guy available in 2 years” as to why he went with the lower AAV. Awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gwen240733016 Thank you! Happy Valentine’s Day to you also my friend! Hope you have a wonderful day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themichaelbauer Honestly, how could he not? That's pretty much hockey in a nutshell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump The only way the Dems will stop their ongoing attempt to over throw our… https://t.co/9ab8Z6I9dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgirlsalina i know it’s only 12 there but i think it’s time 4 u to go to bed LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Dispatcher keep saying the same shit every week! Buddy not gone be happy til I really slide on they asses n take… https://t.co/X0QkeKtktt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton Context and motivation is everything. The Putin state… https://t.co/SGqgjwbVxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barner_ucsd Are your DMs open? It's not allowing me to send you a private message]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm guessing Jeff Gordon or his teleprompter writer intended to say "winless" not"win" streak referring to Kyle Larson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGraphicsinc It’s not easy stepping back and truly seeing our environment and what we have become.   It’s hard.… https://t.co/0sEXH8UeHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeandersonsr the fact that McCabe can brazenly admit what some would say is treason means he knows he will never… https://t.co/lVuTnwtQEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#asot900 @cosmicgate on now @estivamusic just killed it and the man @arminvanbuuren started it. Loving every second… https://t.co/lZElX8tR1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los q votaron ayer en contra: #ExtinciónDeDominio @GustavoBruzone @edufeiok @GFrondizi https://t.co/jhTcoTgxLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod No way--we have a criminal enterprise in the WH: it is time to investigate. You sound like… https://t.co/AQ3RVeXaFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hutchinsonbrown @empiremagazine A definite how to ride out of the hood guide. Rahd to riches.Hoe to get off Food stamps.etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin in background @1GunnaGunna album release party ・・・ Drip or drown..💧🌊 @1GunnaGunna @1future @youngthug… https://t.co/CVvpUULeBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKoenigsberg @woodypaige Allbright says Ross has sickle cell trait. That would pretty much rule him out at alt7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawd y’all just can’t handle someone who doesn’t verify everything you believe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatpeterfox @bariweiss @EmanuEl_NYC @streickercenter I keep hoping Bari will speak in the Twin Cities sometime! I… https://t.co/7wa7hnPggh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaliRanks @jdhmco DON'T this person use hateful speech all the time! double-standard https://t.co/pMgVVaDhoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a You’re All I Need DDH El Dorado by @interboronyc at @CraftysTapRoom — https://t.co/jUyNvRc0Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fair thread from @JonahNRO  I’ve felt he has been too critical of Trump at times and not as hard on the other side… https://t.co/X85RzfOWhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because of Jesus, we have the assurance that whatever disturbs us, disturbs God more. Whatever grief we feel, God… https://t.co/1qoTKSJzTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ant35Durant I haven’t won a series since ant.... never win a series with u lmfaoaoaoa tf. Ur actually retarded. At… https://t.co/yTbacjcYNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Jamarl Baker. Dude cannot buy a bucket anymore. Now 0 for 3 today and stuck in a 4-of-19 slump. Headed for his… https://t.co/z4iGfV2NeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico @realDonaldTrump :  "As long as they have hamberders and cheeseberders, I'm good"   Republicans like em d… https://t.co/lEVMHYdX8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the person I absolutely adore on stage teaching hundreds of people do exactly what she does is so inspirin… https://t.co/aal7CA8xHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swear I just saw a shadow walk into my kitchen. It's fine I dont need to eat or drink today 😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaleJesse @DCComics @ZacharyLevi Ok to be fair, as a journalist... I’ve been in love with @ZacharyLevi for YEARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feminazis  #Molotovs...  Bombas de humos... @LuchyB @__ayduchis__  @vanesavallejo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The baptism of the Holy Ghost has no circumstance,,in a two way Journey it's a one-track mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at United Dairy Farmers (UDF) - @udf_official in Florence, KY https://t.co/QAJFuSRDuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at INTRUST Bank Arena - @intrustarena for UFC Fight Night: Lewis vs. Dos Santos in Wichita, KS https://t.co/1y43H1PQhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @PressSec I say again, You folks have forgotten what your jobs are!!! You work for us!! It will come down on you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocxg1958 That’s why you study into it, not go off what heretics said. We have all the history needed to study up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[day 01 at ‘verks’  “finished” a few pieces on proper nice mounting boards  will soon be ready to frame and sell fwi… https://t.co/krU69H8sXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @OfficialNBARefs, I need a rule citation that explains why this isn’t a traveling violation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer Eh, I think today really clears up any questions about which one is Fredo. (Hint: It's @DonaldJTrumpJr )]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes the entire block’s power to go out for all the neighbors to come out and talk to each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeyAdams420 Not just NBA, it’s every level, been heading this route for while]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once heard “You show me your friends and I’ll show you your future” and that hit hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture A Day  from 2014 - March 6  #leicaimages #blackandwhite #photography #dailyphoto  📷 ©John R. Fulton Jr. https://t.co/EDJmymzBA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @PeteButtigieg is Leslie Knope &amp; Ben Wyatt’s child. This is my head-canon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago today my families life took a unexpected turn. We were put in a situation we thought would never lighten… https://t.co/Qg1DCs60Qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Recuerdas cuando te uniste a Twitter? ¡Yo sí! #MiAniversarioDeTwitter https://t.co/hb3jwY4TTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no doubt that Virginia ABC agents would love to ruin a perfectly fine wedding over a few bottles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitneyCummings i can't wait for all the stories of people getting eaten by velociraptors while taking a duckface selfie with them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44_rem_mag @Minuteman223 @Tactical_review @JenniPrickett @Bearman1130 @pensfannc5 @teamregulators @AverageHunter… https://t.co/dcfhQ0IMK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Memphis_MBB at @UCFMBB today 6PM ESPN2 and as a follower you get to see my graphics 1st! On another note:  • Chad… https://t.co/eepXcDGiXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatJunkman @HamillHimself I would start waiting in line for that movie now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is like watching Rocky trying to do commercials in Rocky II #smillManly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulMaxit Le faux chercheur @PaulMaxit a préféré masquer le reste de la planète. On se demande pourquoi... https://t.co/OlRQJVjAK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[No @AOC  you are not the boss!!! You are a dimented eye-popping idiot. The people in charge are the ones for keepin… https://t.co/PjWrfOtONn]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister sent me this... and I still haven’t stopped laughing https://t.co/jDDmHcUBcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[In between the final 2 big cold shots...another cutter looks likely. Story of this winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 I’ve been an AARP member for years but am considering not renewing. I guess I’d prefer they’d make mo… https://t.co/qpxmSWYU9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoodooMouth @vtmedic511 @washingtonpost @soledadobrien Why you creeping on my shit?  That’s a tad concerning to be… https://t.co/c8anM8cr3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Los Angeles. Hahaha. @ West Hollywood, California https://t.co/KB6qPK3NCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is what you learn after you know it all that matters most.  -John Wooden]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SchittsCreek and @annefrances for this totally catchy and instantly quotable song! OMG...  #naughtyelf… https://t.co/Qwbz0pHher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NachoRgz QUE PENA DAN LOS OPOSITORES, A VER SI NO GENERAN UN CONFLICTO MAYOR RT VA A IR LA RAZA DE ANDRÉS MANUEL Y NO SON DEJADOS RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommahenof3 Actually yes it’s very possible to pass illness through feces. Especially so with worms. Johne’s disea… https://t.co/knUUmSIn31]]></document><document><![CDATA[This summer will be our 20th of running Shootouts in Missouri!  We have some great new locations and dates lined up… https://t.co/a1gTE9yqop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quitting time on this Pre-Friday. Have a great evening. https://t.co/lOMvQfPXxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#riversidecraftbeerfest #untappd #craftbrewjunkies #craft #beer #craftbeer #craftbrew - Drinking a Passport: Pineap… https://t.co/aP2wUCRpWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFNYC1 @joelpollak He loves hearing people cheering him at rallies and watching military parades put on by foreign… https://t.co/4EjoUfROlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to those already shoveling &amp; snowblowing this morning. @WNYT https://t.co/JLlQlXVBlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump She kicked your Puppet President’s ass in the popular vote. This time we will be watchin… https://t.co/vIXhPYJFz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACGonzales7 The way to fix it is to give nfl players guaranteed contracts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hendricks_dc There are elements of luck in all sports. However, in poker it’s magnified in the short run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamilton is an amazing show, one of those rare things that lives up to &amp; exceeds the hype 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefendingCanada @johnnyboy73 @Corp_Raider99 @ltthompso @SaysSimonson @jenniferm_q @AOC How would the democrats kno… https://t.co/QfV1tdynIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latinas At https://t.co/SivopTLug0 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!🇷🇺… https://t.co/hmFKtBSSG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyDogSpirit @Dave_Harden @IlhanMN So we're responsible for actions by El Salvadorian  troops who  disregarded t… https://t.co/tYoutREVPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Gavin, why should people be able to cross illegally?  That has to stop!  A wall is necessary for our n… https://t.co/hlv7IgmouE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkylesmith @WSJ All true, but I wish the article also focused on the difficulty some workers over the age of 50 ha… https://t.co/x2TYfMhNjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the person who inspired me to get behind the lens: happy birthday @lizreyes_6 https://t.co/4w3fYrGafu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake Did you say the same thing when Obama put kids in cages and separated   them from their parents? No, bc… https://t.co/juVXHYoXXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JameyBaskow @GutterTheGreat @ehoeflich97 Meanwhile people are crossing the southern border with impunity. LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Georgetown game.   Let's go Mac Mcclung!! https://t.co/5guCg9rgR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxydavis99 @sfahey_imp @smp0312 @Pinche_Pi @tharpel @marcorubio 2% homogeneized https://t.co/6WmjqgzV9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[so girls. i just listened to the full jordyn interview and... kylie should take her back they have too strong of a friendship omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[CPAC Threatened to Ban Mediaite After Seb Gorka Complaint https://t.co/kVp5Zd8qUM. One example of freedom of speech… https://t.co/wzNsGjiKr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[New song “Son” out now on all music streaming platforms! This one is about my love for my son, the struggles of hav… https://t.co/FNNujMx8nV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga don’t worry. One day you’ll get it ! You’re a star ! #Oscars19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary Someone get Aunt Pitty Pat her smelling salts https://t.co/OD35dRVaXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Volling4Life Okay buddy, have fun with your program and I’ll be happy with our success✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sad13 @bobmouldmusic Mid thirties is as young as I'll go for the record. Sorry to disappoint!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN please don’t let the vile actions of a few discourage you from doing your job. Minnesota ((most of us) are… https://t.co/uT5EGPfeUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down but not out. Looks like I’m going to have to #kickbutt with my right foot for a while and let the #brokenbones… https://t.co/rViurG9JRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't need a garden hose to keep your #WinterBiking ride clean. Just a spray bottle and a single drop of dish s… https://t.co/LSo6ZdEghi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankieSanders @MattBruenig @TeddyRedder So socialism is having a large welfare state with a market economy, and an… https://t.co/TecZ7m01Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeninerDixon09 Hi Dee, just try and do one positive thing a day to start....it will start some momentum. Also does… https://t.co/WDeJWrFufa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeechiiMeech ME TOOOOOO !!!!! I got so much to say 🤦🏽‍♂️ Might just start one 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BloodyElbow Brock Lesnar has no business fighting for a title! He hasn't legally won a fight in almost 9 years and… https://t.co/hKGK3irCfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoundOFF13 I said the same thing about the announcers.  We got the regional guys for this game.]]></document></documents></author>