<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I pray for y’all future kids cuz some of yall got the game fucked up. Yall are gonna create some resentful ass kids… https://t.co/h28FDLBtWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NvisibleGent @jeffleach This seems accurate... @jeffleach - is this about right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump You'll have to add fuck to your iPhone dictionary. I can do that on my BlackBerry Keyone lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItsAparty ! @sirivan superbunnymina @ Villa Azur https://t.co/qgfrGyawMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utah is always among the highest on these maps, especially downstream of the Great Salt Lake. #utwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HebaJudeh *Drake voice* “ YOU’d YOU’d best... THE BEST I EVER HAD, the best I ever had!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A comer se ha dicho! #sushisonora 😎👍 #ElPoetaSoñador #ElReyDeCorazones https://t.co/3VD06mbdqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TYPhilly83 @Bl8knstuff @UnkhanciousAmir @TheKidIrv24 @The1stWright @SibbieBoxing @Im_gr8nss @JackAlterr… https://t.co/dIMnwqlcUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t post a picture of your bowl of ramen on your insta story did you really even eat ramen??? 🍜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Wholesale $5 Larry T Shirt Man Los Angeles Over 40 years In Biz. Call 424-213-0793 76 years Young Old. No Job Too… https://t.co/NnEW8PgYqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 pics of us VS the sheriff's office and 2 of us vs our Team 1 https://t.co/b7KKfs0u9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do enjoy listening to sports talk in town. It definitely keeps me entertained and not focused on our crazy… https://t.co/fRYsG5yBF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Chuck, if the founders knew you were running the Senate and your Party has put Sociali… https://t.co/dCnY52wt7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dax is helping me drink coffee ☕️ this morning. @ Suffolk County, New York https://t.co/8QnOsSJ6D1]]></document><document><![CDATA[in remembrance of the one time a year I wear make up https://t.co/bwNeEt6lu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teelittle0608 Seems like it was one of those things where we felt like “old” Kanye was coming back lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_reymenn My headphones need to charge, these peasants I work with don't deserve it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumbleTeej Kanye is Trump now. If he doesn’t completely vomit on himself in public they applaud him like a toddler acting good in public 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trpdo @frfrankpavone @DrLeanaWen @PPFA A sperm is a live cell in a man's body. An egg is a live cell in a woman's… https://t.co/drBf5fONHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDavidDuke Wait, shouldn't you be happy your Dear Leader is supporting another government. You all hate America i… https://t.co/NksG1eni3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man accused of child sex trafficking, child sex abuse https://t.co/N3MPIHgbC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cabel @DisneylandDrive If only The Addams Family were a Fox property...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more rappers to use their platforms like @YbnCordae , thank you 🙏 https://t.co/IIdcebHfkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aficionados del Fba en México que piden reunificación de la Liga Mayor....sigan a la @LFAmex ahi hay reunificación… https://t.co/Fom9pEt8Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el conversatorio sobre #Venezuela con nuestro embajador @carlosvecchio congresistas @DWStweets @RepShalala… https://t.co/sN8gkBZ9vA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just going to leave this here: no words needed.  📷😎  #weathersband #cameronboyer #grunge #rockandroll… https://t.co/nGu3JFbP3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok this travel pet thing is just getting out of hand!!! What’s next a chicken??🐔 @ Salt Lake City International Air… https://t.co/BRDffX7M10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrynaIvanova Si  eres de carne y hueso uta pos vastante ok ok. C cordiales saludos y bendiciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleadsyoufollow @CPAC @mschlapp @VanJones68 @realDonaldTrump You sound pretty desperate to cite a single paragraph… https://t.co/5cOW3TIEoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Phlebotomist (PST) - Englewood, CO - https://t.co/FRel4AX93H #Healthcare #Englewood, CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never in my life abused a woman physically or verbally never saw my dad do it to moma so.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I'll ever ask of you You got to promise not to stop when I say when]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to believe our little sweetie is going to be a year old on Thursday.  Time is flying! https://t.co/xtVblRyS0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[A long, hard day of work resulting in great Vision and Mission Statements for the Society of St. Vincent de Paul Au… https://t.co/6hhVMK9DBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffPedigo24 man I'm unaware of this lol  just talkin bout him being cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portraits of the North. Inuit art from the collection of the @ArtGallBurl. https://t.co/t7GXbDcTNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you having a bad day, remember. There’s people that buy shit to impress people they don’t like! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally squirted BBQ sauce in my eye today and I'd have to say lemon juice felt wayyyyy better]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Smoking Sunday! One 💛 😎🌎 👁️! https://t.co/UpEsjhneje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Lo único q todos los venezolanos saben es q está podrido es tu cerebro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe encounter's ironic to necessity's attributive, true extent. https://t.co/tzkRQhtqZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmac19 Tristan trolls the red from beyond the grave. Just a warning to one of the very, very few members of the in… https://t.co/iTAesmeGRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenM1978 @pueblo_hnos @mbachelet Esa desgraciada, cuando gano Bolsonaro, salió hablando que iba a vigilar el go… https://t.co/BTwxu7bT6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkhaselden People w debilitating health issues(mental/physical)? People taking care of family members? Talking dow… https://t.co/xjmsQS0yj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam @ArianaGrande Me when I see @JheneAiko https://t.co/z3pxScwIyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smilon713 This is where we are, what was supposed to be settled isn't, Fighting for the same thing still.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcgmc #singitforward #gala #heroesball #foodporn #rainbow #dessert @ Minneapolis Marriott  Northwest https://t.co/h9RiPmIvKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the Trump administration covering up for the Saudi’s murdering of an American resident and the father of Ame… https://t.co/Y9ACM4zRx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loyalty is essential to leadership. The wise leader cultivates loyalty by being loyal—loyal to the Lord, loyal to t… https://t.co/VRIKnJ05YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMFofAMF @WaveItByeBye @Orioles Thank you Aaron, Joe will be missed a ton, that’s for sure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustInformU The reason why a lot of the media outlet say that the Q anon followers are a bunch of  conspiracy theo… https://t.co/GMvJ7AUsXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Murphy8 @BarstoolJordie @NHLPlayerSafety But the elbow before that hit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[...so many Steelers fans in their feelings, worry about your own future instead ours! #RaiderNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Democrats wouldn't tell the truth if their life depended on it, Dan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdube940 A la clinique GMF .Le 05 février dernier mon médecin m'a dit qu'elle ne se fiait pas au diagnostic de l"i… https://t.co/G1DRq5hseT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone got flowers and chocolates and what I got was a cracked screen 🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulfistSV @SpeedyDonut @maximilian_ But it doesn’t mean he has to play Jump Force like he said he’s only going to… https://t.co/Hbtj56B6HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX God bless Kevin Harvick very kind of him to say things like that! I agree Jimmie Johnson deserves more credit]]></document><document><![CDATA[March into the madness with @RiceAthletics in Frisco. Join us!  📍 » @CityWorksFrisco 🏀 » @RiceBasketball + @RiceWBB… https://t.co/jkOKc3WDa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odell Lake! So many memories catching fish and avoiding the osprey. @LaurenKARE11 thanks for the flashback! Love it. https://t.co/a3sB7NHFUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGTreport God bless you Sean! Seems we are about doomed to the same fate as sodom an gamorra. The times are truly twisted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephen_g This is a good book about trouble sleeping. The movie’s really good too. https://t.co/YNeYNb3wv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump I did the same thing. I no longer donate to the @GOP also. I no longer donate to ANY re… https://t.co/7cMrBnVh2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamselby @eierund @lyft There is a requirement to have four doors and seat four people, I think. Which this truck… https://t.co/qBgiZAZLsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[They lead the way. #childrenareourfuture #givethemyourtime #ihaveadream #parenting #education #teachers… https://t.co/DU01ac4Pey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united Yeah, but you could just serve nothing to depart on time. Not trying to argue. I know you guys want to try… https://t.co/MK9ly2Go8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is always a pleasure when the State of Pennsylvania takes an interest in the things that we are doing!  LED Ligh… https://t.co/lfJhN9wBdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods That's only if you're a practicing Mormon, with only one wife. Otherwise, you're a polygamist and a… https://t.co/QjXONzPGfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sweet harvest of death can take me now. JK, I’ll be up until this evening. #RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlonelykt Malia is also surrounded by those that talk a lot and snitch.  I need her to fix that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman Insane who runs this country, the worst kind of low life bullies, the ones with puffed out chests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahCRothman If you wake up in the am and say what can I do to preserve my heritage and culture today? you're eith… https://t.co/5HOu3jrHJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aManAboutFilm It's called, projection. It's why cheaters in relationships see "clues" of cheating of their partner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iangarcia4L @therealnomo They definitely pulled the genre switch flawlessly!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nobody , NOBODY hurting my feelings , I’ll laugh in ya face😩🤷🏼‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohlacy Yes. "Women can do what they want and shut up no one asked you." More or less. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMaxPrice About to have those 1 on 1 sit down meetings with guys. Always a good chance to find out where their mind is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga and Bradley Cooper’s performance just gave me chills.   Also—they’re in love right? @starisbornmovie #OSCARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @LarryMNC Today, still wanted by the government, they survive as soldiers of fortune. If you have a proble… https://t.co/JD0xELxrSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oldgloryfighter Reasonable plan: shoot all of those who would invade or attempt to destroy our country!! So many problems solved. 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Just #HanginOut #And #Waiting #On #Bus @ Faith https://t.co/c1AI6KCSs5 https://t.co/TEVBhcgD9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Playing: Wayne Price &amp; Brandon Hardin’s ENLARGED TO SHOW DETAIL 3. @311 @NickHexum @pnut @BrianaMackay… https://t.co/WGKqg8jcwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talisalilli one of our best ever @FalconSwimDive. In class or on board. #BGGlobal #Champ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lissacespedes Joven, quien adquiere bienes de mala forma no es caballero, es corrupto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linguistic #protip: if the word came out of your mouth, it most certainly IS in your vocabulary. https://t.co/A8Ig3eZ2y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyk1996L5 @AmericanIdol @LionelRichie @katyperry @LukeBryanOnline @RyanSeacrest Listen to #mamacita here https://t.co/VWmS0xVmca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VolkertMath @Cuse_MBB @DukeMBB @espn Oh man! We just got over all that 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are the other songs remixes with hold me down in the runaways?? @travisxthompson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Branko_MA @75Schulte @therealgaytupac @RMFT_Roy @a1flaherty @lovelifetan @JOHNSTE16060063 @Melissa51668186… https://t.co/5WXqFt9cLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enumera una serie de "acciones de apoyo" durante 12 años.... Y en menos de 100 dias en el poder ya se  arrepintió 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desperté a las 4am y, sin poder dormir, me puse a ver el proyecto de @JoseRGuzman CAMINANTES EPI 1, Cúcuta. "Comida… https://t.co/5CMMKfuDEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any fool can criticize, condemn and complain—and most fools do. But it takes character and self-control to be understanding and forgiving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Take your prayers and thoughts and shove them up your ass!  That’s all the good they will do. We n… https://t.co/T6NCzSuenA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to write a movie about a person with severe anxiety going through the day, but throughout the entire movie,… https://t.co/lwPcSqupc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Knowing that a man is not justified by the works of the law, but by the faith of Jesus Christ, even we have believ… https://t.co/BwGVroT7YI]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Cheney grills Pence on Trump's foreign policy: In a private session, the former vice president tol… https://t.co/8OfRRarPxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syrian Armenians miss 'home' while living in Yerevan https://t.co/3sQMqIWdN4 via @TheNationalUAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost from Bob Goff.  This is very challenging stuff. @ Petaluma, California https://t.co/jkSd1n4wZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indiana’s first telepharmacy allows residents to fill prescriptions without direct contact with a pharmacist, givin… https://t.co/TP0EYoYf2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awndrayah_marie Dude how the hell are you completing yours way faster than mine]]></document></documents></author>