<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA['Nother day, 'nother dollar. 👀💸  #selfie #beforework #letsgetthisbread @ Eatontown, New Jersey https://t.co/WgrtA5VmQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[23 years and I’ve never once had problems seeing... i have Theo and my eye sight goes to shit... how? Why? Soooo not fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[swimming day at the beach. not suitable for advertisers as per manual review? i dont understand :( @YouTube https://t.co/Z4Vo47jyXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eriineb um yes. We deserve a night of watching 20 episodes while drinking wine &amp; yelling “David” together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at ´dem faces! Are we acting? Yeah but maybe not... you’ve probably seen this image circulating and that’s bec… https://t.co/aPfhaH6cNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the day:  “Mrs. Brown it’s  a good thing you’re not a dog or you couldn’t eat that chocolate” 🤦🏻‍♀️😂… https://t.co/0DvDPS2CDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton when your married there is no boss you do things together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayley_paul35 happy birthday to our first blessing Hayley!!! We can’t believe that your 19 today. We are so proud… https://t.co/NYSy6NJhut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaaaas, I am so glad you realized how much can change when you drop some extra baggage 🤣 Love ya 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBeeInDaBoot Disclaimer Obviously I mean Gardner having to defend CO as an R in a blue state in a Presidential year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueensBarrios @amazon @Target @OksanaMironov @SamuelBStein @SPAN_NYC Tagging @CDP at @SafetyNetUJC Paula S. Annnnd… https://t.co/ChjqNOYG51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second project of 2019 - thank you visionlosangeles , _pamlyles , and @jstwtg for your tireless work. Thank you… https://t.co/N1xXBdCsXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Imjustajew :”Hey #GoogleHOME . Set an alarm for 6:10 am.”  #GoogleHOME :”Okay. For when?”  *BlinkBLINK*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Lawrence and most of Nicole;  I’d believe McCabe any day of the week over the orange one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I can’t deal with men now smh  Repost from @iamdsprings using repostregramapp - @itsdlai thinks he's th… https://t.co/9p3U1r96Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . Her opponent is absolutely not that outsider.  Toni Preckwinkle started as a reformer, but has become increas… https://t.co/DQfzXO9vIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC’s Mom Left NYC for a Red State Due to High Taxes, Says Daughter Was Not Raised to Be Socialist -… https://t.co/9KGS3Eqor6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Who would think a Government shutdown for a month would have any effect at all. Probably all the hundreds… https://t.co/0J3IZHDk8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at that a typical Democrat blaming others and like he has no responsibility in that .New York has allowed her… https://t.co/8H1eMylsat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUSPress We noticed that. Good idea to choose better representation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregRickford You need to represent your constituency and ask them if they agree - Northwestern Ontario has not bee… https://t.co/1GgLnPHFkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just get an overwhelming emotion of missing someone who passed away years ago? That pain never goes awa… https://t.co/9yti1GQLt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your plane has landed and the pilot comes over the intercom “we are unable to deplane due to the gate being oc… https://t.co/KRFyRT9DXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FizzWizzPop @Devoted2Death @VersaillesFam @Mathilde_Felton It’s a Funko...you can google and locate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Potholes: 1  Traffic: 0  Expect MAJOR delays if your heading on 275 W between Turkey Foot and Mineola as @KYTC work… https://t.co/yJnKQ6GGZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latantepat @migangelgarzam @10APG @TigresOficial Amor amiga 😍😍😍😍😍mi krac lo amo 💛💙💛💙💛💙💛💙💛💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jk11195355 @provdcrumblover @PatriotismCosts @luv2research @SBDSoultrain @NoFacebookForMe @RussellMace2… https://t.co/bqasX4MczK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the All Tournament Team!! #49thDistrict https://t.co/j3jeE8KgiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roma was beautiful. Well-deserved win in cinematography. #AcademyAwards2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACT: House Democrats are not standing idly by. They’re working to stop the #FakeTrumpEmergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuguNdabezitha @TMZ I’ve always thought jordyn and Kylie were more than “friends” if they no gay they could play lesbians on tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[These aholes are crazy if they don’t see the crisis. I’ve had a family member murdered. Trump is the first politici… https://t.co/jjdWDGDyYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HKP2012 @Elle_Noo I think peeing on things is a joy boys never grow out of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @aderisaprod with get_repost ・・・ #OfficialTeaser #GuardingSantos The world-premiere of Guarding Santos take… https://t.co/obFQe2UzDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union represented with great bunch a kids! They presented their inventions to judges! Amazing and brave!!!!… https://t.co/Mpi47QacWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall my sister tax man gone ask her “ how much she want back “ like what 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least the snow kept a lot of the idiots off the roads, but it did make for slow going. I really wanted to skip t… https://t.co/ntmOnJPdk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard a huge bang in my house and have no idea where it came from 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have ps4, please get dead by daylight so i have more people to play with. ok thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love, love, love these women! Thank you for your friendship. Looking forward to working with you again. Dream com… https://t.co/d3CmyneEML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanadabalos Yes beshy!!! Di ko pa rin priority yon now lol pero kung may dumating, I’ll treat it as a blessing ❤️… https://t.co/uSTI1dCiYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovingtonAHS @RyanBurnsRI Exactly. It’s an attempt to focus on observable behavior instead of innate value of kid,… https://t.co/vuiNlxazb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day in my studio 😊 👩🏻‍🎨  #picassiette #mosaic #artistlife @ New Milford, Connecticut https://t.co/Pk8KUu0cgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for humor . . .  #mirth #laugh #smile #absurd https://t.co/hnhve3UjqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[*In court* Judge: “Ms. Williams, do you have anything else to say today?”  Me: “yes..... SLATT+”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am profoundly grateful to be one of the  recipients of this prestigious Award.    Thanks to the nominating commit… https://t.co/9v6xq4Fdii]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people walk around in the morning with a sleeping toddler in the house?! I feel like my tip toeing is an ele… https://t.co/dZFZqqpZjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[*gets call from hailz* Hailey: look at the sunset  ❤️❤️❤️ luvubitch @haileyneel17 https://t.co/5p5eRz5xy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost😎 Me on tha DAILY🎧🎶 #youngthug #thiefinthenight #rap #trap #rnb #hiphop #rockerchick #hippiechick… https://t.co/Ao6eVXfprz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went behind the scenes, hung out under the castle and met birthday Mickey. Basically a perfect day ♥️🐭🏰🗝🎈… https://t.co/YjsZymCC5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerperry Yay! Got my tickets in orchestra section! See you tonight! #Columbia#]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoruba Richen's Green Book Documentary Centers Black Joy, Not White Ignorance https://t.co/fg8rHsBSDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finfanna @JohnTory @ttcriders You know Michael Ford won't.   I'd like to see our Mayor not be so weak on the issue… https://t.co/M0SpBfCdu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers The little boys with their Bibles outstretched give me the creeps for some reason. Indoctrinate them young, I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masks zine has funded! Woot!! https://t.co/bNWb5zbxA9 via @kickstarter #Kickstarter #RPG #tabletopgaming #ZineQuest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special place in hell for them I’m sure of it. I’ll  never understand why people like this even consider these kind… https://t.co/hsVPz33bi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimberviewAVID @mattworkman88 @CoachKHowell Congratulations to players, coaches, faculty, staff and parents! It ta… https://t.co/RJdLs9aTya]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all this rain - a sexy, rainy home cooked dinner sounds like the most romantic game plan for #ValentinesDay, p… https://t.co/dLK509NhvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy Presidents’ Day to my favorite person besides myself https://t.co/8vtCU1E3uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So im getting my hair dyed, a tanning membership, a gym membership, eyelash extensions, and some nails. This is goi… https://t.co/DpXPStMVDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of a fantastic #blackhistorymonth... something that should be celebrated everyday! Things might not be per… https://t.co/JTAt3N6Bwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @spencer145p @LindseyGrahamSC I'd say he's definitely compromised. I have said that to him via a tweet b… https://t.co/D2HuecQZOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Slumchild x @renegade_el_rey 🎬episode coming soon! #GoldmineMondays  🎥: urban_media_network  📸: @BlooNotes aka the… https://t.co/aBAsepYM2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be the single greatest thing about #TheBachelorFinale 🙌🏻❤️ @carrieunderwood will ALWAYS be my favorite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump We have never in history seen or had a liar about the things he has lied about (which i… https://t.co/coTdtJgruz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the most distracting scenes are the wide ones, because from afar it kind of looks like a Barbie with the he… https://t.co/yn9zE75NOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Jordan, a 12 year old who was recently diagnosied w/ leukemia for the 3rd time. In order for him to success… https://t.co/ZSGWXJON17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkolGriswold I’m a die-hard and would stick with them no matter what. It’s the journey that’s the most fun. #skol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a serious question! 🍩🍩🍩  or  🍰🍰🍰 ❔❔❔ #Cake #Donuts #SweetTooth #DonutsOrCake #CommentBelow… https://t.co/myVdM5FtRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verizon Guest Wi-Fi is Ultra-Fast High Speed Internet that works with Largest LTE Coverage by Verizon network.. https://t.co/42ELucjm0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyJoyful @EdWitteman An excellent way to spend the days of lent. Never know it might just become a habit!! Ten y… https://t.co/NJNZ5hLsrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who don’t play softball will never understand the pain of getting hit by a ball or losing a game ...🥎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schraubd @peterdaou @IlhanMN I’m not sure that Irish-American support for IRA 50 yrsago wasn’t characterized as lo… https://t.co/fxmlwnkDX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trumper1620 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂delusional 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂cuckoo 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂my father fought for this country and we love it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The flu sucks on its own. A kidney stone or a UTI sucks on its own. Want to know what you get when 2 of the 3 are c… https://t.co/MzTxq7eZM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, forgetting i do not have a car: i’m gonna go to the summit tomorrow :) me, remember i do not have a car: :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just really don’t like @MarthaStewart on Chopped, @FoodNetwork. #ThankUNext]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 @jdougmar I'm allergic to pot. Both my boys tried it at home. First one got grounded-he was 16. I'm… https://t.co/33jK1zbDud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for Captain Marvel. @ AMC Theatres Phipps Plz 14 https://t.co/oc9lzXZmgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Good Morning Ellen.. Please help me. My sister and brother are retiring from the Armed Forces and I n… https://t.co/wjgyusp4ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portlandia is one of the most cringe-worthy tv shows out there &amp; I absolutely love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s something that brings you instant joy? 😍 Bubble tea 🍹 flowers 🌸 and my @hookedbyangel Rocky cozy are three o… https://t.co/E86y3Ilv1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Williamsport, PA, check out this #CustomerService job via the link in our bio: Food… https://t.co/IbIbeZoEEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The March issue of ToxTalk, the newsletter of the Society of Forensic Toxicologists, is now available.  https://t.co/EPnji6Lek0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLowry_WMS @woodbridge_ms @Gar_Field_HS @FredLynnHornets @HighFlyingHawks @RipponMiddle They did a great job! Congratulations 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughing at the hysterical way our country’s most important issues are being unmentioned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRIMESPORT you need to hire @NASCARPROFESSOR to speak to your guests @DISupdates and @NASCAR events]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryM12105098 @bjcreigh Joe Kaine started Mardi Gras in Mobile before the Civil War. New Orleans picked it up afte… https://t.co/9LA9oHj6sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this small Oakland arts school got a donation of four Chinese paintings, valued at $2.8 million, admin got to… https://t.co/Mx8UG5Crl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just dont be understanding after sex what more possibly could u want? let’s part ways and never speak again. i’m wit all that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RulingSports This one is tough for me to understand as a former horse owner and always equine enthusiast. You know… https://t.co/NatIHWWw3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[If doing self love affirmations and drinking white wine at 5am is wrong I don’t wanna be right. #selflove2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mares in a Jam by @smallponybeer @ #OttBeerBloggers HQ — https://t.co/WwSJirUvGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmHousingMick @AmHousingJim Your eulogy was beautiful @AmHousingJim. I love your stories about your big brother, J… https://t.co/wVg74odYR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the sales. (at @Gap in Maumee, OH) https://t.co/EDompOq46z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMeadows is racist! Nothing but lies and racist gibberish come from Racist Mark and his opponent. This was back… https://t.co/PpTtNbx0JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to work from home two days a week now so I impulse bought a desktop Mac it’s fine everything is fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay is Valentine’s Day this means I’m staying in bed and watching movies..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeymcintyre In front row center tonight! 3 blondes &amp; a red! You’re doing amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natural glam look today on the beautiful kate_kate_marie using mostly @ctilburymakeup ! This was the perfect weeken… https://t.co/Fy3CVs8Py2]]></document></documents></author>