<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Jess: How do you make broccoli cheese soup? Me: Broccoli, cheese, and soup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Bibles R sacred. The fact that those "Christians" had that adulterer, liar, greedy, slothful, gluttonous,… https://t.co/bUWHtNrpas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweets4poppy @Dumbelly @SuzaSusza @PaulMer70053201 @ImabitcSumtimes @speabud @LadyNY4Ever @mdd0027 @andrsngirls… https://t.co/ExLnEKnBxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDubins Matthew, I'm sorry I forgot to get back to you on this. Jim just poked me about it. My mentions have been… https://t.co/v5sp9mrOQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[17th Annual Actra Awards with this man right here 💖 still beaming with joy and love. Clearly I got my eye on the pr… https://t.co/sfZnEAsjxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_volmert @Coach_Creighton @CoachRobReeves @CoachAaronKeen @VianneyFootball Congrats, John!!! 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song sustained me during a low point in my life. I sang it night and day. Thank you, R. Kelly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capthlr @chrissyteigen @JaimePrimak You are so right @capthlr.  That is such a tactless thing to say!  I can’t eve… https://t.co/BIbbjo2Onl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep because I had a bad experience with a photographer. To all the creepy dudes out there YALL SUCK!!! I… https://t.co/gDRNhpwYaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like full light. I’m too self conscious 😂 but darkness with some kind of dim light is good w me 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliantly said 🥇🥇🥇 The most uncomfortable I was, learning and being forced to learn #systemtesting of a medical d… https://t.co/Jmws3tovKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow hardcore nose bleed while I’m on my period - if blood starts coming out of another orifice do I win something or...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gettysburg Tour - AMAZING new Visitors Center and Museum - Gettysburg Cyclorama / The Battle of Gettysburg painting… https://t.co/e51cWeaA8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure I saw Jack White in an airport two years ago and I still regret not talking to him. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah, what a great interview tonight.  I just realized that I miss your show!  I’m happy for each of the young men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@takethat Happy ❤️’s Day..thank you for the ❤️&amp; thoughtfulness you share w/us; we are forever grateful! https://t.co/jgFKIQhI5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jentrification Yeah. I never forget a face at a BGC event. 😉 So I found that interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking love Jake Gyllenhaal &amp; thats THAT.  JAKEY BABY  CALL ME  BEEP ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that they are saying we might get another snow storm this weekend makes me want to cry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSLalonde @banffcentre Enjoy it! It’s a beautiful and inspiring place. Swim in the pool, it’s the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treacle_A But would he shut up long enough for you to be able to do so? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen @LeanneMcQueen1 Thank you!  Right back at ya' from Dorothy and Kevin Nicolazzo!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do your own research instead of blindly following a false prophet. And YOU KNOW THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN RIGHT AND WR… https://t.co/HBm3zruJMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave it to her because 1) They’ve been looking for it, and 2) I like her plans for it. (And 3) There will be … co… https://t.co/GWuwwnZN2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) the “moment of enlightenment.” This style is a little woo-woo. One event, and your life is changed? Not likely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always going to be brutally honest about how I’m feeling when it comes to dating because if someone can’t accep… https://t.co/yVTHYCDWie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the KOA Behind the Sign Giveaway and you could win the Grand Prize of a Keystone Passport 175BH, a $500 KOA g… https://t.co/eJrP69pvAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @RahmEmanuel on @Morning_Joe - universal education is the key to everything. From early childhood thro… https://t.co/MJQL21vFcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanted to say how much I love my friends ❤️ https://t.co/uI7SSwPfUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucker is fucking amazing, I have butterflies 😻🤤🤤 @nickjonas @joejonas @kevinjonas]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if I’m lowkey and not on my phone as much it means I’m being sneaky ? :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[And how can we focus on helping them creating pathways out of poverty. Too often it’s a matter of life or death.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A photo series depicting my feelings towards this winter ft tiny snowman - 📸: @_kathrynamoy @ Brooklyn Botanic Gard… https://t.co/PnRIH55xca]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to get me chocolate covered strawberries tomorrow I’ll be in the floral department at HEB all day. 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleCohn555 if this hasn't been shoved down your throat already I'm gonna say it. I don't care if you consider… https://t.co/6GrBiwjRIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you're not getting answers, ask better questions.” https://t.co/R8Sh7xqyXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boys. 🐱🐱 #adventuresofmauiandaliki @ Rigby, Idaho https://t.co/8IGrbNBYOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandalovescats I love this for u too. 2019(and every year tbh): YOU A BAD BITCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do some girls edit their photos so much where they look like freaking cheetos. lol girl it looks awful😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyEdge @Jim_Jordan @DonaldJTrumpJr @GOP Interesting that they didn't accuse Cohen of lying about Trump commi… https://t.co/SGLxa9ucE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[this moon cycle I chose to not chose escapism and to stop running away from my issues! and ditch my dependency on c… https://t.co/bPHWhC2Y98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMcMullin @thepoliticalcat Never in my life did I think I would say the following in my country: “I trust our m… https://t.co/fPlzCumJcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a parent, I have no problem saying no to $$$, expensive clothes, late nights, dubious suitors... but I absolutel… https://t.co/Kkc3y8IXWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnBardon @DanMuskin You realize if they had one ounce of proof he did something wrong they would have done it du… https://t.co/SRAAX5pSf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather You know every single time Trump has a chance to make an important decision... Along with the Reps under… https://t.co/3SXDvmGvMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Just try not to worry about what people think. No matter who we are, some people love us, some hate us.… https://t.co/vKpDW1mG21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck She has her position because her dad was famous and her mom is rich AF, how much more empowered does… https://t.co/mkT1BhHYDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrooklynIII Even better play on words… But you should look up the organizations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @florence_parly And why are you talking politics and global trade? You know nothing of either. Go back… https://t.co/QvKl4liX9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[my prof just dropped the bomb that he went to high school with hillary clinton like it was no big deal 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @FLOTUS TOO FUNNY.🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣. AN ENABLING WEAK WOMAN WHO PUTS POSSESSIONS AND MONEY BEFORE MORALS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyogaVee I honestly am not sure if a lot of people believe in what they claim to believe. It seems more like attem… https://t.co/lvPTCNtSFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of this financial advice BITCOIN WE NEED VISAS AND THEY POPPIN. ADS FOR WOMEN https://t.co/Ps1TXct8r3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emeril @MontysSunset How do you grill snow crab? They look amazingly delicious 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What are these guys, jerks or something. I know what I’m talking about.” - Don Cherry talking about the Carolina H… https://t.co/SQ89XqN0ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #FieldsFam for all you do for our customers, the community AND each other!!  No squad I’d rather have tha… https://t.co/Gu1jIcL8bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[California is a shithole... a cesspool of degradation. 8 more months and I am out of here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado’s public schools handed out nearly 6,000 out-of-school suspensions to young children. Do suspensions and e… https://t.co/LxXy4gm5lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump when u live your entire life in a completely selfish and immoral way, eventually it catches up to… https://t.co/hVcaX4UNtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LongLiveCashout Bitch I talked to him I told him what you said I said “Ken said he got a BIG BITCH For y’all to hi… https://t.co/iKlqzK2Pw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisRussellTN @MelvinGundlach @MK_McMaster You need a uterus to get to have a say in this issue. I don’t try to… https://t.co/xBvjRcuhSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDietzen @NCIS_CBS @SeanHMurray @CBSTweet @CBSTVStudios @WValderrama @margoharshman @CBS Great show tonight. As usual ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast of Champions @ Broadacres Open Air Market https://t.co/7IhXq8ucNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alllwftopic @Expelliarmoire @BlinkyMclasher @eclecticbrotha @MattMurph24 I'm not defending her specifically.  I ev… https://t.co/UzVfi7Ft6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MeghanMullan for being a big part of why this student @HolyFamilyOCSB loves going to school each day! Th… https://t.co/r7W0MCTD6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jameshill @USLChampionship @PhilaUnion @NCAASoccer Absolutely.   As a wise man once said, the times they are a changin'...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsnia_imani @DKing5_ is UDF where you took me that one time I came up there? 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IcyQueenBee @braveunicorn55 @sewwutnow WE NEED TO HELP THESE HOMELESS, PEOPLE ALL OVER THIS COUNTRY, THEY NEED ALL… https://t.co/ruDDHzJnvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#brunswickroselle did a great job on my daughters 15th bday party . https://t.co/SuvCfas2Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastiskt tacktal från kvinnorna bakom ”period”: - A period should end a sentence, not a girls education.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well logging into Facebook to watch dogs videos now! Don’t lose your minds y’all still time to fight! #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Canadian and I am meh on  buttertarts. I hate buttertarts with raisins. Raisins remind me of dead flies..… https://t.co/LHlFmvkwlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey, does anyone want to be my doubles partner at ascension next month maybe 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step One: Do not propose policy that prohibits gun ownership due to a disability.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 7th graders are getting ready for the next year planning their schedules thanks to our counselors! https://t.co/62Oc8cCb2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone has the keys to emotionally highjack you... change the locks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do NOT order from @dolcegabbana online if you want to receive your package! My order was to be delivered before Val… https://t.co/u1964rpc48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought a sexy lil piece to surprise him but I feel so self conscious wearing it lmao fml 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BxglL @CSonafelt @rosemoczulski1 @72cricket @sharon_schwan @sannbs @MrsSpuds @RidenerTina @ACog1984 Yep, me too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onlymeveronica Agreed! I love Huck &amp; Jim both live and on the album. It’s such an awesome song. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY FRIENDS ARE SO TALENTED AH, i love u all and i’m so glad south hills has amazing students like these representin… https://t.co/kkYK87YOyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 Savage released from immigration detention, immediately flies to metro Atlanta: https://t.co/FZQgjHEAIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[HE DIDNT EVEN TELL CAELYNN WHY HE SENT HER HOME  #thebachelor https://t.co/oyRzqmzlce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lazlovely @thebrainofspock @Emma_black_cat @evamacalpi @BarbaraBpiwetz Did you finds dem Roise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvgAndy Yep it's absolutely crazy! And we're concerned about flooding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattywattyboy not really sure a residence or private space, it’s on 17th!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria Iman Santoso completed the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! Time 02:44:42 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/0sOApTW5NO #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe no North Korea deal...But coming back with a little traitorous treason as a souvenir... 🤷🏻‍♀️ “I believe Kim… https://t.co/7WAvvb4zfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bunch of chick fil a was delivered to our door by accident so spring break is already off to a great start]]></document><document><![CDATA[No picture has ever been more true than this one! https://t.co/Dyc2DqBXc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeltWitch @Fact_Check_Er @pollsofpolitics @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Gee, said IF I offended you, not anything was of… https://t.co/BwAd7s8m76]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you conduct yourself everyday becomes your brand. What does your work, punctuality, and dress tell the world ab… https://t.co/45zzhSPVt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me this morning listening to #BoysInTheBand especially when @DonnieWahlberg starts rapping! https://t.co/SoVwf8KqKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling over a period of time....just a few trips along the way!  Now I get paid to do what I LOVE ❤️😍😍😍........… https://t.co/sB5Yt5XExi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliciaGodinezzz Hellll no girl, shopping on a budget over here lol I’m gonna thrift till i find!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraBoxer Like most people, I prefer the @AlecBaldwin version anyway. 😉🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mosaicartist2 @squarerootsmac @ACTBrigitte @DineshDSouza While using her father's address, a town in which she did… https://t.co/Shm9wj6mY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarborough_ @JoeNBC @CuttingRoomNYC So sad to hear this! Thoughts and prayers your way. I had planned to attend.… https://t.co/jCawm5nG9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[My political science teacher said he purposely will give you one point lower than the “letter grade you deserve” if… https://t.co/buPsDveFoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about verbs and practicing one of our favorites! @NBRFisher @NBUFSDPride https://t.co/d58y7YJVYQ]]></document></documents></author>