<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Boeheim has GREAT instincts in this zone. I think that's a big reason he's playing as much as the threes are helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other shoe companies are so relieved they don’t have a deal with Duke right now. They’re gonna be chomping at the b… https://t.co/dAQKItztID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philadelphia Basketball Black Hall of Fame Class of ‘19 and past recipients https://t.co/Ii58CHa4pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDarling_Author You are totally sandwiched between the monster generations. https://t.co/6hCyyHZxw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDavidHood First thing I’ve covered in a while, figured I better while the Doctors still let me!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrbnHandicapper I press like on bunch of shit not your place to tell what to do your NOT my mother bro🤷‍♂️ just li… https://t.co/4JNOtKhzzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could make an entire Before Sunrise-style indie feature about a couple that meets, falls in love, and breaks up… https://t.co/2f3PkPPvI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madtweetfuckyou @JasonSinger Also it’s free, but the computer component that the TM uses is like 12 dollars one time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders  You have  millions of dollars , help the students out Grandpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening night was great!  Great job to these Horizon Middle School kids! Way to go Karena! Three shows left so get… https://t.co/ye7adUio91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldTakesExposed @CrazyFanTakes I think you mean @CrazyFreezingHotOpions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenlefforge I’m literally doing that right now this second 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 That’s amazing! https://t.co/NG2ZQo6KFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takes a year off from hockey in 7th grade, had fun skating everyday in backyard. #nohurriesnoworries]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I love making friends with other bands cus they know the struggle fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[5AM flight face. #tired @ Norfolk International Airport https://t.co/te9ETl9uCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bama_katie @bodoyle @DrB_baseball Even more than just the time away he has had to change his mechanics as well. He… https://t.co/it1JkfQN1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @RinglingBros do you have that large human sized cannon available? Need to shoot myself into the sun thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AUKEYofficial #Aukey #Giveaway @rinconpointsurf @playdreamthink @SBAirman1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeweljk you’re such an awesome singer. Watching a vid about one of your albums gave me such a nostalgia trip on al… https://t.co/uu89BkbR8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekevinryder @kevinandbean @kroq I feel like the classic “hot” probably pairs well with dog while “fire” may mask… https://t.co/863qP2PQV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirenspear @StefanMolyneux @AlexMLeo Dude if you're idea of winning an argument is calling someone stupid in a myr… https://t.co/8powNGKQCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to walk down 4 flights of stairs after doing leg day with Megan https://t.co/3D6QW7PsvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 years later there is no P.A.T. Only Alexa, Google, Siri... #DrunkPete https://t.co/b4xalwZDNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviWoolf You have a platform? I cannot imagine @Ricochet not at least taking your call.  @ScottImmergut @rcbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easter Candy from the 12th Dimension.    Ray Sipe https://t.co/ELHjCVyMNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RotoGut That’s awesome value. Puig is in such a great spot but I’m starting to think people are forgetting Correa is 24.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sponsor needed: Our blind soccer team is developing quickly but we need some support with training and uniform cost… https://t.co/7hDtDwHBAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C2cunningham @shervin @aripap @hoomanradfar I am responsible for 1.3k of the views]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddogcw Hey Julie, sorry for the delay, cell signal took a long time to reach me thru all these feets of snow :).… https://t.co/S2uMpbcgij]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Schwenkler (@floridastate) finds evidence that we employ two concepts of ‘same person’.  - numerical: eg, S is… https://t.co/iE72lZslDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#patriots #Pats #patsnation #patriotsnation #newenglandpatriots #newengland @ United States https://t.co/68DUSLkHXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would pile drive Mitch McConnell all the way through the ground to China]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 1562 Cedar Creek Pkwy #Grafton #WI  #realestate https://t.co/Cs5lLqzuFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffalobillspop @masterspenceiam @Dragons_Quest @PTPJacob Hey there. If u don't care, maybe go fly a kite or something cool. Ttyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FB_FilmAnalysis I think it’s near 18-20 million... Which doesn’t make any sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @Acosta Jim not only is she better looking than you she's also smarter than you of course that's not… https://t.co/SKuP5E5bVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caroljsroth I owned every Rubber WWF wrestler and the ring. I’d lock myself in my bedroom for hours running wrestlemania.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump blaming democrats for his failure in Vietnam is nothing unusual for trump to do.. P… https://t.co/Zv9eT4O7wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drvox Evidence ?   Or is that something just too inconvenient for Voxers ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im workin on big things Im taking a big step forward and it’s a blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 No One's Gonna Love You by The S.O.S. Band on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/wK6VUS6s6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz @HowardSchultz I have a daily talk radio show in Houston on @iHeartRadio’s @KPRCradio. Would love to… https://t.co/rsfhNEcCWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Captainswoop1 @Cern_lXXl @sygarte The Roman gov under Constantine made Christianity legal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeTalkShow This guy, major dufus! Dont forget that we in Massachusetts have that other dillweed Ed Markey too. Good grief!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are using Capehart road heading into @Offutt_AFB bring your patience. Traffic is backed up past 27th street.… https://t.co/vH5aGAPuFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a jam packed @TheDevilsDen Podcast tonight with John, myself and the always 5 star host @DukeForum putting us t… https://t.co/Clro7pccq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennyhamlin @NASCAR @FedEx @JoeGibbsRacing Congrats man, what an awesome day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a nice 75 degree day with a chance of afternoon rain. Playing 18 holes at the beautiful Jacaranda West in Veni… https://t.co/5xH6jZCCn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said the day after he signed with LA he didn’t go there for basketball. He retired and moved to LA. That’s it]]></document><document><![CDATA[youth ministry room ideas | You have heard of the game Hungry Hungry Hippos – Right?... https://t.co/GNHGFbGfoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaZ143 @CBSThisMorning @PaulaReidCBS I think he is a standup guy.   I’d let him handle my portfolio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be the water   Special of the day:  first 5 Houston calls  4 case count (96 bottles)  16.9 oz 's of our famou… https://t.co/DkPREl3DBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE SHOW. On the latest Pacific Rim, Fumi and I talk what could be Will Opreay's breakout year, King Kong Bundy in… https://t.co/IvZp6v9bH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Roses followers! We're at The Main Event for the weekend, up 8-1 on @GirlsForge at the moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Lindsey is a craven piece of shit dying for Daddy Trumps approval....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/HfhN5n5aOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well after it's all said and done we have travelled over 16000 kms by air and ground. It was all so worth it to see… https://t.co/EOogbcO1CK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedsHood God I'd love to taste that pussy while you suck on the lollipop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam1NEWski @CoachCBlack @JUCOadvocate We might need to make this happen Brandon @JUCOadvocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stan Lee’s &lt;i&gt;Captain Marvel &lt;/i&gt;cameo raises a lot of questions https://t.co/2TJdWUtCCn via @AV_Newswire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews I am saying you've been on a tear lately being outraged by stuff liberals do...that not only liberals d… https://t.co/qv2Z15yBZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epchihuahuas What a great looking ballpark, need to get down there where it’s warm!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, it looks like a thunderstorm was brewing over the city this afternoon! There’s plenty more where this rain cam… https://t.co/j3S38Ifp8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, in WASH’s final mid-credit shot, we show our love for THE CHANGELING again. &lt;cont&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulietteLewis ALL RIGHT ALREADY!! I can take a hint.. I'll host the friggin thing..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @GBBurris with get_repost ・・・ Love. Forgive.  #love #loveyourself #divine #connected #grounded #centered… https://t.co/15JurqOGqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[summer, etc. . . . #knoxville #knoxvilletn #knoxvilletennessee #knox #knoxrocks #tennesseelife #tennessee… https://t.co/AfZRYlMJNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to see the overreactions to the Celtics drilling the Warriors late last night...🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet 25 dollars on 5 random NBA teams to win tonight and just won 200 dollars. Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelKudis @MrSamsonite2 @northsidenotch @theangryfan It’s a forgone conclusion they’re not doing anything. Checkers/chess]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just donated to the Eagles Autism Challenge 2019.  Go to https://t.co/hlqW1h7XDt # via @hakuapp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipwattsinterp @JosephusD @thecjpearson @neeratanden @RuChiOhu What? Did you graduate high school?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeIsaac It was meant as one, sort of. But you should all seriously subscribe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sale happening now! BOGO 40% off.    #hairbyangel #davines #661hair https://t.co/qRIvGwxcG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabriellaCIA13 technically, but in no way do any numbers show him being “inconsistent”. He had a .267 AVG,391 OBP,… https://t.co/FUaoCD7hsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyandreasen My life is pretty public. You're welcome to read: Timeless Learning: How Imagination, Observation,… https://t.co/6KRsd0l8T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigbird_fgc But my favorite restaurants are Little Shop and Kikanbo 🤷🏻‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF I GET ANOTHER MF 2nd PLACE ASS GAME.... 🥴🥴🥴fuck FortNite I had 10 bodies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not really. He has always given his honest opinion when asked about him. If he don't think the nigga is as good as… https://t.co/iRcT334eei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberLeeNews @womensday @CBSLA @SharonTay888 @Patharveynews @CBSLAKristine @EvelynTaft @AlexBistonTV @CBSLAsuzie Wow!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Siri. Now I’m really confident you’ll wake me up on time. https://t.co/sIvrTk7tlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseytennison1 Was interesting to overhear though. He told the PA that I should improve once that is cleared. I gu… https://t.co/752lylQko6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Penske @Blaney @Menards Get @Blaney a Hot dog from the #6 team for next pit stop..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jumbo747pilot @GrSMiller I’m still putting my money on availability bias. The type of local carrier doing a route… https://t.co/M0oyA8PGZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting that the Lakers lost to the Suns and the world explodes and everyone bashes Lebron but no one said a pe… https://t.co/w9MziC6rMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon Not smiling, but impressed that you are not either and show deeper character that way...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just here to say .... go to my edits page and get one . fr . @A1_Edits]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sorry, I gotta boyfriend”   First of all, i know your boyfriend... you single. Trust me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So deeply sad to read this. #mentalhealth does not discriminate. https://t.co/Z55YwREvMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of REALLY GOOD GIRLS teams in the SoCal section man. I was sleeping on the girls game for a long time but I’m… https://t.co/m9962AoJLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cumpliendo con mi salud en Palms of Doral Apartments https://t.co/eA35wjLBjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson @DonaldJTrumpJr @AOC Ok well @AOC doesn’t support authoritarian socialism. Meanwhile you support Trum… https://t.co/0hblQ1dQwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS Listen to Ken Dulin and Vote #Trump2020  Impeach the #CrackBabies of #Congress #BigTeeth, #BigEyes,… https://t.co/9zzUB4EOuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let him try it na,somebori that will be a guest of @officialEFCC after he comes out of that his office]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mmikayla3Smith I’m just ready for real college.. you got a whole other problem lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[until people get mad for being upfront, like would you rather me waste ya time?😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedro Munhoz d. Cody Garbrandt via KO (punch) at 4:52 of the first round #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Golini at 16:50 of the 2nd period 4-0 St A WICE. @Golinik3 @susan_golini]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BOestriecher @WWE The whole Bullet Club/Japan connection AJ has with the AEW crowd makes it even more interesting.… https://t.co/6ASfCtYPt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaDsays Same lunch!  With hummus!  I’m on Altoid #12. https://t.co/elXCVogFMN]]></document></documents></author>