<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Emeraldireland1 Thanks for the heads up! I’ve gotten it in a couple of messages in the last few days but I never c… https://t.co/KbwJd5x1F0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALCOHOL IS A VERY EFFECTIVE SOLVENT   Alcohol will remove sanity, freedom and spouses' relationships.   It will rem… https://t.co/EMcPxkd2Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who?!? Him? The one the camera’s pointing to? #LivePD https://t.co/kI5iYjei8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BA_1225BA @NancySinatra @BetteMidler I particularly enjoy the way Bette expresses herself. I love her spirit. She almost seems unworldly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Just finished watching this @PeteButtigieg and I’m impressed. Love to see someone my age share my values on a… https://t.co/j9NroznF1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow @US1035 well if they need help... https://t.co/tDSb4KKaZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amijstevens @ctsman8 @AnndeRoo @DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump We have a REPUBLIC, NOT a democracy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When producers sample some out there shit,&amp; not the usual popular recycled samples &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimBourret I want my seat next to you after we light a candle in the grotto for our Dads!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s about relationships. An activity: “Write down all of the students in your class. Who did you miss?”… https://t.co/yAOqwgtmDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is a new pension system on the way for Kentucky? A bill filed by a former school superintendent and co-sponsored by… https://t.co/8cD2V5SSdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders A PROVEN CROWARD AS A LEADER ? NO THANKS  JUST LOOK AT LAST RACE HIS OWN PARTY SOLD HIM SHORT ( SCAM… https://t.co/KUFI93BOrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude came up to me and asked if I wanted to catch snowflakes and I had to have him repeat it three times bc im… https://t.co/WzhV75ayIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t do shit on there own I need a new job ASAP because imma end up cussing somebody tf out]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of guys are going to be in shock on Instagram today when they see that the hot girl they’ve been following fo… https://t.co/olMw34Hp0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 years later, and I still can’t over the fact that I tripped and fell in my sisters wedding. Lo peor de todo es q… https://t.co/bj7Hh4uvre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laitonsdad @RFERL Even China too, so you tell me, you’ll like war?? Don’t you know you have to work with your enem… https://t.co/I1Uri6XWmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this sampling from our district’s PLC Showcase last Friday led by each campus leadership team. Great reso… https://t.co/4bgr1cA5Fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbara51270280 @OregonDOT And less than 12 hours later there’s another mess near Cascade Locks with the Interstate closed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've seen so many people get engaged or married after dating them for 2 or 3 months. Like what?! Please don't propo… https://t.co/7OskUTH4bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so #grateful and excited to be a part of this amazing group! If you are struggling, don’t withdraw from your tr… https://t.co/h8i0QGVuSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1120Eclipse @FibromyalgiaWa3 @AmyCurt52463119 @Waybeyondempty2 @Hawkins65S @MartinG8177 @debsteele75 @PajamaDaze… https://t.co/VthKBjDLcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always tell me that I don’t act like a twin 😭😭 like what does that mean ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard4127 @tripprrr @Richard65049965 @nerdyplumber @onearmmofo @deafheaven ChillMaxing Here Keeping It Climate C… https://t.co/LFqJ3k9N72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this app. And that the world is adding more people dedicated to becoming more self-aware and conscious. It is… https://t.co/Lg58m98xvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @energyhill for highlighting me for #EducationalTechnology this month. #ShowcaseSchool #MIEExpert #ISTE… https://t.co/np8SfwZRux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down goes Purdue! Whattup Gophers!  Saturday is going to be VERY interesting 🏀〽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear New York,  I’ll never get over you. 🖤  #fbf #ifellinloveagain #hisnameis #NewYork #thecitythatneversleeps… https://t.co/F5u5mdOC22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vypehouston @abc13sports @sahvir_ @Bonkemaring @livelikecalvin @Justaballer_ @coreydnickerson @ZarzuelaJesse… https://t.co/QP4KevmVuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am meeting with my surgeon affiliated with Mount Sinai next week to discuss surgery, insurance, scheduling and so… https://t.co/L6oQD8jPJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tithenai @larazontally I had to write Play 21 and was uninspired! (I did end up calling the characters Millie and Devon, though.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @sjearthquakes for hosting us!!! We had a great time!   @CowellCade and Sophia Jones Thank your for the a… https://t.co/h9BgPnmm0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patsajak @benshapiro I rarely look forward to any new films.  I’m offended by the behavior of most of Hollywood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerifyThis i you to be a waitress, I personally don’t like this application, it put me in a strange position..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WayBackWednesday to my very first TV role on the CBS primetime series, Without a Trace.  Opposite @poppymontgomery… https://t.co/HcJ5QavkSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Road   “Why did you take  the hard road?” was the question  they always asked.  And although she  tried her bes… https://t.co/RfPUV3o1l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Nev1 @riotwomennn @randreynolds Do you apply that to Melania Trump also?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeStredney @Kimbers05 So you're the one who took the last copy at my store! 😜 I'm ordering it from Barnes and N… https://t.co/3xXKRDIoEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Georgie who are you? Never heard of you, but Trump is the best president we have had in years. Obama was the worst.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefoliver Fun fact for you Chief- I went to Kindergarten and First grade in Ohio. We lived in Reynoldsburg and C… https://t.co/ie4w2my0x6]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you do not know how to handle a crisis, you are not fit to govern because that's what governing is about.  https://t.co/zzSrgD53zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyG56 @NEArlyiLLEGAL It will happen in 2019. I’m putting it into the universe now💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mslinnie325 @JayInslee I wasn’t saddened to see all the visible pollution in Vietnam last week. 😳 How about starti… https://t.co/qGjQNSWMf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTimeTravell3 @FaustianNation @goodtroubleme @Corbinburnsin @master_deli @BettieRose100 @_Spike27_ @katiD22… https://t.co/OjKGrtBaeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendy4SD @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Get ready to build your share of the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I HAVE NEVER FELT THE S.T.E.M. MALE:FEMALE POPULATION RATIO HARDER THAN NOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper: What is Ivanka's expertise in anything? - CNN Video https://t.co/j5ArmY26sb  Money laundering, fra… https://t.co/F286lQt1a2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jen_Royle I don't think anybody wants me cooking for them any time soon, but I sure could eat your cooking every single day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boygeorge...where are you love?...ok I guess I'll try later see if you're on💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[The LORD says, "Then I will heal you of your faithlessness; my love will know no bounds, for my anger will be gone… https://t.co/h4dLDOYEqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJKGRADY_JC i wasn’t playing but being in the next mix lmaoo just give me a button to push 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn... my ex did this and I was shocked when he cheated? The signs were there, man 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll know you’ve changed when I see you’ve changed, not just if you tell me you’ve changed.... #actionsspeaklouderthanwords]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dog sitting and he is so cute I couldn’t leave him alone so I brought him back to my house 🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/BimZzChbyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick with like the worst cold and needed to get out of the house so me and the bf went on an adventure in the w… https://t.co/JUxCf8tdOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love love the BIba Earrings, they are so fashionably unique and gorgeous. Available at https://t.co/dPJYvxNAwu… https://t.co/UYDN5PHZHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTBone @StephMillerShow that is true steph must be drinking about robert kraft and r kelly all trump friends… https://t.co/5g7N5fneN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to win tickets to @festivaltortuga! @MalibuRumUS #MalibuRum https://t.co/5bY12r1rz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in Epcot before work is so hard. Like can I just stay here all day please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody told me I was gone be old and ugly at 60...BLASPHEMY!!! I WILL BE ANGELA BASSET! FU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga and Fiancé Christian Carino End Engagement https://t.co/dwpHP3Cwfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonlwest89 She said “I’m still wearing my ring” and “it ain’t going anywhere” 👀💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is my bedroom always the coldest in any apartment I live in? My vents are not covered and the rest of the house is warm except my room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtf is this true @ICEgov @DHSgov @CIA @FBI because look ik not into freaky fake news @Ranger_Up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larryowenslive imma be there until March 4th, would love to see you on a show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ever I end up reading marvel comics I end up with “anybody have a map” in the back of my head. Everything does… https://t.co/yVPBcyyw5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemma had her birthday dinner last night. I really think she enjoyed it 🐶♥️😂 #roastbeefsandwich #fries #thanksdaddy… https://t.co/vvxq8zPPwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean. It’s like he’s in my head at all times. Let me introduce you to my publicist and lawyer:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to attend morning tutoring on Wednesday’s and Friday’s in my classroom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blerg_Macklin @NickSwardson @pattonoswalt @MattOswaltVA Ferris Bueller would have gotten caught by his parents bef… https://t.co/nEH82Umf9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefDTevepaugh Happy Birthday buddy, I hope you enjoy your cake!!! https://t.co/d8z0LlN1GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! The DI tournament would not be possible without the hard work amazing appraisers and volunteers.  Thank you to… https://t.co/bQB1Z8vFGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLELnetwork @ELnetworkSDCOE @DLeNM @OCDEProjectGLAD @SanDiegoCOE @DLE_SDSU @r_simaan @CABEBEBILINGUAL… https://t.co/Q0h8Oecvap]]></document><document><![CDATA[A full recap of last weekend’s work.  _____________________ #wine #vino #winestagram #instawine #winegeek #winenerd… https://t.co/rYme5zYluf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @adamlevine what are the chances you have more influence and would help Searcy AR win The Small Business Revolu… https://t.co/Ks3uyKTeTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSavickas Just write a blog post...this thread defeats the purpose of twitter and you should be summarily executed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day I did such a good wet willie that I said it deserved to be called a wet William and I’m still laughing about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @JedSimon7 @GroveKilosdad73 @realDonaldTrump I love when you shut them down with the obvious... makes me giddy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re also taking programming lessons this summer. i love this for us. ❤️🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnAFraser @CraigBennett3 Ask her to DM her email to me and I'll introduce her to someone in London that can help… https://t.co/dnc46Ju1Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih Misty Copeland, Michelle Obama, Harriet Tubman, Viola Desmond, Serena Williams, Beyoncé, Alicia Key… https://t.co/ndm49Z9JHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsboys - Greatness Of Our God (Official Lyric Video) https://t.co/svbKFkLyky via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItzKap #ItsKap600 @YungCfour @ Plantation, Florida https://t.co/COJDIsCOqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies... can we please stop calling each other bitches casually.   Cuz I’m not your casual bitch... and neither are you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGT Stop editing people's songs!! There was much more to that song @jackieevancho did from West Side Story. You bu… https://t.co/9VdozIsXSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you hate when you get prepared for a FT date and then they say they’re busy 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[PB&amp;J burger (peanut butter, bacon jam) with sweet potato fries from mojos_dyersburg 🍔 | #burger #pbj #dyersburg… https://t.co/S5dcVJ0k4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Bhava_Jim This is bad. But racism is a familiar partner to @SenateDems hierarchy. They prefer to p… https://t.co/nMucU104qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[if its raining then being laid up is a need. but im not fulfilling my needs today apparently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioNovelli Que vulgares e insensibles que Dios los perdone pero si pasará y sobre ellos ya verás]]></document><document><![CDATA[College boys are so weird they’ll cat call you saying shit like “what that mouf do” then when you flick them off th… https://t.co/LYloUQ8xJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardStern was just listening to a repeat.  Richard May be right being that the GI tract runs from mouth to anus… https://t.co/OLCN1lPuFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[reuploading my crush culture cover because it got deleted :/ here it be :-)  ♡ @conangray https://t.co/TAxIv8xASr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like the friendship I ruined back in 2013 is finally healed and back to normal. Which is awesome and I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu até contaria uma das minhas varias idas à diretoria da escola mas vcs iam achar que é fic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRASHY DIANE REED PEABODY BETTER GET IT THROUGH HER SLUTTY HEAD THAT JEFF PEABODY IS NOT ENTITLED TO ANYTHING OF MI… https://t.co/GUZr27rHTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kotagreek I was already emotional for some reason and then seeing u freaked out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremynewberger Sure Sarah...keeping on saying that claptrap doesn’t make it true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanstead2000 Good afternoon Susan. Just about ready to leave for the hair salon. Hope you have a most wonderful… https://t.co/YiqJgyGCmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZR550rider @CompersionJane @KymberlyPlaydon @Sparki777 @kenziebeck23 @WildChild69 @LandorMelanie @cheomitII… https://t.co/qQWcwUib7G]]></document></documents></author>