<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@softvillainy @sailorbee Is it because of this?😆 https://t.co/wwlcAM7iG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonHubbell2 @GRAAmerica @Gunalizer Wouldn't checking FFL  the job of the BATF?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no fear in love; instead, perfect love drives out fear, because fear involves punishment. So the one who f… https://t.co/5l5I06ae72]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You don’t get to choose what kids remember what you said, or didn’t say to them” - via @CTGProjectHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaja jajajaj… https://t.co/WPKqQSfwf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN When are you going to China, Iran, North Korea, South Korea,Japan so on and so on to get them on board. Un… https://t.co/iuwGIpvf3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Improve your Lat/Tricep Mobility 👇🏼  If you have trouble in an overhead position when it is loaded you may be lacki… https://t.co/fyJym43W1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice with Judge Jeanine tonight's Opening Statement was clear on how Rep. Pelosi watered down the Anti-Semitic c… https://t.co/4Jj1Yo0TyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 yr old hitting finger rolls like that??? He already a walking bucket!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_new_kid_04 It’s the same pattern, solid first half, crumble in the second. Maybe next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump More dishonest fart tweets from Ronna.  Trump inherited the economy just like his w… https://t.co/cYiuVKkvTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[One night romance, futari. #NowPlaying #jpop One Night Romance by Koda Kumi on Apple Music. https://t.co/uKPo6R0Xik]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @TrueKofi wins #wwe world title he will be a triple crown champion @wwe #raw]]></document><document><![CDATA[just to let you know if you think you wearing a silky 95% chance its not a silky]]></document><document><![CDATA[People complaining about how un-PC last night's episode of #DragRace was, but they keep forgetting they're DRAG QUE… https://t.co/S9KnxxSsHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of seeing people’s Management post for them. 6IXNINE CHILL 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ I'm sure tmz look forward to that being the case.put that in your bag of manufacturing news,I thick it's all fill up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vgr Getting lost at sea and stumbling upon a hidden island (Utopia, New Atlantis).  Animal magnetism / suspended a… https://t.co/JRAgzAA2cW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiemmash Not a chance Habs 3-0 up after 15 ! Hope my flight from Montreal is delayed so I can watch the whole ga… https://t.co/C9HuCjRnax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a stop at the delicious @jubalacoffee yesterday! Still hands down one of my favorites! #mocha #latteart… https://t.co/ueWQNwKJkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claybwells10 @GAFolIowers https://t.co/zDGvi5nj8x  How many examples you need? It doesn’t matter if you comply, th… https://t.co/Wn8uo4sYbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concert tonight at 7:30! Livestream link in bio! @ The Crane School of Music https://t.co/Tx68SZLz0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot &amp; edited by me for @CreezLord  Let me know what you guys think https://t.co/Zl4m56m6wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GioWFAN Are you stupid or just sloppy raiders $80 million of cap space]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike customs out here. One of my fav purchases. https://t.co/iT9F7jl4kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy’s Little Man 🐾   #bff #dogdays #golden @ West Hollywood, California https://t.co/bqnfIQQInT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close fight so far, i have it 20-18 Rothwell going into 3rd but easily could be 19-19 #UFCWichita]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even tho I done watched all his standup . Shordie was watchin his shit last night and that shit had me in teaaaaaars]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you hit the game winner in beer pong and your homies are hyping you up https://t.co/JisSClP0K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gizzelle rocking it at the @EvolveIP Orange Carpet Experience talking about their Journey!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ_TacoJack @NRA @mschlapp @HeyTammyBruce It was the law in Tombstone, he swore to uphold the law, Appeals Courts… https://t.co/ap8ZHVtEfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminiscing about my times hanging with jeopardy host Alex Trebek, this morning on the @fox61news . A long time ido… https://t.co/x4hMNsmEop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestG0ATRussell If things go the way i suspect, Ballmer will grease the wheels and the Sodo arena will get built.… https://t.co/4Tn2tOwnKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhateverNeverm9 @allgood_pat @IntoTheUnknow14 @faweisser @magi_jay @agraybee 40+ new Den congreemen/women. I bet t… https://t.co/9Z3Y18XR8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone from the @EmpireFOX crew or staff needs to tell @JussieSmollett to tell the truth. For the sake of those wh… https://t.co/Bk5msLiCIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[😎 "Ain't nothin' but a gangsta (DJ) party" 😎 #DJ #DJs #DJing #djlife #mixdj #scratchdj #partydj #clubdj #alldjs https://t.co/YKgeVonO63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmMeDR @BetteMidler Maybe she’s not free? It is unusual but if it’s Bette than so be it! Haven’t seen her since Dolly closed on Broadway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is the worst when laying and bed and your holding your phone and drop it and hits you in the face 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day, everyone. Love from Paul and Dona! @ Laurel, Maryland https://t.co/ujU0kcXxtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melli_fluous Congratulations and I am proud of you and I knew it and I love you. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating the best cheeseburgers in the world at Skip's in Winchester with @StephDedmon  If you need a second opinion, ask @ElizMillsaps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what we are building at San Diego Tech Hub. It's about changing the narrative about the tech and innovation co… https://t.co/6ey3aeTzlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the @swampscottdems for inviting me to speak at their meeting last night. Really enjoyed the interesti… https://t.co/ZIsMtE4rBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerfully clear this past week how God is moving through @TroyPage to reach Mississippi and the nations!… https://t.co/pP2K2heMm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pompouspablo My boy and I after a long night on the town https://t.co/9GP4Yn3oYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDsTake Glad to see Cornelius getting looks from Penn State! His high school coach played at Penn State and was a… https://t.co/ffvJhDO7zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anthonytoler03 @SeanPrimetime21 It doesn’t really make a huge difference. In the first round you basically choose… https://t.co/4g6JJS6Jto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorCFord @CountOnZach Facts but 2k12 changed the game with Create a Legend Mode. They need to bring that back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyDogJ1 @cltobinstlfd @PettyZ93 @rwalsh532 @YVFD12 Perhaps some other verbiage in the arrival report to make ot… https://t.co/UH2QHCtfvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlostpa10 @TampaBayRowdies @MNUFC Did you make payoffs last year? 🎶rowdies tell  me how it feels......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier accident in #WakeCounty on US 1 - Capital Blvd at Old Wake Forest Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is interesting that those from previous administrations that failed in dealing with NOKO are the same “political… https://t.co/IGg5d0bP9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[You in the FriendZone because your not toxic enough. ( This Spoke Volumes )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ AliRKhataw thank you for sharing your inspirational story and for your beautiful living example of what it means… https://t.co/QWsJorwhVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grufftech Ever since I got to Austin, I’ve been spoiled with Google Fiber. 950MBs Up/Down has been the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davisleighlaura &amp; I will ace our tests tomorrow. Speaking it into existence!! https://t.co/i0Qee1UCEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HabimanaPax @TerrellChuggs @_YoungCR7 @Varadarajan111 Oh, oh he's up on the .... We've never seen anything... OH MY LORD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Willwineguy @randycorporon So that means blowing off U.S. intelligence assessments and taking Putin at his word is… https://t.co/53eTJIppbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinzeeBlend yeah i know! I’m right in the middle of it and my internet just stopped working😐🙄 i was like what! NO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturdays are for education.  Pass the M, please 😜🥃 . . . . . . #themacallan #macallan #makethecall #whisky #scotch… https://t.co/KwPbAc84RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @1k_kilgore Love the @IDF tee. Wouldn’t mind having one myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow at 10 AM this is going to happen.  Don’t miss the bombing of Ajax peak!  One of the coolest things to ever… https://t.co/1yPjaq8a49]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the Spirit of Kentucky Exhibit @FrazierMuseum with @AndyTreinen this morning! It’s $5 February— come b… https://t.co/1ZjSnwIKV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elezzy @MuseZack @lcshorten Yeah he did. Im at least gonna give it four or five eps. His inclusion alone is worth that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a couple sit ups and I want to throw up. Am I really this out of shape? Damn.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professor: Kevin can you tell the class the facts of the case?  Me: Actually the United States isn’t a Democracy. T… https://t.co/Jz4OXImDwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimjack0927 @TDavenport_NFL Jrob always reaches. He should take best player available regardless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amp0630 @DianaLopezRami1 ¡WEY! Yo si las guardo JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA https://t.co/keif5noPou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generosity assists those in need and announces God's love @RHWashmo  #BasicMath]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimWatsonOttawa why is the City penalizing good samaritans who are doing the right thing by helping those followin… https://t.co/VXe0zvuUSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesush1979 @CrazySciTeach @DavidENorman @chonito928 I think the bigger problem is getting snow in the California desert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kurtis Pelletier ties the game at one for Lewiston #mesports #VarsityMaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmedicineMI @EmeraldZoo @Cogitatorium @cannaworldsite @AlexisBortell @renegadestyle @HTGMichigan @operator55_11… https://t.co/9aZFHixWNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Founders Day! #PennState is the 164 yrs old today (and the future is bright!)   Here is fun link with picture… https://t.co/X7ByKxyVgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hutchinson_84 @ArmyStrongTDaly My mediation is that Patrick Mahomes may likely be the second coming of our lord an… https://t.co/UISXLiGppo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Ilhan for your inexhaustible fight to expose the truth about people like Elliott Abrams and other archit… https://t.co/GWsjPRtwyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker must be about to drop something huge with this smear campaign going on. You learn to memorize the patterns.… https://t.co/FdRX29mWYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found on a wall of sequins. Atlanta loves @IAmMoniqueHeart !!! https://t.co/QMjuG2a4hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@commanderzoink @SuperMeatBoy Kind of a bummer to call her out so she gets attacked on twitter. A fan expressing di… https://t.co/W2Z88VJujs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickpearl3 @TheWeirdWorld https://t.co/lebeTxaIDh how it be sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my dawg @SpaceGGhost Show Some Love to the shooter. Love ya Mane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Book is really a Dance’s with wolves level of horrible Oscar win wow  It’s worst than Crash that year was not… https://t.co/L49QVcxpdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @TrumpTurnberry @TrumpGolf I can’t wait to see how you look in prison stripes]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BernieSoBlack shows the Democrats are the real racists, by racial profiling, just like wearing blackface.… https://t.co/cxc6c7mfsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirportBrothers Land an hour and 15 minutes late, but the good folks @Delta and @DeltaAssist decided to have a pla… https://t.co/7HgzrE6Dp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SturgisSports @thiespiegel @Gmwtiger2_Greg @AOC The left is not loosing you because they want to take your money,… https://t.co/vh8W3D9vUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbh39 Also the league needs a team that has a fanbase that will travel like UK does in the SECT.  Arkansas was abl… https://t.co/k8v5rgSXUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a snippet of what's happening this very moment at Gideon Elementary's Black History Show #phled… https://t.co/GtzcWPdQf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Ball is here!! The #DriveFor5 starts today! #GoGuins https://t.co/RoNHsN4777]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBulldog_Hockey Hey those lights look familiar...😏congrats ‘dogs it was an honor to tour STP with you. Best of luck at The Tourney!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never too late, I was in my 30s  before I realized what I really wanted to do with my life, and even at that point,… https://t.co/aDMU7fD9Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleRguez @panekbill Are you laughing in Envy, cause if not, we are gonna have issues!!😱😱😱😂🤣😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[More coaches should be held accountable for not reporting pitch counts within the allotted time frame established b… https://t.co/7LbE79LPe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports He’s full court pressing kids way less athletic than him to run up the score. He’s not above getting screened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times do I have to tell you people, stop telling everyone about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My face says it all,  new toys at the fitness center... and they are brutal!  Awesome upper and lower body workout… https://t.co/KevZReH5Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky came into this game with their big boy pants on ready to play some physical basketball. First game I’ve se… https://t.co/tZZTCC6DOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSBoston @NBCSCeltics @ChrisForsberg_ I’m confused. How much more swag can he give. He dropped 37 and the bench… https://t.co/wIWG9oUHS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#outnow‼️ #insta #quantum #vegan #veganfood #veganrecipes #veganuary #veganos #veganismo #veg #vegetarianrecipes sa… https://t.co/i4sJI3APJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t think I will ever be able to listen to a Michael Jackson song the same way again....]]></document></documents></author>