<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Rainbow Cheese Board for Kids https://t.co/dU63QI7qgi via @raisingwhasians]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1234Carc @rgalante @saammm011 Give Carly Jax and sonny can take Kim 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#24feb #Caracas Gran Concierto por la Paz, la Solidaridad y contra el Imperialismo! | Salsa, música urbana, trova,… https://t.co/2yineUswqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @AliMarvin3 trying to justify ourselves after getting tattoos of Jonah hill and Michael Cera on our ankles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorinnaKopf This is how I feel about @MileyCyrus at the moment https://t.co/0t4Kmy9WsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I go way out of my way for people who wouldn't do the same is the thing I hate most about myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is like he wears teflon..nothing sticks or brings him down  He looks pretty confident to me these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more cars horse and buggies are making a comeback . No meat and fmtravel now across seas because planes will be… https://t.co/AUVvI34WfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:03 am me despiertan ruiditos de pajaritos, me levanto, veo mi cel y apagado, se me había descargado por eso no so… https://t.co/6QwykqUv6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Está hora está súper rara, mientras unos apenas  van llegando a sus casas a dormir otros ya están saliendo a hacer ejercicio]]></document><document><![CDATA[No! Not @JamieLucke too! You will be missed by Lex and KY, and especially by me. Thank you for everything. ❤ https://t.co/pmjlNW7VQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops, Laurie may I two more patriotic faves to Laurie Boat. Appreciate it.💛💜💙💙 @jrdel42  @OldcorpsGrunt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Shut up you spoiled rotten celebrity. You have no idea what it is like. You have a… https://t.co/5f9rxiaDkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been talking a lot of shit but nothing makes me giddier than JetBlue’s “if New York is home for you, welcome home”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to be typing this essay, but instead I’m online shopping. OOPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalEntrepreneurshipWeek!   The City of El Paso is celebrating by having free workshops for local entrep… https://t.co/Vx7UlRZNam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to the local coffee shop to focus on some tasks this morning! https://t.co/VmQrvPXXRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karn120 @DineshDSouza What Trump inherited from Obama is tons of regulations that stifled the economy. Trump nixed… https://t.co/bw4jfwqjOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I am done. I am not starting this morning as I am waddling.  And just like that my trail running career is over… https://t.co/CD8abnre6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What did you read tonight?? We just started book one of The Land of Stories series!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished Violette—15x11 gouache on paper— inspired by fashion, French style, and Paris Fashion week.  Did I mention… https://t.co/ZSH7Ah3xAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next stop....#chocolate #DUMBO @ Jacques Torres Chocolate https://t.co/ap1RcbfUH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Archer thought of the day: “Why can’t this human figure this blood sugar thing out?”  🤔🐕🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your lifestyle doesn't include enough motion, your body cannot function efficiently. #getmoving #hopechiro… https://t.co/5Nxr424ZXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PTFilm @DisneyD23 @starwars @Disneyland @WaltDisneyWorld We just got fooled]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are you gonna do a tour around Latin America we have been waiting a long time❤️🇲🇽#ColdInQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMHSCounselors MCU Symphonic will also be giving a concert immediately after. Be sure to stop by and give them a listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES!!! All is ‘write’ in the world  @mattsophos @RichardGaubert @corybarlog @theorionwalker @AdamDolin WON @WGAWest… https://t.co/ZtZgDIMXhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @Outlander_STARZ Happy to donate for #PrestonMill ! This was a fabulous stop on our #OutlanderFilming t… https://t.co/aBRXyJiScz]]></document><document><![CDATA[let this be a lesson to the rest of the NFL, stay the heck out of... https://t.co/tGPxsYuehN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third flower show in a row! #philadelphiaflowershow2019 @ Pennsylvania Convention Center - Philadelphia, PA (Philly) https://t.co/NsDmXpMiAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@full_courthoops Thank you very much Coach Cara!! I really appreciate everything &amp; I am so excited to be a Bonnie💓👩🏻‍⚕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcow82 hahahaha im soooooorry!!!! I’m dropping a trailer on Tuesday for this short film I’ve been working extra on… https://t.co/uguXO3sBF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma wit on FB all day an order everything that comes in her TL 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be strong Bebe  @hperalejo God is with you all the time and keep on praying. Kahit anong klase ang pag babash sa yo… https://t.co/u5xcwGdgfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judges couldn’t turn for black lady but that white 19 yrs old they turned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best night with these crazies @ Dog and Bull - Brew and Music House https://t.co/VLei0JUcMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreyMia @LukeSawer Almost looks like he has a little smile starting. Precious 💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t enjoy waking up before the sun and then coming home after it’s sunk.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh?! So I guess that apology/lesson learned interview with Gayle King only applied to the Governor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Akotero @CoachWallaceBU Will do Al. We all have much to be proud about you know it right! Lots good things going on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joel: “Hey Clicker, how’s life?” Clicker: “It’s pretty lit.” :’) #TLOU #tlouphotomode #PS4share https://t.co/IKvnXlijMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden you do not speak for me. I am not embarrassed by America. And you can keep that attitude right there wher… https://t.co/wtDpwv2f6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncredibleCulk My son collected lighters as a teenager, which constantly made me question him about smoking! He wa… https://t.co/CEJWszQ2x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AccessibilityPSA - I usually blur license plates, but this is an exception. This guy was using the access area - t… https://t.co/ii6bbzspK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the BEST crab cake sandwich is Chickies &amp; Pete’s bc it actually has a lot of crab in it. Okay bye good morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@017kat Who knows what you will do next week??? Be gentle with yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like cheering for @Alex_OC11 mainly because that means I’m cheering for AOC and to a civics teacher that’s the Ar… https://t.co/YFOybPKufF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother may have been born February 29th, but... I have the same birthday as Chili’s?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSpuds @ChicagoPenguin2 @RidenerTina @72cricket @BxglL @sharon_schwan @sannbs @ACog1984 @CSonafelt He has to make it interesting 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING:  #HouseIntelCommittee announced on #March6 that they are Launching an #Investigation AGAINST Self-Rigged-… https://t.co/kHAhWktnx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Yes, not a time for all that nonsense.  Time to heal.... the Bible speaks of this.  Had my time to heal… https://t.co/d1vdrC2rkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time it was Garrett and I’s one year anniversary/Valentine’s day and I decorated the inside of his locker with… https://t.co/LoJLKXF4No]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Jason! I’m loving spending a day in the Abacos Islands, for every decade of amazing that you are. Th… https://t.co/XNJvgMcl1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven Wherever I see discord, I see bots and kremlin interference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sculpin by @BallastPoint at @lilyflanagans — https://t.co/UIulPdcLw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cross your fingers and toes, and keep cheering for our Titans to make it to the final stage of NorCals! Keep fighti… https://t.co/om5TSHpiOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronecarroll Not lying, this happened to me in India and I was TRAUMATIZED. Monkeys are scary and huge carriers of disease. Watch out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZagumBhatti @CarlosGuevaraIR @baileyannRN @SIRspecialists gross looking foot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTFxG @iAintHarden "how do you not like tech nine bro he's sick" dawg just kill me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paulsy01 I wrote those tweets in January And it's all happening.We will see what happens. Talk to you again about July?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late to the party, but @MarkMeadows this is one of many examples of lasting friendship and partnership between race… https://t.co/HBBJ0Pnn4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I could watch that @ladygaga  Bradley Cooper performance over and over and over again. That’s chemistry. So ra… https://t.co/wH1l7MqQub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesley_jordan Wes your Dad will Always be with you. Please take care of you  you’ll be in my prayers 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory There are too many of these instances happening without any consequences!]]></document><document><![CDATA[have you ever swiped on tinder accidentally and then say ’oh shit I didn't mean to do that.’ and then keep swiping?… https://t.co/dQ27VRLDul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenj3nda @LaMamert4 Mi tiempo fuera de trabajo eso mío y no de la Empresa para la que trabajo. Abusar de los empleados es costumbre en 🇨🇴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton Kids grow up so fast. Especially in the spotlight kids. Or they try to act like adults anyway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn mendes having a Calvin Klein shoot is honestly a full on blessing from the gods themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be able to serve w/a staff that values loving people over performance. Gratitude over selfishness.  Affi… https://t.co/Feho45MRhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torylanez @torylanez you mean like #LOR ??🤔👀👀 by @ajrapsofficial  https://t.co/SiAvJUFdN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVENT EATEN. I HAVENT SLEPT. ONLY @MARENMORRIS. THERE IS NOTHING ELSE THAT MATTERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[is sometimes justified in business cases.  Baring Vostok asks President Vladimir Putin to intervene  The Russia-bas… https://t.co/62NHb5bWfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish i was better at letting things in my life flow and just happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gemma &amp; Remi🐶❤️ #honestkitchen #honestkitchentreats #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #lovethemback… https://t.co/sfShSzriYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirty drop! Never gets old watching it! @makaylamartin29 #29 #beast💪🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakotoKamui Incredibly clever and efficient. I used to do the same as a full time employee and artist. Just throw… https://t.co/seqYglMehA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever tried an infrared sauna at hautesaunastudio?🔥🧖🏻‍♀️Today we went live at their Shadyside location to s… https://t.co/hnJlnv4ptm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA Will he be allowed to drive there?   Does he still have a driver's license?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aswinn @katierosman Ok, I realize there are way more salacious details but also just me or is it weird to watch ro… https://t.co/0fZLrZpTgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my nurses. My staff. My people. And when I think of leaving cuz of administration, it breaks my heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMAckerman @reformanacional En 100 días hemos descubierto que MORENA y AMLO son los peor del PRI, PAN y PRD...… https://t.co/WhPvxYnGID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do whatever it takes just get him out before he starts pimping out of the W.H.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jusss a few pics of the beautiful ass Florida house me and my girls will me staying in 😭 https://t.co/udCRxy2qP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why yes, my Gravy Fulfillment is about to be met ♡ @gravylive Rustyn and mom cant wait to open it! #rustynmomma… https://t.co/1RrpiUfOkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_marr but isn’t firing people the new fundraising in higher ed https://t.co/1RRWMX3to7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @va_cc11 @GOP Yet a Congresswoman calls out a lobbyist group &amp; gets attacked like crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont grow up, Its a trap. #funniness #lol #grin #clever https://t.co/eKDttuLAqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien It is high time EVERYONE  starts calling Trump out on his pathological lies. He's a liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatTheBerner Biden gets 27%?! And Neera Tanden talks about that? That’s not credible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Icelandair - sitting on tarmac @Dulles_Airport waiting to de-ice- major delay going to miss connection to take off… https://t.co/wIwpsAt4FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo..... question.......y’all like Girls Need Love remix only because Drake is featured or you honestly think it… https://t.co/WTchVtoMVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m most definitely happy to have NASCAR back in my life (and twitter feed!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[my goal in life is to travel so much i forget what city i'm waking up in]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ my babies.   Happy National Love Your Pet Day! Register staffers share photos of their pets… https://t.co/rRyG6g1xGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "shift supervisor - Store# 05232, WEST HOLLYWOOD II"? What did you like most about th… https://t.co/0NZv7WKXbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen six.... SIX dead cats on the side of the road in the past few days. I think the world is ending]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rene_gadeCowboy @MoncayoSofi @carlyinNJ Just followed you!  😃😎 #TheResistance #FBRParty #TrumpResign #ImpeachTrump… https://t.co/xZPhwiN3s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveTorresLVDF est clairement une candidate qui a sa place à La joute sur @TVAreseau! ❤️ Sont entrée ne se fait évi… https://t.co/7GV01iPl04]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kinda naps I take should b illegal, swear I’m half dead in that bih]]></document></documents></author>