<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SeamusHughes Are we idicting Drumpf for inciting violence? If the media are the enemy of the people, isn't it the… https://t.co/9rc8UeN7ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@massmediaprof @joncoopertweets @AltNatSecAgency @SethAbramson Seriously? I guess I didn't know Manafort was an attorney!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strayalliecat Us mommies gotta stick together. Ps. I’m getting you something from your registry, just havent been able to yet. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time baby wakes up I think of the line in annie about the middle of the night. But it’s in the middle of the… https://t.co/J2RZB2rBN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLaYBoYKeNxX_2 @NellyyMichelle @NICKIMINAJ Btch YOU SIT https://t.co/7Ijejol9gW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandawinnlee You keep it up Amanda. You roasting these people is a victory at its finest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those are seconds of my life I’ll never get back, and fivolity I’ll never unsee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profcarroll "Our main finding is that the motor cortex is a flexible pattern generator, and sends rhythmic signals… https://t.co/X6pJEOnKQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@how_to_phd Yes, in a great way- like I know all those calculations, terminology, and how they apply. It’s like hearing my native language 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited that this book is getting the attention it deserves! Hooray @ktc131! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinitysir I’m about to buy the 50 shades series, you can read them when I’m done]]></document><document><![CDATA[On our first date, Kyle and I were driving down the Seawall in Galveston and he told me my eyes looked like the oce… https://t.co/4pECXf3knJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coworker and I are the last two standing from our wave and I guess he feels some type of way ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stalker will literally come in to the branch sip on his bottle of water while he dead ass stares at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan prenda* que llevaba chaqueta y el bolso colgado. Rola o no rola. Todo mal, empezando por las amigas(?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @JuliaEAinsley It's a CRISIS  that is killing Americans by murder &amp; drugs every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watching women tell all and i love @demi_burnett. YOU ARE MY FAV. You ARE a badass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snogard77 @JohnBrennan @Mark_Sheppard He cares to much that's why he's trying so hard to make sure socialism doesn't prevail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atDavidHoffman Have a relative who used similar verbiage in expressing scepticism regarding certain actual news ev… https://t.co/gtcAnau4ZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝘛𝘩𝘦 𝘚𝘢𝘯𝘤𝘵𝘶𝘢𝘳𝘺 𝘢𝘵 𝘈𝘭𝘦𝘹𝘢𝘯𝘥𝘳𝘢 𝘗𝘭𝘢𝘤𝘦, a 17-story condo tower with just 15, full-floor residences, is planned for Tampa’… https://t.co/mg8DuptNxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lazy to take off my makeup.....this is why I don't wear it every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chesamestreet said   fuck i look like thot? i look like yes and you look like https://t.co/Lom7s9wwyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably not, national media would just claim it was buried in snow or ice]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl is home and back on her throne. she's getting ready for st. Patrick's day though I did have to spray the ya… https://t.co/7h7mXM7dYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[***TRAFFIC ALERT*** One lane closed westbound on the Sawgrass Expressway. Proceed with caution. https://t.co/QKwW7kAKVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freep I saw this spider in the Forbidden Forest in Harry Potter and was told it was not real. I am not pleased.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmace30 Power play? Coming along? You sit on the throne of lies! #elfquotes #hopeyouareright]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slytherin = Jesuits - ✔️, Hufflepuff = Franciscans ✔️, Benedictines = Ravenclaw (my daughter went to Benet Academy… https://t.co/AzfUzFNGG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have so many good movies and it makes me want to stay in bed and watch movies all day w/ my sick ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elliott_Teters @ReikiTree @22kizmat @RaghavendraSura @worldwidewordly @CarlBozeman @vasumunish @_Mindmassage… https://t.co/NrrspnC2o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@va_nessa92 @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 @Tracylovestay @tarahlovestay @shurider17 @telizabethxoxo @tracesofswift… https://t.co/GEGo6vOAIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Scholar, Top Dawg AND a schloarship😳 way to go baby girl! I can’t wait to see how far you’ll go... #senioryear🎓… https://t.co/4WVdVMb4lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg_Palast Heard about this today on Thom Hartmann's show.  Apparently Kirsten Gillibrand is believing and parroting Trump on this.  Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imjair__ Yea , you almost killed everyone in the car that one day, psychopath 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@find_zoe @SMEAatUW @KHayhoe Oh and she also has this massive list of #climate scientists on Twitter, many of whom… https://t.co/d3dfXd5oVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeataol @Mimirocah1 Tha is what my mother always told me and she was always right !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s do this, bitches!” #TheCherShow ✨⁣ •⁣ •⁣ Happy birthday to my godmother, Aunt Janie! #AndTheBeatGoesOn @ Man… https://t.co/OXjqA8WBph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniieplato happy birthday steph! hope you had a great one 💓 miss you! 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepNewsTeam and @Judgenap are ready to poop there #depends! They are sooooooo giddy with excitement over ANOTHER… https://t.co/9n9ueEwRhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanieoliver More evidence that  having money is not equal to having sense, taste, or discretion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦋🦋 @DreamingEmiily you’re our winner 🦋🦋 let us know your email so we can send over the giftcard :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even Trump with his daughter when she was 13 @jaketapper they made a lot of adults feel uncomfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in San Francisco recently. The giant #Apple SFO store is actually not in that city’s famed Union Square, beca… https://t.co/x9qsLCk1rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LATlands Hi Mitchell, I'm a former AP reporter who wrote about Terence Crutcher's death in 2016 for LAT. there is… https://t.co/iwaRFpkSKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who sends someone a text at 758 on a Saturday morning? 🤦‍♀️. Noooo thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar I’d personally move Unsatisfied to number one and add Achin’ to Be and Alex Chilton.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp your banning conservative reporters who are supporting my President because #FakeNewsCNN said take her pa… https://t.co/9C0MJvCfwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beverleykendall This is when I yell, “Don’t tell me what to do!” at my wrist and then I look up to see people slowly backing away. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a challenge, but my baby girl finished strong in the 800m coming in 3rd place. https://t.co/LUHtZlHwTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be in Tucson presenting an @arizona_sos Roadshow on March 19! #SaveOurSchoolsAZ2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lookner You are suggesting order has been there??  They need to ditch the socialism and those socialist leaders, and so do we!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día de la mujer !! en San Pedro Garza García https://t.co/VJZT9pyHRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I think about it the more United need to go all out to sign Dybala, that's my transfer wish list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioAmy there ARE 5 oceans!!! Call Bobby on it! 🤣 🌊Pacific  🌊Atlantic 🌊Arctic 🌊Indian 🌊Southern https://t.co/KLQ5Dw8ONd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#firstkisses #firstkiss #yqbaba #yqspecial #yqdada #yqquotes #yqdidi #myfirstbook #sharetoshine #tellyourstory   Re… https://t.co/KILqxAXbhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlyPatterson I’m seriously obsessed with these photos! She’s gorgeous like her mommy! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppSame @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @nytimes But it's just a made up Crisis!!! Pelosi can't do her job never h… https://t.co/9JY4TZmgEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scientology @drugfreeworld Yeah another reason why everyone deserves a voice because it may not be mental illness… https://t.co/dxczgOoMPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Century Theatres - @cinemark in Huntington Beach, CA https://t.co/4L6UZA2CQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap I can’t believe this is actually happening 😍😭 @ccmfcruise @JimmieAllen @DylanScottCntry @leebrice… https://t.co/jUt55XDmGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I deal with #UMCGC2019 by going on a walk and drinking beer with my partner. #ForEveryoneBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I care for her and still love her.. no doubt about that. Just because we broke up doesn’t mean I don’t care for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Chelsea   I was born in the middle of the night  My age is literally so much  I like to go to chili’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_sassy @Yuri09067821 @ctanner3 @RodHillis1 @my3monkees @Frances_712 @Aug1405 @1GoodShepherd @misspunk63… https://t.co/zDu8xZULPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_moss2715 @whitneylacee I mean if you got a spare box of samosa I would GLADLY take it off your hands lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfreynolds @stocat1 It could have been more serious, probably not though. Most likely we'll never know the truth.… https://t.co/8sIc4UyVol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My running friends make me feel invincible and I love them and that’s all I have to say (so do my non-running buds but it’s different)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or it’s 1136pm and too lazy to stop at. InNOut so dinosaur nuggets for the win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMNWRIT1301 @Jessifer Hi there!  Just a note on accessibility!  Screen readers have a difficult time with excessiv… https://t.co/YwpnhCenZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I Film/Edit/Upload In one night?!   Yes I did because I was excited   NEW SEWING MACHINE UNBOXING -BROTHER RLX3… https://t.co/S8KRmZBMUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Kagan! Teaching instructional, cooperative and socializing skill simultaneously!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh the fact some even tweeted this , this let me know my tribe is out there somewhere..]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is on your mind at the end of this next deep breath? #whatsonyourmind #thoughts #driven #motivated #dreamer… https://t.co/FbunObMhkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[90 percent of cyber attacks happen through email.   No, that Nigerian Prince does not have $50M for you.    Be awar… https://t.co/20bSbDIyLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re going to #PrayTheRosary and mail a greeting card every day to someone. Imagine if we can bring light into som… https://t.co/jETpRA6Zcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OsteenDodie Vitamin c 3 times a day alkaline water guanabana juicy orange 🍊 too ...everything can have vitamin C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC @FoxNews @ShannonBream hope I can stop up that late!  Give me a wink Jesse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so scared for my daughter to grow up. But I’m working on building a queen...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I always wanted to know why Marcus Smart won’t get a damn chemical peel. He can afford it 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first time to Voodoo donuts! Thanks for being my Uber Tiff!! @ Voodoo Doughnut https://t.co/uxJvq4Ckgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agamanimukherj1 I don't like you I love you from afar.....I can see what a genuine person you are even if I haven't met you💋❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for sharing your experience. We are the richer for it! #NJRareDiseases2019  https://t.co/nkffPKyuRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The OMA art show was a hit! We truly have some artistic residents @ Maple Knoll Village https://t.co/OalRrXiKm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your company is interested in hosting a Valor Wednesday please email me at jen@valorbridge@org 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders You are a far left radical that supports killing the most innocent of all, unborn babies. You support t… https://t.co/DV7jIxEqZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you ask me what I came to do in this world, I, an artist, will answer you: I am here to live out loud.” -Emile… https://t.co/RJkRxC8Bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[this semester has been kicking my ass. only thing getting me through it is cabo in july 🇲🇽🍻🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhMyMithrandir uggggggh I hate the pressure on these films and the pressure on women to like them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SADIQ HARMON AGAIN!!!!!!  His last three baskets just put Putnam up 46-40!!! Two minutes left!!!! AHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so mf cute!!! I pray God blesses me w a lovable, thoughtful man]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hear this, O Job; stop and consider the wondrous works of God. https://t.co/7Y7wUM0DyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGJ72 You need this shirt if you don’t already have it. https://t.co/bo6CPiPsQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emotional Trauma and the Mind-Body Connection https://t.co/oM7bMscufc  from @WebMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my job! So exciting to see the students present their projects last week. #rusdlearns #rusdscience]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey just dropping in to say it costs $0 to respect and use someone’s correct pronouns! you can choose to not be a c… https://t.co/bwpXScG2GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omnivorebooks You’re right! I guess I don’t understand the attraction to them and their giant fake butts and vapidness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Really? How many did @barackobama declare? Your father is opening the door REALLY WIDE. I guess we should thank him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeblebroxBill  Thank you for the tRump/Russia T-Shirt 'Like', Bill! It's available at ReMonVanDeCas ~… https://t.co/xmxAP2xIOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Durante el golpe de Estado del 2002 no se le llamó “autoproclamado”, se le dijo “autojuramentado”.Pedro Carmona se… https://t.co/VxUmrzsSqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is a VERB. Love is the actions you take to make someone feel like they matter #mindfulness #selfcare #success… https://t.co/GcA54XKIxE]]></document></documents></author>