<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Cara_Mell_model @jj_junior_xxx @mplstudios Beautiful hot and sexy wowww,😚😙😁😅❤😘😍😎🤞👍👀❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 90th Anniversary Of the St. Valentines Day Massacre!!! Them bad boy gangsters are always robbing the banks of… https://t.co/PjiMVclelr]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌧 (@ San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA w/ @mbrianaepler) https://t.co/2pJOtT4qM1 https://t.co/sDNWzLLFFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericmbudd Double sidebar: I replaced it with a 4 year old MacBook Pro that I paid $1000 for. I felt my wallet phil… https://t.co/rv5KrShpbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steelerman47 @JimCarrey Just shut up and leave Jim Carrey alone, stupid Trump supporter and stupid Republican. Tru… https://t.co/EoAU5HnLQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @xrey1 @DeptofDefense @OhioBot5000 @realDonaldTrump @JebBush @GeorgeWBush__ @SecretService @StormIsUponUs… https://t.co/4ycgRdrCWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!!!! I hope you approach your week the way keem_given100 approaches everyday. With a smile and  unbelie… https://t.co/M4w29pT96E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raiders have 3 first round picks... and all they had to do was give up a 3rd and a 5th.   Now we can see why he wan… https://t.co/xJFggJ7nHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Friends,  I have been very intentional about living my purpose.   Last week I coached over 112 athletes and trut… https://t.co/fRD1oWPsGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robdelaney I’m imagining you thought of that analogy while listening to the President’s insane press conference ye… https://t.co/vFFwMVGwLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“tediously, predictably, tribally dumb” is @TedCruz going from accurately calling Trump a pathological liar, “narci… https://t.co/UTRoHqh8JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah  I admit it  I use 5-HTP 100 mg  it's @AARPCO   chill -&gt; he said it was ok -&gt; @MayorHancock]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was really great to see one of my favorite podcasts, Mac Power Users...LIVE  in Chicago tonight with special gue… https://t.co/YeEJEg75sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[if a bitch ask u yo age and she respond "oh u a baby" after u tell her she want yo dick she jus aint think u was fi… https://t.co/GgZaoG0Fkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @mamalobo @ChrisLoesch @DLoesch Well said Andrew and God Bless you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a done deal🤝 Glad to make this young gentleman and his little girl a happy mountain home!⛰🔑  . . . If you’re l… https://t.co/pKChedx3e2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They give birth astride of a grave, the light gleams an instant, then it's night once more.... Astride of a grave… https://t.co/X44cbGE2mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terannhilow You can come sit on my face anytime. An hour doesn't matter to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the best questions to ask a mortgage lender before you lock in a home loan? Find Out 》… https://t.co/uM5zrF43yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@555Kaliman @netomunro @JacoboMendozaR @ElPatoDeLucas @MaDoloresRio @alvaro_delgado @Pat_MercadoC @RoyCampos ¡Buenos días!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. I’m looking at this Nets schedule and I’m not sure if they’ll make the playoffs. Every game left is against a current playoff team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you could hide behind me, maybe for awhile. And I won’t tell no one your name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to Outsideinside by Blue Cheer - Album Reviews, Credits, and Awards - AllMusic -  https://t.co/2VK5FnUTwu The fourth listen today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s frightening to think people agree with what Mark Meadows believes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghegamin It will be great to have you back in town with us. I have gone to four churches in Tampa and loved them a… https://t.co/ouDSBVAgwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWCR13 @bogie1491 @taureanb @NOTSportsCenter the baseline includes 3 feet on either side of the foul line, at leas… https://t.co/YuNl2UhUQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: The LEGENDARY @REALSteamboat is here to show his appreciation for @RicFlairNatrBoy! #RAW… https://t.co/yaKVdP9sHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindaskindiva @nebia @NorthParkCenter Let’s ask @nebia - they are listening in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching Aero Smith Live At Donington...granted dude’s are cadaver like, 100 year old men...still put on a show though....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefanMolyneux @TheRightMelissa Of credit card companies, or backs?? Oh wait...it’s already happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkingdonuts (at @7Eleven in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/O8eCXRAoZw https://t.co/3QdMAJdKlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staying Kimpton Hotel Monaco. Lovely Portland Again... https://t.co/YP0v6E6JuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how we get average temperatures in the Midwest. One extreme to the next! #NEwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[YO! Wanna make an easy $50 bucks?  Know some one looking to be a Real Estate Agent?  Send them to me, to us, if the… https://t.co/YmTVhJK0el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsthrowbacks @MBachmann216 @Talkin_Schmidt we were here. What a night that was]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OverdriveUpdate Kind of sounds like John hill, Annette Sandberg and worst of all, Anne ferro we're wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not true you are asking that YOUR ACCUSATIONS IN THIS CASE BE SEALED and not released post YOUR COMPLETE MO… https://t.co/Tqks3krN4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWGlenda123 @DonaldJTrumpJr GED? Clearly you’re not educated enough to figure out my twitter handle 🤣🤣🤣 👻👻👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Story time #bernesmountaindog #bernersofinstagram #bernesmountaindoglovers #dogsofinstagram #bernesedaily… https://t.co/V7qXDxWS8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnettlee @BrewCityChrissy @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump At least that’s authentic Americans signature food, also… https://t.co/buggxyi7wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a difference a few days makes. Same venue. Different event. Same championship experience. @WECkzoo @usacurl… https://t.co/zg44veVzp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[434 S Fuller Ave 434 S Fuller Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/cWR2hgKvrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robvato Yes, but the initial tweet is what was unfair. Especially given your reporting, which I've always appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JustKennn Now I'm meeting a ton of Capricorns. I'm convinced nobody will ever understand or love a Capricorn like another Cap could.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calypsorising @WatchYourRepsSC @KimpsonForSC You do realize that the majority of the gains in the midterms was do… https://t.co/d1N0YbI3Z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some major communication issues here where a clearly written email early in the process could have helped… https://t.co/d8mX7cS4qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to encourage everyone especially athletes to read up on Taurine it's a chemical in the human body an amino a… https://t.co/qno1YDMPp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @RhStowell @southernwayjim @Tweets4MAGA @DanCovfefe1 @TrumpOrBust2020 @VFL2013 @DaRealGrizzle… https://t.co/2fkRhOwHWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwadelsu "I hear it all the time. I hear it a lot."  Should @LSUBasketball retire Mahmoud Abdul-Rauf's (formerly C… https://t.co/Up90Fmd6zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a stress ball, a tub of slime, and a fidget spinner in my bed rn and if that isnt indicative of my current mental state idk what is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shtemlo @AshaRangappa_ @JamesMartinSJ @Susan_Hennessey Par for the course 👌🏼👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Construction in Northern Liberties 🏠✨  •Check out the full tour of this property in my Instagram story.  IG: br… https://t.co/fozvN3tkQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1stOhioBattery If Jarmo somehow turns Wennberg into Duchene then he truly does walk on water. #WeAreNotWorthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Matt Gastz one more of tRUMPS loyal friends looks like he'll might be going to jail fo… https://t.co/BgT4Qv0Gqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start where you are. Use what you have.  Do what you can.  Rev. A. Louis Patterson https://t.co/0phRTS8dVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinJReidy2 @JosephTNeedmore @SethAMandel America First is an Anti-Semitic Dog Whistle?!?  You are grasping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am old enough to remember the way the growth issue has rocked and rolled in Colorado - also the economic downturn… https://t.co/6ZbiEz18bD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliomario55555 @glorialopez49 @saludhernandezm @AlbertoBernalLe @IvanDuque @JEP_Colombia Mamerto donde hay cultiv… https://t.co/XrWlS9SWsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely can’t wait to see this. Line of Duty is the best TV show ever made, ever. Ted Hastings is the best coppe… https://t.co/1bA1SyhbIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyDonevski @peaceinamerica1 @MacBreck @KeecoWang5 @woods353 @TheUnwantedBin @bbusa617 @Wesmoms @TOMRJZSR @t2gunner… https://t.co/a9WuLJB2Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[I managed to have a mental breakdown and throw toast on the floor before 745 am. Then my ex started laughing at me. Good morning 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cavs won a total of 12 games this season... shouldn't have taken you 3 OTs to win this game..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying #9sQuest (1959 - #11)  KAAGAZ KE PHOOL  (India / Guru Dutt) [Jan. 2, 1959]  (Rewatch - 8/10) https://t.co/wDcbPcjZ43]]></document><document><![CDATA[25$ for 70$ of food. You cant beat this shit man. Thanks again @REALSTONEDPLUG https://t.co/rL5CAAcdSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBobCasey (PA) @Sen_JoeManchin (WV) and @DougJones (AL) were the ONLY #Democrats who voted their righteous consc… https://t.co/U8zTlkAxqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilMojoTrail @PaladinsGame I don't know if this is intentional or a bug but there was a time when drogoz could lo… https://t.co/O1LMrmEMat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichP222 @A_verynicegirl Aim is still shaking the cob webs from her rough weekend 2 weeks ago 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wyldhaven1 gave me @Nike Boba Fett SB dunks the year after we graduated high school and I think I am about to get… https://t.co/lzKwda15xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We probably should have done #CommitteeOfTheWhole on the foster care bill. No, really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In closing he said, “I still want to believe, with everything that has happened, there is something called Justice.… https://t.co/VhVIKzBSjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope inec cancels the affected areas in Lagos, their votes must count]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMackeyPG They need to go with Bob, don't you think.  They're in a "nothing left to lose", "backs against the wall… https://t.co/HNfq815LxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_palazzolo Wand should be charged with treason also all of them should go down,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and #HappyThursday from my alternative music station. ☕️ @KHOU @chitakhou @SallyKHOU11… https://t.co/qD9Z7T83QY]]></document><document><![CDATA[VEGANS AND MORMANS — always trying to turn you. https://t.co/3K2Q5VqSin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra Ordinary Q&amp;A at #sxsw! #filmthreatsxsw #sxsw2019 #filmthreat @ Stateside at the Paramount https://t.co/mJqvcwklP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshxdavid @XXVinni They have proven they can't be cured, time and a again; I say remove them from society forever… https://t.co/lSY3US4JmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle, nothing happened. She just kissed me at the end of the night. And I NEVER gave her a lapdance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer review haiku. Big foamy pour here. Bright yet mild hop flavor, good. Beer for wrestling clowns. - Drinking a B… https://t.co/MkRlpdxcp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmfb #GMFB Somehow I ended up with a @Lions Starter Jacket! Rocked that thing for a few years! Dreamt of having a… https://t.co/MpBlQkuHrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna be logging off for awhile (maybe forever if this post doesnt get enough attention) and changing my cover to a… https://t.co/sNrMycBlCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans understand what feminism means about as well as Trump understands what a tax or tariff is, or really mo… https://t.co/lrPSE6mbps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEAsuka wins after @WWE_MandyRose slips on the apron.  @SonyaDevilleWWE looks like she's in hot water!… https://t.co/5j8pu7zgW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly can’t wait until I can unfold my phone into a tablet at a restaurant and ignore my friends and family even better during dinner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 TONIGHT the Legend of the Feels RETURNS to showcase his SPREAD LOVE TOUR! Our beloved @Jeff_Sutorius aka the tr… https://t.co/VkcuDA1Df5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kay_StayStocky My guy this is like the third time this is happening and I’ve heard similar sentiments I don’t thin… https://t.co/bAqNjI8H9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesnicksearcy @peterbakernyt Oh, looks like I've already blocked your clownish ass. https://t.co/So2nWIbAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: :(  zelda’s fairy fountain:  *         *    .            *     .   *      .   *     .              *   .    * .… https://t.co/V6syyczfyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s honestly unbelievable though how man fouls that were made up by these refs. Cal and Mitch Barnhart paid them well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredStillman Duke gets all the calls! Zion plays for Duke, he is the only reason Duke is in the game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyNorseman @fanspeak @nfldraftscout I do mocks almost daily. And have to say I like what you've done. Hills had… https://t.co/Z1BnwmwQKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasonGinsberg Yup, I hear this all the time too from the Anna in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realized  I’m the only person in Florida without a few paragraphs tattooed in cursive on my side of back. What should mine say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betty_bradbury @jayhlalele17 @shySkhu The foreskin is a structure solely designed to provide immense sexual stimul… https://t.co/LTTkAAMpjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know that i’m great, so im neva gon settle @ Madison, Alabama https://t.co/3PbPFTlLap]]></document><document><![CDATA[fk gop.  we dont need to win them over.  trump didnt win by winning dwms he did it by energizing a base.   if we at… https://t.co/Whb5rmEtbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 1200 Saint Charles Pl # PH1 #PembrokePines #FL  #realestate https://t.co/YJG3qJ2BgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nonexistent balls are bigger than your real ones. #humor #laugh #smirk #amusing https://t.co/WIQUn6JJ4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Perrin Fiesta by @Perrinbrewing at @ScoreRestaurant — https://t.co/FKTreqcWLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McLovinIt2Much Buddy hit the game winner against #2 Clemson in college tho, if I remember correctly... but, yes.]]></document></documents></author>