<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dinner is served. #lveats #gangnamasianbbq #getinmybelly  #instagood #foodie #infatuation #lafoodie  #foodstagram… https://t.co/bAdwK1IKq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[heres a fun idea, maybe warn us when you are gonna set off fireworks :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[With photographer @jamaica007  angelfashionsdress  Model @holly_steele   #fashionmodel #highfashion #influencer… https://t.co/zBudEAAGmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise Up by Andra Day really makes me feel powerful, like I can do anything in the world 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noctuarysf Oh wait Noah Dials also made us the subject of a 2$ discount on  well drinks in a room at 1015... a dis… https://t.co/M9G716rzho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNastanovich I know it was a good night! Sorry I didn’t make it out. I was really looking forward to it. I’m getti… https://t.co/Q1an69KbuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying every second I get to spend with this cutie 💕 https://t.co/6Uh1y6dq9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[They Already Give Every Child In America Full Coverage Insurance And Yeah Ussually Pay For Child Care!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely HATE when @mcelroy_jared is on nightshift. Not being able to wake up next to him is awful. 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a lovely break from #festivePDRseason to plant the vegetable garden with @jamestanton       Tomatoes, melons,… https://t.co/liA011cXrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be That Bitch ™ but my playlist fucking slaps https://t.co/67x4L7GJFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We see you Tiffany Snyder representing  @BlySchools!  #BreakfastChampion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, why not younger, we all know your smarter the younger you are.. what a crock of Shapoopy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dreams are so big and I can’t wait till I get to that point where I can look back in amazement at everything tha… https://t.co/9An0YjghIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to play "where are we?" but this is an obvious one...   We're celebrating making it through the first s… https://t.co/c7MV99hc7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommates made the mistake of agreeing to watch Pitch Peefect with me, so if you need me I’ll be swooning over A… https://t.co/OXp9HFUhi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typingelbow @tdichristopher @saracsalinas to @tdichristopher's point, i used to imagine i was in the hunger games… https://t.co/IfVrISaRTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetimes And why not, may I ask? Is the times now the final arbiter in such cases?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bc you got cast a lot in your college theatre department doesn’t mean you’re hot shit just saying🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did a thing on an #art app #benandjerrys @ South Burlington, Vermont https://t.co/lCHSzaQIvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go check out my newest cover of @halsey song Without Me  https://t.co/i8IzRSWpiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr She really is afraid of them.  I can almost have sympathy for her in this position.  When will they… https://t.co/PccTWj8E4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was heading into Starbucks near Patton Creek and two older Girl Scouts were standing near the door with a sign an… https://t.co/2AQDCAJCVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gettv Happy birthday, Majel Barrett. Star Trek. One of my favorite series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So French it is sir 🧐🧐🧐🧐 #Hearties @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkdudeee Aint this some shit?  #SteveHarvey says he can't help somebody else bc he might lose his.  You'd think he… https://t.co/JlZCwOYPUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tjierra @ttcriders @PRESTOcard @TTC They are ALWAYS not functioning with Wheel-Trans. Beck Taxi doesn't even have… https://t.co/BvQzYC69XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanDon @AGNeronha @MassAGO AG Neronha first must consider @GovRaimondo’s executive ‘business emergency’ order, whi… https://t.co/Ydo6dE3uEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson I don't understand why dog walking has become a derogatory expression. I love my dogs and love walkin… https://t.co/pHSmW7t18p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what to think of this honestly. Your childhood friend vs your blood. Like that’s really hard to choose. I want… https://t.co/5ReBwOuPdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PK4Gj1iDmn via @ripplestreetfun Happy Nat’l OREO cookie day!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s’ Day ❤️!everyone. Spread love this day near and far to all you meet and to yourself as well.   HE… https://t.co/puNvrFT2U7]]></document><document><![CDATA[That post snowstorm sunset #sunset #chasingsunsets #ct #greenwichct #connecticutgram #skyporn @ Greenwich, Connecti… https://t.co/p5MTGRcSWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey tuve un sueño SÚPER chingon! Y me quise dormir más y más de lo que pude pero puessssss, no todo se puede en esta vida. Omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreazelinski @Dexinvestigates *they can serve the parent a drink and the parent can give it to the child in a ba… https://t.co/PV9SLFgBW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theludedude @r_rigatony @mLemmingburgh @littleimpressio @lindbeda @atrupar @PeteHegseth @AOC TBH, about 1%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff You appear to be a Teump wannabe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fake Sex Doctor Conned the Media Into Publicizing His Bizarre Research on Suicide, Butt-Fisting, and Bestiality. https://t.co/S9hzNxCL5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanokokoro @ZerlinaMaxwell I know y! It’s the $$$. She’s owned by corporate media. It’s pretty pathetic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought Tesla’s had techonology to break on their own or even drive on their own!]]></document><document><![CDATA[maybe i should have a sign asking blake for a  hug if i ever see him in concert on my bday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Respectpolice63 @SheriffChody @lt_gray @Goldust Omgggggg! Madea is the shit! Now I wanna watch Madea 🤣lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space Force was a great sci-fi book by Childers from the 60's. I think. Anyway. It's not original.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FactCheckU @just_old_joe @solomongrundy6 @WeStandWithEvan @BBackerman1 @JeffHarperArt @HSchouten @WalterLapp… https://t.co/7q9NKUPr1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @Twitter Has @twitter or @jack ever explained why that little twit got a blue check mark?   What did he… https://t.co/5u6GlCzKiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇻🇪 ❤️🙏🏽 estan en Mis pensamientos y Colombia 🇨🇴 esta tratando todo lo q pueda #PazparalosVecinos]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, walking into work, knowing i forgot my bandanna but i’m not going to get in trouble: hopefully they fire me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKONOHIO @1776BetsyRoss @atlcav @greggutfeld @TheJuanWilliams @FoxNews @TheFive I wat he’d it too. Heard this id… https://t.co/jQqNrHaxyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RebounderzNJ for your generous support for our Annual Spring Spectacular Basket Raffle 🎟🎟… https://t.co/JYibW2GA6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things are shaping up for our inaugural Boots and Bling, Family Fling tonight! Stay tuned for more great pics!… https://t.co/esW3laFLcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashbacks-Let The Good Times Roll puzzle done by Alan. How many games did you play as a kid? @ Wisconsin https://t.co/uQB6X1he9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 @AngeleStar11 @andersoncooper Speaking of keeping honest, maybe run a story about AOV being investigated for… https://t.co/1MLlsYkpud]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are plenty of states your system can get itself into that aren't *great*, but can also  totally wait til morn… https://t.co/vqFZsJR5KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposed to go to Target for a 8x11 frame to frame my nursing license, but instead, I completely forgot and came ou… https://t.co/JZH8iMlE4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aprende a jugar con las cartas que te da la vida, porque serán las unicas. 😉 https://t.co/N1nqQwHWfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyDeal4 @lizzieloves @realDonaldTrump Holy shit that’s a long ass list #ImpeachTrump #ImpeachTheMF #whatstakingsolong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CosplayMei @sianoresist For the last time. No I did not take your Cheetos! ... adorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Stop lying Jim, this screams I am desperate the election is coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcmoLEW Ha, glad it's not just me! I used to be a 610 devotee way back in the day (originally because of the Royal… https://t.co/CqZtzw3glT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @SpeakerPelosi so when does the left actually wait for FACTS before declaring someone guilty of a cri… https://t.co/EFN06XPqgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbc5361 @wgrisanti28 Let’s just hope his parents weren’t Game of Thrones fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I almost go crazy. I saw the time. And it was 1.54 am, I unlock again my phone (after hitting my vape) and… https://t.co/GwZ75PDyQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at these amazing student athletes!! So proud of these Blazers! The game was nonstop excitement and slow and st… https://t.co/Pc3Sv3tnVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_schroeder Oh horrors!!! I DEFINITELY need to read this book! #booklove #bookmobiles]]></document><document><![CDATA[this shit shattered my soul.. we do not deserve this #immigrantsmakeamericagreat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating at waffle house thinking of @DonnieWahlberg 💙💙 wonder what he would order 😉😋🥞🍳]]></document><document><![CDATA[With every passing day, I miss President Obama's presence in our lives. His compassion for people and thoughtful de… https://t.co/TLAfPS3VUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new motto      #unbothered @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/zWI5T2zL4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlaDay I said the same thing!!! There were a lot of other ways to address this issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brown_birds But I just wish they had jasmine tea here like at HC! Their regular green tea is fine though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cj_spinks @desertmonkey11 @DemWrite @StormResist 😂😂😂 i needed a laugh after that disturbing display.. thank you for giving me that 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @johnlegend @CaraMiaSG @winegal57 @DemiCassiani @onceuponawine_ @TheFermtdFruit @KellyMitchell… https://t.co/hRr1zb8AlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mackenzieinman_ This is a whole lot better than the “hey do you think I’m dying?” Texts I get]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t think of a better ending to the school day than joining the @VioletAllStars staff meeting for our final State… https://t.co/uTCTNCQoWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kat326 It's like a holiday in and of itself. And when co-workers get you multiple Starbucks gift cards ☕🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I may have rapped Gold Digger from start to finish in front of a room full of people. It was the moment… https://t.co/zpaqsxe4i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK! Here I go! Regular me married white mom of 3...18,24,30 Scared determined insistent!We r ALL in big trouble!For… https://t.co/EsDSBIu9j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met up with Ed’s brother and his beautiful #family #skitrip #attitash @ Attitash Ski Resort https://t.co/dDAAgZaqF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Running_MrJones It puts me in a calm state of mind.                                                I’ve made some… https://t.co/wCWnq97p41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Christians should all hook their wagon to Trump and follow him to prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love music and this man ❤️ #bartandbrit @ U Street Music Hall https://t.co/NDPdF7Ja3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Autisticosaurus Yep. And it has the advantage of not showing how are children are losing their intellectual capacity over time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At it again this week with another sketch as my starting point. I don’t often include man made structure.  .… https://t.co/drBfKUN2iS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buzz That 1 glorious week of code freeze around the holidays. https://t.co/KT8fS1kBLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do kids in movies have really big bedrooms??? Where are these houses at?]]></document><document><![CDATA[BFF Josh captured cuddling the precious watch that hasn’t shown the correct time since 2015 https://t.co/7kR2bxBkUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrolling through on your phone? I've got a few things to counter that! I will be at the #PMA2019conference in Mont… https://t.co/Fkj4vTDeiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SummaCumLiar  President Trump is the best President ever!   Just kidding, he had to pay 25 million in fraud claims… https://t.co/eIoRdp04kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamienSpellman Awww I'm going to miss you. Thank you for your kind words!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t find toothpaste while staying over at my friends’ home so I used my 2 year old nephew’s kid’s crest... t… https://t.co/2WBaPTVKvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Latest Attempt to Take Down AOC Ended Just as Spectacularly As You’d Expect https://t.co/j6FvXH4qy6 via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a while at BWW.. 🤗 @ Buffalo Wild Wings https://t.co/lqRQUv761s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’d really thrive in a 1970s bachelor pad https://t.co/9jJjkceClA]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the parents are freaking out bc their frontier flights for summit got changed and messed up... can’t relate. th… https://t.co/3BiimopCg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamRobinTaylor I can't wait to watch it.:-):-D Congratulations Robin Lord Taylor.:-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Crunch - Polk Street - @crunchgym in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/9bBRqfnCZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cover of this book is doing its job... now I NEED to read this... although the thread where I found the image h… https://t.co/WeCLm4nGeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBulriss Beautiful evergreen state Washington here 🌲🌲🌲🌲 https://t.co/a2eYlAm0Vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do we use the carbon dioxide of Mars to create oxygen that humans can breathe? Mars 2020 is fully funded in thi… https://t.co/zot9d7ZDZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[T1: I see a lot of mistrust and departments not working with other departments to make a better more consistent patient experience. #hcldr]]></document></documents></author>