<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So for all you who have thought or have been visited my Verizon Fios employee’s, don’t believe a word they say.  Fi… https://t.co/6435TykzOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stringerpodcast @KristianJack @AFootballPod I like the way you do an interview. A little bit Larry King, a little bit Marc Maron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine Jason Mamoa and Idris Elba walking in your dive bar on a Sat night. That’s Magic and Bron. Issa wrap, Homie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronvseries @Liam_Fockboy Aye send the addy so I can pull up and switch your pills around]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnlyHipHopFacts RETWEET❗️RETWEET❗️RETWEET  🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨 https://t.co/fXuFuS4NzD 🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨🚨💥🔥🧨]]></document><document><![CDATA[She will be on the back of my car Sunday. #bam #newride #dogsupervision #getchasum #muskysled @BoulderBoatWrks @ Bo… https://t.co/QQ6f7SdN6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Hate My Blog, II: MC Frontalot, Baddd Spellah, Lex The Lexicon Artist, and Gm7 on 'Net Split'… https://t.co/hNF1Q6z0EX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_petriello His 2017 was weird...was a surprise to make the team, then Banny rode him too hard early, then he h… https://t.co/IK6ZZwY86j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draggor2k @scarytoilet I just had a flashback to tent city at Ali Al-Saleem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ueshawk Fairly inappropriate workplace behavior but I wouldn’t say it disqualifies her.  Let’s move on media...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a week ago I had the chance to completely surprise one of my best friends for his 40th birthday and second day… https://t.co/I6HbGtAgWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 I don't think he is...I also don't think he'd care if someone else was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son asked to watched “Big Hero 6” again. I love the look of this film and, frankly, my favorite parts are when H… https://t.co/zuKtgTYAsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3TRINZZZ Lmao that is too funny cuz I really be outside in my robe telling the bro “this ain’t it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a blast at Nerf and Nachos Friday night. @WSCSLions https://t.co/rO8X99TYGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_XXXITG_ Nah! He’s cancer. Defense! Build a defense! Bring bell and bring back cook and sign another wide out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGallagher1 Coach K has to coach...and hey yo isnt working...back pain in 5...4. 3...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian I just want to say thank you for all you've done. Since Harden left you he's become a beast and MV… https://t.co/2JT7zvh1h3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mclayton1970 @jjrrugg I know, my wife from the Midwest couldn’t believe we were tipping at Dunkin Donuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @JoeGibbsRacing and @dennyhamlin For the  @DISupdates Win! #JDProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I always check my bank balance in the morning. My Best Buy card payment went through but apparently I submitted… https://t.co/54J1pUJAbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was looking at Facebook when the phone rang and instead of muttering “UCLA Liver Transplant”; I caught myself abo… https://t.co/cK2yuD87q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B19RedRevival @teefarley43 @TheScarletCream Appreciate the tip my friend!  Will do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrequentPrayers @USAloveGOD @LadyRedWave @realDonaldTrump Phones are better than a tv show, +radio and paper, like… https://t.co/XaU6BH4fQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teddo is so happy the rain has stopped! Thanks so much @WagWalking! https://t.co/6BW2vLFUwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to much to ask of our candidates, right? My latest cartoon. https://t.co/JZI6dUVJVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatherBlazek Title of my time at the cloisters/Platte:  “Resting in Restoration” from Terry, a grateful retreatant… https://t.co/8V0PtGsLYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LipscombBisons you ought to have a talk with  @robmarberry0.  It  appeared he hit the Liberty player above the sho… https://t.co/9yc0wwNpjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @KatiePavlich Democrats are pushing an agenda of absolute evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroadcastBob66 Bruh. You really brought up regular season B1G champs?? Lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Palouse Pelosi is not in a position to demand the President's tax returns. They are none of her damn business!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my Father! Glad to be spending it with you. Thank you for everything! #familyfirst @ Brown Sugar… https://t.co/S6Ce0LnjlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berracahband WW is working, slow but surely &amp; I made 8.3 miles with 204 calories on the bike this morning, gotta do it 6 of 7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindle books don’t have to be long.  Some kindle books have as few as 10 pages or about 2500 words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AWESOME FOURSOME @JacksonGuitars emgpickups @elixirstrings #jacksonguitars #emgpickups #elixirstrings @ Portland, O… https://t.co/WrCR4cFhtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Turnksu @Matthew_D_Hall @RyanABlack @KellisRobinett What did Bruce say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[She really is! &amp; the crazy part is the ugliest people calling the baby ugly 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't need anything for Valentine's Day, I have everything I need. https://t.co/G0dIhhYSrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too funny  Dnc Perez gives super DELEGATES  To a MAN  Already tried a woman candidate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday There should be a question mark at the end of the sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Exit 44 To Ceo...                                 #DekalbCountyMade #DecaturMade #TheWorldPaid… https://t.co/4EoCZykYlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you took the over in the Bulls/Hawks game tonight. 155-155 heading into the 4th OT. Wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BrunoMars @brunomars After Concert In Hollywood @dolbytheatre SPONSORSHIP AND INVESTORS OPPORTUNITIES FOR SPORTS A… https://t.co/XPPW123D1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[The committee has voted unanimously to send it to the 14th order for possible amendment. Will not move onto the Senate floor]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s closing in on that time of year again! Mark you calendars for a great family weekend enjoying the beauty of Au… https://t.co/FpTnyl5qGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LangstaffJamie Lol 1 year later , it’s like texting but everybody watching 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio State did themselves no favors in their journey back to the NCAA tourney as they fall to Illinois at home, 63-… https://t.co/eatAZw6BJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support @dkhos This is what I received, when a rider decided to take something that wasn’t his. In my book, t… https://t.co/01eymRMZBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for everything. I appreciate it so much. It’s been a dream and we finally got see you we love you bro nev… https://t.co/VMRclVctkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are sick, you watch The Lord of the Rings extended editions. It is known.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers aint in a playoff spot because Lebron is out here filming movies 😂. Imma still go see it tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Ford made a #campaign stop in #Miami #otd 1976. @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/GKAKDwEF8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone sign up @GRRMspeaking for this @masterclass with @neilhimself? I need the end of #ASongofFireandIce bef… https://t.co/t05QzdfXPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Özil the conductor to our band today. He may not always have a great game, but when he's on form you can't help but… https://t.co/DJHhTtxqCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lttlteapot 200 wins in the toughest level of racing is crazy to think about. The reason you’re hearing about it is… https://t.co/GhHt8Ujn3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest thing my parents taught me was to never lie, it Carries on your reputation and how people view you, bei… https://t.co/CM6UvQNg8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a small tripod for my phone and decided to try it out. Getting there. #progress #fitness #jumpingrope… https://t.co/3sHaN7AeJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modernpuzzler I bet you cannot tell me what the technology feature is active and has been active for over 10 full… https://t.co/EVODH3tsUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in the city, and it’s already sticking. Follow along with @NBCPhiladelphia all morning, going to be a slippery… https://t.co/7oFMqmyx1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its past 2pm. My #Fitbit has tallied a total of 649 steps #SundayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wowsoclever1234 If you don’t believe in the concept of freedom then what do you believe in ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeepBeepRichie @swct_brokenname @quidd Yet I disagree once and I’m blocked. A number of other have reported the same. You tell me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si @lopezobrador_ decide hacer informe de gobierno cada 100 días, tendrá chance de realizarlo 21 veces. ¿Qué prefie… https://t.co/fWXkhjUlad]]></document><document><![CDATA[at #MyOwnPrivateDisneyland Attraction 90: Fort Mason’s Southside Theater to see Generation Theater’s production of… https://t.co/2UBbNNhylo]]></document><document><![CDATA[QU Baseball takes on Mississippi College at 2 pm!   🎥: https://t.co/4hjTXa21p6 📊: https://t.co/76V7em1pt3 https://t.co/3Ueytfl0Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_J_OShea Considering it got NO coverage by GPB and is played in Macon probably very few.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXSportsMX no tiene más comentaristas para mandar a Los partidos de Tigres? Ese Fabian Stay y el Yeyo de la Torre… https://t.co/9lJjKbyfpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewG1000 @GolfingSwingers After exhausting my allotment of Srixons today, broke out a ProV1 and it lasted 3 hol… https://t.co/G8AEl0HhPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our swimmers had the pool to themselves this morning 😄.  Swim and Dive Team banquet tonight.... https://t.co/m4LUpKN1cM]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has yelled to her letting her know she is here when she comes down. @KVUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandon Graham had the strip sack on Tom Brady in SBLII. He has 25.5 sacks, 57 QB hits and 49 tackles for loss over… https://t.co/36UferGqdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfleshman @parscale Tariffs are killing them. Weather's been fine here. Trump is giving them welfare. Other presidents didn't do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rainy day don't me to break your neck to get out.  Stay at home. Relax.  I don't feel like working today.… https://t.co/oqK5Clhl1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch You’re the one abusing your tax exempt status]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksAbby Blood Orange Wheat, more of a summer beer but wanted something light tonight to go with the pierogies. N… https://t.co/NyxMNqEDwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckySmirks I’m I the only asshole going to work? Who has time for this shit !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For what the law could not do weak as it was through the flesh, God did by sending his son in the likeness of sinfu… https://t.co/VhXKfBuUGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gruber i know it’s preseason but you need to get up to speed on their prolific losing too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why I sweat caring about if I can get an extra bag on a flight without being charged... either they legit dont… https://t.co/g5jH3A5spd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missvic659 @People4Bernie I don’t see that thing so you’re going to have to guess when I’m being sarcastic or opin… https://t.co/WVFc8m2gIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/myZQ6bX8KK @TheDemocrats @HouseDemocrats @realDonaldTrump Democrays PASS BILL THAT ALLOWS ILLEGAL MIGR… https://t.co/3ZysdB7nSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gastó un millón como mucho se busco 69 millones para la campaña de síndico o alcalde de la capital]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DrewOnTheRadio: laissez les bon temps roulez! Mardis Gras today, hope you all get some mufalata and some boudi… https://t.co/5lTh9w2xA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarcasticyte @TheIneptBirder ah, the canon!! also thinking about the sigma or tamron given the price. i sometimes… https://t.co/dm1D2HCoWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anolberding @WMCActionNews5 I’d say it always good when parts of the food chain survive even when we humans are so… https://t.co/J6XHlrKpf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaquinCastrotx @SenatorCollins @SenThomTillis Please understand President Clinton state of the union he said the… https://t.co/h0FThMNTla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth #justsayin #WritingCommunity #liveyourdreams #inspire #create #reinventyourself #begreat #writersquote… https://t.co/HSXnpmNEiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @Coach4aday2 the https://t.co/rC3ZgRWmB1. https://t.co/1ZoyfGACMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU #CELTICS FOR SHOVING MY WORDS SO FAR UP MY IRISH-AMERICAN WHITE ASS!!! WHAT A THRASHING OF THE WARRIORS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bamadesigner @getpantheon @McDwayne Kidding of course. This proactive site check-up is precisely what I look for in a host.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCpoodles2 @Jaysmallz92 @qanon76 Wow. Moronic Republicans attacking each other. This is fun! We even had a Hitler… https://t.co/Yb9X2HkN4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xflyersgirlx11x I am working outside on a roof in Hatboro I'll take any good weather that comes our way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OKNYSportsfan @BNightengale How many of them signed an LTD at the age of 26?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google dissimule des micros dans des appareils qui ne devraient pas en avoir | JDQ https://t.co/vz79lQeR8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the point of having dental insurance  because with it, still going to be like 850... better than 1300 I gues… https://t.co/9Q9FzjSKXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just working when @USAquarium came on SiriusXM’s Outlaw Country 🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽 https://t.co/YqOHN9ciK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekonaplane Oh no I'm not knocking it. Sonic 2 may be my favorite game of all time. It's nearly perfect. I'm just.... Eh you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevilleRay you’re the best VP of everything network that a company could ever ask for! I hope that makes you smile and makes your day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from #aeexpo2019 An inside look at one of the most yearly anticipated industry shows in the world -… https://t.co/CYxYi8SwC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, accurate again Senator Warren. Miller of all people should not have dealing with our Native citizens.]]></document></documents></author>