<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @familyfirstcorp @Priya4Trump @EnigmaMark1 @Aug1405 @Razorsmack1 @direcsjbhan @debiharrelson11 @carmee1… https://t.co/YjJoM5Uetq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multicultural day #buds #playmountainplace #snacks #friends #celebrateculture @ Play Mountain Place https://t.co/J2hSXlej5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know when someone you care about is feeling so down &amp; you can’t help them..worst feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You can put lipstick and pearls on a pig - it’s still and always will be a pig. @IlhanMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mamiadventure #disneyorlando #nature @ Disney's Animal Kingdom Lodge https://t.co/iAC1QpfuGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday young man!  You have a very bright future!  Best wishes from Okeene Oklahoma!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was able to shower without seizing. The weather is nice.  About to eat and hang out with all the homies. It's a beautiful day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedThreadFarms @MGigger Oh, so you mean my “holier than thou” uncle standing in front of our entire family at both… https://t.co/wM3Xun99Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hungryturkey007 @ehchurchill @DrWhoisin @__CassidyRae__ @ToddXena @immommylaura @establishmentno @freddyrace14… https://t.co/17bkgCpvTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper I thought at first it is @MichelleObama standing behind @RepMarkMeadows. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithsonianMag John Quincy Adams travelled with his father to Europe when he was ten years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricky_martin un favorzote consigue la canción para mi hija queda cerca de tu casa está Santa Mónica California , L… https://t.co/zZTckd8tDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExcuseMyFly Lmaooo I literally am dying in my office. I can’t. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/eEtgXq0qWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will NEVER EVER live in the deep south.  Fuck that noise.  Won't visit there either and give them a dime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So amazing to see our seniors connect with the elementary! Great activity @MrsGatesUHS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter THUG is a movie everyone needs to see — and I do mean everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeraCausa9 Thanks for a wonderful thread. Can i ask for the source (book )? Would love to read them all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found out at work today that I got a Pell Grant for my schooling and I’m feelin so blessed 😭🙏🏻 I definitely cried… https://t.co/2Vue4tzHlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PopPrismPower @smarktodeath @thecabinetcast @thecountdownpc @gotstratosphere @giantleap4geeks @GeekdomFancast… https://t.co/NJ6IWBJ9IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 13 Most Confusingly Sexy One Direction Lyrics - BuzzFeed Mobile https://t.co/FvDhc7VDFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think i just broke a sweat from dancing but i like to dance so now my back is hurting but i wanted to learn some… https://t.co/TCdJqb4tp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SillyDadGene @jliza04 Btw, ang unang lalaki na humawak sa pwet ko in public dahil na slide daw kamay nya sa unifor… https://t.co/EdTRMUbDgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVS49 @Mistybucketlist @_____dclynch_ @Brandyputerbau1 @bonbonmonkey672 @DonnaLaCroix6 @BrownieBarasch Awesome!… https://t.co/Yk7FPZRGrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all know Gary's lying 😮 #CassidyReturnsSVU @Mariska @FINALLEVEL @PeterScanavino @KelliGiddish @SVUWritersRoom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olson called for “dedicated funding for a big leap to replace its core system records of taxpayer accounts” that st… https://t.co/ixoh5qJnM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaHluv @BRL_Podcast @cmarieboswell89 Lady T turned in her grave that night. JLo disrespected her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a crazy day! I can’t wait to see you all tomorrow!   Ended the stream with:  🥊 Kill Counter: #203 🏆 Win Counter: #25]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long and very stressful week, I was able to spend some time with nick yesterday ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wanna go to the gym for the second time in the day but I feel like the people at the desk gonna look at… https://t.co/FadzIb8XBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I'd say de Blasio is a bit "meatless" himself, if you know what I mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VEGAN FRIED CHICK'N on tonights Meatless Monday Special @SecondDistBrew @ Second District Brewing https://t.co/DgAUvA6xMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly yesterday was the most fun i’ve had in a while #ThankYouCroParade]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner date with hubby.Happy valentine’s day from us 😘 @ The Hotel Elegante https://t.co/woOPkJ4qRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not even 7:30 and I've sent a passive aggressive email to a supplier. Lordt help me get through this day. https://t.co/l2X1A17Tcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me swiping right on cute guys in Bumble damn well knowing I won’t ever message any of them https://t.co/N1rSWsGwzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence NOOO Terrence NOO😮 I’m speechless &amp; I’m NEVER speechless...😮😮😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 Albert Nelson Marquis Lifetime Achievement Award given to Dr. Cynthia Viola @DrCynthialive .… https://t.co/KRndabh6q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divinefeminist Thank you 🙏 @Kimberl38218406  @divinefeminist  thank you 😊 love ❤️ peace ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never saw any 1D concerts as I just learned who Harry was when I saw him on James Corden!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior Stupid move, Joe. @realDonaldTrump never met a promise he had any intention of fulfilling. For insta… https://t.co/qqr7wXVzRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st Annual March Madness for Lady Irish Soccer! ⚽️🍀  The girls are selling squares until March 17th! Take a look at… https://t.co/JmfkjlPqSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[psa: everyone go do yourselves a favor and listen to @iamblackbear’s #1SIDEDLOVE on repeat until the album comes out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be still my heart ❤️! Emily and Ann Marie are in the garden! geminemi @ From The Ground Up Community Garden https://t.co/oc2QsOCqNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope there’s some sweet tart lollipops and sweet tart ropes left tomorrow @ the stores 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just catching up on the bachelor from Monday and omg Kirpa saying like “oh it’s my opinion and I’m gonna tell Colto… https://t.co/KUQZBKYLlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MishaAnn1 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump I can’t wait til their cool aid has the same effect as Jim Jones variety. Na… https://t.co/L6H5rddjSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a dream I was in jail again, only 6 months pregnant this time.... let me tell you how happy I was to wake up!! 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RichTheMountain for reading At Gleason’s Gym and spending time with our 7th grade students at the Madeli… https://t.co/4vEDblM6VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our son is three this year.. 😞 &amp; all I want is to give my baby the brother he wants.. soneone carry a baby for me💙💙😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 @TheRickWilson @tonyposnanski @ManInTheHoody @MollyJongFast @Kris_Sacrebleu 🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁 @choo_ek  @DrEricLevi… https://t.co/RcI9oB6Kkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had awesome #day2 #bootcamp my arms were on 🔥. #healthy2019 I also walked today! https://t.co/9475VMV0KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind every strong women is GOD! Happy Sunday!🙏🏻❤️💃🏻 #iambellafavela #bellafavela @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/b087sDu5Ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielWGXA Right!? Can you imagine this happening while sitting in class... I would be terrified]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of our amazing challenge team 💪🏻👸 “A Queen on the street but a BEAST in the gym” #leanqueens #fixmycrown… https://t.co/rDWVK8AgVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue I’m at Syracuse handcock airport and purchased an even more legroom seat which entitles me to even more sp… https://t.co/ymsOWHAa4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Should Your College Major Actually Be?  I got psychology.. funny what I wanted to... #mirth #tee-hee #grin… https://t.co/6qgz2HtaP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartlettFred @chasrmartin @GaltsGirl @SenFrankNiceley I hate government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docsquiddy Dragon Heist has a lot of stuff that works off the cuff and a few things locked down. We just got throu… https://t.co/F9sQnPUoYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s pretty wild how people in relationships/ single people give you almost opposite advice on certain situations lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #Quinceanera choreography for the books!:):) think of SmashDance for your special dance:):) #quinceañera… https://t.co/NIckswwVFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isra_avilas @Writer_DG @VisitScotland I would ❤️ to be In Scotland once again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B with @HoganKnowsBest3 🥳😝💓 #RODEOHOUSTON   (Why did I cut half of my face off?) https://t.co/7TdYgdWYSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lurkland @Fourens_ Yesss. So worth it. You get cute stickers too that Ashley signs on the back, vote on future epi… https://t.co/PRbcCKzBtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best ways to get real time updates from #umc #UMCGC #GC2019 are the @inconfessingmvt emails that I send… https://t.co/yJVGVrKBeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjmcgrath1 @madriannorman @thecjpearson I think it’s the one-sided nature of what’s going on that demonstrates dis… https://t.co/35Mkz8JGUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't fucking believe it. @JIDsv @sabaPIVOT tickets sold out before 10:05. I was on live nation at 10:02 and it w… https://t.co/g5kSlCS2dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patsajak The humor about him he said he has to beat it because he has 3 years left on his contract to host jeopard… https://t.co/XuUuXfqTOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder if theres something wrong with me. I dont know what's goin on with the universe...but I really j… https://t.co/E2dnajSpyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m billing Southern for my dermatologist / face care products. Stress is the only reason I have to buy make up. Lameeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janfromthebruce @JohnOberg 😂 😂 😂 It's super cold here downtown too. I imagine those winds off Lake Huron are reall… https://t.co/IFGWjSqhR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHEK_News Already happening—beautiful blooming plum trees on my street in James Bay are being replaced with maple trees.  So frustrating!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHEESH #StriveForGreatness #JustAkidfromAkron #LakeShow #MyHairlineRunningAwayFromMyForehead 🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dronephotos #myrtlebeach #dronephotography #dronestagram #dji #djiphantom4pro #aerialphotography #sunset… https://t.co/ST3kM6btCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxswedu I'm a speaker and did not grab my free pass for an attendee to come to my session.  Is it possible to do t… https://t.co/rhb4xAJkeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I accepted a challenge to post covers of 7 books, with no explanations or reviews, just the cover. Each time… https://t.co/Nsgd0ge5xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMay1923 @Colleen46646347 @realDonaldTrump You forgot Bill Clinton! #MeToo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supermattachine @spunkchili This is a whole day and a damn half you just had in about 7 minutes, so you drink that… https://t.co/bGxTqGMFz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the warm weather almost 70 degrees this past weekend...74 degrees today 😍  Trying to remind myself i… https://t.co/uMjzY7Q2Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me what -3° feels like because I have no idea &amp; I’m not ready to find out https://t.co/unX048AgTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[He says keep the same energy I have with him, with other people...let's get something straight, I can ignore other… https://t.co/PN11C5gU9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trains_Thoughts @Dart_Adams Lol 🤣🤣🤣🤣 if they ran on a roof they and was going to jump and die or break both legs and both arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time of year my morning alarms are always directly related to what time the sunrises]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f4dchief I never thought I'd say wish we were in NY instead of FL in March, lol! Bobblehead yes, snow no!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; Marissa just signed up to run in foam glow, roomies who do 5k’s together stay together. 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[KASH FOREVER! Also though, the bird probably does solid work as well. But yay @KashAbdulmalik!!! #birdman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghalexander The best part is that we get to do it together.   Let's show the world what we're made of! https://t.co/ZGi0PzEWS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great night at #GenderBender! @ Planet Ant https://t.co/ORJauKDlvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all in the details 💥 Wearing the comfiest / coziest faux fur from @revolve to keep me warm 🐻 // You can instan… https://t.co/gqfY4ZxWYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy Cow! That was close. Wow! The dangers of working track side. I’m pretty sure the bobsled has the right of way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentally escaping to the beach after spending SO much time this week educating myself about the TRUE cost of my lif… https://t.co/y82ng5WXOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s Rosie? I am so humble to receive this commission from Senate President Bill Galvano #FCSW is an amazing org… https://t.co/6gwqAtuhHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just imagine what is NOT being found and getting through at our vast and unprotected border. #BuildTheWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gabriela_Knox  #GK5X  #GK5X_FITNESS_PROGRAM  #GK5X_CUTTING_CLOTHES  #GK5X_DIET_PROGRAM  I'm in love with my #brand… https://t.co/xbfGuUJh60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is #NationalDrinkWineDay. I didn’t even know,  but celebrated anyway. https://t.co/2mfdzXWW7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMedzSwag @tiaramvrie 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 you're stupid ! How bout you @ me next time you duck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ Jimmy Fallon Congrats on your 5th anniversary but the beginning of your show last night was awful. Why was Ben St… https://t.co/IwZyHopIBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My amazon cart is $300 and I’ll never be able to check out but I’m fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Court_Kae If I ever get married again, I’m borrowing this for my vows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro for 3 MONTHS STRAIGHT my daily horoscope had “trouble/conflict” under love but not anymore who’s ready to marry me]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s international women’s day and I still have to pay my credit card bill? Smh men ain’t shit 🙄]]></document></documents></author>