<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SBakerMD Wonder what happens if you post a picture of you eating salad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino True. Being illegal sure isn’t stopping it. Let women control their own destiny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay man, pray for Sisqo2k. Nothing’s wrong, he’s just in Saudi Arabia being ugly.  #iMissSisqo2K #BringBackSisqo2020… https://t.co/Z3uJvQKZWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my Rangers followers, please enjoy these photos I took at #springtraining today  This team, despite the down… https://t.co/b6UaGP5S9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[of surgery, where they removed another obstruction from his gut that was on it's way to killing him off.  Chomper c… https://t.co/p1gr02iI4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerriDelCampo I don’t think law enforcement  “requested” Al Capone’s tax returns ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume If President Trump really said this he now has a good idea who the FBI official is. Good to know your enemies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesse James will whoop me lmao but I think I could throw down with Illinois Secretary of State Jesse White for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Men With Broken Hearts by Hank Williams, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/OFjBS6gy9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night a random Caps fan proposed to me because he was so impressed w my hockey y’all. He made me a paper ring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yunggrandslam @torimetzgerr1 @Paul_Vitale721 I mean at this point I don’t even think you understand the concept of… https://t.co/6zbZ0f4IMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is the conclusion surprising but inevitable?  And there’s still some work to do. But it’s there. And we had our fir… https://t.co/ZXaoiMj1lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just more single minded hate from the American media “ enemy of the American people !”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetygirl53 @UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett What's your point?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecoonr,  @safelydoingless and other great collaborators our latest on #pediatricoveruse  https://t.co/emt4sPdams]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times does one have to watch the episode when Michael leaves @theofficenbc and it not be sad? That shit wrecks me. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mon_The_Hoops81 @AOC Ah well, there might be more important end-of-times issues to be concerned about these days. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Songs Spotlight March 5, 2019 Bernard's Featured Songs For March 5, 2019  David Guetta, Bebe Rexh… https://t.co/5oiOP9dTcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rIX2os9Nio 🛑Yahweh the Almighty Father always have the last say.🛑Praying for peace and prosperity and… https://t.co/iQY1p9TmcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @OregonGovBrown Stupid idea. It creates more problems than it solves. Government control is never a s… https://t.co/02vxe7ckiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the people that went out they way to have a convo with me about booking a shoot, agreeing on a budget, deciding… https://t.co/5lXGQ4urqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk what if you came out with your own #cannabis stain and called it #spacemusk ? I think that would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighReport @BrettKollmann Did Greedy Williams evaporate or something? We need a corner, so let’s take a linebacker? Duh fuk?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out to eat before the big games. Go a salad (honey mustard), mozzarella sticks, 6oz. sirloin steak mashed potato an… https://t.co/JsO8RhuFfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all had bunch of college athletic scholarships and threw it away for weed and to pursue a rap career]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would That I is my favorite track off the new Hozier album. It’s an absolute heater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if the inside of you car looks like this....i’m driving MY car and i will meet you there]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is bullshit. What matters are qualifications and experience. We can now seewhat happens when we elect a demigo… https://t.co/fMSf2ss4S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@gatesfoundation Vaccine Delivery team Senior Program Officer @lahegg reflects on the vital importance of granular… https://t.co/yMh4PHCbdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevProUK @zacksabrejr @WillOspreay @JoeLandoA2A @harrisonbourne5  someday book this match please: Ospreay/ZSJ vs Bourne/Lando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReliableSources @Acosta one day, we can be sure Acosta will just fade away]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you need your hair to be on point before talking about spatial navigation at your poster at #INS2019inNYC https://t.co/28xnx23Xkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoteESPN funniest thing from sports weekend. @LeBatardShow https://t.co/Q6mZROKadx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JugglingFitness @robreiner He’s not getting impeached based on the current, revealed info. The Democrats talk a gr… https://t.co/44I1l0Lutx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier i left the bar for a steak quesadilla and came back in to eat it.  I have no regrets. Priorities at their finest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Latest:       Trump administration moves to defund Planned Parenthood;       White House 'looking into' ruling… https://t.co/MWom1eyO0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelereseigh @The_Acumen We use find my friends we always know where our adult kids our, is that bad!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great learning experience at the Kansas Hunter Education Instructor Academy! Thanks Kent, Stacy, Aaron and all the… https://t.co/0oZiW30vZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessFink Also, you gotta get on the @JPsoFLY train and start calling it "spicy water."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FDRLST Fantastic read! Thought all I needed to rad was the 1st paragraph. Says it all! But, great info followed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murderer: Any last words?   Me: uh, yeah actually could you not shoot me in the body? I’m an organ donor so....  Mu… https://t.co/EggVLp1IsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BikeyKnit Fine by me as I’m headed Eastbound and will be flying home it seems!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SantaCruz County is taking new steps to combat homelessness, specifically with the large encampment on River Stree… https://t.co/tyOnlrg5Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brasil! I can’t wait to see you in less than a week. Get excited for #ALIVETOURBRASIL with the official setlist her… https://t.co/ZBUWI0qWEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If nothing else, all these hearings are allowing us to see how dense all these reps are. Do better, Louisiana!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottKellum There are a few here in the spring and summer. Surprising there aren’t more given the city is only one… https://t.co/cz3LVSrY6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also come to Christ while they can because none of us know the hour when God will take us out of this world either… https://t.co/iULRQTZyEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicki did her features in Make Me Proud, Monster AND Up All Night??? Omg I might have to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMcGaryEra College is college, lil bro gonna shine there. Crazy how we was just talking about that too]]></document><document><![CDATA[WPIAL 170-pound final: Canon-McMillan’s Gerrit Nijenhuis pins North Allegheny’s Jon Hoover for the title. Kiski Are… https://t.co/omyiq2Xtra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why hasn’t @Apple made it easier to share text message threads?   I can’t tell you how many screenshots of conversa… https://t.co/3b74hSS0L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly hope @SenFeinstein watches this video and realizes that she comes off as bad as Miss Trunchbull in Matilda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iconthicc_jordd It looks like he got the best blow job one day and looked down and saw it was from a dude and poof… https://t.co/uGjzWDlAD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t forgot that you claimed Save the World would be free in 2018 @FortniteGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreEffinTwist @IR0N710 @LGJRDNS I don’t even know what you’re talking about really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of the ods also have either alcohol or sedatives like xanax in their system also.Charge them all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kieran even canonically *looks like* my canon HoF who is his dad.  I can't tear them apart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should you go out in public with your breath smelling like  “mimosas and pussy”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fashion #fashionista #fashionable #silver #shiny #jewelry #selfie #me #selfiesunday #party #nightlife #queen #gay… https://t.co/d6GFBUW7z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly the eventual passing of will smith will probably be the worst thing we all experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshallMa96 @AmexCanada @MarriottBonvoy Call in after you meet the minimum spend and they may give you the extra 10K points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[clairinthespiritofhaiti #clairinsajous  #martini 🍸 @ 399 Fremont Street https://t.co/GWbA6BnSdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Streetsboro 33 - Cleveland JFK 8 (5:04, 2nd) What a wonderful pass from Rachel Bolyard, cornered on the rig… https://t.co/bgm5XKvHM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NBA is the best organization as far as American professional sports, Zion isn’t even in the NBA yet but is alre… https://t.co/1k6lznQr7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @CodesTrump @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC… https://t.co/Wm6efO0TeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I believe this is the first time ether party attempted a coup of a sitting president. We, the Amer… https://t.co/PjULTeg6Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if #UberEats will bring me, like, a 12 pack of soda from the gas station at the end of my block?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charley_ck14 That's fake, I'm better looking than him. And couldn't pull that Chica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skies_empyrean @CityofSarasota @abcactionnews Hey I’m trying to be helpful here and now you’re getting all in my f… https://t.co/gO6QS7boYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Harden's streak of 30-point games ends against the Hawks  https://t.co/vM2D0JyAPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurrenSy_Spitta  good morning sir. I am trying to raise $4700 for 2 homeless veterans here in Columbus Ohio. I am… https://t.co/jd7cYBa7Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Adam @adammcmichael and great to hear from you! Yes, we felt it was good timing in combination with our long… https://t.co/m6VbIQlQg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsHackCA @JDaIey 🤣 ... nobody outside of the Bay knows that guy, right?  originally i was going to say E-40 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout Turner, 10:45 left in the half. Edgerton up 12-5. This might be the most raucous crowd at Craig since 2002,… https://t.co/iY8I3Ocyoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad more and more media outlets are addressing this with nuance instead of either indifference or fear mongnering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spicetc @TalbertSwan @MeghanMcCain @TheView @TamikaDMallory @IlhanMN Thing is a perfect description for that racist idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSilver Why do #Conservatives on the far right believe unfounded Conspiracy Theories? Are we not justified in ca… https://t.co/ufK7avWoeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running yellow lights while driving down Scottsdale is risky business man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athletic City Update:  These Morris-Sussex Wresters are heading to the Quarterfinals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiasedGirl Time to invest in a good ice pack. Love this one for my back. Chattanooga ColPac Reusable Gel Ice Pack… https://t.co/cl8zXMkTtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS NFL combine is a snooze fest...only pay attention to the actual draft.  A question for Am… https://t.co/HM4O9FFcYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celinedion666 Just gonna guess and say that says ‘let the good times roll’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiendVinny @Weej69 @RepTedDeutch And then you think the police departments make fake felony or domestic violence c… https://t.co/2ZSVMqCivS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DoorDash_Help I did not receive my order and it says it was completed]]></document><document><![CDATA[94% chance brother nature gets eaten by an animal while making a video within the next 8 months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Samanian_ That was just post 911 America for ya; we gave away our liberties en masse in the name of patriotism.… https://t.co/pAYolBGL7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernalJatleen @sunsong23 @american2084 @pam_brundige @JCoker13 @lc1_summit @Kewlbearhelloki @RuleChicago… https://t.co/b67ara59DJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@znounouSince95 NO is Alshon catches it 🤷🏾‍♂️ Carson doesn’t finish two season in a row. And I’m not convinced he w… https://t.co/vNCmUVWKzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truly enjoy our wash day together! It’s just something about being in her presence doing what we were born to do, l… https://t.co/EIcfaeecpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[PM Narendra Modi greets Saudi Arabia Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman  https://t.co/jffHHmxRBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not airborne you won’t get it. : #Repost military_comrade ・・・ @RegulusOI . . ❎ DOUBLE TAP pic 🚹 TAG your… https://t.co/1WD9ryZlEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver is trying to kill em at this point with these driving skills 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dangerous fool and a useful idiot. These are the players fulfilling Murdoch's nefarious machinations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just some final glueing, wiring and weathering and the Alex-enabled L3-37 will be complete and ready for the Jax Ma… https://t.co/gP4iDZnoe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSmorrison1 @thedailyjaws I’m deeply moved that you follow the daily jaws. My man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Therefore, my beloved brethren, be ye stedfast, unmoveable, always abounding in the work of the Lord, forasmuch as… https://t.co/YHUY7LzyEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bprosser7777 @LMaughanJones @vicderbyshire Do you think an upraised clenched fist would be more appropriate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSN690427 Then you’ve obviously not read any of my previous stories or you were recognize your mother-in-law. Don’… https://t.co/eanaFEj9Ru]]></document><document><![CDATA[REFLECTION SERIES . 📸 x markiswhoiam . @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/lzGwb2mKyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay in 1950 the TV sketch comedy series #YourShowofShows premiered on @nbc. The show starred #SidCaesar and… https://t.co/Fb82bY7OQB]]></document></documents></author>