<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Aight so I’m a little late, but I just watched abducted in plain sight..white ppl gotta be some of thee dumbest beings ever created 🤨🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenLambright7 @JoeNBC That’s why I stopped watching Joe. He can’t even remember who he was rooting for yesterday… https://t.co/dWQrZdxUUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after I get out of a 2 hour work meeting... #aaaahhhh https://t.co/HXfTCsE2KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stepdad can’t handle when my mom and I are together 😂 if you know us, then you know why? Twins in every way 👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM SO PROUD OF @desusnice AND @THEKIDMERO .... I’ve been a member of the bodega hive since way back when and I fe… https://t.co/TLWF4jbOdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles daylight savings means u save daylight in the morning.. so sun rises and sets much later.. when it en… https://t.co/G3fNPl8qAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[- How do you say good luck in Japanese?  - Um. There’s no such thing.  #language #shapes #our #reality]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!   Explore the March Literacy Newsletter for upcoming opportunities!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone went black about 8:30 last night and would not cut back on even on the charger.. I could not sleep for shit!!!...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡 Recently Reduced | Lovely traditional home with timeless charm and warmth. 👉🏼 1240 Lenox Ave. | Miami Beach, FL 4… https://t.co/n9gcAXjIhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapping up my Cali trip with homemade pappardelle with 16 hour slow braised lamb ragú.   So delicious I didn’t wan… https://t.co/8SdLPAq5Cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Jonas Brothers interview from this morning and Nick said “my wife” and it just hit me how much has changed in 6 years haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nessa_iloveyou since u have a mans can u text Andrew i want to know his response lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voellercoaster Watched the video like 3 times yesterday. 😬   It's going to be a problem. https://t.co/rtAYpO9kSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinBond1 @_DishinDays Since Chabby are leaving it's more than just it being Valentine's day with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're a rival, I trick you, watch you tag and title I'm a slimer, a grimer, a real big timer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @KendraScott for reminding us that hope &amp; despair can do-exist. 💙 #levislegacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yattas_GotaLota Go to OWN on demand and look for the Iyanla Fix My Life episode for Philando Castile’s wife. It just is so heartbreaking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get trash ass Tristian in the hot seat because he is the REAL problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do u guys have any people that u know from real life but that are mostly your internet friends that u wanna reconne… https://t.co/PFkadzq7Ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 of #7 BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews - goes out to Sandi White! This is “Invisible: The Forgotten Stor… https://t.co/jDX0LEmpFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a wild lunch bunch! #japioneerpride #dublinlit19 https://t.co/9LMqtJdKYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE AT WAR -- Bix Weir https://t.co/t0qeMXEbyB via @YouTube This is my one of my favorite sites. Believe it or n… https://t.co/aXBRfuf9m0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little man was so excited to watch Rachel break the 3 point record in a game with 10!! Way to go @APUWBB1 #SetAPart… https://t.co/C5NRks827z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saveH2B #ReleaseTheVisas @SecNielsen @SecretaryAcosta @realDonaldTrump #15knotenough #savesmallbusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin!! #waltdisneyworld #animalkingdom #up #kevin @ Disney's Animal Kingdom https://t.co/yRaAr5qxxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe you can run up there in 2020. .@harrisonjaime can be our senator. He won’t forget who he works for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super cool! Cadets from Sarasota Military Academy teamed up with 5 local female World War II vets from different br… https://t.co/4VcODOooeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya know that week outta the month where you feel stupid bloated and HUGE and you just wanna live in bulky sweaters… https://t.co/tfohVchiyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Starhopper on the launch pad today. Looking mighty commanding just chilling there. Welcome back to coverage… https://t.co/YJ6Lb7o33T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house in the Applcation &amp; Robotics Centre during break today. (and every day!)   @HDSB_Frankovich https://t.co/RY5s0I2DYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This used to be me too so I just started playing w him lmao if u can’t beat em join em]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Cien años’ is particularly rich in Colombianisms, making its core, I think, even more inaccessible. Here is but on… https://t.co/daIwwSGmuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queendom_ENT But where is this disrespect you keep talking about ????? Lol seriously .. like i said I let that she go after It happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everman Collegiate presents on Dual Credit and ECHS/PTECH.  Register for this informative conference.  It is great… https://t.co/Qmx2AuXyQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Community college can only get you so far. The first two years, great but afterwards you still need to attend a uni… https://t.co/sROqYG4RYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo…Jason Momoa I see that matching scrunchy on your wrist and it’s both appropriate and hilarious! #oscars2019 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good reads. “The Prisoner of Chillon” - Lord Byron @ Haverstraw, New York https://t.co/GkQ2FvJK5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[went to hang out with different friends in DC for the weekend. immediately ran into Annabelle. the codependency has… https://t.co/QPndQFUv4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[To get up to $5 in ride credit, just download the Lyft app using my referral. (I'll get credit, too.) Here's my ref… https://t.co/jYcDodwfS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just wanna know why my hulu isnt letting me start the second season of power :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do people forget that Adam Lambert was in wicked before american idol...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Lisa Bloom, was going to court with trump because she was representing KATIE the 13yr old who had… https://t.co/ICnL4HHTu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preview of this groovy ass hook I made coming soon https://t.co/CMhHvuVy10]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this group! Our growth over the course of this season has been unfathomable. Thank you seniors for all… https://t.co/S0Z8Sf8Ilh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use my phone too much that it’s raising it’s own white flag hays i need to buy a need phone for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinVanSickle Well, my dad mails me hardcopies of articles he likes from the @nytimes. #Even]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaryucd @ZacharyLevi Dude if you love him in that you need to see him in She Loves Me!!!! He’s just 🥰🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can a man carry fire next to his chest and his clothes not be burned? https://t.co/YRhxSdEAxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many will frown upon this but *disclaimers upon request* I hit 160 in the snow! Lmao #ThanksFalken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanderVVtm @TeddiMellencamp I'm completely lost no. I don't even understand Teddy's text. Guys just say what happe… https://t.co/qZaETLLhPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Keanu: very generous of you! but I think it is better to manage your own foundation. Not just give money. But to o… https://t.co/rkoj27wJIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairecmc Please!!! The $22 trillion debt generates how much to be paid in interest at what rate? From whom do. we… https://t.co/qEkhyag3v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkAmesExiled Well, yeah. But you've gotta be a little bit proud of yourself. You got under their skin, right? That ain't nothin' kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this picture of Melania and Ivanka pre-pladtic surgery and dye jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So only “real” people love this country because they want a wall. Insult the majority. That works well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraysonDolan Stay strong, I been there, it’s not easy, but peace comes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raydeezyy agreed. but I am not even sure how to tell this girl that I'm not really interested in hanging out with her friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber @TheBeatWithAri Of course he did. This man dared to walk into court while being black.  He should have k… https://t.co/odZRC0b9xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so windy here they have an empty trailer ban on the thruway past a certain exit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joyfuljupiter 😂😂😂 I mean.... You aren't wrong but I refuse to be lumped in with those other humans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DalePreuett @DineshDSouza @IngrahamAngle @FoxNews The original plan was to kill off the black population in Americ… https://t.co/XHmMNeEjTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool!! #suns player stoped by one of our #ahipoki locations #cityscape #Phoenix ☄️🦍 https://t.co/klTEcsT1KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlyonne She was amazing in that role. I’m so sad only one season left! #OITNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[One reason I still engage on twitter is because you get to find stories like Michael Campofiori. He fought to survi… https://t.co/igj5T01TBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sonic employees quit en masse, tape note to door https://t.co/KzbaWJqx8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I make assumptions about other drivers and they don’t follow through]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m presenting an art installation proposal to the CEO of Ent Credit Union in 2 days... I’m gonna vomit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl I can’t see this/can someone give the readers digest version?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 This is a lie. Used to promote the racism and white privilege agenda. Truth matters. https://t.co/HzPDkTDain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasFlipnMove @DIYNetwork I admire all of you. You work very hard on your houses and the return is not financiall… https://t.co/bHnsnWPBOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ I didn’t think she’s be that type of person, buttt she’s that type of perssooon “ wtf ray 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruter24 @JMontana41 @Brewers Snake Eyes @Brewers @bruter24 @JMontana41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game Of Thrones “Tyrion Is A Secret Targaryen” Theory Explained (@nerdist News Edition) https://t.co/hPl8AYOHdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexevans42 @theginalinetti @mulaney It’s a lot LONGER than I remembered]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the GOP have any intellectual depth? They all seem to be low-IQ, low SAT people. Gym Jordan the best you got?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapefipeRaquel @betyzapi @kia_ra1 @Carmen_R2610 @alo_oficial Buen día 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBacho7 water sausage swims in chocolate is the headline we need today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the result of #CrissAngel 's sinister plan. A true sweetheart! Love him! Can't wait to see him again in Ap… https://t.co/Z9fQmmP283]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lrkappadee @RonnieW11 @tweetingclip But actually I got drenched and put my hair up for you. You know I don’t like my hair up😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course we would have a thunderstorm with hail 3 days after snow #KSwx #whatever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatorshoshana Okay but aren’t they cheap and good? That’s where I buy all of my sun dresses these days. No regrets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations again @KyleBusch on your 2nd win this weekend @ISMRaceway 🏁 And as always awesome job today… https://t.co/p1jq4xAHsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[let 👏🏻 trans👏🏻 athletes 👏🏻 compete  look at the science before you throw your bad opinions at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutterMartin Good Morning!! ☀️ It’s awesome weather today!! And Friday! Woo- Hoo!!😊❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fxp123 I guess that one jackass doesn't know black people or African American which doesn't cover all black people… https://t.co/iknRsB8gNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissPruddi Está cositas me matan de la risa. Quisiera cambiar incorporar esa línea a mi bio. Ja ja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump That is why we’ve levied big ones on China.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at his shirt lol,adorable @ThisIsRobThomas https://t.co/sjyIxr3EsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 12am my daughter hit me with the “ I can’t believe you won’t let me drink milk before bed no more it’s such a sh… https://t.co/QbR4qyKmFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino  that Joey bag o donuts Prob never picked up a pencil to do own tax return ever. What a dope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the last game of the season for Kyle @KyleGrill5 and the Maize JV team.  It’s been fun to see his game evolve.… https://t.co/SlpO6jtSbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I concur! @mccauliflower25 is pure heart in all that she does! I’m proud of you, @mccauliflower25 #blessedteacher]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Spencer with AbleDocs also spoke at the event. He says that accessible PDF’s is a business problem. #H11YHAM… https://t.co/0kRkFvmXXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My significant other is the @gmail robot that finishes my sentences for me in work emails]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanDavidRogers1 I do too David; loved traveling in those trains in my youth back in South Africa. 🚆🚉🛤️ https://t.co/MgDSXah0UJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[u people who a Taurus lowkey pressed nobody like y’all like that 😂 y’all are literally one of the worst signs 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird flex, but okay.   #WheresTheCottonCandyEmoji @ Universal Orlando, Island of Adventures https://t.co/BhWNkD3wax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston got Megan!! Dallas got ERICA BANKS!!! Okay honey period! Go AWWWF sis! 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBP  Americans insist u DEMAND that YOU tell Congress today that America DEMANDS FUNDING FOR OUR WALL..We insist u… https://t.co/m3kUw5Z8jF]]></document></documents></author>