<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[🍭🍬🍡 #candytopia #arwenkb #adventurean17 Arwen’s favorite part was the pink velvet rope outside 😂 @ Candytopia https://t.co/8hqtkQdulG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubydelacruz I don’t remember tbh but I think they were hybrids? N dude yes I’ll probably get them in the summer w… https://t.co/LlrC36hWMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling v strongly about another seasonal social media friends list purge https://t.co/Fw2CIeCGBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! @ Warwick Chiropractic &amp; Massage https://t.co/vx0YfQhIkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again @XfinityRacing you’ve made this west coast swing one for the books!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Interstate 605 at Exit 25 in Irwindale, CA https://t.co/31UZ5pr56g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fherval Wow!!!  @14_mc me puedes hacer favor de conseguirmelos? Al menos el del corazón please!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is way way too nice to people that do not deserve it and it takes A LOT for her to be bothered or mad at any… https://t.co/m4HIFe6uUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first weekend back in #Vegas and I’m sick 😷🤧why??? 😩😩I just wanna do is go out and do hood rat things with my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball @tedlieu He is NATIONAL SECURITY risk. Must include the word "national".  Messaging matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never play with the feelings of others because you may win the game, but you will risk losing the person for a lifetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. It's Friday. Could be a messy one, so be careful. Have a great day. God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who tf came up with this “vans challenge” ?! It’s annoyingly interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know it’s bad when you’re still too drunk to even drive to work at 4pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rboyd0105 @icehockeymike37 I’m with you there. Been thinking this since the Islanders game. Hopefully the players… https://t.co/hldanELOHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ten page paper for coffee is due tomorrow and I haven’t even started]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov  I Follow all #MAGA #SaveTheBabies #BackTheBlue #TEAMMAGA #Trumpville]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know who you might run into!  What a bonus on our campus visit! #CCleaders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a sweet notification for waiting list tickets for @STS9 @BellyUpAspen becoming available on the dice waiti… https://t.co/D2yvQuQ2t4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fleeting thoughts before sleep: why don’t I watch the west minister dog show?!? https://t.co/ViYfOYiJ9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Linda Landman Gonzalez for the lovely gathering to celebrate International Women's Day with leaders, stro… https://t.co/ezFyoXecaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think good women truly go unnoticed on social media, then you've been under a rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats @SpeakerPelosi @StumpforTrump @TrumpStudents @GOP @gopoundsand1234 @CNN @BreitbartNews @NBCNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Repeat, repeat...if you repeat it enough maybe they'll continure to believe you. Maybe they'll see… https://t.co/JfpBxuuPei]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have always loved Jeopardy and this man is a huge part of that love. Sending healing and good vibes your way, Mr.… https://t.co/RCc5TRYPys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody know when @Realdevinhaney next fight is. He is a good fighter]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Fillorian and honorary Fillorian are going to be doing some serious High Kingin’ tonight! 👑 All new… https://t.co/b0h3j2GZRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alive is a primer infused bright gold shimmer. 🌟 🌟 🌟 #spacer #surprise #surprises #makeup #makeupmafia… https://t.co/Eke3zDL1ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesavoie1978 1- Entre les draps de Dan Bigras 2- Mappemonde des Soeurs Boulay 3- Washed away de Five Finger death Punch 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Burt Macklin by @tpbeers at @TPBEERS — https://t.co/1meXWesMSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only buy @ShopprsDrugMart even more now bc #88OFF #givethepplewattheydeserve]]></document><document><![CDATA[3-point play completed by Yarbrough. Birds up 56-55. Under 4 minutes.  #SeniorDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger America knows. We stand with our President Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lordofparis You got this my friend! Kicking them is hard, but it’s the best thing in the long run! First bit is th… https://t.co/PvYLKzJC7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking the dog, cleaning the house, and playing Assassin's Creed Origins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be a guest of the @andoverrotary club this morning. An amazing club with energy and a can do… https://t.co/e0XjsxSiqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWTrump I just read this tweet as Donnie Trump ( president) not our colleague and was about to put you on blast… https://t.co/vFUMAFLyiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What draws us into the desert is the search for something intimate in the remote.  Edward Abbey  __________________… https://t.co/1EokOhm9kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @PressSec @realDonaldTrump You Hit That Nail Square On The Head !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticias24 Sinceramente el sicópata delincuente @jorgepsuv se merece q le pongan camisa d fuerza y lo Internen en… https://t.co/Z5Dky8AEEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Because I know lots of fed up people who want to secede from the financial mess those AMERICAN BANKERS made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lower Body Metabolic/Back/Core Workout.  Let’s Get it Done! @ Onelife Fitness - Rockville https://t.co/QqYIOQaqQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y asi sera, porque el olvido es una forma de pensarte, y aunque mi  corazón se sienta herido, no tengo mas remedio… https://t.co/MsgrrgXaDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried to myself and fixed myself over every fright or conflict I had this yr 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debiowens @Unfreakin In a word, yes. Trump supporters are that batshit crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Recomiendoleer PASIÓN POR LOS ENIGMAS, de la gran Escritora @aureagonzalez En #amazon  tienes la versión #kindle y… https://t.co/Hb5Q2kAt2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo much fun here man omg lol #wedding @ Doubletree Suites by Hilton Melbourne Beach Oceanfront https://t.co/XuGdWir4If]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much can you afford? #knowyouroptions #doyourresearch #callme #princetonpromise #princetonmortgage… https://t.co/Fub41zIx2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop praying for myself too much and start praying for others more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you so much @realDonaldTrump! We appreciate yours and your families sacrifice to help this c… https://t.co/dOhaOwZl4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matchity Is this similar to the underwhelmed and overwhelmed question. Perhaps you just like being whelmed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[😏 her lipstick shade was shade.   The @voguemagazine line originally about @MaxineWaters that never gets old.… https://t.co/pRf1yhtQ9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buttercoffee  #beautyrest #lifestyle #boomers @ Snellville, Georgia https://t.co/zurwSYbqCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though Ryder is on deployment, I continue to tag him in everything on Instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would sell my soul for a cherry citrus @rockstarenergy.... bring it back😢😭 https://t.co/y7PC0F2gyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/6FSlpJRuyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ohmygod wow ive never had this kind of connection with someone before nor have i ever actually dated someone where… https://t.co/Jn6fNUMs10]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the journalists that covered the Presidential election deserve a two-day paid holiday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best experiences of my life... swimming with whale sharks. (Excuse the bad photos) #WorldWildlifeDay… https://t.co/IJYoaLF6TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us on Thursday to educate lawmakers on what HB 426 does and Does NOT do. #HateFreeGA https://t.co/R89xQwrwZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson - Heal The World (Official Video) https://t.co/jspqEt74Gk via @YouTube 🙏😇❤️😎🎶🇺🇸🌎~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaGrantham2 Lily is just adorable! Max &amp; Beau are very lucky to have her around. 😍  She looks like she feels lucky too!🐾❄️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m crying Bradley Cooper is so beautiful #StarisBorn https://t.co/jMPzt48QtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@76_freddie @camilateleSUR @EmpireFiles Wow.  Agree - an empire puppet feeling a power rush.  I've seen that look o… https://t.co/2VC76TF5Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renegoupillaud @GOPLeader @RepGwenMoore @WaysandMeansGOP People want to be RESPECTED. Giving people a few extra ce… https://t.co/uUH2f8NE1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things are happening!!! Yayy!! @Avi_Kaplan @TheBasementNash https://t.co/gjiGGmVdv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totalmente de acuerdo! lo que hace el FrenteAmplio es imperdonable, el objetivo que tienen es la creación de depend… https://t.co/yV5bra4m7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateJacobson88 @orvisceo Wouldn't it be great if  someday there would be armed SPCA armed police to capture these… https://t.co/gtNf5iHzrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personally, I’m very proud of @Kaepernick7 for doing all that he did. C. Kaepernick held his ground longer than mos… https://t.co/euwluplhSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @FHSFlyers teacher Ms. Cunningham is on a mission to learn as much as she can about #LGBTQIA issues, using the FH… https://t.co/4H6QRWxoO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow But if she was a Republican democrats would be hollering and screaming for her removal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorTillis It is important to protect Americans and not supporting our President won't change ANYTHING that Oba… https://t.co/dUqz0OEKLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for pro-life. Probably slipping some kind of drug in the food. So insane but wouldn’t put it past the evil… https://t.co/LppG4In7Kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really fucking lame of god to hit me with my period on Valentine’s Day of all days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕴Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🌂Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/M04jZlis9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use a hairdryer once a month should I get this https://t.co/1p1IDhV5ZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank u @cbhatfield for opening my 👀 to the importance of building the capacity of our students through the develop… https://t.co/0hCvmVxzrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliDeplorable @ringod01 This Pope is not doing God’s work but Satan’s work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NutterCircus ACLU and now their newer arm SPLC was implemented to be the henchmen for the Dems to stop assimilatio… https://t.co/cqnxukYCUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next pregnancy I am strict eating . More fruits and veggies my ass was pigging the fuck out with kaiden]]></document><document><![CDATA[At every DJ we had at Easton in the gym we would all go so hard when dreams and nightmares came on😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaker: Happy #InternationalWomxnsDay! Audience: *weak applause   Speaker: y’all better wake up and clap because l… https://t.co/We7afrgVan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jumonsmapes @RachelBrods @emilioherce @natalieweiner Also @jennieo504 on jazz - she’s never on here but I loved he… https://t.co/o7BIbr7kxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won a pair of AirPods for taking this photo...  and I’ve only used them a total of 7 times since last May...  jus… https://t.co/mxaFWALEaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postmodernsperm I'm in between computers rn, I went back to my old computer that worked better lmao. Im about to get a macbook pro tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aoiferocksitout @karriehiggins If they did that to me I would flip them the bird and make sure they got a pic if that. Some people...smh 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_artiga @Vovchick22 @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton @AOC @IvankaTrump patients to have Medicare.  Many docs have stop… https://t.co/sIzBgdXk4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m a nicer person when I like my outfit.” #Emerald https://t.co/XqZCLQwlQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is fantastic on and off the court! #derbyproud #greenismagic #greenisfamily #uncommon #basketball… https://t.co/pMV0KUxvuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmaaaaariley You’re welcome! Definitely not suggesting not to check out some YA fantasy because honestly the age… https://t.co/EDI43Aex8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThoroStride @WinStarFarm @OBSSales One of my favorite colts from Rose Hill 2017 Crop. https://t.co/q072oTiRc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icycoldicelady1 It’s all good. Not from Texas but I live here now. Great folks here. Just some bad apples like any other state. Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do couples get good pictures of themselves together? Am I just bad at selfies or do I have to pay someone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good to there no hypocrites that are conservatives.  Oh, the guy you call your leader is the biggest hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeSlimedMe___ Naw, eff that. That is some The Perfect Storm shit right there, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katzyna @grizzlygirl87 @cariboukait @ewa_orlikowska @wailscn I absolutely have a whole file of traditional headsho… https://t.co/6OwSWo9edC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Daytona 500 pre-race show and my gosh it’s been a rough last few months in terms of people passing awa… https://t.co/VawOP4zF90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JharrisKevin @smcathletics @SMCWomensHoops Thanks for watching!! Was so much fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_papamarisa_ Marisa have a great today honey!!! You deserve it.  Your beautiful, smart and the world is yours!!!!… https://t.co/3kdt4b9VT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is my #ootd . Tonight we're going to a hockey game so I'm wearing team colors. #Hurricanes #hockey #selfie @ M… https://t.co/Jt5lwkrVAz]]></document></documents></author>