<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NickMcglashan @WickedTuna Heck yeah!!! How did you like the first episode?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me giggle. Appreciate learning. | The 23 Wisest Things Spongebob Ever Said #laughter #chuckle #smirk #funny https://t.co/uI6JSLZMgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got my black seed oil, sour sop and sea moss delivered to me 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching theme through music! #3rdgraderocks #identifytheme #music #makesthemmove #andlearn #happy #letitgo… https://t.co/YQtiLURani]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today!!! Free Home Show Tickets for your entire family!  Use this QR Code to get a whole family into the Home show… https://t.co/gpcBAH2Ozl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken723Ken @WisDOJ BeWARE!!! #WakeUpWisconsin #FreeBrendanDassey #FreeStevenAvery #GoToJailKen… https://t.co/o0pcExpuyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryangrim @Ilhan Scalise needs to learn HIS bio! It ain't pretty down her the boot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always tell myself that i will do my cleaning on Saturday so i have all Sunday to relax. But here i am, still in… https://t.co/nvwt2Naqey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @LionelRichie She has good energy...can't wait for Hollywood #AmericanIdol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AplusCR @jgrayatua @codeorg Computer Discoveries student @EufaulaCS 🎉 #WeAreECS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful! Great idea.  Could become an another economic driver for the area spurring tourism. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally what the fuck is wrong with you? YOU are what’s wrong with this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEWRENCHLEFT @GOPChairwoman @GOP @realDonaldTrump This is a comment only a total CNN brainwashed asshole would make]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, does it make a difference? It seems to be a group pic of All council Members]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone to look at me and show me the same kinda love my goddaughter shows my new godson 💯😩💕 #KayleeanahRose… https://t.co/0E6qATNMip]]></document><document><![CDATA[VOTE FOR #MyDurant TODAY AND EVERYDAY FEB 12-19 ✅ durantmainst @smbizrevolution 🙋🏻‍♀️🤗👏🏼🙌🏼 @ Durant, Oklahoma https://t.co/NxG3N690hN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucas_chiodo18 is back in the house tonight! Welcome back! 💙💛 @ Barrie Colts Game https://t.co/kEfenokkSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swillstosols @tannerJolson Are you guys getting a dog finally ?!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @lauferlaw I don't get the holding on part of some men and hair. Let it go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dreyaaaa Don’t play wit me I’m with the shits 😭😭😭😭 https://t.co/aVRPBvFpDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not scared of commitment, I’m scared to commit to the wrong person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobhoke74 @CoachKiotee Do you know if the South River girls game will be broadcast tomorrow on anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happened Tuesday night. So happy for these 2 men in my life. Stuck in Bend, Oregon. Hoping we can make it home… https://t.co/SkEnxVrnQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnolan49 Are those for Obama, his Administration (including Hillary-criminal, murderer, traitor &amp; liar?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work. - Thomas Edison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@79SemiFinalist Honestly I was just shocked. He’s also older than me too. It totally changed how I viewed him as a person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for the Emerging Contaminants Environmental Professionals Network (EPN) and spring Water Management Associatio… https://t.co/P2zrFFMvDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffries Trickledown economics has never worked. But, some are still able to peddle this bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to think that I’ll be living in a different state in a couple months, really can’t wait but life is going by too quick 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@recovery_rn .@AlisterFMartin Can you hear us? #GetWaiveredTX We look forward to your talk next week at #SASUS2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownWhovian It had special effects added to a still photo....pretty cool editing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comparada con NYC desde el aire se ve bien lo chiquita que es San Francisco! https://t.co/X2FJoYBWSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing Gerry Brooks this weekend, someone decided I needed pudding! I laughed so hard!! @gerrybrooksprin https://t.co/Ut2h4j8nGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that this is an actual role/team within a meditation company (🙌🏼🙌🏼 @Headspace). As a recent grad, my dream j… https://t.co/uyRXTGw3sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is absolutely NO reason that #UNCvsDuke should not be trending!!!!! For those of us that ~know~ it is the REA… https://t.co/YYBvnkzkm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 If I was not so busy laughing I am sure I could have found an appropriate comment. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please let me know when the hype over the Jonas Brothers is over so I can get back on Twitter, thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday I wake up contemplating if I should take a day and not go to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC NO actually Nancy Pelosi has already told us what you democraps do it's called smear wrap up campaign where yo… https://t.co/3VY1LPDbik]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a woman, I refuse to pay to get into the club right, I was late to my event tonight and they said I had to pay ,… https://t.co/jjecVQcida]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather for Sunday is really ruining the plans I had for my P!ATD concert outfit]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun at #candytopia with lilydemegs yesterday!!! #candy #moa #funwithkids #candyart @ Candytopia https://t.co/zBg2ThBm5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re going to the @billieeilish WWAFAWDWG SAN FRANCISCO show on May 29th dm please! Need lots of participation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga  I saw love in your eyes with Bradley Cooper I can’t wait to hear the announcement . I have watch you sin… https://t.co/si0dzwiG53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11ForTexas @LoriinUtah @AOC @battleofever @KatTheHammer1 @yogagenie @phillyeaglesfa1 @Hank63R @RealMAGASteve… https://t.co/VMcCA15D8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[this gonna sound weird but it’s for my drawing anyways the ouija board is so hard to draw and takes so long omg akks]]></document><document><![CDATA[First song in and this shit already fucking slappin’ @travisxthompson https://t.co/13P9puFy5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherylunderwood You look beautiful on @TheTalkCBS today!  Love those colors on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Codie and Tommy❤️ @blacklovedoc #blacklove https://t.co/BTgCJll636]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I just want my life to run as smoothly as the Chic Fil A drive through]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teach your children to confidence in themselves, not to doubt themselves, to trust themselve. Teach them to not lis… https://t.co/Q6uLbUVe4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope they all send flowers to your jobs today https://t.co/TZYQmKjlHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even afford to watch this video with my overdrawn bank account 😩 #TheStruggle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond proud of OHS senior, @_AlmaCooper_ who will continue making a difference at West Point next year!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We haven’t had a full week of school since December 😱 #nomoresnowplease #RIPtomylessonplans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tripletoes https://t.co/EQE2JpJ73x  !!! I found this accidentally a while ago, but I 100% agree that more people should skate to it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowe's is hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Click the link in our bio to apply: Sales Specialist Millwork #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up with your heart still lost in your stomach.. it’s a different kind of hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love having headphones in I can listen to a song 1000x and nobody can say a damn thing about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharonwaxman @acnewsitics @RoArquette For sure. I know who I'd rather live next door to. This young woman has class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#waterwalking Fun at the lake handelmanallen @ Skaneateles Lake https://t.co/hbvFClZ8u5]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all you wanna do is wear your Birkenstocks but God keeps MAKING IT SNOW https://t.co/VPSLvZ8xI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BernieSanders for having our backs! The momentum to move #BeyondBillionaires is building, and partnershi… https://t.co/oHOQ0q3av0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BQDuong_PGx @AmLyRichards @Publix @OBPBuzz Ben. Benjamin.  I miss you. But you live closer. And my love for Amber is Next Level™]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Her husband paid the piper so she can dance to the music. Hope she does better than her skill set would indicate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry fellow #allergy and #hayfever sufferers these#mulberry trees are about to pop! #epgardens https://t.co/VsgWkXXXQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cinnamon Toast Crunch cereal milk in my tea is a the best thing I’ve ever done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano How FAST THEY TAKE THE **TRUMP HATE BATE** .... IS SICKENING......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeidnerRoger @PastorDScott @Michael29149423 YES!!! U got it! EQUAL JUSTICE, for a change !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[JFK hired Robert ... who had been a member of the House on UnAmerican Activities committee... that must make the le… https://t.co/HYSJTAvU71]]></document><document><![CDATA[216 PHOTOS: LA Rec Sunday Kickball Fall 2018: Week 4 #VglSocal https://t.co/mWTh0EJicN https://t.co/lwCCqqwQRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shift in power from Joe to nick is the sexiest thing I’ve ever seen....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ihteshampatel @BDUTT @IPSMadhurVerma Sadly, the only thing would prob be to move their attention onto a different… https://t.co/x9YoW0f7j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anamariecox Absolutely and you could be considered racist for assuming white people wouldnt think that! When r peo… https://t.co/c4Dmg3B9fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexPatriotGirl https://t.co/xNLtKtRF5w Nurse at abortion clinic tells it like it is. Ppl have been killing babies… https://t.co/p3KImCy10s]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, @BillMaher we DON’T want to be you!!!                                          Bill Maher mocks Middle American… https://t.co/a6HGVpEUPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Or good night depending on where you are. 🐾🐉🐲🌵🎄🌲🌳🌴🌱🌿 #arianagrande #arianator #ThankUNext #sweetener… https://t.co/j5fZss285x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@in_pubs @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Roy Cohn could not prevent Joe McCarthy from being CENSURED by the Senate 67… https://t.co/4pdumJq0xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And she's back!  Cherry had a tail light out... Easy breezy right?  Wrong!  All LED lights with no way to replace i… https://t.co/RGD3mlYSD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicki_marieexo Why do they have to air out their dirty laundry like that 🙄🙄 these girls think they’re ballin’ now… https://t.co/8BAVVk8x1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone tries to do “Shallow” at karaoke and they are not me: https://t.co/zrmNqaL5cD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveStarley @Monique_PR_ @FoulkesBrau @Beachbabynorth @deoudehuize @WilfullyMe @BraaiWeather @BraaiBoy… https://t.co/jS596aAEDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw that coming.  #Potus45 is not so pro jew he would not sacrifice his son in law to save his own face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMHotFlash @mommamia1217 Meltdown?  Yeh, in his Crib.  Sounded like my four year old Grandson--Kicking and Crying-… https://t.co/AVB94R4eu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[How me and my future husband will do our vows:  https://t.co/C77My9fzKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer! #quote #quotes #quotestoliveby #quoteoftheday #quotesofinstagram #instaquotes #instagramquote… https://t.co/ZNHepMPU56]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember one time I was really drunk and sad sitting outside my apartments and I called jay and told him I needed… https://t.co/VeH3R11ozf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IStandWithIlhan and I’m not here for anyone who chooses to do otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phew! Just took in a very moving performance by an awesome cast featuring @OfficialSting ! Go and see… https://t.co/7xbEkGM8bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my girl trying out for MCHS Varsity today!!! You got this!! https://t.co/TCok2AdFQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch Thanks Tom for having our backs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i’m saying is, if you don’t know what is in your makeup or skincare - it’s time to get you some better products… https://t.co/S4k284QvTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy new year y’all! @cubs #baseballszn is underway! 👸🏻💚🐻⚾️ #gocubsgo #flythew @ Sloan Park https://t.co/wcP4aBPIun]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd period sophomores became actors and directors today. They planned and staged their interpretation of act 1 scen… https://t.co/GwVA0qXiVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does #Minnesota keep replaying the same winter movie?? ❄️😩  https://t.co/X43sxKmi6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[My throat hurts. Avriana’s party is in 6 days. I do not have time to be getting sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Looks like someone didn’t get breast fed as a child. 😂🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I should have skipped shoulders before an evening rehearsal! #goals #weights #workout #weighttraining… https://t.co/KtylWGnb2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaychris206 @reesewaters That was one of the funniest lines of that doc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any bets on rather he meets @deputyblanding in person before the show ends? 🤔 I want to hear this guy repeat his st… https://t.co/nXbzmoJ0FD]]></document></documents></author>