<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[comedy is good for the soul. #humor #tee-hee #smile #cute https://t.co/UX1JUVprFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some mirth. #mirth #giggle #smirk #farcical https://t.co/76UwyRidbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuafilmer Nevermind. I had to enlarge the image to see it. Beeeeernieeee!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The cross is all the confidence I need.  Your love won’t give up on me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey bitch if you want to stock my shit how about you tell the whole fucking story instead of assuming shit and quit… https://t.co/a65dVBMPDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I don’t wanna go back to school already 😭, this weekend shit is not it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@51stDC @MarkWarner @SenatorBennet @SenTinaSmith @ChrisMurphyCT THANK YOU Josh! For ALL of your hard work and for y… https://t.co/XMjRSsmgPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Ruby Singh @cruiseplannersruby for planning an absolutely perfect train adventure for our mom’s 80th Birt… https://t.co/c4F04e9aeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamal Jackson checks in for Sabis. He had a great defensive game in the semifinal off the bench. Bulldogs are likel… https://t.co/lyXc8PO2NX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSchulz Ok first off I’ve never heard of those hideous creatures in my 40 years of life, lastly that’s exactly… https://t.co/Kiyf9vuZGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Us. Hopefully we will be rid of him and some of the “taking the knee” bs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Library of Congress explains Baseball acronyms for visitors to it’s exhibit. #jargonhorn #acronyms… https://t.co/QVpFHuQUxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to keplersliteraryfoundation for a refreshing and #literary evening of readings by #newwriters!… https://t.co/SmZiaAwAaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self realizations:   1) I’ve become a competitive gym biatch rat 😱  2) I smell  🤑  3) I hurt my knee again (see #1)… https://t.co/RHpJvVdFtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little sister not supposed to be eating in her room she gone put the chips by me lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[“New knowledge is the MOST valuable commodity on earth.  The more truth we have to work with, the richer we become.… https://t.co/4lPyUzZO8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know! Track will do for now! They got 1st in the 4x200 Friday! Just wish he had more events. Love to watch all th… https://t.co/zu1jXpmrYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntoniaNia28 @ErickBrianColon Esta due la primera vez q hiceron tour en EEUU. Siempre están en sur America digo yo. Ahora se van a Europa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mudslide on I-24 EB this morning at MM 40, just north/west of Briley Pkwy in Nashville.  Traffic is being diverted… https://t.co/14Y94A2FCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motivate Me charms #Spring Sale!!! Grab one for you or for a friend. https://t.co/RXKIQjSbBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleebb21 Bourbon. I try so hard, but I don’t think it’s gonna happen. https://t.co/kbTlrYSByo]]></document><document><![CDATA[All caught up with @CrimeJunkiePod soooo im moving on to @MyFavMurder   Because I can't not listen to a true crime podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theapplenut В следующий раз сниму видео, как ты уляпываешься в розово-малиновой краске, пока красишь мне волосы по… https://t.co/rx4tDbpEYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all go through it, hope this helps one of you going through it right now 🙏❤ https://t.co/KuGMbuYzlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we walk and let out our Pyrs in the cold and rain tonight in the Carolinas, we wish we could be visiting CGPR al… https://t.co/dliewj1Oxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey moms and dads check out this quick video from Pastor Blake and Mrs. Cathy!           Send your testimony to Sup… https://t.co/o3b6slsQJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to meeting some amazing people at #sxsw especially fellow #WomenInSTEM #BlackTechTwitter… https://t.co/LL8iRSYNxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Château frontenac à Québec city 🇨🇦 10 heures de travail 🥵 #draw #drawing #dessin #quebec #canada #dots #line… https://t.co/8fr0j7feOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acgme @CarolBernMD Well deserved award to @CarolBernMD for changing how residency and fellowship programs around t… https://t.co/ip7bOZ3P7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to fall asleep but this #killercouples episode is just getting good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rekoobb @Guggenheim I certainly am inspired to continue painting my feelings rather than what sells again now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly 60+ year old white men don’t know how to manage Universities or countries, so why the fuck do we keep putting them in power?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel this deeply with regard to my chronic illnesses. Really helps put things in perspective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[cutest video ever!!!  😭🤧 the way she was trying and being patient and then getting super excited and hugging her mo… https://t.co/KhABdmlBhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matty_WanKenobi Bill Russell would of abused Shaq, JMO, Matty don't get so mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentsaner @criener @ZachG932 Because of a situation he did not cause? The sub was fired. THIS kid was arrested! I… https://t.co/Sgld7le0aY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rip Actress Katherine Helmond of 'Who's the Boss?' and 'Soap' dies at 89 https://t.co/wsi4sIA391]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debreveles @PetersColonyES @PCCounselors @CCEJenschke It’s all he talked about this evening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have my internal “know before you go” meeting today in preparation for @WFFHQ #WFFCONF. What are your pre confere… https://t.co/2PFoViqIoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the town of Straight and Narrow,  There's a dark and misty place.  Everything is hazy,  So the people are afraid… https://t.co/nO4erdaOze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no but God is The Healer Always, he gotcha and you are always in my/our prayers!!! Heads ☝ at all time! Believin… https://t.co/4mIsZTrbGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost librosyversoss with get_repost ・・・ Y de repente. . . . . . #amore #reflexiones #instafrases #ella #vida… https://t.co/lTIOXsIkDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trumper1620 Is this a joke? A spam tweet? I mean, it’s like the onion right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t I just tweet Kamala Harris without annoying trump supporters trying to debate me like go away please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day my love!!! #Valentinesday #myvalentine #blessed #Godissogood @ The Cheesecake Factory https://t.co/fYd5bVz7cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My top 10 United States Twitter trends... 9 for Pokemon stuff and 1 Cohen.  Really America? https://t.co/EGM56QvwER]]></document><document><![CDATA[We came in with 350 little tufts and are going home with two (unless someone spots me at LAX). Had a great time mee… https://t.co/7uuGt62H4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[are u supposed to leave ur eyes open or closed while getting ur teeth cleaned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmmcopeland @Andrea31762 @NKCSchools @JeremyMontague @MoAESP Awesome! 👏👏 Did you know he’s a singer too?? He us… https://t.co/V4BzxnSdxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol you know you’re head banging correctly if you lose balance while doing it 😂👽 #headbanger https://t.co/EOz7iabn5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter storm grounds more than 1,000 US flights, airlines waive change fees - https://t.co/DnmAH5yBTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[♒️ A Q U A R I U S ♒️ . . ➡️ FOLLOW @lauracristinax (me) for more! 🥰 . . ‼️ New posts every single day around 6pm P… https://t.co/9KkkFIUCK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hype song of the morning! #kpopinhouston #kpopintexas #boss #jaypark #hypemusic  https://t.co/0ZKc3JrCMt https://t.co/RBiDhRVRsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurelCarlson33 @reagan80mom1 @Toniraebenedic1 @JohnBrennan @HillaryClinton Hope you like your health care - and no retirement etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory I didn’t know that his space occupying lesion between two ears could think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I can't believe it is really happening. I am going to say good bye to a job I've had for 13 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed with this song.   Listen and dive into the words.   #songoftheday #hopelessromantic #backstreetboys… https://t.co/WfwWBfRXN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit the water for Sudan Website .  There are several resources and videos. Some of the videos of Salva may be a h… https://t.co/Xo5yHGRwkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to Trevor, his relay team, and the rest of the Titan qualifiers in sectionals today! It’s been a fun seas… https://t.co/xjKrn4l36l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning light at @RoyseContemp ! Come explore @toofangskinny latest collection #bothdirectionsatonce today! We are… https://t.co/ffWvWlCoLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having your manager hold down your station while you go to the bathroom&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aunque parezca insólito pero ahí está la evidencia. Más claro no canta un gallo https://t.co/BM3xvsmhsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liz Story recommends great books like Eye Spy Wild Ways Animals See the World  #mra19 Kids are going to love the wa… https://t.co/kJe9KpQkfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just made me blow water out of my nose. What a gift and a curse to have been a tween during the Twilight Era ™️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i forgot i accidentally subscribed to Shudder for an entire year last april and i haven’t fuckn used that shit since]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love and light to all hurting today from the #ParklandShooting . People all over the world are thinking of you.   T… https://t.co/1U5ifjoBoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @brian_littrell YOU deserve to have a great day! 💜💜 #HappyBirthdayBrian I cant waist to finally hug… https://t.co/FWTup8vKLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[U ever be like "hm I wanna tweet about this relevant topic or correct this persons tweet" but u know all ur fake wo… https://t.co/QXbnl1SdB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This seems like a good time to remind everyone I came out of a screening for the Darkest Hour and Mendelsohn was st… https://t.co/we9SUuobW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not being held in DC this year, rather Denver. Great program grad students - apply by March 1!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theycallme_cas Right. And most times they stay with "the shit" boyfriend anyway. Talk about low self esteem...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond grateful and thrilled to announce that Lingua Franca is one of only 4 fiction features to be awarded the gra… https://t.co/QXDxJPrZEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Probably about the same as when they realize that infanticide is acceptable in our society. "Can yo… https://t.co/Jrp0YefwRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let the bones fool you, my love for animals is my strongest quality, and has been since I was a child. At thr… https://t.co/YdyHmy72Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickerySec @tedcruz They don't want this investigated because they don't want the gravy train to stop. They alread… https://t.co/TgrTtNuJiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update:  they came back this morning and asked for $20.  I’m now an easy target for them AND they doubled their pri… https://t.co/NUncjic7XI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottaLaff Look at that wide mouth jerk. All those DUI's got to Gaetz's brain cells.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lunarheritage @KWAHS @holdengraber @keywestlibrary @DannyShookVideo @EricdeMarylebon @MontyGreylock @michele0511… https://t.co/OMfTLAIQFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[· we're cute sometimes. i'm lazy all the time. ·                 #ARMYSelcaDay #ARSD https://t.co/as2mNBHsPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamriel1776 You should also have a playlist called “Wind Guide You” that was recently updated to have more song.… https://t.co/2GHn6ZVkgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next:  Torres HS Varsity softball to end Jelly’s day yesterday: Jocelyn, Haily , Luz, Bella and Stephanie.  Great y… https://t.co/3xRRMgxjFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PacNorthProud #HD1044 #SafetyISPersonal #club365 Super Proud of this Team! Safety is a choice. Thank You!… https://t.co/UvaLisKoft]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are here for the Joy and Thirst of learning. Thank you, @CotsenAoT @_JulieMitchell_ @RascalPride @RowlandEdTech… https://t.co/LoFHIS6mxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAAAAAAS 🎉🎉 So proud of this project! @SafeCemeteries you got a shout out, this project couldn’t happen without you… https://t.co/gTifCBGp7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsMichael 🙄 I didn’t give UP mine, I just meant we’re starting OURS today. Asshole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[dude i imagine people w flat feet walking around just high five’ing the floor bare foot 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Journo_Christal That sounds bad. So.....his pals Donald and Roger knew he was this bad, but still let him run the campaign....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Listed in #Hartland #WI. N92W31300 Hoff Rd! Please retweet!  https://t.co/lLTZ6N3rX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally to a point in my life where i realize that if people truly wanted to be in your life &amp; be an actual friend, they would be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueSerioFox29 @FOX29philly  Snowing in Landenberg PA just started ❄️ https://t.co/XDmljbdbV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Isn’t odd how he has at least two sealed felony indictments for stealing the election via… https://t.co/5lOazErYOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanitaylor I got your book yesterday and finished it tonight. Couldn't put it down! I'm so proud of you and yo… https://t.co/8gV200O8In]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost didn't buy this #sweater... cuz I don't really wear #sweaters.. but I did and I'm #happy cuz #ifeelpretty… https://t.co/fmtGK80LWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support @Squanathon All of the proceeds go to families whose kids are fighting life alerting diseases!!! #FTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlygirlsguide I am 10 months out now. I tapered 25% a month for 7 months after 15 year use. I have protracted wi… https://t.co/leplgAZWd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I initially was angry that they got rid of the lemon sandwich cookies and replaced them with the Savannah Smiles (w… https://t.co/3G4mOuVOQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC Good for Lisa R ,butt is rattled , he is happy now to answer gentle queries from Colin F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaDzhaketov Me at brunch last time when you said “it’s in my name” &amp; I thot you meant your Christian name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Struggling with liking my body since I’ve been out of the gym for a month. Even with a supportive partner, it is ha… https://t.co/dSn5QYAXfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who I met at the RV park that I'm staying at the Thousand Trails Peace River my DDV Fanatics? It's Steven Thom… https://t.co/4zHa6uwE4m]]></document></documents></author>