<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[this guy comes up to you and whispers “i like em big i like em chunky” in your ear, wyd next? https://t.co/8cFjQAiEGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirderTori Truly ridiculous. But hey, rack up some frequent flier miles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many students at my school who never take responsibility for their actions. Your actions have consequence… https://t.co/XIgfZSZFAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stassi Have you seen Cash App? Try it using my code and we’ll each get $5. PVXDKBL  https://t.co/iQiEASHqvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a powerful story. Unbelievable this can happen. Respect @Enes_Kanter for not backing down]]></document><document><![CDATA[When work is fun! Thanks to Amy Scott for contributing this gem! #b2b #Marketing #AFFEXinAction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shakty_Miranda I feel physically ill after watching this and the fact that people still use “retard” as an insult makes me extremely angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[♡ ♡ ♡ #bbwgram #cutebbw #bbwbabe #effyourbeautystandards #lovetheskinyourein #beautiful #beauty #gorgeous… https://t.co/9FTd28VvvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continued prayers for their families, friends, &amp; community. #parkland #msdstrong #parklandstrong #lives… https://t.co/yIVZBHekst]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s tonight guys!!! can’t wait to see all your faces 🥰  18+ is actually 10$ before 11 and 20$ after  but i have ro… https://t.co/b3NKfSa9wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[will I ever make it on time to my 8am this semester? the world may never know]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it!! Super excited for @spaceykacey !!! #snowinglikecrazy #happyandsadatthesametime #forgetgoldenhour… https://t.co/7HY1sd9aOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoRodNews Los venezolanos para ellos somos nadie!!! El usurpador y su combo odia a los venezolanos... por alg… https://t.co/0cZVmKQO1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Game Highlights vs Easley  by Destiny Middleton on @hudl https://t.co/vmZDUoCaGf #hudl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholasFerroni #Iwishmystudentsknew how much I truly enjoy teaching them. After 30+ years, they still bring me jo… https://t.co/7gbtlOyQFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s context to everyone’s pain. You can’t just look at someone as bad or good. Be open to their story and tole… https://t.co/XzZlTHr84n]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being 19 almost 20 &amp; still havin your mom fight your battles :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyricalarrow #DontMindMeImJustWatchingArrowAndShippingOlicity #Arrow #Olicity https://t.co/pdjiwfSU74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I finished early at my moms apartment. My brother said that he’d do the rest and I have to believe he will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you manage to me irritate me at this time of night... you’re an ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Canadian_Jay @HockeyCentraI @Prospects_Watch How amazing would this be if he actually did smash him in the face tho?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for perfect skin? Call for your NuPerfect Derma Peel appointment today and reveal NuSkin that’s flawles… https://t.co/DW1bhEwF3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let nothing be done through strife or vainglory; but in lowliness of mind let each esteem other bette…… https://t.co/kWuWAQ1Ck8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickerySec one hashtag as payment to lay this little diddy down.. #CruzThis...ok..so I never know if people are hu… https://t.co/RVUjtrFMYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[SLANDERING ME BECAUSE YOU GOT TURNED DOWN 40 YEARS AGO NUMSKULL IS JUST PLAIN STUPID.  YOU ARE NOT MY TYPE, AS I DO… https://t.co/ltkaQju4Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim Horton's card rather than Starbucks.  I know they're no longer Canadian-owned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeLightly @Tracie0313 @rose33090 These days there is no empathy or caring as much as I hatred 911, we were togeth… https://t.co/m2HPlVtVPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodyWyatt2 @mrcrockpot @Bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBINSIDER_ He never said Harper was signing with Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think the birth control i’m on gives me terrible attitudes. my attitude rn is bad i dont even wanna speak to anyo… https://t.co/4LO7xDF85n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexi_amy Interested to hear what you think. I definitely have Opinions about In-N-Out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mata_tausch @anthonysoler9 @Beverly96602100 @AlyssaM70687116 @cmascorro14 @PattyHe14648229 @emilyrho Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@perrybellegarde repeats what he said when Indigenous Languages Bill was introduced: “Royal assent.” Notes 4 month… https://t.co/VQZeze5sDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wonder why i don’t have a good body as i lay here eating cookies at 1 am :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mercedes Benz stadium looks like a huge scary monster with all this fog and rain and just parts of the top stic… https://t.co/tdsrKytSJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_gothest It depends on a lot of things for me. I have a lot of dvds. Sometimes, I like the semi restored VHS ri… https://t.co/CAwmQsVR7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is the #ActualEmergency. Sign the petition to tell Congress to revoke his emergency declaration:… https://t.co/A0v7TOO6WA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been all this time traveling to Ohio &amp; finally enjoyed RocknRoll Hall of Fame!! Loved it!! #musicislife https://t.co/xQPaDT7T5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[But let’s take away funds that are supposed to go to military housing and built a racist wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We love 💕 you Mr and Mrs Trump! Thank you for Making America Great @realDonaldTrump you call it li… https://t.co/n3yeIYoLtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[First breakfast in #pdx! Salt &amp; herb bagel with smoked peppers smear and chai latte https://t.co/qEICwbR9bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @iTunesTV I am now the proudest owner of my favorite movie EVER, #fromjustintokelly. My bad week is about… https://t.co/ZCLxAeJTsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I’m always gonna do is gas people up. Ain’t nothing wrong with celebrating success and wanting your people to succeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psyched to see @SuperBaston highlighted in @NECN series #SheThrives! She inspires and continues to pave the way for… https://t.co/jQ2iHscmrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cream Cheese Blueberry Puff Delicious  #desert #lunchtime #delish #delishious #columbus @ Olesya's Kitchen https://t.co/JuM1PaSqvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother would be appalled but I will be #gardening in my jammies today with my fabulous bed head! #mytrueself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave Bizarre demotrash make up lies about Pres Trump.  Want anyone to vote every where. Will they bring Put… https://t.co/Arvok4uYDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[RSVP TO: https://t.co/bxIQok1dDb to see the fb live event at 7pm bc of the cancellation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh yessss🙌 I don't like to do fancy valentine's or anything so this was the perfect gift idea for @finbegin this y… https://t.co/Q3aIQkrTTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever ain’t forever so be my baby until whenever ! &amp; if we ever go left just be my friend until we back together ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graceb369 @nushnushhhh @krrazykat 😧 another freaking weekend of FOMO ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bruce_LeVell @realDonaldTrump @DiamondandSilk @VivianChilds @day_gardner @AA4TRUMP That is so cool!! Say hi to Diamond &amp; Silk for me!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great campaign in our local schools!  #BrilliantBoldBeautiful 👩🏾‍🎓🦸🏽‍♀️👸🏾  @CBSU_UIUC  @SalongoPAR @ewezo_uiuc… https://t.co/9jLTAcdDbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MzCristinaMaria @hcsunshine_ i have oily skin but only bake when i’m going to an event! also, mine never turns out… https://t.co/w9Rq10Msdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a dog I’d never met before stop and wait for me to come up to him and pet him. I feel the love 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bold - A Lagree Fitness Studio - @bold_studios in Berkeley, CA https://t.co/w4Z7V7Zilc https://t.co/cqwF3NFWK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CashNextDoor Ughhhhhh i needed this for my brunch look tomorrow im really over it this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[i came downstairs in sweats and a hoodie and my mom was like “you look cute!” and i was like “NO I DONT??? WHY ARE… https://t.co/Qg81CAn5lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t Colton know that snitches get stitches? #TheBachelor #BachelorMonday #Bachelor #BachelorNation https://t.co/2IHkzIaCJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s that???? Lupita!!!!!!! Why is she 7 rows rows in front of me???? She is so gorgeous *swooning* #sxsw… https://t.co/hSvFxpBfn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyOFay @dearsusanbranch That's terrible! At least she couldn't take your memories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpitfireAN Meu Deus e a moda está pegando , onde se vai parar com esses jovens desgovernados pq sabem que não vai acontecer nada !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews He lied last time what made u think it wld be different this time? He played you...again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnragedApostate @Richardwaldo1 @dogcanyon @cspanwj @NatlPopularVote If you look at history and the fact that, at t… https://t.co/KXZOhahHww]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #Team90210 on @TyltEnt—#90210 is my favorite primetime soap ever https://t.co/2InSNbj4uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tonight I decided to have an apple instead of ice cream and I can comfortably say that I would’ve rather had ice cream...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen também diz que Trump sabia e orientou negociações sobre construção Trump Tower em Moscou durante a campanha e… https://t.co/NOGiJUWXEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I am nobody and Jesus is real but not anyone here now.  This and me was all a setup for the antichrist and f… https://t.co/Y8t0vwJdCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW @KevinOGarrett I’M SPEECHLESS 😭🙏🏻 #hoax #dontrush ANOTHER MASTERPIECE🗣 https://t.co/Zs35uw4d64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camhardy513 @RayshonMack @CincyMegsGOP @IamCPS @CityOfCincy @mike_moroski @CoachOzie @OHDems @JudgeWinkler… https://t.co/t6KyHFUiHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs I think the rest of us would much rather talk about your deal to rush shipments of nucle… https://t.co/1phwGlWdh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Me! I've mostly used my skills for costumes over the years - not really for "regular" clothes. I'm… https://t.co/CpszlKCW5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Former FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe doubled-down on ABC News' "This Week" over his insistence tha… https://t.co/9CdXXgqhsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowayjeff Right below Baylor too??!!!  I live in a college town, KSU, so yeah.  Trees must be wonderful there too lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayeskiMark @tommy_thayer @KISSOnline @genesimmons @PaulStanleyLive Pobres de Los Viejos ellos no lo pueden entend… https://t.co/RFirSw2GAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of note, in that discussion we should go much deeper. Rare disorders require the same development steps and can be… https://t.co/zew8zz2n5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @PoloOrtiz9 @confessions_cup @TW2CayC @cazij @JustJane2019 @JustMyTweet @melanie_korach @JackConnie… https://t.co/nWBPPK0a3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies in the town n country area! Where are some good places to get my brows threaded?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoMartelle @stradlemonkey @Biggybadass @Brooksidefilms @Mark_Lapping @KITTKARR83 @dfeague @elecporcupine… https://t.co/nVWpu01A76]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doughnut let me catch you not scanning!!!! @NP_UPSers @JaradZimmerman @UPSers @UPS_NP_IE @JohnVPeters @SophieKich G… https://t.co/uJC2QZIDWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is calling the colors and colors for you. I was born into the first snow day of my life. My age is a bit of… https://t.co/xlg9iPR6vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No matter what anyone outside of the border states think .we need a wall.i invite you to come stay… https://t.co/BsJ8A1IfZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesslanai552 @ava @ThePerezHilton @TheAcademy The only movies worth a theater visit= giant spectacles like Black P… https://t.co/j9NkbTiJhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilosParrots @Talkmaster @theleveloftime @JohnMorganESQ Time to leave Illinois.  I did 30 years ago and don't regret it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A math problem should not look familiar. are we teaching students to do a certain type of problem or to be mathemat… https://t.co/eKwY5DoaXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I came in tha game been a REAL ONE... &amp; ain’t nun change cuz I’m still one 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch so cold on me 🔥🔥🔥🔥  Prod by okay.jones x Me @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/WQtGCeEyeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically if you’re raised in a super fucked up way you’ll probably be fucked up and/or if you’ve experienced somet… https://t.co/IEOQSI7g1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to adjust your clocks one hour ahead tomorrow! #SpringForward #DaylightSavingTime #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/XwRrTS7mZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You don't make any sense. How are you going to accuse Trump for conspiring with FOREIGNERS TO "INFLU… https://t.co/1vMOZSngwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. So true. But y’all @Pink is coming to Columbia this week and I’m like 😬😩🥰😎🤩🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the beach and I’m feeling really happy 💛 https://t.co/RjcnbEFeyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Diva Spot Beauty Bar/Events https://t.co/E6ejf6by9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good lord Virginia basketball is just so pretty. 😍😍😍 #UVAvsCUSE #Wahoowa @UVAMensHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY DOUBLE IS BACK😻😭 im not going to stop until all my goals are reached... no matter what. @ Cheer Athletics https://t.co/TqAyeH1BLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the type of journal that will make people not trust the peer review process. What person in their right min… https://t.co/48F3EhaOxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sockacat @LPDOfcMeade Look closer at the bullets in the cylandier and other specifics of the gun]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s our leader! @Mar4Smith @ORBoysBball @ORSchools  https://t.co/9E0bF8UUUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissLyds77 @RadioYeg @AM900CHML Thank you for your support. You are correct. The current “restorative justice” tha… https://t.co/bkatTIxXR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ve peaked in life. I finished my conditioner and shampoo at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Right back at you, Bernie!  You’re a Loser &amp; a Traitor!]]></document></documents></author>