<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I miss playing @paizo #Pathfinder and reading the comics with it. I always thought that those tie in books and audi… https://t.co/KDi0CVWksd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit. A follow-up on that last MW2 tweet.  The game itself is older than the majority of Fortnite players. 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#model #actor #hideandseek #champion #nobody #ever #check #in #the #trees #inner #monkey #use #it #or #lose #it @ S… https://t.co/Pr3z71ZFuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbeAbbott4 @TalibKweli @junotjoyner @AmericanIdol Then he posts this. Dudes a coward and a homophobe. https://t.co/HmNRulIDje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add this to the list of other misdeeds to get her and her friends out a here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that with a simple software update you get more and more features! Tesla is way ahead still of other… https://t.co/q4xdjv6YAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and "The Girl On Fire" Impact Wrestling and WOW star the amazing Kiera Hogan @HoganKnowsBest3 #impactwrestling… https://t.co/l1dt69Ij1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racerbluegold We were needing some rain. The mud was starting to dry out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawniesblood @thnkuariana @intotun @arianavxntii Did you try charging it in the microwave geez 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLinero Amen, tus mensajes y oraciones la mejor manera de comenzar el día y fortalecer nuestra fe para esperar lo… https://t.co/Zo1yodvZ4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[People commenting on Twitter don’t know anything about the thing they’re commenting on? You don’t say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodfoster The fact that the black person allowed themselves the be a prop is a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyCorben @JoeCarolloNow @BallAndChainBar Who the hell keeps voting for this guy? Those are the real enemies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong seasonal in corn kicking in. May corn over the last 15 years has rallied about 11 1/2 cents from Presidents… https://t.co/MSjalUSoK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmorfina Se ve, y sobre todo, se siente.  En circunstancias de crisis, la clase media resulta siempre la más afect… https://t.co/81lWzHbLs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is setting your alarm for both of u to wake up hella early, and not being able to stop talking with her till 1am]]></document><document><![CDATA[And who’s the muthafucka that said “yea, everybody needs to know all these math topics, cause they’re soooo important”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyrieskamp Ride or dieee🤞🏽🤞🏽 thanks babygirl i love you 5ever and can’t wait until i see you again 🤪🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leahgreenb @goldengateblond Yep.  This needs to be said again and again every month or so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning - Drinking a Doug Things by @CycleBrewing @ Cycle Brewing  — https://t.co/BbZWvAkZMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in the City of Gilbert  It must be Opposite Day! https://t.co/KkegNUEZ9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlevate @AOC There are so many things I could say. I won’t. I’ll just keep you safe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update - I spent 3 days on a cover letter and eventually applied. Now ima message a girl who works there who's help… https://t.co/8C86wInk6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must seek to understand how excellent teachers think. There is no program, acronym, or technology that can exceed that.  #VisibleLearning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartitaAlanis Bowl* bowel is what you’ll be doing to that poke in 6 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VainPretense @Isles_Life Is it a bad take b/c he doesn’t share your opinion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate saying goodbye. One of the things I never like about the military. People leave and that’s the reality of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cards that make up your #mtgdna (should've used all rna cards, but what can you do)  First card you remember being… https://t.co/7Aeeo8P8R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/t2llVXsZlF 🛑Criminal, unfit liar, fakenews Trump is a puppet sell-out to Putin of Russia and Saudi's.T… https://t.co/E8qthZXrCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this why I gotta pay $400 for insurance because these dumb ass niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[JCPS postpones ACT testing as it watches for a possible teacher 'sickout' https://t.co/TDOLeWmxLH via @courierjournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Valentines Day! Hope you waste your money well!! Remember you should be this loving all year long...… https://t.co/HUxDUX0EgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[trump is OC and have no real plans, he has been exposed for the scum bag that he is, he’s a idiot and every time tr… https://t.co/eAvTDR1nWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just deactivate and sit out the rest of the season #LakeShow @Lakers https://t.co/ZnyBJIPKTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that’s a wrap for amplifyatx: $11,221,087 raised by 30,849 of our neighbors for 746 Austin-area nonprofit organ… https://t.co/pnuOrygM5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highest lunch ever? (@ Vista Haus - @breckenridgemtn in Breckenridge, CO) https://t.co/ao9yXZgKgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connecticut Attorney General William Tong says state will “aggressively pursue” claims against Purdue Pharma despit… https://t.co/RE8E05scff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaE6969 "You can burn up my clothes, smash up my ride...well, maybe not the ride" One of my all-time favorite @prnlegacy lyrical lines!  💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gorgeous white sand dunes national monument of New Mexico @ White Sands National Monument https://t.co/xc9oq1RQFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcapaldi28 Yo keep your head up girl, you way too cool to be sobbing! https://t.co/jnk3Y12G54]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP #KeithFlint. The Prodigy - Firestarter (Official Video) https://t.co/FK5x0nnZzv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man says Michael Marks wouldn’t have been shot if police were armed.  Says he talked to several students and t… https://t.co/PTAQs3lYel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CjDig86 @ufc @Ruthless_RL You’re beginning to embarrass yourself. https://t.co/NjYh2MDnWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maq_atelier @slutsaucekhloe You some hatter patter Why don’t you go on down to waffle house with them hashbrowns]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a simple game. You use this things at the bottoms of your legs to play! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most important thing is that Zion is not hurt for not just our season but his future. But damn if we don’t lear… https://t.co/rk1r0Xh9od]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaperRecycles How about recycling your paper pulp to go back to your Broke chest instead of to the Kalamazoo river… https://t.co/O4xww0K8cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foone Bad news... GameStop is the literal result of those two chains merging. There are a few Software Etc. locati… https://t.co/sR7lFWL0xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA FAN THERAPY: A Tough Week For Boston Sports https://t.co/BkDrLegQpy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLBravesGirl12 Bryce started out asking 10 years at $425 million. Now it’s south of that. 💵💰⚾️⚾️ https://t.co/a31sdZ9tJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bencasnocha Noise (or lack-thereof I should say!), is astonishingly pleasing 🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRDandelionJack @mrjohnsontchs @TCHS_Booster Timber girls are currently in first with 65 points and Central is tie… https://t.co/3qww8la5br]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean yeah he trash obviously but how do you even get involved with someone like that in the first place? Lol like… https://t.co/1HpGJkxsGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @_sallyxsquirt @GentleLilBird @JessikaGotti @Maxx_attax @x_summers @JennaIvoryxxx @AliciaSecret… https://t.co/ThAylXgtBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former US counterintelligence agent allegedly spied on colleagues to help out Iran, indictment reveals… https://t.co/r9chQdQX6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd Now I feel good that, the few times I did a dumb, at it was pointed out, I apologized. Do I win the Twitter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Trump doesn’t care who you sleep with, he wants to protect our country Foriener and domestic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Chuckie16 This race baiting and horribly bad argument never get old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the #Epcot news and the #Ghostbusters news the only thing it confirms for me is that straight white 80s-kids m… https://t.co/QsWAm7iuwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Pot called. He said you the kettle are black.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta read about 5 chapters today. Already read one this morning I love reading 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uninterrupted @THEwillieCS15 @SacramentoKings This man said I ain’t never seen D Rose! What? Are you 10?! The fuck?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine a car crashing into your bedroom while you were asleep! That happened to a Madisonville couple overnight. I… https://t.co/PtHJ0DX22s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahTheRebel Don’t ACK like you ain’t loved. I know you got friends in your corner. You want me to Uber eats you some food over there]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News Alert:    California AG Xavier Becerra to announce results of his Stephon Clark investigation      V… https://t.co/XoB6bmEmAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way @indianambb would lose with Zoe celebrating birthday number 12 with, by far, the best diving program in the… https://t.co/3L8h9hqt4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonS302 @arklep1989 @BrianDawkins @Bharper3407 @Phillies You're the WORST kind of fan. You complain and talk tra… https://t.co/sXjkkT3azO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glassdoor just announced the 100 best places to work for 2019 (is your company on the list?) @bizzwriter https://t.co/oL09hHlc1z via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clyda95 No doubt. Like I hear it. I blackout and almost cause an accident on the road then come to my senses and i… https://t.co/twkx8B20Ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin but I discovered and Angelica two things I never believed in until I met her. Soulmates and true love… https://t.co/Hex2eF1iaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdsu 23 and add Shrimp Poboy at Domilise's Po-Boy &amp; Bar, the Oyster Poboy at Smitty’s in Kenner and pizza at Gio’s in Metairie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyRoseNC How did I miss a bingo opportunity? I’ll settle for a great night at all county chorus for middle schools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmSocram I’m wishing you condolences. Also, in my experience you don’t quite get that version of you back. You le… https://t.co/upuEZI156K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I smoke I get yikes goggles. I see everything in terms how yikes shit is. Like damn that shit is yikes. ✍️✍️ https://t.co/7PP4tSMouR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be on this stacked lineup main headliner hasn’t even been announced yet thank you @oneawesomenight https://t.co/V7qI6IWLF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WVUhoops Brighter days are ahead.  Keep the effort and the wins will come.  Need to work on outside shot and free… https://t.co/DeQCkwUnTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg You would be smarter if you heard what the Republican party has to say about socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NandovMovies Yo Ali gots two oscars in the last three years fkn amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to tweet my dog shit on my pillow 4 days about .5 centimeters away from my head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shayne_hope Says the guy who moved east. 😂  (PS. I’d expect this kind of comment from @Lacytalks... I thought you were better than this).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time off is nice, except for the going back to work part. 😂😳😭 Good morning folks! Happy Wednesday. It is Wednesday,… https://t.co/Cmfsc65s75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @CalHospitals for featuring @interfaithcs partnership with local hospitals and health plans to help a Vet… https://t.co/fHIZbAYxMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawndunbar81 @ABC You're definitely a Russian operative https://t.co/KJbQkVuFzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My growing distaste for politics - summarized here https://t.co/dufz2TIU56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger teams for everything. Where’s the SWAT team for a business? Strategy, execution all rolled into a single quar… https://t.co/z6RgOK2gg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 No other than the infamous Carl Albert High School gym!!!!!! @CAHS_FOOTBALL14 @MidwestCityOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s just take a walk out into the woods.....problem solved.  Trash like that doesn’t deserve prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[If publicly embarrassing people on the internet is your thing, please unfriend me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usta @TGRFound @AEGworldwide USTA  HOW MUCH ARE US OPEN REVENUES?  $330M, how much you give to the foundation?   1… https://t.co/bQGfL3WPFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boost_jj @betmybookie @ShooterMcGavin_ He shouldn't have been standing there..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill I think you have it backwards.  100% of the people who want socialism have no idea what that means and ultimately leads to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RazorbackMBB Whaaaaaat??? #NCAAM #Basketball #Arkansas #Kentucky #Upset #OneAndDone #WooPig #ESPN #Razorbacks… https://t.co/jcssjoGbC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonschaeffer @ohrnberger @XTRA1360 Nothing yet... pretty sure I'm on some sort of list now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conscious effort to keep prices low to get more people on the wagon. Invest now...you won’t be disappointed!!!… https://t.co/8CjUOln57I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol any man that gets offended by this is either a virgin or a dirty nigga, 🤦🏽‍♂️ it opened my eyes. 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is national #SkiptheStrawDay. While you spread the word and skip the straw, call your legislators in RI, MA,… https://t.co/2BI1Pxi2wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For God is my King from of old, Working salvation in the midst of the earth.” Psalm 74:12  God has a plan and it’s always at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  yo, fatty, did you boycott watching the PGA today since it was in Mexico?  https://t.co/WDYAysCyhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know right Bill! This fucking guy's name comes up whenever and wherever scum and skeez is found]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t ask questions when I stop coming to class cause y’all took my ride away 😤]]></document></documents></author>