<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NathanGBetts DEMONSTRABLE NOAH'S Ark Absolute Truth, What is your Rebuttal Demonstrably World View for the SALVATI… https://t.co/apRbv499KQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theTeenyTay @Dean1sw Fantastic. Swept in the first round and blow it on the draft again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyndinator You can pet your horse. That’s basically just a big dog and totally counts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unite4Truth i can not believe anyone still follows trump and the republican party! it is not the republican party… https://t.co/OJ2cNY29kr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doc has a new set of wheels #drburdorf @ Dr. Burdorf DC DACNB https://t.co/hYyGNGmhBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyStars27 Taillon is my favorite non-Ace (15) and Flaherty and Berrios at 18 and 19 respectively....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my God, Luke Perry?!?! One of my first crushes. His moment as Pike walking into Buffy's dance was an iconic scen… https://t.co/CSdWHBrnjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport @codeofvets @gepehill1 @KarenLL11 Further proof of Donald the Moron.  This is not new wall.  It is Re… https://t.co/faKcB7kvND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searching for ideas on presentations and capturing student work for student and teacher #reflections Thank you… https://t.co/MIQzQimhwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mentor is someone who sees more talent and ability within you, than you see in yourself, and helps bring it out o… https://t.co/j0dp0VYwBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Likewise Jesus is the greatest Lord because he was appropriated by Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @JoshGerben Smart move with the upcoming Tournament. But it will only have impact outside of on-campu… https://t.co/7yNzFQijjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know if these beard oils actually do anything, but they make me feel cool, and now my beard smells like coffee. Seems like a win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As soon as this fool administration is deposed and locked up, WE will tend to fixing all of trumps fuckups, closing… https://t.co/pLcuxQmSzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laszily @NoFascistLies So can I, I just don’t HAVE to justify them to a total stranger on the Internet. Ask yourse… https://t.co/qcSq9zuhK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austen_johnson @TimBontemps @wojespn Adam Silver won’t want small market team to upstage his Lebron plot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh 🙄 again... #snow #minneapolis #minnesota #cold #snow #badweather #blizzard #oldbuilding #historical #history… https://t.co/7dJSVHKFg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The derangement is just verification that OUR President is going a great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otto is tired from a a good night’s sleep &amp; needs a bit of rest before he starts his day. https://t.co/kuhExZpk7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[That waking up to a late night missed call is top 5 (non life threatening) worse feelings ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muddletoes Please don’t both sides this. The left outed themselves this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“People say that there’s nothing like a Championship Saturday inside Madison Square Garden. We want to experience t… https://t.co/gs7tglHh4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last time I saw Twitter freak out so much about a couple was when Jon and Dany got together in #GameOfThrones #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time your sister got the tickle monster out to get you to smile! https://t.co/JsEk9THasO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tower Records Tuesday:Stone Sour (self titled)- #stonesour is the debut studio album by American rock band Stone So… https://t.co/ix5H6yBk8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toomanycommas3 @ggartrell_82 At least your not talking to the neighbors cat from across the yard like me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eso se pudo organizar en una casa, no necesitan tanto espacio juar juar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Wallace @NASCAR Right On Kenny. Your Family Has Given Plenty Back To NASCAR!!! Thank You 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once every three months or so the Baby Alive jingle gets stuck in my head. Science can’t explain that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well congrats to @Maggiekgoff who just confirmed her acceptance to @VCU next Fall!  She has been ready for  #college since Middle School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol if you’re gonna like a sorkin president at least make it Andrew Shepherd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMPhipps @Mamaw1724 @newschannelnine @NOOGAtoday @FOX_Chattanooga https://t.co/AXeK7B6tgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darlene_666 @LitKimm @darlene_666 next time I see you https://t.co/kfRtd4fP6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FamilyAffairs3 @xxxworld4 That's the erotic part of "porn"! Seeing the facial expressions of. especially women, pl… https://t.co/KnGUsqODVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itstetona You welcome @ItsTetona looking forward to seeing you and the crew this season on @BoomerangOnBET was the show taped in #NYC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealGacinski @DrMichaelLBrown Pretribulationist use eisegesis not exegesis to arrive at their conclusions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackGirlHockey @NHLNetwork @JamieHersch I’m available if you need me! 🙋🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning church. Let's gather and make much of Jesus!  8, 930, 11 https://t.co/F4kuPDyrCc #MY2NDFAM @ Conway, A… https://t.co/iFzD2O0xC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta imagine the crossover between people who care about not ingesting corn syrup and people who drink American… https://t.co/7T6hmrbC7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have nothing interesting to tweet about ever, but slap a fuckin x10 multiplier to that after 12am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormResist @SenateGOP Nancy will guide the way. https://t.co/DL2UbrGRQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there are a few factors at work such as trade-tensions with the U.S. are showing up in data, housing market… https://t.co/NrJbKdc8q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already seeing people posting videos of Captian Marvel spoilers/end credit scenes Seriously I’ve met infants that are more mature Stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s wild dogs have the ability to sniff drugs, fight crime and sing, but all mine does is fart and sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tactical_review That will go well with the assult spoon that's making people fat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here on the weekend awesome (@ Boston Market in Clifton, NJ) https://t.co/JQ5oO3ysVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Femennenly Oh ok me either cause I got gassed in iraq by an IED that was made out of a nerve agent shell]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m more than blessed to have a teacher that supports my every move on stage, i have been on the stage since my fir… https://t.co/b6yuVNPsk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE LAUGHING THEIR ASS OFF JUST LISTENING  TO OCASIO CORTEZ..SHE IS THE STUPIDIEST  IGNORANT.INHUMA… https://t.co/CdvUrGoMJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justo esta semana nos toca feminismo en mi seminario de teoría contemporánea...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @kenmartin73 on your re-election. Our party is stronger because of your leadership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realtorteasdale @realDonaldTrump You full of it I got a TV set that’s older then you your generation n… https://t.co/VjVTKFqw6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is it his call? Wait, Mueller is running the investigation right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsolsonsays @MorganFeldman7 @realDonaldTrump Okay! https://t.co/gLak5u5phz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLVanderSloot @Melaleuca @CivilRights Albert Einstein — 'If A is a success in life, then A equals x plus y plus z.… https://t.co/dIYMJAN6iX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RepresentativeOmar listen up hateful so you got a bone to pick,but you might as well be picking your ass,because y… https://t.co/IkwqMPvXbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herculezg @MLS @LIGABancomerMX @ahoraonuncaespn @ESPN_JorgeRamos cuantos más? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, this kid has hit some very valid points, and I respect his opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little sumthin  for the Fam @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/ybJXbQvb7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justinredalen @Hownotamovie1 @danpfeiffer Exactly. Despite changes of party, policy and even ostensible tax rates,… https://t.co/DRFI4NnwJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynJ2017 @jill_magnussen @malekalby @bynsny @LavaletteAstrid @Adele47018578 @monibhachu @barbaragetliff… https://t.co/Sksi5DVaAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Kavanagh In fairness to herb everyone thought he was going to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had thought about switching my legal first name (Jerair) and middle name (Jerry) when I turned 18, but glad I did… https://t.co/uu7HhynKVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone other than me want to know if @Ilhan still has her genitals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesqquick I see your amazing desk. And raise you my cubicle in the endless cubicle farm. https://t.co/Zmxc031VOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venice Beach show now 20 days away come support your boy March 23 from 12–8 https://t.co/jmfcde6SSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOANoticias @heiderlogatto NO ES POR LA AYUDA HUMANITAQRIA,  ES QUE EN ELLA VAN SOLDADOS DE USA RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postmanwes fuck harden, but wb Giannis? he the only guy I got above PG rn but not by a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelesteMabbitt I wish, everyone just be like then not say anything like im not trynna be bestfriends or some shit https://t.co/LDfIZiSSXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down goes Blitzen! Down goes Blitzen! Down goes Blitzen! https://t.co/ndA06foNjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud #cliquemom moment. Our 7 year old belting out #chlorine in the shower 🤣🗣🚿 @tylerrjoseph @joshuadun @twentyonepilots @New_Era_News]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindor will get 400 if not very close to it. I wouldn’t be surprised if the longer this goes with Harper if what yo… https://t.co/egM3NhCzFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/2iZTrIUOja]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be a Civil War Re-enactor, but they won't let me play Pope Pius IX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivia_kelley44 @CoachVlahakis Congratulations, @Olivia_kelley44 !   I couldn’t be happier if you were my own daug… https://t.co/0udnqfDDrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMileskiKFAN Small town hockey survives on repeating successful families.  Nothing more true than that on Greenway… https://t.co/9MZgQ74xn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goatee_k @gatewaypundit you can't deport americans, can't shoot Americans nor use the army against Americans, woul… https://t.co/9PxMlZmmhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyPresidentsDay to the best @BarackObama 🇺🇸💙 https://t.co/zBBeKxTSf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParableJean No he was not , but wish he was and couldn’t get back in the USA .]]></document><document><![CDATA[My uncle has two courtside seats for FREE to Boise State game at 5pm! Who wants them!? #SeniorNight #BroncoNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marine Corps lids in four colors at https://t.co/fVmCY1PV0i https://t.co/IU0PoCuXs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Ok...  I know you’re not gonna call me “repulsive” and still think you’re gonna get these shots for free?    Th… https://t.co/LHnGaRvB1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's no longer just a Northern Ontario problem, its an entirely across Ontario problem! https://t.co/jtYTSMaikQ via @torontostar]]></document><document><![CDATA[That lil nigga went rogue fr 😂😂......I’m so sorry I had to (ima like and retweet tho)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garetrobinson Truer words have never been tweeted.  Team Cru For Life.  #rad #crujones #helltrack]]></document><document><![CDATA[The blues streak may have ended but I still have full faith in this team to go far]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentsDay @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton @funnymemes https://t.co/nOagTGnHdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this humorous there's something wrong with you. Chuck Norris Jokes | The 50 Best Chuck Norris Fac… https://t.co/wKOrifL0nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew Luck really 11-0 against them sorry ass Titans. DADDY https://t.co/QUs8U4B3gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vicente Luque/Bryan Barberena just had the fight we all wish MVP/Paul Daley had last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddZolecki @matt_breen @baseballhall Rollins # needs to be retired before anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good start to the Second half from Nichols, and a quick time-out Middlebury.   Marcos Echevarria to the line to sho… https://t.co/OSIWkIRmQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoxPCPrincipal @georgeofman @RobHartWBBM @rickgregg School principal. Nice language. SMH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Château Bouscassé atmosphère, un lieu authentique, une place à visiter .... bienvenue dans l’univers singulier tell… https://t.co/dZwv0VRC3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historyinmoment Pretty sure other stuff happened that year. Historical stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It created a shitstorm of getting her unceremoniously kicked off the list,” said one U.S. diplomatic source famili… https://t.co/FRIn5GiG2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarleTorres29 Ya lo respaldaron a Jubero? Ahh entonces ya tienen al sustituto!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paulaminger1 @ntwo @DoleFoundation @PhilipsNA @DeptVetAffairs @megkabat Paula you’re one of the lucky ones then!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprising but still a shame. If they wouldn't keep Daredevil, no way would they keep any of the others. Still… https://t.co/nDIHYH0Zx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fantasy_hustle @therealNFLguru @ochocinco @tae15adams 3 straight years with 10 plus touchdowns. Adams without Rodg… https://t.co/144F0woKwa]]></document></documents></author>