<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to set your clocks ahead one hour this weekend. #SpringForward #DayLightSavingsBegins https://t.co/cqA9MLUDOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEL SILVERMAN ARTIST Designed 1949 Viking Yearbook North High School Denver CO #Auction #art #vintage #yearbook… https://t.co/yzi4ujdbau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Musicians React To The Death Of Kofi Burbridge https://t.co/ItavU3VJ9a via @JamBase]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no fear in love, but perfect love drives out fear, because fear has to do with punishment. The one who fea… https://t.co/pNtXeDetvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @sahilkapur I watched him get out of his bus to stop at a rural school outside of Syracuse NY  to surpr… https://t.co/9hlpAFUmfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmerc495 @CezaRubio What a wonderful day to be alive 😍 have a nice day both of you, handsome boys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Ok, and y doesn’t it concern him that American voters were not given all the info before voting and th… https://t.co/eB5kYx6Bhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horowitz39 So sayeth the rich mans dog. The millionaire who grovels at the feet of billionaires. The… https://t.co/ssW7sWab6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pvtjokerus @lyndiejay From the start @IlhanMN has taken anti-American positions in Congress. She is an enemy of the United States.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impopsy @rivernorthbrew @ephoustonbill @zappafaye @lhtetrick @cellmavin @RealBMaxwell @DRE_Go_Fish @RJellyman… https://t.co/BdLUNwemW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your HOUSTON COUNTY BEARS 🐻 @HocoHoops are in the sweet 16 @HocoLocos close but a win is a win @coachdhudson… https://t.co/yhiyOdMvvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealSlimChan @JayBilas I actually agree with Jay on most everything including especially that athletes should b… https://t.co/g9Ee9ADyx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillies @Bharper3407 Dude you gotta flight to catch to Philly, hurry up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teririch @cduhaime I get that they should enforce it, I’m just curious how active companies that be cracked down o… https://t.co/IKmNfKEpAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fungus_Time_ @EU_Commission Yet the UK is also becoming an Orwellian state at the same time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karol Imagine if this was said about a woman. You seem like a pretty bad person but you’re entitled to spew nonsen… https://t.co/4YAWbynmgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatgracemclean @MadeinNY @LCTheater ❤️❤️Yaaaaasssss dear! You deserve it! 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisCarson50 @CNNPolitics Race is a different topic than the one we began with. I brought it up. The parallel is… https://t.co/sqCeKPixHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vpaaacaldwell @DCFBJackets @MannyMatsakis Administrative support is paramount to success! From the top down -ALL IN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Wagner reaching double-digits, the Bruins now have 8 guys with 10+ goals this season (@pastrnak96 , @Bmarch63… https://t.co/yZxgQ27WPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lowkey glad there are billboards all over Weho of where you can find weed. White girls used to stop me on the d… https://t.co/sxvMR0cipY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was really excited when we first got him but way too many injuries and dropped balls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met @paulscheer in the bathroom before Good Boys. Can you guess which one of us had consciously decided to leave hi… https://t.co/c1Kjq3rMdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nag 1v1 mi sakong manghud ba, arun kinsa jod mas hawd sa amo mugamit kay Miya, nadaug pa bitaw ko suko kaayu siya loooool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauleyP @JussieSmollett @PauleyP I don't always see eye to eye with you, but I do respect you and all of your huma… https://t.co/UopZ23OBOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ass-hats are yammering that, as everyone know, he’s a lier. Soooo distracting.  Since he’s already sentenced to… https://t.co/Cs2NEl7hDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spchamp1 We usually don’t report on fires that haven’t started burning 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tips on how to have a successful meeting with your legislator #RareDC2019 https://t.co/L9kTv8E3gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jlawhat @fivefifths In the long run they calculate they have more power this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absolutely mind blowing....you mean you can be a Professional Baseball Player and not swing for the fence e… https://t.co/EvzqxAR8bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arkansas leads Alabama 63-54 with 5:23 left. Gafford is up to 21 and 14 in his maybe swan song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/Ks8ynh6cXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what? I ain’t about all that playing mess and shit, either you get it together or not. 💁🏽‍♀️💁🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a first time guest @creekchurch904 tonight say he loved how we actually preached through the Bible verses in… https://t.co/3TSnUNZtp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib Nor you! You will always suck! Get out of my Country now please!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent many a long night with Gene Moore in the DG ER/OR in the early 1980’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[A este papa le gusta el marxismo, difícil que ore en contra de la causa...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuck Everlasting,  playing (not forever) til March 24th.  At the @cctcolumbus get tickets at boxoffice or… https://t.co/7Q9jN8JXNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway through the challenge, -9.1 lbs, - 2.3% body fat #noletup @ F45 Training Five Points Raleigh https://t.co/EiCJ4ZvSDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grammielynda @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump An insult to cheap fiddles everywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get out in search of a new destiny,searching for a new sunrise, and I joint to know people without measure, the o… https://t.co/qQNQmhQHNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmmm. Is Matt Gaetz afraid Cohen may just have the goods on his "Fearless Leader". Or now that Cohen is out as Tru… https://t.co/r2yvQaSfIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This heat is killing me... although much rather this than the snow! Suck it NY @ Weston, Florida https://t.co/QCBQBrZtwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress I read it. I also screenshot it. I'm going to print off about a thousand copies and tape them all over th… https://t.co/75VxunAhfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFAN1003 ...not sure who's on the air right now...but they are terrible! My gosh, can't even listen to or make sense of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow @SavannahGuthrie Is @LindseyGrahamSC being disengenous to act like he didnt know about this counterintel… https://t.co/VEVv0k4Bbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Studley416 Don't blame rappers when white people been using it for years bruh...Do you really think it would stop… https://t.co/QSxBdicUwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @mamahotone2010 In his alternate universe they are building it. And it's a big beautiful wall being bui… https://t.co/U5tXmJv8Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign of the Times deserved a Grammy. The whole damn album deserved at LEAST a nomination.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh my car would fuck up out of nowhere, about to spend the money I saved 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithyUtd @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/oX74bYtmXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lavendrnhoney @ukpe_viktor She gonna mess around and get Salmonella, E. Coli AND Listeria all in that one bite https://t.co/EayQWFBHxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goodknight43 @USMCLiberal How stupid are you?? Any legal matter between Trump and Cohen! Why was Cohen disbarred??… https://t.co/2waVMUlbcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@walmarthelp What's the problem with the Hammond, LA store? Consistent inventory issues throughout the store.… https://t.co/fKzf3iF5uZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@305miami6924 I ate at an "irish cuban" place, in south beach, 9 yrs ago! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday Open House Follow Up!!!  It’s always nice to send a thank you email to the people who came through yo… https://t.co/DszBFU6pSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Comic Book Couples to Read About This Valentine's Day | The Mary Sue https://t.co/28XXy4mWjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now back to watching Uncle Drew actually I never started it but who cares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  what Kind of Local are WE talking about in the lands known  as Pakistan and India.. ?? well they have older m… https://t.co/yFrTi2eOlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the eye doctors for the first time in years and they have the best pop punk playlist I’ve ever heard in my l… https://t.co/P7Xx1NgXJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll end this thread by pointing out that this story, which is an offshoot of the first Reefergate articles by Brei… https://t.co/e51deuUbCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Duke-North Carolina and Louisville-Kentucky....College Basketball rivalries really fall off in terms of "Must… https://t.co/qpYw2g1sGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDanielsPJ One thing they all have in common? They will all be there longer than there coach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christo31456275. I Been hanging out at Starbucks at los Alamitos !! And Hope i found some body i could make friends with !! ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fans starting to line up for Blue Saturday. The fan-favorite “Temperature Deal” among other ticket specials taking… https://t.co/Qjnq7468Pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @MaryPharaoh What a shame - they have devolved into Fascist Neanderthals. https://t.co/jV4E2y7Egl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davereaboi Because they project their own policy aims onto the whole electorate, many think something undue must b… https://t.co/Z4bAsIBuwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daetradez @danshep55 Proud of you man now we just need to grow that options account]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why more football talk shows don’t use more football guys on their shows like @ProFootballTalk is doing wi… https://t.co/mLZNAuWokm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastclubam Hell nah the NFL ratings were down last year he proved his point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answer to Why did EA stock bounce back so hard after bad earnings? by @bakergavin https://t.co/b55CUuVtoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AestheticLiquid @greninja216 @RealMyUsername This "greninja " guy is talking trash, he really needs to stop trash… https://t.co/8tZRMuO5NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Wow this is disgraceful!! I guess all that served in Vietnam were stupid then!! https://t.co/gXvBHqBCfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CU_SPS_Sports @SloanSportsConf @sportsbiz @scottrosner @kenshropshire @IvyLeague @Columbia_SPS @Lj_Holmgren… https://t.co/67PvNTKW8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 One wrong word. No-one, not everyone, said it couldn't be done.  Many said it shouldn't be done, tho… https://t.co/Ab4Z9OU81R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riley: LeBron leaving Heat made a 'dynasty fly out the window' -  https://t.co/OnjiNrCyF1 via @ESPN App https://t.co/BsjimxQQ3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Austin, TX job and click to apply: IT/OT Cybersecurity Engineer - https://t.co/jLHJHED6Qu #Engineering]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suite Life of Zack and Cody was a cinematic masterpiece I don’t care what anyone says]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous snowy days in #Toronto create increased hardship for our most vulnerable residents. Be sure to shovel, off… https://t.co/ouDQl0vu3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t get mad about the little things , mature people don’t get mad about the little things. mature people find a w… https://t.co/2MwHVOlVeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danutty200451 @Corinne4Hillary @HillaryClinton Donald Trump is doing everything but being loyal to this country or putting us first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doubles 🇹🇹 Troubles, spreading the word about @MinaMalikForDA because we know that our brothers and sisters aren't… https://t.co/e4pSWg3Qoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for th help everyone! Roxy is now home sleeping with her furdaddy....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes I am so highly proud of this album. You are so incredible 🙂👌😝 #ShawnMendes https://t.co/hwMNh54gnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 And feeding you, and feeding you! 👐 @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/F55iuQJEGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did lights and sound for Billy; Three times in the late Seventies https://t.co/poeZr3El04]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 3️⃣5️⃣ YEAR WORK ANNIVERSARY TO OUR GIRL BOSS, ALLISON! Thank you for continuously and consistently being suc… https://t.co/0hhi8kaIpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the time Lebron takes one step he's getting the shot off regardless.. y'all need to stop clowning Bron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chairos, Fifis o lo que sean, en lugar de defender a un gobierno exijan como lo hicieron en sexenios pasados.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfessorGeorgy @iandavidmorris It’s Abe Lincoln. He learned it from Paris Hilton, he did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latifa Abdin is clinically walking us through the functionalities of WhatsApp ahead of exploring its role in the 20… https://t.co/y5nT3yjzvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmpireSportsNYG The realist in me may not be that happy (unless they draft a QB), but the loyalist in me is ecstatic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We did it @ The Mills District. 5k. With this great community of world changers. #beyondthehustle #purposeman @ Mil… https://t.co/4bjh5g887z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing ventured, nothing gained. Kudos to @TheRayHighway and @GADeptofTrans for their leadership.… https://t.co/Xbxa1UzE6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Rebuke to U.S., Germany Considers Letting Huawei In (The Wall Street Journal). https://t.co/fIZwfXoYVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaywardWinifred @lsarsour @SeeMiaRoll @womensmarch @AdyBarkan @BeAHeroTeam It is people like you that make me conf… https://t.co/fcGEtaDz1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goooooooood Mornin' #indianapolis Morning TV time!!! Time to put some clothes on lol @ Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/g09HV6WHvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[How people that use light mode on Twitter look like https://t.co/FFHzPIQVxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Think about the consequences before the act..that's what wish men do. ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine’s Day! Hubby loved and fed and put to bed. Time for some self love! That’s what karaoke means to me https://t.co/sXGsBm1klx]]></document></documents></author>