<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@msilvers1979 Wasted* If he signs back in NY then we got 2 worthless draft picks, even though we’ll still screw up a first round pick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life's a brief moment/Utilize every 2nd-Realize every breaths special-every heartbeats important/Don't let disappoi… https://t.co/u5OeaD3w3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s day 44/66 of the #gymshark66 and I’m down to 186 lbs😎💪🏼 Also SWIPE to see how taking pictures usually goes for… https://t.co/VPu4KTLDZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSUTigersVoice @LSUbaseball @DT9TIGERS @LSUradio @LSUBasketball Looking forward to your great broadcast of both ga… https://t.co/Iu4SBiUCj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You a BIG cap if you're gon honestly try &amp; say this shit ain't slide a lil..lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citadelchief @Countryboi567 And they’ll get it. If the Chiefs are serious in wanting to get better on defense then… https://t.co/9MAz4SVNmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great @MLB contract/free agency discussion on @ryenarussillo podcast.  A fantastic listen if you’re a baseball fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans Hi Zak...what is the best day/time to goto the museum? I'm sure it's always crowded but I want to plan… https://t.co/H3ni1i8r2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SariArhoHavren Didn’t get a deal, but having a hard time seeing how walking away from a bad deal, and letting the… https://t.co/t6MOmsM0WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your heavenly Father didn’t create you to live a #life of mediocrity – you were created to live life in the #faith lane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CShadegg Guess it’s better to be morally incompetent than factually accurate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see me at the @GeorgiaHempCo Sunday 1-6pm. Got all the #CBD products you need... gummies, tablets, oil, vapes,… https://t.co/L5jGm43Vxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princesskate_GB. Give little George a  hope , The Carpenter s Yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a extra ticket to Mumford and Sons if anyone wants to go with a dope group]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think wearing my hair in a man bun today will help my Valentine’s Day chances]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NelsonGord @_JeremyBooth That’s a good question but for me not to answer. He was not allowed to attend a lot of things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New proposal from Connecticut Governor @GovNedLamont could soon cost those of driving through CT. Details this morn… https://t.co/jRSxDtgqC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoskyLiz #NowIGNITE inspiring kick off...voice and choice for our kids. All we have to do is get out of their way… https://t.co/EKopwrRn8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cap-tip to @thehazelmae and Rick Houston for pivoting and getting to St Pete for this important story. Awesome job… https://t.co/MIvCOAtqRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biscuitkun @thedragonprince Was just tweeting tonight about how desolate the Runaan fans must feel without him aro… https://t.co/xCJHI6i9qP]]></document><document><![CDATA[snapchat reminded me that this happened one year ago today https://t.co/9SJ3PmuwMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS What?  So...  He has taken a picture with you to help boost approval rating… https://t.co/DEZ3Ra53XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k00laidIT @tbgree00 @jhoughes @NerdBlurt @jfrappier @vcixnv @KCDAutomate @al_rasheed @aaronbuley @importcarguy… https://t.co/0kNM3bApyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husam_Hamdi @Manoama89203646 @johncrossmirror You have no European trophies whatsoever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weegee56 @SpaceFarceCEO @patrid1959 @NBCNews The guy said I was groping a woman.....I was simply explaining it was… https://t.co/m7rGFB99jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting game for our JV boys tonight. This was our third game in three days, but our guys dig deep and held a 2-lo… https://t.co/HJcAOppkFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You for correcting me! I thought I was losing my mind… I blame @PNemiroff 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieJoyce @BrianBarwig You're taking an even bigger risk by not hand delivering the banana bread to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRE-ST. PAT’s PUB CRAWL IN Asbury Park. I’ll Be at Shot Wheel bar after Registration. @ Asbury Ale House Sports Bar… https://t.co/8zKr8mJmP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I think Sanders should not run. But I have a question Ed. Are the Democrats intentionally working to re-… https://t.co/uYmRnpkDRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fedor watching Cro Cop KO his brother https://t.co/88zrM95FwU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[iguess being real now is overrated you neva see it but they always say it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright so @CentrFit has playlists on Apple Music? I’m so ready to use them. It’s lit 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really good deal on amazon. 128gb Switch compatible for $20.99 https://t.co/CWK89VqfSU #NintendoSwitch #SamsungEvent #Samsung]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love understands us now, in a way that we will understand Him only at the end of all time, in His everlasting embra… https://t.co/SE8zMUuIeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[so @AAdams726 and I just made copy cat chipotle. we almost died from the canned chipotles, but we did it. and it’s damn good. 🌯🌮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or has @Zaxbys heavily cut back on how much seasoning they put on the fries in the last year or two]]></document><document><![CDATA[MMU Alpine is back at Burke Mtn today for the Slalom portion of the State Championships ... #CougarNation🐾  Boys ar… https://t.co/IgVR81RO8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzyLuGME Do you have a discord channel? Looking to join it if you do! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crayzeigh It’s apparently from 2013, but still, yikes  https://t.co/kEyGBPCRkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, yeah! Hey everybody check out this retweet. Afterwards, please hit that retweet button and share it with all Y… https://t.co/8x45MNAb2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gary_needham Too many other conferences, Melville's 200th... Will be there in spirit. What is your SCMS panel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Stay close to anything that makes you glad you are alive.” #WSHH worldstar @qworldstar 💯🙏🏻 @ Dutchtown High School https://t.co/qNLmYabZsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it worth it?  Maybe when you go home I don’t want to be here  Trying to think about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LewisFranck @A_S12 @NASCAR @stevephelps @sbjsbd @GettyImages Many don't know that in some years new model cars wer… https://t.co/BBTdZuqspx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up with people from Venezuela....sad to see what’s happening to their country and it’s people #SocialismDoesntWork 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflections of ones self @ Regal Cinemas North Hills 14 https://t.co/pYt5Hf4MCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was pretty down in the dumps February so streaming Half-Life games (or anything really) didn’t pan out. Feeling b… https://t.co/bwNytM7PQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advice from Matt Olsen, Chief Trust and Security Officer @Uber, on how to approach #digitaltransformation and… https://t.co/XANFqJvEUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartsNewGlasses @aztectravis Eh. They made 4 straight tournaments and a sweet 16 in the early 2000s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Fabiano Damn man,can you be more negative about Buffalo?  Still better then the Jets lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisstraub @ActivePlayerNet @katewelchhhh @Wizards_DnD @PA_Megacorp Hey that’s me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker denizen of the swamp and a perfect example of what must be drained from it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Gearshifter IPA by @StoudtsBrewery @ Lancaster Marriott at Penn Square — https://t.co/V0hdgeVl3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old friend, artist #NikkiTerry gifted me with this fabulously simple painting.  It still soothes me. #home… https://t.co/uZntawhcvS]]></document><document><![CDATA['Very proud of the team we've built' - Stephanie Riley opens B3 Creative Agency https://t.co/mHkF28bZ7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt #bwood and #vault #trill sh@t #bwoodknows #redsheppard #dffs #calvinandhobbes  #harlem #midtownscrambling… https://t.co/q7WxO1sBlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! I hope everyone works hard today and brings value to their industry, community, customers, and partners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoddessofGrain @sellis1994 Your premise is your answer...it all depends on when it is finalized and what it 👀 like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lara Croft #KatsuCon  #katsucon2019  #thatguywiththebattie https://t.co/qH7JPt8aHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leo is definitely ready for daylight savings and so am I! #catsofinstagram #catstagram #caturday #dantevelasquezny… https://t.co/f1KLtwRGF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should try DoorDash, it's an awesome food delivery service. Get $10.00 off your next order when you sign up wit… https://t.co/zKDXJytdTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump and Clinton spar over Stacey Abrams #gapol https://t.co/5aHt7fUu3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44_rem_mag @akkingon @Minuteman223 @kooolhanluke @bushcamp2 @WassmannBill @teamregulators @pensfannc5… https://t.co/iqzHYinfVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ratch_t lol yeah it’s so accurate that sometimes i get mad like, “THIS IS SPEAKING THE TRUTH BUT I DONT WANNA HEAR IT!” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, the appliances we dropped almost three stacks for.....three months ago, will finally be here tomorrow........or… https://t.co/GDBm9DolfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@facebook  My account is Blocked for Posting a Gun Description.  It was NOT For Sale plus I do not live in Orlando,… https://t.co/RNxTSrxkFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Create coherent curriculum 2. Promote authentic literacy 3. Deliver soundly structured instruction. Thank you Sc… https://t.co/PKysVWbnkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Love Your Pet Day! #loveyourpet #nationalloveyourpetday #dogsofinstagram #catsofinstagram… https://t.co/GRFIEgrO2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just discovered a new kind of crazy. The “stay at home-home school mom” crazy. Wow 😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAWPro @sammyguevara @DarbyAllin Good job, Sammy. You’re okay, Darby? #ARTOFWAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[climate has changed since the dawn of time.  Brian, the Maunder Minimum, as atmospheric physicists know, is coming… https://t.co/Yk3ZeJKBE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressTV Wait, was that on the #calendar? You need to send out #reminders next time. #SoBusy #MultiTasking https://t.co/Z0VdOuO9uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamlevine @johnlegend Let go of the garbage of the past. Its a new season and  a fantastic one.  Love the kiss scene with Blake so cute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't trusted Jussie since he got loud with Gordon Bombay. https://t.co/mUq3qHOAox]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's actually been a good couple weeks for jackets,Amanda got me a sick element Wolfeboro work style jacket,and tod… https://t.co/r7hXQUzEP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME TODAY  I really walked in that room 30 min early. Sat there for 10 min. Got up and left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out custom Williams multicade for sale at TNT Amusements! Call if interested  215-953-1188 or Email at tntqua… https://t.co/TSaq6yrVjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackFinkNews I guess this is what you do when you are in the minority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceellison @CoryBooker We should tax money being sent back to Mexico from illegals. But Congress won’t approve it.… https://t.co/ozpPfuaAoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:11:11 happens twice a day because everyone deserves a second chance 👌🏾⌚🥃 #weekendclosingceremony on… https://t.co/oMZczw4TDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight on #Twitch at 7 (pm) join @CryBabe___ &amp; I for #BlaqAfterDark! We’ll give our reactions to the… https://t.co/ECsqWbWvb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[1:48 2nd | Santos-Silva gets the easy bucket on a dish from Evans. Officials reviewing an out of bounds call, stays… https://t.co/2ISMmdcEE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My sheep hear My voice, and I know them, and they follow Me.” John 10:27  #teamjesus @krazy4ujc @Hetz20 @SticksMix @sues3jewels @KSchottPhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iconmaster I was just about to add that nuance to the thread. I contain multitudes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leozuckermann @EPN @lopezobrador_ @RicardoAnayaC Gracias a @EPN por construir las condiciones para que… https://t.co/BqzZmUgBHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guelphhumber @EMERGETO odds we can get Ernie to make a #VerticalFilmMaking course?  Forget 4K, this is what we nee… https://t.co/O6lLX84Rty]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s one thing in a movie you wish you could taste? I’m thinkin’ about those peaches from Holes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binarybits Apple’s GUI computer based on the Xerox Star was the $10,000 Lisa. The Mac was a crazy Steve Jobs skunkworks side project.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting it done on the courts and in the classroom, good work girls 🎾👩🏻‍🎓❤️    @hannmacias @caligiertz… https://t.co/iH4jsX0QVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsbyCoachP @CoachHixonDimes @CUSportsCoach @DavidBoydhoops @DaveNedbalekUTT @CoachRjayBarsh @chibbs_1… https://t.co/2h2yL0Njgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeGalindot @Rayados Ha tenido por ahí algunos partidos flojos, por ejemplo, aquel de Alianza en El Salvador.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man who assaulted Grealish is sentenced to 14 weeks of jail time.   Thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Clearly, you have had your "happy ending"  after this vitrol against America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Switch to a cleaner electric mower. Manual reel mowers are even better for the air and your grass. Replacing unnece… https://t.co/HA4WdYo1ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t need to do a skin routine because @emoblackthot cleanses my skin with the tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctryfan28 I definitely think we can work together on a format that would work for 3rd grade. As far as SM, let me… https://t.co/agPT4rW8sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's ‘national emergency’ border wall cash grab flounders — a huge chunk of the money has already been spent: re… https://t.co/yEo7PibNrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidebrady @wsbtv Only if you're a filthy frog or a frog wannabe. Two silent vowels? Really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest inspiration for playing guitar is going out to see bands live. The last concert I went to was on a Sunda… https://t.co/6fkAGIBXE1]]></document></documents></author>