<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance Hated Tucker before this and even more so now. Why are so many Republican men such pigs ?? Where d… https://t.co/CYcI5NN7jT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road trips are aways fun and hilarious when listening to car_talk   #roadtrip #roadtrips #roadtripessentials… https://t.co/I27XIfU06u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBlizzardxo @LisaVanderpump I’m not liking Lisa Rinna much anymore 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michnic70 The same IRS that targeted conservative groups will be TOTALLY FAIR AND IMPARTIAL in deciding your medical care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttoTitsling @DrJenGunter @GwynethPaltrow Did you ever watch that show "1,000 ways to  Die" ? I will never forget… https://t.co/ubpeRtJIAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I don't this for religious reasons. It's just a practice from childhood and I haven't challenged myself for awh… https://t.co/L0UQMFzgo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey I couldn’t forget you Owen I have been watching you and Rachel for years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RampCapitalLLC McDonald’s uses methyl cellulose as a surfactant that allows the salt to stay on the surface and pr… https://t.co/AjNEbkJ5Hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela colapsando por los incompetentes q Ursurpan el poder... https://t.co/OnlwW7BGo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHONJ Teresa is UGH 🤢🤮 I really try not to attack women in life. She is the exception. She is vile. Horrible Awful… https://t.co/bZvaPRXWdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh, I’m lonely af. But I know that God has someone just for me and therefore I’m just gonna chill until I meet tha… https://t.co/kcxfYW0RPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  I agree with everything Michael Cohen said about you. You’re stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh Slavery may be over, but the Republicans show us daily that racism is alive and thriving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally have a good analogy of anxiety. It's like the unbuckled seat belt sound in the back of your head telling yo… https://t.co/gTZKAj1TXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, after the game, I drop Teegan off at home, I give him a kiss and his response was “I want another one, that kis… https://t.co/b0fvLeEnsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KanyeW3AST I’m gonna call Cigna for a list of therapists in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSigrist Yes!!!! One of our favorite resources at #vanmeter is #PebbleGo Next from @CapstonePub 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to epic film scores at work in attempts to get me at least slightly motivated 🦸🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[did tyler accidently rt something on his main, is that why he deleted it so quickly???  #tylerstanaccountmanhunt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but she was terrible on ESPN. Good luck #Mets #mlb #baseball #jessicamendoza #baseballoperations from a… https://t.co/zNzhYjMEx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I talk to my mom on the phone we literally say “I love you bye” like 20 times before we actually hang up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado #communication professionals, there’s still time to join us Feb. 19th to talk #socialmedia strategies with… https://t.co/9YUyAyBeR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[college really sucked the melatonin out of my brain. even if i’m exhausted i’ll just lay here for hours w my eyes c… https://t.co/s8482KuOea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/xg8wR2TMLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabFitFun @EleVenbyVenus I'm having trouble trying to change my shipping address! Page won't work]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @cmorganmusic #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/egley9jXsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarlinSincerest @VANS_66 I love the sunflowers.i would love for you to paint shoes for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious question:   How in the Sam Hill is it in Israel’s long-term security interest for SAUDI ARABIA to have a nu… https://t.co/I9oj94UyoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_cingraham @Brainyack524 1) That is NOT their fault-- it is the fault of #Republican legislators, Trump, all those… https://t.co/VTAASRbB6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaDonnaGagn2 @sueellen93 @Koji262 @JohnPtye @XJAPANUSA @YoshikiOfficial Absofrickinloutely! Jayne too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relationships will never be me don’t get me wrong I love watching other people in love but I love my solidarity mor… https://t.co/TZW46Byo0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he can’t handle you at your Bauhaus he doesn’t deserve you at your sammy Davis Jr singing “Feeling Good” followe… https://t.co/85cNu7yGtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TracyMcMillan And the etiquette class was a fail. Sigh. Hard to call this season]]></document><document><![CDATA[So which one of my friends is trying to go get wings and beer with me tomorrow ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Sounds dangerous to me! Why is the Trump family always so secretive about meetings with dangerous heads of countries??!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Facebook group stats https://t.co/gIbbAMCQIQ https://t.co/R4JU3n7whf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am officially a #poundfitnesspro! Thank you @michelleoppe for a rockin🤘 training! I can't wait for my first class… https://t.co/zgweF6F9FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R0ckyIntertidal @WhiteAbalone Since we’re controlling our egg:sperm ratios, most of the fertilization success is p… https://t.co/41L6Ez9okT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone needs a birthday present idea for me I’ll take urban decay naked reloaded eye shadow palette for the thre… https://t.co/yQO8NuJhtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since he has family members that are of color, no he isn't And saying he should go back to Kenya isn't racist, it's… https://t.co/L7arYyBbTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plane crash pilot killed in Yorba Linda was Antonio Pastini real name was Jordan Isaacson. He was responsible for f… https://t.co/lwvrbXUuNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peady @EastCoastKnits And the more you stare at the dust, the more you’re convinced it’s moving!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meteorologist Karen Minton retiring after nearly 33 years at WSB-TV: https://t.co/iKbwVjIuqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be leading worship again this week at church with @mrjoshramos 🤗🤗 it is a JOY singing and using our t… https://t.co/38tEo8hTlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cardiologist said that as long as I don’t get worse or start passing out again then I won’t need anymore appointments :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rottenscotty12 @FartyCheddarCat You're wearing a watch cap; I rarely see cats in knit headgear. Looking nifty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bishop Kenny defeats Ridgeview 67-16 @DuvalSports https://t.co/bvJnVRKZ8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airport (BWI) in Baltimore, MD https://t.co/GxRgT72D3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot hot hot ☀️ reached approx 30 Degrees today! #Melbourne #Florida #MelbourneFlorida #Sun #Sea #Sand #SunSeaSand… https://t.co/cShYvFZTpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say that they want to see me it literally makes me tear up!!like really? You want to see ME?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me- Hosting Open House 1-4  MLS#:218075521  705 WEDGE DR NAPLES, FL 34103 #openhouses Breathtsking views of th… https://t.co/YsR5YWCBig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit that low tide just right. Beach looked untouched from yesterday’s snow. #beach #winterbeach #seaglass… https://t.co/VYPGyZ26KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Newlin10 Hahah really? Yeah I never thought I looked like her but other people seem to think I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been so much fun helping this beautiful sisters buying her first home!! Congratulations Jhoselyn and  Tatiana… https://t.co/Kfo1ZirGyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAPDHQ @NapervillePD @LAPDCentralArea @LAPDTSHarrelson Awww, let the cutie have a few extra days here in SoCal to… https://t.co/kjnFxDqmT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen Isa born liar what to believe what not believe. Excuse me good deal I'd better if it looks bad for president give me a break]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS 😂  so I messaged my boss letting her know that I went to the ER and I’m kinda scared and she DEADASS goes   👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheItalGal @BleedblueTammy @LovelyEbonyDiva @AngieCats6 @dianemariereid @triciaa310 @DianaV7654 @PwrFulWmn… https://t.co/RIATqnLEGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from amccoy4474  -  It’s all priorities, I’m working on mine daily! #selflove #priorities #betteryourself… https://t.co/sKJ7oaUzCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin told me “you better not be posting at 1 am YOU NEED SLEEP” He’s not wrong lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP  @HouseDemocrats  @SenSchumer  @SpeakerPelosi   The caravan comes leaving a violent wake. THIS is what Am… https://t.co/brK255viZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had too many good sleeping days in a row. I knew this night would come. https://t.co/RTu3G6ynof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume @DanHenninger And how odd that GOP is the party of Russian appeasement. Who ever would have guessed we would be here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tracing the African Diaspora: Places of Suffering, Resilience and Reinvention March 7-9, 2019 | Coastal Carolina Un… https://t.co/owqGbrWb4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendenfingers If that was all he said I wouldn’t be bothered but he literally said “I am embarrassed to tell peop… https://t.co/ngU0TaWlTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The enemy from within. God Bless and help @realDonaldTrump and America🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[livre, leve e solta no Wynn.. hahahaha 🌸🌼 em Wynn Las Vegas https://t.co/r7LGwUxoJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to give a very special shout out to my friend Michele @theonlymich1818 her sister took this video of… https://t.co/OgTYHhzmOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachaelAtWork That person on your bottom left is incredibly handsome. 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[this Lo-Fi Beats playlist (plus candles, of course) has really made this working Monday a chill one.   will def be… https://t.co/gdZQIAmKef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progressive nations (...Sweden) have reliable primary health care! It’s of concern to see what’s happening in India… https://t.co/7olDz55Jgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[and served 14 years as the Chief African American health officer of Oklahoma County. Dr. Haywood was also a charter… https://t.co/5L9rdDVtX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤸🏻‍♀️ ❤👏🏽💪❤🤸🏻‍♀️  Just in case you need some #MondayMotivation!  Well today is Monday so it’s time to set the tone… https://t.co/YCqG9Z3vmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im going to visit my family back in Puerto Rico on April it would really mean a lot!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy I got to see @HippieSabotage last night with my family!! they threw it down!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing our Sunday work.  I’m grading tests and Penny is drawing a potato family. https://t.co/Fbr9tDs77Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s_elishah @allie_baum_23 @Kilcrease28 Love, love, Love @allie_baum_23 @Kilcrease28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoRhapMovie @QueenWillRock @ItsRamiMalek @DrBrianMay Here I am with my beagle Edge watching #BohemianRhapsody  Goo… https://t.co/pUMw9QJr2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senoritav76 @Outlander_STARZ @caitrionambalfe That blanket is the best thing ever! I got Jamie , Dougal, and BJR p… https://t.co/HRuGGs8tj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMT_Cory @PanolaWatchman They don’t? I’m not entirely sure. I just know that even though all of our sister newspap… https://t.co/rtknhuNcK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patter5275 Sounds like a plan to me.  We need to get some release dates on his other projects that are coming out❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[follow @dolansrcanceIed! its a gad acct made by the dolan twins in one of their videos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendajlair @rob_sheridan @realDonaldTrump @TwitterSupport Oh, you're a bot troll, just saw that on your profile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MedicalMarijuanaDispensaries #Texas is literally surrounded by states that have made it legal, medically.… https://t.co/Y3ZfgeMyD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rrod78501 @washingtonpost Americans said YES to Obama and his policies in 2008 and 2012, by landslides; first pres… https://t.co/Wo65HW6Jiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been really good about not cursing on my social media profiles lately I’m proud of my set goal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exdemnewRep @lawanap6 @ZARATHOOSTRA1 @DauntlessCandy @cruzzer71 @tictoc NOT bc non-citizens are registered voters.… https://t.co/rOl5BRv2Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nebraska bound. Read a little on the first flight cause let’s face it, I’m always sleeping on travel days.… https://t.co/Xtaqnm3wfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Accidentally” Stab him and when he says take me to the hospital, say you’ll do it for 7k retweets okay honey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner honey, you're aware that he said he wasn't aware of any collusion. He didn't say th… https://t.co/9Ncc2OVVVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatTheFFacts Thank you for being the caring and kind person you are who makes a big difference in this world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes you think he will keep his promise when not one of their leaders (who actually signed an agreement) has… https://t.co/ab7F7eY5lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half Baked - 50 of the funniest movie quotes ever https://t.co/DrT52Wzr9o... https://t.co/Dl4IFkk2cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una disculpa a las alumnas de la mañana.  Ya hice mi clase, sí la puse mamona. No era mi intención.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people have loud phone conversations on the bus: thank GOD for noise cancelling headphones. Though I can still kind of hear him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we should care what a  rapper named @KillerMike has to say about Jussie Smolllett? Forgive and move on don’t rea… https://t.co/Eh7wjz2Tim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhipontheX It was given at 202. You said it was crazy. It didn't work. I switched to 102.9 and they gave age. That… https://t.co/ebRnWvWSEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼  I love how early she is talking about paid family leave with such depth!!   👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼… https://t.co/1P55CmduDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjanaes i can’t get the image out of my head and i’m truly in pain at the flashbacks i keep receiving 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday again BBG !! 🍻🎉#usthisweekend @lexieeramirezzz https://t.co/sTVThgf1lL]]></document></documents></author>