<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[LabCorp is hiring in #LaGrange, GA! Read about our latest #GeneralScience job opening via the link in our bio: Phle… https://t.co/BAmd328rt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktpoy I wish you could move to the street behind us. The renters that are there now.....aren’t the greatest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rak_f1 @realDonaldTrump You are DISGRACE !!!!! ...And Jus Do You Know Our President Donald Trump@is Above You And… https://t.co/YQ9TXHXzSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #winewednesday today so before you #indulge here is a little visual reminder of how much #sugar is in #wine .… https://t.co/AASctev3fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is your thinking about RTC projects? Is Jeff on board? Jack? It is a big deal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, this just gave me life 😉 #wishusluck @ Kickapoo Lucky Eagle Casino https://t.co/oFpVFaap8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWhiteFB Congratulations!!  Great job coach!!  Looking forward to next season!  Go big blue!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christianbrotrz @Jozefowski @NBCSChicago @whitesox @Bharper3407 So true. Watched Machado antics way to many times as an Oriole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @AOC Simply not true. WOW...@SpeakerPelosi is a fool for not overriding her kind of behavior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He got shot by IDF snipers. Netenyahu tweeted this morning that he loves his IDF soldiers. The silence of so many i… https://t.co/SFILmqFvWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurHof11 @JustBeU1111 @alycou22 @kaylacoughlan @La_La_05 @Msk1809 @marinelli51 @GinPhilPhan @C_Noskow @BonJulie1… https://t.co/BboQMOIJZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESPN: “three of the best five team in the nation playing tonight.”  Actually, it’s four.  You’re leaving out Gonzag… https://t.co/I1LpF7E0bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Feel Good Friday at @KCS_Roosevelt !  What’s that? Our amazing 3rd grade classes have decided to be intentiona… https://t.co/CvvUryGQ8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This moment really MOVED me.   I believe in the American Experiment; if you really show up, and are ALL IN; work ha… https://t.co/vmlfS5i2Ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien I read it, and I thought it was insightful. Feel free to criticize, but read it first. Always a good idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freeadora “Doppelbanger: (noun) Someone who is attracted to people who look just like them.” Who knew there was a term for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas need to know what type of lotion she uses. 9/10 we can’t afford it. So nvm lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of #CellularIoT connections is expected to reach 4.1 billion in 2024 - increasing with an annual growth… https://t.co/ejdBd2OZAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton True, but I for one love seeing the senator from California having to deal with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Republicans questioning Cohen⬇️ ..........They appear to be upset, how rude after subjecting us to Trump's lun… https://t.co/hMeLyu5ngc]]></document><document><![CDATA[i still??? can't believe??? the favourite did not win for best screenplay?? roma and first reformed sitting there too!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PTSD, Fibromyalgia, Anxiety, Autism Spectrum or other mental or physical issues that keep you from sleeping well?… https://t.co/XF4biG6jc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamShadowhunters on @TyltEnt—I will miss ‘Shadowhunters’ the most https://t.co/1rHTr2Bi3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radiothon 2019 is finally here and phone lines are open! @BroadcastBybee is #live all morning long! #CBS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3ChicsPolitico #Maddow Oops maybe I was wrong! I was sure she had talked to Pence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enJOYRYDE @HARDrecs You killed it as always!! When will your album be available on vinyl!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinSatie It’s not a reverse harem? I just saw a couple of her other books are that type. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to being able to go to LifeGroup, worship, and serve on the same morning. Woot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #InternationalWomensDay graphic I made celebrating female athletes and their sports!! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[En los peores momentos una buena platica con con mi mamá me sana el corazón]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really disappointed in your customer service @Upwork and your refusal to answer the simple question of why you… https://t.co/gRTyeeT5j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_TrumpIN 🙋‍♀️🇺🇸❤️ Me &amp; my whole family continues to stand with our great President Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing night of training tonight with these guys! Thanks for pushing me 👊🏼🇧🇷💙 #bjj #jiujiteira #jiujitsu… https://t.co/PMZW7FWoiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christogrozev Sincere question-- is it possible he was duped by whatever he was "allowed" to see? If he bought int… https://t.co/YxxBYFgRS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got my nails done today so now I’m currently watching YouTube videos on how to get my contacts out 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never been so happy to have school before in my whole life #SPTProbs #NoSnowDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenneth Tobey . . . . . . #ClassicHollywoodLovers Gals:-) #kennethtobey #oldhollywood #oldmovies @ Hertford, North… https://t.co/5kNd6nownZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still thinking about that email that started with a welcoming “Good Afternoon!” that I sent at 9 this morning today...Is it the weekend yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zodiakary Well that’s your opinion and that’s okay 😊 you weren’t there, you don’t know what fully happened. But you have a good day now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really breaks my heart that I can't get my truck to the body shop until Monday 😜 #ls1 #lsx #c5 #c5corvette… https://t.co/wRzn2fd3JM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't sleep because I'm craving pizza and panckaes... Why am I like this? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h0n3y_73 This detention needs to be handled A LOT better than it’s being handled right now‼️‼️😡📣👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time last week, I had just returned from a week of advocating for California’s drinking water y wastewater sys… https://t.co/6TZLO1VMoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse knew they would find nothing. Take the monet paid for this witch hunt, taken from taxp… https://t.co/CQlNsC1epp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm writing my letter of intent for grad school and it's so depressing because I'm talking about my social life in… https://t.co/Tr9WO8WF5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flee ye, turn back, dwell deep, O inhabitants of Dedan; for I will bring the calamity of Esau upon him, the time th… https://t.co/3JSdvAVKmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @CheriJacobus @realDonaldTrump You know, I had no idea the KKK was still around until Jasper, Texas.… https://t.co/B1SJMh4jza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoodleNessa Unfortunately, I'm worse! I had to call in to work this morning! Hate that! Got an appointment with my… https://t.co/EGsQ9SnVE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stealth_singer @ShawnMendes @ShawnAccess Oh girl! If only we lived closer!!! We would make it happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTVNEWS You can’t buy a pink velvet tux off the rack ?  Seriously, though, Karl Lagerfeld had an excellent sense of humor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberal are so typical—- totally miss the true abuses children suffer— maybe cuz Hollywood abuses children also]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate being sick and I know this isn’t healthy but I’ve been drinking NyQuil like it’s water. Somehow being asleep… https://t.co/2ASUPGXti4]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine taking 50 different pictures cuz you feel cute n the lighting is nice &amp; only ending up w 2 good pictures lol 😔👎🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Garofalo just called enshrining gender equity in our MN Constitution through the equal rights amendment is the… https://t.co/Z5oGTxjl9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of Technical Rescue Training with @sdhumane. I never knew how hard it was to plan rescues and keep everyone s… https://t.co/iT5bXumBEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Engle_PHS  okay but how did I not know that my feed would blow up with nothing but #Oscars tweets from you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Lorin and I we’re at a restaurant in Newport last night and we did not know it at the time but the CEO of Revolv… https://t.co/l3ifz09pOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusSequeira @EricVictoria6 @yourgirlsavi @thaboi_austo @arianaharriss @ItsDrew33 @danibryan_ @drewski090 yea th… https://t.co/MWC5LTtg1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder "The evidence will show clear violation of the #EmolumentsClause Article 1 Section 9 of the #Constitution."… https://t.co/0qkNGQSD6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber strikes again. Yet another driver refusing to take me and my guide dog in their vehicle. The second he drove… https://t.co/STEeUm5FQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @sex_positivefam!! Very well said!!! #sexpositive #sexed #sexeducation #comprehensivesexed… https://t.co/J3IA7h3dwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrerTaylor @gwarren25 Gonna call these Brer biscuits in my recipe box!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMGarland So jealous!!! Way to represent! You are just missing some fringe!🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treatment haircut and style to make you smile 😊 🙋🏻‍♀️💁🏼‍♀️ you look great! We love your hair 🥰❤️ @ A List Salon https://t.co/nh2cHYTGS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASlavitt @PrincessBravato I just keep taking them. Only way to survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinceMountain @Remember_Sarah Checking Elizabeth Holmes off the list of of potential borrowed dogs then. https://t.co/fhHkHizhTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[so if u wanna go hmu plssss because i know no one else that would interested but me and trust it’s gonna be great this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen Hearing my baby's heartbeat the 1st time via fetal monitor made it real for me. What an amazing sound]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chica real y muy complaciente, pregunta por mis servicios. ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/qz7BTkpH7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Builds confidence, facilitates communication skills, promote family engagement, and most of all development a ❤️ fo… https://t.co/I1tUDYmBfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get married and make some sweet love with that special someone.... 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Yes it is and you should serve the people and not your personal agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello because i’m a hypochondriac a lot of people don’t take me seriously when I say I’m sick and something is wron… https://t.co/vaF5ySqg6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready @KleinForest they are coming to you soon with some serious background knowledge!! Thank you to our amazin… https://t.co/k14iOyOLyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs He’s a heck of a lot more believable than you are! #liarinChief]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fjC1oN082X  ATT Customer Service Number 1-833-554-5444: Fish out Unwanted Technical Errors and Glitche… https://t.co/CMXX0uYUyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big thanks to @Elon_Tres and @melaniebullock for presenting the Valuing Each Other session of the Phoenix Leadershi… https://t.co/dGz1asOYso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful rich color and @hotheadshair for length and fullness on this havenmeridian babe. • 💁 • • • •… https://t.co/5g4m7EVqrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Inspiration Of Time With God For Today - Jesus said, "I am the way and the truth and the life. No one comes to t… https://t.co/Ip8sQqD3Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte NC Sat Feb 16th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Rain Lo 39 SUNDAY Chance Of Rain Hi 45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregBeast32 You haven’t seen how many times Hobart has been spelled as Bert in the last 20 years like I have 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I just went on a positivity rant... but Im sick as hell and lost my voice 😫 any at home remedies for a cough… https://t.co/1sCIHzti91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddlnewsbackup @ddlovatoffnews Lionel and Demi need to sing together again 🎦 that was so good I love seeing everybo… https://t.co/6uPjUzvE4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limp weak message, what are your thoughts. @ Illinois https://t.co/lWAw05iawU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Dreamed a Meme: Les Miserables Meets the Internet. Click thru for Les Mis Memes #hilarity #tee-hee #grin #jolly https://t.co/pUgQ5sO67a]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear friend is waking up this morning as the day after her loss. My heart breaks for her and I wish I could reac… https://t.co/p3dndTWUiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmendrews @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Just common sense and love for our country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These kinds of weekends have quickly become my favorite.   ________________________ #mxweekend #goodmorningsunday… https://t.co/Sxia6QIura]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep listening to the postgame interviews on @ZoneSportsNet and I woke up after having weird dreams about… https://t.co/WxtmdKV4cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabbySidibe @EricHaywood Don’t sweat it.  It’s a director occupational hazard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma be married laid up with my husband and still tweeting men are trash 😂🤗🙃😤 just not mine 😘☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jidk1187 @asmith702 @SarahGould_SA @amandadeibert @CatStaggs @ashleyn1cole @cmclymer @docrocktex26 @carolineframke… https://t.co/7piepOGZyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick &amp; can't sleep! Here is an awesome hike with with some great actors. https://t.co/Dz3mPiW2Kr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 He is so transparent. His parents didn't like him, the kids at school bullied him, girls laughed at him… https://t.co/baA2kFzP8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDennisDavis @CharlieDaniels @sunshinec07 Really what about when U get a Hurricane Like Michael i Don’t Care Wha… https://t.co/Tk0R4TGssR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possible O'Rourke White House Bid Spurs Action to Mobilize Students https://t.co/duB9Qu65xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whataburger I was expecting to see pictures of chicken strips and gravy TBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Service starts at 10:00. Come to a place you belong! @ Redeemer's A.M.E. Zion Church https://t.co/4bJ6eveff2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to wear a different perfume today and i grabbed one of the samples i received, it was a men’s cologne. 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone loving on Taurus sun/Taurus moon has me feeling so validated 🥰]]></document></documents></author>