<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@politico What? All of Wall Street loved Hilary Clinton. Of course after what Bill Clinton pulled with Fannie Fredd… https://t.co/cV9PAZsPMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzpeitiaThalia yes!! we miss you all to so we definitely will have to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westervillecly Not sure when she learned it, but she just told me about it a week or  two ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Good I’m glad he did maybe something in the United States will get done now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalNugent I love you more &amp; cant wait to see you 🖤 thank you babe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EUinNigeria @USEmbassyAbuja @UNHumanRights @AmnestyNigeria @POTUS PLEASE HELP NIGERIANS VOTING PDP THEY ARE NOT BE… https://t.co/QgfPtaKh2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loads of fun this Mardi Gras season @CHNOLA! #chnola #pediatrics #donuts #beads #bacchus #thoth #musictherapy… https://t.co/0KiI3zoMXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for the ride to savannah @jetblue #weekendvibes https://t.co/BphQyImqUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woodworth_Alex Bitches love flowers 🌺 and chocolate 🍫 foot 🦶 rubs not that hard to win a girl over 🤷‍♀️🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida Recortan y recortan y yo no veo que la vida de los ciudadanos mejore... si es para los caprichos del dictador bananero...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important lunch hour text messages with @kaylacsmalley   Thanks for supporting team bonding, @glossier #glossierplay https://t.co/CMwRro0qH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an idea to keep my spirits up during my current fight but to also shine a light on  the positive people in m… https://t.co/jcddF1WOD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow This is an embarrassment to our Country and we have no one to blame but ourselves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriseng My favorite thing to do when I get my teens phone is to add in a few shortcuts. “Ok” becomes “love my mom… https://t.co/rTe7y7BTJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#C89robandmegan #apartmentlife @ Fort Erie, Ontario https://t.co/9tHRRyGr1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lamiss927 @thehockeyexpert @woumaxx @Kotkaniemint @MrBooth_7 @olive_molester @notdrouinsogood @TheRaphMan77… https://t.co/tjX1VBXXUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @AppleSupport when im@waiting for my Uber is NOT the time to have the apps start updating, I kinda need to access that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[We I’m sitting here at this @Bucks game and suddenly it’s announced that Ja Rule is performing at halftime OKAY WHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshEngen @KarQGames @emonggtv @FRANA_OW @Jared_Gilmore https://t.co/1Ax41c62pB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big sis drops real truth #catiegram #pdubdew #dewtwo @ Cockeysville, Maryland https://t.co/olyerfrGBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered that working sucks so I am currently on the market for a sugar daddy pls hmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, @Thesoleboof for introducing me to new music. And our conversations are lit. Ayeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esa es una vende patria al igual que la mayoría de los diputados. Los únicos hasta ahora creíbles, son los de la fr… https://t.co/P7Hnnzyvi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broooo I’m not even gonna TRY to go to Disney this summer bc I know for a fact it’s gonna be hella packed bc of the… https://t.co/m62GDCIwaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f_bbv1234 @HuckleberryPies @WhiteHouse God Bless America, God Bless The WH, God Bless HuckleberryPies, and Good Bless me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night @buckymalone703 went in on #wishlist electricmaid 🎤🔥. . . . #wishlist #dopemc #electricmaid #nuwave… https://t.co/XblZmiM2HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feardragon64 @FutureofTerran @SCAstrea @SC2Epic @robbieplata I believe in u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joined our @BankofAmerica #BofAVolunteers #myenvironment team touring the @TalkingTrashPHX recycling plant today.… https://t.co/vAcUOJXxa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamScurry @WrongReel @WMassLiberty Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Had you never seen it?! Cagney is iconic. Now go watch White Heat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffRussoWKBW @WKBW This is unacceptable and they should be brought up on charges you supposed to be protecting not abusing the system]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston 12 jobs for me. And, now I'm curious about how everyone else's LinkedIn profiles look with all these jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LoveLike_JESUS I love reading the events in the Bible leading up to this. Just think, He caused a blind man to se… https://t.co/eIglQtOIez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toryshulman @SamSchacher @EricaCobb @steffrjones @KellySchuberth @dailyblastlive @BrandonLondonTV @aljackson… https://t.co/Movbb8CCWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[somedays you just want to do all of the fitness. today i was a bit down, but happy to do oly. #onesayatcrossfit… https://t.co/b9eWQLg2XN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen is really my role model. Nobody tell my mama I said that, please. 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silky is performing at a club and resents a photographer wants a pic with her backup dancers. so she dismisses th… https://t.co/RasMY5l62W]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️Happy V- Day ♥️ #yoloswag#mylifeBlike#urkrakrachic🙋🏽💯🇩🇴🔥🎶🔥💃🏽💋❤️ @ New York, New York https://t.co/J9lql9WRtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: Started the day by shooting zombies! No cameras inside, but this headless horseman was cool! #mematfmtrip @… https://t.co/DzDncKWaPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Drones Help Stop the Spread of Kenya’s Invasive Cactus? https://t.co/EnBAo6kLVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyCharms1961 @cspanwj Can you see your own deep and pervasive hypocrisy on this very issue? Democratic party we… https://t.co/5Dd2JscUc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s some niggas on the TL that buy pearl slandering Robert Kraft rn tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BentStraite Right. That’s when niggas start talking about sacrifices and shit. That’s how dumb that move was]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristieC733 Ann I'm surprise you are saying these things I'm a big fan of yours have been over 20years But are st… https://t.co/fRX1wrHI2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I have like 300 games on my Xbox one.  😅 Switch and PS4 libraries are lagging just a liiiiiil bit behind 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese Shinning light? Only in an alternative universe.Trump is cruel and stupid. Most of us want to send him to Russia collect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color and texture makes our hearts happy ✨  📸 professional pics coming soon 💐 adesignresource   #coloradowedding… https://t.co/G9MzL3zZy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your not in the medical field if you don’t feel the need to buy scrubs everywhere you go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BentleyAudrey @AmandaRay02 @sarbjeetjohal @evankirstel @treasadovander @archonsec @jdelacruz_IoT @DrJDrooghaag… https://t.co/jmEzkrUIvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I woke up to this morning Nassau Bahamas sls, what to do first😊 https://t.co/JpBkiY9pTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gotham Tonight! 1 Hour!!Bring it Jeremiah 🙌🙌🙌 @Gotham https://t.co/0dWKSxfvJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieMRA Literally same. I don’t want a crick in my neck talking lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @EagleJack7 That is dictatorship🧐 That is what socialism and communism are. #StoptheMadness #America #MAGA #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MLBNetwork it says y’all were going to show the #MetsvsAstros ST game today. What happened???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VegasSnow is what author Dan O'Brien @AuthorDanOBrien is experiencing right NoW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wonder what will ruin my car first: potholes or crashing into someone from swerving to avoid a pothole]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have become that person who calls the police because construction starts too early. But, really, on federal holid… https://t.co/c4Wd9NXiUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year later, Kevin still doesn’t mind all the snow ❄️❄️❄️ #goldenretriever #goldensofinstagram #dogs #puppy… https://t.co/HJOtbm1UUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from my lovely 4th graders! May you all be filled with love and happiness on this special day… https://t.co/KMWERRq1aU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @FoxNews Sorry, Eric. You are wasting your time if you think that Fox viewers are open-minded. Fox is… https://t.co/1scjUPYup6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio So now you're okay with him declaring an emergency for his wall,  I thought for a moment you were putti… https://t.co/1DV7ABCPZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun girls night out at the @countrymusichof with one of my faves, @MidlandOfficial ❤️ @ Country Music Hall of Fame… https://t.co/UAt19dX48r]]></document><document><![CDATA[AR is one of those states that the landlord doesn't have to make a place livable. @AsaHutchinson can't do anything… https://t.co/CBXIyt2yU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Captain_Arizona @mindykaling Why would anyone want to kiss his big fat ugly ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're getting very close, folks! Very very close! All the wiring works, but holy crap am I tired of soldering. Stop… https://t.co/lEbK7lHcOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out you probably do pay it: you got taxed when you bought tires for your bicycle, right? All tire taxes are p… https://t.co/ZeEFmgHtrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@namik_paul Namik the show was so popular n whole wave of people joining Twitter n Periscope just for you was huge… https://t.co/cp5yRqP0W2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why blocking Trump's Title X changes is critically important. Please educate yourself!! It is not just abou… https://t.co/AsecNLgvh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazart3005 @leocastillo87 @galot_antonio @Plnche_Puerco https://t.co/xWQRx0EkGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this girl thing the nail salon can control her nail growth ???? 🤔🤔🤔😂😂😂😂 this gotta be a joke or she’s just tha… https://t.co/vWIgrfkNPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're an excellent example of why I hate men. #comedy #giggle #grin #clever https://t.co/TF7WPvo2gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an angry man. He has opportunity and talent that many would love to have. Why would anyone talk that way to an… https://t.co/6S8mAAhsr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaoticBlood1 @uncledanald hello im oli I like to make colorful art :) https://t.co/EryBY841Xk https://t.co/9cB9q4il04]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LarryDavid will be back on #SNL payroll this week @nbcsnl #BernieSanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneGoodallInst @JaneGoodallCAN @JaneGoodallUK  thank you Dr. Goodall for endorsing MAPS. Africa is calling for MA… https://t.co/heiqXAznNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone to made tonight special. This is so hard but I know I’ll over come it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_pimpcess_j @taIIant Hahahah us happy prancing to the parking lot to go home &amp; rage 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is a good question. We live in rural N.Y. and I am pretty sure we are in trouble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are willing to listen to detailed apologies &amp; vows not to repeat those unconscionable errors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Retro_Series El único que lo puede hacer es el becerro de @NicolasMaduro  entonces también movió el miércoles de C… https://t.co/oDttEKbP5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcapriles Si Entrará Gracias al Pueblo de Amazonas Mercidamente Ser Los Primeros por Su Valentía]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acasiagibson @mdemoya Thanks, @acasiagibson! 🌟 https://t.co/KwPCvzRMIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times #Drag Brunch #hamburgermarys #weho #doralacorredora #MarysWeHo #dan_naab https://t.co/CO7doLEY6i https://t.co/M3VW5IKOqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etamny @Priscilla_MR21 "Once. Once was good." - Ricky Bobby   #TCMParty #IAMMMMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important things to know ahead of a #CodeRed weather day in Middle TN. @FOXNashville]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better together 👫clavex #misanvalentin . . Feliz día a los enamorados de la VIDA, de los HIJOS, de la PAREJA, de la… https://t.co/smLZThgnQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg #boysintheband was fabulous. It’s already stuck in my head so I drive my students crazy sing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People! PAY ATTENTION IN MY CROSSWALK!!! Not a great way to start off Friday! #payattention #crosswalkcrash… https://t.co/0DHRro0QCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milo__rambaldi Omg we have three now and one of them is one of those ones with food and I hate it. I still get 4 d… https://t.co/uZYZUkARJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FatventureMag Oooooooh this is Very Good Info for my comic Subjective Line Weight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods If they worked as hard to help our country we would be great but that’s not what they want]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me dijo que era su favorita y una hora después la aventé con la puerta del carro... Fracasando desde el 96.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Who wants to be connected this presidency. You will have that dishonor following you the rest of your life. Blood stained record.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You sure you weren't high? I too, have asked my sister this when she started talking funny. 😂 #BlackLightning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmoe @munsongs I really loved it. What became of murder cat? We need to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalikAzizOne @Dallas_Observer Duh there’s not enough of them. We’re down 800!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ProtectingMueller is the ONLY way voters will learn the #TRUTH behind Trump’s  #dirty dealings with Russia and wha… https://t.co/BuIccFqHdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont, you’ll waste your time waiting to do things im restricted to do 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matabroski @oamdoe @DJBABYCHASE @iAintSh1t @imemersonn @w______z @G_Alexander757 Love you 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Swiftie91_ @taylorswift13 @latelateshow @JKCorden I forgot Google. https://t.co/6VfhyAWWQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, nos hagamos ilusiones, con tantos muertos por falta de luz y no se vio ayuda, que podemos esperar😌😢🇱🇹]]></document></documents></author>