<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@transitapp I assume the agency name next to transit modes are the agencies providing the data? Streetcar and the t… https://t.co/3nR3flcB8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, @SFBART is demonstrating clearly why people drive in the Bay Area despite the traffic. Massive delays, poor com… https://t.co/P5ZwvT7KXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveourcustomers❤️  #hotsprings  #allentilleryhotsprings @ Hot Springs, Arkansas https://t.co/xoP8FGyayf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44ina4door See, your problem is you are arrogant and think you know better than anybody. That is bad enough. You h… https://t.co/MOga1cZdmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Applauding this. Be what inspires the market, not a hack leeching off the instincts of others. There’s merit in bei… https://t.co/GMlzD6qfOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The things these dogs put up with... #Hogtied #rhodesianridgeback #ridgebacksofinstagram #ridgeback… https://t.co/JPs0G8cmaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday #LucienPissarro!🎉The French impressionist painted this serene scene of the River Thames in London wh… https://t.co/NxW0s2XKcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even a solo hike allows for friends to join. @ Blue Hills Reservation https://t.co/irGTnyAEjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have drastically cut down on my Facebook usage recently, and I'm realizing that I don't miss it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason- All of the John Hughes movies are Chicago.  Home Alone included. @SiriusXMFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AD | We love BBQ, but we love selling homes in TX more.  Thinking of putting your home on the market, let us show… https://t.co/O5bmiSMOcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerriakiSan @LaceyForChange @EmilyForCO @BernieSanders And you're a bitter loser for going after his wife instead… https://t.co/bNcqrqlgD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 3 episodes left of Handmaid’s Tale, and I gotta tell ya...I’m deeply disturbed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanObeidallah You know as well as I that Barr will bar release of the report if there’s anything substantive that… https://t.co/IVkzwyZn1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Bottle Night tonight at @ultraloungeazul All tables Sold, kelly and Crystal putting in work, Epic night if you… https://t.co/YMNVyRqc2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same here and I’ve been going for almost 40yrs. Go red and your dead to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler @RepJerryNadler Impeach for what? Obstruction? Talk to @AlanDersh before making a bigger fool of yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveP34881829 @RealJamesWoods Respectfully agree 100% nobody wants to have a face full of unfounded offended femi… https://t.co/vg4VwYueOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and your girlfriend get home early from going out and drinking, “WE MADE GOOD TIME!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LayTwoTimes Also don’t come at me like I’m advocating for sexual predators...you should keep that same energy you… https://t.co/AqShMpGqN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing room only for @bryceharper3 here in Clearwater! Great day and environment for a ball game! Appreciate… https://t.co/4IkQlwb5Wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh you with little faith! LOL! I would have “Eaten “ my tweet if it happened to us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NachoRgz Comer "periquitos" alguna vez debiéramos experimentar todos en cualquier etapa de la vida y darnos cuenta… https://t.co/WHCY1Mud8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Original_Turner The #SpecialOlympics #BasketballTourney in your home State of Texas! Is this weekend Could you sho… https://t.co/4sxf526g3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rkellyinterview why the appearance of Rkelly and Juessy! In their interviews, thinks it will help what people thin… https://t.co/lLh9esfInX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haileygarza8 I mean I can put it in reverse terry and run you over again😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmatthews @rachroldan @taylorcamarena1 @UOsojc @debkmorrison Wish there was a double-like button.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The debate continues.  #Husbands. #godsgreatestgiftislove.                 United Methodist Church to take official… https://t.co/sHEBe9cIWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL @Russian_Starr Yes, a deep dive into Ms. Pirro is warranted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody still hot about @ShelbyHarris93's great #Broncos game-clinching INT. #TheDLineman 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Guercio89 Couldn’t agree more. Doesn’t have be totalitarian but acccountability HAS to exist for these guys. I th… https://t.co/YmAsYT5sfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shurider17 I  need all the help I can get -I have Hypothyroid.. have gained 50 lbs which I have been trying to los… https://t.co/Rmym7vaTxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi I stand by my characterization that ALL eye doctors are nothing more than voodoo witch doctors.  And D… https://t.co/kHWtzonkY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @RepGwenMoore @WaysandMeansGOP How's it going color coding Trump's Skittles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 3 voicemails on my phone from my dad that I listen to daily just to hear his voice. One is about his only granddaughter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is if you want give the village idiot Top Secret Security Clearance. I don’t Bowie Kuhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @CoachStew06 to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day I'll challeng… https://t.co/hGXKwFa2UX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Under 21 people..... enjoy not being 21, I drank way more under age..... bars are expensive...... by your 30 packs… https://t.co/t92zs1cBHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldyNFL Great quote! I say “It’s not real until there’s a certain amount of danger” when talking about four wheeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhacker615 @GailSimone Or alternatively, Dinah Laurel Lance is a DA by day, serving justice at night to those who… https://t.co/qTm2XFjIBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got bigger problems than a damn border wall. I better learn how to swim😬🙃 #ActOnClimate "Rare 'mega-storm' could… https://t.co/ZC6pLyP3WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Affinity Bound by @CommonRootsBeer @ McLaren Croft — https://t.co/GutR9EWS0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every economist apart from a handful of right wing loonies like Minford said exactly that in 2015]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do y'all use that shitty iphone feature that makes your light FLASH when you're in a college lecture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for my brothers this morning. May we magnify Christ today. Preach the Word! @brettmarlowe @jdsturkie… https://t.co/bWR6xBz2ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanSpindle If only you could have the galaxy far, far away as a lead-in every night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roy_churchill @BRVingadores @DanielNewman Well, I can guarantee you don't live in San Diego, California. Doubt you… https://t.co/kkyln3WUwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner last night at Upperline in the Garden District. Old school New Orleans cuisine done impeccably well. https://t.co/MjqvsUI9yO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfplante_Droit Est-ce qu’il va arriver quelque chose avec Melnyk d’ici au 1er juillet?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only the Hyperdimension Neptunia Re:Birth1 Steam key remains. The other 2 have been taken.  Send a reply to get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cashed GPP's with 10 of 27 lineups last night led by the @SanJoseSharks stack going for 44 points. No HUGE lineups,… https://t.co/xyxVVwvcba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJJRomi Not going to have a birds and bees talk with you and explain how a child would make that mistake... Howeve… https://t.co/8cbKLUe2qM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbygrl247 @TrueFactsStated They have to subpoena, getting ready to read the article.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottJenstad @MustSeeTV314 @davepotts2 @chadsch23 @usbergjo @KJ_MLB Thanks Scott, much appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySovine @abbeyobrien I can’t tell if that’s you the two guys are sitting on or not. The camera pull stops just short...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieSaidWTF No BS but the second a socialist president is elected the United states would disband.  I'm guessin… https://t.co/A1bDtAs1Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanONolan @molratty I get that the botnets and trolls are annoying, especially for larger accounts, but this ref… https://t.co/ALvS2qtgzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently If you work with someone and they take a photo of you with your camera and lens and say you can edit you… https://t.co/Cl0a4WM33y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job celebrating our @DonsAthletics Legends tonight Anthony! You are a Pro!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Westwood Town Center Cinema - @amctheatres for Captain Marvel in Rocky River, OH https://t.co/MAPXWEYW96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/QUuwOx4Tpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very proud of myself for not having a second dinner tonight #FoodBlog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaalreadyknowww They should have canceled the dunk contest after that smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[HMI data has always been funky in this cycle in terms of confidence to output and this is why I cautioned people no… https://t.co/OFfFx2PUah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gate17marco If Thomas Edison was Maurizio Sarri, he’d have tried the exact same filament 1000 times and we’d all be sitting in the dark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStigall new facial recognition software proves #Northam yearbook photo is Al Jolson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @KORcombat  #UndisputedERA @roderickstrong @AdamColePro @theBobbyFish #NXTOrlando https://t.co/uAc8r3Ql9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great artistic achievement by Alfonso Cuarón. Very emotional and visual movie. #oscars2019 #mexicanmovies… https://t.co/DMH5tFpv8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerrisBadcock @WPTV @MartinFLSheriff @MeghanWPTV @TownofJupiter The lack of feminine care products is disturbing.… https://t.co/iRgVjzK3S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSmartyPanda @AntonFletcher6 Yes. By accident. Twitter won't let me undo it! :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BOSsportsaddict @BajanRebel @celtics @tom_rhoades13 @kmike1900 @EnvYmrTurnerr @KDTrey5 @KingJames Fiercest of my t… https://t.co/hFnnKw9pol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir @Peggysue21Adams @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris @TheDemocrats No.]]></document><document><![CDATA[College books cost about 6 dollars to make &amp; they charge roughly 200. Not even @Apple makes that kinda margins on their computers 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess we all know now what a wimp Nancy Pelosi is.. Pelosi was totally afraid to call out Omar, and now Omar is l… https://t.co/LNZWhb7JZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/tkTNEioHiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davehluchy @wvjoe911 I'm trying to protect innocent life.., you want to destroy it ...and you think I have hate speech?? Ok...got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having thousands of followers is overrated. Now THIS number is where it's at. 😎 https://t.co/aLDfZadtVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[8am class is nothing compared to 8am work. I feel gucci right now, not even worried about sleep 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[woke up early to study for an exam and did that for like 6 minutes. now I’m rewarding myself by taking a nap before… https://t.co/wUCfcRV1ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the same 7-day period I watched the sun set over Venice Beach while watching the sun rise over Atlantic City.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Et on valide le pari :  "Manchester City remporte le trophée aux tirs aux buts"  Gains : 3 000 euros 😎😎😎  Tu braque… https://t.co/kWTIZnbtPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianaLima @angelcandice @RegalMovies they made me wait because I am tweeting and disabled - rods and pins in my… https://t.co/VaPLscIArK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find me somehow Lisa I miss you all the time.. I want to take you to Hawaii with me I want to take you everywhere w… https://t.co/6QZY6ZBEYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDiMarino @bkydspacemnkey @LauraAGillen @mattkamper1994 @LIRR @HempsteadTown Forgot about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegracegordon @pattersonpatte5 @hi_chriff @iamdonald2 @T_LynnMcKnight @CamDiem_ @lcgandthex @condoleezzanice… https://t.co/w78hjTPX9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nautiboy66 @DamoneHardy @AmateurFB_Talk That's fine with me,  of course you would like a guy like that just tough… https://t.co/NfMPmywKCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you’re looking for fierce 🔥 competition, learning, or practicing your skills with new friends...   Every We… https://t.co/qjHMt2yhTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Griffin vs Gump fight results; after further consideration Forrest Gump wins a close decision]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Raheel I know that Neymar isn't playing but how many times do you think that he's flopped to the ground already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bricks ounces deuces of pure COCAINEEEEEEEE ———- @OjDaJuiceman32 AYYYYYYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwenstefani thanks for an amazing show tonight and to my sister @lolatlala thanks for bringing your old man brothe… https://t.co/Rob0JqwzJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know about the famous 3 legged #Buffalonickel ?? Neither did we until Rick showed us. ☎️ (702)272-0006 🖥… https://t.co/ePWumchYhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGATOUR What’s the game plan today for round 1 and 2 tee times of the #GenesisOpen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slattimo @MollyMay1923 @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey You replied you must be listening. Are you feeling sorry for me or for yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright people, we don’t get to say this very often, but it’s snowing in Tucson. Can we just call it a day and send… https://t.co/S04az7bWXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left out in the cold, these retired #Baseball players reveal shameful #MLB tale, writes @BarryRozner in… https://t.co/RyIWiyGJqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter look for Brian and @cnn to dig out all negatives they can find on CBS reporter Lara Logan. Admits tha… https://t.co/Lh7mVV2C7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s day 1 of the challenge I accepted from @Mister_Wagner to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no re… https://t.co/JNMifLAKpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you agree, emerging from the Tour’s scheduling shuffle, @THEPLAYERSChamp back to March, as the rue King of ev… https://t.co/3DsGBZZdZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cyntrxll And that's fine. He was better than matakevich and aside from coverage better than fort.]]></document></documents></author>