<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@edmundrambo @brithume @dbongino Sounds just like Nixon did until he was impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom just sent me this old picture of us. Look at our little goth family! https://t.co/3D8m70t42a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another beautiful #sunset in #Burlington @ Burlington, Ontario https://t.co/tjCT1ySB5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the first one with a confirmed @Tesla Model 3 Standard Delivery date?  Thanks @elonmusk for delivering on your… https://t.co/hzzsBSSXGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlannyMLB with Esky gone, how many players from the ‘14 and ‘15 years are @Royals HOFers and can any have numbers retired?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bollingermotors Not sure, but the new LR Defender body was ruined. I’d anticipate the entire following to convert… https://t.co/zN55AsMsK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisalderson @GeneralHospital Great opportunity that Todd has you, Cole and Hope safe!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@18IPACapital @EigenHenry Ha, ha. Send it to info@osam.com, I'll get the book to you. Include your Twitter handle so I know it's you, cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hier, j'ai eu le grand bonheur d'être à l'animation de la finale de la promotion Vegas au @casinomontreal. Ce fut u… https://t.co/ETfPATLLs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinDuhaime @arendtiana @kimguilfoyle Post birth abortion is murder you moron!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESanders_10 @JohnnyHart7 What don't people understand about the biz of #NFL?  Only "restructure" that is fair to p… https://t.co/SXNaJn3Sm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @johnkim77 and @jonnylitecoin look what I finally did to sell my toys! https://t.co/YRwf9IM191]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumor comes from a Youtuber with damn near no relevance, who claims to know a guy who knows a guy/gal within a mult… https://t.co/PdLqmW0FsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@star_burgers @TPCarney @brithume Wow! That's a stretch! https://t.co/LJxT56MCdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fireemblem #aguascalientes “after the party it’s the hotel lobby” oops 😬 @Rico_3MINDZ 💯 @ Crowne Plaza Houston Riv… https://t.co/NaU3luSBZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[WinterBall 2019: Smooth Championship Results pt4  #winterball2019 #fredastaire #winteriscoming #fads #wisconsin… https://t.co/N9CnKlO620]]></document><document><![CDATA[Distinction I’m grappling with: User-centered design only makes sense for technical problems that have a defined pr… https://t.co/dIq3uk5Uai]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Deal: SFO to Fiji just $396 roundtrip - SF Gate: Deal: SFO to Fiji just $396 roundtrip  SF Gate Ca… https://t.co/8BuPgXAYoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @NatashaBertrand @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi @SenatorSchumer  @GOPLeader  Surprise, surprise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful to the extent imagination's ironically reason, extrapolation's grounded, true description. https://t.co/6FeMaQqfxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnStolnis I highly doubt SF can beat what the Phillies are offering. Even so, the Phils will top their offer any… https://t.co/6ylhWlR5N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gee thanks @espn us @PackPride fans really need to be reminded of the 24 point game]]></document><document><![CDATA[The regular star destroyer is complete and a good scale reference! #legostarwars #superstardestroyerbuild… https://t.co/YpMs0cZ1s1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HvonSpakovsky Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @FoxFriendsFirst w/ @jillianmele and @SchmittNYC Thanks for support… https://t.co/XPkWwxhLe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Ball, bass guitarist &amp; vocals for Voice Of Reason  Voice Of Reason at Looney's Pub Bel Air 3/1/2019… https://t.co/C92HPshNoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to @robreiner and thank you (Michael Stivic) for helping mold me into the liberal I am today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kateheartfield It’s interesting how many people (inc me) would post telling people to keep watching. I wonder how… https://t.co/JwzczqdMFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @SpeakerPelosi Democrats Need to concentrate on issues that will put them in position to win the Pres… https://t.co/mw97phMhUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@racemutt @ALF2448 @DarynPittman Last night it did not work in his favor, some nights it does.  Ask Donny Schatz an… https://t.co/HLsLYJc1du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheReason540 @BrandedRu @OzzieR89 @bb_wolf55 For real who is replacing him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josimunix Ohhhhhhh I thought this whole time we was talking bout clubs 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkorac10 Any idea where the injury is at on Tarasenko instead of just upper-body injury? Any idea on how long he'll be out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jhaneiii Yessss 💪🏽💪🏽🙌🏽. Aren’t you proud of yourself and how your results are gonna look? 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingAD514 @JaredDudley619 Who he needs to be supporting right now are the young guys on his current team. Brooklyn… https://t.co/yOhP14T5Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited and honored to be able to get back to my roots @mssupersummer Looking forward to pertnering with… https://t.co/scUwWt3VCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyroslund @Stephscreati0ns @LisaAnnWalter @Robert65459915 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump That's the point. Even if h… https://t.co/CwP4D5vVSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Camellia_Alexan @maegan_laporte Well that’s a weak perspective then. Maybe ask next time and not assume. Your side… https://t.co/7jTn690vXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Podcast Drop... listen on your fav podcast app or click one of these links Itunes at https://t.co/3hbeHXWAMp  S… https://t.co/v0Zo4N3U2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilkehagen1 @EWErickson @politicalinsidr @PoliticsGPB @OfficialGHSA That technically was probably a violation of G… https://t.co/2yUhERzutC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BulwarkOnline Hell what he's going to do, he's just as scared as the rest of those demon nature GOP Leaders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ross_Homan1 Has he been playing well lately? I was pretty high on him in the draft at 17 on my big board]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same cowardly Republicans as always.   Print their names - call them out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch Again, have the peaked around Minnesota lately? I’m sure they will find Bin Ladens son organizing th… https://t.co/C0ym4vDFy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cinloou7 @AlanDersh As a “former non-famous member of the group of famous people on Martha’s Vineyard”, let me ass… https://t.co/OQIbKVG5ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im a firm believer in food stamps for people who work full time and still need extra assistance. But for someone wh… https://t.co/BPgWUDjTG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOXRoundtable @RyanBrownWJOX Who does the cooking when she is out of town?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChanotSha I used it night before wash day, a little bit on my finger tips and rub on my scalp then brush my hair i… https://t.co/cdYdby13lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Keep the main thing, the main thing. Be where your feet are and control the controllable.” #Daily @DrKevinElko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en XEM Automotriz, S.A. DE C.V. https://t.co/2X5iJNmlXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I see ANYONE just accept defeat and go home, oh Lordy, I’m finna be heated! As a fan since day 1, I believe it w… https://t.co/jeudtc8CRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst pain is getting hurt by the person you explained you pain to...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on a long journey through the deep forest wish us luck. But always be “INSPIRED” https://t.co/jeyW0rs7bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @lagaviota521 @obrienmaggie17 @grogan537 @berracahband @BestEverYou @helen19242686 @SanaMello… https://t.co/7Ip1S4zxiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmagierowski The Shame for the State of Israel, such a moron sent as Ambassador to Poland. Will this help to win t… https://t.co/xYyMdK06la]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azzenstudent66 @johnastoehr I'd expect a fuller understanding of the Buddha from a Zen student, but so it goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeautifulRed7 @queerthoughts Well I suppose some people could wait for facts instead of  endless speculation of no… https://t.co/GSZkBuVFh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerwaters Hey asshole, trucks loaded with food and medicine for little kids were incinerated yesterday. If you s… https://t.co/twRz83wJuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup. Time for another arrest of a racist white woman for assault. #KeepRecording]]></document><document><![CDATA[From #Albania to #California. Only crazy people do business 13 hours by flight far from your daily job! #LosAngeles… https://t.co/XtMxqsAMN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrakeBulldogsMB My heart truly goes out to you. Be so proud of what u accomplished this year. @UNImbb good luck tomorrow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeutifulConnor @TheFaction1776 @billmaher @iamjohnoliver Right?  It's like negative humor.  It hurts me it's so goddamn unfunny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who go to school are gay id rather get this bread outside of school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargoAgape I hear you. But we must fast to become mature Christians, victorious sons and daughters of God. Start s… https://t.co/ACzcSSv137]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta get outta Arizona one day soon. I got to. Too too many bad memories/vibes here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcwashington Didn't we already establish that the eggs were nnot viable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superyayadize @Jali_Cat @SpeakerPelosi She knows how to work the system, personal gain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Picks at Louisiana 2-26 1st 6 5 4 1 2nd 3 2 7 4 3rd 6 4 3 1 4th 4 2 1 7 5th 7 2 3 4 (7-BB) 6th 5 1 6 2 (1-PP) 7th 2 5 3 8 #youwiniwin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattNBCBoston @denise Hi Matt, Denise...Received 2" of snow here in Stoneham, with a layer of glaze on top. Temp:… https://t.co/YL3KM5NJpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luckily it’s #audiodrama otherwise I’d need to get growing some serious sideburns for Sunday! See you at… https://t.co/qlQfQTqSvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drawnonward @BoardGameGeekCA @teoismatt @HeavyCardboard @CardboardTruth @jlobkowicz Pssht! CA to D.C.? That’s like… https://t.co/wqQyNzKEKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you find the letter “M”? If you do, retweet this tweet.😁 https://t.co/MHKNzppDsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afilando el hacha en "Halcones de Ventas 2 " en Auditorio Municipal De Tj https://t.co/Vxfe6hnFZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_WISH_utd Same here. The saddest thing in this country is that a particular sect refuse to admit or acknowledge… https://t.co/mLgwCcJPb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cszabla @realDonaldTrump Maybe you should find out for yourself and not sit in front of the TV and watch only what… https://t.co/8BvSRu6GKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random post at 4am because my body doesn't know what time zone I'm in. Gravity got weird flying back to Miami becau… https://t.co/vDCJFLfi6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so I had to stop and get this little piece of flotsam out of the back of my head. (Which I did, thanks to rai… https://t.co/cNgrqfUyie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter You'll say anything to get young people interested in old fogey music that has 7th chords.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mirror_Stencils @b_dan6 @Buckeyes23701 @FatherFoge @dannykanell Caddys get the 10% not because of a single tournam… https://t.co/kGAQzeuGGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JA_Elliott New Democrats generally don't stand for white-collar crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am pleased to announce that I will not be delivering the commencement address anywhere this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choffstein Thank you, my friend. Looking forward to catching up in LA soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathangrouns @AJacobBrown How is it that you equate pride with a desire to label things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CatDaddies of the week for YCHS football! JR Matt Spencer JR Allen Burns and SO Dae Dae Smith! Great job men! Exem… https://t.co/vaBNPkM1iS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iceberg21Slim5 @Jenifa_0_Jenny Slim.u never lived with a guy huh,  that wake up wood is killer cam, do your resear… https://t.co/zCVs01H2vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really be to busy to give someone my attention 24/7. I have priorities 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobJohnsonsDuc @Dax_x98 I think they would do something more productive with it. https://t.co/TYvlJzI1w7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellis Island NJ Thu Mar 7th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Clearing Lo 21 FRIDAY Mostly Sunny Hi 39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlitaMovie is an Awesome movie!!!!  Thank @RobertRodriguez https://t.co/K55hHhPWsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Training Angels and White Sox baseball ⚾️  beautifully outside! @ Tempe Diablo Stadium https://t.co/kulUgXntF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are going to want to hear this one guys  I can never get enough @NatashaBertrand 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 11 @Nationwide leaders have just earned their #Kanban Management Professional certification!  Congratulations… https://t.co/FGdj1tqoX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aspen___JCH Chili Cheese Fritos leap up the table,  not quite displacing the Doritos Empire, but close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeyWrestle @craigsesker @WillieAtFLO I applaud you for your stretching ability. https://t.co/jxIDwcrSsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your favorite artist is Khalid then you probably peaked in high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sommer_001ss @LeticiaReynoso @JesusEV7141 @Erickisback1 @VerdadCallada @SinlineaMx @ChalecosMx @Mariana_Diaz_Lu… https://t.co/9Veq6vZ4Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revndm Stop. You're going to make me emotional and I don't want to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @nbcsnl the shows have been really funny over the last couple years. How about booking @JasonIsbell or… https://t.co/H9oGorIPUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jccolyer  are you in #NYC Thursday @TadaTheater 7pm for “TheRehearsal” ?@MVZaGoGo Maureen VanZandt is one of the a… https://t.co/N450rY0MGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @POTUS I’m trying to get healthy to live long enough to see how History treats you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarblagGames @megadumbcast I've been into Savage Rifts lately. But I really like the original Star Wars.]]></document></documents></author>