<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@landscaperstev1 @andrerucker51 @SarahGould_SA @Itridpm @DudekLinda @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/Rf1vA0jLCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever planned a shoot for months and you finally do it and it’s literally everything you ever wanted and yo… https://t.co/thJHkOM2v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinOTooleMP You do know that your quoting lines from a fringe made up sci-fi show as reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[$15/hour sounds great and all but what happens when employers can’t afford to pay their employees that and people s… https://t.co/0dr5isG6Pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet baby boy is 9 months! Can’t believe how fast time is going and how big you’re getting! Thank you again… https://t.co/xcUlpbcurS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is too short to look for things to be mad about. The world is fucked up enough on its own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today. #creativecolloquy you never disappoint. Thank you to the most rad literary community ever. For your words. A… https://t.co/sHEnTjfHop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill When I was maybe 2 my parents were pushing me around in a stroller in NYC. And assumed I had fallen a… https://t.co/Bfdkhr3qsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy international women’s day to all the beautiful goddesses in this world. you are strong, unique, and worthy ❥ https://t.co/zwXZjlCUnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @marc_lotter @YouTube Socialism is one step away from Communism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why’d my mom just ask me if SEAN KINGSTON was the sean ariana grande dated i-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Dana, have you seen this hat? My friend (a Navy Vet of Mexican heritage) made it. @patriotordieapp I will… https://t.co/nrqA0ThhZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 He's only distasteful to them when it directly effects their pockets. Utterly selfish, greedy people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANA offices are closed today due to inclement weather. Stay tuned for more updates regarding our ADAM streaming eve… https://t.co/9FQMg3Q4qE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jonz970 @ctanner3 @ToranzoJ @way_toni @RodHillis1 @Teriface73 @CaliRN619 @NickRye12 @Abunajohn… https://t.co/8jAEWHpecC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LemaistreFred Well done leason from a true Long Tall Texan. Now you need to explain the more complicated “y’all’s,… https://t.co/XOOmbRq2oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath @RVAwonk I don't follow her but when those I do were worried, I kept checking. Glad to see a response. So happy for you all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[holy mackerel @ScribnerBooks make such beautiful books. So excited to read this. 🌸🌸🌸 https://t.co/Px1F95LVL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also please don’t fucking say “you know you’re skinny” and shit like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mims_words Isaly's ice cream. Seriously, is there anywhere to buy Vienetta any more? I tried to find it online a c… https://t.co/QYJ1wKeEo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep and I’m lying here thinking about every embarrassing thing that’s ever happened to me https://t.co/ARKzNeO741]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still trying to process the @SamandColby and @KianAndJc collab and now @thisisLANY and @ShawnMendes might be a… https://t.co/O95vEOKChJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shirahanau This is a lie. It exposes antisemitics Big difference if you were honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekahunter He is such an elitist snob. His obvious contempt for middle-class America is sad. But - he is stupid… https://t.co/BL8uX2tMdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StahlTrystan @riswold @nordstrom_andy @brandongeraets2 @marie_chloe02 @ellymaee09 @Olivia__Stelzer @MasonGoeken… https://t.co/BRdidNI8pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryScribbler Sometimes they astonish you and overwhelm you with pride. Then you realize how lucky you are to be witness to it. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomDaddy11 @CountOnZach @_IndiaMorgan Orrr the one pizza could just go 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ Please HELP ROXY CHANGE HER REALITY and get OUTTA this SHELTER and into a LOV… https://t.co/C9azvNmr7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 50 years, America drops again  Agent Orange on Vietnam! #VietNamSummit #Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[mi bebito tiene auto y cama ya😍 no lo conozco pero ya lo amo💚. mis amigas me hacen feliz]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG I so do not want to drive home from the airport right now. Hope teleporting is a thing before I die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i spent the last two whole days at the san joaquin valley jazz festival volunteering and now i have to goto work and i really don’t want to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Bailey for admission to the Med College of SC for occupational therapy. Congrats Alexander for an offer at… https://t.co/u0VgJSrtpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apollo11movie was fantastic! So glad we took the little ones to see it! It was so cool to get a behind the scenes… https://t.co/NOOA4oud8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[“we’re not friends with benifits because we’re not even friends, we’re intercourse acquaintances”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to be part of a team that volunteers together #plantbreeding #bayeremployee #teambuilding https://t.co/0Q7Fllma6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk what bars you go to where it’s considered sketchy to go alone but maybe you just go to the wrong ones??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends, Romans, countrymen, I am getting 110-190 FPS in OVW training room we’re back in the saddle for sureeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[📌He esperado tres meses por un permiso de trabajo en Usa 🇺🇸. Finalmente ha llegado. Tengo entre miedo e ilusión de… https://t.co/c0KXiVKd9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current guesses are current guesses: Monster - Kevin Hart Lion - Rumor Willis  Bee - Gladys Knight Rabbit - Joey… https://t.co/5gaRqEfE4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love moms, no matter how old you get they love you... snuck my valentines gift in my sons backpack, he just f… https://t.co/taKCmP04b4]]></document><document><![CDATA[31 years ago on 3-10-1988 The World lost #AndyGibb 💔 So #Talented #Young #Love  🎶Wish You Were Here🎶 https://t.co/u6TWA8Cviy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I move in my first apartment with my boyfriend in less than a month and I can’t wait to get my backscratched every night!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night out with my sweetheart ❤ stevecer21 @ Downey, California https://t.co/lOox3ecz53]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only time I don't get annoyed when someone calls me Janet. It's a great day for coffee! #starbucks #monday… https://t.co/7M2wudtgLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[we should stop calling them “anti-vaxxers” and start calling them “liars” or “people who are wrong”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow There are consequences to our actions. Good for good, bad for bad. She chose poorly and now has to… https://t.co/Mdxhbvugfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took my bff to the hospital for stomach pain.. after squinting at the ultrasound screen for 20 mins, I guessed ga… https://t.co/y4Z0qJ3LUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexLeavenworth 1. I love this.  2. I’m trying to wrap my mind around how to reconfigure my 5-inch boots so I don’… https://t.co/m7cv5B00Z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCuban: politicians who make it to Congress have a defined role as legislator to vote yea or nay on pending bills… https://t.co/7G4EqmVkUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #Annapolis! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/ZRHHhvqIWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martin_hayn @RegSprecher @MunSecConf Ich dachte....in den USA sind die Fanatiker hauptsaechlich auf der Rechten We… https://t.co/RZBB6Lv0XO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread! 😂 I think I still have my old Intellivision console packed away in the deep recesses of the basement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lady_ruthven There are people in the metaphysical community pushing me to teach Kabbalah but honestly it feels a little blasphemous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keepitdeanly @univofdayton rightfully earned and graciously accepted 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[...is it really already Sunday night?!  I swear I blink and the weekend is over😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one and only Sandra Cisneros! Chicago pride 🙌🏼 #LatinoUSAChicago https://t.co/Vwn2VwFZwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siubhan_H @badzoot7 @AcampbelTeacher @Zigmund_Fraud @Rosewind2007 @KimPaddockASD @djt10 @JuliaHadley15 @SueQuez… https://t.co/b5kFIDGRo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your varsity girls tied for 1st place today at the Frisco Invitational!  It was a very long day with over 20 teams… https://t.co/rUDr2eSsFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s A Good Tip 😂: Maybe if we all sit extremely still,  Monday won’t be able to see us. #Mondays #WOW… https://t.co/Fq2qdAkSkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zac and yoshi are cuddling so adorably in their sleep and I want to take a picture so badly but they are also so peaceful 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindofrezO friend me at genf966 and call me at +19737673086 okay https://t.co/AA7e2qL1UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Venetian Resort Las Vegas https://t.co/5dycO5S78e]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; few clouds temperature down 74°F -&gt; 73°F humidity up 69% -&gt; 78% wind 14mph -&gt; 10mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElGiganteDiablo Ellie: *mumbles, then does that awkward hyperventilating laugh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexsolarez Lmaooo when I got to Joseph’s house he was like babe did you smoke?? I was like, NO i was freaking hotboxed against my will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickygervais I am not often moved to teeet anything personally, but your show moved me in ways I didn’t expect. It… https://t.co/3CDgiU9mW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@club_berebene I`m Professional crystal cup manufacturer、if you need pls contact me .all of my products are handmad… https://t.co/m7fiTvd8GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cynthia75684948 @JohnIECedu @CanadensisMax You beat me to it. Lol I was going to write the exact same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Husker Power isn’t just a quote it’s s reality! 4.5 years in and I still call on my coaches @RhondaRevelle… https://t.co/OBxdXrGKpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean if she worked out that bottom part she would look great I’m sure (:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ronald_vanLoon @DigitalTrends @evankirstel @kashthefuturist INTEL = DYNAMIC TECHNOLOGY!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Datathon teams! Great to see so many UofI students spending their weekend on data challenges.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How will you fast from sin these next 40 days?  "By the sweat of your brow, you will eat your food; until you retur… https://t.co/Moyb39uX70]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m up... but now I’m not. 🐶🦴#Weimaraner #blueweim #weim https://t.co/dyQ9KiLB9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabethscraig: Using Twitter For Your Author Platform:  https://t.co/EK9Sh4yljH  @wvancamp #wkb71]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fan update still 1-0 Ridley Tigers. Headed into the 3rd period. Let’s make some noise 🐯 https://t.co/0FprVV4EHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genuinely thank for my past relationships, for the people who got me here today and taught me so much about myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! I got pulled to a different unit tonight and the boy who I drunkenly slid into his FACEBOOK… https://t.co/ZG8oM3eSNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone deserves a Happy Valentine’s Day! @ Gresham, Oregon https://t.co/bn1HyEodCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby Wait, sending food to another country instead of his own?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some real grown heartless ppl out there who are obsessed with bullying others yet probably wouldn’t say a… https://t.co/aINqc450RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper saw this on tv - NOT reruns - considered sex ed back in the day https://t.co/G591DLbjXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be wonderful. Hope they get the support they need.  #ClimateAction thank you @EnvDefenseFund… https://t.co/sukc82AKgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I cannot believe how amazing this was.  Nothing will ever beat tonight #jonasbrotherssecretshow 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhymeswithleia The most famous person with my name that I can think of is like 100 lbs max, so probably. But she l… https://t.co/SMQR5ddBsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are the bestest of friends! 🐶🐶♥️  #Puppers #GoldenLabrador #DaschundTerrier #PupperFriends @ Indian Bayou, Lou… https://t.co/hSoZptZ4FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anamariecox Limited access to wet food is unconstitutional and will not stand. https://t.co/dPLngUrtJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC All I can say for the President of Mexico is that he is the best president so far. Those journalists who said… https://t.co/o4Bj7Lk4Ox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring forward (har har!) with arrowgroupdc open houses! . . 1623 New Jersey Ave., NW   Open 1-4pm 2 unit rowhouse.… https://t.co/zoULFcv6SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephan_Tyson @Vegunz @AMAAnimalRescue @_PJParker_ @Canine_Rights @DogRescue2014 @Burtonportrescu @cassandra17lina… https://t.co/laAwead6Ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witsupcom I have a vague enough recollection to be very nervous about this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had no idea Rami Malek was American!  Makes his role even more impressive! #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDaveTPiR No Diggity. I’ll take it — missed it being the Macarena by two weeks. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hondaprojason My two little girls and our CTR look forward to seeing you tomorrow at cars and coffee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan wouldn't know the truth if it came up and bit him on the ass in a locker room. #impeach45]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to calculate what credit score you need to get a mortgage for a house https://t.co/vcEcX227dN via @freep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalwomensday ? Women serving women (and everyone else too). is there a better way to celebrate ?  Proud… https://t.co/mkgwgSIqTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 22 to 24 years he shouldn't have lied. But he has 2 more trials to go those sentences are suspecte… https://t.co/go0lQVgPQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strange, coming from a woman, who would’ve allowed (and encourages) her abortion (or that of #BABIES like her). Hyp… https://t.co/GM157INtMh]]></document></documents></author>