<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Greg_Byrne Please consider this man for our next basketball coach!!! https://t.co/xmkhLdo9zK]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Sacramento Bee reporter was detained at tonight’s Stephon Clark protest. A photographer was shoved to the groun… https://t.co/QDzQ7E7hOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck is it about the last minute of each period that this team always gives up a fucking goal?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieMcCullough @KerriKendall Not so random, but I did send a bouquet to Ms. Valentino for V-day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scottbrasher1 Ur Sweet Juan! So R Ya’ll! 💋MUAH💋 https://t.co/EmXvBTq33P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the third anniversary that my cousin Muhammad AKA Terry Ali passed away from multiple sclerosis I miss him… https://t.co/iFUJ2Jwjbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YesItsLynette @KarQGames @emonggtv @FRANA_OW @Jared_Gilmore https://t.co/VjbABnd5cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald trump has ruined exclamation marks for me. I cant use one in a tweet anymore without thinking it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HeartOfTurtleIsland book by #MarkZelinski Page 16 #Manitoulin Island https://t.co/6ez8BRSdqY At Sheguindah… https://t.co/On3z20p6wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX2News Yes let's keep this summer time hours I'm sick of falling back in the fall]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the #1 thing you need to know about #Iceland !  Welcome to your Nordic Hell! Full video here:… https://t.co/hADS4P7BGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it once... I’ll say it again... Andy Isabella could not be more of a Patriot... Belichick has already signed him...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyhawkerfinds @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @POTUS Another Republican sex trafficker if children.  This is wh… https://t.co/W16R53I01f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manny_ottawa You mean "catching up to Canadians" other than stupid Liberals, the NDP and Green Elizabeth May. Our… https://t.co/pZhxfrwex4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elguapo64 @BreitbartNews I think he's just trying to get his client used to being on the receiving end of gangbangs...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tell my step son to get me a Twix and texted me this 😂😂😂 @twix or does it? 🤔 https://t.co/wVfhanEYlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[we #grow within the #storm  we need the #challenge, the #struggles we grow within the storms our #faith is strength… https://t.co/JDv6ohEzn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If #Friday had a musical intro, it would be #Thursday! #ThursdayMotivation https://t.co/zWZZSbTkVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just leave me alone. I know what I'm doing. - @RaikkonenOficia, 2012  https://t.co/mxuzjAhXBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathrynvarn @Ellen_E_Clarke @amy_hollyfield 67ers unite! I got the chicken scampi AND I took the second entree (sa… https://t.co/0Vmg1gQMT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he restructured to fit market value I don’t think this is a conversation anyone has to have. But to maintain the… https://t.co/Qdp9oDUWZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rellsestev What do u like about it I need to look at the channels, only reason I’m even considering fubotv is caus… https://t.co/WXEAJhwS0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bienvenidos a #Miami. Great trip on the @DisneyCruise #Magic. Looking forward to the next one. https://t.co/Q7suBXVBZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[No es posible que los SUELDOS que se pagan a las cabezas de los organismos "autonomos" se sigan dejando como un cab… https://t.co/EhrfO4m4cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tru_marooon @gatorman23 @ScoutSteveR Don't change the subject. You didn't sweep us, even though you are bragging b… https://t.co/F8VgVprASn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penn State beat Virginia Tech.   Virginia Tech beat Duke.   Therefore Penn State is better than Duke.   That’s how this works, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakeThemMastrIt Thanks for letting me know. I forgot to open up the permissions for this demo. Should work now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A todas las viudas de Messi que mojan la bombacha con sus goles de hoy les recuerdo que jugó el mundial caminando y… https://t.co/va8Oq2h2Vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Trump does the right thing. Kick the father's ass out also. He sounds like an ISIS sympathizer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have WFH tomorrow per snowstorm but I don’t have WiFi in my new apartment yet so um where’s a good place to work in Greenpoint?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mossow @vinman905 @NikkF07 @heelEvan @KwnStorm @Beers649 There is a right way to get heel heat but this is wrong way to get heel heat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And of course I’m sitting here tweeting about it instead of actually doing it. 😑😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gavan_Sanghera @knickthoughts You wanted Wenger dead and now have a header saying you miss him. If that isn’t an L I don’t know what is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[should I watch #VampireDiaries ? only reason I'm considering is because its about to be gone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cblackst @Sheila_Copps Absolutely disgraceful! This just goes to show the long work we have to do to push these mi… https://t.co/uCTDNl1yZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard that dudes in ATL walk up to you in the club and tell you they fuck raw, as a way of flirting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCharlotteWWE Good morning to u, are u ready for a triple threat match.? After watching #Raw yesterday… https://t.co/fmqk3HBvEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealDisco @Paul_VanDerMeer @funder noboby but you and FOX News pal. LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTeaz89 @Dee_Beautiful_1 @DianaPerince Yeah she is just there. He's not directing any of it towards Gayle he was… https://t.co/K4wgtYxjBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you call me I may not answer because my ringtone is the office theme...🤷‍♀️ sorry not sorry, hopefully your call isn’t important!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is everything!! The whole audience on their feet! Everyone singing with @MariahCarey I feel the vibe!! 💕… https://t.co/M3eK5IVioA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitanfallBlog I love your game so much, but I can’t go more than 15 minutes without it crashing on me. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of people are these assholes, the evil in people anymore scares the hell out of me😳🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelastkvng 😂 that nigga 50 a straight asshole some the shit he has said but he funny asf with it and Floyd is always gonna be Floyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[G’morning, Tweeps! Please give yourself plenty of time to get where you’re going safely! There’s an inch or so of s… https://t.co/MOdPhMCMwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firstdrafthell The "ground floor" of Seattle is actually the 1st floor. What your seeing is the true ground floor. https://t.co/3jZBGhozet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jefferson, North Carolina https://t.co/DZHXUrvwAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd Did you know Obama declared 13 national emergencies while President?  I don’t remember the media or you… https://t.co/2Pf0B0a9cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started cackling while that Dion 3 was still in the air cause right from takeoff that thing was crooked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else have the flu and are too hot and somehow too cold at the same time?? I can’t be the only one]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy for my best friend she’s been through a lot and I finally saw her genuinely happy last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico What the hell was he waiting for? Will he call for another 'emergency' when congress rejects it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ONLY good thing about the clocks turning ahead an hour: the cats think it’s still 4am. So they didn’t wake me up! Idiots. 😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haley’s out tonight so what do I eat? Fungus and red stuff of course! Yummy GF flatbread pizza with Parmesan, tomat… https://t.co/FkDtoxrZs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi Bella Ídola @anettemicheltv ¿Verdad Que #EntreNosotrosDos Hay Una Linda Y Bonita Amistad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jill Ellis has the most talented, deepest team in the world. Someone tell me WHY she doesn’t play them in their bes… https://t.co/ibkGz3QMk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoDucksnet I was just looking back at a Facebook post of mine from 10 years ago lamenting that our football team o… https://t.co/gEklaxgPFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope someone signs Kaepernick and builds an offense for him just so people can be reminded why he was benched BEF… https://t.co/0VkYzkicg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A balmy 30 with wind, but it’s great to see the Cats in action! #BleedGreen https://t.co/VUn5vguBdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Peace to everyone everywhere pass it on form #Florida Best #Value #Wedding #Videography &amp; #Nextgen #Game… https://t.co/zfBo8lsEoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp so relaxing - Drinking a CBD Pilsner by Untitled Art @ Trouble Bar  — https://t.co/Wcj9Des6sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been able to grow and learn since my time working with the GOP and I’m honored to have great activist friends… https://t.co/tgn8LUZ7DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello New Yoooooooooooork!!! @ John F. Kennedy International Airport https://t.co/OpLJ5S757O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardTHardy Let me know when the mastermind @MarkHarrisNC9 is arrested]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Somalia is her home. One of the most barbaric and polluted places on earth, fecal matter flows alo… https://t.co/RyuOIbVLGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to @nice2meetme88 every time he come trolling down my timelines (plural) https://t.co/0ePdmc4pSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV Broncos Get a Walkoff Hit in the 9th to Beat Corona 2 - 1! Marich drove in the winning run to score Kaiser from… https://t.co/BQIwovw2fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why so many Americans refer to The Netherlands as Holland.  Stop already!  You're furthering people's ignor… https://t.co/mrwaLAQo0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impedimento O Barça hoje é um time merda com um gênio salvando todo jogo. Só aumenta o seu reinado neste século. J… https://t.co/aEYKWjaX37]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of the ConUS Precipitation Forecast 03/03-04 #NWS NEXRAD Radar Reflectivity and time synchronous Winter Weathe… https://t.co/90bzH4UqwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surgery went great! Feeling much better than I thought! Day off today and then start prepping for the @ValleyHoops… https://t.co/IiGpZVXfCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raycomfort Well, this little bit of Ray-ism doesn't appear to be serious.   Do you have a history of repeatedly ma… https://t.co/VSrmPyzhbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who thinks basing military nuclear bombers at a commercial airport in a residential neighborhood is a good idea?… https://t.co/MaINyKnDbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wxmann @sdutKrier Yea we're near the airport...apparently the bottom fringe of the AR ...still a good soaking...hope it comes south today]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2008 #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram #tutorsofinstagram #poetry #poems #writing… https://t.co/YHNDEvuFow]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my Monday email this week I mentioned that it was so hard to capture all the cool things our teachers are doing… https://t.co/iBXjay1YKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember seeing this last year in Lynwood and I was wondering why the McDonalds had turned their sign upside down… https://t.co/e6wAkV6k5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarrySoetoroTM Doesn’t quite look like Creepy Uncle Joe’s speed! Oh, there you go! Ha! #CreepyUncleJoe2020… https://t.co/l3yuTiIirC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemackey Good chance you have if you live in Kitchener-Waterloo! #worstroads]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun!!!! For our TN peeps needing some much needed sunshine.  @WRCB https://t.co/lKAWIgvkC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMikeGuy @brandt004 @thedrive @DKorecki And more. https://t.co/jahATB1x5D https://t.co/PBNvr6Bq3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warriors vs. Bucks or Raptors betting favorite to be NBA Finals matchup https://t.co/D4T3CjgVS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ De Gustibus Cooking School at Macy's https://t.co/ScHNjPuCKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost weightsonwheelsnj with get_repost ・・・ HUGE Congratulations to our student athlete Griffin for winning Distr… https://t.co/jeCcOUNMML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would not want to be the moron @UGABasketball fan that threw the stuffed UGA onto the court and cost them a game tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmcp66 Absolute madness Ranieri only got 3 months to work his magic...Khan is insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a Time in the Old West! #oldwest #happytrails #blueskies #mountainman @ East Glacier Park, Montana https://t.co/YvggFATwbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_bratt @jbblawmd Vancomycin doesn’t seem to have hit it much. Slowed it down? But not improving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @CoryBooker @maddow There was a  #HowardShultz @CNN town hall #TownHall? Did he serve coffee? https://t.co/fX25QI62cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @mschlapp no emergency declaration has ever been issued to do a end run around the House of Representat… https://t.co/tsKPkus2oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reaction is a level of enablement. One that I don’t want to allow anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember the "(first lady) Hillary bombed Bosnia" hot takes?  Those were fun. The Russians found gold when they out… https://t.co/Nkx01vbr51]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Rest 4 Tne Talented  Mz Blue 2 be blue! Just Keep. Moving 4ward Kiddo!@unite4strength Remember When &amp; Now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parroting someone’s tweet about parrots is peak Twitter. https://t.co/lLjnui3Yub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSzanti @cenkuygur Lol, ministry of journalism? Is it so bad to want to be able to trust your getting the most… https://t.co/2lGLNQUSPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went Threw My Basement And Found All My Dad’s Old WWF Figures! 👏🏽 #MemoriesOfMyFather #DadsOldStuff… https://t.co/9mrWX3gm83]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we make laws to allow doctors and new mothers to decide whether or not to murder a newborn child, what's next, e… https://t.co/WQpPj0MixA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second he declares this national emergency is the second House Dems should collectively introduce articles of impeachment, right???]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you always say “no collusion” but you’re on video saying “Russia, if you’re listening.....”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to know what someone fears losing, watch what they photograph...]]></document></documents></author>