<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? LPG Palliative Care Physician - https://t.co/ltw1UWMk1I #Nursing #FortMyers, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @InSpiteOfTrump @SenateDems @SenateGOP Thanks @SenatorCollins for supporting the far-right criminal in… https://t.co/dtXflE1Ted]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tabletoptuesday fun time vans with @Secondmoto tonight. #rydazryde #lifebehindbars #tabesforthebabes @ Chick-fil-A… https://t.co/ClpJzJ9DSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was JB’s first of 22 runs yesterday! His new record. (He could barely stay awake through dinner) @JBHarvey3… https://t.co/u9z242U3WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenifa_0_Jenny @WizzyDizzymite @Astrochologist Jenny stop caping, she can't write or play the piano, u have low st… https://t.co/N1mZKLxViS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilsolondz what kind of HR was Yandy's? Fast moving missle or majestic and deep?]]></document><document><![CDATA[*not begrudging all homeowners but it is a critical lost perspective in city govt in a highly volatile time, where… https://t.co/bWDa2PzCXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve talked a lot of shit about trippie redd but this shit slaps bih https://t.co/OJVYvP1U7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddZolecki This is starting to feel like Jeff Bezos is involved in another form of extortion. This drama with its… https://t.co/TOHdwIhe14]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAKE $10,000 EVERY MONTH IN 2018 NO SURVEYS THE EASIEST BEGINNER PROOF M... https://t.co/SJPzwLVKla via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 cleaning products that are cool.  https://t.co/kcHfOgxRle  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Why wld Trump be "embarrassed and humiliated" by his tax returns being made public? That question… https://t.co/JArSSLC4a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellaHudsonFCA I’m torn about bringing my family. I miss my kids while I am there but if I brought them I would ha… https://t.co/B9JerLBPop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcb05 When I realize the horns may have more wins than the Rangers this year. https://t.co/4PhBhMxCzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @IvankaTrump @SecretaryRoss BULLSHIT. stop lying for the treasonous Trump!!!!  You’re embarrassing yourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerLenox Why were the firefighters already on the scene of a grassfire that clearly just started?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone stop me from buying this edible arrangement, I’m in a dark place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbiaBugle @SpeakerPelosi Too drunk to even know what she is babbling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning #TwitterFam!🤪 Have A Blessed Day And Remember To Brush Off Any Bullshit. It's A Brand New Day, Utilize… https://t.co/Z8nKhGBuGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how old you get or wherever in the world you play, there’s something about hooping 🏀 in the park that bri… https://t.co/ULjXfqv1eL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyndseyAlana I'd call you something scathing like a young whippersnapper, but my back hurts too much. You doing well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Hi Alaska, my name is Kevin Simauchi and I am so mad at your Airline because we have been moved and canc… https://t.co/FlgJRokdoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Classics: McDonald’s Classics are, without a doubt, the best thing to happen to bacon. #TeamClassics FTW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraigMeyer @JonHardister Would love to hear more from both of you about the efforts of this bill, and to talk with… https://t.co/YDEIOfBdl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But those who #trust in the #Lord will find new #strength. They will soar high on wings like #eagles. They will ru… https://t.co/tRx1GymuEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[He won’t be you have to be a Trump supporter and Republican for that to happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN So what you are really saying is that Democrat Rep Illhand Oma is a fucking Idiot, we understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaneTJv69 @JustRyCole against a 73-9 team and then again against a team with 4 all stars on it. Bron did more agai… https://t.co/xfISc6ZI0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoopid_matt The back of the mansion scene is the courtyard behind the Canadian Opera Company building on Front Street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiderLoot I’d say it’s more likely that Bills pulled out because they got wind that AB would never show up for them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HR 1 #PoliticianProtectionAct violates constitutional rights  under 1st Amendment by expanding definition of politi… https://t.co/SdWgFi9eDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best subreddits: /EarthPorn and /FinancialIndependence. Change my mind. @reddit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marujatarre Me han acusado de eso y mucho mas, pero eso no me afecta! Hoy estoy contento con la llegada de… https://t.co/ISBWqkyrjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoiscockrobin @InterMat It is the bald man getting his jollies, again. It is tax season. Should you not be busy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[City officials make case for more funding to repair aging, deteriorating streets https://t.co/XjdE47w2Ei via @tulsaworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaureenOBoyle I am number one of 9 children and only one mother. I know your childhood must be similar to mine exc… https://t.co/q7kzgW15qT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes a little bit of luck...  But you're already pretty damn lucky...  You got me in your corner...  If you nee… https://t.co/N83MJk9SQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I wouldn’t expect much out of Bird.  All Voit has done is hit hit and hit 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_souliTude #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/DN8Bhr8jfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom The Jayvee team is defeated?  The story, how B.O. pulled all the U.S. troops out of Iraq...]]></document><document><![CDATA[After one look at this planet any visitor from outer space would say, 'I  wanna see the manager.']]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at myself like the child of god, that I am since I’m staying in 😇 https://t.co/MGTzxEqSY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinche_chillona Hahahahaha fuuuuuuuuuuck. It really sucks that you’re watching that alone lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is trashing tannehills value but he will be highly sought after once he’s released.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittGuru Thank you, Harry. Very much appreciated. My brothers Ron and Bob read your report and sent me a note today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God Bless America! And God Bless the future mother of my kids ⁦@KendallJenner⁩ ✨❤️ https://t.co/Fr6yBp9xRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woulda been jumping over it pretending like I’m @chrisbrown in the Next 2 You video]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of rich the kids dudes gotta be tellin, he be getting robbed every other week lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @JTDrook to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews - just the… https://t.co/WtVMFMYPkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlantic Salmon with deep-fried salmon skin, Quick recipe, remove skin from salmon and scrape off any excess meat,… https://t.co/ShJpHPQ6eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying this out w/ my lovely bride and our friends ... (@ Green Street Smoked Meats in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/lLijl4OAQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maniacmiler @gretchenwhitmer Glad to see you doing the work of the people. No one more qualified.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you Ketel Arizona? #diageorep #ketelone #ketel #vodka #westgate #westgateaz #salt #vip #bottlegirls… https://t.co/fUyorLCq67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@searls @marick That’s because they were idiotically getting excited about technology buzz like micro services and… https://t.co/XcIXtB7oZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2398-2350 W Washington Blvd 2398-2350 W Washington Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90018 https://t.co/1idyeC5YT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last entry in the stroke brain sketchbook. Goodnight. • • • • • #sketch #draw #sketchbook #pen #instaart #doodle… https://t.co/KzOt7QSEAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, and please provide it as a shortened or text link, not a URL, which are not descriptive, and are ugly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Old Numbskull by @AleSmithBrewing @ Beerage — https://t.co/WuCzADTqWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders What’s crazy is that a candidate who or serves to siphon votes from the opposition is running.   Now get the freak out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending get well wishes to @AmandaJane321.  Being sick is never fun!!  ☹☹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon everyone!:) Also wanted to let you all know that I now have an Instagram page for my company, Timoth… https://t.co/7EsoNLZT5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Gonna, God Said this morning. Amen @ Sussex County, Delaware https://t.co/1VadRm3V09]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found Cat! (Capitol Hill): Found a very sweet cat, hoping to find its home! Microchipped but not registered. Not su… https://t.co/89YNHfIopU]]></document><document><![CDATA[DONALD TRUMP TO BE ARRESTED NEXT!! ROGER STONE GOES DOWN! https://t.co/OqwFd0hPQ5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the point in the day where I cannot comprehend my podcasts. Gotta switch to music now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livlavidalychee @tjawoke Idk bout affordable lol but yeah state universities are just as good as Uc’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Video of Justin Williams scoring early in third period*  Don Cherry: there he is gettin the OT winner what a player  ?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyHSD Bonds is the goat bro, even over Griffey. And Griffey my favorite ATHLETE ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. Afraid to be the butt of jokes, and there was a gymnast he was in love with at ASU.  We told him—as awful colleg… https://t.co/MBBol7Tlb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Games4Kickz I think it's a great idea.  You could to a mini series of each alpha from A8 to A17. Ending with a blo… https://t.co/kAWF2FDBOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my family husle day and night for you 2 and ur mama @AshleySauce https://t.co/5LJSrZZZWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trap Therapy Thursdays - Free Cup before 10pm ($2 after 10pm)   $1 Off Drinks w/Cup @ The Legendary Boobie Trap Bar https://t.co/C6ECL5qMzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBR @DCComics @TomKingTK @MitchGerads That would be great. I’ve had two copies of Mister Miracle #1 (VF-NM) for ne… https://t.co/SaYlENTdnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@covvb0y @JayBilas Multi-billion dollar industry identified as "amateurism" when it's convenient to line the pocket… https://t.co/AJ6XT89zkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter dropping Adam bombs this morning @PatMcAfeeShow https://t.co/ohpudDTgkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy with the opportunity I’ve been given.. waiting for the right people in your life is always worth it 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful views in the country in Indiana.  . #igersmidwest #loveindiana #loveindy #myindiana #picoftheday #indiana… https://t.co/c46AxCXtGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The casino sport books are posting all bets and odds this weekend. Stay tuned!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithfullyBP Once, the editor of a Christian magazine took me and a pastor to task for it. He said the church is t… https://t.co/qy1eVBb0YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is love and basketball the only movie on the TV side? How did Steve Eurkel beat Brandy, Damon Wayans and Tisha… https://t.co/21VIZENzzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely training at midnight for no reason at all. https://t.co/NrRbaKisac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnAPairChris @humberto_wwe I was there with my sons!  Yeah, he stole the show for me.  I had seen him on tv a fe… https://t.co/Y5KzQezfmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJMLCMX2 @RCle420 @NalaReigns @fatboikay89 @BobbyBattlelyon @kokotwist @camdasilva He literally said he made a hun… https://t.co/TbXOJDT1yO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge TS Ellis sentences "Blameless" Manafort to four years...waits with bated breath for nomination to the supreme court from Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse This the stupidest thing I have heard this morning. But coming from you it's to be exp… https://t.co/g0RbXWVJZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyMrsRR1 I still believe were building the wall on the wrong border ... 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@205jw Lil jake dad was upset lol 😭🤷🏾‍♂️🤣🤣🤣 he should’ve used his super 🦎 muscles]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only thing green about #greennewdeal is how much green it’s going to cost taxpayers,” Mike #Pence at ACU’s CPAC on… https://t.co/OWXxqx2p88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigShaneW @JacksLures @OnTargetFishing @dyehardt @Fat_guy_outdoor @FarOutFoodz @BlueCollarFishn @BagwellFishing… https://t.co/0izrtAtrvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we all agree that @RepRashida is a bad ass mofo? ❤️ #CohenCongressionalTestimony #CohenHearings #ImpeachTheMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes sir, I have a @gwenstefani in my life, happy Valentine's day Hazel, love of my life! #HappyValentinesDay… https://t.co/or2RF20ysp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickyPDillon @adamandsteve Ricky I’ve told you we can make a song literally everytime I’ve seen you for the past year 😂💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FearHavok @SantanaLAX @Ortiz5150 @PWRevolver VIVA LA RAZA 5150! LAX GOT GAME AND THEY'RE THE BEST TAG TEAM THAT CA… https://t.co/MjiJMjlfRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angiestweeting @MWoody29 @SenSchumer We know democrats make laws they themselves won’t follow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still Mad AF My Plans Fell Through For The Wknd Smh..Was Hype As Hell For No Reason 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know what genius was like “you know what would be tight? Mixing strawberry and banana and making it a drink”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway @MTA where the fuck are uptown A trains ?! it is 9am on a weekday, everyone other than @MTA is held lia… https://t.co/Ks8ZljovYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[La juegan a los correctos solo por tener un puesto más alto que el de uno. 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UglyRunningFace #NoShame #Represent #KeepItReal #NoFilter @ Portland, Maine https://t.co/qF4orRBzTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willyking212 @TheHerd @ColinCowherd The most pippen ever averaged in the playoffs was 19 and anybody else on the t… https://t.co/Y11lDWBxDh]]></document></documents></author>