<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[S/O to dude name Jay for the tip at work :’( so kind of you Jesus Christ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray to the old gods and the new that I raise my son to be literally the opposite of the asshole featured here. 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to the reviews, I’m the only one who sees a ... um ... problem with this banana holder. https://t.co/Z1HZxj6jVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pg_Benson Keeping the hope alive. GO YOU REDBIRDS! https://t.co/UmwqSO7exu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woahhhh wait a fucking minute bitch 😂😂😂😂😂😂 please watch this until the end]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edit of this cutie @bordie_ ✨💖✨💖✨💖 #bordie #edits #vsco #picsart https://t.co/33Fwq6wnN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: using my hockey images for profit, commercial use, and redistributing it in ANY form is illegal. Ask permissio… https://t.co/cwB0H048nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[cumberland has brought me so much stress, but it also brought me one of the best friends i have ever had. you are s… https://t.co/dA8CYuppXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcpatenaude @EnricoCiccone @IanLafreniere @David_Hlne @DomAnglade @marcpatenaude juste a regarder l’image j’ai le sang glacé!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The year may be 2019, but this photo is 98 degrees.   #contentisking #90skids #welcometodetroit #litfam  🔥🔥🔥 @ The… https://t.co/UqsnczYmb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B &amp; Bruno Mars - Please Me (Official Video) https://t.co/VKBkxluAqV via @YouTube yaasssss @iamcardib I see you 👀♥️💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Funny that you list the opioid crisis. Where does the majority of drug come from? Through the souther… https://t.co/irpPtX7m8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @NRA @realDonaldTrump Do you ever shut up. Your a Hateful Snit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making It Happen!!! #youonlygotonelife #getit #motivation #thursday #doit #beingthebestme #goals #shaunalaneteam… https://t.co/J6PugrFKBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyon talk about the Value of the New Born Baby "Body-Parts on the Market?  https://t.co/zvNF2LxMNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anc08c What did she say that made this ok?? I didn't wach it, but i cant imagine what would be excusable other than rape]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A137HEA If you don't mind a bit of advice from someone who knows... try to stretch, stay hydrated (very important)… https://t.co/ph1t7oS6gQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meu auge tendo que silenciar tag de novela turca 😂 https://t.co/8BoYQyZdEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Video – Learn About The Wonders Of #Israel And The @ICCM_Israel - the International Community For… https://t.co/JAO0i2EtdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a child walking to school while talking animatedly on her iPhone and I have never felt so Old Man Yells at Cloud in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl what that roach ever do to you?? So #rude. So #angry. #movie #AMC #reaction #LiveTweet #spoiler #Alita https://t.co/d70PZWh7rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, why is the @UN just sitting by and not doing something? Children dying while locked in cages isn’t violat… https://t.co/edao06Jo8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lord_Calvert @barneyray1 @ErinZirpolo @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump The same way you refuse to believe Trump is spread… https://t.co/3x8hbpv2w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandorable1968 @CanuckSassy @CandyisDandy100 @QueenBeeCanadas @2Suspension @kbllaw @RandomOntarion @mally_da… https://t.co/G1y5b82rrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson I’m trying to learn: don’t let anyone make you feel like less of a person. Know your self worth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinyhippo1979 So excited to use this in my Victorian history class next fall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UniqueStore #SanDiego #flaneur #streetphotography https://t.co/80TjwXTsvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamOnTV Oh My Gawd I’m so happy I thought Green Book was being ignored and it’s my fav of the bunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @SideHustleWino @VinoSocialNancy @jillianne_gray @RedWineCats @suziday123 @DivaVinophile @GrnLakeGirl… https://t.co/JBqhSq5M4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenCryptoAckbar @IlhanMN Huh...and your choice of the word color was what? #hellopotmeetkettle #IQmatchesPotus… https://t.co/NHKikuZXP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally no one: texans on go texan day:                   ☝🏾.      🤠        🐛💤👔 🐛                  ⛽️.👢… https://t.co/CkbxvD45J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who would’ve loved this song? Lmao 😂😂 @alexissssrusssh @alexysX_ @_JassssyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could go to sleep right after a nut like niggas do. This man snoring and I’m folding laundry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliGirlKandi @ErinCondren @WeWomenTogether @jenniferdnadel @GillianA I really love this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volunteers from across #Missouri converged in our capitol yesterday to oppose Guns Everywhere, #HB258. And sporting… https://t.co/l2FENAbWOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE AMOUNT OF SUPPORT I GET DAILY IS FUCKING UNBELIEVABLE &amp; ITS HARD TO TAKE IN WITH MY SENSITIVE ASS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Lord, that when I cried out to you for help you answered me. Thank you for turning my life right around!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTSchoolPsych  Our own Paula Gill Lopez is presenting at NASP. We are proud of EB Member, Committee Chair and Univ… https://t.co/r8jmao2Bum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamieblynn @evan_real @jaydubargh @nickhautman I watch everything on bravo BUT vanderpump... I find the people so unlikeable I can’t do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoleaPfeiffer @Lin_Manuel @HillaryClinton Just start singing Stop the World from CFA. That should do it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardio this week!!!! @ Anytime Fitness Potranco https://t.co/l5y9DKEcq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npaolucci7 @saramz20 @kd_smith You know we’re about to make your wedding sooo much fun !! Get ready]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkLeneve @Axolotl_2019 @rickygervais @WeatherDog3 Ok, I’ll work on that. 😆. It might be a British thing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r0xie_f0x Mueller and the SDNY are handling these issues. I’d prefer the Democrats to work with the Republicans on… https://t.co/uWPMRWPyn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bitch who my ex cheated on me with really texted my best friend talkin about “Let’s hang out!..”  LMAOOOOOOO exit where you came.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyArquette I've been thinking the past few days that I wanted my mom too. She's gone almost 8 years. https://t.co/CXKG5gF1H1]]></document><document><![CDATA[not ashamed to say that this why my intro song on my myspace page for a hot minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @jeffl76 Impeachment should have happened right away. It should still happen. It needs to happen but f… https://t.co/dW0Bf33UOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SainTroop @sainkendall I am assuming @sainkendall will be making those for us Winterfest chaperones as well! 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Go back to your office. You are too damn old, too white. Give it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is very disturbing.  I feel bad for Otto’s parents. Trump’s behavior is very scary for a president, he continu… https://t.co/hh7eQALPA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t even look forward to the weekend because I have a paper to do 🤦🏾‍♀️😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[who thr director of housing at #MyAsu cause im about to cry about this water .]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had to celebrate our Blues tonight with a delicious Mexican meal #santafe #mexicanfood #delicious @ Santa Fe Res… https://t.co/NG3eRSiANA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMANGO @ChicagolndSpdwy @704NASCARHeat @DannyLeBlanc24 @dega_boy_87 @KCJO_LABMOM889 @Pixxydoodle @spyderrider63… https://t.co/TomstKPFWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rathompson01 @chrislhayes I agree with you, Ray. Where's the backstop to this? Is there a positive way to interpret this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched new station19  episode! Amazing! Tune in March 7 @abcnetwork  station19_daily #costumedept… https://t.co/AvaZrcoS9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radixalem Dude she’s seriously the cutest thing ever! Evert time i see her pictures i show Jason lol he was tellin… https://t.co/XrZaub8lHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cate_the_Gr8 @dvorakoelling I dont think the majority of white America is ready for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is such a interesting yet exciting day in politics. It’s soo juicy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEXT Orlando was a blessing! Back at my old stomping grounds at Westwood Church. Being in Florida meant I got to se… https://t.co/CpHMddoyg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 DDU-DU DDU-DU by BLACKPINK (Korea) on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/WwL3xOQXMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will be sunny days... There will be gloomy ones. 🌞☔️ It’s how you deal with the “gloomy” ones that matter. Do… https://t.co/5UAayw2xBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dantej21 Omg!! Praying that nobody was gravely injured. Thank you for sharing this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triviainsfire I can see both sides. I am all for Amber alerts and trying to keep kids safe but there has to be a w… https://t.co/MVNqr6pwVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t trust bitches who tell  their friends business like girl keep that that between you guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[You either support the legal way or you support illegals being hired when there are not enough US Wrks available.… https://t.co/E8xXUObFad]]></document><document><![CDATA[The adorable mess to the left is mine. Love this crazy kid and am always proud. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so fucking upset and I just laughed it off, like it doesn’t matter to anyone else so why even care myself???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC I had a dream about you last night, no seriously! I dreamt I was at a very nice drinking establish… https://t.co/xLlSA9FdPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelloKelly333 @sianoresist Tell me you took a picture with her!  I love her!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joan congrats on leading and providing resources for WBBall at Tenn- I don’t want to be against you- I wanted you o… https://t.co/kzxEAFFwbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lewis is still crying. Because he’s a diva- and I’m over here like “I have to buy him EVERYTHING he wants and check… https://t.co/E7Y5X78aCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC folks, come join RCDC on March 16 to hear from @RepRaskin &amp; @DrVikasSaini on drug pricing reform!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @iluvleafs @SenatorCollins Since when did you let what was in the best interest of America guide your… https://t.co/ef7A3BFf3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCunninghamGHS is the best at these conversations. These kiddos are so lucky to have such a passionate advocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker just asked me why I’m not pregnant yet. Uhhhhhhhh maybe because I’m a child myself?????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valentinifrank this is who we want not Jasam why is this so hard to understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaetlynnnnruiz I love #InvestigationID and #dateline !! #deadlywomen the acting is always terrible but I can watch… https://t.co/zgMoXzcbLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaaaah Paul Holes and Billy Jensen are going to have a podcast in the Exactly Right network. Yesss!!! April 1st.… https://t.co/oZsUGLhowe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @Sp00kiiee @shanemcmahon @WWEDanielBryan @TrueKofi Yayyyyyy❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Safer barriers walls are very crucial safety for the racing car drivers and these walls take the he Technology is… https://t.co/WCq6677BbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight fucking up. I be seeing these videos and it makes my mouth water and question ?🥵😖 Like first of all where… https://t.co/ebyKQFQCCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet, a pesky fence between neighbors 'festooned' with razor wire and rumor has it there is more to come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NijahRenae i never participated in pop outs 😂😫 except like freshmen year. lmfao i’m coo on itttttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh @RosieM1919 Could be too much botox has not only froze her facial expressions but may be responsible for… https://t.co/MJK2aKLNdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[when it’s the day of love &amp; your soulmate lives in another state https://t.co/xl1is1OkRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww 😍😍 WoW   What a splendid news this morning   Yeeeee Yeeeeee💃💃 💃💃 https://t.co/Nqh65GqN5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buddies 🥋 #LoveUs #Karate #LoveHim #LegacyShorinRyu #Legacy #Family @ Sir Wilfrid Laurier Secondary School https://t.co/neWAQ5FVB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came back into the classroom with the flowers Mantha gotnme and the kids started asking me if I got married. HAPPY VALENTINES DAY. 😂💐💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FantasyStocking @jxsswhite @Wyld_Wych @Cammydoll @ky_klicks @GingerLiqueur @Naughty_Toronto @geek_toronto… https://t.co/FNuP037HTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC: @GOP just confirmed a known member of a #WhiteSupremacist hate group to the Fourth Circuit Court. This is… https://t.co/gkTbJex2aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpovic02 I'm a woman but this is getting rediculous...  I don't think we NEED TO RULE THE ENTIRE DAMN USA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all who joined us today at Magerks in Horsham for @SportsRadioWIP #BirdsTownHall AWESOME day with… https://t.co/uad4Z6zezz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I saw his blatant LIE, yesterday, on MSNBC, and I was horrified.  My horror isn't directed at Trump,… https://t.co/XvPtmrGik6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wear Red on Tuesday March 5th for our schools Respect Rally! https://t.co/jzKLH5NIBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhondaTorreson @ShortndPatience @emilygigs @rhymeswithvery You really said upsilon instead of y? Im crying 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw That would be THE national emergency. Trump declaring the election rigged and attacking the results was t… https://t.co/DFwSC6TE4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cat #catsofinstagram #catstagram #cats_of_instagram @ Fairfax County, Virginia https://t.co/AooNyjvAGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huerta_marcus @james23williams Yes I do believe this is @james23williams dream!! 👟]]></document></documents></author>