<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@rondom92 Na just student loan debt. Mortgages are good debt for people to have. Student loan debt however is total… https://t.co/TK1kHctd40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryLeathers87 @Kyle_Mahnke I’m a wee bit younger. 07. I know a ton of Antonian 05’s tho. Kevin Michel is a good friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillerMike what’s the name of the black shoe company you mentioned on Vlad TV Interview. All i heard was Classic, didn’t catch full name]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkhammer @s Here are a couple of honorable mentions Concrete Angel, Martina McBride, What Hurts the Most, Rascal Flatts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @BoeingAirplanes Who controls the access codes to the particular Boeing rc chip? Recently hacked? Access… https://t.co/XT7bGlaFgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynamicWebPaige @krisnova Unfollow bug 🐛 has been making the rounds...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Always Eatin' Dinner by @BeerdBrewing @ Lowell Heights — https://t.co/M0kgPrC9MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to prepare to call a game...with the goodness and comfort of Pete's! 😍🔥 @ Pete's Restaurant https://t.co/KZ6bIDyai9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go #Browns! Can’t wait for FA announcements to start flowing out of Cleveland. https://t.co/kediyznUrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always love learning about the great city of Owatonna from Mayor Kuntz. His love of public service is obvious. We… https://t.co/AG6EhitJb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Mexicali, Baja California https://t.co/cPg9xbIHV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best scenario to wake to would’ve been: 1. Harper signed with LAD 2. Weir fired  3. Walton fired]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jscotthelton @JenScott35 @_ImNotShai Excuse me James, did you just take her side???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo McCabe was obviously telling the truth about Don the Con.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_jerostr @realDonaldTrump You should be tweeting to Satan, for the Dotard sold his soul to him eons ago.  Trump… https://t.co/e5XxLN5Ky2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Columbia #Thunder +18 on the year @gamecocktrash #greatestrivalryinsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal Ocean Grown Crew One 💚☯️☮️🤬 @oceangrownseeds https://t.co/vggskCiwQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vuhdo @jkmaclaughlin The follow up response of the gif is incredible 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louisville should be removed from tournament consideration after that embarrassment of a game]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy pub week @ilya_poet ! loved rereading your poems from both DANCING IN ODESSA and DEAF REPUBLIC 🙏🏽 looking for… https://t.co/s7H9MuIMeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjesse You made Jen laugh too...I can totally picture get doing the exact same thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow that was quite the crash! 19 cars. I will get to watch my first race under the lights once they get going again… https://t.co/NcIccA2a9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sadly won’t have any traction because the Democratic Party has no space for actions like @GovernorVA but there… https://t.co/HUymR9Qyx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up with one contact on and now the world may never know where the other one went. 💁🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Superherologist Purple and green are also used by Disney to note a villain. Sometimes, red also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for some realistic talk.   NITology.   Gamecocks listed as a 3 seed in NIT on this site.  Listed as a 4 by SB… https://t.co/KHs9jeWbrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Hey Keith, are you hosting the Not Top 10 on Sportscenter tomorrow morning? Trying to figure out if… https://t.co/mnwxrjPKx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this soul playlist on spotify where each song ends with like 2 mins of scatting and I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ken_wheeler @trueadm @sebmarkbage Surely you can’t be serious. https://t.co/K05ZAliHSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaDNews @NewsHour Well done! Always important perspective from you.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/MrNqggTGaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... how often do you change things up? #gym #gymshark #gymmotivation #fit #fitnessmotivation #fitness #fitfam… https://t.co/uC5jRZ5Fac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a tweet that said there’s hard working women In the sex industry, how it’s it so hard to lay on your back… https://t.co/Yek1Tfi0WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMo37540912 @darhar981 @IlhanMN Apparently groups of Jews in MN told her to tone it down. She didn’t. So they… https://t.co/58P61IIbaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday. At least she liked the gift I got her from my trip. https://t.co/F9XBXCOLTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgreenesix @KymFrank @Cbmoss @WVUSWG @TVanWoeart @MarsAVIT @The_AVLife @road_av @vacajun @NECDisplayRenee No. I’m… https://t.co/uQsEDPJp87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conorgrayfilms To this day the most incredible, breath taking thing I’ve seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I can call about the ending of the Daytona 500 race yesterday was divine intervention]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blodd20 @Marcus_Mosher Don't know how a person couldn't fall in love with Eighth Grade...one of the most emotional… https://t.co/k4UVHMNry3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the @Orioles on @masnOrioles and @realbenmcdonald is a #baseball analyst #Baltimore #Orioles… https://t.co/hhSLhTcDIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Central American history up to the present is just one prolonged derrame de sangre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryancrawcour Nope, but I'm in that age range and will have only had one dose, not the two that is required for lifetime immunity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gneicco I was the National President of Close-Up in 1987-89. What a great organization. Enjoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[how is society not even using the sarcmark yet when i already need a punctuation mark for when i’m *not* being sarcastic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHesselhoff @jonbellion @Z100NewYork @elvisduran This has to make the cut on the next mixtape for sure 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since the behind the scenes that @drevinciwrks kept on getting flagged. lol I had to make my own #behindthescenes… https://t.co/pWPO40KmFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kung_Fu_HoeDown @sahluwal First off they werent raped and no suggestion was implied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Have all your extra extra liberal free school nobody pays but more taxes friends vote smart this time]]></document><document><![CDATA[This group of union workers just went outside their comfort zone for 12 weeks and performed in plays they wrote in… https://t.co/xBQXlOR46P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicvaiana It used to be one of the working class suburbs of SF. In recent years, it was massively redeveloped to h… https://t.co/IXO1BJYDER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProjectAuuman I was damn near in tears at the end and was reminded "oh yeah the Incredibles 2, stop showing feels"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryBr15507394 @donniedeporte @dodgers_randi How’s it feel being always a bridesmaid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesNe23829680 @JohnHookfox10 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Yea greenback man for socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osita_chidoka It is insane. This is exactly why progress eludes us. There's so much waste and insensitivity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad Father James Mitchell and Sü Yung they lost the war but a deal is a deal now Rosemary got Dark Allie on a l… https://t.co/VfxPZwBBoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myrtle Beach..... I need u in my life. 🔱 @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/x7xEpyi3bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOE_JON_FINLEY @TheKspecial_ Tell me about It!!!!! I’m just happy to have shared the same meeting room with guy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Eclectic Boogaloo by @barebottlebeer @ Sand Creek Pub — https://t.co/mJx5XOawyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matmenpodcast Apparently Christopher Daniels was being considered, Jake Roberts would have been interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in the hell are this little boy's parents not in jail for child endangerment? I would argue that had he died, i… https://t.co/8s633DtYke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump 🛑WHAT PUPPETS GOP CANT EXPLAIN AWAY.*MR COHEN WORK 4 FAKENEWSTRUMP. CALLING MR COHEN CURRUPT.… https://t.co/I15IyS3ZFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gelshenen @MoneyLobster Factors also show you which stocks *not* to own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at General Wayne A. Downing Peoria International Airport (PIA) in Peoria, IL https://t.co/qIe6lPcVOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe, It’s not a solution. You don’t know who you can effect, love, make smile, inspire. My sister took her life and… https://t.co/87mfWXVrxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how @realDonaldTrump can quickly call out @JussieSmollett, but can’t call out White Supremacy. Ijs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Louis Armstrong New Orleans International Airport - @no_airport in Kenner, LA https://t.co/Cw8lnSRtFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Career Opportunities” was on the new episode of A. P. Bio and it was perfectly placed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTooleConnor2 @CoachKyleConley @lakeeriembk Congrats you have worked very hard to get where your at.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photos: Try #Hockey For Free Day at the Mullett Ice Center in Hartland https://t.co/sh9bBsSAtI @Mullettcenter… https://t.co/zxGs9kTbpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smellysj ever since customer service told me I wouldn’t be getting my free tote in 2017]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiSiCkLe Ha we’re not organized enough to script it. We take notes while we listen(mostly just to recall which son… https://t.co/EViAf2Uv6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[While simultaneously also admitting to want to install via the 25th the Vice President who is only Vice President b… https://t.co/4XNRJQYaNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[He lies more than pelosi and schumer Schiff claims there's already 'direct evidence' of collusion by Trump campaign https://t.co/tP2Frp6epQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews What an idiot. Take a look at the Dumacrat platform. That's the greatest danger to our nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdawgswift @OSAASports I’ll be coaching our 12 seeded wrestlers and hopefully headed back home with 🏆 in hand. I’m… https://t.co/x6InW6rTxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeNerlens and @Keefmorris will be a MAJOR part of the playoff story for the @okcthunder 💪🏼 #ThunderUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear September, please hurry home I need some G10 throwdowns!  #rockytop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris surges into lead among Democratic party candidates https://t.co/tqpS0hIYSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadloder The ones I write...  Go back to code I've written a year or more ago... "who the f wrote this tripe?...… https://t.co/3TBRtOX5Oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  High school stoners on their Snapchat stories: https://t.co/0koRwXQQA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo..Many...Wall...Balls #trainhylete #HYLETEnation #hylete #crossfitnorthcobb #crossfit #19point1 #wallballs… https://t.co/jPomEA7Ppo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There always have been repressions and there always will be. As long as the state exists.”  - Varlam Shalamov, The… https://t.co/SItRMehikZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible season @SCWarriorWBB! The energy and spirit you brought to campus this year was incredible. We a… https://t.co/F4NdCH6CRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When anyone tells you that Gentry’s record as a head coach doesn’t matter and is a weak or lazy argument, ask them… https://t.co/d0ue7wSABH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I also had an amazing dream of B after a long time of praying is insane. God and Blain are amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #SundaySessions-have a great Sunday! Share and Tell me your favorite hymn! ✝️ #worship #gospel… https://t.co/x3Ivw2ve2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s reading a script someone else wrote for him.  People, PLEASE, he is totally incompetent. What more do you need?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the gayest bear on Twitter today?  Thank you, @Devinsdudes https://t.co/PKlEhOui46]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Unión Europea ahora, con el maltrato que la tiranía le ha hecho sufrir a miembros del Parlamento Europeo, padece… https://t.co/a5MVw8RKfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[MISSING WOMAN - Gabriella Antoine - Missing since Jan 23rd. She has a medical condition that affects cognitive func… https://t.co/7TDkfUUbqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What businesses don't understand is that just because hemp was legalized doesn't mean we can start putting #CBD in… https://t.co/3C7wrl9pJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump USA Law for Being in the USA is a lot like some of our other laws. U have a License/Permi… https://t.co/bO8jCYV454]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyRedsGal The look on that baby’s face is incredible. Like WTF you doing to me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped by second grade at Porcupine School today to do some math 🙋🏼‍♂️ Thankfully it was just addition...… https://t.co/TMVz8LMWYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then Matthew thought of something he hadn't before. Maybe McDonald’s, he thought...doesn't come from a store. Maybe… https://t.co/hNtKjWHUU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PtCreditVoter #cdnpoli I know just fun to point out  that you never know who is throwing shit from the dark and we… https://t.co/oZy7o61DUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolTrent if your PG also plays baseball this must be the only form of play you’re allowed to draw up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aroomba Smh. Lyft use to be better but now they want to charge me $70 to get home. Heeeellllll no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveryancarter thank you for an incredible message today at @NorthRidgeNews Your love for the word of God truly pours out! #Grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 @tseaandland NOW ALL YOU trouble making liberals. THIS IS NOT. I repeat. NOT black face but green face.… https://t.co/Ev0DTGAzI3]]></document></documents></author>