<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @MBrake02 What is he...three?! Use your better words. Please. You’re the Prez, not a toddler, for God’s sake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📢 MATCHDAY! 🚨  Get in, Beach Gooners! ⚽️🌊🏖   #WeAreTheArsenal🔴⚪️ #UEL🇪🇺  📺 🚫 💻 @brlive 🍺 @FroggiesVB 🔗… https://t.co/iN60VriqH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeepBeeep33 I see what you did.  I'm not a Trump supporter, so of course I saw it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Williams notes schools can’t discriminate race, religion. Dress code is allowed, though. “This is a generic bill al… https://t.co/Bv9Kcp47lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grown_upenough @ObvslySherlock @bookgirlwlove @HarryWatson1988 Eye fucking is a form of safe, consensual friend loving]]></document><document><![CDATA[i tried... i really did... but im back on my graphead bullshit 😔🤘🏽🍇 https://t.co/5JeIhlZKUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s sad? Your baby holding on to your leg because he doesn’t want you leaving to go to work ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travel overnight will be slippery. Slow down on the roads and wait until daylight to travel, if you can.  Watch… https://t.co/AfmobO7lDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third, he was given three opportunities to repent in the three questions that his father asked him and three times… https://t.co/MuhtHC15ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Addictions (A Thread):  From loving people with addictions I’ve learned that people with addictions have one view o… https://t.co/kOxchc1AZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[(reposting — apparently GIFs don’t work in IG🤷‍♀️ Re saved it as a video) •••••TUESDAY!  What a great day to be ali… https://t.co/IOwxzhdboG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse It occurred to me that Okawa new the outcome not the journey. You see, you wil… https://t.co/JVY8wDz6q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My momma took me and my bro out the streets from a different country she had get 2 jobs so we wouldn’t go hungry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f0xonee is such a nice boyfriend bc I made some neat fried rice and wanted mac and cheese with it so he paused the… https://t.co/vNtl8eYPit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhanStopMe I beg to differ on M&amp;Ms and skittles and other sugary junk.131 countries 400+ cities and counting ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a hopeless awards show fanatic. It’s too late for me, so save yourselves. In other news, Gaga’s necklace. 😍#Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@60Minutes This idiot should be embarrassed that he didn’t have any evidence other than wishful thinking to start a… https://t.co/HyvHIWqFRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap!  What a year for these freshman! Nice job, ladies! @AnkenyNorthview #allactivities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KtinaHarris @EyeCon3000 They announced Stephen Colletti. Is there more going to be added since @KtinaHarris said n… https://t.co/m9u19CDQSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay Blessed With This Amazing Grace A Cappella Version! https://t.co/04vSMRHV86 beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanDechart @ForTheWhyn Thank you so much for stream @BryanDechart 💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialRezz @ErikP0711 Look who’s in your city!!   Afters at LVL?? 🤭🌀🌀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSLalonde The function of Butts not very believable counternarrative was deniability. And his story doesn’t ho… https://t.co/q9QCNEXhIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ngl watching these girls use meat as a personality trait just pushes me more towards going vegan. Like eww I don’t… https://t.co/HUpfa6rRHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reggieaqui @girlscouts @stcookie What the heck is the savanna smile????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliOberlander @HillaryClinton @EmergeAmerica @emilyslist @runforsomething @NikkiHaley @RealCandaceO @IvankaTrump… https://t.co/peTlaPXjF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[😬🥶  #tuesdayevening #coldweather @ Massachusetts https://t.co/1zlxvWRZlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrFullertonMPP @lparkpc @KarahaliosPC @PBethlenfalvy @ONPCWIP Happy International Women’s Day https://t.co/Eokv3tYgcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfc92zx @ewarren You're missing the point of what Sen. Warren is saying about consumer protection and removing their influence from  D.C.]]></document><document><![CDATA[45 FUCKIN DOLLARS ???? 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭 That broke ass bitch. That’s an 80 dollar set out here man , shit maybe more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuckkkkk. I hate getting up before my alarm goes off. Don’t call me before 8am thanks 🙏🏼 #DoNotDisturb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave Ridiculous! We will remember them and vote against them. They don't want us Safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganwimberly74 @ShannonSharpe Then why are you watching his tweets? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night Brenden asked which tooth brush was his and I handed him Nellie’s and he actually used it and I haven’t stopped laughing about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetSpectrum hello, we live in a rural area outside Buffalo, NY and last summer they installed lines to get cable,… https://t.co/pOWXFXueTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbraStreisand @churchboutique I see a "Kindness" in U I have not sensed B4. We're same age; I've been a fan sinc… https://t.co/tRFmmlfmXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks pretty cool! https://t.co/5PURvaPMCg #sschat #scitlap #scichat #sstlap  @kerszi @Katiemc827 @kylelaurie… https://t.co/lQLuLSAQi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@word_criminal @AmericaNewsroom @LindseyGrahamSC @BillHemmer @HeatherChilders Because I follow foreign policy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[bottle cap crafts - Bing Images #hilarity #laugh #grin #jolly https://t.co/1FMTelUCwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMtheType @Kandi ✨AWESOME FAMILY✨ I fell in LOVE♥️ with CANDI after  watching her on this show 🌟👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTube All Americans should watch this video.  Be warned that AOC and others are not who they appear to be.  Keep America safe🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch And #ChristopherPaulHasson  Is a very fine person. After all what’s wrong with wanting to kill Democrats a… https://t.co/5DJxZE0Nse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xoComfort I’m glad you said this cause it looked really good in the trailer but looked like it had potential to be corny 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[In real life, I’ve been fasting for three hours and I definitely don’t need Trix. Maybe this weekend though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My environmental science professor reports a turkey that lives near her property to the DNR so that they won’t hunt… https://t.co/Pobbnhw9qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ceirrah_ Dont you know that if you do not have the same opinion as someone else you cannot be friends!  Basic stuff here !😂🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll ban a bitch from booking with me in 2 seconds... sorry. I’m not the one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @realDonaldTrump @VP Thank you @Franklin_Graham 😇 for a spiritual reminder. 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you’re dating someone who’s name is also an abbreviation for “thank you” 🤦🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/M6mmFHvg0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Your so worth it! You work hard and deserve it! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @realDonaldTrump Tom it’s a shame how your blindness to the truth won’t allow you to see how this president has lifted all boats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he wants to right a wrong. He should work to get girl in texas out of jail for voting not knowing she couldn't.… https://t.co/SuPlrFcUCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article about my amazing cousin who conquered cancer &amp; is ready to trek to Mount Everest Base Camp!… https://t.co/beJrokVmOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eckitsyoux3 It is!!! Can i just be a student and in debt forever :))))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@52Frog @CBSNews @60Minutes Nope. I’m talking about mr McCabe. The president is under no criminal investigation. Nice try though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc what anyone says, the way you treat people reflect how you really are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... it was good! #adayinthelifeofcarynblack #realtorlife #philadelphia @ash_a_laaaay @ Butcher and Singer https://t.co/uslcteKVdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisona15 @Mistywatters Don't have nightmares.  Enjoy this exciting time.  AND, make sure and give @Skrubba05 ple… https://t.co/ET6omPOVsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwoodjeff I’m pro human but working hard to improve- it’s part of the reason I’m starting @LeadershipPort1 move the needle locally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy, but still pretty. #Gatlinburg @ Gatlinburg, Tennessee https://t.co/GTuzPbqsXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I created a back to school playlist for you to ease your nerves about your first day at UW,… https://t.co/Fbo3OM2hz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of you @JimmieJohnson and Team48.  You could not have been more relentless! @allyracing #chasing8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are accepting playlist suggestions for our road trip to Mobile tomorrow.  Go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I’ve seen myself smile or laugh as much as when I’m with Zach, I found myself a keeper]]></document><document><![CDATA[When women support each other, incredible things happen 💕♀💕  Shout out to all of the women in my life that have inf… https://t.co/8JdExFLOyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait till Taylor Swift releases new music and is the cause of my death]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling that🏆 kind of night #MakeItYours @UAAWBB  @NNUSports @ESPN3 520pm pst @DarrenGoldwater https://t.co/NilMheeOQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EPA  This is the National Emergency. People are sick and dying in Flint. https://t.co/2ehzPA7Iwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even in the mist and fog HIS creation is beautiful! #nofilter @ Peaceful Getaway Cabin https://t.co/KhVEfXmAWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This💚💙💚 supporting Organ Donation AWARENESS! I actually had the chance to share Allie’s story with her teacher @ co… https://t.co/qcL3vI9yGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachaelGreen @DjHushka @jen29wil @STARZ @Outlander_STARZ No other couple will work as well as Jamie and Claire..… https://t.co/DbYizBZP3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sad but important story. Victims should report any abuse to @MIAttyGen at 844-324-3374 or https://t.co/KOtdAnz1wO… https://t.co/RIQJKvqFLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my head in the clouds and my feet off the ground. 💙🌫 Tag your favorite #gemini (Although they will probably s… https://t.co/HQrLvxGmnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casual conversations with @swilensk:  Me: Tomorrow’s Valentine’s Day! You actually have a valentine to celebrate wi… https://t.co/LrYK83sV4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonEllis5 Hahaha that is awesome! Have you ever live tweeted a show? That would be awesome😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWriteWhenIRun So true! I occasionally run onto short stories that have my name on them, but which I have no recol… https://t.co/OHX8cJeQcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the flowers fade, a little still life from Casa Hipharpy’s Valentine table. (@HollyNorton2 knows that our ma… https://t.co/iKnrG8sJzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMMAHIXOFFICIAL And I quote “any man that can’t sincerely apologize for making a woman uncomfortable whether it wa… https://t.co/2AzmuvDlmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marielvaldes Te extra mujer! 34 se ven bien! Estoy buscando un tweet que me encanto!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HedoCosmetics shadows, @ColourPopCo through my eyes palette &amp; @KATVONDbeauty lightning liner https://t.co/Rh22vUOf5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiStateJournal Because if an Act 10 case came before him the first words out of his mouth will be "I'll be imparti… https://t.co/wPT8QCbYKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 more weeks and the only real pain I’m gonna feel is getting my whole back tattoo’d whoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Analyzing and plotting data on Titanic’s life boats. How many more lives could have been saved? #lpsleads #starssc https://t.co/9Z1PE1OemI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyknitsshit @peterbakernyt @nytimes @nicksearcy I agree and they need to take "news" off their logo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cory_B_Mason I just wanted to make sure you were watching. 😉 I had no doubt we could screw it up! 🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love a good athleisure look! I land up wearing outfits like this often because they're the easiest/most comfortab… https://t.co/Kf1MGv4u25]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a note to myself to watch that documentary about misophonia I just found out about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul I doubt it. Every time he is asked, he quickly says he is not a Democrat, he is an independent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Labour will back a public vote to 'prevent a damaging #Tory #Brexit'  https://t.co/Jh0UWGN2Wx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: PHYSICIAN-SPARROW URGENT CARE - https://t.co/MPacHuHhK3 #Lansing, MI #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamCrack15 what does that have to do with being a licensed cosmetologist? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re all just living inside a Robot God’s artificial simulation, so what does it matter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen To be fair...it didn't get good until the dunk over Shaq😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southercandy @grumpcrusader @Valma_Bunce @Pigface0  @MikeJMele @MyMJJisLife @AlexaRenee1 https://t.co/3up9pqOd2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daffodils are already blooming in Nashville! 💚🎉But our weather is schizo! No it’s more like the three faces of Eve!… https://t.co/TeW18Qg5Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I've been extra weird/annoying recently. Will investigate reasons after I say some other weird shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nachomdeo No te gastes, manejaba un camión y no tiene ninguna oportunidad de salir del marasmo utópico cubano- rus… https://t.co/N5F6wHXFZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the ride with my kitty! #Tigger #catlover #catmom #catsofinstagram @ Mountain Home, Arkansas https://t.co/NbwxOqWWui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous Vintage Books 📚   — —————————————— Comment MINE when you find your Vintage Love 💗 and direct message with… https://t.co/tHtXZLCK0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#8: SHARPAY👸🏼  Sharpay is an outgoing and dramatic leader. She always gets what she wants and makes sure a job is d… https://t.co/xqAjgbVDdt]]></document></documents></author>