<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Clem’s, Neon Sign, Williamsburg, Brooklyn NY #clemsbar #clemsnumber1 #clemsnumber1forever #neonsign… https://t.co/C5DgdevSqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charles__Kay @jimj266 @sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein if she berates impressionable children publicly on camera, imagin… https://t.co/x3jFxq05CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best deals and coupons for https://t.co/NV5VTtOodg https://t.co/OujGKVAoqV via @yazingllc]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @dmorey’s logic in 2017, @JHarden13 should not repeat as MVP.  His award was well-earned last season f… https://t.co/lxIKWOMMyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow my documentary “Celebrity Entrepreneur” premiers in same slot as Tony Robbins “I’m Not Your Guru” at AMD… https://t.co/BjCSyO8aq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoltonSharp I bought one of her books once for a quarter at a thrift shop. It was way overpriced, but I bought it anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my valentine right below 👇 here.  My amazing, excellent mother Stephanie Williams.  ❤❤😘😘.  Happy Valentine'… https://t.co/JbcWv45Lgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will see what shakes out care to elaborate Sinclair producers your talking about my life I'm nice harmless]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love reading the Trump Deranged Syndrome Liberals trying to twist #RacistJussie’s story around.  Especially multi… https://t.co/v7QSVlYT6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of the folks who listen to the music I’m a part of were born with that same privilege. If you’re one of those… https://t.co/YWpzSQcIrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAMBINO PLEASE, also Cudi, Boogie, Rexx Life Raj, Saba of course, Juice WRLD, ASAP, these would all be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Irving went live on IG smoking a whole joint and said fuck the NFL 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leveled up leg day. Most challenging session to date. Made it through. Another one. #DailyDeposits #gonestreaking… https://t.co/7nfR5B7Vfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshvisser @sashakalra And @bryangreenberg just keeps getting better to look at too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When God said to rest on the Sabbath he definitely did not have sacristans at Newman Centers during Spring Break in mind 😂 @PhoenixDiocese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC But you voted NO on the birth bill .....  allowing a child to die on the birthing table and to receive no medi… https://t.co/Ir43VgSZI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFC needs more dynamic width. Chicago can’t use international spot on Raheem Edwards.   Yo, @torontofc. Send Chicag… https://t.co/ljaVjJOp9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandanicol3 Wow that shit is unbelievable. That’s why my circle is small. One thing I tell people who are younger… https://t.co/xKa0H2FSdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive Biden called Pence a nice guy. he git some flack from the extremists and he folded  like a cheap suit and… https://t.co/dkF77pJu5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamGotham on @TyltEnt—‘Gotham’ is the best superhero origin show https://t.co/6gqLQg7BgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why set an alarm when the anxiety of missing your alarm jolts you awake everyday at the ass crack of dawn!!!?????!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao this I never even met shordy and she kno everything about me 😂😂😂 wtf I’m trippin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhmxo @Chadoucito Este mamaguevo me bloqueo despues que le pase el articulo del NY times con el vergero de fotos d… https://t.co/oPZzWsRwxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We decided to spring ahead 24 hrs! It is Sunday. No need to check your calendars 📆 #SpringForward #AMNewsers #maine… https://t.co/Xtw0RVc9Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaHorwath What he'll ford doing only thing he needs worried bout is trudeau an how we get him out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSDFW @Ramon36069 $49 to Hawaii, so do they just strap you to the outside of the plane?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daringfireball Zuck should censor Facebook, I guess we should remove flat earth videos from YouTube, and conspirac… https://t.co/61nr0Uvbj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hels Why didn't you post this for the #SXSWEDU attendees last week, @hels?   😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews @ErielleReshef Trumpsters be like: grab her by the #craftyBeaver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a reminder to be grateful?  “ There are people praying for what you take for granted.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah dawg they sure do 😭😭😭 they don’t see none of the ain’t shit qualities until after the baby is born]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although the Olmsted Girls lost today, this team had a great year! No reason to hang your heads ladies, you left ev… https://t.co/YaWBhVC7qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the way the world ends  This is the way the world ends  This is the way the world ends  Not with a bang but… https://t.co/nWVbrCs3sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellmonEQ2 Never seen this one before..I guess hence the "hidden" part, lol. What is required for this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Patrick’s parade today in Toronto but not up for it this year. Windy and wet. https://t.co/234qYygSSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hits close to home for anyone that has worked behind the scenes on a radio show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Richard Nixon ordered the CIA to MURDER Chilean Elected Socialist President Allende and supported a c… https://t.co/9X3wbw4DOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @JaxonSkellz you already know i got no service so i have to tweet you out. Can you give me a rife home from tutorials at 4:00-4:15]]></document><document><![CDATA[You start by subscribing to @HBO , then turn your TV on , on April 14th , it’s not that hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say Romy rom in the da house you better watch yo Mouth ... #piscesseason #piscesgang #pisces♓ #0307 #whynot… https://t.co/YkYS8IO8Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the fbook ad algo was really so all-hearing and omniscient, then it would stop trying to get me to sign up for netflix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@get_delta Really like the new font size for the total portfolio value.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish It sounds like the judge is racist, or doesn’t understand the meaning behind women wearing a hijab....or both?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 58 of #blackclover on Toonami starts NOW!!! https://t.co/nRXuY4Zdgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be concerned that she's a plant from ISIS. wouldn't put it past them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the detail of the Carmel Table Lamp from designer Thomas O’Brien and Visual Comfort! We are showing it in… https://t.co/kvXAhturx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one is even better than @KachelriesDavid football snap @ESPNTop play! Beast Mode!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnalive But, when there is an IMPOSTER AT THE HELM, why wouldn’t his underlings b imposters as well. AN APOSTATE o… https://t.co/2wmtv36U85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FootballBeast91 @JordanSnow35 @charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/iMrIE6ULrU “They only care about who”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freireotranota No! Ese man me divierte, creo que le gusto y tiene alguna fijación con Joao y conmigo cuando andamos en bicicleta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weyland76 @suedehead_ Same. Used it for a while and no issues and all of the sudden one time it was like my face w… https://t.co/QKhEQvueBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjweber03 @zgo_e @SMathy21 @RealBradWeber Won't be any Cardinals on my team this year. None worth owning IMO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajc It should read “maintain her lane”, not “maintain her land” as written in this article @ajc .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serving our future STEM leaders through field explorations @ywprep @gsnetx @grandprairieisd https://t.co/L20TCTSbrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending a quick #ShoutOut to our good friends @portlandgear 👊  Over the past 3 years, we @SOLEFinancial have embrac… https://t.co/0JE7wTJlXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alphacracker1 @Alpha_Omega_Yah wow you are running on dogmatic practices and principles and not that of the word]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherorourke7 Good morning Heather &amp; Happy Friday :) Have a really great weekend  :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[First #Disturbed concert tonight. #frickingpsyched #evolutiontour @ Van Andel Arena https://t.co/Vy9PiXGwyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman , @BretBaier , @SandraSmithFox  - Maybe the Republicans should put King back on his committees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @RealCandaceO Republicans are part of the problem. It is CONSERVATIVES that have to stand up for what w… https://t.co/wby8KGTQm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say something is their “spirit animal”, I’m oddly annoyed but I think I get it now. Holy crap this is f… https://t.co/t4RSE6Yd2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Most I remove my furnace and replace with solar panels and windmills?  But what if I'm cold at night and it's a still night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ineedyouhere04 You need to stop! You know that you don't make people sad...good grief you are adored]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowday reading: Ex-CBS correspondent trashes media as 'propagandists' who are 'mostly liberal,' says she knows sh… https://t.co/3FCJO2CcF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve got LOTS of availability open ever since i opened up my book on the weekdays. DM TO BOOK. https://t.co/P4y7lWRkvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Via Original Video Copyright strangemusicinc ©) |"NEW MUSIC FROM @TechN9ne OUT NOW!!🔥 Listen to "EDI's" and "I Cau… https://t.co/OEF6HV6qxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY HAVE ALSO IDENTIFIED THE LEGAL CHRISTIAN RELIGION FORMULA ALSO. ALSO THEY HAVE CONFIRMED THAT LEGAL FORMULA. I… https://t.co/Ia2bFqPtyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetCambria8 @Kat_Obser @RepLouCorrea They are required to seek asylum in Mexico.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Terrific - Seaver Will Always Be the Essential Met https://t.co/p9CwO9Mj2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overall? Bad move to bring a flask into any place of business. But if it's a super expensive cigar bar? And u don't… https://t.co/qpfwRIOL3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richroll I've been vegetarian 6 years after being a evangelist for the paleo diet, and now I've been a #hospitablevegan for almost a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I have seen a couple of pieces of news on her before...I am not against it and understand that if she has not… https://t.co/5J4PRkZKD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thoughts, Scot. I believe some of the principles of @EHDiscipleship by @petescazzero provides some answers and… https://t.co/dcTLuHXXnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Macdreahh Thank you hip hop. You’re one of the few that hasn’t changed lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to a great coach for getting a great opportunity. I know he’ll do a great job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, it seems that with better medical coverage there would also be fewer abortions because people could actually a… https://t.co/ObSqxwSn1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devoptimus @kady @SeanRobichaud If so, then it seems a judge will answer this question for us long after it’s become politically moot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquesDoucet This is what happens when you have a history of having a bunch of loose lips in your administration and leadership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ilhan Omar is NOW the most important Member of the US Congress!”  -David Duke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jade_wayfarer82 @ZachWeiner Or if you say claimed 30% of the country would applaud children being burned to death. That’d be insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my life experience #robyn's popularity, heck anyone knowing who she is period, is the biggest proof of the… https://t.co/n4lvbezgyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsmith_co pizza Friday this week at the lab if you want to come by. Hosting home labbers from Reddit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basketballisso2 @SLAMonline Bruh no one said the Jazz didn't have 2 HOFers what you talkin' 😂😂😂?? Bruh quit making… https://t.co/bwVDzeN9g9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeroyComrie @patkiernan @NY1 I guess we're no longer holding union busting companies accountable anymore via the boycott of @NY1...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki_WVU_49ers @aspiringinvntor @Astro_journey @AtTaylorForGood @AussieDebBell @AwulKimberly @b00gie_mama… https://t.co/5qFT2QY3DH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I dream this conspiracy? @Vincemarotta @Burnsy987 @RodenburgZach NBA wants Sarver to sell over their concerns o… https://t.co/HHOj4dMAi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The street where the houses are bars!! #beststreetever #austin #saveyourfivers @ Rainey Street Historic District https://t.co/ljU6YucDsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradCabana @JustinTrudeau @RCMP Trudeau needs to be assessed. Perhaps he isn't a liar but is insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, the master deal maker. Ha.   Trump promised to shrink the trade deficit. Instead it exploded. https://t.co/RzpmF9Fe6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiecappalli teaching @karahogan12 how to make Brussels sprouts might be the highlight of my week https://t.co/Bi2y1KLqlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaceYourself22 Hold off for a bit lol I’m starting another reapers run]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @AppleMusic, if you like the band Anal Cunt you may also like Dying Fetus, Agoraphobic Nosebleed, Carc… https://t.co/i4UvmDZxEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emphasis on coolest in all senses of the word. Still love this video and everyone who worked outside on the coldest… https://t.co/itH90gaPlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day out on the @mototrax_snow 129 kit..snow so deep I spent a lot of the day digging out..thanks for the invi… https://t.co/XI3GK9bYND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chamblee54 @SimeonTheFool @wartwatch Ah. Then English was the problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrjonlamb @Gogo The new service @AmericanAir offers is far better but who knows at this point which plane will offer which service.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was able to cut down the net when my team made it to the state tournament my senior year of high school. Never woul… https://t.co/LIL8SxSTxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tiffanylang_ Those surprise naps have you waking up not knowing what year it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaPavlovic La instrucción 1 no me parece atinada más bien me parece tipo "espectacular" yo creo que se debe d… https://t.co/AmQ7wah2tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[making another jumpsuit. Sooo excited about this one!!! https://t.co/4QqDRdw2zF]]></document></documents></author>