<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There are more ladies who I love with my whole heart, not pictured, but still a source of love and light in my life… https://t.co/GruiHwjfDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not let these perverts skew the facts. We have had enough of that from the WH! #respect #fbr #resist #RESIST… https://t.co/POcF0XybDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Are you in your safe corner? Writing that crying fund raising letter. How old are you? Got to be in… https://t.co/M3VGiHJ4wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍 Good morning sweetheart!!!   #firstchair #firstcoffee #timberline #timberlinelodge #thankagroomer #somuchsnow @… https://t.co/1zXKyuSVza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a banana recipe you'll love.  Email me- biancaisfit@gmail.com #ketogenic #ketosis #ketodiet #ketofam… https://t.co/EPOSilVELP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidsearnmoney is a scam so please be very careful they will not pay you your money..... so report them......  https://t.co/dXkL580FsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddpoints @hrtablaze @Carina14186914 @SpeakerPelosi His Balls more like it 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vvaleriacayo Jajajajjajjajajjacualquier cosa estamos en posición tortuga jajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rich_Holmes22 I cant get enough of their victory videos! Just wish they were here to see it in person!!! #time2r1se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1 Hey domo! I’m a struggling grad student just trying to pay off tuition so I can get my masters degree… https://t.co/uKJUBoN1BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[YASSSSSSSS! Maliyah is ready! She has found her love....#CompetitiveCheerleader #CheerMomAndiLikeIt… https://t.co/ZAtInjGz57]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kourtnee!!! You continue to amaze us everyday with your intelligence, beauty, quick wit, and dedicat… https://t.co/BsSxTi7ZNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earellano3_LCES Awesome, way to go Sophie &amp; good luck at state 👏!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston Kamala knows what to do to not be infected. https://t.co/yM540U1O3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also thanks so much to @wpengine for hosting (and @TheZebraCo for being a wonderful co-sponsor)!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to do this cute snoopy tonight! I still have some time if you want to get in one this Valentine’s Day special… https://t.co/ZsIhiJ9yE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some mirth. I read this like Lil Jon would say it. #hilarity #laugh #smirk #humorous https://t.co/UpYXJrBOV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This project is perfectly in line with Siemens’ vision for future business in Ghana and other African countries. A… https://t.co/yy4jj8a6R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow I swear, she’s one of the most brilliant journalists—watching this made me feel like I just got filled with… https://t.co/fmDgOf09c0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/PvFVURvDm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF!! 🤘 Join me TONIGHT at beercreekbrewingco starting at 5:30pm for night full o’ tunes! 🎶♥️ #SantaFe @ Beer Cree… https://t.co/HQ7xGz3z5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly proud of our Regional speller! Mason did an awesome job! #ParmleyPROUD @Darajune https://t.co/dgatmufInl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh boy freezing rain now. We barely got a dusting of snow.  231/36 Put Co. INwx https://t.co/CUhpdmf41O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot that I was soaking my Roselle #hibiscus seeds. Was only supposed to be overnight they've been in there for f… https://t.co/ocbP8ik69F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_toriwhitley @ShoMarq 😅 thanks y’all! I’m so excited for spring to return. I love bright colors! Pinks! Yellow! Li… https://t.co/40hKrQLEMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my bum ass tooth taken out &amp; I'm waiting for this mfer to heal so I can slap fat dabs &amp; not get anxiety.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leha_H A lot of attention was paid to extracting the egg sack and guts. Also he mentioned the wound on his hand be… https://t.co/ca2KX6fadX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Out thoughts &amp; prayers are with you! Stay strong👍🏼🤗💞💪🏼💗💪🏼💗💪🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieBallou @tomwatson Pressuring Sanders, like Sanders only listens to Tad Devine and not anyone else. We have b… https://t.co/HSXS7fxMke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetTxBlessed @WildthingMyers1 @Aug1405 @jajones338 @clydecrusilla @RoundaboutSteve @CollinSummers12… https://t.co/aEVnq09lXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home, unpacked and ready to relax! I am apparently in desperate need for a pedicure! #LongTrip #PoolDay… https://t.co/ApdxGF55ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[The older I get, the more I hate going to shows at the House of Blues tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorisJuneHB @MSNBC @MaddowBlog Oh, yeah. It's a normal thing to do...in trump's little, selfish mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh so this guy has never seen Gabrielle Union...got it  #ShesTheHottestWomanAlive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing the happiest of birthdays to @sabsabal @sabinaninasabal ❤️❤️ thank you for all the hugs. Ily gorgeous 😘 🎉👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse It sure as fuck is!  You are the antithesis of what America is meant to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa! 5th graders are prepared and have come with 🔥 to advocate and respectfully debate! Incredible teaching (… https://t.co/99RmKrkctm]]></document><document><![CDATA[How am I supposed to lose weight when the best part about  life  is food ? https://t.co/0grzQapJDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to a wonderful teacher and agriculture advocate!  @AgClassroom @NCFarmBureau awarded Kristen McCoy… https://t.co/xug8KyjEAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah you’re beautiful but “something’s” in my way  “”= space and the fact that you probably don’t remember me https://t.co/0dxWLHrWkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports Outrageous! “Otherwise blameless life”  give me a break!!!!#JudgeTSEllis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot new paper on some hot microbes. Maybe I’ll make this my first paper of #MarchManuscriptMadness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg I have gone to all concerts in WA and have waited outside to get my first selfie with u and still h… https://t.co/evwgFTczZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5n0nBxqEzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last time I tried out this gorgeous, #kekewig from inhhair, I went for a dramatic, plum eye, paired with pinky… https://t.co/k66YzhUnS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you’re just two friends talking to each other. No one should feel inferior... except for him. He should feel inferior.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosebud702 @andrerucker51 @Msgargoyle13 @DudekLinda @hey_butter @evilgrrl @Itridpm @poppij @SarahGould_SA @delgeo1… https://t.co/7aXwYcpZOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umichmedicine ... 2.5 hours later, I'm still waiting and was told that a doctor hasn't even "picked" my case yet.… https://t.co/6gD4jGDMfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Historic Overland Park, Overland Park https://t.co/i7Ls9yYFyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bell_Support I have the MyBell app. Can you direct me how to do it? My dog ate my remote. https://t.co/KIs9CvYSCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UESPrincipal This is Amazing!  What a great way to share out information!💙🦁💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was writing a ton about the Anita Hill hearings during the Kavanaugh disaster, I concluded that I abhor all… https://t.co/W2P3t6VDis]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEXT TIME I SEE YOU, I’m giving you a high five ... cause hugs are overrated just FYI... https://t.co/xnNjTSUd69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got layed off Monday &amp; already starting a new job today. #Blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Chicago, is asking for it again....I sure hope they know what a great opportunity it is for 25,000 ppl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mywaterworks #H2o4LifeWC 💦 🔥 💜 https://t.co/CNSpb777QS https://t.co/1N7gdJrcin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zorro es feo , está muy mal amenazar . Estamos en Democracia, verdad? Las fotografías fueron puestas en las redes s… https://t.co/JYDjIx8A6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EkbMary @MerriweatherSun @sharon_elle @ElizabethPand11 @SonyaBaker2 @MustangRehab @eschaz12 @CyntWhite… https://t.co/hlY4doQuc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueerAnthro Hello! I was wondering how I could get more involved? I am currently an undergrad with a Major in Anth… https://t.co/ulmq7kCIcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SophNar0747 I'm bisexual and get similar replies. I'm a faker to them b/c I'm married w/ kids. Your last article spot on in my books]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fried Shrimp Po’Boy! So much shrimp, it was spilling out 🧡 From katiesinmidcity. Love that they use Gendusa bread,… https://t.co/0Hzqxb2YOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a sugar daddy/mama to walk into my life that don’t want sugar but only want to bless me with money 24/7 🤣💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom We need help in Guerneville!! My 13 year old list all her clothes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisHandsomeH @BachelorABC @colton Colton needs to choose Hannah G. for his wife. I’ve pulled for her since the f… https://t.co/pyyfIm3QyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a Sunday! Check my stories for all the deets from today 💐 This dress just dropped and is available to shop. Ta… https://t.co/TUyCwl4N00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boyd_2650 @Barracuda_Bella YES.. PLEASE.   BUILD THAT WALL! And..while your at it..don't forget to LOCK THEM UP!!… https://t.co/QVYKLZeYND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexiadlcruz Man the more I read these comments the more ridiculous yall seem to me. You niggas wackkk 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I don’t even watch the Kardashian’s  Also me rn: https://t.co/Ls5olhQg9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haley_Greive there’s a clearance/sale dillards store at the eastgate mall in cincinnati!! everything they sell is… https://t.co/BiPfuJPof5]]></document><document><![CDATA[for Enoch diligently sought Him! Hebrews 11:5-6 By faith Enoch was translated that he should not see death; and was… https://t.co/dEwm0iyeb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissNyetTrump @jsmith28998 #twitter is where i go for news: #WeThePeople don’t have #CaymanIslandOffshoreAccounts… https://t.co/T0qABeD7HN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RICH_MARGALEFF @MeCaigoDeRisa @YordiRosado Claro que sí duelo de titanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ivanka got caught in a lie..I guess the apple doesn’t fall far from the tree@IvankaTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadowCellMedia @adambarnhardt But... the double standard is that people are less upset when it’s all male? That’s… https://t.co/dIagf3aHWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidental train? 🤔 By definition that's gang rape so the only place I'm taking her is the hospital and her therapi… https://t.co/Fc4f7gREnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[when fiona apple explained that she didnt put out an album for 8yrs because she was cleaning her house i felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work with these teachers. They are not going to carry a gun. They have enough to carry as it is like school suppl… https://t.co/NUdImitPDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Hit by The Sugarcubes, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/ctRWk8BxJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Trip For Two to Miami This Winter! @h2oWireless and @1035KTU want to send YOU to warm up this winter in Miami… https://t.co/0RsDgZsP8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angrypanda0613 @Minecraft @Neakapuff @ryandoling Of cooouuurrrssseeeee!!! 💕💕💕 https://t.co/Ot7ManfzB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una dictadura disfrazada de dictablanda moral y con corrupción avalada por su Mesías...]]></document><document><![CDATA[KINDNESS MATTERS;💖Caring for my brothers dog Kappa, who is a sevice dog. We were out walking, struggling to breath,… https://t.co/BPGCC7d5hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[need an array of federal subsidies. Farm subsidies are costly to taxpayers, but they also harm the economy and the… https://t.co/79JptZoXec]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready for some warmer #weather and some #color in my #world.  It's been cold for too long! . . #txwx #texas… https://t.co/1l4SfWvqk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been the shittiest past two days of my life ngl and I honestly did think work would make me feel better but honestly it totally helped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Plunge is Right! Thank you Ridgewood Fam for all of your donations. We raised over $5500 for @SpecialOChi! The… https://t.co/ETIQHry8KA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mnwild practice underway as Bruce and co. Work to right the ship.   At first glance all players accounted for. Bra… https://t.co/uPIR0eNbCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoPleaseDrinks If you learn how to illegally stream things, you can in the US and Canada at the same time! 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@detlef_klann @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump So, when trump took millions from devos, and then made her education secret… https://t.co/4wgmWdrRM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noevalleybakery This @noevalleybakery is the best bakery in san francisco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letthemuslive @M_Aradag Por que siento que a Guaido lo van a calificar peor que a Capriles y a Lopez?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blondemaddyb00 did you ever feel this pain in the week you had nipple piercings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never seen anything quite like #AbductedInPlainSight What the hell!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanidaPeters @gbroh10 @POTUS We need to recall her. She is Trouble with a capital T]]></document><document><![CDATA[do u ever get so broke u start actually considering it when the pyramid scheme girls dm u???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosie_rosella @BetteMidler Bought 2 to assemble catios $200 each connected them side by side with clear passage be… https://t.co/FM4amj6k0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peregrin33 @LaurenHopkins96 Omg 😮 who is commentating?! I’m at work so not watching it, but I have it recording in… https://t.co/IYJVrninEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schoolover13 @JolieC @ScoobydaDog @Rayford512 @bigboutya1 @RealityDoc @aerich_a @GatorGrad929 @pattidan… https://t.co/gyZ6Vz0zXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lemonhearted Orlando is not only lucky for all these AMAZING women entrepreneurs but Orlando is so very lucky for… https://t.co/KguewvFZG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, first night in our new place and I think Clarence has found his new favorite spot. ❤️ @ Powderhorn Park, Minn… https://t.co/aVAYSXBTB5]]></document></documents></author>