<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MaralinaAntonia The line was too long and I woulda been late for work 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMCTalkingDead @RamboDonkeyKong Oh shit yea I do!Hey Ryan do you even realize the affect you have had on this fand… https://t.co/VcLRDUM3Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did truth, become a bias?  The truth is the truth based on facts. One fact is that it is not half the country t… https://t.co/dVKyws5F5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best arrangements of this song that I've heard: https://t.co/sjbp6g5Oho]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is an emotional heaviness to the day with Capricorn moon conjunct both Saturn and Pluto in Capricorn. We can’… https://t.co/AzVqbmgv95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @ragstorm When your aide or assistant forgot to remind u of what they tweeted on ur behalf. Someone is getting fired.. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, hello, I just heard about this insanely bonkers story - how is this not on the news everywhere?! https://t.co/NUwf1nAAlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopHaloClips @MostDopeFPS @LuxGOfficial I’m pretty sure @holysnipxr would’ve gotten the killtac but lose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northherofx He's also desperate for a good summit with North Korea. China still has alot of leverage over NK]]></document><document><![CDATA[One would think there would be enough women in their 40s running the show that it would be easy to stream 90210 tod… https://t.co/YGlIceGQt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids when the plane takes off vs. me when the plane takes off https://t.co/w4pTSZdB08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luigipalazzini @ProudResister I’ll bring the wine! https://t.co/glMkgo03DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrillKitten 1st off he needs to know it’s a cast iron skillet and B. That’s old fashion cornbread w/o the jiffy mix 😩 fuck he talm bout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @LindseyGrahamSC Her is from South Carolina... The other asshole McConnell is from Kentucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another item on the bucket list checked ✔️ Last night was certainly one for “the books”  😉 #raos #foodies #friends… https://t.co/83CIyimDVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lista! Marca o manda whatsapp 044 811 280 06 04 #FelizMiércoles #BuenMiercoles  #MasajesMonterrey https://t.co/jXzaSmBIb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely proud to be a part of this group and excited to continue shaping the future of a forward focused law firm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews GAME OVER: Chicago Police Reportedly Believe Jussie Smollett Paid Brothers To Beat Him Up https://t.co/bBVQncxZYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @IvankaTrump Any way, Ivanka, being paid is not “giving”.  It is “earning”.  Why, guarantee?  When d… https://t.co/eL0eFc3ovD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmarknewman Yeah and then you find out that your body processes opiate so quickly there’s no point in giving them to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Waterford at Valley Ranch Apartment Homes https://t.co/T2ZO0bke6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting for a hearing to begin like...😃💕💘 https://t.co/5NbkvY6nwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracydavidson @LBustamanteNBC @brittneyshipp @KatyZachry @NBCPhiladelphia Look at this impressive group of women. Roll models for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen My oldest brother loves liverwurst.  We're pretty sure he's not actually human.]]></document><document><![CDATA[your phone isn't listening to you! that's ridiculous! you're just paranoid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For I have sworn by myself, saith the LORD, that Bozrah shall become a desolation, a reproach, a waste, and a curse… https://t.co/VI7kUytXTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megan, I don’t understand you sometimes. You say ur against murder of babies, and the other hand u say well I don’t… https://t.co/XOSr61dTbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjesslonett Yes that is exactly how us middle-aged men feel about classic rock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rich triple layer #chocolatecake with fluffy #peanutbetterfrosting 🤤🥜🍫 #mmmmcake #peanutbutterandchocolate https://t.co/ojSVW8X995]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PageSix How low can a man and his mistress go for Valentine’s day...just pondering.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . .  And how art, and the meaning we impart to it, reconciles the two, a ceremony of ancestors that imparts a spi… https://t.co/yhEQEeSvDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that you say it, I think you're correct. He never has offered up a reason for needing names. And I've asked rep… https://t.co/UiBCuZ89jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a bad habit of buying #GirlScoutscookies even though I dont eat them, it’s like looking at the box is a comfort... #FormerGirlScout]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sounds like a good idea until you’re the one standing there fishing for hours - starving cuz you can’t catch a… https://t.co/tgbAHM00J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending #WorldWildlifeDay2019 day dreaming about this glorious land @byronbay #SaveOurOcean #Byronbay https://t.co/giHOSRzz8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #FakePresident #TrumpRussia #TrumpTaxReturns #Trump… https://t.co/Arhan3SlSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote Photos $20  Sonja Runar Photography Goodchilady@mindspring.com @ Bend, Oregon https://t.co/GqQIfAY7jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You glow girl! ✨ Illuminate your look with these silky pigment-packed drops. #makeuptutorial #makeup #makeupartist… https://t.co/vW0Gumyxhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally my man and I 👌🏽 we keep accidentally buying each other food. Then we just over eat all the stuff we buy f… https://t.co/FkYAeCczDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[not one shoutout to Don shirleys family or story in their best picture speech. Not to mention only 2 POC on stage a… https://t.co/ywRdc1Ct9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, caught up on the end of last night's Glendale City Council meeting and (drumroll): Council members propose… https://t.co/uDJKmphRXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EICarneAsada @whenmotion This is the best mod of the Die Hard arcade game ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeAnneYounkin @armando_yanez @myteamswearred_ @hqtrivia Gift drops, I got zilch 3 times in a row]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time some ones tells me I have “great vision” I’m like https://t.co/IaGgMsvVUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreabarber I loved the monkeys hey hey were the monkeys people say we fool  around but were to busy singing to p… https://t.co/6JL5Bk5CEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life doesn’t hit you until you’re three glasses of wine in next to CEO’s you’ve heard of your entire life at SXSW.… https://t.co/jG9iyocSOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwlivetour I really hope you will be in New England. My son is obsessed with @JurassicWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yo ElastaGirl is mad thicc!” @lisloval #squatgoals https://t.co/qma6A5co4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg if I have to see another tweet about comments being disabled on youtube videos with kids on them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump I agree. Yesterday we saw a wannabe tyrant. Someone better do some damn something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karli_bonne @AnonCassi @TWITMO_INMATE @AxlRoseyBird @Determined1776 @piprincess @OleMuzzy @GodHasThisNow… https://t.co/KqR2PbxQqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[10. Heights. Which I only learned of in the past few years, and only outside heights like high balconies, steep hik… https://t.co/3ckcjsCvpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmonroy Lo de los bancos no es mentira están cobrando $$$ para abrir cuentas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Husband says, “3 eggs???” Should I have had 4? 😂 #protein #eggs #paleo #lowcarb #glutenfree #nutrition #healthyfood… https://t.co/Awq3OINUjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[demi join the jonas brothers on their reunion tour and make it the longest concert ever challenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your morning includes breakfast pizza, you know it’s going to be a good day #TGIF 🍕🍕🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loveandhiphop Nope he is being cautious cause I truly think this is the real deal this time. Hoping they make it stick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MikeWiseguy !! 👋🏼 You’re from Napa, worked in Sac and now work at WUSA9. Google is awesome. Now let me tell yo… https://t.co/VXfEiN7t8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG 😮 ‼️ this stuff is like crack for your skin!! I canNOT go a day without it❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriandt31 @Trump454545 @POTUS You still hiring little girls you are going to get caught?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only get on Twitter to look at funny tweets and talk to myself... 🙇🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tao is to flow with life and live in the heart. 🖤📸: com3backkid #tao #taolosangeles #birthdaydinner #birthday… https://t.co/O5haWLI0fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooo I swear I can see the future sometimes. Rezz and Elohim collab I call it @OfficialRezz @elohimmusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love hearing my sister scream on the phone that @en_sscnapoli sold Hamsik this early in the morning 🤗 who else needs a wake up call?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On of my favorite women is Kathy O’Connell from @radiantability! WATCH our interview at https://t.co/g1nN91mBHL…… https://t.co/ElKXaR0fib]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/KZtewEzTql]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that it is #February and I am supposed to be sick of it by now...but I still LOVE the #snow ! It feels magic… https://t.co/fPSR8EAD2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haymarketbooks @Anon2World 43 now. I think I always have been, but clearly developed a growing understanding of is… https://t.co/KPq580APPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacramento county Division of Behavioral Health Services offers therapy from self help groups to hand in hand assis… https://t.co/PbMEoJFL4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denniskennedy:  “Lawyers miss great opportunities with in-house counsel because they assume that they know what in… https://t.co/CjAfNRGUCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[(#ad) Enter to #WIN $150 credit from @JoliMoliBrands in our latest review &amp; unboxing video here:… https://t.co/ELMOHlJro4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson You have the gall to speak of what is lawful??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be having me out here thinking u riding...if I can’t call on u stop banging my line]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't it amusing how dook students will inhabit tents in the mud all winter for a chance to worship at the feet of… https://t.co/CnxMtmKsuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[so, this is rare: GOP candidate lost a new york citywide election for a top position in a special race. but instead… https://t.co/dn1fBIuE5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet sleeping kitten @ Elmwood Park, New Jersey https://t.co/NmTlyOE4us]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that’s a wrap! Had a great time at #HIMSS19, learning so much, reconnecting with colleagues near and far, and m… https://t.co/733KH1BSyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live my life in a very “you’re only sick if you’re dying” attitude bc I can’t say no to this bread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How blessed we are to have an amazing art program at Rotolo Middle School ❤️!  Thank you Mrs. Meyer for sharing of… https://t.co/Q4T2GLgVXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edmaverickmus Viendo Que por fin tamos solos tú y yo ya https://t.co/KQGmVAQQ8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course when all my NIC friends are in Florida for a tournament I’m out playing in Alabama 🙄😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopping to smell the flowers! #soblessed #lifeisbeautiful #livelife #loveofmylife #lovelife @ Los Angeles, Califor… https://t.co/QeiWvwenRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Your Friend, where the hell do you people come from ??? Rocket Man murdered his own fami… https://t.co/16LqCL46Py]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wingstop you guys need to get control of Clifford center drive in FTW! Their customer service is horrible!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget the time the whole Pharmacy school got kicked off a fancy boat for being too intoxicated ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLPSTA @michaelschweitz @chunkled If you have a Mac, just hold down and save to photos, or any folder, from pop up menu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC_Breaking American doent care about his tax returns.  Id like to see the msnbc anchors post thete tax returns… https://t.co/NTRou9JWAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khickslms @HSESchools @Daniel1Teach Thank you @khickslms! We are humbled and excited!!!! 💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[*at golf tournament* Tina: “Damn, some of these girls look like rats..”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToughPigs Caroll there is nothing wrong with retirement.  We love you and want you to look after yourself. All the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delavegalaw @JoyceWhiteVance @NatashaBertrand Wine that he turned in to water!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone join hands and let's get solar on all our neighbors roofs. Leading with solar in California.… https://t.co/twu7YA2nkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get my life together before I start work on Friday and yeaaaap I suck lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best thing i’ve learned from my social work classes is to put my mental health first. it’s so applicable to not… https://t.co/UxszL923pO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawaii 🙄🙄🙄🙄 you’re almost the same temps as Rome, Italy 🇮🇹 https://t.co/8joOV0GyCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatdancer @MSFTEnable @Microsoft I can’t believe we signed the same sign!! Wait... yes I can! What an wonderf… https://t.co/panQpQyRx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[These girls earned their Spring Break today! #undefeated @ Willowbrook Sports Complex https://t.co/gEsMN6Ju2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't make an effort to actually spend time with someone, don't be surprised if they stop trying and disappear from your life 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceKern @Stop_Trump20 @EricaInCOMO @MBell88689408 @VelcroYuppie @samrosen26 @SeattleCycleBob @thedaywedecide… https://t.co/dvaL8w9htD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#floridarealtorrose #remaxtowncentre #remax #downtownorlando #lakeola #citybeautiful @ Lake Eola Park https://t.co/Z9g4XjrEXQ]]></document></documents></author>