<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Quote of the day, "If you had fun, you won." John Ivison, National Post. Too forgiving? "Suck it up, Buttercup," mo… https://t.co/D0bbGfOJHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Springfield, MA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/IuBTC4jGs3 #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson @SpeakerPelosi . A different experience in the use of her brain is more likely..... https://t.co/gKO5zK20m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSires @SenatorMenendez @RepDWStweets @RepShalala @carlosvecchio The Maduro Regime is capable of anything at thi… https://t.co/e7Kth682M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I see my old strength coach is back at it!! Lol he’s the reason I got so strong in college!! Take the weight ro… https://t.co/bHt0ihSOGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerpetrie43 @jordansnc Bucks clinch a playoff spot! #BucksInSix #FearTheDeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[$BTC.X any suggestions on upgrades? $ETH.X $LTC.X $XRP.X #AfterMarket #iG #Q @ Kissimmee, Florida https://t.co/Yl8TC9ZaRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[to their credit, snl has really improved their sound design for musical guests games the last two years or so. thin… https://t.co/2VfOF7cSvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMitchellXX I have a question. How to maintain an erect cock and play video games and look so blasé.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe as ove written bibi Netanyahu words thing for Israel just like chump and u.s. bibi is like antagonizing t… https://t.co/4kvJ7bZAP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AROE77 @obianuju Sad display of freedom of speech being erased - and yes totally agree with your tweet - go and ca… https://t.co/4FjmUGJBDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamaalBradley @yyates05 Hey Michael, where can I see more about this?! 👍🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @IvankaTrump Oh you mean he’s He’s destroying any chance of socialism ever taken root in this country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[all of this, but he was, well, you know.....Footnote: None of this is intended as an insult to TCM Host Josh Mankie… https://t.co/tajaFOPqX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn I asked for your help with my wife Seems like everybody in Texas is just blowing me off Iam a US citize… https://t.co/1Xt7yCC65s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marclamonthill Imagine any other business making millions off someone's talent.....and paying them relatively mini… https://t.co/jA7nheoVTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseOnGame When you say interesting that means something is up. And I have the Preds on the Puckline tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vrdmn @Beau__Cameron @EricOverfield @ChrisO_Brien Couldn’t you still package the ones with dependencies per template per function?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did your head hang, while your department covered up the murder of Laquan McDonald? What about that injustice?… https://t.co/YIKoSkaCxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGsovski No inherent contradiction. “True” Catholics support the murder of liberal priests and nuns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superklb @USArmy We are all proud! Congratulations for raising a beautiful and brave young woman!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkdikes832 @BallGame723 @fibonacci1123 @_mrfo20 @Raphy_Taffy Damn just seen the highlights. I missed a good ass ga… https://t.co/g8H2xuTdBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dirt is necessary for growth! So when things get tough or your break through hasn't happened. Remember you are… https://t.co/30pyx6tkt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting Insights at the #InvestorForumCA  #RealEstate #Investing #Mortgage #Housing #Realtor #Property #REINON… https://t.co/IaQycTCzp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job tonight Ms Merck and the @schsredskins band in your Pre-LGPE concert. https://t.co/i27jgCL18i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JagexHelpStevie I got a new phone and now I can’t log in because of my Authenticator. And I no longer use the emai… https://t.co/CUx8kzSHC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajmanx ‘When you get up in the morning, how do you decide what shade of black to wear?’ 🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama want to be the next Secretary General of UN, to push an agenda of the new world order and globalization. It i… https://t.co/FTSRAbeaEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelCoachDavis @RebVoice @thduker I don’t know, Coach.  Can’t just wearing them for every game be enough?  Those… https://t.co/CQkrsMdNJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The twin-engine @UPS @BoeingAirplanes 757-F can carry up to 88,000 lbs of payload and has a cruising speed of 535 m… https://t.co/nHsMJKxxF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN HBO will make more than enough money to settle the lawsuit. Its all about the Benjamin’s baby!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big shout out and Congratulations to Dedrian Parmer, Geno Artison, Cameron Hines and the rest of the Drovers for al… https://t.co/aimrbSnwGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flat White for the road (@ Dolce Kimera in Dundas, Ontario) https://t.co/XxaVVwHuzf https://t.co/jIssl7gyro]]></document><document><![CDATA[If simple creatures do a tour and I dont get to see them I'm gonna cry for weeks I love them so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Statistics, like any other fact based analysis, are krytonite to these kind of people.  They send their ki… https://t.co/LbtHInWMbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porter-Gaud has a JYD on the loose in a cillege basketball tournament championship.  2pm Central time today!  Let's… https://t.co/Y4TPL9wE7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_hassing @jennarafe @nicholasrafe @VinceMcMahon @WWE @FightOwensFight @TrueKofi @WWEDanielBryan @Sprite… https://t.co/vTIl1cifaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrMike_62 @PudLightLime @Djaevlenselv @DanielTrescott @donttrythis INTERESTING!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨TONIGHT AT 7:30PM🚨  We are proud to partner with @MileSqChurch   It will be a great discussion at our office:  120… https://t.co/l0PcDItnkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[2006, Fenway. I was hanging out around the @NESN booth and saw @nickcafardo ... I asked him a random question about… https://t.co/2GzDZhTyF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The legislative committee which is charged with reviewing Arizona’s $485 million+ in tax credits hasn’t met in 3 ye… https://t.co/tqRXYRizsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing home, almost new, coming soon for less than $200k. Stay tuned for details 💜 Until then see a “hot list” of… https://t.co/FHwnMhED2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a minute, but we've got the salacious gogo_luca back on the #gogoboy box this Monday at @thecocknyc!   Wa… https://t.co/zi937QA5db]]></document><document><![CDATA[I JUST LOVE MY FRIENDS. I JUST LOVE EVERYONE. Y’all are killing it out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDawsonWright Bad photoshop and probably (hopefully) not the official cover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSU_Foundation @MSU_SApres @MSStateStudents @SBCoffeehouse @maroonband @MSU_Delegates @MSUPanhellenic @HailState @NewMaroonCamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the overwhelming support I’ve received over the past couple of days. You never think that you’ll ever… https://t.co/BnF5R7i2CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The RS Politics 2020 Democratic Primary Leaderboard https://t.co/evNdnonNdm via @RollingStone @PeteButtigieg https://t.co/VBYenJmPLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searching for properties the whole day. Finally got it.  Coming soon.  Call Andy for investment properties in South… https://t.co/Uqr8yEBQuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump You do a fine job of making yourself look bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After appearing during Cohen's testimony yesterday, Lynne Patton was told her services would no longer be needed an… https://t.co/kXsGCVOqe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We support our police; we support Ron Taverner, the premier tells the legislature. He is unrepentant about the Fo… https://t.co/2y1il2w8V5]]></document><document><![CDATA[║░█░█░║░█░█░█░║░█░█░║ ║░█░█░║░█░█░█░║░█░█░║ ║░║░║░║░║░║░║░║░║░║░║ ╚═╩═╩═╩═╩═╩═╩═╩═╩═╩═╝ ~fireflies~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @kate_manne Your last sentence articulated what I have spent pages trying to say and not as well as you said it in a few words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, say it ain’t so, Tom Terrific. This is sad news but I hope he can still live a full life. Dementia is not good.… https://t.co/eNp2fLCwKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aarhead_ @rhj_24324 I’m sorry what? I just told you K is up all time against Carolina (even tho it’s close) and Du… https://t.co/OwdKpkmfxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I imagine that hell is just a large Justice store on the day after Thanksgiving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julio Iglesias - Amor Amor Amor (Remastered English version). https://t.co/yCGXR2iE3w via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bucktailes @BucktailLures @1MonsterMission @Lizardkingfish @LowellMiller17 @panekbill @XStreamFisher @burnside4141… https://t.co/ZQ1T01OLYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Victims of Flint caused by #Democratic run government, victims of California wildfires caused by #Democratic r… https://t.co/D8bOzR1dGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedHott93 @KevinEnglishSD My bad for backing up this #FreezingColdTake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. @ThomTillis and @DavidRouzer listen to the people, not Big Oil https://t.co/b04NolMebm #NCPOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poniewozik Haven’t seen the female version, but Ghostbusters 2 was atrocious]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/JBFTeod62F]]></document><document><![CDATA[but niggas cheat on y’all and y’all take them back 😂 so who really weaker in this bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FollowGod_Only @brentepling @KyleJamesHoward And we should, but know that in politics, many profess Christ for pol… https://t.co/nGAvSwcWtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Communists and socialists in the media and congress?  McCarthy was right. It’s proven daily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @SuperkickSoccer CFL Session II HS Boys Champions! 🎉🥇 #PlayCFL https://t.co/8SvI3WbGV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbrunorunner I’m with you Kevin. Constitutional Conservatism, with free open Market Competitiveness, free from Government intrusion!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLKWD The Commander I spoke with had a firefighter position in the reserves waiting for him. His inpatient ass… https://t.co/cIp4JcNHZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sangrita Gose by Bingo Beer Co. @ Bingo Beer Co. — https://t.co/EyGdLl9nzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Puzio @ScottMathusek @JackCurryYES With so many teams tanking and so many other teams afraid to spend over th… https://t.co/2kAvC5S5HB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went from a cheap hiking trip to a  $70 trip 🙃 and I’m over here “trying to save money”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bilan de l'opération impact-motoneige de la SQ https://t.co/xFZkRZGkUQ https://t.co/gRnZQStcSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try to do my due diligence every day, but especially on a large sleep, so I’m thinking slip through the cracks. A… https://t.co/J44T2flCl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[when we introduced ourselves in class one person said their hobby was modeling and another person said their hobby was conciousness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helpful Western Trauma Association 2019 Annual Meeting tip: if you send your beer back 3 times because it tastes “f… https://t.co/L0XPen47Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepArmstrongND is ignoring the Traitor in the Oval Office 💯‼️ https://t.co/CrxEphjzVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the air in moments on @560WQAM  with @560Friedo and @AlexMSolana. At 11:00 @jeremypiven will join us in studio! https://t.co/xOCbNBMfoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This glam-tiger was seen stalking the RV show and eating cinnamon almonds. @ Timonium Fairgrounds https://t.co/zdJ3Te8C7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurchyMard @TonyPaul45 @OneVoiceUS U didn't hear on the news how USA STARTED 3/5  I got fake news. Most valuable t… https://t.co/sZv4TO8Yc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at map by the University of #Chicago.   In 47 years, the wealth of this great city split in 2 completely diffe… https://t.co/IdtMj63OgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I asked the toughest, strongest, smartest, most beautiful woman to take a chance on a guy. She took a chance… https://t.co/nxvXNoyBlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I’ll be watching #WWEFastlane tonight.... 🙂  ** Besides when I’m marking out over every single spot of… https://t.co/PLX4aUsYsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StansburyShow you know the first week of March madness is the busiest week for vasectomies right....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strouse_kristy Yes with the nostalgia, I understand, but I’m worried that I missed my window!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When receiving negative feedback/comments: 1) anticipate bad news 2) ALWAYS thank them for feedback. 3) follow-up a… https://t.co/WpegOZZWfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being able to express yourself to a person you care deeply for the best feeling no 🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImDerBatman @Just_JD38 Agreed. I just like the NFL OT better but you’re right the college version can be fun too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookRiot I have been using them for a year now and absolutely love them. I need an infinite supply, as I leave them in place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, you won't have much to look forward to in prison so i guess you gotta spend your time waiting for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DepreeUSMC He was declining a bit physically it was obvious. However we will miss his leadership 100%. Him and Fla… https://t.co/kAPUYYMF8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winfrey_steve @Bounty Gotta tag that.  @GoldBondInc That’s how deals get made.  #protip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice picture here by Diana Halligan from the show at the 20th Century Theatre last night. Thanks to everybody who c… https://t.co/QfvymW1NZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pangaea1 That’s so great!  I recommend they stay downtown if possible.  Market square and gay street gives a good… https://t.co/FjFW7i8Qz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite this tweet if you think @Matt54Johnson should delete his Twitter account]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Secrets re: sources of info that proved M’fort was lying, most likely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarnelPlanning @NrinderWard3 Darnel, clearly autocorrect jumped in and apologize if you were offended. I’m not goi… https://t.co/w5Wbh2kswV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @DjLots3 @AOC It's her vision, we'll see which later. @petetalking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbk_95 @FisheriesPod @MJWeberLab If you had come to any of the AFS meetings, you would have known he was coming up already!]]></document></documents></author>