<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@wisewinston @jennycohn1 She knows her shit. Take this seriously and as the emergency that it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSKChavez_ @thatsorielle @Hapalani_ @nicksolokid @Kevin90648 https://t.co/nXfsJK1BP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechJahnke Only if I land the work! 😉 Business Owner life #entrepreneur]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously feel like a kid on Christmas Eve.... Excited for what tommorow has to bring!! 💖😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackfriarsGdns Did you follow my flower fail trying to grow sweet peas last summer? I think the southern heat just roasted them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett just got Donald Trump reelected and the whole situation is just SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of times I’ve been offered cocaine in nor cal at the age of like 14/15 😂😭 wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo @margaretbavis! You nailed the mismatch between how nurses are perceived and the reality of our roles. The be… https://t.co/hxKjd4J7p6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody in this family is honest. They’ve all gotten away with breaking the law for so many years, they think they’r… https://t.co/U1ll7UPahA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LaurieBaedke for having me on your podcast!  Such a blast as always chatting with you :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many have lost their way with God because of the good excuses for not praying, not going to church, not forgivi… https://t.co/sRCnSs4OFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djmont @rauchway As they say: Zhistory is written by the winners! Depending of the political and social views of t… https://t.co/L0ubgFbvB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie is an old hippie who was to lazy to make it at the commune. So he left start making money own 3homes, millio… https://t.co/dXI4jhycvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So inspired from the summit this weekend . Thank you to everyone who organized this amazing event . Thank you… https://t.co/sWpgaa00m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who hope in the LORD will renew their strength. They will soar on wings like eagles. -Isa 40:31🙏🏽💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carloshs61 @Claudiashein @olecarrazco @DiputadosMorena @Mx_Diputados @sinaloagpmorena Fueron de todos los partidos, diputadas y senadoras.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidvisentin1 1. That guy reminds me of Martin Short 2. Martha Raye, Peter Lawford and Judy Garland (had to look… https://t.co/fRqoaIHddL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday, March 9, 2019: Day #6 Challenge Completed during my P90X Live class this morning. I just had to get a lit… https://t.co/dO7ynZkUIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow is still falling so Sauk City is still digging out. These friendly neighbors are taking care of a friend’s… https://t.co/qal9PzU2cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends/family don’t always want to hear about your condition, and that’s ok because that’s why therapist exist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 I miss my girl terribly. We put her down two weeks ago due to cancer. Not a day goes by I don’t thin… https://t.co/O42lvYNKf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué sabes de frío sí nunca tuviste frío, te pusiste una chamarra y la chamarra estaba más fría?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsgayh Thanks girl! Made my day I got a birthday lunch with some friends and it cheered me right up]]></document><document><![CDATA[my skin is currently as bad as it was when i was in 8th grade and i am NOT here for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol if poor countries  want freedom and democracy.  Let the people  in there county  stand up and FIGHT  FOR THE RIGHT TO BE FREE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Now without faith it is impossible to please God, for the one who draws near to Him must believe that He exists an… https://t.co/WrO4yuSSpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandy_mclaren *2019 🙂   @mandy_mclaren Excellent job.   I wish Twitter would allow us to edit like every other app… https://t.co/BXKHKituYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the back of the classroom and listening my #finance students talking to each other and themselves about… https://t.co/bdLq3sg6eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.7.19 cαlí • drєαmєr 🌴  - 🅨🅞🅤 🅐🅡🅔 🅔🅝🅞🅤🅖🅗 📸 hannahcelestevisualz @ Cha Cha Matcha https://t.co/2hTk4U2813]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again, in an ironic twist, Conservative Christians are the Anti-Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Space Oddity by @JWakefieldBeer/@eqbrewery @ Hawthorne Bottle Shoppe — https://t.co/A8USwNba1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re almost home but this guy keeps backing up and going forward for 10 years 😂 #imhomenow #trains… https://t.co/v5x2wQ0NJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lupesmithlewis Yes... you must watch now. I own it you can borrow. It is super cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshundaSanders @JPHoward_poet Indeed. Well deserved! Congratulations @JPHoward_poet and @WomenWriteBloom]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @TheIowaClinic losing the same records over &amp; over makes me afraid to go to any doctor there 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittlovesx3 I’m just gonna say I told you so when you’re on your death bed bc of a cat girl😂😂😂💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@62WalterP @mommamia1217 Put him in the furthest corner where there is no traffic in an unmarked grave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillandTed3 In the theater when it came out. I was three but remember seeing that and the Little  Mermaid.  Both b… https://t.co/ka0hv9i0xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EnoughIsEnough #Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping… https://t.co/AKg4EsPyPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[being friends with an Italian-American is incredibly difficult when you’re tipsy bc they’ll be like “remember my au… https://t.co/ia1FWcOIcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StephonClark THREAD 7 @SacCountyDA: Clark then jumped another fence into yard Officers turned corner of home, open… https://t.co/iW7ANSSd9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For I have given you an example, that you also should do just as I have done to you.” Feet washing Servant Jesus in John 13:15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahahahahhaha you will never know!!! I’m taking what happened to my grave 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[6F at 3:30 a.m. here in Troy. Big wind has finally died down. Feels safe to stoke the fire again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red, violets are blue, I’m happy I’m single and you should be too 😉🍭💋🌹 #TinderPartner #SingleNotSorry… https://t.co/s9EwEBHpdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNDOUBTEDLY I got NOTHING to promote only that I had to help my metabolism out a bit by eating 6 times a day (small… https://t.co/Ry4brcs89n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@james1joseph1 @_MarshmelloPat @UncleJoe5465 @PoliticalMixol1 @moralsofmayo @Tigertomjr @Mharris888H @GhostOfTick… https://t.co/1nkQ63bRND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sole_less @_TJuice @chazz_72 @Finessekid_7 💀💀💀💀 https://t.co/oqWgJUhX5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a double ear infection &amp; I’m about to listen to tractors. Happy Valentine’s Day luke 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow thank you 😊 I have a family friends and a life back with my life now please thank you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Stone understood this better than anyone.  He use to say ‘Dianna would go through a break wall if I ask her t… https://t.co/clUcrvo0vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep right now and am watching @weartv’s 3ITM. @wxkaitlin, @WEARLauraHussey  @JaredWillets - you all are g… https://t.co/jzkAZNbJOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Shouldn't Ivanka's advisors try to prevent her from making ironic, stupid comments? She is certainly n… https://t.co/9YlJV0r80h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras mi padre observa emocionado la materialización de un sueño, otros de despedían del antiguo formato del per… https://t.co/kJuNksr7TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“so you’re gonna launch a presidential campaign? you’re running for president?” “that is correct.” “what’s differen… https://t.co/JqHozd6f7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi esposo and I are on island time 🦜🦜🦜 beers at noon, then drive to GR to see @GIBBZmusic 😻 Do you think… https://t.co/E7XgXZQdJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for walking me to work on your day off🙃❤️ @afinney8 https://t.co/CwkJ6OwTSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convinced I could’ve gotten 12 hours of sleep last night and it still wouldn’t have been enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo - girrrllllllll come through! ⚡️⚡️⚡️  Almost makes me forgive you for that #Motown tribute 😏  This is going on… https://t.co/NKfbirCVsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Always Remember Your First  . . . Congrats Nolan Crisp on pitching in, and closing out, your first college base… https://t.co/HrCe0Gxp85]]></document><document><![CDATA[in the mood to delete everything, go missing for a month, get my life tg and come back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sisu1953 @tetxnu84967 @MAGAforc @tee10202 @JeremyRobards7 @PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99… https://t.co/vySoOXH7Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AshWednesday is the start of a soulful season, taking time to consider the timeless AND ephemeral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skijoey @eastcoastgal100 I have been trying FOREVER to put words to how I feel about her and thank you for doing i… https://t.co/Yz5sBX3F7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[u florida drivers are so damn impatient beepin ya horns every two seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 2nd &amp; Charles - @2nd_and_charles in Hoover, AL https://t.co/YrHXsU8g3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotriousBob Haha when I do get an intern, it’ll be coffee and lime runs lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewCarney Thank you for reporting the whale story correctly instead of all the negative hype we heard this weeken… https://t.co/ZrCiIwgSF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Livestock grazing on #covercrops is like 1 + 1 = 3 says @BrekerJoe The benefits are incredible! @IFAO123 #IFAO2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget when I got my first job and my boss called me to tell me that I didn’t get the job, but thanks fo… https://t.co/Fjy1HJDuZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every morning now when I wake up I already have @mtrench #MTphantoms playing in my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am always proud to be a @KleinForest graduate, today I am a little extra excited for my alma mater @KleinISD !… https://t.co/fasHWLZykn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m kind of salty you can’t put gifs on Instagram. I’m gonna have to re-export as an .mp4 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage of my new photo session the hair made by @angiedoll1989 James R Smith the best New Your City photographer https://t.co/D1L9ziGNee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincipalRLA Thanks friend! I try to shake it up every now and then! #champforkids #122edchat https://t.co/2lAYsDeuJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyx_idyllic @NYCSanitation @gensler_design @ECOveRy @CenterForArch What a great panel of #GreenBuilding friends sh… https://t.co/NsBea3pQoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one friend that always complains how you don’t see them but when they text you and you reply instantly they ha… https://t.co/Ap5Cx59Xgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gobierno de España: BAN  on Hunting with Galgos!!! Stop Spanish Greyhound deaths: - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/GloAOK791D via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneknottsports What you gonna crunch? #NationalCerealDay https://t.co/bbfjWuGxQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSaysWrite We were having crazy wind last night here in VA! Hoping that’s the winds of creativity and hopefully spring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf Wouldn't it be great if we came together on values? We'd have to start by recognizing the value of newc… https://t.co/dVJ6qhsQA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working from home but having to call into a one hour Meeting is mind-blowing.  😅😅 https://t.co/Tzwn1mTwOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinKarr89 @DarthBlount47 @realDonaldTrump @nytimes https://t.co/5g1mEpPW51 https://t.co/GkzzR5ZJq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[this man left his jacket at my house after he tried fwm and got the audacity to dm this today, boy if ur fuckin goo… https://t.co/ANlpUzgmGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWuuu @_alexrass said you might come to NJ! I’ll make you zucchini bread if you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The new water heater was installed and residents now have hot water again.   I talked to several residents… https://t.co/B5LqeIgmyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacramento County! CSEC 101 Basic Awareness Training @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/x9kfQA4qMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some members of our afternoon bus duty crew enjoyed giving our #SuperStar drivers some awesome treats today!… https://t.co/X2uYW3vjoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely disgusting!! Worst part is everyone watching and doing nothing and especially the adults !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZNichols15 Imma need you to get your head together right now. #TheChallenge33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to watch Schitt’s Creek ASAP. I’m forever thankful it’s given me all these GIFs for whatever gross a… https://t.co/6sGGtXq1SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to the love’s of my life❤️ You all mean the world to me😘 @kaybeireis @GageBeireis… https://t.co/AdgsSNUhEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUN FACT: One lap around the U.S./Mexico border is 3,500 steps  Maybe if u know where u going it's only 3,000]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instructor Trainees and our Instructor in the house.........representing Evergreen Beauty College at the WAC Worksh… https://t.co/l6BxlU6U3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mention I’ve been bingeing Friends literally all. day. https://t.co/vZkoSwpP0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[wishing the happiest birthday to one of the best people in my life 🎉 love you Jo, thanks for putting up with me (an… https://t.co/rSdPjACgGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mimibeck617 @RHOGossip @collinsp1960 @MandyBa48181836 @hwivesfanatic @AllCelebPolls @RealHousewivezz im moving to… https://t.co/5Ywzb49bsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisYow14 @walkermcguire @lukecombs @jamesonrodgers When you find out about this and realize you won’t be there..… https://t.co/EmF4YOwLMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Good, probably a trumpster who thinks they can bully their customers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montrealsimon When he's on a 'Trudeau Tear', he usually runs out of steam by now. But he's still flying high this… https://t.co/oWYSzQAZ02]]></document></documents></author>