<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SaphiaTWN @weathernetwork Local warming followed by local cooling.  The climate is changing every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dillon, best new cookie now at Great Harvest Bakery! #HspM383 https://t.co/8Uii5ydTny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Duncker333 @Christian_Racin @DisneyPixar @NASCARonNBC @SherylCrow This was never used as an intro for NASCAR. He’s saying as a what if?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisasEyeRoll @MIHomeYGK Totally. We’re the best at communicating on Twitter! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chayitomoguel1 DELICADITA LA MADAM. ASUMA SU RESPONSABILIDAD,ES SERVIDOR PUBLICO, PERSONAJE PUBLICO Y ESTA EXPUEST… https://t.co/0IqlYj6VBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Food Service Worker - Auburn University Dining - SaladWorks" at Aramark? Applicant trackin… https://t.co/MWfWjSeBsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killer_keller64 @AvantiLockhart @Coach_Medrano Good work bro keep grinding🏈💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanblanco76 Great article. I'm going to put some of these strategies to work. Thanks for sharing. https://t.co/PIS8VTNnYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu I love it when you post Teddy. You are hilariously stupid. Keep them coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realJohn_Stiles @MarshaBlackburn Yes people like you will start a war because you cannot get your way via the demo… https://t.co/LePUuXhKKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Higher Level Sports Boys Basketball Tryouts  Sun 2/24 and Sun 3/3  Elementary (Grades 3rd-5th) @ Saunders Middle Sc… https://t.co/t9jwbx2Os6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a world where everyone’s always burning bridges I’m trying like damn to repair mine. I’ll be goddamned if I’m le… https://t.co/VtKl0BSU0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwilliams_49 @CoachBigHU @HardingU Happy for you bro bro!! Patience is always key and it’s your time foolie👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulswaj @PiratePoots @robertliefeld @ComiCarvaJoe9 I unabashedly love Age of Ultron. For all the hate it gets it… https://t.co/NL1TuE1mzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best news of the night. #RomanReigns is in remission. Welcome back Big Dog!! #Raw @WWERomanReigns @WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Inti_Smash Nah the last one on the 3ds wasn't even good. I just want gen 8, gen 7 OU is the worst meta game to ever exist]]></document><document><![CDATA[No cap. People take that free knowledge for granted. Books are tools that can be used to change your life in many d… https://t.co/WXYbuNz3RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[FFF #FF #InternationalWomensDay⁠ ⁠  @kalieshorr @Lauren_Alaina @runawayjune @IAmMaggieRose  @AshleyMcBryde… https://t.co/H9MkiUJJTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobJMP2 @MrsRonnieM @CynthiaRunnels1 @delta1160 @arkiegal411 @PATRIOTCITIZEN6 @goldendoekd @EmzdadRunToWork… https://t.co/33JOSfh33v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacedOutRadio @DeepTalkRadio @WQEE99ROCK @kzfxradio @kdunradio @ParanoiaMag hoax lols maybe BUT them fuckers ARE… https://t.co/hv5B6e9klU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zehb_BR @TofuRE2 @UiroMochiRE2 @ImKatastrophe Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool rus… https://t.co/D3CQmeml9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @realDonaldTrump Otto W statement he made was a blunder imo and it was such a easy question to anwser he can’t make those mistakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the Auto Show for the 1st time with my lil guy this weekend. It was over after he saw #Bumblebee  . .… https://t.co/qFtaT8wEKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[As #Blackhawks blueliner Erik Gustafsson continues to put up points, he’s showing he’s one of the more offensively… https://t.co/fFxtiNws1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wendy's fries and you can swap out the curly fries for potato pancakes while you're at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auweia1 @renebfolena @jonbuchwald @justinzollars @sfzombienation @LondonBreed @sfbos @SFDAOffice @TheCoalitionSF… https://t.co/bKc3rhBkd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great season Lady Cycreek Cougars basketball @Morgankenise2 #ourtimecoming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Matchday everyone! Let’s get those 3 points from that Suburban Illinois club! #CHIvORL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasSowell @Imaginer77 There is absolutely nothing wrong with blacks being conservative. @SenatorTimScott is a f… https://t.co/nPz8WC4WBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho you talked about people who have never watched independent wrestling companies That's me never watched… https://t.co/an2QwnqPly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemichs 😂😂😂 one time I did that for me and co worker... turned into $22 for 2 starbucks. 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overnight @JetBlue flight 150 from PSP to JFK. Pilot said were waiting for 15 mins (closer to 30 actually) for a pl… https://t.co/u0sQ1rOF9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Had to check first if this was the joke don trump! You trully are a moron dude! Cant wait to see y… https://t.co/6medRLzKKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firelands' Payton Burgdorf scores a quick pin over Williamsport Westfall's Chanston Moll in their D-II 120 consolat… https://t.co/7Uu2HkqjrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lngway2neverlnd And the Adult conversation is over back to normal. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMirror If it ain't broke, don't fix it, my Nana told me that 50 years ago, still true today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachneebt @Robert_E_Lehman @StanKachowski @ThePoniExpress @steelers @ArtRooneyII There is not one team that would do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJ Khaled and Bieber about to drop another heater to own their third summer in a row. Let’s go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cherryblosom013 @retrozitro64 @Jackj9122 @Anthemuniverse If you think calling you delusional is an insult you are… https://t.co/ocVr7pSlz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaijinGoombah @meowth900 Caught in a landslide No escape from reality Open your eyes Look up to the skies and see… https://t.co/nkefc7t3rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChurchillXCTrac @ilovemychargers Great job ! Very proud of the team and coaches!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God blesses those who patiently endure testing and temptation. Afterward they will receive the crown of life that… https://t.co/Bit7ADAz3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor and I watch Food Network or HGTV  a majority of the time when we watch TV. Are we in our 20s or 50s? Find ou… https://t.co/RYyzwLdrbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth waking up for... #Florida 🚴 have a great day y'all! https://t.co/6R2wBVjIZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers need to atttact another star on a Max next year cause bruh , Kuzma Ingram and LonZo hate Bron lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol So dude. Sir. What do we do? From an ownership standpoint we have to do something. Lead us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[444 S Cloverdale Ave 444 S Cloverdale Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/8XGq2cRlb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@17_katrina @ParisHilton You are not even close to he a princess like her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nophilter13 I do feel like Jarmo has built up enough good grace to make it through if they get bounced in the firs… https://t.co/YqyhADfMlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theheolikein @b1gnate_11 I have Jimmie as #1 and Gordon at #3 but both still above Petty. Not a knock on Petty by no means though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is ever in the bank. Can’t take anything for granted. Gotta have the warrior mentality and out-tough them o… https://t.co/E4ECfIQJyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunriseTrader I like yo buy 1-2 month calls on setups ready to breakout. I do not really keep them to the end but… https://t.co/3Yhzh8YOUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGirlVenice10 ..... the fuck does any of that have to do with her being black]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzMeCosmology Thanks for the RT You could say this butterfly held its own "in the ring". Bad wrestling pun? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me ... pass up the opportunity to go to CPAC!  Are you insane?  It’s probably bigger and  better th… https://t.co/eTdBpOvdpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShattuckKen @CardinalJWTobin Ken, Google Pew Research - "how did the Faithful vote"? Answer Evangelical Christians… https://t.co/B9UXdZ3UQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE it when players grab shots out of the air after the fact. Don’t let opponent see their shot go in, even if it doesn’t count]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LaurieScottPC clearly @fordnation told all his minions to push this out today after the beat down @MacLeodLisa to… https://t.co/1z438BPH5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear #Lexus #yesplease #sexyvert #winner #onlyasiancariwouldconsider 😎 #V8 @ Southern Command https://t.co/01shvXnXeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big, bold, and beautiful Oreo Whiteout! 💥🤩😍❤️🦎 Such a cool morph! Geckos Etc. Herpetoculture… https://t.co/jGbpI3p4jV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamByron You were great Sunday! I see a tremendous amount of growth from last year.  Keep up the hard work.  Y… https://t.co/t7GjVsij2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy great meal to celebrate a late Valentine’s with @__feverqueen (our 3rd?!?!?!?!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has shown her contempt for the constitution she took an oath to defend !! Her time in Congress should be termin… https://t.co/WlpkVhBN8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @hmcghee Stop fear mongering ! The sky is falling the sky is falling. Global redistribution of US money is you… https://t.co/cnmOrrTTR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do hope the #UND men’s hockey team can deliver big win over #UNO as it is final home game @ Ralph Engelstad Arena for the five seniors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelEMann Capt. Ed does not seem to have the Valentines day spirit in him anymore. So Happy Valentines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to @jimkchin @AlexHonnold and everyone who worked on #FreeSolo https://t.co/8s6ch9H83f]]></document><document><![CDATA[#amigos #comidita #14febrero en Zacatecas, Mexico https://t.co/udqUEBSPhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlainaAppaloosa hahaha i don’t hate her. she’s just veryyy vanilla, i hope to see more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Documentary Review: "Rocking the Couch" (2019)  https://t.co/cjwvVtgQ0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilladyGA I miss my Panthers. Right now I'm watching the AAF,  that new Football league]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Not IoT, It's IoL: The Internet of Life! | Psychology Today https://t.co/4U002ffhbS #IoT #tech #digitalhealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenaAD80 Maybe a good idea depending on how schools are these days. What ever happened to Civics class in high s… https://t.co/8nCtztXGTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmieJohnson @NASCAR Wish I was there. Raining like cats and dogs here in East Tenn, lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaroldBingo Joe Rogen is truly a coward cause he will have ppl like Peterson, Sam Harris, Steven Crowder spewing m… https://t.co/NaWhYEolDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry He's already "under arrest" and gets "arraigned" before a judge this morning - CNN can't even bring them… https://t.co/jsSBJNGRR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ٹورانٹو- پاکستانی عوام کو ٹی وی چینلز کے زریعہ حواص باختہ کردیا گیا ہے۔بس ہانکنے کی دیر ہے مشرقی پاکستان کی طرح۔ اورپھر سکون ہی سکون۔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hbd to my best friend! I’m so thankful for you because you have always been there for me. I love you sm and thanks… https://t.co/LRzam9xr8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleCherrick I’ll definitely be considering a battery system down the road]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, please! #doublefatso #cheeseburger #merkts #latenight #fries @ Fatso's Last Stand https://t.co/rTFnMWEXfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJPreller @Truthistruth15 @C_LosR @RedTheTrucker @FightinFriars @TooMuchMortons https://t.co/uW8EJe02ZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people driving slow down all unnecessarily just to look at a wreck on the other side of the road. 😐  *M… https://t.co/Bl9k1IKqpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFIAM640 NYC ex-pat hear you’re way off at what’s going on in Long Island city if Amazon did come there it’ll be t… https://t.co/e84amltJZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving KC on a jet plane and heading home! @ Kansas City International Airport https://t.co/sKuAoXgNF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamJuJu has the world by the balls. Hope he COMPLETELY forgets this senseless and grade school behavior by @AB84… https://t.co/A3VMNKPc4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice is done. El Chapo is going to the super max slamo! Congratulations to our legal system that expertly conduc… https://t.co/CaXcWubri3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jctee13 @BridgetPhetasy There is a market for it. Just as their is a MAGA market. It's not the words it is the reg… https://t.co/dtKkXXhD6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonka’s aunt is gonna see Cardi B &amp; she has no idea who she is 😂 I’m excited for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[N’shade we kinda let “Wet” by @NicoleScherzy go too unnoticed. She fuckin worked that music video/choreo outtttt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out! I donated to 'Orange Ribbons For Jaime' -  https://t.co/PDFVjTInGF via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this mean I'm old????  #WheresGrandpasHat? @ Bowlero https://t.co/4hGWePKBk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoosiers showed much more intensity against Purdue. Good effort, bad shooting, and that should have been a foul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight @LionUpBaseball has a chance to make ULL 1-7 (lolol that’s terrible) with a win!! they beat a ranked texas… https://t.co/liJa2ySfku]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ultimate sacrifice to be skinny is leaving my house on a Sunday to go to the gym 😭😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JodyOls02485820 I’m a firm believer that you teach people how to treat you 👍they will figure it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[United States citizens will need a visa to visit Europe starting in 2021 https://t.co/vIPjMbF5Ox via @CNNTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work for the president. If you want me to speak about the president and all his gratitude I will. Anypresident. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirgilioPonce @SolRevoBol @EmbavenezParis @glennadaboin Nicolas "El Carnicero" Maduro... y estupido en extremo! https://t.co/oG5oM3LmFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecto1outatime @MalcolmDavidSt2 @SauterRory @real_defender @realDonaldTrump You libtards,  can you read this map? https://t.co/AVdAxkiMVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear it and believe it! #AndSatanLaughed #RepurposeYourSkeletons #Disqualified #PictureOrStory]]></document></documents></author>