<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[She’s always been the one to watch since she came onboard many years ago. Tosa is lucky to have her as part of our… https://t.co/ur911zS2No]]></document><document><![CDATA[After she died in 2005 I looked at her life. Her tears dried from my eyes. Over 50 years of pain and brokenness in… https://t.co/6u58xJPdBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bringmemission @LVPhantoms section 109 row 4 seats 5-7 “let’s go Phantom’s!! https://t.co/XoV4tPvqwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had my dog since I was 8 man. EIGHT. I’m 24. I don’t wanna let go :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at how this man is looking at him..he's in disbelief of this mormon being president of the free world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to all those friendships that were ruined because of someone catching feelings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bundled up is better, I wanna stay that way. 📸: @bagladies - . . . . . . #snow #winter #naturallightphotography… https://t.co/fxShoYjpHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wicked cool to see these hard core surfers 🏄  at Sand Beach @ Sand Beach https://t.co/M1ivk9CyNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go read #educated by @tarawestover immediately! I devoured this book in two flights. Inspiring and thought provoking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for listening. It’s all I needed. (When your friend makes time to FaceTime you and check up on you)… https://t.co/9HMKJ8tcUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FinancialTimes @Edgecliffe It was a branding mistake to put 2nd headquarters only on East Coast.  If he was going… https://t.co/7nVxyoryjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitmanhedge Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I wouldn’t trade living in the city for anything, I always love coming out to the country for family tim… https://t.co/CQZJYdAtii]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sundayread on #tech news in Canada if you missed it last week: #cdnbiz #Blackberry announced over $300 M… https://t.co/h1e9rts5dH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigredwavenow 😄 Santa, my tweets disappear! Too much Truth burns their brains.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emt4godgranmma1 @AstroTurfUSA @njfarmerwife @turk3655 @OldCarNutz Thanks so much Carla!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @heartzcf to post the cover of 7 books I love - no explanations - just the cover… https://t.co/tp6G7pNP78]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so done with everything😭 School, Softball, Work, Friends, Boyfriend and Family.. I can’t do it all! I don’t hav… https://t.co/bcVtrzl4Gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Who is falling for this fake publicity stunt?? Who??? Just fyi.. u ain’t foolin most]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victoire des Dragons @CollegeLafleche 12 ième victoire pour @antolyon31 5-2 vs Sorel-Tracy 🥅 #goodjob https://t.co/vdgbC9CnSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY WEIGHT DOESN’T DEFINE ME 💪 . . It’s taken me a long time to figure out that my weight isn’t my label. I’m soo mu… https://t.co/vinqGHGF8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone stole the pic of my tat and put it on insta lmao i don’t fucking think so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please follow me, Twitter had locked me out from following anyone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Dick Cheney’s longtime cardiologist accuses Trump White House of ‘hiding’ his medical data  https://t.co/sxDWpc1K7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[The passing of my granddaughter is devastating. Please keep my family in prayers!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyones telling me to get sleep for my birthday and let me tell you, im not leaving my room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like a kitty 😸 lately✨💋 #meow #vibes @ Lighthouse Point, Florida https://t.co/DvnJwWdLbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shekystudebaker @nytimes They had one job. They failed. The met the consequence. What’s so bad about cleaning the comb?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedology @TforTieBreak Ok do orange, I’m convinced! It is very pretty, represent! 🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleEggert I was the same way with my daughter and worse with my grandchildren! Mama don’t play that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZonTrill Got these people looking at me like you ain’t got home training.... only person that know about those is me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot make this up! #pitbullsofinstagram #violetjune #divadog #princesspitbull @ Kantz-Vegas https://t.co/xHMoJ0Fh0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful experience working with this group @westernuEdu the past few weeks creating a dance about body image. Eve… https://t.co/6qPf5bUR6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is coming for dinner?  #share #mayanypizzabarngrill #pizza #dinnerinmesa #italianfood #wings #sportsbar @ Maya… https://t.co/iQffayI0HK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this girl is one of my bestfriends and I’m so incredibly proud of her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estebangerbasi @mudo367 Maravillos padrino López las Ratas como tú no deberían existir y con el perdon de las rata… https://t.co/TDtThMn3Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all looked so good in this video...ps Max should wear yellow more often 💛 @maxandharvey https://t.co/xwjXrLiaql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tellement surprise 😉 Le Momo challenge est un leurre... #hoax  https://t.co/Qw73rtGXGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SaturdayThoughts #SaturdayMorning #SaturdayMotivation https://t.co/jJnqa0ITcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLoeSeattle I have muted several people over the weekend and this morning, how did you know ! Gonna wear that button out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay wtf.. why do I only look cute at night???🙄 https://t.co/uab03ZBRXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deronearcher When hell freezes over. They’ll never break the chain of women surrounding the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beettthhhanny I guess we both decided to pick up overtime this week! 😂😂 Maybe Wednesday!! I know Thursday is wedding day!!! 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rewire_News @PPFA @HHSGov THIS IS A LIFE ....STOP KILLING IT https://t.co/bXbjSFekzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thatcher fouls multiple times to send Scottsdale Christian into the bonus to stop the clock to chip the 15-pt lead… https://t.co/IPVUmJvoBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuchmoreIT @NASA Um, no...I do nap to golf, though. Is that the same thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌈 disco lights for Mr. Disco ❤️🧡💛💚💙 (My photos from the Buffalo show of the #prayforthewickedtour @panicupdating… https://t.co/rhecpJal5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inventory is coming! Many buyers do better prior to the Summer market. Competition is less with other offers. Get p… https://t.co/wskbmGvSZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to teach my pop culture class tmrw and frankly the #Oscars count as prep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Developers are working to turn a former west side church into a mixed use building. https://t.co/Qc8iEr6nCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 Data-Backed Tips to Increase Your Conversion Rate on Twitter [Infographic] https://t.co/2c8IjitLlF via @HubSpot @lkolow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan Seriously man I had to look twice at this to figure out whether it was really the cray cray or you… https://t.co/cMO0O7cXVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @beers300 @madsatan6969 @The_Fool_Monty Yes I do but damn I dont want to look like him lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[despite the ongoing economic harm and taxpayer costs.  Between the 1940s and the 1980s, Congress considered farm po… https://t.co/ZbZOVjE3mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contre l'abattage conscient des animaux de ferme https://t.co/THBXs6bjBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DeSantis on #GrovelandFour: Upon taking office in January, I took action. Joined by our cabinet members, I approve… https://t.co/y5aV5feaxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabbisayings @ASHHurance_ @Annclifftonn Peppa talks now. It’s like a faint little oink]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well hellooooo beautiful ❤❤ @nvidia @NVIDIAGeForce #pcbuild #myprecious #geforce #rtx2070 https://t.co/2FkxnUgZpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well her face is all over the place - her 15 minutes of fame will bite her in the ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSanchezz32 @Mariaana_Rangel He puñetas que tienes es mi crush desde 2018]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 It was a privilege to watch in person such an inspiring conversation about #GenderEquality with… https://t.co/hhipB7AG1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[75 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19 #Southernu_rys19… https://t.co/H83uVMus7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que increíble capacitación de negocios con una mujer que con su gran conosimiento es el poder la educación es la pr… https://t.co/9EVMb2eMKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You do not honor women - don't pretend and don't give us the BS about jobs - the women in the jobs… https://t.co/JxBPx3fD1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMidtownMen I was there!! Loved the evening, especially @LONGORIASINGS "  click here for his version of "Can't t… https://t.co/09h8Xiu8MK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danyiel Walker charged w/ a slew of sexual abuse related crimes, has appeared in court. He listened intently, spoke… https://t.co/2VTjYmepJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So afraid to give a broken heart, when it’s tied to misrepairs, but starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was pho-nomenal! Pho noodles in delicious seafood broth plus snow crab and shrimp! Def need to go back for mor… https://t.co/Wd2ZHY1F8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annendil @MomAutie @ellievan65 I guess I will never understand people who are against trying to reverse damage done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all of our trailblazing community a very Happy Valentine’s Day! 💙🇺🇸❤️ #BlazerNation https://t.co/hnbk0VvsND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtheannaconda @annakilar4 It’s the dollar store how good can it be??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasoncomix I never used to be able to sleep when traveling, but then I had a job where I was traveling out and bac… https://t.co/ymvlPaYAzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today starts the year of all the “lasts”. Good luck to my cheerleader and all her friends trying out for KC cheer t… https://t.co/ACOKr8IRlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mincanada @bentleywoods3 @77_ghawk @IlhanMN Immigration has gone down because since Trump took office the laws are… https://t.co/7u5Pjf0MyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I only slept MAYBE an hour if that. It’s been a rough night, but hopefully I’ll enjoy this runDisney sh… https://t.co/NCZ5eg5oyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A career at BJ's Restaurants, Inc. is the complete package -- everything you want a job or career to be! We are loo… https://t.co/DECkIaugAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[tfw when you are visiting Central Texas for 24 hours and you forgot your moisturizer in Houston.… https://t.co/kYU6ssHGre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitlizgrace People just need to understand. We had a tiny wedding because of our venue. ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ cant please everyone but it’s YOUR day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing all these cute #valentines cards online today...came back from lunch to one!! Fun! Great colleagues! ❤️ @ De… https://t.co/rU0UWpOqj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the best meal of my life at @steak44. Exceptional service and the most amazing filet mignon. Already can’t wait to go back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today ten years ago I went vegan at the age of 14...... and I still look 14 skdndkfkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAKEme_a_samich thank you paul!!! i REALLY appreciate the picture of the dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankfulThursday,#BlessedAndGrateful I'm part of such a #friendly #community. #HollySpringsMS is like no other wit… https://t.co/TYqU9PUms0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vespertine77 @SarahMundy15 @Joe88688676 @HenseThomas @chipper83150233 @DarrenPinnock @MelanieLorimor @SViolyn… https://t.co/uTDOPy0lrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KafrinAfrin I’ve already started my bed stuff in the laundry and completed a massive grocery shopping trip. This i… https://t.co/rjCZfUwoVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell if the noises I’m hearing are my 6 cats or the ghost that lives in my house. It’s kinda annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate an edible before bed thinking it would knock me out but now I’m in the paranoid overthinking stage lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anything ever happens to me, don’t ever act like you fw me when you didn’t 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao jokes on her bc that was a steal for all that extra stupid shit on her nails 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to say I’m more than willing to replace #JordynWoods in the #Kardashians lives. All I require is food 🥘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatGeo Hope at 100 I'll still be chasing men ???? Good 4 her u get - em girl 🐾🐾😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPowley Exactly!!! I'll spell his name wrong but chizmikahaley said it well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ana_milan999 @ProtecttheFaith Oops I should not tweet “on the go”. I meant “There” and Dubia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Tasting - Added more to my lists, Thanks❣️ @TheJaneGonzalez @CspellaneLfcisd @Evans_LFU https://t.co/eyMOjpwuXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to count the amount of times @realDonaldTrump says “people” and “billions and billions”. He’s disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were too little babies on my flight, they cried a little but mostly they were SO CUTE. also kudos to the guy… https://t.co/HAazEsl5pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got tagged by @GMHS_Library to post the cover of one of my favorite books, with no explanation, for the next 7 da… https://t.co/OKiF4BYtSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grzegorz_braun Pozdrawiam i zycze sukcesow w dalszej pracy dla Polski. Gdanszczanie stracili!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValarMorDollars Same. My mom had two TIAs in front of me (one when I was six and another at 12). We were prepared the second time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infinxtyonhigh I’d be good with being pranked by Loki right about now....]]></document></documents></author>