<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hate when ppl be like after 9 pr before 8 like just gimma a fuckin time]]></document><document><![CDATA[￼  One of Britain’s most successful athletes was forced to sit out an entire Olympic cycle after suffering serious… https://t.co/Rwxnv7zUoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at DSCC Building 20, 3rd Floor in Columbus, OH https://t.co/1HNr6yli1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrs_Van_Matre Aww...this is so sweet, thank you! Your costume really captures Cloudette's personality. Here's a vi… https://t.co/LjCkFQCfjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seeyounvr @ladybaguettee Don’t gotta ask me twice 😌 that would be all the vibes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Album Spotlight March 8, 2019 Featured Albums For March 8, 2019  Mystic Crock - Seduced Sen… https://t.co/xYlRlZFKkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLCowgirl @StLouisBlues @AshleyHomeStore Took a slap shot off of his knee in the 1st.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if I had like a 1% influence with these two I’ll take credit. They’re pretty bad ass. (They made me switch hat… https://t.co/c24zNKGcOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonUrista Nah man that was Harlem’s hero. He tackled crime with his bare hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetoBiden @Demgirl50 @antitrumpresist @maydaymindy9 Will offer Joe and Amanda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harikondabolu https://t.co/RDpe675iWz  The amount of hate crimes against conservatives exceeds hate crimes against… https://t.co/TJpq2qEDLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torinomonty @alamort This is the biggest carried in the supermarket where I work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow @GettyImages @MayaRudolph @tinafeylaughs @smrtgrls @TheAcademy @KevinHart4real @randomwrld it's hilarious ju… https://t.co/bxhgHe4NgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Coach Dotson &amp; Wise Central Girls Basketball Team Bringing it BACK to SWVA CONGRATS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GajaShtirka @EdKrassen I'm trying really hard, but daily to see this 'also' you've apparently invented out of thin air.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cornerman Red Ale by @BrewDetroit at @HopCatD — https://t.co/uWowmu6bpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISMRaceway @ChicagolndSpdwy @CBellRacing @NASCAR_Xfinity @JoeGibbsRacing jinxed!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember dreaming about an external 5MB HDD for my Apple IIc that cost something like ~$1K at the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[F1 should contract Frederick Wiseman to direct their next season-long doc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alvean_Mer @chrissyteigen @KaitMarieox @LoganPaul I didn't ask anything but yeah. Have a good one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I buy moose tracks ice cream I work up an elaborately unfunny joke about how it started out as regular unt… https://t.co/huptBLPuvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: POS / Technical Support - https://t.co/nKAlCG7VLU #ProjectMgmt #Coppell, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hence why the @Giants are looking up with no hope to get better any time soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vslystocks11 @SportsCenter James Harden would Foul out before Halftime 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[This household gets super hostile when we start playing super smash bros]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally time... I’m really about to start the finale of the office for the first time ever. This shits got me… https://t.co/mBvRXiFzOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[VHSL quarterfinal 3:00 left 4th,  Ridgeview 45  Floyd County 36  #GBB #HCBG #VHSL @tnsportslive @BHCSports… https://t.co/Wdsx2sEvtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KustomElvis @AbacusMike She got her powers the same way as characters like Spider-Man or Daredevil via accident wi… https://t.co/Ic28omyd3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[In about 1948, began to be taken over by Prescott Bush, election night coverage 2016 presented as the comical culmi… https://t.co/W6kmoxA4ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Nothing but the best for the fam.. I don’t gotta flex for the gram! Too many rings for my hands, so we stack em an… https://t.co/T6fUoiHeJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickbaumgardner Come on man. Michigan had half their team sitting through the whole game. State went to the foul l… https://t.co/QM91wAQL1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVacchianoSNY @BigOliveri Ralph, as a fellow reporter, how many times can we beat the same angle on a story. I und… https://t.co/GuJrQfKqNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here thinking you haven’t a clue what you’re talking about and should probably talk about something else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy that Uzi dropped “Do What I Want” in 2016 and it’s still relevant, he could join ISIS and blow up NYC in… https://t.co/SH7ldpcwoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paraphrase 1 Cor 13:1-3, if I have all the gifts that we all celebrate, measure, put on stages and aspire to but do… https://t.co/A1i3Plmizb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choked by the USA into this position pure evil by America...   Doomed Venezuela: This One Number Shows Just How Bad… https://t.co/dtGYwXAfTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day’s first witness FBI firearms examiner Erich Smith shows jurors 3-D reconstructions of #CoreyJones shooting. Pro… https://t.co/5Nqid5YCC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LIBfestival GOT MOVED TO BUENA VISTA! I’m hyped I might actually get to go this year, it’s soooo close]]></document><document><![CDATA[YIMBY has some traction in lower-level Denver races, but not the mayoral election. The top-line race is all about n… https://t.co/z80DVsTYw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkmacneill @Buccigross I sure know what I'm doing the weekend of December 6th. ASU #PioneerTogether road trip!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three Baltimore Teens, One 12-Year-Old Charged with Sexual Assault https://t.co/7QcEtUecAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy no fue un buen día en En Algun Lugar De Juarez. https://t.co/QLjqBvGUkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Born!!! (Part 1) Highlights!!! Muse!!! Live At The Palladium!!! 02.09.19 @muse @mattbellamy @Dominic_Howard… https://t.co/5TifhNASuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because I clapped that shit doesnt mean I'm obligated to be your man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont think UNC is 1 seed but can we stop Duke as 1 seed talk...ACC ain't getting 3 #1 seeds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x0taylormarie @khloekardashian That's a good thing. I prefer a Taylor Marie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ChrisPope That’s two dirty plays by Formenton this week.  Let’s all wait for the OHL to do something this time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know is that I have 5 /4 years worth of bottled up love and affection. Who ever date me next and I'm giving o… https://t.co/krngEgZiFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you say on Twitter is up to you but what other people say is not. #Stoicism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PossessionWR @Nick_C_C @Barstool__UNLV @TheRunninRebels @LasVegasLocally I was most definitely already alive and kickin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[DBs at the combine number one need to make their feet shoulder with apart &amp; not close together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michigangirl203 Because I can't imagine why anyone would find that guy sexually appealing]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to my roommate for waking me up at 3 am by singing in his sleep??? Wtf man??? I’m moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[RSVP to Dehd, Waco Brothers, Tatiana Hazel, Tasha, The Curls, Half Gringa at The Hideout, March 09, 2019 with Do312 https://t.co/AAcAqLLl9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4boysnanny @jlw8375309 Try not believing right wing media I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Ea… https://t.co/6758mJzyoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ternbicycles @BicycleShow @BoschEBikeUSA @BikingToronto Sorry I can’t make it, have a great show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You swipe right on me on 3 different platforms. Don’t want to talk to me. And then you unmatch. What do you want? F… https://t.co/7fwchK4pGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night last night!!! We all had a blast... #TheCollaberation #WorkingClassCultura @ Wild Willy Cantina https://t.co/y18GT73knl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your failed leadership couldn’t even get it out of cloture!  What an embarrassment you have become! @timburchett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @mattgaetz Treason, racism, stealing, pathological lying. You fit in well with the disgrace in the… https://t.co/gu902iRWTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has everyone in San Diego been a all the rain we've been blessed with lately?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Beto is another fake! Second only to Obama!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_Padival @enn_nafnlaus @PlugInFUD @CGrantWSJ @markbspiegel @WallStCynic Hi @S_Padival you're a huge idiot and I a… https://t.co/QjAxx7jsq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moments That Will Last A Lifetime.  https://t.co/ke3UYH3yZq #whitebarnmanor #wedding #weddingphotos… https://t.co/tjSk5hpQps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unscriptedmike @larryqqueen I ALSO REMEMBER LEVIN MOCKING TRUMP BACK THEN. SENT HIM A TEXT, EXPLAINING MY SUPRISE… https://t.co/QoF126EjjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWasHrren Three double Jacks usually relieve the pain and free the muse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Papa Murphy's in Dubuque, IA https://t.co/MA6L54Mz7f https://t.co/qcIBYDWDMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, I visited the Wende Museum of the Cold War in Culver City. #california #love  #culvercity #coldwar… https://t.co/4GnDKU3kZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonflyJonez "I did not kill Joffrey but I wish that I had. Watching your vicious bastard die gave me more relie… https://t.co/YRUIiEBCh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jg_block_cap @sassal0x @APompliano Cut it out, you’re ruining my narrative 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaMardoll "Revenge of the Nerds" essentially glorifies rape when the lead nerd dresses up as another character an… https://t.co/aCgvOkAXJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lernvsradio No doubt. I will say most of it is from the younger kids from what I see. I could be wrong. Either way totally disrespectful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help us at @FromTheHoodFor1 with our fight against homelessness. https://t.co/ISvCzNqIcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we can see more of the official network instead of watching the players. Great....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 3006 TINKER DRIVE #FortWashington #MD  #realestate https://t.co/BaXxgbJCgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re so thankful to work with a software and systems partner like @ConcentricSky and the @BadgrTeam who make tools… https://t.co/q4zOJYXVPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The flag bearer of SOCIALISM = The Democrat Party (which is anything BUT democratic)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For the $3 Billion in tax credits that NYC planned to give Amazon, NYC estimated $27 Billion in total revenue.   9… https://t.co/QiS8sZI2P9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olobersyko I just wanna say man thank you for your music I’ve been going through some tough times with my depressi… https://t.co/fcEQlVthJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t have to go far to find adventure. A walk in Muir Woods (just 25km from Pier 39) can feel like a world awa… https://t.co/BWSN23txk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s another one of those nights where my love for my friends and mutuals is at 120%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KenCarman Is it to soon for me to order my #13 “Sevensome” #Cavs jersey? Asking for a friend... @D_Diggler69]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s heartfelt to forgive loans. Wonder how those that worked hard to pay them back feel about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @realDonaldTrump Nothing to see here just like what’s in your pants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom You are losing credibility because you are not calling it what it is: A cult #TrumpCult]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks man! Keep being real with people and shining the light.   Now clean that mug out. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furthermore, since we’re on the issue of the safety of public institutions, why not introduce a bill that will allo… https://t.co/nPuohSV64e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamMegl Basically, if im right 60% of the time, and when I'm right I win 2, and when I'm wrong I lose 1, well then I'm making money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was very excited to welcome ONW grad and recent Houston Astros draftee Austin Hansen to @OlatheSouthHS today to dis… https://t.co/q7Dpn7kGMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dingzip @rob_sheridan those phone booths;;; look out they're gonna rotate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@losexpulsados @gap_mar @BerePadilla_12 @pattyrodz_ @MiguelAngelMuri Miedo?? Pon la foto del que le sale espuma por… https://t.co/UyX5JcyLQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/CRnCWUOA37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @realDonaldTrump @NASA You did it dude. Launched and landed. COOL!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ L'Oratoire Saint-Joseph du Mont-Royal https://t.co/R2Qj4UETbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docamitay @ONPsych Oooh. The shit disturber in me want to be rich enough to start a lawsuit and make them public.… https://t.co/E8nxi0Pm1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELaw20 I Will Always Support Americans’ Rites Until I Think They Shouldn’t Have Them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepingabbey @TheStraightHops @ephoustonbill @zappafaye @j_cohl @DRE_Go_Fish @RedStripeRocco @Just4BeerLovers… https://t.co/UWbsmggvcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did watch the #Nets earlier but because I’m home sick, I’m wasn’t gonna allow them to get my blood pressure up to… https://t.co/tNp6RnXOKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell this to my tattoo of an albino rainbow hat wearing elephant... #LegalizeFreedom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @ava “More Minority Outreach from Republicans” by William B. Turner https://t.co/UwCe7VpFQh]]></document></documents></author>