<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Pervaizistan I came to praise scallops, but the landings data buried them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANCALERTS Not a chance on 2022 presidency. Voters will want to know how Davao city spent P2,739,726.02 pesos  per… https://t.co/fAVgF19G9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprise visit to Madison,WI store today and we had a blast with customers! @Hawley11511 @jimmills22 @tracySprint… https://t.co/hA8Za8XrYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mental illness didn't dall far from the tree. I'm sure she was hugged a whole bunch after her screeching ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elfloridian@yahoo.com Papo dos letras para felicitar a Marina por el día especial de hoy - cariños a todos, Albe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever have a teacher running late and 5 min goes by and you convince the entire class that since the teacher i… https://t.co/on9yUgYDR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know anything about Carol Danvers aka #CaptainMarvel so I bought the first 2 issues of the new series to see… https://t.co/glenx5lmYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit thought I got snubbed at the Saloon by @manbearkitten but then did a double take and it definitely was not hi… https://t.co/jlqfIsw4yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJohnYarmuth You should be ashamed of yourself and dems, Obama increased national debt by $12 trillion u n dems said nothing! hypocrites]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precision Training instructor Hannah from @FlywheelSportsDupont is taking over our #Instagram today. Find us on IG… https://t.co/UdXhr5eNBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a new week let’s all start it right! #mondaymotivation #mondaymood #positivevibes #zen #atpeacewithmyself… https://t.co/YNd5Btx8Az]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiss at the Whiskey was an amazing show.  Smallest stage they ever played on]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an honor to meet with Senator Cornyn in his Capitol office. We appreciate his responsiveness to issues importa… https://t.co/OpC1bCncP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Queen Solange blessed us! Def was bumpin’ this &amp; Chainz getting ready for work this am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano @GaryWil16118163 She's fake very fake!!!🤬🤬🤬🇺🇸🤬🤬🤬🥓🥓🥓🥓🥓🥓🥓🥓🌭🥓🌭🌭🌭🥓🥓🥓🥓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaledonianKitty @tiffanytunes Jo, you are exactly correct! Such a Beautiful Lady! #TiffanyForever ❤️🌹🌈💕 https://t.co/pzzN9Vzttz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeneVeritas Cualquiera que admire y aprecie a los Castro no puede ser ni ecuanime ni democrata...mas bien todo lo contrario]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nolamastodon @_RHancock19 @_QTip I start judging by quality of plastic used in them go-cups]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, it helps I'm a Liverpool fan, but I haven't enjoyed watching a trio of teammates like Salah, Mane, and Firmino… https://t.co/Osx56F9ErI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else having trouble getting people to follow back I follow resisters back and wait 3 days if no follow back… https://t.co/tiLLjyxIni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meigs boys trail 28-26 at the half in their first round District 5-AA Tournament game. Samuel Anderson, Noah Davis… https://t.co/slzI9GGQ7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[$740 million — that’s how much Alabama Power (a subsidiary of Southern Co) plans to charge ratepayers for a coal pl… https://t.co/AzsvftWWyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPWomack See when you do the clownery... https://t.co/Qbdm7PEY89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllTheHockeyz @wyshynski Yeah lol or the fact that he was willing to kill a baby for food. Crazy movie, really wie… https://t.co/pJe49t4Kqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: CPD says #JussieSmollet criminally charged for filing a false police report— not formally indicted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karinabarbosa Jajaja muy bueno, me too. Y eso que tu tan guapa, pero así es la vida, caprichosa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Dancè by Machel Montano &amp; Jacob Desvarieux. https://t.co/3Vw3SDlbZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a pleasure working with this guy the past two seasons! Can’t say enough about his work ethic and compete both… https://t.co/o8V7FU5pEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyAdell Tatum, Brown, the Memphis pick... what else do they have to offer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[La poesía te abre los ojos, te deja soñando y hace repetir las palabras y los versos en voz alta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzanier468 Virtually all Italian films are dubbed after the fact in the studio. Regardless of the language the act… https://t.co/j1AOUz3XVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timmmo510 @RealTeamJon 2Lie about Kings. Fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents… https://t.co/PZN4kGCKbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @obj and @DustinFox37 got Twitter into a hoopla last night when it might have been the AB stuff all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabbiiii_vargas I’m lowkey scared of animals that aren’t cats or dogs... https://t.co/W5mXjYR5QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@start_82 I can't speak for Cup but can say firsthand with trucks, now Xfinity, is way more than being a supervisor and signing time cards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️ Happy Humpday! ⭐️  📸: @pernelllanghorne Edit: @jc_musicality #humpday #beach #gay #gaycute #gayhot #gaysexy… https://t.co/dJq4yBreix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great session on the opportunities that exist for students to find lucrative entry points into the workplace and ca… https://t.co/FAFgj4htWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love great headphones... has anyone tried these @Dolby ones? I’d assume they aren’t on-air headphones but... how… https://t.co/1KJEfwBI70]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrific ending to @winespectator Seminar Series at #sobewff with this great lineup from @GBvins gerardbertrandusa… https://t.co/VaayNsp4xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Pres Trump    Please get amazing legal minds of Gregg Jarrett    Alan Dershowitz    Joe Digenova a… https://t.co/LRV4lWehMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro That is sad and funny....60% gone ???...cite your source...]]></document><document><![CDATA[gather up your #brokenness the #shards, the jagged edges give #God your #shattered pieces all of your #hopes, your… https://t.co/hr3sPLXADG]]></document><document><![CDATA[State Dept. isn't consulting with Congress on tougher Russia sanctions as it promised  https://t.co/2l3cTAJGWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @ForgeFCHamilton the “Galaxy” of #CanPL? i.e the team that fans of every other team think are being set up to win by league powers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo this show #Impulse on @YouTube Originals is awesome. It's like a sequel to the movie #Jumper I think... anyway t… https://t.co/0QQxANP6mC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demaryius Thomas escapes car crash with minor injuries https://t.co/KpPXbqhtaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadJohnBrown @daveweigel sounds like the standard democrat of the past few decades]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu The logic itself is faulty. Garbage, the Garbage Overwhelm Party. They rejoice in garbage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATomEAtkins @mattyglesias Yeah, but at that point the train is totally pointless. A Greyhound takes half the time… https://t.co/TSJG4WHlPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@discordapp is BY FAR one of the best apps I have ever seen, I'm just waiting until they have an xbox app, I am des… https://t.co/h033lnNEgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soonerrf I haven’t tried it yet. I’ll let ya know. I love that stuff, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drmistercody My best friends’Sister’s Cousin (who lives in Denmark) is an Historian, and told me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[me n my buds  (thanks to shari.elf for the whimsy and scottayotte for the foto) @ World Famous Crochet Museum https://t.co/MiNzV2oRxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like waking up and realizing your spouse isn’t really mad at you and that it was all a dream. Or was it? Sh… https://t.co/seFR0diGG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkup @sarah_edo @_ElleOhElle_ @JemYoung I've been at Google for two years and I got blamed for this today too. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bagel With. Da schmear. Back when I lived on Long Island it was always fun to go w the men to get bagels on a beaut… https://t.co/3aFloSp6bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSTwinCities @NWSTwinCities I measure 9” of fresh snow over the last 24 hours in St. Peter. https://t.co/tPWQS1JQyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#addict 🚫 #liar 🚫 #junkie 🚫 #failure 🚫 #druggie 🚫 #criminal 🚫 #choice 🚫  how about... #HUMAN ✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the children you separated from parents? Glad you’re concerned about them. You found them all… https://t.co/RetK3Ep31d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanWoodDFW @AuntieAnnes The noise I made was not appreciated, but it’s a REALLY good pretzel and I’m not gonna apologize.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeahhhh, it's gonna be a rather tricky parking situation. Whatever time you were thinking of getting there, I'd mov… https://t.co/o6hvw5dTKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh... This was just a sparring session for Jones. Main event sucked! #UFC235 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here is Caldwell 1 (at the open end of the V-shaped asterism at center left), a star cluster older than our Sun… https://t.co/MAJLuHIUjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron planting the seeds incase his ass don’t make the Playoffs. Typical Lebron, nothing new folks... 🙄 #Lakers… https://t.co/NWnXFFtGDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you listen to someone's personal story it has the potential to change the world for good #SusanFowler @sxsw #SXSW2019 #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedo_jesse @Psychedelex Nah you just got that backhand boi, me and Alex just too old for you. We was cramping up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a New or Certified vehicles? Call or ask for Andy Bedolla AndyBoy "King of the Ridiculously low prices"… https://t.co/sByCaF0yUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBTamis All I want to read right now are pieces that help me understand how close we really are to a full fledged… https://t.co/lfudHp3PcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the tattoo artists are eating wings and teriyaki and I’m jealous af😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaitiaremateos Vaitiare , te ves preciosa y súper sexy en Hechos AM te amo 😍😘😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotoNutJob @tommytickover @biker_Ian @GL650_LynneG Old man winters not done with us yet. We’re still under the avg in BC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless our Veterans! @ Westgate Entertainment District https://t.co/ftxyoPC7DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gizadame @YossiGestetner @politico @LindseyGrahamSC @Jim_Jordan @paulsperry_ @TerryMoran @DonaldJTrumpJr @LouDobbs… https://t.co/if5UNVFpIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I listened to @toogaytocarepod as a whole ass barb and I finished like: https://t.co/PefJk6GwNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Mueller should question Adam Shittttt how he got away with molesting teenage boys and paid them off with tax Pay… https://t.co/VTlyjLIfdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, all be Jamal for 20,000 an episode. When’s the next audition?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheekee996  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. Yes. I'm on @GridleyDaniel's pace to have the best weekend ever. This is how we start three days of the profess… https://t.co/vYiQhmSXLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Not a bad choice either. Maybe too "white"..? (Given Biden's past - &gt; Anita Hill)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielMKishi @CharlesFLehman How about "we need to stop treating them like infants who can't be expected to make t… https://t.co/4O1zbE3me1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDudley85 @IdiotTracker @Revkin @mzjacobson @arevkin @sunrisemvmt Their permits allow it and there's no permanent facility elsewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6abc Popeye &amp; Olive Oil’s kid 😳 #criminal #kmart https://t.co/2QZN9m834j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this open floor plan. Come by and see me! We have awesome move in ready homes and lots to build on.… https://t.co/0rfZUEkZMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyMacTV Brad Thompson will be there next Saturday? Can you share who else is coming?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Leavitt They wouldn’t exist without our infrastructure.  If they use it and it’s part of their success they should pay their share.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden @UDBidenSchool @jmeacham I hear you are going to  Run All you going do is run the US in the GROUND REMEMB… https://t.co/5EqbfwCVZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching AWS serverless model with @alnutile #nerds19 https://t.co/xpTxmjk1xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nra membership needs to do something about their leadership that allows for this to happen. 😠😠😠😠😠👎👎👎👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCicilline @davidcicilline @donlemon @HouseDemocrats I’d rather eat lint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw #theotherjoshcohen last night at #westsidetheater.  A really fun, heartfelt, clever show that celebrates the ni… https://t.co/dGiHGhE5kU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNewton @pardesoteric I'm borderline impressed he's still alive; it's like he drank Kieth Richards blood or so… https://t.co/hSTYfEJc4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight of @NEO_Wrestling 10 competitors are in tonight's finals at the @NJCAA West Centrall Qualifier in Parsons, Kan. @NEONorsemen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebettes Come on Mike time for you and Alex take a road trip together some meet and greets maybe at --25 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartenRoorda I agree @MartenRoorda. You can have the best curriculum in the world, but if the #teacher leading the… https://t.co/69hGogUYUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we lose the sec championship because of the Florida Gators I’m gonna slit someone’s throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@augustmcgregor Love the lapels on the vest. Pure #badasshaberdashery   Awesome stuff in drop 2!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys (Boston media) have a lot to do with where the chemistry went.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me why the day I’m tired and looking crusty af people Ik and haven’t seen in a while decide to walk into my restaurant?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently the @WSOP satellite @Horseshoe_BC got chopped 10 ways for at least $4000 each right after my AA got popp… https://t.co/R6ETrtTtlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonalds how are you supposed to be open if you're only accepting cash right now? How are you going to get busine… https://t.co/k3bOU9ZZgd]]></document></documents></author>