<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Team_Penske @Pennzoil @joeylogano @NASCAR @NASCARonNBC @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCARONFOX @FordPerformance Looks great! More coming!🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[think i’m just gonna get some snacks and watch everyone’s spring break on the internet bc im poor as fuck 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SperryBernie @ScrewedHumans So now we are going to kill babies in the ninth month and kill the seniors at 80, wow, thanks Democrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariannaNBCNews She called his behavior racist--she did not say HE was a racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect little angel @ Fayetteville, North Carolina https://t.co/JM807gA67d]]></document><document><![CDATA[vday reminds me of whs men’s basketball team running sweetheart laps #iykyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is TRUMP not in jail??? Sexual Predator. Serial Rapist. NO means NO! Liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heneidocof @QueenJAMES_2you https://t.co/xNLtKtRF5w Nurse at abortion clinic tells it like it is. Ppl have been ki… https://t.co/LyIhCvhmsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rt for good luck if not this will happen to you. Sending all bad juju vibes your way https://t.co/rTtowmxuQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @RepMattGaetz I was thinking same thing. Lots of coordination here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias Chile 🇨🇱 🇻🇪💛💙❤️🇨🇱🇻🇪 #Repost @evtvmiami (get_repost) ・・・ "Democracia y Libertad, Venezuela!"🙌🏾🎶 🇻🇪🇨🇱 - La ed… https://t.co/FkIBbQEnz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquelineLabr7 @jazzteamstore @vivintarena @utahjazz @4judyblue Thanks so much Jacqueline!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tame tall tart @mainedcm  / Stacy  #DADDYSGURLFirstCrush  #MaineMendozaBarbie60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con Sue Photography and Design  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/p1DIMNX5Ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[DASL provides para educator training. Check us out to help your para educators get needed hours. Capitol School Dis… https://t.co/EhfioxVGAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetSetJamerson @boosted_podcast @SabbyrinaW @michaelaaann @DaniGeorge_ @noellemarie_w ur one of the true homies ja… https://t.co/Gc15hocNHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally made it to wafflelovesocal - absolutely delicious! 5 Stars! #wafflelovesocal @ Waffle Love SoCal https://t.co/x4h6x0Y4qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataalieej @precioussxoo i would say yeth but thorry i have no money https://t.co/9KgqK3MnZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeff53 @BettyBowers @chrislhayes That long stretch for a 70 year old man is a life sentence. He's facing up to 24… https://t.co/sYVFaJvtTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want your players to be successful...it takes one effort...believe in them enough to encourage them to believe… https://t.co/YCVJmX4qQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn’t accidental, they’ll be apologizing in 2 days, and we won’t be accepting it]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love posting pics from child care programs and Pre-K classrooms. This is where the magic happens!… https://t.co/KrLSWrgqEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow We heard about this a long time ago. Why was this not pushed at that time, when Jared received his final cl… https://t.co/tmgPMHpli0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me dressing for live shots this morning 😬 Our thermometer shows 22 degrees but it feels WAY COLDER because of the w… https://t.co/eNStE2KVuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Whew, it’s been a long, rough day,” she thought at 8:17 AM. #parenthood #thesekids #goodthingtheyrecute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandackich “I literally have no talent” The world agrees Dan #purdue #BoilerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly the besttttt driver when I’m drunk, driving sober I’m the worst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized how to train your dragons 3 game out this weekend..... sooooo who’s going with me to see it tomorrow night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom : If your friends jump off a bridge you jumping too?   Me present day :]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyofD_ 🤔🤔🤔 yeah, not sure about the ACC tourney. He'll be back March 21st or 22nd wherever they fall in the March… https://t.co/QtpHVzRMMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anxiety is at an all time high.... please somebody put me out of my misery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captainmarvel @brielarson Omg me hubiera encantado estar ahí ese día yo fui día viernes ☹️ https://t.co/pJmTfH10wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Bomer on Playing a Gay Super Hero in ‘Doom Patrol’ – Variety https://t.co/9pVnh5cy21]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breathe in calmness and breathe out worry⁣⠀ ⁣⠀ ⁣https://t.co/gDQHOOb70O ⁣⠀ #yogaphotography #yogaphotographer… https://t.co/GyhvVfi3xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDisgusting -- Departure Gate: B16 Arrival Airport: STL Scheduled Arrival Time: 7:16PM Arrival Terminal: 1 Arrival… https://t.co/Enod9ixcqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha! @CrashClark I was like, I see @ShibaRussell got her request, lol!!! 🤣🤣🤣 Love you girl!! https://t.co/rtqCYKxHXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GusGowland @TheTonyAwards A Funny Thing Happened on the Way To the Forum starring Diahann Carroll and Anna Maria A… https://t.co/w4cGmUZtc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie_George05 A 1v1 with you would be a nice prep for ACC tourney 😂😂 . Considering the last game went well 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USCCB Yes Stop and Abolish Sexual Abuse Of children or Adults  in our Churches do not cover up 😭anymore. Protect a… https://t.co/LFBfnWW4rP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señor Alvaro Gonzalez, yo tengo 24 años. No es retaliacion, yo tengo mucha carrera por delante. #menosmiedomasfutbol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanctuary City Man… Worst governor ever… Pollis is right behind him 🤬🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[China closes its Mount Everest base camp to tourists because of garbage, waste - ABC News - https://t.co/F6U4WCDKQy via @ABC News]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyclaiiree Yeah , i know 🤔 welp... gonna be a while before I’m used to this shit man. Single after two years ma… https://t.co/z8Gc8oIx75]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to mention, no payment. Please do not expect a blogger to drive 30 miles to your location for a dish that… https://t.co/FayxG16B2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun Boston Weekend Visit w/Sister-in-Law Dawn: Tour State House w/Drew at helm (former tour guide now BC senior), m… https://t.co/Qv4UqVrlyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever ends up marrying me has to deal with my sarcastic ass 24/7 and I truly feel bad for whoever that unlucky girl ends up being 💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ridethisBMW @BleacherReport @apiecebyguy He’s training, for the night is dark and full of terrors 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra Yo no soy un BOT!  Es muy cobarde de tu parte que si la encuesta no sale como quieres digas que es… https://t.co/L1dE24FMpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitch: Samurailexx  PSN: xsamuraixlexx22 ❤️😘 https://t.co/bPiHd3eORB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teacher me: Still 7 weeks until Spring Break it’s never going to get here #Teacherlife.                     Mom me:… https://t.co/LeDVeC44fC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Totally pisses me off!! I've been at rock bottom, and I worked 16 hour shifts to put a roof over my… https://t.co/ioVvVxr6RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don't forget history what Republicans did to Clinton.  Started with White Water and ended up with… https://t.co/yOOEgGfAks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpFailure and he is too stupid to know it.  @realDonaldTrump We don’t praise #dictators #dotard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personally, I’m here for the three layer jeans. Who doesn’t like feeling trapped in their denim? #thatsalottalook]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for making your way in to my room &amp; supporting the learning! ❤️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shouldn’t matter how much money you think a person has in their account. If you owe someone, just pay them their… https://t.co/iG4p8gKD0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d be at a party and people would literally come up to me and be like “are you @fatasskate from twitter” 😂😂😂 yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpringMill1836 Can I assume from this tweet that you are open for business? I tried to google information this pas… https://t.co/pr0R7nr5gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I put heels on to put me in a better mood and that’s fine until my feet start screaming at me fifteen min… https://t.co/BJtGKAd1eW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eeeek I'm only 20 followers away from 1K 😱 it came so fast I don't know how to celebrate! #booktwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[her comments were not anti-semitic, they're being so hard on her bc she's a muslim woman who wears a hijab. think o… https://t.co/VHwdfXng8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolfAriom @funder @AOC Yeah... I especially like the facts don’t matter bit... as a woman, I want factual, intelli… https://t.co/K7RSfcFzV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katefraley_ man i hope he can squeeze an appointment into his busy schedule 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna believe there’s still good men out there but y’all really wreck your own reputations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cut her off by K Camp came on in this party and I started saying “snip snip”by myself .... forgot I wasn’t at Howar… https://t.co/qs8zNLFRk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day gift from one of my students! So grateful! https://t.co/waPHi7y6lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSmithJr @chadfelixg I take comfort in knowing that I did what was right for him. You should, too. They need us… https://t.co/I0m0UB4ITp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everyone! I am Holly and I am a Reading Coach from Tampa, FL! I am soooo excited to go host this TweetMeet on… https://t.co/545ZpTlZBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, time to get ready for work.  7 days a week is hard, but eventually I’ll figure out something better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Spark Joy (and Curb Envy) with Muditā https://t.co/W3gTlljKkJ via @shinetext]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexigallo like what the heck i just spent the last 5 days living in the libaray then as i finish, i open twitter a… https://t.co/dIHIDrjq3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @dsshep1959 We have been unlawfully convicting people of felony crimes that they're Not Guilty of c… https://t.co/900GN1vgJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP is outraged that Congressional Dems asked for documents from 81 people. During Whitewater,  GOP got documents from 1200.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seth said , "let's walk!" I was like, "oh yeah!" https://t.co/5s4O9G5Muf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I go to visit my mom one of the things I enjoy is seeing my niece and nephew as they mature. Each of them find… https://t.co/84qPwNpBne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy Miss this man - loved his movies❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sachant Same. I’m a little curious about whether or not it’ll address issues like animal abuse in the circus envir… https://t.co/aMz3eLm2QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[tomorrow is liquid stranger day and that’s the only thing keeping me going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalidPhares Great commentary and insights in discussion with Laura Ingram]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went with my dad to see the Golden Knights play last week. It’d been so long since I’d gone to a game I forgot how… https://t.co/djlpz3EX9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students ask why they give up PE once a week for social justice class.  My answer: By learning about the history of… https://t.co/Qj4uxLs5gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was #InternationalWomensDay. Today is #Barbie60 birthday. Last night I saw a lot of #Barbie #dolls in a v… https://t.co/99QJBGiIC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorJoyThayer @Smurgen I’ve been a pony con VIP a couple times; I’m gonna be a community guest at BABScon in Apr… https://t.co/nghK2bHOru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffHudson .....and as the national debt is the highest in history, thanks to Trump’s/Republicans’ tax plan, th… https://t.co/1goBxRS3L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Brexiteers didn't have the hats, but they ran the Leave campaign just like Trump's campaign; stoke fear… https://t.co/ExI9Xs4sdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Celebration of Women's History Month- I am thankful to glean from so many great women!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billkuchman i have my issues with tina but she could do it for sure but i'd really love seth in the role but peopl… https://t.co/WqAP1BL8Ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieEscoto2 @_WeStandUnited I'm glad that just now Abby put Joy in her place - Joy is glorifying AOC, but Abby s… https://t.co/KUwykU4n1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I betcha @CarterWinter could do a really sexy cover of this song. 🤔  https://t.co/VslheiOF0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expectations vs. Reality  #motherhoodunplugged  #oldaf #halloweenbaby #kids #parenthood #celebrating… https://t.co/Gt2fIOvEEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[La condizione delle donne attesta il grado di civiltà di un Paese https://t.co/OunNcoZBEz via @repubblica]]></document><document><![CDATA[so we just gone forget how the beauty and the beat music video slapped i miss 2012]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KYdcTShsJd Jesus I Need You - Hillsong Worship.....Jesus...I need U every moment...I need U!   Remembe… https://t.co/GABd6KeMAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix  @thedragonprince i can’t believe 2nd season ended like that 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/C0mckgJYu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @luluHru @Serremmy @grannyanon1969 @BundyGP @SealeyGerald @sianetta @GKeile @PennsyMtnGirl… https://t.co/FzmaWoWhp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Billings Central CATHOLIC Rams are #1 today in Boys AND Girls Basketball. https://t.co/Qy03CFHYAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bekind #NorrisKind #Proud2bMPS We finished off read across America week with a phlebotomist as our mystery reader… https://t.co/qaVf9Uzyj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my niggas encouraging me to go to class. Grad school is really hard and I be scresssed. Always appreci… https://t.co/Q47FiTkA7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to be a heels wearing person, but where would I wear them to... the grocery store? Lol]]></document></documents></author>