<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Aaaand suddenly I’m back in 2006, ‘The Year 3000’ is playing and I’m about to graduate from high school. 😍💃🏼🌟 https://t.co/WcAqGwNVSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosenberg tell @mRpOrTeR7 not to forget his back YODA!! but show him mine so he can see mine got laid before his d… https://t.co/8q3Zo8syyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bri_shamwell @khloekardashian @jordynwoods @RealTristan13 fuck them both they ain’t shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Deardiary the time change probably wouldn't bother me, if I didn't have to go 2 work😿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyPaws @Lukericardo @notcapnamerica Yup, lol. I used to be a teacher and I would laugh at myself when I would y… https://t.co/WltzfQz37z]]></document><document><![CDATA[new game: guessing men’s signs on dating websites and then never replying again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicsrenshaw @MothersCareers @GetAheadVA @info_outpers @Neelam_coaching @Lucindavdh Thank you for the kind words Ni… https://t.co/spaTSdVJM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimesworld This will be Trump in a few weeks. Crying he’s the victim here in this witch hunt. Just like Netanyah… https://t.co/ywGcnRfd1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitewatercrew Happy Birthday Kimberly!!  Hope it's THE BEST day ever!  😊🍨🍭🎂🎁🎉🎈🎊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryanballantyne_ @diluted_brains I mean thanks but my lips just get really fucking set a lot and I hate it]]></document><document><![CDATA[New equipment, nice! Love the concept. Great job @BillyTolley #GhostAdventures]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate my roommate so much omg!! I’m really nice to her but she’s so rude! So I’m just like fuck you bitch!… https://t.co/KA05gWdmbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any #OUSD student who missed the deadline should apply before by March 11. Students may submit applications at… https://t.co/oCFqGtYiqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, can @kobebryant go to the men’s game at Gampel on Thursday too?!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lookin at Love after Lockup and this show wild 😂💀 lookin at the screen the whole time https://t.co/neNL3bfTsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mccaffreyr3 And look at the history of Jared old man, another CON ARTIST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgentSheryl I've honestly never heard of this person a day in my life 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEVAplanks @mrronclark_ It was!! KEVA planks are so amazing they even made my dream world biology class interestin… https://t.co/AYJGmvQoJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gehrig38 Maxine Watters told her loyal brainwashed followers to harass all conservstives. Its absurd. I hate to ag… https://t.co/87yPRxtHLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of art in healing. #2  #MSDStrong  #ArtHeals #NeverForget #PowerofArt https://t.co/MBcKWX2Jrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Heart... #CharleySue 😘😘😘 @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/hnDda3s46n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how Jarred took me to Chick-fil-A all the way in south Knox when I got off work just bc I was craving it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Well it's Monday. Let's make the best of it. Have a great day. God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 @realDonaldTrump it’s about time for you to pay the piper on your pedophilia. #tiffanyDoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsvn What? 😂 Send Cruz on an expedition to locate the billions of dollars the dude stashed in the mountains! That’… https://t.co/J4X4TYEqaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[وزیر امنیت غذایی پاکستان مطرح کردپیشنهاد پاکستان برای صادرات گوشت و درخواست صدور مجدد مجوز ترانزیت از مسیر ایرانhttps://t.co/DCW3rVdNzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HilaryKimMorden @PainNewsNetwork @ScottGottliebMD thank you Kim exactly what I was asking. please tell me how its… https://t.co/4864TJC8q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair you are an inspiration to all of us who suffer from MS. Your courage/strength is so beautiful ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson One of the few good things about living in Arizona, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @Bryan700 A guy with the same exact "crime" walked. I remember reading about it. Some IT guy originally from Pakistan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed One joint equal to 7 cigarettes! So do you think you can't get lung cancer??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurastacotruck @NicholasPoe24 @JohnHol43241796 @tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump Turn CNN off &amp; actually do your OWN fact finding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I absolutely adore #Biden but completely agree with your husband. Unfortunately life is what happens… https://t.co/waPNqSWFls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine @oldmanluvsmineo something needs to be done about the CA criminal cabal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dark Mode 🌙 just message someone with this 🌙 and it should work. #Facebook #facebookmessenger #facebook #darkMode https://t.co/BjUpfVqqIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShakurStevenson Ummm can we Not put God next to Faulk🤦🏻‍♀️..... u calling the devil 911 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbbaus @JJMeath2377 You know you get less popular with me with replies like these.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usdmbb @StephenRayMusic Thank you for a fun performance, you were great!! Best of luck to you in your singing care… https://t.co/HWvHZFNPP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rules  1. Make money 2.  Use that money to make more money 3.  Repeat #PaidLabel 🤑 Click on the link in my bio to s… https://t.co/0gAURgPJ2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_issajoke @Dehboss284 The horror. Always thought it would break down and slice the car in half lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's picture of the day. @ Hesperia, California https://t.co/mb3BKRkzMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉🎉🎉Tonight, we celebrate!!! Free Entry 5 to 7....reduced cover from 7 to 11 if you're on the guest list. Text MYTH… https://t.co/Sk0QMjbnDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonBrownWV @kbird925 @iRacing @RichmondRaceway Thanks for picking us up!! We had a blast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skoochie23 @EstudioSublime @RobertMaguire_ It is so hard when they go over the rainbow bridge. Sending hugs your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow the time he took for his fans that’s what i loved about him he loved his fans so much and he was not in a hurry… https://t.co/iIoN8lhGof]]></document><document><![CDATA[He just let his fan to post pictures his flying somewhere commercial for me to see ☺️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dykrh271 @PatGrant7777 @CristinPereyra @HasanCelenk6 @Hello2U8 @akomama_tm @Hsnklil @LaxmanS26324965 @m_studart… https://t.co/IVHwgmGkGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musiclovinlife @SetItOff @withconfidence_ @superwhatevr @TheRealDeadKids BET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariajuanadas @Naty793 Precisamente es eso y unos ruidos más que otros. Haz el test. 👉🏻 https://t.co/x88JhPTc6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panerabread 2 questions: Why did you get rid of Hazelnut Cream cheese, and will you ever bring it back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I peeped how important turn up music is, just cuz it's a vibe. And from there a majority of the years I spent… https://t.co/r8pMgJ5MNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't  think she's a werewolf. She could be like me -  full moons and changes in weather fronts cause me to have… https://t.co/7UpUivKwfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 46% Off at Paul Mitchell The School Charlotte https://t.co/nCvPmrYDmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always learning!! I have the hardest-working first &amp; third graders ✨ 📚💗 @Mathnasium https://t.co/vniYwKQAsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump puts his Insanity on full display every day for the whole world to see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump MOST of the asylum seekers are CHRISTIAN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmcguinn1 @realDonaldTrump Not only a dork but also a fool to believe anything the NK leader may agree to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so ready for a walk along the seashore under a moonlit sky on a beautiful Spring night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ladies of the @VASenate and our biggest fan. https://t.co/ZtBag4g9Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommates have unanimously decided that I am the same person as April from #ParksAndRec and honestly I am HONORE… https://t.co/Tt5FvZDWdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Raquelle and I are the only lesbian couple in the world that doesn’t have a single tattoo between us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell * spell check always changes hell to he'll  Royal pain in the ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonLeto #birthdayboy #best drummer I hope you have a wonderful day! Thanks for all you do! 🎂💜 https://t.co/HQCsaBc4jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii What a great son and a beautiful tribute to her life. Keep you both in my prayers. I understand how di… https://t.co/NiMYZJ0aEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got sad that my flights are so delayed that the airport bars closed. Trying to see it as a silver lining that I may… https://t.co/aerFgxToqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BgSpinner LOL my family is a bunch of dancing fools so yea, I know all of them! LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ang landi landi nakakainis hahahahahahahahahahahaha gigil ako netong dalawa cute cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_Deathwish @KingdomKarrie We rescued a pair of brothers some years back. SMART, even as babies, and sneaky and s… https://t.co/u26Vo06glb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’M GOING TO MY FIRST WEDDING IN LESS THAN A WEEK!!!! 🥰 (and yes i WILL be drunk and rowdy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Fernandina tortoise spotted for the first time in over a century”/ It's been in hiding so that nobody kills it.  https://t.co/HmBbyis8Qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaddPeter @DannyApgar I’m not for paying as much for beer outside the stadium as I do inside. Grab a sub, a 12 pa… https://t.co/rJkw8QJqPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gone find me some live ass Houston friends if it’s the last thing I do😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[the past week i’ve tried more positive thinking. PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE listen to me when i say even if it feels like… https://t.co/FbYwF9e9F7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_adaniss For everyone asking what it is: Baklava. Made with layers of fillo dough. Halfway between the layers is a… https://t.co/YU47RqA9Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it really feels nice to have found a place where I’ve been able to slowly learn to get over that. I’ve found ot… https://t.co/hWtiDngNaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLilly1985 @LandryLocker You don't think Riley is skilled enough as a coordinator to put Rosen in a great situatio… https://t.co/FReB1Ek95z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive omar comes from the district that has had the most people leave our country to join ISIS. Any take away?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been guilty of this very thing.   #blessed #serenity #acireshanta #acire @ Acire Fashion https://t.co/7Znc5AZtwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Disturbed @misutachows @inwalksthechow @RAFACORE @JohnMoyerBass @MikeWengren @DanDoneganGtr Love me some… https://t.co/UwLMvL4DCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Would someone please explain to this twit the financial aspects of the Amazon Debacle? She still think… https://t.co/7pC9CStuwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll definitely be dancing to eso y mas by Joan Sebastian at my wedding idc if Adam don’t know what he’s saying 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump If they did it to every President as bad as they do President trump but its not funny sa… https://t.co/Y0EWxDSIe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to literally my favorite person on the entire planet, @Simkonis1. as a present, i won’t post the fac… https://t.co/rVq3YZGpqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TSA pre-check &amp; #unitedAIRLINES Premier check-in close at 7pm, on a Fri evening, before Spring Break 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas tried to kill my brother and counted him out ... Doctors said he wasn’t gone make it.. y’all hurt my momma m… https://t.co/trH7CxPNLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyJenks @THR @GalGadot Im glad you and many other Film people are speaking up about this! After all, without th… https://t.co/D5c5Irtvng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our future child and I will chant this and flap our wings over you @BleedBlue52 this is sooo damn cuuute!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adunham428 aww thank you anna!! ❤️❤️❤️ i already miss my lunch buddies on kairos:”)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lipstickonapug Happens to me like 3 days a week. Lol so scary actually feels like you’re dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Icegirl69 First I'm hearing about the burlesque club but burlesque is not exploitive! And whether he's single or n… https://t.co/5MCrhKIk7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larhing @marc_lotter @realDonaldTrump On line shopping is the cause of the store closings.  It is the wave of the… https://t.co/CtlsjSelMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jen Carfagno at The Weather Channel is NOT an International Spy. She's never had a cavity! She's not even CIA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! BayMeadows times 2! Keep doing your thing guys!! @iAmRachBrooks @AndrewNFJax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannaMarie32 @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @SharonG40210896 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @jeanine_new @Mary60053440… https://t.co/OG88VMOgtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when I see him or I’m around him he makes me happy and feel comfortable around him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo! @UNTsocial @Rho_Delta1920 @UNTNPHC ... @DallasPD will be on campus 3/4/2019...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nadler is right. To conduct an impeachment, we must convince Republicans that their Emperor has no clothes and no m… https://t.co/fPc70J7dmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alectrik @GwadiLad @BernieSanders @SenSanders @SenatorLeahy In 2019 he’s on a wage increase bill with many senator… https://t.co/xeCNVPPwyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CondescendingAF I was kind of meh on his Tito last time I saw it. (But then, who goes to that opera for Tito?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy girls are prettier.  that’s it.  that’s the tweet. https://t.co/nlzWh3aaJx]]></document></documents></author>