<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not one of the replies calls this dude out for calling a woman "deranged b!tch." Where on Earth do people get their… https://t.co/tnOZFpEhIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaWarfield How does the existence of lesbians unfeminine straight women? The honest answer is, sexuality is fl… https://t.co/dQMivByuiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovinoKristen I use ~$300 Celestron Granites, which are great to look through but one trip to the beach and the fo… https://t.co/6XVtL9hocg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Phoenix! You were a great crowd and I'm so honored that you're ready to join our Mission for Arizona. Let… https://t.co/usaUvm6Ahs]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s #AATTNMW  It feels like I’m front row in #ENGR145 or rather at U of I asking for the 3rd or 5th time about a… https://t.co/H92Z9LgxJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods This is a down payment, the appetizer, a taste of the goodness socialism always promises to bring...Hope you love it👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Afternoon #mojito!! @ Noah's Bar and Bistro https://t.co/tMBIB7WBZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soonersbigred That was fantastic viewing. Bet it was even better in person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOUNG WRESTLING FANS: google Nick Bockwinkel. He was amazing. My favorite non-WWF ‘80s wrestler. Seek out his promo… https://t.co/sCH98Lz5yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic night with @fofg sipping the award winning whiskys from wearefortycreek paired with some tasty dishes! Ch… https://t.co/PkTgrrZL8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 PAX post @F3Columbia #TheCastle for YHC’s slow fast circuits &amp; fun on Tombee with burpees @M_Fresh72]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, the PM will not be in #QP tomorrow, but he will have media availabilities in the morning. #cdnpoli https://t.co/V2ffJ7jGWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish this socialist government would take over then I can have free Wireless data at all times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbmontreal  https://t.co/n4T64IgIgz My New Clear Music comes with a 4 Minute Smile Guarantee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexithigpen97 @BrittanyEsquib1 Mood cus my appointment is in 2 days 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee18 That hit me too.  Standing 50 yards away with my own son.  Also loved the kind words from Robbie Keane on… https://t.co/tPhEQMpQlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anvilhead8 photo from my in-laws back yard in Redlands https://t.co/CCdF1DYRt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveVittorini Your right not a good example too justify a fare increase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods McCabe is a moron and a traitor. Wish the great @realDonaldTrump would throw him in jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Details from Kwang Young Chun’s exhibit of 1,000’s of paper wrapped foam chunks, aggregated and rendered into moons… https://t.co/np4eVw7cqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPS is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #SupplyChain job openings, including "CKE Representative I PT… https://t.co/aOI5vWfQix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dos fuerzas posibles: la militar ( opción uno) o la fuerza de la maldad, más miseria, enfermedad y auto aniquilació… https://t.co/VpdK613o5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best I've ever done so far!! #3 w/3 kills! I'm getting better at killing. -Blest #blackout#3 #codblackout… https://t.co/26V5HcV3ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of focusing so heavily on, at this point, needless profits, it really should demand higher wages for the pe… https://t.co/lzmyNrorM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to go out and have a beer or grab sushi shoot me a text I’m bored as fu*k and hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimiuorio Going to have watch Ian Happ bat another 400 times this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When everybody got they taxes but bae shits still pending 😒💔😤 https://t.co/4nNftQbVuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanSchwartz20 @jelynchjr Maybe you are on to something. Prostitution is legal in Vegas. Maybe Middleton saw the Ro… https://t.co/4fUDKu6bPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWalden94 @BackAftaThis It's like he just took a sip of MCDs Coca Cola lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood of Wisconsin provides affordable, quality, and confidential health care to more than 61,000 wome… https://t.co/9PHooJheEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shutterdaddy3 @RealJamesWoods That guy is a POS! Needs to be prosecuted to the fullest and set an example!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZooMFGC When I saw the first uppercut I was like “damn that’s weak as fuck” but then it started playing out and it had me dying 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMEmmaSmart @DanielWElliott @latenitefilms @fcpxpert1 I mean it’s nothing complicated. Import footage in FCPX. Imp… https://t.co/e2q7X7U5B2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I type Philip into search, Google suggests “Rivers” first; never heard of him, but he’s a quarterback so no. But… https://t.co/GXnIIEGMw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almuerzo llegó! #SunnyIsles #PlanDeDomingo #EnFamilia https://t.co/O1W81HMldz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr4thAndLong @michaelirvin88 I watched every episode of that show. It was cool when we met in Dallas and I was lik… https://t.co/HSdpQknGpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all you Trump fans. We built the wall! Because our Little Monster pees over it! #Trump #Littermaid… https://t.co/UQ3J8cVYCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTDemLttrDaySnt @brianschatz I’d add that part of the problem is many things declared legally as emergencies don’t… https://t.co/mDvZK8zGUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBurrisWESH @SpaceX @NASA @WESH Thanks for your coverage. I'm so busy with things I would have forgotten if not for WESH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These secret cabals are the stuff of Socialist totalitarian nightmares.  With the help of the all powerful F.B.I.,… https://t.co/1Cx013qqBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You probably weren't aware what an absolute piece of shit the Jewish Forward is:  https://t.co/y30WwFcAbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost car show season!! Maybe I should go model again. 🤔#NewProfilePic https://t.co/JTWrwV21C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[All gratitude to you BABA for my yesterday,my today and my tomorrow. @ San Leandro, California https://t.co/gXpLCdoVhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss karinka__boss The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MOST Beautif… https://t.co/EggT9JPm80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t had Cometa in a long ass time. Bitch I got flautas and tacos al pastor. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@cainmma is officially back! Watch him casually blitz through pad work at the #UFCPhoenix open workouts https://t.co/nGINr2sxJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost mgelaherrera with get_repost ・・・ Some unpublished pics from the album, definitely my favorites !!! Missing… https://t.co/YzMyP3eY2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tactic works by because his main support comes from the uneducated, gullible, and racist among us. Sad very ve… https://t.co/ScWV6PWmfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatonMl I’ve heard old folks talk about having to take cod liver oil or castor oil, which even SOUND nasty. Why c… https://t.co/H96RfBsX5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @NRA I’ve always believed that quietly, gun makers voted for Hillary, so they could leverage every m… https://t.co/c6bDUc6QSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mine is I tend to go all out for everyone that I fw 😭 idc if we just became friends, here’s my last $5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier You have to remember. THIs is in Chicago and nothing will happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be here if you need me. #deltamedallion (at @Delta Sky Club in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/ZrtGp5Q6d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be great to go to a concert together and see our favorite bands! ❤😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordperks "We have to make THIS...fit into the HOLE made for THIS...using ONLY the things on the TABLE..." (*prett… https://t.co/8EiwDklJQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonoabroad @stilgherrian @AusCERT Most planes I've been on don't seem to have the data lines connected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 27 - Axios AM: Mike's Top 10:   Both Chicago mayoral finalists are African-American women;     ⚾… https://t.co/KmAfZsLoIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YungSethRogen @Hiphopoptamus @KrangTNelson @megynkelly Can't wait for the next movie in the series. "Ralph Breaks the 13th Amendment"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 Ironically, Twitter blocked her picture of a sad puppy, because they claim I have chosen not to see p… https://t.co/GiktM9AHxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my favorite Boricua planing our growth!!! Happy Woman’s Day!! • • #fitness #nutrition #mindset #momlife… https://t.co/v3j6tykSGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Blowing Rock, North Carolina https://t.co/6EFBiZi5E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCageWhite It's a good first two sentences James. I'm excited for the rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm Remember last summer when Rudy G, Trump's personal lawyer, was also trumpeting the imminent end to Mueller… https://t.co/5B1anGwSHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KariLakeFox10 👏👏ummm...and with that I think I will just climb in bed and pull the covers waaaaay up😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShastaMchardy @JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr You got the wrong picture should have Nadlers up there and little Adam shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Also, keeping good affordable healthcare away from all Americans.  Spending twice as much on militar… https://t.co/FDuBEOJv8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @UnwrapYT  video on the mouse lighter than the new final mouse. Let me know if ya wanna try that final mouse 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixing all your favorite music for your #Charleston #Wedding is ONLY part of it. You gotta have a #DJ with the perf… https://t.co/TvLkjEvZKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[God’s measurement for success is not popularity. It’s not follower’s. It’s not job title. It’s faithfulness.  Want… https://t.co/ISwCndI87G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact, kids know that the 600mph winds at @eldoramtnresort are not pleasant before we even got out of the car.  Onto the carousel we go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_humphrey @stejwill @AtheistBigfoot @iamAtheistGirl And I can use the same exact argument correct I been studyi… https://t.co/vtE0Kc6lXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSXcapital How do you figure the Sundance power station conversion will impact #AECO in 2020? If I read right, the… https://t.co/n8cCE5wCiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Diamond Dust by @purebrewing at @khourysfinewine — https://t.co/AmcdQ02gLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure if it was a celebrity Westbrook would have been fine with it. What a shit bag, I bet that kid could shoot… https://t.co/jfqUXmjbDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Thus showing his extreme bias which was on display when he was holding a position that was supposed to be neutral. Riiiight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsDecemberFalls. Show this band some love she started out doing drum covers on @YouTube  @meyta1cohen  Check out A… https://t.co/t3LVDQCoDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danieltdeacon This is serious and needs judicial intervention. Where are the Originalists?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWOOD 👻 #GOONEYSAINT 😇 #CASHAPP #MADEINNYC #NEWWAVE #TARHEELS color-way @ Lower East Side https://t.co/4eZEf9yjY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Karacson Male Sissy Crossdresser Feminized No Longer a Man #Faggot #Fucked #Bareback #Michael #Karacson… https://t.co/AuFzgyd6Nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @JillDunlop1  @douglasdowney @C_Mulroney @CBCMorningLive So, why aren’t you helping workers at GM? They… https://t.co/mr8Ut9uvHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@women_want_more YOU DONT!! You’re complaining that they play more songs that male sing than female. Well no shit. There’s more of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the opportunity to interview #afrobeat living legend Seun Kuti on @dublab for @BtsOfAllNations radio 037.  S… https://t.co/ZB56fKfQzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[And creating coterminal supplementary angles... #T3IC https://t.co/y9ESRU52dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beyrima She clearly does not really understand the issues and consequences on this file]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vladi_VillegasP @HectoRodriguez Los Chavistas en sí mismos son un error, extraña mutación que transforma potencial… https://t.co/V9tVSlMSNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC Hopefully the ether will be worn off by then. Then they can make a reasonable, healthy, responsible choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost forgot..... Go see fighting with my family.  It’s super good and really funny.   Loved the entire movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[refer to women as bitches #WaysToLoseCoolPoints https://t.co/IcMPjNFtHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside the marketplace...😍😍😍 @ Mitsuwa Marketplace https://t.co/xJ2Zqn7Ypy]]></document><document><![CDATA[not me buying this expensive ass hotel room just to not meet ariana goodbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyFerrando Aye I feel you there my brotha. We got a 40 hour guarantee with the railroad tho so this snow is low key a blessing haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Hermana 😍😊 yo pensé que no había fotos!  Qué recuerdos de cuando andaba chipilón y me cargabas para llevarme a dor… https://t.co/IAZYSoPidq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing my support for one of the best designer I know @Ikaika_designs . You don’t want to miss out. Get Ikaika in… https://t.co/oJRSgxv2xE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @chuckwoolery We can pool together enough money for her a ticket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...just wow. Apparently @WSJ has not been paying attention the last week or they would know sharing such truthfu… https://t.co/lx0dFDMZzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariellec Yo it’s hard Asian, latinx and country  Maybe it’s cause there’s mad latinx in the south and they migrate… https://t.co/hOp0V0fka7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un Cover que grabé de una de mis canciones favoritas de Mijares !! Espero les guste !!! ✌🏻✌🏻video completo:… https://t.co/AnHhRGvbBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wattswebedawgs @WayneDupreeShow @man007_b The USA is a mixture of socialism and capitalism. Anything preceded by p… https://t.co/yM9cqaOWKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genirodriguez The streamers present a choice. They do not force the public to not go to the movie theater. The lov… https://t.co/xsc21lVxhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gary4z @HockeyHangout @markscheig And even if we don’t win a cup, we most likely will still have dzingel and almos… https://t.co/mDuG2JUIDw]]></document></documents></author>