<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Let me down easy 🎶🎶🎶 ...but your love for me is strong 💔 after watching #dongiovanni - phenomenal Opera - wearing a… https://t.co/O16Vbj6SHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyCountry Coming soon ... @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ... https://t.co/0KyvZw1zN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family photo lol. This picture was so hard to take. #puggle #scottishterrier #mypups @ Ottawa, Ontario https://t.co/UMC3bSTeLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums it up...🐾❤  #lilabug #finnhenderson #bichonfrisepuppy #bichonsofinstagram #bichon @ Pell City, Ala… https://t.co/iXRlOsSZt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 @KilllerBee777 I am so sorry for the added stress on you both.This shows the country the debt we owe yo… https://t.co/8wTtNRigkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danadoggett15 And our Ts and Ss @EasternWCPS are growing from your model so much as well! Thank you for so willing… https://t.co/rIcumJn8bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want her back. The confident person that she was. Not this person that she claims to be...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethhill2829 @ConsciousD @mmcknight32 @SELearningEDU @RippleKindness @DisruptedTv @Joshua__Stamper @BarbaraGruener… https://t.co/yXB6PL3X4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoraSamurai First: oo those poses are interesting and the action is so heckin intense—  Now: I’ve only been around… https://t.co/qZvd8fceGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALSEY AND YUNGBLUD ARE DOING SOMETHING AND IDK ABOUT YOU BUT IM ALREADY CRYING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonMarduk Nice! Don't steal candy ok! You got to behave yourself! That better be bought candy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiestaMex923 Hola, me podrían complacer con el nuevo sencillo de @julionalvarez #CuandoTeAmé 🎵🎶❤ @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @GOP @RandPaul Yes they were at the border, no they were not trying to cross illegally… https://t.co/ER6Pj2PI1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delphine_frank I would like to offer my support during this difficult time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arla53 @CanadaLove2019 @iamIqraKhalid @JustinTrudeau She's a shoo in for re-election. IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooooo she could possibly be the IRS on a burner account bruh stay woke]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What’s that in your mouth” “what’s that in your mouth? Oh you’re a juuler bro.” @amandatriana_ @TheHomieBrian]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon Very sweet.... All dogs descend from wolves... my breeder cyndie would be handle this easily....]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of all our SHS HOSA students for qualifying for state. A special congratulations to our 11 students who pl… https://t.co/3Sn7N01j5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredithJoNC @PrairieWisdom @MomsDemand @shannonrwatts https://t.co/aICYrygoXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mente es lo más poderoso que tenemos. Juguemos a la mente positiva y verás que todo cambia a tu alrededor.… https://t.co/Tt4g9p57vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoecoffeeNYC Much too late in the day for me to have caffeine. But it sounds lovely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[She cracks me up #GirlGoaliesRock reesechill @ Pope Lax Field https://t.co/L6VpxolKHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @JanaMBurns to share my seven favorite books,  no reviews. Each day I will challenge some… https://t.co/AJE1WAXGhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have complained multiple times to multiple people and they do nothing. Time to step up and take stand behind your p… https://t.co/yLJOnE9OAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonPotesta as I was listening to your show yesterday I’m sorry that I didn’t know you were talking about Bob, he w… https://t.co/mH1PRDYlZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyG_415 @oscoopie @MichaelAvenatti Yes they did . Cohen explained that in order to met $130k reimbursement with… https://t.co/UVEo3kGRuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SugarRushToo  Couldn’t let the day end without sweets for my #Sweeties!  So many choices.... @ Sugar Rush Too Suga… https://t.co/HEV09vTXtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[you sure you should be calling anyone a douche bag with that profile picture, David?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful book signing! Wish my coauthor @sallyatwood was with me. @NAPDS9 @CTLatCSUN #NAPDSinATL https://t.co/NV5mHpT5g7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosBolsonaro Sr Carlos, vamos falar da reforma da previdência. Por favor,desce do palanque! O Sr já consultou s… https://t.co/t6AkJU4Bwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the time someone tried robbing the house and my car when I was home. What a fun time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacRepublicFC @villbijev @cchantzo21 Nice guys! Looking forward to Saturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[also, if and when you hurt mr  trump, youre hurting  america.  finish this wall!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revsusanrussell @Adrian_Benepe @IvankaTrump @Lawrence So she’s lying all the time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nature therapy...Winter in Sarasota! #Hike #Birds #Birdschirping #Turtles #BlueSkies #78degrees #Sarasota… https://t.co/2u5YX1wokY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought new glasses from @ModernOptical. Any bets on how long it’ll take my husband to notice?🤓 https://t.co/cQBSZ2rD9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a strong independent woman who resists the urge to say out loud, “I love this song” for every song I put on my… https://t.co/n4lGHzPGVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I got this big ass delicious caprese salad and I honestly cannot remember where tf I was and I’m heartbroken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @bubbagump324 Yes! He's very slimy and devoid of sex appeal. If she loves him, fine by me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaxAustin Yeah, the pizza and a drink.  Or maybe even the frozen yogurt...😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can isolate a strand of my cheek cell DNA @MunfordHigh https://t.co/b8GupSS49g]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how just being nice to someone can be taken so fucking far out of context]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think it’ll ever stop hurting I’ll always love you as much as the very first time we said it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoriaTHD0139 @altamarie1316 @Brad_Peebles Excellent! Welcome to the D2 Family!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar guess what I got!!! I’m so stoked! #sisterapproved https://t.co/fvDgeILJc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell Twinkle toes is idiot!  Never had to work a day in her life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eer13art @KingsMenPodcast I hope he stays spiteful, then. I'm okay with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter this #giveaway to get a FREE &lt;XXXX&gt; plus a ton of other awesome prizes! https://t.co/ZYiUzVcTXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on the DFL endorsement for Ward 4 City Council to @mitrajnelson! https://t.co/g44iPUXJPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande @TAYLAPARX Wow Liz's post are nuts. I hope she feels better soon. Damn. @ArianaGrande , on a positive… https://t.co/aQ2X9VirQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyNPH @Davidburtka Happy Valentines Day you two. Your love is a shining example of what true love looks like. Love your story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is key to have a mentoring network. Surround yourself with peer mentors and guide each other through the fox hol… https://t.co/QUCrV3nXEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week W.I. Rep. Duffy voted no along with 189 members of the House on H.R. 8-the Bipartisan Background Checks A… https://t.co/zj3GwrKscq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teamwork.  We are all about working together.  The journey is sweeter with someone supporting you, working with you… https://t.co/98NaD7yGZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sessions and my program work, are leading edge and none of which existed before I created them. And I now a very… https://t.co/U6Ly6a1pWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I’m cool enough to get a friend request from @TheEllenShow @ellentube ! 😂😂😂 #ellen ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisquiethour I truly believe that God is you’re Total Resource and will give you the Grace, Stength and Courage t… https://t.co/HodJlVdAGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit my online store ErickaBox now Bride and flower Girls hair accessories my website in my profile!#fashion… https://t.co/AKnikmvau2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also even though I doubt any of my followers need this reminder lemme take a sec to say declawing is super gross an… https://t.co/1K5bVdupwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather When the president of our nation calls someone a “rat” in gangster speak, what can we expect? Atrocious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Obviously, Dems agenda does not include the safety of Americans or America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slaytergirl @Jim_Jordan This information needs to be published far and wide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#womancrushwednesday #humpdayhotness Repost from anne_cathrine_fit . 🖤 𝐆𝐨𝐢𝐧𝐠 𝐰𝐢𝐭𝐡 𝐭𝐡𝐞 𝐜𝐡𝐨𝐢𝐜𝐞𝐬 𝐭𝐡𝐚𝐭 𝐬𝐜𝐚𝐫𝐞𝐬 𝐲𝐨𝐮 𝐭𝐡𝐞 𝐦… https://t.co/v0Vez5asUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people just repeatedly take “backhanded” compliments or accept rude comments from others w/ no push back? Wh… https://t.co/wD2UKUj9Yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a shame the way I used to think when I was younger. Thankful for growth. ✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump You are not a real person,  trump has fake accounts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MumfordAndSons for the energy and love you had for #Cleveland last night! The energy was electric! https://t.co/2XJAjJd99D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mon_Commentaire Mais elle peut penser ce qu'elle veut...y'a rien d'enfant roi là dedans...c'est son opinion, c'est tout]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinders enjoying weather centers @OldTownEagles @WSFCS_Science https://t.co/eeRba8ddfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Your job is to #PROTECTUSCitizens!  Building a border wall is an absolute necessity in accomplishing… https://t.co/f9nOoM55Y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year later and Marley still hates me when I wake him up in the morning 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s a new day!! New goal for the entire day is 80,000. Let’s double it!!! Let’s get it, let’s go! #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/1675exrUaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why not #KeanuReeves to visit #WashingtonDC? He is in Rome: why not fly to DC to meet #Tatiana. I doubt he is shy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch 22 on learning nutritional value of food. On one end you can worst case scenario a salad on the other end you… https://t.co/HMpkSyVZ6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont miss the BLOCKBUSTER NOVEL Bounty Hunter Report thriller scaresyou from the DIARIES of #GreatestDetectiveAlive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMuscutt @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @LivePD_LEOS @LivePDNation @LivePdBlueLine @Livepd_fans @LivePdFantasyLG… https://t.co/Z2sXzRpOvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmirHKhan23 Hiei is awesome! Thanks for the follow! https://t.co/toCp4FFTlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oilooooooooxxxz @MilanSilva17 Previo pago, claro. https://t.co/ztPr5R4LgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taebabylove @BTS_twt @ImThirsTaeKim Girl how’d you manage to get tickets 😢😢😢 I wasn’t so lucky this time so I’m still hoping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight, moon. Goodnight, squirrels. I’ll be better enough to chase you soon. https://t.co/AeTmz38gTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign #TrumpResign… https://t.co/ugwEMjRvJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@textualdeviance @Alyssa_Milano Would U like me to make the reservations? You’re talking to the wrong person. I wou… https://t.co/UpUvB5K3LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the plane finally. Hang on Beckett... we are on the way. Pa Rob and Ma Reen can't wait to see you!! Houston, we… https://t.co/SOxrGh404e]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Who could imagine so great a mercy? What heart could fathom such boundless grace? The God of ages stepped down fro… https://t.co/aGrShVB0bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllinKeene shares what gets and keeps kids (and adults!) engaged with learning. What a delightful general session!… https://t.co/i4eRGoqwpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 It’s not like we didn’t see that coming regardless of claims prior. 😼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us art advise you spiritually at @SPRINGBREAKshow !! 🔮🔮🔮 Playing with this year’s curatorial theme of… https://t.co/BSECeujPVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matchbox20_Fan @MatchboxTwenty How do I play along? Not into sports but I can get into this ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah so last night I watched the quinces episode of ODAAT and I literally started sobbing when her family got up to… https://t.co/pksHEoZLeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealMrNixon Oh!!!  Lol Iam in Buckeye country .😂😂. Well!!! Do all at least have the hungover look in common???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lettytrrs259 @LilaGraceRose @KamalaHarris This is simple don’t come here with your children, it’s all over the new… https://t.co/oS5was0K1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly think I’d be hellllla skinny if my body didint retain the gallon of water I consume a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @NiallOfficial I have a pair of ridiculous socks for you. Where can I send em? 🤷🏻‍♀️🍻🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @SpeakerPelosi She has learned from the best how to use the system to her advantage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl ringing me up saw my Tata pouch on my bag and she’s like are you going to their concert and at first I wa… https://t.co/nM2XfKkTED]]></document><document><![CDATA[47 fake student shootings in Cape Coral and my little sisters school is one of them. What has this country come to.… https://t.co/63DR58gcYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accessibility ramps are beautiful b/c they show that humans care about one another. Any human who finds a ramp “una… https://t.co/cwzDK0G5nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlakPhoto @instagram Check out the Nov 29 pod cast episode of #streetphotographymagazine they have a lot of great… https://t.co/eIq6HAGKCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I watch a movie with the Rock in it I’m convinced he was what he always smelled cooking because he’s constantly sweating.]]></document></documents></author>