<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe i just ate almost an entire large pizza from dominos in my car on my 10 min ride home ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mj7757 congratulations! We already knew you were a woman of distinction from time. Now a few other people know too… https://t.co/E3PgljiKmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[brandon will simultaneously roast me, while also defending me. I never knew it was possible 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitLove88 @Reelhousewife1 @Kimmer4444 @Twitter @TwitterSupport @TwitterDev @jack @ReneeLibby2 This is fucked u… https://t.co/GnLOnXzlaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we really have to wait til next Monday to see what happens?😭 #bachelor #BachelorNation #Cassie #Colton]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you're a @fitover35 member when.... you're 58 and crushing 20 pound slosh pipe step ups in the sand like a… https://t.co/SKetuijneR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbykessinger_ girl i swear. i also swear im gonna answer your fts from now on 😭😭 im trash ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddiePoppe I only took 3 years. I barely passed and only got through Spanish II.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regional champs 3 years in a row!!! Raiders win 78-57 against Joliet Central!! On to the sectional semifinals Tuesd… https://t.co/Z5TRLUhf9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It was nice to talk to her because she’s smart, and I don’t get to talk to smart people very often” - my mom, throwing shade]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been crazy weather here in @visitnc today is going to be wet 🌧 and in the 60°s. It snowed the other day! My sk… https://t.co/YVhWAJXMMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Store visit at WM 3213 with Premium Rep Rafael and AE Brian. Talking about qualifying questions and conversions!… https://t.co/55YaBhw8U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine being one of those people that sleep in contacts. omg i could never]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasminecainrock Good morning and have a great Valentine's day. https://t.co/aAso8TzvQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp He is a lying liar and you know it.  He is enriching his pockets, his family's pockets and probably your… https://t.co/yvQgjbj31s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews I cannot wait until he is taken down...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbumSenpai @WalmartInc The problem is a few of these greeters have been killed across the country by people that… https://t.co/tY4ftT1lbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunooTex Honestly, saints row 3 was fun but that shit was a downgrade and 4 was just oof]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this when i was in JRC and avoided this committee every time after 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly only have time for the things i need to do for myself at this point in my life &amp; im not sorry about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMillerShow @bobcesca_go @MalcolmNance Oh don't we just love them. Such a great team @StephMillerShow, making… https://t.co/GUWIL2RkQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight 🙌 Last chance to learn this combo at forward__space ➖6:35PM  Adults Only! 18+  Beats High Lights Low🔊… https://t.co/3KSiivZFCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s been an increase in jobs that require documentation of graduation now, so I also had to get my GED. It’s ac… https://t.co/Njc9kMurqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enthusiastic bipartisan cheers for @repdonyoung who is now the longest-serving Republican member of the House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should get a Black History Month Award for this one, Crespo.  Nice work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicman128 @KevinNoahRiley2 Had to tag u based on your tweet but so funny! LoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1MikeGulley The cheapest I remember gas was 29 cents a gallon back in 1971.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKateWolin @nickisnpdx @dahern1 @connectedhealth @jkvedar @JohnSharp @DrSherryPagoto @SBMPresident @BehavioralMed… https://t.co/z6mLzRDQM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillScott113 @coleswindell I have a ticket I may be selling.....hold off purchasing Jill !]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m here for the long haul. whether ur my best friend or my S/O. i love u. and i can’t wait to see our future. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried explaining the Jordyn, Khloé, Tristan drama to my coworker and she goes “wait..... Jordyn is Khloés bestfri… https://t.co/nOHy1Ne9BR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adulthood means recognizing that snow days mean nothing now. It’s either go to work and get paid or stay home and not get paid]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to talk about people who pave the way, @fauziamazhar2 should be at the top of your list. From the… https://t.co/QpUlMGRUuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Infectious Disease Specialist Of Northern Virginia in Fairfax, VA https://t.co/LZj9yHH82R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Kamala Harris, on the campaign trail in South Carolina. @mollyharrell @kamalaharris @ M Vista https://t.co/D8J6jTJSbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliStokols @Delavegalaw So Trump is saying that was true about no collusion (which isnt exactly what was said) but… https://t.co/EWLDL7ztYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonydepalma @trngchief11 @PressSec @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Ewwwww! No thanks, don't do drugs. But I do block stupid. Bye...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reading a good long novel is in many ways like having a long and satisfying affair.”—Stephen King, Skeleton Crew… https://t.co/rplPfepeqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best time with these cool humans last night!! Maddie is now my official BFF due to showing up in a… https://t.co/v9UBN9V3GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@litraolitran @KatyellyCabral @marquito121 KKKDKGKDKGKKKJKSKGKKDKF meu lado filha de professora de português amou essa piada]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been nominated by @nathan_brighty to  covers of 7 books that I love: No explanations or reviews, just covers.… https://t.co/18wk0b5wHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mars rover really gave us a life changing expedition , no one expected so much from the little rover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @robinlrotham @business Too bad the building still works so poorly with its surroundings. An eyesore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenFeinstein @JaredHuffman @ilike_mike @GavinNewsom  We are in a disaster! Please help declare a na… https://t.co/evoHZCMFad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RheaLitre @VanessaVanjie @GanacheSilky Baddezt but are the coolest....yea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover The Thrill Is Gone by Dee Dee Bridgewater. https://t.co/N77NPVu8rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure barrel racers never take off their make up..they just keep adding layers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHart123  I hope your day was the Best!! 😊🙌 https://t.co/4AalzXBWI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls 2nd Round Playoff Game: @Dscottcoach and the Lady Mustang Girls Basketball team taking on Manvel in Alvin.… https://t.co/DCYf5c1p2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least he gets up in 3 hours..I guess I’ll just wait until then to sleep🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @west_baltimore_ruins on Instagram   https://t.co/AaeuVDwGyw https://t.co/bWR0PV6Cp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always!   The first day of March may be a snowy one but... 🙋‍♀️ it’s my Birthday month so I don’t really care 👑 https://t.co/hp7WkQ4Mj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[its saturday night and im at home drinking beer and doing a project for class that’s not even due until next sunday :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie's so excited to see me! #dogsofig #dogsofinstagram #dog #goldenretriever #golden #goldie #goldensofinstagram… https://t.co/NfkSGcIAtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t we know it. Go Post, Go Post! @PostMalone @postybae @PostMalone_Fans @rriproarin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luc333 @Ilhan The majority of Americans do not want a wall. It's only the most racist 45 followers who still believe it's necessary.  SMH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealautoblog @VolvoCarUSA I've driven #SwedeRides since 1989: 240, 740, S80, S80, S60.  My first S80 passed the… https://t.co/q0sbwg5Jrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to say this , they all auditioned to be Solo artists to begin with.  That was their dream.  So let's just en… https://t.co/nxSMgiA85F]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were so blind that they could not recognize that in the multiplication of loaves, the New Moses was before the… https://t.co/6fRyLSdvIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grotesque gender dynamics about commodification and men feeling it is permissible to make such comments, which I co… https://t.co/wtTQDPtcaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to help my grandpa send an email is like trying to give a cat a bath... 😴🤦🏻‍♀️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassBaller @BetsyGervasi POTUS O is the total opposite of this daily crisis we have now. He liked the rain ☔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizpt2 @cordova_kaylee I mean it depends on where I go, bc If I go to my place back home, they stay on for a good… https://t.co/eXxuu1coZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another cold morning so we will have indoor entry this morning 3/5! Have students come prepared to go outside for r… https://t.co/d8VLigF96Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Aramark team! See our latest #FacilitiesMgmt job openings, including "Floor Technician - Susquehanna - MVC… https://t.co/3L2qCYE5AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever happen to the ring Barry gave Iris for Christmas during season one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting clouds yesterday late afternoon over the city.   The ice is thawing on the Chicago River. We’re also st… https://t.co/05AYaN0tR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget on the worst day of your life, God is still good. People just praise him for he Sunday days. Wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for all the powerful woman that have paved the way for a better world! #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/6iWfNF2MGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IikeRez12 that’s not how it works lol you’re supposed to have rice &amp; beans]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m capping registration for my March 11 round soon! Only a couple of slots left! Sign up or get more info here:… https://t.co/Zp4srYoptr]]></document><document><![CDATA[new glasses are giving me serial killer vibes. love that for me. https://t.co/WCKplegCYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vayesfan @renerabril @pam_brundige @goldeemxtra1 @HollieWolfen @XDaneelOlivaw @AMHotFlash @patricia_tuel… https://t.co/ldygHIozk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalpernAlex Alas, this is where the imagining comes in. How can we turn all of these reasons it can’t be done, int… https://t.co/iQaILemEpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wine_mami666 no deadass those lil chokes are the ones that cut deepest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rick Santorum Yes the American people see the difference between this lying sack of crap president and any other NORMAL president]]></document><document><![CDATA[More #sundayfunday with Chris! (@ Schermerhorn Symphony Center - @theschermerhorn in Nashville, TN)… https://t.co/2LtvuxKhmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Tuesday....612 BURGER!!!   #ThisIsWhereItWas (at @Houlihans in Fort Worth, TX) https://t.co/whAO7yyJNE https://t.co/5CXpeRTang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Hunter! 💚💚 You are such a handsome sweet boy. Angel Ella and Angel Spencer....always in our hearts a… https://t.co/FJZrGqnvXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdavis_20 That’s the funny part. We laugh at our pain lmao leave us be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJKoch @MsKenman2008 Omar shouldn't be a part of our country's governing body. Her allegiance is not to the U.… https://t.co/3BMy5HLaoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of great insight here on how networking can be a superpower of yours. ⬇️🤝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @BrittNicole1214 we’re watching the new Sam and Colby video and we were so scared we had to stop watching an… https://t.co/vPZzjxMlzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing like the aroma of freshly baked bread... especially when the fun is happening in your kitchen! My g… https://t.co/rMf48POH81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulLeeTicks @RandyResist Oh how we all needed this levity after the crud we've had to put up with from Trumpville.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My salon moved to a new spot in the West Loop and it is... money. You have to check it out🙌🏼  Drop my name for a re… https://t.co/IKfA2Hne98]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful day in Orlando, as my favorite part is spending time with the team! #enzoshideaway @ Wolfgang Puck Bar… https://t.co/Lkgd5ivhgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_manTheGreat @MissSwaffle I also have less buying power with crippling student debt and and a $20,000 hospital bill for breaking my leg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're a true #queen without autotune..#badu https://t.co/iE6er3HtGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw @KaceyMusgraves in Tennessee, and we just booked our trip to see her again in New Orleans!!!!   My heart… https://t.co/BFtDG1L9jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@p0cketfullasuns @jade_cabochon7 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse ???????]]></document><document><![CDATA[O Art Gallary of Ontario (AGO) tem mais de 90 mil obras e está entre os museus de arte mais ilustres da América do… https://t.co/zpLjw10Oo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[she’s showing me pics of her sons, my brothers’ age 😂 they are not unattractive...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch and freezing April’s food! (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/jzD2oLdxRq https://t.co/TBt4ysVLig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of all my friends. Like, one just got a major scholarship, another is becoming an ait, other are going… https://t.co/SFecZLlTyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prof suggested I work on a research project with her and go to a conference in Valencia to present I’m- 😢😢😢😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @NHOILsCARES for this gift! Currently wearing the protect oil and I’m obsessed with the scent. Can’t wait… https://t.co/ffwEalWIGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP B!tch! Moan, Groan &amp; Complain! Once the camera is off, you can go back to you same old Bigoted Selves! 🐽]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time I was on a plane, I was in my teens and I was flown out of my hometown (300+ km away) to access ment… https://t.co/KMZBAICQQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeroOnlyYou1 @el_fmas @SJofficial @Yechul4 @shfly3424 Calmada.... @siwonchoi miraaaaa]]></document></documents></author>