<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EandCPod I can’t wait hear the pod this week with what went down at #FastLane2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jawaan Taylor, Benny Snell, and Bryce Love all talking about how they’d love to be drafted by the #Jets because of Sam Darnold 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justinifcation I dont see how you do it. I passed out at 8 last night lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryonnyM @Trump454545 @spikelee should go back and read history, because apparently he has not yet!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatcha gonna do brotherrrr, when #GRITTYMANIA runs wild on youuu?!? https://t.co/qFmYGnAEuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Satans tool bag is full including the proponents of butchering unborn children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle Mr.C, you've always been electric on the screen, but your strength, resilience and power in real life i… https://t.co/o7CaeaNnXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarasikS @ToKeNasty And that’s fine lol they would be very wise to tag him. I’d be upset if I were a falcons fan a… https://t.co/dd2pwkabVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Amarillo #TX  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/fsTMASwUCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[a big fucc you to any kid that says they wanna be grown... I would do anything to be a kid again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another awesome atmosphere at @MoheganSun Arena today.   In light of tough news this past week, the @NEBlackWolves… https://t.co/lSo64mf7Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just see a toilet paper commercial with a gay couple focused on getting clean “down there”?! 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah we’ve seen worse blowouts this year but that doesn’t really make me feel any better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep. Too excited for Foeder for Thought and all the talks I get to host with @GreenBenchBrew on Friday. And… https://t.co/wOVbKwDJFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I was lucky enough to get these two in the same frame🤣📷 @carsonweathers @brennenweathers… https://t.co/9PntQHhfU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSquawk I awoke to all of this. It was amazing to watch. Glad to see that you are pushing Andrew in a good direction. #mentorship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachary1978 @BarkMSmeagol LMAO He just finished writing a book about Tesla. Why do you think he has been so quiet… https://t.co/1lO6v5bzkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alineación 🦅 1️⃣. Agustín Marchesín 3️⃣. Jorge Sánchez 1️⃣8️⃣. Bruno Valdéz 1️⃣9️⃣. Emanuel Aguilera 2️⃣2️⃣. Paul A… https://t.co/prcpF6w8dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4thnGoldPodcast He also has 500K/year in per game roster bonus and 100K/year in workout bonus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucid Dreams | emkaytownsend. . . . #portraitphotography #photography #garden #flowers #model #la #ca #portrait… https://t.co/1XjfTJhWOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graddy Oof. I'm sorry; that seems hard! I found a good home in the ELCA for a while, though, and I hope you do too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr So, when your dad is stoking as much outrage and hate that he can is that rehearsed or is just winging it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for #DOAS #ADOS #AmericanDOS to decide who has delivered. @realDonaldTrump delivers jobs, @DNC @TheDemocrats d… https://t.co/gY22tctpSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveUSC 7... Miracle Makers   A los de Wanat Haz recordar, Con rayo, Con trueno; Y luminante paz  El gran milagro… https://t.co/MdN7gUhtDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prof_gabriele This is official policy at a local community college. I find it 100% contrary to the mission of high… https://t.co/1L9FEv7zVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseMonkey1 @DaleMurphy3 @RidinRosters @Phillies This lineup is better than all of those lineups lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Burns looked real good on his 40. Put on weight and still fast, things looking better and better for him #NFLCombine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys My Perspective will CHANGE, With a CERVICAL Collar! Back to Can Do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHookfox10 @garway95 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Do 48% of American voters not realize what high crimes and T… https://t.co/VvV0u2ZVYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight saving time is the practice of advancing clocks 1 hour during summer months so that evening daylight lasts longer,and it SUCKS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marty Funkouser: “Okay. I got some great news. Guess where the Funkman is going for three weeks. LONDON!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What @budlight has taught me is that corn syrup makes beer better @MillerLite !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might have to hit up @johnwessling’s show this weekend. One of my favorite friends from radio, and a damn funny MFer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashlee2217 Well when I got my puppy she didn’t like the cage as well. So I took a blanket and laid on it to put my… https://t.co/xI28PsJgk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So charming, so home alone, the one that I know the most 🛫♥️ @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/KaFq7vhktc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean to tell me...that another rapper.... just got arrested? I’m utterly shocked. This stuff never happens. Mod… https://t.co/G4QlHQfg6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roexcy1 @nataliauci16 @Ismaray151 @dellylien1 @dicson_r_2000 @rislaidy @AAB_Cuba @alicia_senra @DiazCanelB… https://t.co/NcKd3Q2gBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattybags2313 No shit I was asking so I can literally give my cat away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong Start is good... #everyonesacritic #realtor #kellerwilliams #kwstudiocity #openhouse #awsomeplaylist… https://t.co/VJZK3TKGCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoSwells @ajponderbws @NerdDadZech @ewarren I will thanks. Everyone pays a form of wealth tax. It’s called income… https://t.co/ffANH5QVat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now 5/6 on the day! Playing both up &amp; down. See the trades below. Lots of opportunities today! @ChazAltitude… https://t.co/GzIN51HWt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmrecker @charliekirk11 Our nation never has known the truth of God.  Particular individuals within our nation hav… https://t.co/Ych1vftLyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preview of Boys D3 North Bracket and predictions: . Final Four: St. Mary’s, Minuteman, Watertown, Snowden . Champio… https://t.co/y6jemiwvPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RalphCindrich That’s very sad especially since players like him did not make a lot of money at the game was a lot… https://t.co/nOoZF9ypLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwilk I don’t view this as black and white. The idea is to create flexibility and options with a lot of people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was simply amazing! To Inspire! To Empower! https://t.co/0EXmtLWpZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft I better not get a no-show fee on my ride when the driver doesn’t even show up. Called and texted driver no response!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwe #WWEFastLane2019 @reymysterio loses the #USChampionship match without the ref picking up and dropping his arm… https://t.co/3Oxu64qZ6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want things to clear up and to feel in control and confident of what me doing is right, that I am doing what… https://t.co/a3W7S3XW6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it illegal to offer $5000 to whomever finds the guy that did this, duct tapes them up and throws them into a fre… https://t.co/0TDYLhvg6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#timbuckley #blueafternoon #vinyl @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/ZmWCjG2FyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should stop whatever it is you're doing right now and go see @captainmarvel. That's all. #CaptainMarvel… https://t.co/SKAuLMSy78]]></document><document><![CDATA[me having sex with other psych majors (especially white men cuz they’re the ones in GE and TA positions) is dangero… https://t.co/CtAT9J7D7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desgnatedsrvivr @LailaMickelwait Yup, just like I thought. This person isn't interested in learning anything. https://t.co/uhfOjKr9iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought Aang was gonna merk Ozai too, this fight was everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/1w1I1kffu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have learned two very important things as a psychotherapist: there is accurate insight and there is skillful deli… https://t.co/9D5r2XbBA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christinaajolly I've rarely seen libraries mentioned in the books I read]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgers_randi ...instead of going crazy with the kid at customer service - I simply explained to him how much my s… https://t.co/y0b4BbaYRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emlouhoo People 15-20 miles north of us got a bunch. I’m thankful (really only in this case) for urban heat bubbles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartosSophia Hi Sophia, we are conducting a free 45-minute martial arts workout tmrw @ 12PM at 285 Green Street i… https://t.co/DkUZ2j2Xzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReinaHelton That’s great to hear! I can’t either should be some amazing events @CrimeConHQ this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunbag3 @JoSan6772 @NanoQUANTech @JusticarStef @bioware I was able to solo "normal" without any issue but "hard" w… https://t.co/GFhCKAT9LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbcmundo Educación y obediencia sentido común y mucho respeto eso lo hizo una potencia tan desarrollado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoingMedieval The Spectator likes to consider itself a "centrist" publication. I suppose that misogyny must be a c… https://t.co/76g6WDtrLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyDoyle47 MBV. I’m gonna take an unopopular stance and say the rest are overrated (but that doesn’t mean they’re bad).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyffmariedadiva @myperfectright @leonematt74 @Poniesexposed @darlngal @PurpleFlowrz71 @DaChampjd @NY5639 @NYG4248… https://t.co/buU2YpihD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breadsx @YESEEGHOSTS Also said it’s not a listening party... so what’s everyone sitting for?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Herrera’s Production presents @anthonybachata music video - Aun Sigues Aqui check it out and follow him #film… https://t.co/OU6IQ1b6Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGigger I would rather we empower students to become engaged and create agency in their own education. Active, not passive. #longgame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishaashley @HVCoombs @GwyneddGarage What kind of garage door is that? Does it slide?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bay_staatsoper [image of the happy couple from https://t.co/nySM2VaAQm]]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bc there is no way in hell that @IlhanMN would ever be a white supremacist unlike someone else we know]]></document><document><![CDATA[These brain geniuses think the roads will just magically fix themselves. This is conservatism in a nutshell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheamusmurphy then of course there was this,  https://t.co/MSzxtsbDyz  JWR: “Whether someone is recommended or hig… https://t.co/fxgJPsVe6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrancewithMe @kravitz_raymond @BerzerkerBuilds @YouTube Always delivers like a morning cup of coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoDucks42_Mick @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCAR_Xfinity @lappedtrafficpc @NASCARBTW I also missed it but why did Bell have to start at the back ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nichole_sara What kind? Does it run good??? How many miles is on it? There I go again being a mom, lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cz_binance @bskousen @binance Can I meet you too please? That response was legendary. A man must admit when he was owned online. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport A man without honor, or a sense of duty, is not fit to be POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAYLIGHT SAVINGS REMINDER  SPRING FORWARD! @ Warren County, Ohio https://t.co/qOUL5iACU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mojofearless @realDonaldTrump Well, there's impeachment to look forward to for that pendejo's "accomplishments."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Michael Cohen Was Pitching A Book PRAISING Trump…Right Before The FBI Raided His Office https://t.co/Hp4HP2BYCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minakimes To be able to pay other players too? Lol they restructured his deal multiple times to give him even more guaranteed money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's amazing how the right soundtrack can transform your day. Music is escapism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait to see that dishonorable discharge you about to be hit with 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JettGoldsmith @realDonaldTrump Starr report in 1998 alleged 11 grounds for impeachment.  The only difference now i… https://t.co/VjgPbzy6ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A10Talk Jeepers! Davidson losing to UMass was like THE DEATH KNELL on their at-large chance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner, 21, overtakes Mark Zuckerberg to become the world’s youngest self-made billionaire of all time. https://t.co/VcEJCDVWaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump Misadministration launches its #DomesticGagOrder imposed on Planned Parenthood and other clinics who perf… https://t.co/EcVhI8eDiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidgura That would be Jesse Watters. (IF HE EVER READ A POEM IN HIS LIFE...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAThurstonDC @5t3ph_54X @BELBaltimore They at least lied to me. They promised Remington an open community forum to… https://t.co/ZTtH9kxDeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takes a healthy amount of courage, especially as a somewhat public figure, to out oneself. Gained a lot of respect… https://t.co/qKJjbAULx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyD @fubarcito @YouTube @YTCreators And yet YouTube has also shutdown innocent channels like Mumkey Jones demo… https://t.co/XPlCweDZZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así seas una obra maestra de la fealdad, tu estilo de vestir te hará sobresalir del lote, encuéntralo y verás como… https://t.co/58Iqz3b9xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarthaMad99 @realDonaldTrump He is not a Christian! Stop pretending he is! Jesus would have nothing to do with tru… https://t.co/2SyHlor62E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Match the intensity @Chargers! You know who to get! Derwin Needs his partner in crime😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you're doing well @PureSportsTX I don't expect you to remember but I won't ever forget fixing you up with th… https://t.co/J2qLVzEpzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsKiaraMarie Let’s talk about all the good things and the bad things that maybe...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emteehall It takes me so long to get out of the house now that I have to kiss every new before leaving]]></document></documents></author>