<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@r9miles @ReadingShanahan Trying to truly work and live within a growth model is hard if we don't all share the vis… https://t.co/DiLLDorLjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EscapingNY#fireescapes#oldbuilding#Architecture#beauty#lifestyle#dwelling#NYC @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/xE90Ls5ewA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s baaaaack! There will be an intro class on Monda, March 25th and the series starts April 1st! Go to… https://t.co/1BOTvpoUpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Far too often as Christians, we’re persecuted for the wrong reasons. https://t.co/GCMHn3Nbob via @GregLaurie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#albannach #nickwatson #drummer #pipesanddrums #bareknucklepipesanddrumes #CelticFamJam #SertomaYouthRanch #celtic… https://t.co/6CjqfY0OfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Huge Thank You To This Amazing Publicist And BFF @sashastoltz For A Fabulous Night....3 Parties In One Night Feel… https://t.co/OlFMb46fGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes your circle has to decrease in size in order to increase in value!  If you’re not making the progress you… https://t.co/iQ82WUjbWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landed in Vegas, ready for a great weekend.  #roychoiismybestfriend @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/nZadpJE5VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staff affinity spaces can be a space to provide support and reflection to process through experiences that maybe ou… https://t.co/4XVrntbvZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BecketAdams The inventor first tried jello filled beds? https://t.co/LMGMuuXQc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine Gift to my Husband: about to go up in this beautiful WWII baby! #BUCKETLIST #enjoylife #lovemyhubby ❤️ https://t.co/Bol9crCEnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[... AND HERE COME THE NUTS SHAKING LOOSE FROM THE TREE JUST IN TIME FOR 2020!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yess!!! They want you to report it and they tell you are you in danger ... yes bitch!!!! This a warning and you nee… https://t.co/BxM7W3ghls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suziday123 @RoadtripC @RoarLoudTravel @always5star @FoodTravelist @GalsWander @MyVirtualVaca @RickGriffin… https://t.co/xrahfoGVrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m glad that @peta took a break from killing adoptable animals and people’s healthy pets to be disrespectful… https://t.co/XWtvJYAzWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 23rd birthday bro ❄️ ethanrussel  #happybirthday #dayones #youngflash #worryfree #nojumper #worldstarhiphop… https://t.co/tlfzHjBEnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sullyrecruiter @TheAthleticLA That’s what I thought originally too, but after further research it appears to be on… https://t.co/A88ru3jzq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t practice your religion all year but participate in lent, you’re living a whole ass lie. Sorry not sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery Don’t watch this unless you pray first. You will be forever haunted https://t.co/RSDIpBQ32A]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a cute General Store! This drive home has been a mini vacation! And yes, I did buy @julianhardcider I couldn’t… https://t.co/0PN906UC1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! #big12wr #okstate #finals #oklahomastatewrestling @ BOK Center https://t.co/c2ebOKpv8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my newest #listing 137 Clarence Ave #SevernaPark #MD  https://t.co/VP5SM8T34u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Makerspace @msulibraries has equipment for checkout https://t.co/U2bpBIv421 https://t.co/LfJ4PD40WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsCWirtz Congrats to Team ♾. I was also amazed by the behavior of the students in the audience. They were so well… https://t.co/SuApoDPQbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of Birthdays my sweet fister bester baby! Lord knows how much I miss you and our belly laughs!!!!! I hope… https://t.co/oCFyvMwMtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIY photo bookmark craft. The perfect gift for readers. Add some hearts and make it a... #mirth #tee-hee #smirk… https://t.co/TDtHMjKhsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[As my good friends from Cross Canadian Ragweed would say...  I’m sick and tired of being sick and tired. 😢  Come on… https://t.co/MKTfRO4XmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[⏰Time for a WIFEcast!💍 We are EXCITED to bring you our 1st LIVE EVENT for 2019! Our WIFEcast will be on Monday 2/25… https://t.co/zWjGR1TH4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like I found the perfect opponent for my Impact Wrestling debut match. Find out who it is tomorrow night in V… https://t.co/WcnagCtYMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @FoxNews @JohnCornyn @SenTedCruz @senatemajldr @GOPLeader Trump doesn't need Cohen the fixer a… https://t.co/tATopLNA6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great site that documents different types of flows at different companies on different platforms! https://t.co/fzfLKnXW3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the fact that Nobuhiro Watsuki is a pedo so fucking much for God's sake. Rurouni Kenshin is such an elite ma… https://t.co/Y6OTYM4xbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @GeorgiaStateU @GSUArtSci Applied Linguistics PhD students are the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all i swear i met the man i’m meant marry at this service event. i’m visiting every amy’s ice cream so i can find him and shoot my shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad said have you ever felt/hear your heart when your sleeping I said not when I’m sleeping but when I’m high 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kathy_Valentine I replaced bread with romaine lettuce and yes it made a HUGE difference. Keep up the good work Kathy!!!👏👏👂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhateverIguess_ @angee_nero @YUNGBANS Lmfaoooooo this is still a thing ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCGoodGirls @maebirdwing @unfoRETTAble @chrstinahendrk Just got my husband all caught up on Good Girls Season 2 E… https://t.co/kvmmsapLsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[And whatever you do, in word or deed, do everything in the name of JESUS, giving thanks to GOD the Father through Him. - Colossians 3:17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que triste caso de este reportero  , que quiso entrar a la conferencia Presidencial y no lo dejaron!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @DonaldJTrumpJr ‘Loser teachers’. As if teaching isn’t hard enough without this ass hat spewing his p… https://t.co/CP9oznyREJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@theskimm - SO disappointed that you say we should give an extra shout out to celebrate a woman getting engaged. I… https://t.co/45Hv0i66F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol How about bringing children into the world, and standing back watching starvation, and other social il… https://t.co/dITjccMJ8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Not a chance. His stock just went up. When you are in trouble with everyone in DC trump loves you more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He got a permit 🐸☕️ Be a shame if someone were to shut it down “hint hint”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@99JAMZ   Show'em how we do in the MIAMIIIIIIIII AKA 3055555555 BABYYYYY @DJEntice 🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾💋💋💋💋💋💋💋💋🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶 iamcar… https://t.co/9KF3WlWrzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was a fun night! Who knew I liked Bob Seger so much?! 🎉 @ The Forum (Inglewood, California) https://t.co/RFN95mcI6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations and thank you @JamesPray for the inspiration. You must have been born for this because you have a g… https://t.co/PGPeatp42q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before #derailing from #workingout #haulingass #5miles a day #powerwalking #urticarialife #urticarialvasculitis… https://t.co/orEIE0cktn]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 tattoos, 2 small pieces and 2 big ones. Gosh I want more and more and more😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston Oh, it was vintage? That explains a lot. About the jacket, I mean. Nothing wrong with having a little retail therapy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyWolfeMusic If you have an oriental grocery store in their part of town, most of them sell aluminum straws. I g… https://t.co/KLqqn53R66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone else ever wondered why if “Grande” means “Big” in Spanish why Starbucks thinks that means a medium?]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were so sweet 😭❤️ love them so much 💕✖️ @SamGolbach @ColbyBrock @SamandColby @PlaylistLive https://t.co/lmyKObsYZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h0lamely Salmo de súplica y confianza  Oración de David.  86 Inclina, oh Señor, tu oído yrespóndeme, porque estoy… https://t.co/WdpyaVI5B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Love you all. Just one correction, Joy. Clinton was born in Hope, Arkansas. Hot Springs his hometown not Little Rock. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tenshi_no_Akuro @baneschmico I wish they would support in giving the fandom more seasons that would be better… https://t.co/fiIyIms9KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[no person is illegal unemployment is at all time low we need more workers and the more we have working the more that pays into SS @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BEST time for new beginnings is NOW. 🌷🌼🌺🌻🍃  . DON'T stay where you're tolerated, MOVE forward to where you're C… https://t.co/ABflEzQtsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsonlflores pitch perfect phrase: when psychology columbused anthropology!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To succeed in life, you need three things: a wishbone, a backbone, and a funnybone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a 5 min study break in pharmacy school is equivalent to missing 2 weeks of school in undergrad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara @60Minutes @AnneMilgram I believe McCabe. Particularly saying Trump said he believed Putin over US In… https://t.co/t1CnB7dWyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of Happy Birthdays to my best friend!!! 😍 I know this year will be fun-filled, joyful, and prosperous for… https://t.co/i2N59RXg9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my computer died at 52% today and I lost an essay that I didn’t save that’s due on Tuesday and a half-written co… https://t.co/xqMhEbofQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am beyond grateful I was given an amazing opportunity I have now before settling for Corporate America. Lord know… https://t.co/r1Oxj58Srd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Wow, just when you think Don Jr. can’t say anything dumber, he does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MUNI Bus Stop - 30th &amp; Mission in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/BzXvmut3Cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahmCanison @toriisu @Arkeus88 I'm sorry, but I'm just not a monkey person. I didn't like Chimchar either when Po… https://t.co/MgnqhQPubv]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I do on the weekends?? Yard work! Today was the cutting down of the tall grasses before spring! #hardwork… https://t.co/yvWYgVvOIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My apple storage subscription for .99¢ got declined bc I only have .12¢ on my card]]></document><document><![CDATA[Televisa Draws Criticism for "Brownface" Parody of 'Roma' Star Yalitza Aparicio https://t.co/LgyS37Wq6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last person to join the Panel was the Dean of the University where the Conference was hosted.   She walks in an… https://t.co/0G18uaWWEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristina_CP24 loll first time like his brother did not often show for question when he was Mayor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF 13.1 aka mud run. Muddy as hell. Most fun race ever. It took a bath and a shower to get all the mud off! https://t.co/Bh6F5a58JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter the time - this l’il guy is always waiting!   🐾 🐾 🐾 #dogsofinstagram #boo #dogsoftoronto… https://t.co/KuXibi8QK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackConnie @ClockworkHamma @Peeperpea29 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @karenslinn43 @MyEngland2016 @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/8criWR4Zyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LelandOrser #BerlinStation #WhiteTShirtGang he did what you couldn't do you bastard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumps not given nothing take away from America people’s but this boo vote for no loved for you either]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got to set up a CHARCUTERIE board at work tonight I've officially peaked]]></document><document><![CDATA[▷ 04.03.2019 †  Be Free ; Be HAPPY  #makmakselfies @ Golden Gate Bridge https://t.co/QNyH8ycLRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉 CONGRATS to my crew for completing the longest run of the season with laroadrunners! We ran 21 miles this morning… https://t.co/EA61duXC0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Trump_Train @Carol1238806 Your full of BS... Where do you get these conspiracy theories.  Your an good example… https://t.co/RnoGx7ZzpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it’s not like I was expecting the rest of the season to live up to the last few episodes anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "ENGAGEMENT SPECIALIST - PART TIME" at CROSSMARK, then look for people… https://t.co/ovPUqVdeOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all positive...getting ready to get on Twitter and congratulate Lebron....and this the first thing that I saw..… https://t.co/gouFyPIc7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero que ya estén vendiendo apaleados en Hpo porque llegaré directo por uno]]></document><document><![CDATA[I began my day teaching women they can do anything. I ended my day watching captainmarvelofficial save the world. G… https://t.co/VthLcjaJAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story needs a voice. Something serious going on that many of us do not realize!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Qantas Will Remove 100 Million Single-Use #Plastic Items From #Flights by 2020 https://t.co/A64CenCBpU… https://t.co/UQAYaVo54f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBonner_ I use to facilitate a classroom management session for new teachers in which I modeled how greeting… https://t.co/cqA1sa5F9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[The brain tumor was unexpected and is rapidly growing. Symptoms appeared a week after graduation, taking her from b… https://t.co/1LfuoqQO8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[when @pauljasonklein said “am i starting to hate california, why am i in la?” i really felt that except about dtla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @Jesus_Luvs_Us @ClockworkHamma @MyEngland2016 @Iluvinspireu @Jilliemary @ann4252 @Peeperpea29… https://t.co/CbiUbXKjuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave Follow him with @kathygriffin and @Alyssa_Milano I would love to have a suit on them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also anyone who attends community college for free has to work for her double the amount of time they were in schoo… https://t.co/N6EhkfaRXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shovelled our driveway and our neighbours.  Just because 🤗 https://t.co/92EPYO35Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seantimejumpa @bassnectar @peekaboobeats HIS LITTLE DANCE LOOK AT HIM HES ADORABLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySinatra @Shareblue Nancy, please read my pinned tweet. Last month, Joel Sucher wrote our story! Joel started… https://t.co/vNMzd1iiiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nouran_i96 @ShawnMendes Oh I didn’t realize! I see you girl, having my back👯‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>