<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ISMNESS @amylovesnkotb @JeffreyGuterman @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids FAKE BOOBS!! are the enemy of the people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura Niles #hysterics #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #losangeles #marvista @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/CHqlQGyEF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys will do a French tuck and cuff their jeans and act like they're a fashion ICON! It's me, I'm guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notittryagain But it can make a difference in people’s lives in ways that you may never see. It’s a pretty kickass… https://t.co/hO328S5jCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand up, be counted for what you believe in. These are only some of the faces of the Montgomery bus boycott. Integ… https://t.co/Jt0ptQH1ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was tagged by @CaitlynSaxton to post my favorite books for the next 7 days, adding a friend each. This book inspi… https://t.co/2sRORQayTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aria_Enterprise Hi, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we w… https://t.co/N10Ldw4Aci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Reminiscent of Bill Clinton’s statement, “it depends on what the meaning of IS, is...”!  These politician… https://t.co/K7ccTisXmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most common phase the ppl use on twitter to strain away from being dragged by the barbs is “Im a fan too” No bi… https://t.co/UiwvCcfFQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember sitting like 2 feet away from the tv S H A K I N G man this fight scene was craaazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw The Chills last night in Jersey City. Thanks to all it was a great show. Took me home for an evening. https://t.co/1ukkACpsOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I see meteorologists talking about #WinterStormTaylor hitting the Midwest and New England this weekend.... 👀😏 https://t.co/IdXSRfqUhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a stacked fight card!!! 🥊🏆🥋#LightsOut #MMA #CROSSvsKUPPE #DeltaPlex @ The DeltaPlex Arena https://t.co/pX7UB3h8aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soda_hunter @FullyPoseable @HOVAAA @feedme_tacobell @ppwpodcast @MJGIV79 @FigFreakJLC @FScopers @RingSkirts You sa… https://t.co/fJf8wscola]]></document><document><![CDATA[still over the moon for this one. love you @ItsRamiMalek 💘 https://t.co/Tx6HSAnXPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was never interested in putting my whole life on this shit 🤷‍♂️ such a distraction. Unless you making money from it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding panel today @AmericanLegion Washington Conference, discussing Military Community employment and educati… https://t.co/1iY5uYqmPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Arkansas is literally the worst state in the nation for renters, and about a million Arkansans rent their homes.… https://t.co/Jyo3Kqrgda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haley_ross_ a couple of dribbles and a layup (I believe Julia Mazanec got it to her - Ms. Mazanec is balling - I h… https://t.co/PUued9PH4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatSaysKill @___jaimie recent trend to do yoga in essentially a large pen with baby/miniature farm animals like go… https://t.co/UkQeTQtpva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaRoyal1 Well walmart they fired me because of a cash shortage on the register but didnt show me proof. And amazo… https://t.co/HGrkOpBLVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it’s 7 days later! I cracked her open and after a little skimming off the top, I removed the Masontop Pickle P… https://t.co/YPDNAtnTp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiahthomas Looking forward to see you “live” for the first time on Tuesday vs. @okcthunder. Go @nuggets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have faith that his words will come back to bite him in the ass. What a miserable despicable old man tRump is. 😠😠… https://t.co/cxoDlMkKim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobRathbunTV True and that seems to be happening more these days. I feel like that’s bad for the game, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @IlhanMN  maybe someone like Soro helped and a corrupt election system]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the entire IAVM Region 7 team and the entire @SDConventionCtr staff on a stellar conference! Tha… https://t.co/NnNIs6Fv4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hootsuite_Help I expect a refund for all the time I have paid for but not been able to access our firm account. No… https://t.co/ZG28MMiK6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_doomsdaygal @knowlesfen Same. As a parent, it saddens me to. Her father needs to get the gas chamber.. don't even… https://t.co/ht0kZyGhRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly @davereaboi Recalling yarn about William Shatner in Oz, probed about marrying rumoured fling, busty A… https://t.co/sEnZVPbZiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not afraid to express how I feel... I think it’s nice considering most people stay quiet because they are scared of what others think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senrobportman Did you discuss children still being kept in cages at the border?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathleenVets @jameco01 @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls @TheFive @RealJamesWoods I use too lived in Palm springs.… https://t.co/0N4cel7wNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianBaseball stays hot - adds three more on RBI single with two outs by @LazerMazur19 and @baldubra delivers big… https://t.co/Xr3JDLn9w4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrewrosch @JHeyMcK @ClifBar @KINDSnacks @profgalloway Speaking of @profgalloway, are you listening to his podcas… https://t.co/LyIoQ6ZWa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Hart to Hart again. I’m still thinking it might not be a very good show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired of good music going unorganized. If anyone cares help me get this song where needs to be!! Beautiful T… https://t.co/8v4dXmXOzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fin de semana en la cola de caballo los astros me favorecieron con el caloron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigMcLrgHuge @elisecterry @bkerogers @sarahmquinlan https://t.co/drYHfc6okb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCARRATL It’s just one of those days .. O’Neil knows #21days    https://t.co/wCU4OSmsvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Mullaney13 I definitely worried out of the gate, but he's made huge strides.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 24 Hour Fitness Super Sports in Walnut, CA https://t.co/Df63wHFEt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW! Join us LIVE! Camera work: @baylee_harveyy https://t.co/z5cdi2dUJC https://t.co/EwQHvns8Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, and most policy people won't say this openly, the US is due for a quick intervention. It's been a minute sinc… https://t.co/5mnqhcFObF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀CLASS B1 FINAL | #1 @BHSScores vs #2 Midlakes - @SecVGBasketball   Batavia 32 Midlakes 24 | HALFTIME  •Stefaniak w… https://t.co/v8hJY0Swvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT: Photos of students  wearing black face are showing up across the country in college year books, including… https://t.co/fc4AQMTtv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m reserving judgement until I hear a third bop. #CarlyRaeJepsen https://t.co/LXzb1AZ3Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should probably sign up for a steeplechase this spring with all of the #kcmo snowdrifts I've had to hurdle this week #runchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I LOVED IT when you asked this one guy: “are you a federal agent?” Him: “Yes, your honor.” Judge Judy: “Get y… https://t.co/iNEJNi149P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @IvankaTrump My code response:  #🇺🇸Values .NE. #TrumpValues]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just get a quick set of quotes like they suggest. Then you'll know if it makes sense financially.… https://t.co/3mdNiOnlz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you don’t have a clock in your room or a watch on your arm...staying up til 4am working on your passion just k… https://t.co/SLGrAoC3IP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Fredo.... “worst judgement in the world” from your own Dad... How big of a moron must that make you… https://t.co/1q5lLzbgkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse We have over 1.7 million illegals immigrants just here in Texas Chicago has 1.5 million just go around… https://t.co/MdiFqJCGF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always say, thank you! It’s the small things that make a HUGE impact. 😊@Hyken #DallasHospitality https://t.co/bT3thjJnqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carltonreid Rocks no longer available as cities pass Cain &amp; Abel laws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here in Albany at @NYSchoolSupts. Love seeing one of our Golden Eagles in action as AJ Vita performs with the All S… https://t.co/IXOhPx2AVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a good day. Because it’s the day Georgia is the day she rode space mountain for the first time ever!… https://t.co/fjBIwTOGDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what @dogfishbeer calls desert.  #smores @ Dogfish Head Brewpub https://t.co/nTYQCnpn4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredibly excited to be one of the two slates involved in the runoff! We’ve fought hard to this point, and we will… https://t.co/ykAv1XFFqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Marlette #MI  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/GWJpYGmzjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing at poly freshman year omg the grass was so horrible let’s see what they do 💪🏽💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHN_AdamWodon What I saw there wasn’t a hockey play. But hey, by today’s rules Maine and Denver would be headed to OT in 2004.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherylReeder @funder @debilu2 Obvious, after Trump cautioned all of us to use eye protection to view lunar eclipses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinHopscotch @grovesprof Can’t use Wikipedia as a reference in a Groves’ class 😎.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKUM_Migs @SKUMGaming I’m down! After I do battlefront tomorrow we can bang!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s lost on everyone at the PGA is that being able to play quickly involves making good fast decisions. It shoul… https://t.co/GmyD9fi0Nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp Amazon.  They delivered one of two packages.    Left one on front porch.   It’s not like we are not in… https://t.co/FWnpYO1Iys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods So, the guns were the problem then?  Not mental health, a woman that was trapped in a marriage, a w… https://t.co/V5z7HcQlug]]></document><document><![CDATA[values of the rich old white Republicans are becoming known, and America will reject them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your body goals should probably be in the same height category at least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three segments, massive amount of toxins after 448 am, extremely toxic after 1202 pm https://t.co/fSrZxl0PDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Fills Ranks With Antisemites Tied to Jew-Hating Scandal https://t.co/9HKRWsraui via @pamelageller]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitch at nite, March 7th, don’t miss it #innovation @TechHUBjuarez https://t.co/zvmoXmmwKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeucesWild9 Depends on what you are doing and when you are there.  It only gets crowded on weekends.  Vultures rou… https://t.co/UmtLGRKRBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyRhodes  @TheBrandiRhodes @MattJackson13  @NickJacksonYB @theAdamPage  @IAmJericho  @AEWrestling Just saying, J… https://t.co/WLINT2sv43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoSera1 I’ve signed up with 3 different emails. Over a week ago. Only got the welcome email. Buddy of mine si… https://t.co/sF926UmA0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Julie! @ Shuckers Oyster House https://t.co/HeRN2WFHQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmore_Social hey guys, the orioles are hosting tryouts for ball staff today! https://t.co/oondAr7u8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_simms31 Hell yeah you just want to get them back for wins so you run best of three. Then you end up losing a shit ton 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ganobleberries @TurfSpartanLord @_BigMatt @andrewmuntz @rtdemayturf @BPolimer @JamieMehringer @gndkpr… https://t.co/RuRQiPIrQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larry_levitt @ACPinternists There are a lot of issues and concerns that will have to be addressed: cost controls,… https://t.co/GH2PQayyLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[sissy_764 is stoked for Daytona SX and in love with her new deano_merch @deanwilson15 hoodie! Who else is ready for… https://t.co/YYXNuq4Xdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyMacSparty @gshep1970 Way, way, way too early to make that assumption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THECatRussell What an honor and pleasure it is for Crisis Chronicles Press and I to have the opportunity to work with you, Cat! 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serving up fresh pan-seared salmon today with a fresh salad! Spring is right around the corner, and so is Spring Br… https://t.co/hMuMeJJhU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sunset view of the mountains @ Temecula, California https://t.co/UPPEPN8KJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuspendedTommy A lot of people must agree with her that its a disability ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when you leave a conference like #ACETHA19 with tools you can use. @texashospitals debuted… https://t.co/GSh1AAUeT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xGramps701x @RyanPoptart That MXPX album is the best thing they’ve ever done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan And what party was found to have a had a rigged election Oh ya the REPUBLICANS in North Carolina? Ur an… https://t.co/jWi9ITIyzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @LoveBling6 The left are so out of touch with reality its sicking!Trump being the GREATEST President… https://t.co/4VOCEDOq9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to #Garrett #KY #Appalachia #photos #architecture #history @ Garrett, Kentucky https://t.co/aLi4W9lBib]]></document><document><![CDATA[No @NickTahouHots garbage plate? Disappointed in this shoddy reporting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsLandvick118 @PeterSokolowski @skrashen @LydiaStack @Bilingual118 Can’t wait to see what excites you the most!!… https://t.co/bsgZCW4d7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudiMantere @Jim_Jordan Shit may as well switch back to Cohen, Alonso is going to get skinned by Son]]></document><document><![CDATA[46° here. 76° in Miami. Six years ago I lived in Florida. Why did I ever leave? https://t.co/syl43COz1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming back to my line soon! #March #PlayingCards #Magic https://t.co/FaLwSwwgfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera &amp; it’s going to make it increasingly popular as well...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiz: “Tagging some rollerboards” is A) a skating term; B) airline slang for checking baggage.]]></document></documents></author>