<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Eathbound420 @tetsuki @canadiandaws83 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4… https://t.co/TvPpF8fcvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mustaine3651 @JoeGiglioSports @ryanhoward put the Phillies on his back down the stretch in ‘08. CARRIED this team… https://t.co/RktVRtv5o2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay for sending her that message. Only to recieve an answer when I'm dead asleep. 😂 #workingprogress]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t believe any president should declare an “emergency” because Congress didn’t do as he asked, regardless if I… https://t.co/KyTKh7yzPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL @sunrisemvmt So let’s agree to disagree https://t.co/MkqDt9E32v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to krank it up one time 🤣🤣looking rusty but Tampa what up?!🔥🕺🏿🕺🏿🕺🏿 #AKT813 @ Tampa, Florida https://t.co/TYldRWHfRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched another 🔥🔥🔥🔥 episode of #TheShopHBO @KingJames @mavcarter @iamjamiefoxx @2chainz @MeekMill @AntDavis23… https://t.co/Jig8KGa1qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karl Lagerfield was not a fat shamer  The only thing he ever said was in response to people hating on the size of m… https://t.co/crFrK6E6IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number of scams calling me daily is out of control. I have a guy calling himself Leonard Skinnard calling me mu… https://t.co/1Q9Lzlyr9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I played ultimate frisbee at Culver City high school tonight and I’m fascinated by this tower structure behind the… https://t.co/IZrFIGCApM]]></document><document><![CDATA[442.450MHz https://t.co/zPl92Udizi DMR TAC310 (@ Benchmark Tool And Supply in Chesapeake, VA) https://t.co/Ywe1Exkawf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hornerr_23 YOU ARE HONESTLY GOING TO BRING KEVIN INTO THIS IN FRONT OF THE WHOLE INTERNET WHEN YOU CAN'T EVEN ADMI… https://t.co/jTaEQePlIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bet2win98 @DLoesch @RealMattCouch The fact that she is attacking the truth at a time that she and Pelosi turn arou… https://t.co/yuhuLygQRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abstract Latino-influenced artwork infused with Light Language and cosmic downloads . . . #latinart #latinarte… https://t.co/ZxowZYc3AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesTheDill @High_Lethality @Blaands017 I think that might be a Springfield.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: it’s nice out, I’m gonna go for a run   My couch: no you ain’t   Me: What?   ***falls asleep and wakes up an hour later]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had @NorahJones “Sunrise” playing as our entrance song for the  wedding reception.   I still see the indoor flow… https://t.co/WFyAA07LX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consequence WHERES #LaToyaJackson IN 2019?WE NEED A NEW #interview ABOUT THIS?   #Confessions of a #JacksonFamily… https://t.co/PWc9vIHdsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lainnafader The issue is quite simple. Either we prove that nature was right in evolving consciousness and self-aw… https://t.co/JWDYIIxrTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDGamble @nickolai_32 I mean the #CMPFAM has your back but please right the ship. Our brand image is on the line dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanged out with friends I love, saw Noname, and Chris Hero had a good match with WALTER on NXT UK, so today was great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryankingry @PaulZanon1972 Fuck outta here.... 1 million I can probably get that money from @FloydMayweather if I k… https://t.co/zW47ezDDmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawg I NAILED this special ed chick in the face with a volleyball in middle school on accident bc Cody smileys bitc… https://t.co/14KlvOdIB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/vDdANVg7m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moodsmusic Is now taking pre-orders for the Mohamed Ali Pop! Quantities are limited so order yours now! Just send… https://t.co/AUacWjJU5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please listen &amp; add to your playlist! 🎼🌏🎹🎧🎼 https://t.co/td085ndrWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also i was plan going to college after High School but I changed my mind why? maybe because I don't want to go it m… https://t.co/jjpj4n14wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycherrera1 @JamesxGamesYT @leesheriff That pig needs his face slammed into. What the fuck asshole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all know about the #RightHandOfFellowship? Here's what the #LeftFootOfFellowship looks like:  #Religion will… https://t.co/wOF9h4tpGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Yorker level: spotting a one night stand from 2 years ago and maintaining the proper distance to avoid detectio… https://t.co/GfK8jxDxbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was @Jim_Jordan sitting on a phone book yesterday? He’s so small...in every way. @HouseGOP @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @CNN @MSNBC @NewsHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoRulesReview So you’re constantly struggling between grabbing your best events and using the opponent’s best ones… https://t.co/maQiERSz06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partee875 @sdutKrier Not too stressed because this pineapple express stretches out far and everything will sag sou… https://t.co/Q61XptJEjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing by... (@ Second Story Bar in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/kNZeimaezM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @VancityReynolds was  Mississippi Grind (2015) a component of final #workshopping for #Deadpool?! Well done BTW… https://t.co/oWTqb9xyhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[7sausages, 6 eggs, 2 potatoes. 1 amazing breakfast @ Yucaipa, California https://t.co/iB4Cw8sbjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another lie, tried to pull the same lie in Texas, all the voters were American citizens not non citizen, but stupid… https://t.co/FS61E83OoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hasya23 But now we have Diversity, and old women are now in the act!  Rejoice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finna stop arguing wit pieons about street shit niggas don’t understand yeen gotta be out dere and if you gon r… https://t.co/BfmBGeEXck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bill_goldthorpe Maybe. They offered what the Rangers felt was the best package available. If there was a guarantee… https://t.co/fuxOUVSQ8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cumsace Bruh Harden gets killed by the media every single day LeBron is ehhh cause I see it every now and then but… https://t.co/yI8XVNNcZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Didn't even get a 1st round pick? Wow! Big L to the Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katierrae One time I wanted a haunted house with it's own graveyard so I made giant families and kept killing people 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump No facts just programmed by the media!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Courtyard by Marriott Los Angeles Westside - @courtyardla in Culver City, CA https://t.co/Wza7AMWq2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black people cant be racist, since racism is a function of those in power it is impossible for anyone who is Black… https://t.co/2ib5O10nGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camcamdamn I don’t think either of us knows exactly what happened. I do know there is a police report w her name o… https://t.co/WI5ha1lAFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another terrific day of basketball at the County Center. Great atmosphere in the place semi-finals and finals should be played!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lo_Blackwell That giant H-Star looks like it was designed by Disney people. Like, the very look of it. Ya know whe… https://t.co/XCpPepcxMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special night for a special team as the Conant boys' basketball team won a record 12th state championship with a… https://t.co/OyI2Q1aX30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan @RandPaul Tell me about liberty when my country is no longer my country, RP.  Just what is your sense of lim… https://t.co/heoOSzHY1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NJT - Bus 119 - @nj_transit in Jersey City, NJ https://t.co/5FUHzsgxtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered I lost all my videos from Homecoming on my phone.... they was in 4K too . ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorisEP @realDonaldTrump Ah Sinclair, the weak second rate state TV. 2nd to Fox.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been to countless road games for the @Bengals and been to @AVFCOfficial games in the states. Never been to a road m… https://t.co/JPEUytpqYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no quit in @K_m_Mitchell.   After a bogey-bogey start, he has steadied the ship.   Birdie on 9 to pull with… https://t.co/2fq22zy7yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading yet another great @333books, this time it’s @tompetty Southern Accents and my main takeaway early on is how… https://t.co/XPRKTpKNG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 24 Hour Fitness Super Sports in Walnut, CA https://t.co/4tg9RPJBWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I always wondered what "apprehended" meant. Such a bigly word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis papás piensan que quiero carro para andar de peda y la verdad es que lo quiero para irme a pueblear🏕🛣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WagerTalkDwayne @Johnny_Detroit DB he didn’t jinx you!! https://t.co/YI1l62FBdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbobocce @katrinatulloch Ehhhhhhhhhh, there are exceptions. Few but they exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @Jeanjeancrook Years from now this photo will prove to be an embarrassment to these stupid women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure what is happening to the gay population and dying their hair blonde but let’s face it... we look gooooood.… https://t.co/BkAOYDaEwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next stop... Da Bronx! Rise &amp; Grind, #GroupTraining edition. Let’s Go. 👊🏽🏃🏽‍♂️ https://t.co/HUhCXKJLPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_m_riddell @SouthwestAir Ha I’m so thankful I’m resilient. I can survive this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outbound River Road before Royal Dominion Drive: LEFT lane BLOCKED, crash #MDTraffic #DCTraffic @WTOPtraffic https://t.co/XEK2LCzQQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fagiolista @Currentzis @SWRSymphonie @concerti Das ist der sogenannte „Schweinemarsch“ :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisShockley76 I’ve been following them on twitter for years. Always posting quality tweets, sir. Here they are, @loneblockbuster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 Unless he tells her he promises not to.  Like the scotus boys told her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA2K why do you rig the my team market? It’s pretty obvious y’all buy out cards that aren’t selling high enough,… https://t.co/8o7Rge1R2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Polish president after Netanyahu comments: Israel shouldn't host European summit (Haaretz)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneypappas @allieellz @LASNYC1 There will be a ton of horizontal running at our offsite, wherever that is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i give you a rope and you hang yoself everytime, so what tf i’m posed to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cambillings6 @newyscruggs Bolden and Zion out and Barrett 4 fouls...whose out for UNC? I’m drinking Bourbon, so mi… https://t.co/9EssoVn6pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kramerica100 @xfl2020 @XFLTampaBay He’s bringing his tool box of concepts down south.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse ... Check your stats WH, especially if you got them from the President of the U.S. He has a tendency to fib, just a little. ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc  Just sayin Bigdoggpinc on Pinterest to see more... https://t.co/kffIjJzM2H #xbox #ebook    via… https://t.co/FRmTEjKHId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letica_mike Hi Mike, I was transferred to Metrohealth Trauma Center in Cleveland Saturday night. Having my back su… https://t.co/jDSjLpD7Yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome party this morning in Richmond, VA for a good cause! kennedyyy_gracee jmcmillian318 @WoRBandOfficial dranda… https://t.co/XLH0iBOSdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandieLove @Kasparov63 The treasonous trust-funder got his fee-fees hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incomparable, unchangeable, You see the depths of my heart and you love me the same. You are amazing, God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People gotta start appreciating what others do for them because we’re grown as hell, no one is obligated to do shit for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already consumed plenty, but not gonna lie...my @TABASCO consumption has gone up dramatically since visiting thei… https://t.co/lz9IuQWVUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“His personality’s meant as much to us as his game has,” Few said about Geno Crandall, “and I don’t mean that to sl… https://t.co/dBvSgvi2uA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishin I was in my happy place right about now🌞 @ Bonita Springs, Florida https://t.co/47mrVUPvpv]]></document><document><![CDATA['I am not calling the gentleman, Mr. Meadows, a racist,' say Rep. Tlaib https://t.co/ykOaFLbXim via @msnbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sendiego Pizza Port by @pizzaportbeer at @pizzaportbressi — https://t.co/1Rt0zH6Wjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[D-Wade could not go out allowing Dion to have that buzzer beater against the warriors. #wadecounty   #OneLastDance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!  A little #flashbackfriday post from February 2015 .  Working in my home studio while still employed… https://t.co/8CQ4q9v8eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/l6PIho6zTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[to my fellow creatives: update that content calendar, book the shoot, network, but most importantly, be you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smartass...You’re comparing a national opioid dependence crisis with a brutal left dictatorship, what is the minimu… https://t.co/8D3kbUgULd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonReitman Any chance the new movie will pay tribute to the late great Harold Ramis?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlG_HONCHO @shaperka @Gunschilli Because I respect people and their wishes, and I thought perhaps you would want t… https://t.co/fxD7CgMuy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterframpton When I was growing up in Rochester NY, my neighbor and friend Janine played Alive every day. I could… https://t.co/AziRY20Esj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me 'that's a goal'  Lauren 'they didn't call it  Official, 5 minutes later,' hit the camera and crossed the line, therefore it was a goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner anyone?? (@ Bamboo Beach Tiki Bar &amp; Cafe in Fort Lauderdale, FL) https://t.co/Dt4xwjnqx8 https://t.co/3QlH8A3kCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder: many things are getting better. Poverty levels are down, child labor is down, food takes less of… https://t.co/j5WRwGetVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight months pregnant, and yes, she’s literally glowing. https://t.co/eNjyecrdGn]]></document></documents></author>