<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[2. @Royalfamily: the tweeter of that pic is not a name I recognize. It looks like it might be a painting. I searche… https://t.co/FOT2brKDbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[POLL: How far will the Los Angeles Lakers go this #NBA season? #LakeShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siubhan_H @AcampbelTeacher @Zigmund_Fraud @Rosewind2007 @badzoot7 @KimPaddockASD @djt10 @JuliaHadley15 @SueQuez… https://t.co/4zQvLQkT7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful #sundaymorning #crispandcold  #bluesky #appreciatethelittlethings https://t.co/IwpXZdtFak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tap and share 👏 #dothework @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/gJQBkkV54i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t recovered from the @jonasbrothers announcing they are back together yesterday #Sucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to my tio’s and tia’s.... go update your Facebook profile pic tia y para de hacer más chismes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretaryCarson @HUDgov You have been doing an Excellent job with HUD, Sec Carson. God bless you so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @ericabuddington Because hate is more important to trump and his followers]]></document><document><![CDATA[They never stress Weed Smoking..Its always Cigarettes..think about It 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nearpod is like a box of chocolates. It’s full of fabulous goodies everyone loves. #NearpodTransform]]></document><document><![CDATA[*20% Off &amp; FREE SHIPPING! Site-wide sale is on NOW! *some exclusions* This is the best sale of the year! Thanks… https://t.co/mglGkbgAUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched some girl In middle school rip her eye lashes off w a lash curler so we don’t use one over here]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Stop thinking we are post racism in #KWAwesome/#WRAwesome. We’re not. Stop the denial and focus on decolonizing… https://t.co/prDsfYYjME]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my daughter didn’t know my number by heart cause I’ll fucking change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yamakiri10 @m2d08 In thos #tododeku comic, is Midoriya's mom meeting her future son in law?]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6.. 7 pm.  Come watch Max and his stacked Illinois team take on Missouri!  Sure to be a great night of wrestl… https://t.co/lRJe4slPTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixfootcandy @jimidragon I am. You retweeting me so that your followers could jump on me proved it. What did you e… https://t.co/a0pse5sAlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I STILL think David Letterman is the EXPERT for this problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t with Kardashians getting involved with the Bachelor... like please stop... no one in the bachelor world wan… https://t.co/PHbAatEFu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kendrajames13 @GirdleBound Oh yes I have been playing dress up all my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went and got new shoes! #Nike Got the black pair too! #Sales #bargain https://t.co/kOefDfgiuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to have been #2 of the 7 Of the Best Kick-Ass Books By or About Women. @SammyLove86 qthat the anniversary f… https://t.co/UrFBixfULz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to win @tacotimenw for a year in their #MenuMadness bracket challenge! https://t.co/z5Nwke4aSC .]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the get go. 1. Trump supporters have better things to do than attack people at 2 A.M   2. It's the radical lef… https://t.co/gadn1LzHPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 Connect with Public Advocate candidates tonight in #CrownHeights with @DawnforNewYork @NomikiKonst @RLEspinal… https://t.co/uYlXTzfiCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. It is absolutely no one’s place to tell me what I can and cannot do with my body. The only opinions I consider a… https://t.co/YNSqf31WnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout NoHo after Percy drives in hard from the corner and hooks it in from under the net. 41-23, Braves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @SideHustleWino @DivaVinophile @FionaMorgan79 @GailBenzler @joneill55 @Starofthesea007 @hmgivingsoul… https://t.co/lFAOS70nbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicdibitetto Made my day from a just a fine one to the best ever. What a guy, this is so special God Bless 😘😏☕💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[New tutorial for this cheap ad makeup tutorial I did. Now available on my YouTube channel. See how to purchase. Lin… https://t.co/Woub5bhbmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[NK Summit Decode, 3/14 Steele Testimony Release, Barr is THE HAMMER https://t.co/aXEynOszOp via @YouTube @RedPill78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids What about these kids Melania ?  Ur nothing but a phony,  heartless  Putin appointed so call… https://t.co/BQj4npFSRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AARPadvocates Senator do your homework on cost of popular drugs in other countries. Sometimes 100x cheaper. Americ… https://t.co/gP6maifTuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benorlin @DodaniLab @UTDScience @jasminetutol @christianelol Good luck on the new book! I promise we will try to s… https://t.co/IH31a9DjFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never flying Jet Blue again! @JetBlue Been sitting at Newark Airport since 4:00 am for my 6:00 flight. Now being to… https://t.co/ONvODKvauV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusickMichele @MattWichner @blondemonkey71 @aj_mazzola @RushbrookKevin @Hol_Lis @MaryDevine6866 @Ramos_Jon325 @JulesNelson13 So nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paige_Emma23 👍 Congratulations! I started out at Mayo Clinic as a 5 year temp. Don't give up. It will all happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr #icallbs why do you misrepresent every bill⁉️Just put it up for vote ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo que comprar ropa ahorita pero pase por Montacometa y NO ME PUDE RESISTIR 😭  de por si soy pobre y como quiera… https://t.co/3cOtYEaBfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[He told me he wanted nothing to do with this baby the day I told him I was pregnant. He told me to get an abortion.… https://t.co/x9hwL2l4Ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand this throwing cheese on your baby? I think the most ridiculous things are funny...but this isn’t one if them]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re hobbits today! #ImGoingOnAnAdventure (@ New Jersey/Pennsylvania State Border in Delaware River Bridge, NJ) https://t.co/1ze8LV13Fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIChrisMannix You've been waiting to say this the last 2 weeks lol. Missed your chance against Milwaukee, Toronto,… https://t.co/zPYZSXh9UX]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get caught doing something you shouldn’t be doing.... police turned around the corner at exactly this poin… https://t.co/8Z2SRbIMOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this guy... 8 shows in 5 days @spot_sv with an incredible show of talented young Company actors. These… https://t.co/mA6iKIfoGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would just like to cement the fact that I am 1000000% glad that I left this dude when I did HOLY FUCK and stopped… https://t.co/S4zgmcGXlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nagpapahiwatig na ang AlJen noon pa pero di binigyan ng pansin Sino nga magaakala yung Mag Nanay sila pala Ccto  A… https://t.co/mopR2LyJVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine wanting a nap so dang bad because it's #NationalNappingDay and your whole BPA chapter decides to congregate… https://t.co/t0Y4s7997x]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time to attend the Ontario provincial finance diversity gala.  First time to sing a stanza of an old folk son… https://t.co/iCMcJ29sjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this movie but this movie so messed up to me.  Literally the only scary movie that I’ve seen that’s freaked… https://t.co/I3AP5l8wfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyRaChaCha @buffalopundit We were driving from NYC after our connecting flight was cancelled. It was...not good. Home now though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daneng53 @NoahCRothman Are you serious? Every 2020 Dem candidate has endorsed the Green New Deal which advocates t… https://t.co/yG25Enkw1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson Jeezus and I thought US guys had problems. I thought about leaving until we dump Trump. Canada? Are y… https://t.co/DWeGPFXKmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jglidden007 @beachykeenmel @pauly7777f @jercorley Please, don't remind us. He only got 10% of our vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally at the hotel — what a long, strange trip its been. Almost 2am here ... (@ Hilton Garden Inn Charlotte Airpo… https://t.co/OrPSP855PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Eric_L Assimilation means the new culture is not like your old culture so find a Muslim diner where you will be… https://t.co/TugM5QrSaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenjaminNorton @rosendo_joe In all reality, this shows no one eating. Nor dancing. What are you actually doing? Ar… https://t.co/kccD08BKeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Pittston Township, Luzerne County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/sIoNdPjmaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch my review of the Komplete Kontrol A25 MIDI controller here! https://t.co/jJp0sKYEhQ.   #alixillusion… https://t.co/EdoSxsrfYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazingLovelyGM @ChristiesInc @GeorgeMOfficial @GMichaelNews I would agree with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateFromKY @hans_kohlhase @jb836836 @ScottHech every fucking body lies   it’s life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woofbarkdawg @marklevinshow @realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump  Is predictable.  His targets🎯 haven’t changed: 📌Hil… https://t.co/4zsQeUg3i0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveBresnen @ZaZaDallas @HotelZaZa Please fix it. This will drive us crazy. Welcome to the hood, ZaZa!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet.” 🍎     #polarvortexish #nineteendegrees… https://t.co/xyPogLTxsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were in Valentine’s candy marketing I’d make a box called “no weird stuff”]]></document><document><![CDATA[im having a fever dream there is no other explanation https://t.co/Cr3jrGuXs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge to post covers of 7 Children’s books I LOVE: no explanations, no review - just cover. M… https://t.co/WbJOlpoMnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just can't with your parents upstairs anymore. #MillennialWaystoLeaveYourLover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @NicolleDWallace @DeadlineWH Great! I tend to understand things better when you explain them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerryferrara I love that my friend @JamesCrowder  is friends with the KNX gaming  master @jerryferrara &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones… https://t.co/ebe48YWRPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cherry, cocoa nibs, vanilla,  cinnamon,  and habanero.  Hab taste, but no real burn. - Drinking a Sombra by… https://t.co/kzbvAGPOQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t know man believe what you want to believe or talk to me personally please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @JaneMayerNYer None of that at CNN. https://t.co/fi8llYj8QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stedwardpbp @dotoole41 @SEHS_BASKETBALL @_BBHHS @beevillesports @sehsathletics @bwathletics See you tonight!💚💛😎☘️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhianmarie @DeafInstitute @IamTomWalker @hitsradiouk Those hypnotic eyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@82nd13 @norcalbbgm @butchbaccala @_JeremyBooth @JasonMcCuistion @CedrickHarris11 @SBetkey @mactiner… https://t.co/zL6a6P7Tc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Mike &amp; Micky last Friday night (March 1) in Medford. Great show! @ Chevalier Theatre https://t.co/1uzJAbmiOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPOST: @Razo681 Did I mention I had the amazing opportunity to photograph the @iabdinc festival this year? This wa… https://t.co/bfwlI7ViEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you SCF Volleyball and Lewis Gibson for these chickaaaaas 💕 #bridemaids #GetMarriedOriti @ Saint Petersburg,… https://t.co/u9BNLHq2ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders He is a dictator who only cares about himself, starving ppl and you still support socialism ! Wake up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariannacordovaa I hate how everyone thinks she’s not acknowledging he’s trash I’m sure she knows :// but did u wat… https://t.co/HNCu4E82xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wandohigh Boys Lacrosse team joined us for Read Like a Sports Star week to celebrate Read Across America!… https://t.co/kmQdDpAL8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great group of amazing surgeons! Thanks for the good work @WomenSurgeons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewoodieslive @iris19jones @amymaytrust @freefromfarm @GemmaEvans @foodallergyuk or better yet don't criticize ap… https://t.co/rchaCgibTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to film this product tomorrow. Mmmm fingers crossed it’s a good product.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyOdonnel4 @garthbrooks @edsheeran Yes!!! I soooo can see him singing this to her. After all, they are Perfect! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compassionate pragmatism and other helpful concepts explained  in @zpodcast podcast with Dr. @AndrewTatarsky from… https://t.co/g9NFISfqad]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sports is your modern campfire. All gathered around the flames, with a strong sense of being connected. It’s the s… https://t.co/MzuZ2yGA8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SayHeyKid These overreactions are insane 😂 never seen this with anyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 Dart Free Day Celebration!  Ontario Night Ramp👍🏼 #SoCalSoSafe #TogetherWeAreUPS #MostImportantStop… https://t.co/RuTDCP9XAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remember boy and girls... I use _followersplus___ weekly, so if you #unfollow me, you gets yo ass #zapped ⛈… https://t.co/gBQfS9EYsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to be in Hawaii today .. but instead  the urgent care .. thxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @uccs #StudentMediaAdvisoryBoard meeting. Next one is on March 19, 2019 (5:30-6:30pm). Open to the public.… https://t.co/KaGdRCRdVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week's sentence better be consecutive, not concurrent. #ManafortSentencing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a guy say “you be out here entertaining hella dudes.” And I deadass asked him what his point was. 🤣🤣 I’m on my… https://t.co/kVXfjD6n5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @Deive107 with get_repost ・・・ Marque nos comentários quem te ajudou no início da caminhada, que respeitou o… https://t.co/YR9pAZLPXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ronni_2017 Happy Valentines Day to a very special young lady.  You have brightened my life since I met you here❤️❤️❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Hobi   💕🤫🗿🤪😓❄️🤐  stream HOPEWORLD ;) #BTSArmy #bts #HobiBirthdaySunshine #jHopeOurSunshine… https://t.co/L8YBSvBETL]]></document></documents></author>