<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I’m not paying for a show when I already know the ending. #TagYoureNotIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evilt58058White @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Everything you open your mouth stupid flies out.   You can talk intelligent.  I can watch you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE 💕 &amp; BELIEVE IN YOU 🥰  #BODYBYROCCO 💪🏽💪🏽  #LIFECOACH 💯%➕  BE~CUZZIE CUZZ #LOVEISLOVE😘 @ £Ov€ is £Ov€ https://t.co/3bM3hdofyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Because I still had feelings for the other person. I had to deal with my actions for the last 5 years of my re… https://t.co/LuYtqhqrhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like being called on your accent, with pin point precision as western pa at 7:30am on the phone in Florida… https://t.co/nDBSP5G81f]]></document><document><![CDATA[📌 This illusion looks like I’m very small seating on a chair that doesn’t exist hahaha  #MuseumOfIllusions… https://t.co/IDOau9Axlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a huge Metallica fan but this song has one of the best bass lines ever written.  #bass @ Queens, New York https://t.co/kXsLRtQZsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trumpty_Dumptee @Debbie_Gust @DogginTrump @realDonaldTrump Well I guess his base isn't as poorly educated as he th… https://t.co/LPbzvqM4dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepublicanSwine Will he explain why his "Italian" wife has a Russian accent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zur_dito La justicia es súmamente lenta. El#caso del padrastro q mutiló al nene, está en etapa de selección de jur… https://t.co/MmKLLfhDlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly's birthday party, Monster Jam 2019, Woohoo. @ Ford Idaho Center https://t.co/0SrJyRBnb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zubinanary @tesla_raj @teslaownersSV Count me in for real. I’m in Bay Area also. Wow - very generous of you to off… https://t.co/wD8c974t6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perspy2 @RepAdamSchiff Haven’t you figured our @TheDemocrats are lying to you about @realDonaldTrump ??? He didn’t… https://t.co/PcssIrfkHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LaFamiliaPicnic #LaFamilia #LaFamiliaWeAre #Squad #GangGang #TropicalPark #Drone #Food #Drinks #Fun #Kids… https://t.co/29zb42vd1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffspolitics Congratulations... Been subscribed to your channel for a while now... Always appreciate your work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmanDaBomb Yes though I’m more referring to people assuming I wrote all the music for some of the bigger titles I… https://t.co/co0M4HlGtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamBtrg @CelticFC @umbro @Inter @Nike @FCBarcelona @USMNT @DFB_Team_EN @adidasfootball @FCBayernUS @Inter_en… https://t.co/FEh33uJmbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great to be back at this place! Wasn't sure I would be again. Looking forward to a great season! #Crew96 https://t.co/1tB1IwOqOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Make sure to get a slice of the @MyCicis BBQ pizza. #Classy #MyHero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidraWayfarer Honestly, the best thing it's done is made me spend more time cooking. I eat a lot better when I cook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @vincentgabriel for the cool shot! . . . . . . . . . #fannedfret #alternatetuning #percussion… https://t.co/NwpHdynVkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going Live Tonight so stop by and enjoy the stream also show support by following us @Twitch. Running with the squa… https://t.co/R0QOWXLIBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad @Bharper3407 left honestly, that dumbass wore a Golden Knights jersey to the Stanley Cup Finals, he can ch… https://t.co/n75Rf3XtS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for the delayed post - we’re here with teh new comics! Lots of good stuff out. Final issue of this Detective… https://t.co/YjOA5MaZuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelHoneyBee_ @FatKidDeals @FatKidAlerts @pimpinwear You we're the 1st person that came up lol good account to foll… https://t.co/vKf18zLOFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[How on Earth am I supposed to know whether or not my model of reality is even remotely close to accurate? And if I… https://t.co/SD1SlHhwpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellente série “Ainsley Eats the Streets” sur Netflix.   https://t.co/CqG5CoRYO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @PitbullTina @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/RnnS41IFef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rake all that shit in a pile and put a sign over it that says THIS IS WHY I DRINK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonah Williams testing isn’t something to ignore. He could very easily be there at the end of the first if the draf… https://t.co/Liqdvnb4rP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing funnier than watching someone fail after I gave them the advice to succeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TB12_Forever Good morning Suni! You have more there than here. Be safe, have a great day!😊🌬❄❄☕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir may I have the record locator of a partner carrier for a fellow passenger?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I guess it’s that time. Head to work to make the scrilla then I got a day or two off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittniSacco @FanduBelts If this doesn’t make you ❤️ wrestling than I don’t know what else will !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that we let robots fly the spaceships proves once and for all that letting people drive cars is a terrible idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrix2 @gahawolf @Jimmysimmonds1 @butchey12 @stevebikoartist @SherylPrattERA @AB2Coaches @heavenencounter… https://t.co/7PNEI007Rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pouco se fala mas em poucas horas joga meu cizeiro https://t.co/TZcDa2mnbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimmy Loses It with Robert Irwin on a Hot Mic Before Animals Segment https://t.co/MGs5b1F7hJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn lol I can’t tweet shit without people assuming it’s about Roger 😂 despite our differences and issues he’s alwa… https://t.co/KfgqKMYAF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbp71 I'm sorry, please don't kill me for laughing, but that's HILARIOUS! 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Failed Elguerial from Boom Boom Huckjam, 2003 (not sure which city). No wonder my neck is so stiff these days; deca… https://t.co/gYUhKbaFSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryDBrooks I’d live to make an entrance into First National on my skateboard with my fiddle a blaze!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iCapital_ The Pirates start 2019 with a group of players that will all earn raises in arbitration by improving as… https://t.co/X7QpSdBDXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever feel like #PresidentialHarassment is a diversion from a bigger issue? https://t.co/JwqTpEbrvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler By the way, you'll never be Janis Joplin. And Beaches movie didn't age well.  I used to cry at the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Chatwood pitched 3 innings yesterday throwing 67% of his pitches for strikes. Chatwood threw 56% of his pitches for strikes in 2018.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remove his clearance Now! From Discover on Google https://t.co/VZcWTpEphi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to this guy!! Phil has been with us since November and what a wonderful asset to our team ... . . .… https://t.co/ZXWXhbKP1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women were really into something when they said “I’m single until I got a ring”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterWilt1 @goldenaceinn @Schlabst @tomdunmore @NipunChopra7 @McGin83 @bjett15 @MollyK10 @davejsports… https://t.co/ymF9NjeWqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Lincoln: light rain, 35°F 100% humidity, wind 13mph, pressure 997mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAngelBean @FUNimation Correct. The judges would have also accepted “Born to Make History”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon and its race to the bottom has been a debacle. But I worry that the far left maybe paralyzing development, f… https://t.co/xR17ylBZbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 Or do you not know that your body is a temple of the Holy Spirit within you, whom you have from God? You are no… https://t.co/JZx882SvCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheShipyardSD @Sideline_Sizzle @MemphisAAF @AAFCommandPost @TheWarRoomSA @ApolloAudible @slcstallion @IronPodcast… https://t.co/SirTHbhIbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡El Manchester City se lleva la Carabao Cup en los penaltis ante el Chelsea! Los de Guardiola se coronan campeones… https://t.co/zWFq79b4nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stuyrobb No it wasn’t ☹️. The Blast missed too many opportunities to put the mall in the back of the net.  Now we’… https://t.co/y7b8K62bEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday’s Work. Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel See the link in my profile. #drawing #sketch… https://t.co/Si6KpTaMcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[El día que Andrés cometa algún error lo señalaré. Por ahora está haciendo más trabajo (y bien) que 6 ex presidentes… https://t.co/eRLxhnqyE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theintercept And @Snowden is in exile for blowing the whistle on illegal NSA surveillance that resulted in legislation to curb it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the anniversary, I’m watching it today with my wife...who has never seen it! That’s just bogus!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m grateful. Happy Valentine’s day. That is all. ❤️ https://t.co/83Fqlgxauy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobProvince @chadfelixg @lgbtqnation I'm gay and I am voting for Trump again because I utilize common sense and respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiking a burned area. Florida has a cactus?? @ Ocala National Forest https://t.co/B8UZBI7wKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCampingRush Hey Rush, when I went to update my mobile fortnite, I went to the reviews for a sec. and the only o… https://t.co/J6VKyrCGqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is always fun to visit #otr in #cincinnati and we really enjoyed @kruegerstavern this weekend. The burgers and b… https://t.co/jGB4ng1dNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onpage11 @Crown_mekinggg That’s a problem in itself frfr not even being funny 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina and I’m sure we don’t agree here but having a RB in that top 5 cap is not the way to build a conte… https://t.co/3lQ4tKJ4DJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDuckett11 @shershey22 @bearcreeklmc I would read anything as a kid and that included all my mom’s Nancy Drew boo… https://t.co/hy8uopHjpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥎 IT’S GAME DAY 🥎 ‼️‼️‼️  OC Panthers 🆚 Marshall  🗓: March 9, 2019  ⌚️: 12:00 p.m. 📍: NISD Softball Field #1   #OC… https://t.co/mp3T5vmpRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if we come back and win...Butler does not deserve a tourney bid. This is pathetic #Butler]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it out the trenches, it got harder for my niggas.  I just wanna see my dawgs ball, seven figures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kait_tiffany “he actually calls her “Xan Frank,” in honor of Xanax.”   Couldn’t get past this. W. T. F. is happening]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samipuckett6 Call us sensitive if you please, but it’s his actions that got him terminated from coaching]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnsonF We’re unappreciated in our time. History, however, will be on our side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this place! @themifflintavern music starts at 8! #livemusicrocks #livemusic #acoustic #southphilly #acoustic… https://t.co/TiTzKOc4wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because we don’t think you should be allowed to buy an AR-15 doesn’t mean I don’t think you should be allowed… https://t.co/INMpBPvClv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters As Hallmark "Royal Court" member, Commonwealth Trust donor, fundamental revivifier of the English language… https://t.co/9rINUkPIO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FearedNightmare @chibi_missy @bowski477 Yeah, I’ve watched all of them multiple times but have never actually read… https://t.co/0DYoy5zFXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you @4uds4evr . Happy days to you always. 🚀❤️ @ Tempe, Arizona https://t.co/odPrhUNCf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Attyg3 Lol, same shit this moron just did. But hey, all you have to do is bet more on the winners right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remember, they love you when you up. .  .  Fake smiles &amp; handshakes. They don’t know that struggle. But thank you GOD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN We know whats going in...we don't need u to tell us what to do. This isnt Somalia !  Go home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When done right #bluemuda can be a great tool for sports turf managers. @MegEVanArsdale knows how to do it right an… https://t.co/lrNGe8l0UY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseyMcEwen Your are an amazing human being Kelsey! A class act .... so proud of everything you have accomplished!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Bows @profmjmack @AOC If you want tweets to make sense, you're on the wrong platform.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rozacalderon How many of the 158,000,000 are working it because they can't make on the other job they have. And th… https://t.co/zhqhDGNZ1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reach out for God and find Him,though he is not far from each one of us.Acts 17:27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t ask for a better race in Detroit!! @elitomac gets the win and also @CRtwotwo gets up on the podium!! Your… https://t.co/IOJH8mYqqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach @jcboice reviewing R4 with our QBs today. @ Howell, Michigan https://t.co/76RJcqhwGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPBF_Gianna @WPBF25News @SenSanders YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING MORE BS FROM HIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson It's important to remember what country we're living in and who our opponents are. 'Socialist Jew' w… https://t.co/GSJJnBOmzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Latest:      Sherrod Brown won't run for president;     Crony capitalism may bring down Justin Trudeau;      Pe… https://t.co/SCi7i8r5GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albertonlibre @AOC Alexandria Ocasio Cortez doesn’t know where philly is but she’ll grab one for lunch today. You’… https://t.co/lvq3XVcYdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gather round the Snapchat children, I’ll tell you the tale of the landline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanWePhixItMLB @pivettahype I would fucking love this. I am at Disney World drinking dogfish head going to see 311… https://t.co/yIXTUlC1FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThereelOG469 @3YearLetterman @BarackObama @NASA @MarsRovers Give it up, pal. I used to like Bob Knight. Your coach… https://t.co/kSfKh8Cfpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need Kenny to have a big game. I need Matt to have a big game. I need Xavier to have a big game. I need Aaron to… https://t.co/8brSTICTEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay soo the day i leave from Sedona im thinking of spending MDW in Las Vegas]]></document></documents></author>