<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EllenPage Thank you.❤️ Yes, one story does not negate all of the hate that happens every day to real people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @AACOPD .  How can a noise complaint be filed against the company that runs the street cleaners in the… https://t.co/b04QIGOkOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[DISCOUNT FOR THIS WEEK!!!!!! - - 20% off in full sets 💕💕 @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/y3YzOOYhe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm mad at the entire world today. On Valentine's Day, which happens to be my favorite holiday. Or it used to be. N… https://t.co/MScNn78fSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought the momo challenge was like 2 years old... what’s with the hype now? 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merindab @Dschulija_the2 @gizmotrinket221 @221Bcrow Yeah I avoid calling in sick like the plague https://t.co/e5JSd96y7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your heart is filled with faith, there is no room left for fear. "Who can stand up against the Anakites (Gia… https://t.co/Xhfa2sLC68]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NDHockey wishin' Luke a year filled w/blessings both on 'n off the ice #GoIrish https://t.co/plD0BmcaQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my baby brother my other half the peace to my heart my twin!!❤️ but I know he is watching over me every day… https://t.co/bKsq1DYzZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and des just got pulled up on stage by a stripper. That’s all I’m gonna say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should’ve known better than to order a #phillycheesesteak from a cafe 🤦🏻‍♀️🙄😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have an 8am and it’s 2am and i’m sitting here crying. welcome to heartbreak kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell y’all Aunty Jackie is STACKED. Please believe me. My all time fave MUA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBridenstine - And 9 teams will have access to them shortly because we are confident we’re going back #Moon2Mars… https://t.co/jDxYP7MqSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omackson Seattle right now. When is Spring, really?? https://t.co/25qyZP9M4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newlandfarm @FisherP22 @stevie_farm I’m fighting pathetic old age with all I’ve got. Current effort involves the c… https://t.co/TBx6TXSeJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wave80radio @MusicMan1730 Don't you mean the best of Van Hagar? https://t.co/Q2iJbihsdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Fisher&amp;Frey! @pdkeeley @coachbreyer @ssmithsanjac #LiteracyandEquity @CorwinPress https://t.co/xbSXoMMasi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo mientras revisan en el VAR el gol del #Ajax #CHAMPIONSxESPN https://t.co/9gQWXWz3jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreakyFridays presents  #marchmadness #hiphop vs. #reggae #OpenBar 🍹🍸🍷Before 11:30 enjoy the best  music in a grow… https://t.co/zQ08VhN6yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You say you want it..⁣ ⁣ So go f*cking DO IT already!⁣ ⁣ Get that ass in GEAR and put it where you WANT TO BE. No e… https://t.co/Mt8kqASbTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just your average witch day... #actor #actorslife #actors #actress #onset #costume #witch #green #goddess… https://t.co/P3jdE4xhdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyShookVideo @DonnaFins @thepainterflynn I got my eyes on you🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/HgOl89Jsys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dive-In - 4 Thank you desertx superflex. Beautiful work! #divein #superflex #desertx #art #instalation #palmdesert… https://t.co/2fPB4kewoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philopelt @rwidmer11 @CPyles8 We for sure called it states. Not sure why]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t cook much but I do take pride in being able to craft a few classic cocktails. I’m so glad JAX now has a gre… https://t.co/K1BGqqpfqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just packed workout clothes/shoes for Austin!! I don’t recognize myself!! #sxsw #SXSW2019 🏃🏿‍♀️👟 https://t.co/eWIhqxsknk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness I am in #LOVE with a #AStarIsBorn. #Mascara #crueltyfree #unitedstates #Australia #Canada #Mexico… https://t.co/0gigQ2yetl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my wisdom teeth out yesterday srry 2 flex @ Tip Top Of Okemo Mountain https://t.co/FPKPRHABDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see @tanamongeau win the #ShortyAwards! Vote now and to help them #GetTheW! https://t.co/kJfG28RQFK (my b… https://t.co/y2EcmpGyqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Don’t Hate Women Candidates — I Just Hated Hillary and Coincidentally I’m Starting to Hate Elizabeth Warren - McS… https://t.co/04gwxnWjFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love working with this guy! And loved our first headshot workshop with @russ_mezikofsky hufnagel_hair @Nelse80 aimc… https://t.co/dDJxHTnKke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighHSelby So would a tax break fund teachers salaries. It is also nice to have things that are “free” but someone pays for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday cuddles, books &amp; love! 📚♥️ @ Independence, Kentucky https://t.co/e9WlfWRvMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you take advantage of people....especially if they're humble and just live a lifestyle of letting shit rock...… https://t.co/aAYuzTgcgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaC120369 @wgnamerica @OfficialDOGNews @bobbybrown719 @Derm_girl98 @MLB2MLR @KellyCorby4 @Shekimber1 Hahah I beat you @PamelaC120369]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many exciting literacy experiences today! What a way to say ‘Welcome back to school!’ after a long weekend. I lo… https://t.co/zzfGMB3cpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindiortega Me too! It’s soooo good! WAtch Ozark it’s really good as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please tell me wtf I just watched?! HOW DID THIS HAPPEN? HOW?! So disturbing &amp; infuriating. #AbductedInPlainSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read this for the citrus salad and was unprepared for the random ode to French fries. https://t.co/6kKuFpTWFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never be southern enough to think pickles on a chicken biscuit is normal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Chula, would recommend if you’re ever in NY! https://t.co/b2WyOJDUiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[SunKissed ☀️☀️ #ClientSelfie 😍 iamposhofficial 💎💎 • • #AtlantaMakeupArtist #MakeupForBlackWomen #AtlantaHair… https://t.co/ax1iMjC33x]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just made me tear up. @colinb1123 and team are making it happen in NM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the new #JonasBrothers single is the sole reason for my happiness at the moment and i’m okay with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahgpipes This is great advice. Are the lashes uncomfortable after you get them done? Just like in daily life.… https://t.co/e7aWkv1A3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree 100%, as I’m sitting here drinking my matcha green tea and reading The Assassin’s Blade by @sarahjmaas ⚔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[His listing system blew my mind- A.... 60 miles an hour 2.... you pull into a parking lot and leave me half hanging… https://t.co/o9WpLGP4C2]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my life You have been faithful, and all my life You have been so, so good. With every breath that I am able, oh… https://t.co/MeuebKaeiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you find stories in your own neighborhood. It’s one you’ll only see on @mynbc15.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“El agente especial a cargo Meléndez dijo: “Tareck Zaidan El Aissami Maddah ha ocupado cargos clave en el gobierno… https://t.co/Qt45fMaZer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishopPMorton Amen Bishop. We are so glad God sent you our way here in New Orleans years ago. You thought us the t… https://t.co/i6vr09yr1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at my nieces newborn pictures😍 I’m in love https://t.co/O1FV2wc9dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay ladies!!! My friend Adam is the KINDEST, most genuine, pure hearted, thoughtful, honest... Truly special perso… https://t.co/jOsZGj5f2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a good time catching up, planning and presenting together! @kamithor #learningandthebrain @learningandtheb… https://t.co/RyQOCajWV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler came home this morning and told me that he listened to the new Jonas Brothers song and I asked him if he like… https://t.co/e9Jq1JHmtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embodiment practice for tonight feat robynkonichiwa b/w looks from @rhondaintl past ! Circa 2011-2014! If you’re no… https://t.co/YEv3KtOZVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM SO HUNGRY, &amp; WEIGH INS ARE AT 5 TOMORROW:(( so I’m sorry if I tell you stuff tomorrow in school ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLeguizamo @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @IngrahamAngle @TomiLahren @AnnCoulter… https://t.co/lfssUSveem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember messing with the idea of not vaccinating my children. Then I had a sick child and all that selfish arrog… https://t.co/0eftJtmPYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corey_gantt He’s being a baby and don’t wanna go. Told him you and I will go 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out "Beyond Borders with Nicole Ramos of Al Otro Lado" https://t.co/qw7vNUPXVN @Eventbrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iankar_ @jkwade @KyleVanPelt 🙈🤦🏼‍♀️ omg. in my defense I did not fact check only did a grammar/flow pass. learning… https://t.co/0sspamggx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadensisMax Pssst   Have you seen Donald and his Mommy issues... YEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fanficconcrit @GMRasp @McAdooGordon @EsotericCD I'm a 35 year old Millennial and I knew about the interview. Soooooooo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @RepCummings @RashidaTlaib @MarkMeadows @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN Now you see why they dont want to go impeachment route]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @s_slate90, we are so proud and inspired with the work you lead for all of us @Cisco @WeAreCisco… https://t.co/Sdl2tRrvOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graciemoss1 Happy Happy Blessed Birthday to my awesome Sista/Friend Gracie Moss. It’s your holiday lady so get out… https://t.co/gjOvfP9gUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamacta7 @AshaRangappa_ I always forget how much I love that movie. @AshaRangappa_ gon' make me watch it again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luiibaton @bl4cklodge Her name is Amy and I believe she’s from Taiwan, she is the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[چقدر جالبه این پادکست where should we begin...! گوش بدین اگه علاقه به روابط زوج‌ها و مشاوره‌شون...! :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraphicMatt to have to fight for this amount after the waste of BILLIONS going into shoring up the past its due date Gardiner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my Birthday @lillypulitzer earrings!  They go with my new dress!  Thanks mgrasmeier #birthdaymonth🎂 @ WZVN-Tva… https://t.co/ndZvd60o7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayraGuerreroMD Welcome to Twitter!  Who to follow? @womeninmedchat @RUBraveEnough  @GirlMedMedia   @TIMESUPHC… https://t.co/tUsRmLsOm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just put my pop tart in the fridge and the milk in the microwave...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you from the bottom of my heart. I am humbled to have my name mentioned alongside some of the finest journali… https://t.co/RYH3NPY6O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is absurd. friends quotes from the show | Funny Friends Tv Show Quotes photo Katelyn Annyce's photos -...… https://t.co/eEOG3MMSpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone want to bet she will sneak back in? We can't seem to stop anyone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1funnykat @SarahPalinUSA 😁😂😆🤣 . A bigger boy picking on a smaller boy and you're blaming Trump . Really , your defending a bully . Wow !]]></document><document><![CDATA[answered facetime &amp; first thing Brennen says is “woah you’re glowing”]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad woke up this morning cleaned the car, and even went to get me coffee, breakfast and a sandwich for lunch !!… https://t.co/b1HgfzYYaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberdiscko I'm a Taurus and that's why I don't want you to feel like it was just a thought. I will be there in a few minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megansmith1219 @akkfletcher @serahayden Amy’s new best friend #Respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up from an epic fight scene in my dream only to discover my frowning love with a scratched up belly. #sleepfighting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMikeBloomType @LianaBoraas @roundhoward Loving the #RHAPBnB!  Just that whole Masked-Singer-type of deal with the… https://t.co/4PpXtrwuyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! I want to take time to appreciate the women in my life. To see my relationship wit… https://t.co/GnpPtV5mNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieTheWXLady @WichitaUSD259 @MarshallUsd259 I want to be in your class! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does he do this? I get meeting with him, and trying to negotiate, but saying you like a murderer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaymondMDuchar1 @FaithGoldy Let her explain it .... 😂😂😂 @FaithGoldy shilling for the @CPC_HQ takeover of the… https://t.co/oNpPHIP9LV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brent really be going through my lunch bag to see if I brought Girl Scout cookies to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome Home Saratoga Springs Pl 4 Bed 3 bath aprox 3040 sqft built in 2003 Listed at $480K for a private tour call… https://t.co/pUNkZqjtSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, glad she’s finally gone! I hate the thought of having to continue to see Tayshia the rest of the season, I rea… https://t.co/7vdcagogyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been saying that for the longest, since he arrived in the White House]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q3 6th graders learned to draw 3-D form shells. Contour lines, shading and blending.   #toltmsart #toltms… https://t.co/HjP427HNWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffRBennett @NBCNews @WSJ It’s DEMOCRATIC SOCIALISM.  GET IT CORRECT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s looking for a Dinah zaddy 👀💦? 🔜 #thedinah2019 . . 🔒IN 🎟 NOW https://t.co/H2l9vGiKzQ  #dinahshoreweekend… https://t.co/oW0UgXdTh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump   @senatemajldr     @seanhannity   @LindseyGrahamSC   @GOPLeader   @GeraldoRivera   @AnnCoulter… https://t.co/VVLjlW9QKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RmEHz4STpU  Happy Friday! This is my last push to gather data on representation in #DnD and #ttrpg I’l… https://t.co/Ghhp53o333]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your boss insist on waking up at 7am but you wake up at 5:30am, you realize how not accurate the alarm clock i… https://t.co/cbvAGZu3XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberRo70828563 @alyssiaaaa_ @Rere_blu @unguardedgrande @khloekardashian Same]]></document></documents></author>