<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Don't You Worry 'Bout A Thing by Stevie Wonder, from #SoundHound wit… https://t.co/Wkakdu8c7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Elitehairtrapper #menshair #menhairstyles #mobileal #menshairstyles #barbers #kidcuts #mensfashion #hairmodel… https://t.co/zE42mcR5oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Dems attempt to impeach the Pres, for whatever reason, especially after we tolerated that clown Obama for EIGHT… https://t.co/z9kNbTbBUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be more excited than my 4 year old son to go see @MonsterJam next Friday at @AllstateArena!  (telling mysel… https://t.co/49ttd4nQ2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveScottGarner @PaulSaucier9 @impinkestgirl @ChuckKeller14 @ResistanceNOW77 @ldog562 @dougarrell @SteveShippee1… https://t.co/CyLxfCphUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best wedding date I could possibly have asked for! Thanks for bringing me to Pville, @jordanriz96 💍 @ KC Hall o… https://t.co/JZjHzaQzy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArizonaLuke @PhxGOP @KariLakeFox10 He’s an equal opportunity attacker though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DO NOT SEE THE HUMOR IN THIS ....AT ALL!!!’ @Alexandria Ocasio-cortez gets humiliated in Congress for asking dumb… https://t.co/tkAijbHwm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im gonna be in Miami around 4 o cock does anyone wanna have dinner/go w me to buy some clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathyco51278506 @SenateDems @SenFeinstein They should not support trump for anything he’s a lying pice of shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Young_Shootaa climbing the @StonyBrookWBB record-books  #AEHoops #SeawolvesUnited https://t.co/KN2FOY7yVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @VickiMDonovan She has a Boston College economic Degree🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 Raiders or 49’rs?? Since you in Cali and there’s no other place like here in Cali. #AskAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @IvankaTrump Who on here voted for her to represent the United states?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #samsunggalaxys10plus arrived yesterday and it has 4 different #livefocus modes, here's how they look #nofilter… https://t.co/57Ga0jYVwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing peaks, climaxes and gets the attention of a vc than a founder who stands up to the flakey VC.   VCs can’t a… https://t.co/52hWVr4eoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkLazerus The fries are the worst. To me, the burgers are just dry and bland. If we're talking fast food burgers, Five Guys is better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Camila_Cabello Karla Camila Cabello Estrabao is turning 22 today! I cannot believe ur 22!! Where does time go?!? https://t.co/2LRrOQDqsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[these poor ladies were waiting to cross the street downtown, this big ass truck blew smoke all over them. I kinda f… https://t.co/76uJinE5xL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna lie to you guys, this story that I wrote that’s been stressing me out because I had to wait basically… https://t.co/IQETVz2ZNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow's coming down, time to fire up the woodstove. @Adler_the_Eagle would hate my house #PolarVortex https://t.co/k7dtm3FaR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aminmlalani sharing that we need to call failure data in education and learn how to use this to positively impact… https://t.co/W8lHalELa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkNats2 Jeez, @Bharper3407 just go away! Boras has been blowing smoke up your rear end. Who cares what you get?… https://t.co/a4sBjtsMOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guardian @realDonaldTrump  I guess it takes a wacky nut job to out another wacky nut job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Mr_Yezzir @IamMathayus005 Bitch get tf out my mention cuz you sound stupid connect this fucking hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdouglass1969 @OWHnews I guess we are. Ours paper delivery person does that and we didn't ask. But, to each their own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @TimHayesGCSDSup to post the cover of one book I love every day for seven days and i… https://t.co/NO5MPFuQ0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake87__ Not watching tonight. I would just shut him down...he looks THAT bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday March 4 - Daily Yahoo!:     Republican calls out backers of the national emergency;       Alabama tornado ki… https://t.co/ysZlWKQulB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheComedyStore @troyconrad Happy Birthday Danny https://t.co/SHE6rgKsuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindacadena2017 Gracias igualmente Linda te deseo un excelente inicio de mes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel (@ Monaco Pictures for Captain Marvel in Disney Digital 3D in Huntsville, AL) https://t.co/2KnMZWfXDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosVictorM saludos desde NY ya hablamos d playoff? Recién empieza esto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias It's no coincidence, that DC, with the most expensive cost of housing, has  young representatives Wal… https://t.co/JE8P4t70F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawrenceBlock So angry with Dave and me that we haven’t put that word in Chuck Rhoades’s mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: I should start on this 10,000 word essay that’s due tomorrow.   also me:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGGYAZALEA When are we getting the album cover and pre order @IGGYAZALEA ❤️🔥💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember @rodneyrothman specifically telling me to watch Farley’s segment this night. Epic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewhoov @MarshaWarfield I'm curious what other words you would consider equivalent for this purpose? But I'm spea… https://t.co/iIGkO3lDLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @9_11_IsAnInside @AE911Truth @xrey1 @Boeing Who did the UN PISS off in Ethiopia? Details maestro, pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candidates be mindful that you will be running against the media in 2020 as well. Don’t take the bait on certain th… https://t.co/exE1bMEWzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent many many hours in the clouds listening to this album in college]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a tweet that said “one day all of your childhood friends hung outside for the last time and y’all didn’t even know it” 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[calling every billionaire a dick is a bit silly. every act is intended to gratify one's self; otherwise, why act? w… https://t.co/c4OMJXOxEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson  My wife and I went to go see captain marvel yesterday.  We both loved it. We can't wait to see you in the new avengers movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ella se pinta como lo que es. Una déspota que sólo necesita estar en el poder en PR para dar un salto socialismo y… https://t.co/IZ5qcO8zW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday mi gente hermosa @ Avondale, Arizona https://t.co/llsbXcMsJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harper’s Bazaar Kicks Off First Podcast With Olivia Wilde as Host https://t.co/h95T8sjn3Z via @wwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE BROWN EGG AND THE BAGUETTE SHUDDERED WHEN THEY MET THE NEW KID ON THE BLOCK. ........................a.........… https://t.co/hAnd0r9qly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieJayneC @DebbieTalks Holy smokes Debbie you sure are taking on alot. Becareful of burnout.. Humbdolt Strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillerMike @SusanSarandon @johncusack @ninaturner @CarmenYulinCruz   @BernieSanders will need @TulsiPress’s help 2… https://t.co/yYHXcWxLKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[apparently spotify makes playlists for horoscopes now and the taurus one is poppin’ and this lowkey made me feel be… https://t.co/fpRLssbMw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Thanks for always being a caricature of yourself. https://t.co/4Jmck1oGya]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to McDonald's and got a 20 piece McNugget, they hooked me up 21 nuggets and 10 sauce packets. I might go buy… https://t.co/YjN0Wsxrys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hot_tea_tod_dee 10 K, none of the above. The perfect toast is flipped twice during cooking to prevent one side fro… https://t.co/AMvBedO3Kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Boffin Despicable. They may claim they were just trying to be funny with their depiction of Luke, but then why… https://t.co/n0bzuYKWot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almostjingo @JerryNadler This recent quote to ABC News from Ty Cobb.  #WitchHunt https://t.co/qfSRZddFVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[1John 4:11 KJV—Beloved, if God so loved us, we ought also to love one another. No man hath seen…  https://t.co/LmfJT2msp4 via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @LindseyGrahamSC is a fool. Although this speaks to how many people he knows that commit crimes and cover them up with cash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit was epic‼️ Make sure you watch the full video on https://t.co/DaCBmVNjT2 📺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our danger is to water down God’s word to suit ourselves. God never fits His word to suit me; He fits me to suit His word. -Oswald Chambers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump Does everyone notice, every confrontation a Dem backed person,crowd,event, or media discu… https://t.co/yvvrBBxX0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Medford school district board of directors are currently discussing plans to find a new superintendent after Dr. B… https://t.co/fNyDBt5a3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[The smallest of teases for an amazing music video I helped on. Coming soon “Born for this” by Travis Sterling until… https://t.co/nL3UjI7z6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuidryMyles @JimCarrey You're already calling Jim Carrey a hypocrite, in which he's not. Jim isn't insane either,… https://t.co/TaVopg9YxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Macri @Buster_ESPN @ScottMillerBbl @lauraarmy @PaulHembo Who’s going to pitch ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would perhaps mean something if Republicans didn’t regularly accuse the Democrats of being the party of the KK… https://t.co/9bTegdrQXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m used to seeing @SIUEMBB getting embarassed on @SportsCenter but not @SIUeSoftball 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[A esta puta hay que colgarla de las torres de parque central y déjala ahí 5 días, para verla morir lentamente no se… https://t.co/lOZ18zV5xB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting anxious for the Chiefs to make some moves https://t.co/XZDX89cBeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheistRepublic I’m ashamed it took me a moment to realize the ridiculousness of this claim. I was stuck thinking… https://t.co/UIS8k3QuG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really does amaze me that my home town features eight Dunkin Donuts and some towns don’t have any]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolefischer13 I would have made a last-minute attempt to play the phrase off as “rooster headquarters.” #WorthAShot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr yo daddy pay off my loans I’ll vote for him next election 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL do have any insight on the broncos. Keenum? Own free agents coming back? Top target moving forward? I… https://t.co/4Wc9IoBisR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was @realDonaldTrump being guided by the hand of God when he raped the 13 year old girl? Did God want Trump to sexu… https://t.co/dbBhWk6RkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like the World famously known lyricist, author, and self-motivator #djkhaled would say “ Another One ☝🏽 “ @ Collect… https://t.co/ZmK7xiXNEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckeyeTalkPod @DougLesmerises or if y’all could kinda address this thread at all on the pod]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Saturday morning about to let @a1pretty_bscott get me looking good for this upcoming road trip. Grooming at it… https://t.co/4uBUL4HSXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackTonyStark_ @DocQB ! We just talked about this at the diner lol. Great post Ron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Glad people are waking up. Why disturb an enemy when they are destroying themselves?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chambleebrandel Is it possible that number will come up as we get further into the season and see longer roughs in… https://t.co/pDnavN6pGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It absolutely should not have KOMH had the best production of the entire show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Levity!  This is really good - Drinking a Medulla Oblongata by @LevityBeer at @levitybeer  — https://t.co/AIvdBzJIAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geteero I’m ambivalent about this. Color me cynical, but besides privacy concerns, I see this as a clear move by A… https://t.co/WFPlP2RQfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cuhris96 @RaidersBeat The guy has been BEYOND hating on this since the rumor started. Can’t wait 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my assistant Jake Burling, PGA @jmb_lnk for attaining your @PGAcom membership today at the nebra… https://t.co/4KyYd729GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yesterday I learned never to call security, “Gatekeepers”. They will immediately get offended, correct you that… https://t.co/vf1HMOQ4my]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROGRAMMING NOTE: (When) the Lady Bulldogs win on Wednesday at state 🏀 tourney, the Magazine game will probably be… https://t.co/8oeepnfV95]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t wait until I made it to New Orleans for Mardi Gras in March this year. I had to overnight it to DC. Than… https://t.co/Ku4iWQ24P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried online grocery shopping for the first time today and eff those people who say stores are dead. It was a fan… https://t.co/ugmT7hZ6hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottmci007 @SueBee1410 @CheriJacobus @ananavarro I would expect them to be hard on both sides. I will say, my all… https://t.co/zmErJvPbz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VivianGonzalez7 @wsvn #ClubViv it's never to steamy for South Florida 🌞🌦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriLeigh1012 HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! Let's meet up at a softball field soon! ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uclagymnastics @fish_hano @katelyn_ohashi @espn Let's go @uclagymnastics ! https://t.co/UiJAtQ4zzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leonlec Habla lo que pasa en la cancha no queremos saber de fake news !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBartholet @Romi_Rain @therealemyreyes @underthemoon177 Have you seen or spoken to Brooke Haze recently? I just hope she's okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a border wall, combined with other actions, makes great sense. But I get Paul’s point. Emergency Action wou… https://t.co/0JHXP0UqU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in a relationship and your partner is going to Rosarito this weekend just know you’re about to be single.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBI taking down college coaches. Guess the @NCAA was too busy cashing @marchmadness checks instead of oversight.]]></document></documents></author>