<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Niggas b walking round with $800 shoes and clothes but no vehicle or crib 😂 real life bum mentality]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stone Or (The unexpected Virtue of Ignorance) #ImproveAMovieWithOneWord]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Original KoJa, a satisfying fusion between Korean BBQ short rib - or kalbi (#갈비) - and a burger 🍔 Except instea… https://t.co/eUmspuDpLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Kathryn at @SenKamalaHarris office for compassionately listening to our stories about our children wit… https://t.co/CuUyFeyITy]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE GIRL WHO SHOWED UP TO FLICKER SESSIONS ORLANDO AND PRETENDED TO BE IN A WHEELCHAIR BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT THEY WO… https://t.co/fXto0oGUGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY CANT FITZ AND OLIVIA JUST MOVE TO VERMONT AND MAKE THEIR GODFORSAKEN JAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, I love this. Very few things make me happier than when the Avs beat the Wings. #GoAvsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twosidedcoin23 @DiapersOnAPlane @ExpatSnips @KaraDiDomizio @rollinwith_ @rollthere @thisbigwildwrld @sanityfound… https://t.co/ephL3X8WCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Municipal Drug Strategy: Lessons in Taking Drug Policy Reform Local https://t.co/zmCwGuQRSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[People flock here to enjoy these freedo.s but if the People you elect destroy those values and allow criminals and… https://t.co/9O2stOssSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for your journalism@talykrupkin. In Israel women must face a committee but my understanding is it almost alw… https://t.co/7OimDP3Tmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickWilming1 @laurrrelyse You like makeup that's cool ! I'm obsessed with @ABHcosmetics eyeshadow formula it's… https://t.co/oZdVtfnc2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irvingprimaryhp @SOMPatriots One of my favorites 📚 https://t.co/41mGSbjgjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eLiZaBeTh_R03 @hipcated @thvgcess @khloekardashian @jordynwoods I mean no use in staying here lmao you said what y… https://t.co/4avbxz75u4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy texted me so I replied. This guy really said wow I'm surprised you replied so fast it useally takes 2 to 3… https://t.co/QcPpg8m3Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen made his bed of deception he must lay in it.  We believe nothing from him now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyBurnsPR @Bulldogwgr So sorry this happened. Do you have a place to stay? #NoBoNeighbor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptd3001 There’s a very long list of Disney movies I’ve never seen and  probably never will #donthateme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristiancrespoj BIENVENIDO PRESIDENTE GIAIDO!!!!! LIBERTA PARA VENEZUELA!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch For some reason Democrats think whatever hateful, rude, illegal thing they do is ok...time to put them in their place?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHOtheCALL @JohnnyB371 The old saying....you made your bed, now lay in it, Muthana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SXSW key 🔑 themes: failing forward, pilot projects, human-centered missions, connectivity, storytelling through da… https://t.co/f1Ji8790Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t imagine missing an ex let alone wanting them back fuck that yall are wild and not in a good way]]></document><document><![CDATA[But since we’re still on the #yellow, has everybody noticed over 100k people can gang up in the same place in the… https://t.co/V5rX40woEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Don't  apologize for telling the truth...and I am a woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaannwert @Quickbeam2000 @theoneringnet @ElfitUmi @KamiBY2 @buddhistchick75 @LotrFanClub1892 @HappyHobbit1… https://t.co/sKxwyPEacB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to all of you and to @escott818 and @Tony Keefer for joining us tonight! #MarchBookMadness #TxLChat… https://t.co/nJlDIUbV4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SisterAct Finale did not disappoint! Talented young people on and off stage, amazing educators, dedicated parents… https://t.co/dr5iwVqPjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightfootForChi  Good morning, we're having our church's family and friends day program and would love for you to… https://t.co/sol3CTrvCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is me constantly trying to decide between “yolo” and “you need to chill hoe” 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. Another headline in the “what’s making you feel old today” category...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idea. A guide for basic grammar usage called Comma(n) Sense. https://t.co/Vxqj8WB08v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oajaramillo @tibehtblanco @pedroferriz3 @lopezobrador_ Qué interesante tu trabajo!! Las series de tiempo es algo q… https://t.co/D6RtlF6neH]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LWMcV brings some truth to Well! Clarifies that counting women who have used abortion services is government intr… https://t.co/vJsstouOc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addy_pez @RCSD @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @WomenPatrol Congratulations Addy &amp; Luis....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to accept this recognition as a Distinguished Star Partner on behalf of @ConsumersEnergy - supporting… https://t.co/Y2OLdWVu0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCSchembri @jaceyhill @hildemh Speak of Sign Languages, have you seen Bangladesh Sign Language? It had a mix of… https://t.co/vQgQq5IAy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic Employer!  Just re-qualified as Platinum Member Canada’s Best Managed Companies!! Congrats👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[This didn't turn out quite how I wanted. But it's still really cool! @ Lafayette, Colorado https://t.co/DwlMVNkO2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsoEsLoQueHay_ Si amigo, estuvo sabroso el desayuno 🥞 jejeje 🙋🏼‍♀️saludos cordiales]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally stranded in Biloxi 😭😭😭😭 I’m so tired like i just wanna go home and get in my bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inmates help rescue baby after dad accidentally locks keys in car https://t.co/TuIi8OHR68 https://t.co/if6VgslpFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoulder tat went from straight shatty to classy and I adore it.🤓 liked the *idea* of my beloved harry potter tat,… https://t.co/AZLnQ8dG7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God the majority of our U.S. population knows this is very wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lipstick Twins are getting some fresh hair! #hairday #baptizedin40volume #thelipsticktwins #andtwins #bleach… https://t.co/VJRVZE3Hts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twin Falls, exit 34 on I-90 east after North Bend. Official trailhead is at Ollalie State Park, and it’s a very eas… https://t.co/QTPGz3aYW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 18th to my sweet avid 10 tutor @emilyburr_ 🥰 love you beyond words and hope you have the best day ever💗💗 love… https://t.co/ouCyYL45Fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently waiting on my @ipsyCare pkg, like..🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼. I live in central Washington, under a “whole town shut down”… https://t.co/s5oF18NXLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people I went to high school with start following me on social media. We weren’t friends then, we aren’… https://t.co/jWMtl9flvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re gonna wish you’d realized how loved you were.  NO ONE WILL LOVE YOU MORE I ASSURE YOU.  YOUR OWN MOM SAID YO… https://t.co/CouM1wdshB]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that's missing is you! I'm hosting karaoke Friday night @ Torii's! Come sing on your favorite stage! Tiffany wi… https://t.co/bcLHfsYLAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, so hard to have so much money at stake that she can’t hold @POTUS @realDonaldTrump accountable.   Complicit.… https://t.co/e91tcoVPH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D0GSAREFAMILY I hope you actually love your dog and will make sure the poor thing is taken care of by a vet.  This is SO NOT FUNNY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d I wish i was getting paid for every time i RT you @gtconway3d —I seriously can’t hit RT fast enough on everything you say 🎯🎯🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far u have #LindseyGrahamSC #MarkMeadowsNC #RichardBurrNC #JimJordanOhio on #FoxNews defending the #POTUS.  Wher… https://t.co/s8CzY97OLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lacunalingua @weareoversight Sessions is an honorable man....unlike Holder who implemented the Obama Abominations Fast &amp; Furious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gingerson11 @realDonaldTrump How you as a woman can support this misogynous cheating borderline pedophile is beyond me. Shame on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erin: “It’s really hard to mess up making soup so..”   Me: “You set a lemon on FIRE in the MICROWAVE”  Erin: “FUCK… https://t.co/EpgMyAOGYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow and Sun #911memorial #coscobpark #greenwich #marchsnowstorm @ Greenwich, Connecticut https://t.co/cnX10RWmPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen Great, just wonderful...and that’s why there’s only 2 left!!?? 🙄🥺LEAVE MY CRUMPETS ALONE!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michie8 @Huchgirl @feuer1073 @kate_1980 @ClaireGowling @Carmenbatb @erika67392462 @MuseOlivers @danfaz94 @Leoclara… https://t.co/dxOj6z5hDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnRing16 @BetteMidler So basically if you took off your rose-colored sunglasses you would see the beautiful artwo… https://t.co/qjM5Jb24XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all all be liking the same cute ass baby pics so they pop up on my TL... I don’t need this in my life rn 😅😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isla, Sasha, and Olivia #diffeyewear #festivalcollection https://t.co/dkpRLZRxKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sexappealsaturdays #Hiphop vs. #reggaeton Everyone free before 10:30 Hosted by steveynewnez @ceofrenchie101  goldw… https://t.co/qlIXXHKBlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD Till next Friday! Have a good week #livePDNation https://t.co/4FBK6t8JmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am the worstttttt at forgiving i can’t bring myself to fucking w ppl again after getting done 🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoadtripC @loveGoldenHeart @beckworthandco @aftertheflash @JulesHalvy @FolderRed @monstervoyage @suziday123… https://t.co/bzfNSn3rYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt when I read that I thought “duh, both” and then saw your sweet tweet. #southernboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @kare11 Listen to other young adults who has lived under socialism! They have escaped to live in f… https://t.co/PkJoe5M2ZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIGHTING FOR MIGRANTS' RIGHTS TO ENTER THE U.S.A.---ILLEGALLY... Central American 'caravan' to end in Mexico City,… https://t.co/QXp7OWM94q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielmarven 1. That I would be arrested if I pulled those 'do not remove' tags off of pillows 2. Murderer's were… https://t.co/ISSLScU34T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheRaPrincess I’m an American born and raised.    Love my country no matter what !!!  Compassion ?    I have for e… https://t.co/FrZPTemkfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else try to figure out what you were going to be when you grow up based on Richard Scarry books? https://t.co/SaGoL7hDs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i LOVE all my guy friends to death. So many times I wanted to break down and y’all help just by making me laugh and… https://t.co/anUozhXn3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrronclark_ @KEVAplanks We totally did! You’ve never seen so many engaged middle schoolers!! ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need 2 bottles to myself bc i am pretty sure i am about to mf explode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition calls for Verdun to ban single-use plastic water bottles https://t.co/T1CB0bqFAE #MondayMotivations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping Angels 👼 💕 @ Rustica Lounge Bar &amp; Restaurant https://t.co/nT741SIlit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daltonorwig is talking about this “he said/they said” story this morning on #MobileMornings @fmtalk1065]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for @xPandora13xx in the MV Contest Spring Break Contest @manyvids https://t.co/uOwYJ7uMcx I'm on page 3. #211… https://t.co/kWGlbqy8Yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stabpossum @teekast7 @Matkaufman1220 @nypost @amazon @AOC It’s not just SDE. It’s PM and financial analysts and ot… https://t.co/AWcS4vEou4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @politico Nope and I’m sick of this clown getting to do what ever he wants with out Consequence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dave Bautista is a fellow Tampanian who apparently has a “tasteful man cave” not far from where I went to school. T… https://t.co/i6bER4t8jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommatzzie No... not like this...usually boring... President Trump will make 2019 4th of July GREAT!❤️🇺🇸❤️🇺🇸❤️🇺🇸❤️… https://t.co/z6IJnOKHa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pasó cuando murió mi abuelita. Vivía en Medellín y siempre que llegaba a Quibdò era el primer cuarto al wue entr… https://t.co/yzoFhopLje]]></document><document><![CDATA[God dammit i know ymaewk already did their last show ever but can they just reunite in Chicago once a year??? Or ev… https://t.co/X3t0SAbvDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it's not the right thing to do but I turn my face up at the person I catch staring at me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*behind the scenes*                        photo creds: my sis https://t.co/KO31dyKVgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickandMorty we’ve all made mistakes but I spent 10 minutes on photoshop making this specific one a reality. https://t.co/qAbU8eKd6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @JLeighSaucedo! #SanAntonioWomen #TogetherWeAreStronger #MentorshipMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got it in the mail it’s official God thank you I did this with your strength every step of the way. BLESSED .… https://t.co/0kNHkVyYcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CADualEnrollment opportunity for our programs to shine! @CADualEnroll @jfkmchs @fresnounified @DrKristaH… https://t.co/6yPPmaPrWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDPundit @LivePdFans Please have a professional teach Salinas PD what to look for in an aggressive dog. We hav… https://t.co/Gnx0YKYKSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar Is this true?  Doubtful, as Iran supports the agreement reached during the Obama administration and Obama… https://t.co/eYgv6t3Q3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxnflowerawsten @underscorebriee *insert me screaming after seeing Geoff*]]></document><document><![CDATA[You #45? Are Such a ##Idiot ❗️You do not Know What the hell you are doing or #Saying about our #USA ⁉️Ur The laughi… https://t.co/b8zLsTWfIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mile_Hi_Dave @realDonaldTrump More childish vulgarity and name calling from the left]]></document><document><![CDATA[The underlying dysfunction of this team is not discussed nearly enough. First, Draymond and KD, now Kerr and Draymo… https://t.co/RnQNbpMP7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko And how much are we (the taxpayers) paying her to hide from the WH briefing room?]]></document></documents></author>