<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[To the girl who said if she had a billion dollars all she’d buy is 10 dogs...  With the leftover $999,999,500 could… https://t.co/wQ62rSIB5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[why am i having a vision of my grandma in a club when she was younger and the crowd chanting “GO LINDA!” as she dan… https://t.co/62VhW8Mp55]]></document><document><![CDATA[do/bu was honored to submit to the Supreme Court an amicus brief on behalf of the Digital Justice Foundation and Am… https://t.co/1iRCAqEBcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio is seeing an increase in Hep A. Free vaccine today at columbus public health. https://t.co/ABTC3qjUPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriceHennings I think 2 weeks ago I saw they discovered the Hornet on the new. Sank in 42 at Midway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living that Bro Life.    3 sailors stationed at Ft. Gordon charged with rape https://t.co/H4WBKtzR9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would anyone believe it if I told them I taught this young lady how to do this in our Gymnastics unit?! What's your… https://t.co/C4Hq4gs0X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Israel does the right thing, and shows the world what you do with a “trump”. @netanyahu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long time no see.. Had to show my face since I’m gettin on here postin quotes @ Lake Providence, Louisiana https://t.co/Wjx9kRI9LM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve ese negocio esta generando $42 por hora ... @ajotac ponte pilas y compra un generador que la gasolina es gratis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Kamala is a MORON, and a liar,  Trump knows full well its the USA Birthday, as he knows that DC is  the  N… https://t.co/K57LoU94fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani "Generals for Bernie"? I don't think that not materializing is entirely a competence issue. No veterans… https://t.co/xJAdJYZC6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunkedTa I was tempted to hit the strip but I don’t want to fuck my week up early I got helllla work this week 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonSpurs @SpursOfficial Rumor that BHA could be the first match there. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is your mood you highkey sick in the head.... let me find out you or someone touching my grandma like that.… https://t.co/O7qP5qA2e3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chasalpha Oh.. How about Obama and that racist Lewis Farrakhan?  Let's start there https://t.co/GIA5QkRz2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud @joshgardner Not sure if this ranks as Shit, Good or both #ShitGood]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hay atajos posibles si queremos mantener un municipio con verdaderas condiciones de seguridad. Es entrándole de… https://t.co/eAa2v6oPe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit record producers Arif and Joe Mardin @ Atlantic Records, NYC https://t.co/tze98xyy4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HipHopRepublicans Criminal Justice Reform. America needs a National Incarceration Commission. Forget the Reparatio… https://t.co/gRO2XQgrU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikhinderer @domdelfino @NiranEC I don’t blame IBM, ink isn’t even dry on the merger. RH gets the FUD Broker award here. Sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del Frisco’s for dinner and Honey &amp; Butter for dessert 😍 Triple date night was splendid 👌🏻 https://t.co/kP2GC2e2Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg @MichaelKoman @BTuckertime @kenanthompson @nbcsnl @idriselba @Lesdoggg You are a LEEEEGENDARY COMIC!!! ❤️U Girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlivatiron That toe (?) sticking out in that particular area startled me for a second!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, liberals just ignore facts and act as if the facts (Truths) do not exist!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On god, shorty been done with that nigga, they just needed that storyline for the next season 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real G.O.A.T, Kareem Abdul-Jabbar,  memorabilia auction raises almost $3 million for his Skyhook Foundation… https://t.co/aJZjl283Ic]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump Presidential Twitter Library by @TheDailyShow might just be the best @sxsw showcase ever. https://t.co/jWsn6GoVzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[lakeshorechurchdorval  #lovethischurchfamily #connections @ Dorval, Quebec https://t.co/tqTxnS1iNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@01HM2 @ziyatong 2/2 This cat fight doesn’t end so well. Viewer discretion is advised.  https://t.co/PDN6VxsI2J via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we had the pleasure of celebrating my moms 90th birthday! She is a tremendous woman who is strong, wonderful… https://t.co/tuDp53fngj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slacker_ga01 @JoaquinCastrotx @POTUS Flush Castro https://t.co/QTgikwvZR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTodKelly @trizzlor @_mike_schilling @J_RtheWriter @vikrambath1 An equal chance at sitting in front. Jfc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Women’s Players Sue U.S. Soccer for Gender Discrimination https://t.co/rBJrgmBXLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewmorgcomedy Well I mean my entire generation keeps getting left out of survey results shown on tv so I can sympathize]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4568jan @calvin_knapp Now you are most definitely peaking my interests. Throw in some good eats yet, and where do I sign????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackroomSteve @stareinthesun I’m just imagining you wiping the tears from your face with one of the white ink scra… https://t.co/JjvhSHSwDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[VANTAGE CAREER CENTER Open House and Taste of Vantage - Monday, February 25, 5:00 – 7:30pm. Tickets to try tasty fo… https://t.co/tUzATBBIx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caranorth11 I knew Columbus was a hot mess of a town but didn't realize it was dirty too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizMcEwan3 @aterkel Also, isn't it ironic and predictable that the same people who rightly point to NYT articles h… https://t.co/kBh8gcO6yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSBreastCancer Hello my dear.  Good morning.  It's a brisk 41 degrees here in Mousetown!]]></document><document><![CDATA[College gives you false hope for a fulfilling life, but there’s nothing out here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewmorgcomedy The whole "choice" question has wasted incredible amounts of LGBT energy for decades.  It doesn't f… https://t.co/nNfiRXAoxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent two days curled up in the fetal position with the flu. Started feeling a bit better, opened up my work comput… https://t.co/5YDfFRSZgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonBream @LibertyMBB @ASUNSports Didn’t realize you went LU. I went in 94. My son is in The a Marines as well. Geaux FLAMES!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjandersonb22 I hope u come https://t.co/BHvg7KaxY7 the Broncos and give this new qb more weapons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been trying to use the restroom for like an hour but every time I walk in there's someone fucking there. Waiting for it to be empty]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should not be talking about credit recovery. Instead we should focus on learning recovery and more importantly, student recovery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have all the stuff to do and you're not here I really don't know what you're doing you're in big trouble don't p… https://t.co/MyxjPsL6Hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voici quelques clichés de mon meeting pour mon prochain projet.  J'ai la chance d'être entouré d'une gang de person… https://t.co/ULKRlMUATO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAgaggy63 @Loristalcup1 I got mine on EBay for $400. It retails for $1200.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the ‘72 set up for L.A.... (@ The Crossing Bar and Grill Worth in Worth, IL) https://t.co/UCtyf5PWpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look around your street and find the hydrants that need to be shoveled out. It takes less than 10 minutes, and coul… https://t.co/UhbSwVbRFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Innocent-looking enough, right next to the green but filled to the top with water. Hoping it'll stay together till… https://t.co/x3bZIM82q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Ted Lieu: Dear Alan Dershowitz: The 25th Amendment is the law. @VP and a majority of the Cabinet can invoke th… https://t.co/vacwOhg4IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhaledBeydoun I mean...he accomplished more than Matthew Stafford on and off the field...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the thinnest driest chicken I’ve ever tasted.  Very poor experience over all.  Sorry. https://t.co/97RKzo0Ci7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahh… https://t.co/rTCQHjkSdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byron_athletics calls another timeout with 1:34 left in overtime (the longest in the history of high school basket… https://t.co/4OTl05G0kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you call the Girl Scout cookies with the caramel, chocolate and coconut?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colby just stormed into a Casino shouting for Uncle Fester on IG Live and actually confronted Dana while he was gam… https://t.co/PO0WGr3iN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hurricane by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ Morristown, NJ — https://t.co/SCSnlaSjcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just the two of us! Spicer Selfies! #StaceysParents #MyGIANT #SpicersLoveLiveLifeTOGETHERThroughItALL @ Sheraton Im… https://t.co/VHdhUO2IVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today / Sunday: Woke up 🌤 Recycling ♻️ Donated clothes 👕👚 Organized storage 🧳 Lunch at Habit 🍔🥤 Costco 🥩🍖🥚 Worked o… https://t.co/lsx9LoBlUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inc.: Tim Tebow Just Told the World How to Handle Haters in 2 Brilliant Sentences. https://t.co/gFNxTrSXZ7  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broadway Joe and the auctioneer!! He is the man, came up to me to tell me what a great job I did. #respect… https://t.co/OhWclIJtUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you get a papercut, on your toungue, from a razor in a papercut...👅😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMCouch @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN Get off that crack you’re smoking dude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisperkins713 @sean_nettleton @TEVAchrisk @BryanBoock Safe to say it varies farm to farm ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyPlumpton @theScore Not actually sure what’s happening on this team. Or if he’s trying to motivate him. But Vlad is the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite that, Konosuba and Tensura are good wins! I may skip Promare if it conflicts with seeing みなみ though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rewatching “Punch-Drunk Love” for the first time in years, I am struck by how much the camera work and editing remind me of Tati.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreacherLawson #PreacherLawson #AGT @AGT #vegan https://t.co/5Ok2LMBUK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t been to eat at my restaurant @MMPitmasterBBQ , do your taste buds a favor and swing by. You won’t be… https://t.co/UYjd0LW5PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh vans workers say they ain’t for the bs!!! And he said the dude name was ray Allen😂😂😂😂 I’m dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely have to earn them. Don’t just show up and expect to get one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kbPp0BzJyy: JUSTICIA E IGUALDAD PARA KEIKO FUJIMORI - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/ogaQqsEi8j via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSullivan The Lions can’t draft, so yeah they are probably better off trading away picks for players that have… https://t.co/egLIWIXkrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reesetheone1 Yeah I think this is rather but they hammered Hillary over dumb shit so oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big respect for @terrycrews for sharing his opinions and convictions and being humble to listen. We don’t all have… https://t.co/xWkZn3ohzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewT61830774 @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow What is Intersectionality?- https://t.co/07pnsCfny6; #PragerU; #BenShapiro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamDevinV @Masala_Messiah2 @jblah3000 @Benaskren Jon Jones was a juco national wrestling champion and also a New Y… https://t.co/yMuge2U4E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryamSaleh @mehdirhasan @IlhanMN Rotten people that actually did kill others: James Earl Ray, Sirhan Sirhan, Timo… https://t.co/E0TuO7sN7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/oDnxwXLb2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Time Change Is Hitting This Morning. I Hope I Adjust To This Quick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have A Wonderful Safe And Blessed Day On Purpose Everyone God Bless @ Baltimore, Maryland https://t.co/16dbzLiYvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How nerdy am I? I saw this and found every pattern I could. The total # of digits=digits of squared # *2, and the 8… https://t.co/EuUMxga3MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @foxandfriends @FoxNews I appreciate these warnings. I can cruize channels &amp; avoid nausea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dropbox They're getting inspiration from @Dropbox Twitter postings… https://t.co/H89lGOhEZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bullying Ben How Benjamin Franklin Overcame Bullying...The Video #bullying #benjaminfranklin #StopBullying… https://t.co/TfpzDYKo0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NifMuhammad I do the same thing for Atlanta cups and they were the only thing in the house I put a protection orde… https://t.co/RTv7NFP92D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course you're correct. The world will NOT end in 12 yrs. Suspicions are more than half of #GreenNewDeal is unach… https://t.co/gX8zBH5GKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch Stand up America against liberal leftist George Soros ❤️🇺🇸🎚]]></document><document><![CDATA[CD sale! #fenwickbooks  #leonardtownmd @ Fenwick Street Used Books &amp; Music https://t.co/qvpynpk4GY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauriis_c @gaaby__cm Idek Nigel on a personal lvl, but I was thinking about him]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DIAV #VDAY 🇻🇪⭐️🇻🇪 VENEZUELA LIBRE!  Pedro Jose Chirinos Dorante, Coronel del Ejército Venezolano en la ONU, se sub… https://t.co/KLJ6A3TFc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Ferrari just got me at the light.. Just another day on the Cape ferrari @capecodinsta @ Marstons Mills, Massac… https://t.co/37finfEXHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlimAlmighty @NEXALMIGHTY @_greeenteeea Make it stop!!! 🤦🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/bbVtMIvf95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@absolut_joe @GavinNewsom That would be dumb,the homeless don’t vote democrat, the illegals do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Trinitarianism is a gift of revelation before it is an achievement of the church.”  Fred Sanders (@FredFredSanders… https://t.co/odj2CQuf8D]]></document></documents></author>