<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[not overly sour; not overly impressed either. - Drinking a Boysenberry Tart Ale by @TroegsBeer @ The Midtown Tavern… https://t.co/2s4lui5G7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage preshow. Ah, fate... #MaryQueenofScots #ThreeElizabeths @ComplexHwood https://t.co/eXHViJMNzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[7) Chairman @RepCummings @OversightDems  @GOPoversight @freedomcaucus as an American Citizen, I respectfully demand… https://t.co/3RVvGMhKt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coffeespoonie I hear ya and agree. I catch myself saying 'sorry' in place of 'excuse me' in similar situations whi… https://t.co/CZxT5SuaSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@necianat how much is it, how much are you selling it for and when does it have to be used by]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids from Club Encore wish you all a wonderful spring break! We will see you back on March 18. (Club Encore was led… https://t.co/MVIToZzlv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@americnhumanist And I’m sure the american “humanist” (cough cough) would be thrilled if it was based on Satan or w… https://t.co/9jzRHeI5f0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eldiablo0786 @loveGoldenHeart @1228erin @alexdomelle @Lisandre_Moreau @pkamla1 @coachmekat @reeves5150… https://t.co/RYY4tRTbJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom You don’t speak for me. Why don’t you try to make improvements to California instead of making it a $hithole!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate Harry cropping me out of this pictures, as I was wearing rollers 😂 We love you Georgie!!! Best of luck… https://t.co/mdqjGrdO9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristiWalling @CherubNation @bionicanadian @DansoyGomez @eagle2186 @justfara @Light4ASD @CharlotteKent20… https://t.co/F3xlrjKBUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up bright and early in #indy for the #pltwsummitindianapolis    What a view! #jwmarriottindianapolis @ JW Marriott… https://t.co/rzv3fCORBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I was proud to join thousands of other @txstatepta  members to march on the capital and rally for our childre… https://t.co/5pUBxD8wYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[...is in the air. #love #itisasign #specialmoments #venturablvd #iloveLA #moreplease @ Ventura Boulevard https://t.co/qDMu49VNHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shinedown Awesome concert last night. It was epic. Thank you, guys!! ✊😍🤟]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @ginger_teach82 to post the cover of one book I love every day for seven days and in… https://t.co/R2zBuriesD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 I hope you all brought tum's with you as you had to watch this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaKTVU @KTVU Tip of the iceberg. Kaiser gives doctors kickbacks 4 non-treatment of patients. All of healthcare h… https://t.co/3aAmiLKBhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing that boudoir shoot was the best thing I probably ever did. Social media is the best. That’s it I’m happy. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The brats are running their mouths &amp; the house...while Momma Pelosi makes excuses 4 them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robjh1 @marthamaccallum - Ms. MacCallum was on fire last night. Oh by the way that black top was very nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlo731 @LakePointeOwls @Novel_Effect @BeamanReaders I used Novel Effect too!!😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaddathree I’m dying to see it!! Is it gorgeous? https://t.co/2GDIQzuMyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @marlonawalker, update on annexation legislation that's of interest to those watching tax dollars and boundary… https://t.co/m2LJan7Cii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morbrem Hi, I’m a reporter with The Sun. I’ve been trying to find people who might have known this man. Would you… https://t.co/Mr5a36zwjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling some fitgurlmel vibes... hair and all 💁🏽‍♀️💪🏽 ... #bodybybrie yes I made that a hashtag briannasmithfit  .… https://t.co/04AjONAOHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanted you to watch me dissolve, slowly, in a pool full of your love ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what I’m doing with anything and I’m so lost and bored and tired]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get sad every time Isabel goes out of town ☹️ and I don’t even see her like every other day when she is here. Does that make sense ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen so many who are angry at the parents in Abducted in Plain Sight obviously y’all didn’t watch the doc 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrueschuh @krassenstein @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 @JohnBrennan @RepAdamSchiff @RepMaxineWaters @ericswalwell Stated*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important information for @LongRealty @TierraAntigua @tucsonrealtors_ !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabionPicheco He is now that he's going to the Big House now...and the jurors are going to witness protection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Nevadans we are lucky to celebrate #InternationalWomansDay by celebrating the inspiring women that make up the f… https://t.co/l53CxLdEcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmycthatsme I loved Thunder Road. Thank you so much for answering my question 😁 🎬]]></document><document><![CDATA[$VYST LOW FLOATS MAKE BIG MOVES BOTH WAYS!  Remember it took only 1/3 the amount of shares to go Up then it did to… https://t.co/F34FETFsgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super thankful for @ChaleneJohnson, @bretjohnson11, @seancannell, @kkrummenacher, @jjvirgin, @steveolsher,… https://t.co/3Z63aG2WWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bschapiroMD @solarpulse7 Food for thought!  I wish @GOP and @NRA had a conscience!  Perhaps it would do something… https://t.co/v4vvRwAL97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studio visit chez Manuel Esnoz 💥✨⚡️ . . . manuelesnoz #artist #painting #studiovisit #contemporaryart #greatartists… https://t.co/Jv4bkiO3Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! So can you be home right after work? We need to leave as soon as you get home @ Wisdom Tree https://t.co/sNwuCkfTp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late tweet. I don't even care for the song Shallow and I cried at the performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5_0pac Right. David was in the Van Essa trying to put his jacket and backpack on when his balloon flew out and he… https://t.co/GqSBGtESz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever feel like it’s taking FOREVER to reach your goals? Is it possible that procrastination is at least part… https://t.co/7Wu2KUYsqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReyPerez21 @nahudotorg You’re not even here and you are promoting!!! Miss you!! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked out of work with out my purse.... and got all the way home before I realized]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best things about @GraceandFrankie is all of the guest stars from childhood television and films https://t.co/mboosk2gGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC No, he meant "I didn't need to do this" bc you could have done your job. Common sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FierceCheerMom @CHEERSPORTCorp I have no skin in this game but it’s nice to see. There will always be complaining… https://t.co/tcwyIZ5BQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[to this day my mom will not let me live down the moment that i ran into her room after seeing on tv that michael ja… https://t.co/TsGd8bUzt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder twins powers activate!!⚡️⚡️ After a kickass run including sprints and stairs. 11 total miles today. Cancer i… https://t.co/nQ0MMfz4aC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week's #52weeksofhome Is "looking up".  When I read this I immediately thought of the sign in the hatch door t… https://t.co/ixwz5KbvPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turkish Eggplant Pie vegetariantimesmag  #turkisheggplantpie #eggplant #creativevegan plantstastebetter #pie… https://t.co/JZ6NYNTXve]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Circa 2013  C.A.T.WALK Boutique sidewalk sale featuring a new Tory Burch sequin dress for $25.  #sale#warehous… https://t.co/2FpVzyaq6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamattingly @realDonaldTrump I think his mother called him #verystablegenius and his father called him #orangeclown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialUHWBB @doribranche I am so proud of you Doro and Good Luck this weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luke5sos can you follow me back to make me happy please. i need you :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessmichaelsbks I hate when that happens! I know I have some treasures waiting for me in the yard from last week,… https://t.co/pJr2qDDQ6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok y’all, my cousin who’s a 7TH GRADER just shot from NBA range. Yes, I’m bragging 😋 @ElishaRogers24 https://t.co/t89FddPnsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[And see Esi Edugyan live at #Congressh at @UBC on June 2 as part of this year’s #bigthinking lineup! Check it out:… https://t.co/7u5Y8ScFL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls night is always a plus with some amazing girls 💝 https://t.co/Vp9PAFEU7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osoriochong Hilda Flores gracias x todo el apoyo siempre brindado sagrada familia bendiciones somos PRI saludos https://t.co/4echqXBLOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I have discovered the secret to hearing news other than Trump on #CNN. Watch at 4:00AM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I don’t want to hear one peep about kids being separated at the border from the same party that al… https://t.co/V1AeqwHUqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao so out of touch and delusional I cannot believe the nonsense I was texted this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica @donlemon  they say you get the face you deserve.  Isn't Don handsome? KellyAnne...hag.(because she's one nutty bitch)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amstefano988 He killed Earl so he could move on and write more songs. You need to have @jimmantel tell you the whole story! He knows it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told @MckenneyKHOU that it’s #NationalLoveYourPetDay and he popped up this picture of his 15YO chihuahua named Ch… https://t.co/eRKpTFHz8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcorippo @dhabecker @alicekeeler @MrVaudrey @robertkaplinsky @KevinMonsma @mavenofmath I would say “with Ts co-pla… https://t.co/yDzpDtVwsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if Kyle secretly recorded Dummer blackmailing him into marriage so after the surgery he can get it annulle… https://t.co/zscasyNzRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rest of the days Daddy-Daughters adventure. @ Six Flags Over Texas https://t.co/dp417hCSke]]></document><document><![CDATA[LSU tried to stop me, but jokes on them, I still got a ticket and will be in even more orange since they ticked me… https://t.co/mainN1hLSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[gasty rompia las bolas con q queria laburar urgente  y hace 10 horas que entró a un tbjo y no lo dejan ir jajajajjajajajaj, labure hijono]]></document><document><![CDATA[My skin is SOOOO BADDDDD lord help me that once a month curse is miserable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stolen bases: 5..... someone ate his cheerios this morning!! Well done @Jumungi_Soriano ........omgeeeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me get this straight, newcomers is the new word for illegal-I mean -undocumented? Changing the word does Not ch… https://t.co/qds8gKJ40H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 47th Birthday to my guy! Like you said..You are 2 years old with your new heart! https://t.co/6XYxfqSFyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom’s chicken was killed and Evan legit just said “oh um sorry for your loss?” I’m dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a solo podcast without YOH because he’s busy with his personal blog (and also seemingly has no interest in it… https://t.co/NDXlaDirsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[me sinto bem flopando na internet porque isso começou a acontecer quando eu parei pra VIVER ao invés de dedicar muito tempo a minha imagem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonalds I’m at the store in South County St Louis on Telegraph and all the employees are yelling and cussing! Li… https://t.co/ymWEvzYPgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone should go back and take a look at the cases “Judge” Jeanine worked on. A person who thinks like she does is… https://t.co/Z7aPrk0LXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @krassenstein Agree! Fox is like the Home Shopping Network of politics. Literally, sales of an ove… https://t.co/pl5pVgxYcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[As my mom calls it, End of the Land! @ Lands End https://t.co/f83HEVfeWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake Welcome to the conditions in which I launched my own business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i ate some hot cheetos and 2 of those cupcakes that be in the vending machine and a morning bun today . DAS IT!! I need to eat healthier 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[pulled a muscle in my neck doing literally nothing. god i love being an adult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ughhh gusto ko tapon phone ko. bakit ka gnyan Lee Jong-Suk??? 😭😭 grbeee ang pogi mo😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[That of course is good we want safe vaccines. But if you think vaccines are bad talk to someone who was a mother in… https://t.co/wWibtATwRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protect Your Possessions with Suitable Window Caulking Service https://t.co/E93plnqquI #Windowcaulking… https://t.co/jwH2xrdQx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to travel period. 😩 California, New York, Jamaica, all of that. #Jackson_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porter notes he struggled with reading but was fortunate to have support system. Other kids don’t. “There are no ca… https://t.co/xKF4DXh7mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleeFrosta28 @epifer99 That’s what the word from the top used to be. It changed around the time that KASL took on the program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dp_moriarity OMG - 💯 me. I promise it’s on my list, @EllmanLauren... I’ve had it open on my desktop for dayysssss.… https://t.co/9IoD4RqXbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told myself I wouldn’t do my own tattoos anymore but fuhh I want new ink 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant agree more. Ive seen one girl cancel late appointments, but be 2 hours behind lol. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend most of my time in the mornings praying that I can keep my faith and wits about me on 485]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @realDonaldTrump I don’t think my head can handle much more of this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevthkid The shrill voice! HERE WE GO! WERE GETTING CLOSER. Man you sure used a lot of characters to tell me you hate women tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sweet baxie crossed the rainbow bridge this morning, so blessed to grow up and have this sweet boy by my side fo… https://t.co/RcCzO9oboL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m exhausted.... I swear I love my sweet Wednesday!!! My floors have never been so clean yet so dirty at the same… https://t.co/mZKZoezKMv]]></document></documents></author>