<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Great energy throughout our classes this past week. We're looking forward to having you join us at the Penobscot Ba… https://t.co/UhslMabCBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Champagnephilly In fact as Im catching up my TL is appears that its an untrue rumor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una lloradita y fuga! (@ Mesas de Trabajo in Monterrey, Nuevo León) https://t.co/QCo7FjvgiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL from @BaierlIceCmplx   (2) @_Mars_Hockey 1 vs  (3) @FRPantherSports 2  Shots: MA-38  FR-18 #PIHL #PLAYOFFS AA… https://t.co/nRplhbIenu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite a bit of rise since yesterday! Could likely go over top later this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinaNadia @MrsTyler78 @DandMe_MomOf5 @Dapple_TXUSA @judyohtweets @LifesStyleBlog @RichP222 @riapanacea… https://t.co/ssmg6Ny7Dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was fun!! #fitleaders give this a try 👊 #EmbraceTheChase #boycottaverage #Align #4amcrew @fit_leaders… https://t.co/VZoP3bh4XH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ, listening to @Timcast on Rogan is excruciating. It’s like: dude, twitter is not a public service. You… https://t.co/UBJfrNk8A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronSopchak @DomiNateFF @aaron_schill @therealNFLguru @ffdynasty_ztp @tacitassassin13 @RyanMc23 @TimNFL… https://t.co/XszfuyQlzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrbish You know I don't share your love of Joe Lieberman. We talked about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTM_DRE Appreciate it bra 🖤💉✊🏾 can’t wait to see you back on the field dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillieKayWWE I really wanted you both to win, especially after that Super Amazing pin combo that you both did.  #bestteamever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverAgeTV @RealGilbert @RealGilbertACP @Franksantopadre Happy Birthday Robert]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: I T’D UP THE STROLL OFF ILL BE POSTING MY DANCING VIDEOS TOMORROW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Let the gop show their true selves to the American people and let nature take its course. The more these co… https://t.co/e5jo4vq65T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanxpinto 80/20 rule.  Expend 20% of your energy to become 80% proficient in things you’re interested in. Thi… https://t.co/jK6M5OfMcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im v angry at terfs right now. I dont understand how SOMEONE ELSES identity affects u at all. If ur gay and attract… https://t.co/g65mxU3BNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[NLE: Phillies NLW: Dodgers NLC: Cubs WC1: Cardinals WC2: Nats  ALE: Yankees ALW: Astros ALC: Indians WC1: Rays WC2:… https://t.co/WSZLMGAXac]]></document><document><![CDATA[America, you know you have a preference.  I want to know if you’re right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sykehm every so often i forget that that this exists and then when i do the timeline curses me with its memory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hasbiyallaahu laa ‘ilaaha ‘illaa Huwa ‘alayhi tawakkaltu wa Huwa Rabbul-’Arshil-’Adheem .  Allah is sufficient for… https://t.co/aZReTDx4Dx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callmebailey89 @urbangaygriot I’m just showing support. https://t.co/KQCIZrzADQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber builds an app with pinpoint accuracy on where I am (live view) and where I’m going. Yet, every damned time..… https://t.co/QxJ0WgajAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The TaleSpin fireworks segment almost fits into a minute. Almost.  #talespin #disneyafternoon #fireworks… https://t.co/PrV4syJTyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeambs @thumbelulu Non-response? Speak for yourself. Stats were from 2016 U.S. Census, nothing from Wikipedia. T… https://t.co/I8bqNg6nlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renate1217 Happy Wednesday Renate! I would not want to meet him along the trail. No events?! How can this be?? Enj… https://t.co/NCZP4oHbT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And none of y’all believed me when I said that the game has out played the dude after Ready Player One. The future… https://t.co/yaYSbB4gmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to trade in your flip phone and standalone GPS for an all-in-one smartphone.  Or you could go back to printing… https://t.co/2vLwtxWt3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤞🏼Hoping to bring a little luck tonight 🤞🏼 timberwolves #AllEyesNorth @ Target Center https://t.co/WqSnMpiIbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean I actually have to deal with another 2 years of @SenSanders ? I think the fuck not 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BSoMT_2018 @thunderworksgam There's never anything wrong with more Roll Player goodness!  Just wait until the Frie… https://t.co/4OQjvP9CCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You must be really stupid Eugene. Anti trumpers like you use Twitter as a forum to laugh… https://t.co/zQZoYeVkGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy that being homophobic is just supporting white supremacy and so many homophobes are oblivious to that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trom771 Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@narvaez_jordan @AlonsoDT Ni hablar ya de miras al siguiente partido pero cae alas cheves joto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen darling.  Sometimes you're Cinderella. Sometimes you're the slipper. Just lost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: I have accepted a challenge from @FrankMirandola to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no revie… https://t.co/GsYNSWyLL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchYourRepsMN I cannot imagine there was proper oversight of internal controls.  If it receives a rating of good… https://t.co/XG8z1toLYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m out here looking at art while drinking French wine and listening to live jazz. You broke bums can’t even spell… https://t.co/x3D65nuO60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a lot to be seen this morning as electrical is overheads are empty and shelves are filled, great job Mike P.… https://t.co/DTh7hd46cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just WOW!!! Absolutely love the University of West Florida. Great weather, great day of training, great coaches, gr… https://t.co/j1XG2C0OTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeeganMatheson AA needs to show something soon and Dalton needs to keep on spinning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradKrysko That’s awesome.  I knew the real blash was hiding somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyJohnson_Jr Hey TJ I hope that won’t affect you next weekend at Phoenix? I’ll definitely see you at Gainesvill… https://t.co/LpV16m0XFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My International Women’s Day Squad 💕👌 christineposa psunde nola_sunde  #iwd2019 @ International Women's Day https://t.co/YHigfdPkhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pretty_0dd Ah, was gonna say as long as it's not Orlando you should be fine. The coasts are cooler in the summer. Central FL is an oven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I think I’m gonna hurl!” “Don’t hurl! If you hurl, I’ll spew!” “Ha ha ha. But seriously, we said goodbye to so man… https://t.co/T1HAVM59d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people are just crazy.   Tesla driver appears to be sleeping in car as it travels down California highway https://t.co/17mNVtV07g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakehirsch77 @jzharmon1 @ForecasterEnten Are you kidding? Obama's Iraq position was the *only* thing most voters knew about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today on The End Zone...NFL news and notes plus guests  @Gbradbury_11 and the Godfather @Gil_Brandt "The Bee Team"… https://t.co/660v4UA12Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SantaMonica The Global Home of the #Royal #Crown Brands. 👉🏻🥇👑💙🙏🏻👈🏻 #Rulethesand #Repost @bvnevents with download_r… https://t.co/t6PlDulyM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Oh wow!!! 3 yrs for $30,000,000. Not bad! I'd like that job, is he hiring? Criminal in Oval Office, criminal J… https://t.co/bYDdtcaiKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBK: Congrats to our Northeast Inland All-District AP selections @charliehenegar, Mason Higgins, @BiggsBryce24,… https://t.co/FI9JFuxsug]]></document><document><![CDATA[August Alsina was in that video crying and I felt every bit of pain that man has. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Onate_Inc  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist 🇨🇦🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LjHaupt Here in California it's difficult to accept that a majority of Californians recognize the danger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveLaurence I love your tits now much better. Fake tits are ugly. I was watching a few clips of yours on the hub.… https://t.co/yMDmrWX78b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shortguy @CoryCouture67 @MarvelEntCA no im saying those most likely to interview you for your movie are white male… https://t.co/DiDpSkHyGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Military to Permanently Cancel Large-Scale Exercises on Korean Peninsula https://t.co/M4dhBVtAu5 via… https://t.co/DVE4VCteoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re opening for @lsnrocks this Saturday night at @roxrva. No cover. Show starts at 9pm. We had a blast playing wi… https://t.co/UrXTCDfBA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LookingBeyond2 @johncheech @USMNT_Watch @herculezg What choice when nobody has bothered to contact him, what about… https://t.co/31S23pp4Vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes in an 🤕 injury case, it makes sense to “structure” a client’s tax-free net recovery under 📂 US Tax Code S… https://t.co/n9R43UB05p]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have created this company to help small and medium businesses survive against big stores. We are a discounter fo… https://t.co/qcUDfNknMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would be a wonderful Christmas gift to Santa Mark, if Mueller released the report right before… https://t.co/qsdTM5x8Pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffschecter @KevinMKruse I think talk radio was doing it successfully before FOX went on the air, so there wasn'… https://t.co/NGgInLeWs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligatory trip to @PintsPub in #Denver managed to get a snap of the tiny bit of the U.K. in @Colorado https://t.co/zRDhxdrk2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cougzzzz No. Bottom 3 finish. Again. What does a win matter when the season was lost weeks ago? Every win now is a… https://t.co/UKnzPNLNdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[toughman 2k19 night number one was a night to remember https://t.co/Dnmr6CYvRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[He who sings prays twice (@ St. Gregory Barbarigo R.C. Church in Garnerville, NY) https://t.co/EAlvzk37FS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for them. Their programs suck so badly that even I felt bad their uniforms were so bad too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como cuando vuelves hablar alguien especial y sabes que algo bueno hiciste 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crampell First, they came for my neighbors...who are assholes, so I thought: "Go ahead, take them!" Wait, does that make me terrible?]]></document><document><![CDATA[More @sambassartist items for sale at the North Carolina Racing Hall of Fame. #SamBassTribute #NASCAR https://t.co/JbwmmTUN9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sierraveza by @SierraNevada @ The White House — https://t.co/tABZGK2sym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajackson You’re telling me that he will face no negative consequences and people will forget about it in a week? That can’t be right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsolomonReports That about covers all the liberal leftist idiots who think a 40 years Friend and Attorney Lanny Da… https://t.co/a9A0VrUa3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnDelahanty Daniel Gibson’s three point rating had to be a solid 115]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP #RogerStonedtotheBone #cukoldRoger #ImpeachTheMFTraitor #realDonaldJethroTrump… https://t.co/f84zPOXqGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deaanuh_ @Almighty_Quinta @JSTJR @papasandbeer @JusCollege @alfreddterence @A_Gomez26 @Stefanieniee @kawenjasmine… https://t.co/sguCRoivIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYSportsBiz Yes seriously. They dont call him Creepy Uncle Joe for nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPS still failing miserably. nobody knows where my package is, when its getting here and i'm sitting here like o_O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenZarra Yeah switching is scary, but I think Canon is finally realizing they need to catch up to Sony in the… https://t.co/25MUwS8Yag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Above1stBase_ Titles were won with Stick’s strong farm system and free-agent fill-ins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XGamerPC @NVIDIAGeForce @TEAMEVGA @EKWaterBlocks @EVGA_JacobF https://t.co/8ybuFQQtmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Baby girl not so little any more lol @ Glenwood Roller Rink https://t.co/2bCht78F0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVCabChronicles On one hand he would save a ton of cash the other hand they will break up anyway. My son had the s… https://t.co/DCCG4N296E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Happy19111 @KeithDB80 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/QE0h9kCdvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pitching to 9 yr olds in a cage with no net. What could go wrong? https://t.co/4yPv7GKZLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NStewCBS2 Still nothing but a few flurries in the far southeast corner of Iowa City. 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teleSURtv Que tambien hagan un planton en la embajada de Cuba para pedir la salida de todos los militares cubanos… https://t.co/I0c5TvPA6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter outrage addicts just learned who John Wayne was apparently? Fucking morons. Invent a time machine to go wag… https://t.co/zX2A8EwJo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that tool isn’t on Spotify is the real national emergency, not the fucking southern border]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Corinthians 7:10 (NLT): For the kind of sorrow God wants us to experience leads us away from sin and results in s… https://t.co/tlfNPFCDIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ @eloiseblondiau It is not a sin yo be transgender. Organs are modified, not removed, for the health of the patient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to the gym right after work is the move - just an extremely exhausting one. It's almost Nap:45 though, and I'm excited. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[These squalls are playing havoc with the roads .. #ONStorm #QCStorm check @weathernetwork for highway conditions +… https://t.co/Rhkmm37L4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardhouz13 @Lalaluv420 I won’t wear any of them. If I want my brain fried I’ll stick my head in a microwave and hit the button.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sorkness_troy @TMbakwe32 He was ok in HS much better in college and pros]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit I can be a real asshole at times and it makes me feel like shit :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KC4UTM I hope you get a ticket for not parking in your designated spot.]]></document></documents></author>