<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Wax_Trax @VeloCloud Awesome! Thanks, I’ll take a look and share with our team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pastor @vancepitman speaking the words of drtonyevans so inspirational.... @ Hope Church LV https://t.co/R2Tx2ewviF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sudsy911 I'm a Staal guy so I'm glad he stays. It's refreshing to see a guy WANT to stay in Minnesota. I hope he c… https://t.co/Q6Z4XhPAgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My takeaways for #SXSW2019 trends— AI, immersive, inclusivity, intersectionality, CBD-infused everything, e-scooter… https://t.co/UCljXDv1QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Tuesday dart leauge! We are at the Tilted Kilt. Not really a dart bar. They have two free standing boards. Sma… https://t.co/jhNjpKXWeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShotsRangOut @ValeriePrimros4 @SpeakerPelosi @TheDemocrats @DrSueDVM @lenlucas46 @tgradous @ChgocadChic… https://t.co/cuo0RVpPQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oskarmelia "no hayas". hay que escribir correctamente, mas si es para criticar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@NHLCanes⁩ ⁦@CanesOnFSCR⁩ ⁦@WRALSportsFan⁩ it’s Sun☀️ day! https://t.co/XdgIrRudGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is a school day in life you choose whether you want to listen or not        Happy Saturday Over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dale's Pale Ale by @oskarblues @ Golden Hill — https://t.co/ehPdnKPhpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the Lady Eagles today!! Congrats on the dub at state!! Excited to see what @jenessa_hasty and @KaeRobey wi… https://t.co/B6oHh0vVZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brief appearance oSerial killer Samuel Little is drawing his victims for the FBI https://t.co/eAlf7waC7f via @NBCNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_curtis30 @Grand_MasterM I know a couple of neighbors said that when I moved in on my block lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaabreu610 @NoMayoNoRanch @djinnome @EduQuinn @sambcoltrane @mj_lee Tuition is elective. Hurricanes are not. Also,… https://t.co/VS4hD9aMul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie The #DNC rigged the primary against the American voters who wanted @SenSanders . We #DemExited because of… https://t.co/1146Gwyk3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSmit69151889 @RidgeOnSunday @SkyNews @simoncoveney @SophyRidgeSky Ireland is being civilized. It’s the UK that’… https://t.co/D9NXQL24m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week at the Speed! Kentucky bourbon meets French Bordeaux. https://t.co/T5kG7us0Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen from Gylenhaal sweet goal 5-3 Germantown 4:00 left in 2nd @SCHBlueDevils]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattengdahl @UMassHockey No question even when they play bad they’re really good]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also started covering state Charter Board mtgs, and I @FarnsworthEddie was on an agenda to get an ok to sell his… https://t.co/27AqMoRCYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganBDaniels I wanna know how you knew I live like 4 seconds from that Howell Mill Starbucks? 🤔 Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Thursday to all. Wish it was Friday, but that's just me being greedy. Have a great day everyone!!… https://t.co/dOpQZGepoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason imagration never got solve, because of the republicons have always twarted it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachEJDawson @1runninX I think you would be surprised at the number of late birthdays or kids who started school… https://t.co/26QC5H8i27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryCrnobrnja @RobertLusetich @bhughesgolf yeah, but the club head is not a free body which is the trouble I have w/ the KE = KE analysis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[roy nelson is sponsored by Rico’s Cheese so i’ll watch all of his fights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan hear hear    Whoever tgat was    Waste of time    Important hearings on border issues nominees it shoul… https://t.co/mnZaUDb1J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como que le sabe a eso de las fotos... en Zombie Fest https://t.co/FB7SQNeoK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wimill05 @briciosegovia @IvanDuque Títere? Mirese al espejo #PetroCatrehijueputa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmateus @LaurenBaratzL @TheEliasRework @DNC Fuck Yeah! https://t.co/dyk7Oo5tUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @MaryMcDonnell10 @BetteMidler @RobertGBeckel watch this video this is sickening but UCB looks other way unle… https://t.co/O1cMOc9iNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakeosbornee They have walk up kiosk it took me like 20 mins when I got my I’d last birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[El amor no se condiciona, tampoco se pide, el amor es un sentimiento que nace para ser entregado en su más pura ese… https://t.co/cJtHnmPKsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once thought there was a possibility that the Becky Lynch storyline was just so straightforward and so simple tha… https://t.co/uCiHndm7qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobtheberto What would they explain as the reason we can’t see Tulsa with a telescope from OKC? lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For real, though, plants can make your living space or office space feel brighter and more alive when everything o… https://t.co/ts2LqxjcQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyJoyce44 Hahaha did you really hear that or are you just breaking balls?]]></document><document><![CDATA[CEREAL &amp; INSOMNIA #AboutLastNight #cereal #insomnia #Tattooart https://t.co/tqd5wbOODw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Gavin, are you able to prove that the weather is statistically different than it has been in the last… https://t.co/HVjeqCjGrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m an aggressive pisser, if I see u using my fav urinal ima push u aside mid stream n finish where u left off 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_linenberg @marcddaffner @AOC The local communities in @AOC area😂 have you been to them lately? The ones who won… https://t.co/88rbzEaVGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guilty 🤣 probably 3-4am computer pushes update on those “will read eventually,” tabs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarryForestell @Puglaas She has certainly demonstrated the qualities one would want in a PM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freebbqtx @x0sharon That…….. is not a Max…… or a Boeing for that matter. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedolsen @Cardiphonia Isn't a person blessed by confession and repentance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bodyleedavis @Arielthemermiad That is simply opinion. And even if that’s your opinion then you still can’t tell me Edward isn’t also hot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally just remembered I start at 3 &amp; not 4 today fuck. Why am I like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adafruit A real-time indicator for when answer time starts would be a masterstroke! . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is the most valuable thing you can give a person ....the older I get the more I prioritize my time....shit means a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time in snow, nbd #VegasSnow #VegasWeather https://t.co/IAaOTt0iz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaurabhRai_INC @RahulGandhi @priyankagandhi @JM_Scindia @PiyushGoyalOffc पीयूष जी खलीलाबाद बहराइच परियोजना से बहरा… https://t.co/mc932u0Gkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#putyourheadon #stevesshoulder #whoawhoaoh #whisperinstevesear #BASS stevie_benton  @ShawnVNB  drowningpoolofficial… https://t.co/xFVXfVI29J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMikeQuigley    Can you look into this?  Seems a lot worse than what the #FastAndFurious scandal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verifying myself: I am zanepocock on https://t.co/T40Hm0BApc. 3NGXBzc1q4xBoZn0uYRnSPqJ9QYOwOXAp_lU / https://t.co/5dBgxUfdQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of your boys were on call of duty one night and no one knew it would be the last time 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[He Stabbed His Girlfriend’s Stomach to Kill Her Baby, Won’t be Charged Because of New York’s Abortion Law https://t.co/3sQSWgpFU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our extraordinary Lighting Designer hard at work. #BareTimon opens February 28th! @ St. John's MCC https://t.co/wAMdaqWOjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro forces birthers, who refer to themselves as pro life, all cheer this in unison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Here's the whole Trump family associating with the kingpin of a human sex trafficking ring https://t.co/I0dGLj1Y98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIP_music @AB84 @Kaepernick7 No he didn’t you fing idiot.  You can’t be this stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday!  A good day to leave the drama behind. Let go of the need to control the outcome. #relax #breathe… https://t.co/flFj4xNW1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiss actually celebrated Japan’s surrender ending WWII. Current tensions aside, China was painfully involved as par… https://t.co/RtzAABGC2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S. tweeting this made me think of @joanjett and how bad reputation is literally the dumbest song of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willwilkinson @DanLehner1 Wait, is this an internet argument in which Michael Tracey is in the right? Can we just… https://t.co/aEzGSazBKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Solo is the best of the new #StarWars films , don’t @ me . #Netflix https://t.co/yEA4qY5Guk]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: MSNBC PANEL PANICS Over Socialist Ocasio-Cortez: Going to get Trump reelected [Video] https://t.co/9fqXw51dtS https://t.co/Ocd7Kzw0GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettHNews @carrieunderwood @Pharrell @WAVY_News https://t.co/Paz9R2aUk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait and see - YouTube https://t.co/Q1qft0PcmM @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/nWWH80LjZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill People act like every prostitute just chooses sex work as a lifestyle. So many women/girls are forced i… https://t.co/i36466mx18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great, more Bernie Sanders…at least we’ll get to see Larry David on SNL again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marc_Bertrand It’s a family vacation so I won’t make a crass joke like could Reiss make the height for the rides. I won’t do that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurencsho @Gaohmee "It wasn’t my choice to be kissed," Friedman stated in a 2005 interview with the Library of Co… https://t.co/liTggtpjgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maridiannnn @tanjila @HippieSoulful Doesn’t make a lot of sense to excise sexual structures off infants. Barbaric… https://t.co/T5go9aIdn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO IN THE OLD DAYS REPUBLICANS WANTED SLAVES AND THE DEMOCRATS FREED THE SLAVES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #NorthRaleigh on Glenwood Ave between Morehead Dr and Hollyridge Dr #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo #TWDFamily one more time it's #Kelly @IamAngeltheory  #OscarsRedHat #OscarsArt #TWDArt #TWDArtist #WSCArtist… https://t.co/oMkgRrteVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If then you have been raised with Christ, seek the things that are above, where Christ is, seated at the right hand… https://t.co/EiH9kxWzpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHEESEBURGLAR45 @VeronikaPinkert @CoCassiopia @ChasVivian @realDonaldTrump Ikr, like I was supposed to be hurt bec… https://t.co/FMwu6h0NXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TehRockCritic @Jackamanlol31 That 4th love is dr Strangelove isn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HFT2415 and HESP members on the way to Austin.  It’s early, but the rain might hold off!  #FundOurFuture… https://t.co/lOIianQ2U3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Pence is the only single argument against impeaching trump. Bad as trump is, at least you know what you’re getting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @RepDebDingell @kasie Passionate? Is passionate "the new" uninformed, illogical, idiotic, profession of kn… https://t.co/lwkJbw3D3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman I thought Martians despised Earthers because Earthers have nearly destroyed a perfectly livable planet… https://t.co/GB49S05WlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie visiting my mom and his Nanna in Pennsylvania last week #Littlebankstyle @ Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania https://t.co/XurX8FgZ7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoubleDeezze @GalxbyGlobal Improving the world, one image at a time. Go forth in braided Majesty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally completed .. CJ should be happy 😁 #Fallout #PipBoy #Gamer  #CJwatchesPeoplePlayVideoGamesOnYouTube #ButWhy?… https://t.co/mLKouh4Qug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrawyPopulista Niespodzianka mniej więcej takiego kalibru, jak ta, ze po niedzieli jest poniedziałek :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[El despertar social implica debates ideológicos, estar en una corriente política no significa pensar igual o estar… https://t.co/rm0xGkaxnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdias_5115 @Steve_Dangle Yes, especially Nylander. He seems so timid tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunSentinel Too bad this had to spoil everything because sounds fishy it would be gay peeps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoodedMan @a_leesha1 @raiya_zak @angelasmithmp Yeah, I don't think her racism is subconscious at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notmily and also bc i’m in literally 3 other relationships baby girl I can’t be responsible for another]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kisekisymphony They didn’t change it they simplified it. A simple game got even simpler. There was 0 challenge the… https://t.co/Og9MKGrsAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youmgbIood I can give you some @TheGabbieShow solo dms to give away if you follow my other account @gethonestlynow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaderAdrift @ItsMeSveta88 @DanCrenshawTX And before I hear "HEEEEEES A VETRUN," that held water BEFORE he started lying about this bill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePundick @Harlack @NateSilver538 Although it would not be that hard to run trains from Milwaukee to Kenosha or R… https://t.co/nsDlmEPNrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 4 Red Hook defeats No. 5 FDR 56-50 in the Class A quarterfinal, and will play @ No. 1 seed New Paltz in the sem… https://t.co/BDM4qhuvpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new addition to SOLIDWORKS CAM 2019 is the ability to automatically vary thr feedrate for round and sharp corners… https://t.co/LoJikehM9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLastChantz It really did because we modified our press a little and it was effective late when we went to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbra72 @4danlopez If the roles were reversed, the media would be our to hang every God-fearing White male who su… https://t.co/PMeYURZWcn]]></document></documents></author>