<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@doctorpemm @BldCancerDoc @drkomanduri I will be there tomorrow night I can’t wait for #NinfasOnNavigation and #TCTM19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d20Dames @stormbreakerer @TahoWF @Wizards_DnD @Gregtito And clearly the name should be Podcasts of Ghosts so you c… https://t.co/Fjxvmtu7rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a deep breath. Do you feel that?  You are breathing. You are alive. How awesome is that? You are truly spectac… https://t.co/XGB7LaYNGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the national folks notice how awful the @American_MBB conference officiating is ... And it ain't much better i… https://t.co/AvSVcQbukW]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @LATechHoops, switching between @WKUBasketball and @LadyTopperHoops. Talk about a stressful time to be alive.. I… https://t.co/7M2pmxZZpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ever looking down at a plastic item and asking yourself  “Are you single...use plastic?”  An easy way to te… https://t.co/XIlhPT0WT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_allthelilies totally worth the wait. Hope you can get some sleep. Thankyouthankyou https://t.co/9NiWbyB0SK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hailey1801 @emb613 @ChloePaul14 @sydneeyeager @April_Aguilar11 @mora_wiliams @kaylanichole316 @aliyaj514… https://t.co/w67bha2eVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are incredibly proud of Richard for receiving a medal at state for the highest individual score on his… https://t.co/sgCWPq1Mq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a pharmacist once tell me they felt the effects of a narcotic by a droplet through gloved hands. i had fentan… https://t.co/uwFFlxmbD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanDead @RobertMosesFox5 @sukanya @fox5ny Thank you!! Yes enough of this winter already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolmesJosh @benshapiro @AOC Yeah, she’s kinda all over. Too many thoughts running amok on steroids. One thing @ a… https://t.co/lpb6rShNeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity the 11 GOP congresmen who want to block Trymp’s emergency plan are probably taking orders from Soros w… https://t.co/EN8TmIexmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brash_1 Soooo glad to see your opinion!  I wondered what you thought about what she said here!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femalequotient @sxsw Here’s to more #womeninSTEM   We are here to mentor, promote and support you all! Join us!… https://t.co/p6qF7ZIaEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt like my face makeup looked really weird today and I finally realized why. I forgot highlighter :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyElves Horrible. No way. They don't have the forgiveness of Jesus Christ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have to ask me where Bali is, we don't need to be having conversations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to this on a snowy Monday... what an awesome sight.. this is my mood ! Go Bler Go!...#UglyDogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[These shotgunshell lights were up for Christmas, but I like them so much, I think they’re here for good!… https://t.co/0sLNENS9H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tclaybuck @EphraimGopin @PamelaGrow Waldorf and Statler!!! The best! 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello does bulletproof coffee really not break an intermittent fast??? hmu @bulletproofexec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FryPeggy1 @deedee_regan @TeriWenzel1 @CheekyAussieGuy @sheri_lynn95252 @tazsdog11 @AlexSan85617527 @Djpk10Denise… https://t.co/nbdyV5RfD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap on @catapulttheplay at theater_for_the_new_city   I’m depressed and missing the cast and crew already… https://t.co/am9kjz6I1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Healthy hair journey at Stephanie of Gone Girl Hair Studio Follow me @  https://t.co/doVP5BYaVL #tapeextension… https://t.co/GVvFvaQj3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't posted in a while so I'll leave this here... Lol 😂😂🤣🤣 https://t.co/fJsU4geRcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian I think you are the most gorgeous of the Kardashian’s and one of these days you will find a man that treats you good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanEdinger I work at a study abroad office on campus and one day someone came in and told me they either wanted t… https://t.co/M8Z96b3kn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow her on Instagram! She is an amazing illustrator! https://t.co/TyWnJ3g65G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luke5sos i hope you had a great day and have a lovely night. love you always. 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samsung already had wireless "airpods" since 2017. I can't with y'all. They don't need to copy Apple. They've been… https://t.co/w9EOeSNWdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You signed a check that you shouldn't have signed.  Can't wait until they put you in prison for th… https://t.co/yi7MQmqKyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielledsouzag @DineshDSouza That's exactly what they want! Government run everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day back in the office in almost 3 weeks and I missed this place, didn’t miss the cold commute though 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at all the selfies I post even tho no one asks or cares for them https://t.co/JMtH1Z44xA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my shirt! #harmreductionohio #harmreduction #getyouone @ Troy, Ohio https://t.co/mH90N8otWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas bound!!!!! #liveinlasvegas #robbiewilliams @robbiewilliams https://t.co/SYpwuotSuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattduss @joncoopertweets Look, this woman has to visit her sister under the bus where she threw her to run for of… https://t.co/IMSpCgOhtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Raziel are getting tacos Sunday and I can’t stop thinking about it. Se me hace agua la boca just thinking about it, hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cww35 @DeadlineWH @TheRickWilson @NicolleDWallace Forget not Steven Miller.   Is someone following him and diving into his background]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shaun Frank opening for Tritonal at House of Blues in Boston on Friday night. . . . . . #instadaily #instago… https://t.co/2Dxnmcn8aG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grr uh Spider-Man or Wonder Woman or Darth Vader https://t.co/NKh2nq5z6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oohblackdiamond @CarolineRoseFM Has he ever been to SXSW? The whole thing is one massive marketing campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaoo I remember this shitt talking bout Ciara was a hermofadite. Me bex see]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! There is I've on the river and finally snow on the ground. Now this looks like winter! Perfect day fo… https://t.co/m6YvzpvAgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msunderwhelmed @MarkArum @FBlankenshipWSB Thanks for saying that! They’re the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJHughes45 Aside from their extremely awkward 1-on-1 heather was my favorite so 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a sweet acknowledgment in the mail today at work. Thanks, Darryl!! https://t.co/oalCgsI4Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaw dropping home in Stonebriar Country Club Estates. Call me for a private showing. @ Stonebriar, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/6VWwEkvQUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[And i really want #WhiskeyCavalier to survive (mostly so @ChristaBMiller can do what she wants with her hard earned money but also yours)]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting your nails done in the privacy of your/your nail tech’s home is 1,000 times more relaxing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You are so dirty Hillary for Murder yourself I am surprised when you sweat you don't drip blood on… https://t.co/297dsuNPOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lately, my daughter has been very choosy about what she will and will not eat.  I shouldn’t be surprised, because I… https://t.co/20pm8yM4ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come we haven't been trying to grow solar as a society all along? #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh this sh*t is with an audience? BOO #TheBachelor https://t.co/IptR1764U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdAllison @bamagirl_17 @algernonradish @DonaldJTrumpJr @trumps_feed Forgot to say. GO FUCK yourself!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@subtlefemlt Thanks, we ended up at Sids as that was the only restaurant open at lunch time. Restaurants are expens… https://t.co/VpljWDu7hC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Tried and true stomach flu. My son is emailing his professors that one cos he's staying home! LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[thinking about hoe incredible my life down here in orlando is and how i have the most amazing friends and just how… https://t.co/Lkb5CFxilx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Statement on @browardschools board vote from Lori Alhadeff, who wrote the proposal to fire Runcie, to @MiamiHerald https://t.co/Lg8xHwEDxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just wanna look at something that you know is gonna hurt you but you do it anyway lmaoo why am I like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normonics @HunterBergsma @QuinntheComic Did Category Theory emerge from Complexity Science?… https://t.co/tMQO5kxMxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo Girl, you crushed it!  Don’t let them bring you down.  You were incredible!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sara_Jiang @MidwestVetPath lol. it looks like she is judging YOU for watching her eat the plant]]></document><document><![CDATA[You forgot 8) millions of unborn lost to the world—FOREVER. How many Einstein’s, Mozart’s, Gate’s, Steve Jobs or ML… https://t.co/2iEWafl36G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleesascion My deepest sympathies and most profound love for you and your family.  A very courageous Angel ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollbluntss it just said 1.8 billion trees barely would help . so you want my no job having ass to go plant a tree… https://t.co/BYuVyQJLT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinjaGabe13 @TRHLofficial One day your wife will send you to Target for your daughter’s first box of tampons. And… https://t.co/zIMVNc3piD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk We need all the Republicans that don't stand by the President to be called and emailed and remind them who they work for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill No, but he accused him of a bevy of other crimes. Open your eyes @LindseyGrahamSC and stop being a patheti… https://t.co/4cnABAMfE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gearing up for a great #HBASF event with @DianeBryant #HBAimpact #GRIT #Leadership https://t.co/HNWdwUbEzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[First mammal species goes extinct due to #climate change‼️👎🏻🐾❤️😪❤️🐾👎🏻‼️  https://t.co/QCA3ScXV8z via @NatGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about using this wallpaper for a retro kitchen! What do you think? @ Maple Grove, Minnesota https://t.co/rAzcAcbeoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Negotiating 4world peace with a dangerous country like North Korea is like walking a tightrope! Kim may hv known or… https://t.co/2fB8zVDhf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I think this judge either failed to remain objective or is compromised. Whether or not he liked the s… https://t.co/ytD3bjXfHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SerafinaLopez @Rude_Astrology I pledge to help in any way I can. I’ll kill that baby Voldemort 😤😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is bursting with pride.💚These kiddos alone raised over $700 for the Baddour Center. Our school as a whole… https://t.co/qXvXjYk8Yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlligatorHamil2 @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Yes. That’s what we have here. A President that is incapable of pe… https://t.co/UyLYNXpkM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaLanier54 @John_KissMyBot @gtconway3d Unfortunately the Liberal Fools running for President won't have to live in it. They are rich!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisValeska @MikeRinder @LeahRemini @BryanSeymour1 @ChildrenOfScn @Clear2Insanity @WomansWeeklyMag This article i… https://t.co/bXUiAmI1VV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer @IlhanMN Would you stop supporting them with taxpayer dollars 41 billion to a rich country is ridicul… https://t.co/EBbkkLGimJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Richmond, IN is ranked number one best place in the U.S. to buy a home for less than $100,000.    And Muncie is nin… https://t.co/hcD7klOhSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I should post the nice pics but the others are so us usually silly normally laughing and always sexual… https://t.co/I2nBY4gKiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Adding $ to Tom Steyers name is a antisemitic trope. It furthers disgusting stereotypes… https://t.co/NMjsETLJ5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mount Zion rejoices, the villages of Judah are glad because of your judgments. https://t.co/U4oJWC3cxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can NEVER forget who is campaign manager was and his voting record !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just told me... "Stacie...it's not ALL about you." Really? I said.  Can't you read? 😂😂😂😂😂😉 Stacie Krupa Fin… https://t.co/ug2xkmyvJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And black unemployment numbers are Obama’s so stop taking credit for something a great, dignified… https://t.co/tuUY6Kaw3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students are using ideas from our class novel to discuss the connections and differences of the ideas presented. Lo… https://t.co/oXJgzaWnrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[how y’all fall asleep during training and is ok with getting called out on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Through our Lord Jesus Christ, your Son, who lives and reigns with you in the unity of the Holy Spirit, one God, for ever and ever. — Amen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She smells 🥀 She smiles @isabelle_levi #LoveIsAllYouNeed #BeMine #GalentinesDay #HugsAndKisses… https://t.co/l4rARLO9sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s this popping up at game day??? Thank you for the support this morning @teamstevenson74 and @shortartist!!  Yo… https://t.co/uTORCvM8bL]]></document><document><![CDATA[does this bow make me look innocent? because i am👼🏻 https://t.co/vHxjFE2ZTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning Mary #makeup and #hair by me #love #beauty #galgadot #lookalike #beauty #boston #bostonmodel #model… https://t.co/ZpoSdcELTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been cleaning my apartment all day and i finally sat down and poured myself a glass of wine... I can’t express… https://t.co/sywKEkBevU]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone pls find me a second job.. i’m so tired of applying &amp; applying &amp; getting nothing 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Motivations by “Daniel Jones” - “I feel motivated to sleep” - @nixops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teathebiscuit_ @MariaMMtz7 when Austin was tripping when the guy hit on you and it was just instinct to say your m… https://t.co/Jt8NPXXeXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that I got so much good mail like random holiday cards, Girl Scout cookies, wedding invites etc and t… https://t.co/DDIBGvr0cK]]></document></documents></author>