<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@1kingker I bet you Stephen A needs to be smoking on an hourly basis. Might keep him out of his feels a little bit… https://t.co/qbirEIJBEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikDRVT @MrEarpLA It would seem just.Trump is our 💪🏻man . We love Trump !We love Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richschellhase @macmasters_a @ScottPaterno My ability to get VA benefits because of my honesty and willingness to work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pogician_ @Tarekitani95 @ManUtd @Ibra_official Look man, I’m giving you hard stats. Tangible stuff. You’re giving… https://t.co/sncwuJ0LiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[That must mean that there is A PUTIN Church Service as part of The Coward and Chief's Daily 6 Hour Executive Time.… https://t.co/1MnFggvoDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Philip_Iglauer @lausdbd5 @Jackie4LAUSD @Monica4LAUSD The California Charter School Association helped put a felon… https://t.co/iUTgfWJpIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp @Ilhan On that note, I hope this Muslim is shown the door soon. She is not on our side by her words and deeds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one more person texts me about coach B ima lose it... wasn’t his fault. No chargers. He’ll be on the sidelines S… https://t.co/OTpp8T2MrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessitron @chriseppstein Well written unit tests shouldn’t prevent refactoring - if they do, then you’re either do… https://t.co/M9JUvgDDht]]></document><document><![CDATA[The straight left hand. The left body kick. Uppercuts. Vintage Mirko! 2-0. #Bellator216]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEHorst1 @ainsleyhorstman @StJoeAngels @stlmarathonmom So excited @ainsleyhorstman that you’re an Angel!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKirkSBN Most are dead Germans or dead singers so I could definitely defeat them in battle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man held his fist out for me to fist bump. Soon as I do it.. he asks “does it feel different fist bumping a white guy” 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[so let me get this straight...you can be under 18 to strip...but 21 to get in a strip club...im confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Gerardi Totally agree.  Team played so well with just 4 D and to leave those types of goals in that late is ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señor Barovero:  Solo quiero decirle que he sido portera por 10 años y EXACTAMENTE ese poste siempre fue mi problem… https://t.co/iFEBx8ASdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sun Daily:     More women work in construction that’s still a man’s world;      Thousands attend climate march… https://t.co/yyHYHR4ZqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know...i’m late for #watchwednesday but better late than never right! ...........................................… https://t.co/GyyGGL1eV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pray &amp; support the efforts of The Ekklesia of Oklahoma in Abolishing Abortion in Oklahoma! #abortion… https://t.co/FVWEAf5cN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein An Important ‼️ Message from Brian Krassenstein ‼️(audio) @EdKrassen about Jussie Smollett ||… https://t.co/138taTMAij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquesDoucet @WAFB The people voting yes more than likely outside of Louisiana or not fans of LSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWV The debauchery alone makes it the last program I would ever view.  #Hollyweird]]></document><document><![CDATA[7” face anchor exit strategy and we outta here. I’ll render and go surfing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Seward County Women 81, Barton 80. Barton couldn’t hold on to a 5-point lead going into the 4th quarter. Lad… https://t.co/2skzrNpEG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandadeibert That just made little kitten Elsa’s day. https://t.co/te2lSb1XGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aberrantabeer I’ve been there. And thank you for all the likes on my tweets and retweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teenteen_c @aswwrestling @TheJimCornette Now...$13.00 PayPal garydamron@icloud.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pressed #2wongsmakearight (@ Barracuda Deli Cafe in St Pete Beach, FL) https://t.co/mfxRNILAYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kchoya @NotPeoriaMayor @Uber Yup, but my meeting was at Canal Place, and I had a hankering, so that was the closest, decent one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems find a broken norm they can get on board with. 2020 😋😋😋 #NationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanMcKellips @jayyrik @finalmouse I’m not wasting my Saturday morning going back and forth with Garth Brooks bu… https://t.co/dFJmP0lRPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever wanna piss off my brother just let out a big sigh.   The bigger the sigh. The bigger the anger.   Super… https://t.co/kIwiolunwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[SXSW 2019: Comcast NBCUniversal House #sxsw  https://t.co/Afj1swhK4M via @sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats must rally to educate and denounce Independent Bernie Sanders, the divisive and Principal architect of ma… https://t.co/UdKUtbPU6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Collectomaniac3 @stefthepef @99piorg @PghVintageGP @Fallingwater If you ever get the chance, visit @Fallingwater..… https://t.co/o7BVW0ot6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerrierTracker Really running the floor well, and two great passes by dtl to find him on both]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysonst I love this!  Can we start a petition or something to elect this guy commissioner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ It's Still The Worst Mess In History :(   ..........!!!! https://t.co/zByRCB8GT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn't quite describe my shock and awe at seeing friggin #SNOW land on my car in #Pasadena but I had to try to cap… https://t.co/rYdchDAy5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bohemian Rhapsody winning Best Editing is like an illiterate winning a spelling bee. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/MMtf44sYZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Cooney @Fenner_6 Hey @CraigSmylie is allowed to do that - he’s retired to Del Boca Vista with Frank and Este… https://t.co/gP6zFCXzwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EngineOfMore a new blog post Engine of More: the 3rd place https://t.co/NCeBFvL0iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Patton Oswalt breathes new life into 1984 hit The Warrior”  https://t.co/Wgu9CijRpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck Entertainment can happen while praising excellence and talent innovation  ,luck of the draw doesn’t make part of that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless the jury is from Philly, this officer will be found not guilty. Other than the 'Burg and Philly, the rest of… https://t.co/m19yzIhaxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyAdell @Handsome_Jake_ Nah Lowry is much better than Russell. Siakam probably should have made it over both tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiter, I’ll need a side of eggs with my toast. And don’t forget my coffee. https://t.co/wfjEpKw4ZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dios sabe que amo los bebes pero tener uno atrás de ti pateando tu asiento por más de 4 horas es una prueba de tole… https://t.co/8tLAXJCuUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchelTruesdel @IA_Cub I watched Star is Born with my wife. Good movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killaking2018 @MysticPabbz Nah cause I ain't scummy like that some of you men got your priorities ALL The way fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a former AG in your corner is a great advantage because they can help promote your message with their old fr… https://t.co/NTDWD9th7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[always givin me butterflies 🦋 @ Indiana, Pennsylvania https://t.co/qAYt5Xplvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_D_Crow @JKSteinberger @EthonRaptor @ProfMarkMaslin @coxypm @StottPeter @PdeMenocal @simongerman600… https://t.co/4iTbbK25DU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_More_xxx @Vistaprint Order from a hometown boy. Email me at signguy_12@yahoo.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[But then I get frustrated at the restrictive timeline I was given, and the fact that critical pieces just didn't ex… https://t.co/NkFbMlkbYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a perfect day for some bowling! #winterbreakfun #extendedday https://t.co/QxH3DOE72s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPD101Pct @TheWaveNews 101 is action not just words. Great job by all these amazing officers. @NYPDnews @NYPDCommAffairs]]></document><document><![CDATA[,,, So, You want Control of your Government, take all your Money out of the bank, it’s that Simple ,,, Hit Them where it HURTS ,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghanaian_Doll Get your groove on, Ghana. Happy Independence day to all you black star fans. @ghanafootynews @GhanaFootball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hasta cuando estos delincuentes de toda monta estan libres y burlandose de todos...? https://t.co/zKmGvjACxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back from LA and the set of @WrenchWars. Thanks to everyone for an awesome shoot! Wait until you see these rides. https://t.co/CDW9YPBnDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonchibnall @DonaldJTrumpJr Actually they turned it into anti Trump and supporters with the lies of MEGA hat and d… https://t.co/Sk5wA82XYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to go to a $8 Clippers game fuck it, atleast they might actually win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn @StephenCurry30 That’s wasn’t the highest point at MSG tho but I get it. It’s the Knicks we talking it. https://t.co/Z3dmXV0ZLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGuyyGregP Shaq Roland was the best I ever saw in HS. When Lexington came to NA and won like 56-53 with ESPN on… https://t.co/JBc0juvYTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACCBarstool @mccavman "ANY" body contact? There's a difference between illegal and marginal contact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaVuduPuppeteer the  term is now used as a weapon not only by the political Left, but  also  by far too many on th… https://t.co/uhXrQE3iYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women spend 364 days talking shit about Men. That 1 other day is Men is expected to cater to their ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbump @studiesincrap It's no small feat to translate music fame to film. Many have failed. But I'm in a deep pre-O… https://t.co/GMkmBdpWUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyVanBramer @NYCDisabilities @maawallace @brentoleary @NYCMayor @macartney @FabianBuchheim @MakeQueensSafer… https://t.co/FM6H2zSTRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time in my 23 years of living my dad “asked” for something for his birthday. Anything is possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @FoxNews If they paid out of there pocket fine, if we the taxpayers paid for it, there some explai… https://t.co/wsSACoZmzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a gym partner you can be my guest at planet fitness  #ssu #blackcard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAmyCode But after I turned 50, I quit my job that I'd held for 14 years (as a word processor at an intellectual… https://t.co/y0MsxVmN48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeavent @moon_dad @thatluckyolsun @Popehat @vineyardvines Three fourths of the country has no knowledge of Carvel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hallyleadbetter Whoops, maybe I shouldn’t have hit the like button. 😬 Well, unless you have a good Lawyer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need to see how MKO Abiola’s daughter @IamTundunAbiola who interviewed the idiot on @ARISEtv was so excited ove… https://t.co/PdjGqkF7SH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down the rabbit hole: Ted Gunderson, ex-FBI, exposes government involvem... https://t.co/GFl26YgmYC via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prosperous05 @silverhelen2093 Por fin, y tu por allá quitando cuentas .... 🤣🤣🤣 eres un cura mendigo wey !!! Alboro… https://t.co/uVQ2axbIod]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy who took my position at work is so worried because I deleted him off my Facebook. If that’s the worst thing I do. Lmao 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all... i get the allure of capitalism, of decreasing taxes, but when it comes to healthcare... do y’all really th… https://t.co/kO7rp5hITs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthSublem @048_and @marchmadness @KentuckyMBB @UKAthletics @PJWashington Decided I had more class than you. Woul… https://t.co/e1bfCkbLlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilsimmons @WTNH A Major Mess We live at the East Haven, North Branford Town line. Plows have not even been on our… https://t.co/BDAxSRuP4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DragRace Lmao I felt like she should have gone home first as soon as they did the cast reveal and I saw those outfits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMEN23MNB @Giants2019 @mrchris172 @PLeonardNYDN @Giants I've been saying it on Twitter forever. The numbers don't… https://t.co/5d8awASKDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mlle Mickaëlle Michel @MickaelleMichel  and Land Of Fire a very good 3rd place today at Hippodrome Compiègne… https://t.co/4dyCxqX6Da]]></document><document><![CDATA[Army said the club also needs to work on its shootouts. "We have to finish in the shootout.  Maybe we spend time in… https://t.co/LDYZcSMois]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re willing to sign kuechel, who’s basically the ace of a perennial championship contending team, to the Yank… https://t.co/n3ABgJzjLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HitlerBigfoot Sam Elliott’s description to Ron Livingston of how he killed Hitler and why the act was meaningless was damn fine acting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People may be right in their own eyes, but the Lord examines their heart. Proverbs 21:2 NLT https://t.co/utjGoE0daQ https://t.co/XIw8qMMAHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrippeyD Odd, because to us, the 100 dollar bill is weird and almost monopoly money compared to our other bills th… https://t.co/Jv50WNMouu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody else you want right there other than @henry_ryan34. He has earned the spot and will continue to dominate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole premise of #LivePd is it’s “live PD” - not “lets go to commercials until we load the guy into the ambulance” ??? #sellout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doozerblake @JimmyGoetz @DaredevilHall We are only trying to make a difference one establishment at a time Blake. We can do this bro!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Given the number of hoaxes perpetrated by the Left, you should double check its veracity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at JFK AirTrain - Terminal 7 in Jamaica, NY https://t.co/rAE03yFGQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goin' to the city, gonna listen to lots of emails... #HistoryOfTheFuture #BlakeHarris #Oculus #Peaches https://t.co/2TliMzytWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarcyLRoss So, uh, we (finally) are—characters signup here: https://t.co/kTlaFj4HPe https://t.co/uVPOUDSXUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[MIREN EN LO QUE GASTA EL GOBIERNO DEL TRAIDOR Y MENTIROSO DE MARTIN VIZCARRA]]></document></documents></author>