<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Buhler_I @LKTurf @TylerO_Harrells @SOS_StrongBeach 2 and a half year old and a 10 month old ... #clarity #morebeerplease #imeanvodka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends You have defined the present situation correctly. It was a coup attempt.  That is n… https://t.co/SqPC6xjESW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pendleza @kevinokeefe @ABATECHSHOW @ABAJournal @LexBlog Subtweeting @associatesmind and @richterjw like whoa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Sunday night at 7:00 (central) on “All That Jazz”, “The Featured Album of the Month” for March 2019 will be re… https://t.co/rFzVxlIRSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirRantAndRave Maybe? Like... it depends on if they think Flacco can last. This could just as easily be a Kurt War… https://t.co/kOA2RJOchA]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACT: California has two Senators who are Democrats One is a #GreenNewDeal co-sponsor. The kids wrote a letter to t… https://t.co/GUJ0qdoHHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transient just showered our news van in 2% milk... Lovely start to the morning. https://t.co/hzFceGPuxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darhar981 @HarrellRyan1 Independent Conservative Women for President 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family trip to the Bridge #deceptionpass #whidbeyisland #pnw #SnowMageddon2019 @ Deception Pass Bridge https://t.co/ibY9Xliwlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAHNNYMONTANA WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOW YALL I MADE THIS JOKE AND THIS NIGGA STOLE IT. THATS CRAAAAAAAZY. IT BE YOUR OWN BROTHERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @VinceMcMahon and @OliverLuckXFL please hire @INDYHEADCOACH1 to coach in the  @xfl2020. I don’t see a more perf… https://t.co/zCoErCBUjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devising ways to explain to my girlfriend why I had to stay up until 4am looking for treasure in Tomb Raider to increase my power as a gamer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreedomWorks @AOC @nypost Living it ‘up’ in the world is more like it. Just another “do as I say not do as I do congressional member!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryBattenberg I love that. Can’t stand what pick up usually turns into]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillfromCholera @hoynsie Santana is the DH. Bauer is the 1st baseman. They will split time. Hanley has sucked for 3 years now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This heavy snow caused a tree limb come down. Elkins Ave in Shillington is blocked.  Not a good start to the day fo… https://t.co/uL17xdHcZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTenNetwork hey no one wants to watch the end of this basketball game put on the wrestling !!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very tasty and hoppy Pils! - Drinking a Thousand Stars by @alewife_brewing at @BronxAlehouse  — https://t.co/Kg0iLZhNAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came home from work and made tacos. Now I'm going to bed for the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The mother of world boxing champion Caleb Plant has been identified as the woman shot and killed over the w… https://t.co/O9fw42cYx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samanthadjb @anabailaoTO Bradford too, but he's voted almost identical to Tory since Tory endorsed him and gave hi… https://t.co/vqJArH23yR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting to page 8 of a 9 page paper and literally having nothing else to write is the worst feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mmount378 @JonahNRO @nickgillespie @ScottAdamsSays The Great Dissonancer himself?  (I wouldn't know as he blocked… https://t.co/Ybf6YpUGFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmeisler Here comes the time where everyone gets fooled-we breakout above the resistance, rise another percent, then fall back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowes So 1. Ignored me 2. Rude when finally forced to help 3. Does not problem solve or recommend other solutions.… https://t.co/Qp5YitxyC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Gillibrand has pivoted on so many issues, she's going in a circle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCTigerTracker He looks misaligned. Can you jump in there and help him align next time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[long live the rose that grew from the concrete 🌹 #BackIIBlack https://t.co/cEWB7f5I1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT, if you have ever been shadowbanned since Trump won the PRESIDENCY, and have lost FOLLOWERS as well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignofTroy @PenguinOfTroy We all know the issues. At the same time, Penn State has more players in the portal tha… https://t.co/TD0lH4nNbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Lesbian Feminist Goes OFF-SCRIPT on Tucker 🏳️‍🌈 https://t.co/uQD0hFLIfT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 #youare31youarebrokeyouareguarnteedtobeagreeteratwalmart #willneverwinasuperbowl]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Bound Witness for time clock keeping. When an employee shows up for work and goes home in the evening. It will b… https://t.co/reKYiTBGIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WessellsBarry @SpeakerPelosi @RepGregoryMeeks @CNN @ABC @nytimes @washingtonpost @MSNBC @CBSNews So let me get thi… https://t.co/OPigQ9XLaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Kendall nears third base watch the 360/spin move by starting pitcher @chardonnay013 💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @highbrow_nobrow Tonight on the show The Circus Jim Jordan was asked about the check that Cohen displ… https://t.co/eIymoZ2hRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadoftheDecade @fred_guttenberg This is literally too dumb to reply to. It's rare, but every now and then a vetera… https://t.co/B3rsSUxQ6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contract for America, Gingrich extremist. Radically nasty view of this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump SNL is hilarious Donnie🤣🤣🤣where’s your sense of humor...a hot dog will holler!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCBazacoPhD Yeah the motivating factor for me to leave Texas was the lack of barbecue joints. 😒 Maher had been, is… https://t.co/65ELwmtw2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTuckFrumper Unless you're watching FOX News for professional reasons, (find out what they're saying), You aren… https://t.co/tRjpRUZ9h8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spurs Meeting him for my Birthday when the Spurs played the Cavs here in Ohio as this was my Gift 2 days before I… https://t.co/iz1LAPWV7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrando el cumpleaños de Georgia .!! @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/wtRT3b9TR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoPaw19 @jgeltzer @CNNOpinion @realDonaldTrump Why would he refuse to leave? He will leave when he is duly replace… https://t.co/3Ouw52KSaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who talk to themselves on twitter need help💀 go get a mans or talk to your mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t hide an S-Class...in any light S550 Certified Pre-Owned 🌓 . . Mercedes-Benz of Virginia Beach #s550 #sclass… https://t.co/vL4X10UW6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT @reeves5150 G… https://t.co/CEOCkHNXoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny to me how one of the most common arguments that people use to say that UCLA won’t get a solid coaching c… https://t.co/4WIxq7jy53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c4tsounds @LampMoritz @9to5mac @benlovejoy Wouldn’t recommend vita. It doesn’t have L2 or R2 which is terrible experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that man only knew how many times he brought me back from the dead....RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black-owned barbershops create community in NE Wisconsin. Today's @gbpressgazette, design by Jamie Stade.… https://t.co/QJXSFh3KkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No quiero imaginar la cara que pondrán las personas cuando sepan la calidad de momazos que publico en fb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillerMike Bernie’s voice will not be enough against the corporate Democrats once the debates start. Tulsi’s voice… https://t.co/VpqT4zFBPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in denial like Kaci once. It didn’t end well.... AT ALL. #TemptationIsland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did it explain how you were going to collect the wall money you promised to extort from Mexico that you are now pro… https://t.co/8lJOukaLtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen is returning to Capitol Hill for a fourth day of testimony as Democrats pursue a flurry of investigat… https://t.co/ApSLV2lwrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDX2BB How’s your handwriting?  Are you giving them to PR legibly?  I say them as I get them gents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felixtennis @ASUNTennis @NicaiseMuamba @LUMensTennis @LibertySAAC @Derek_Schwandt @BSmith102688 Those forearms tho https://t.co/36fZRvZh5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was chilly day at work and ever since lunch all the restrooms have been full 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlyDebrusk @Mikael_Habs They're a bunch of self centered pricks...as per usual. Didn't ya know there's no other… https://t.co/VT7SCdmBRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myasu The Bruhz made up for it and shit still going on it’s blowed #myasu22 #AUM22 #AUM Guys $10 Ladies $5 OH AND… https://t.co/Q73XYFdfOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCMOTD @BBCOne Am I able to view this in Florida? Currently on holiday but may struggle to cope without MOTD . . . Must go suns still out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching them how to fish rather than giving them fish.. pure love.  School ball is over, thank God! Lol!! Now, we… https://t.co/TgwAyZHWMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bengaljims_BTR @NFL Come on Jim. Krumrie in the tenth round! Love my fav qb all time but also love Riley!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill NO BERNIE. ITS U AND THE GROTESQUE DEMOCRATS THAT OBSESS INCESSANTLY ABOUT RACE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlawedIrony87 @themikenorton @SassyMamainLA @renfamous So what did you say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any fool can criticize, complain, and condemn— and most fools do. But it takes character and self-control to be und… https://t.co/dLeDmJwa35]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet @MStrooo6 is glad that Machado is headed to the NL. All the rest of us are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skarn222 @21WIRE @p_piotti @TulsiGabbard The focus should be real restitution.  Locking him up just costs taxpayer… https://t.co/PT2WW6eQuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nlechoppa1 shotta flow makes it feel like I’m in a gang when I put that joint on....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Felicidades. post excelente. your best that i’ve read! i particularly love the sobriquet: “BreadLin… https://t.co/iyS3yJSFSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonDrLJA @PoliticsIsDirty The touching of a person or any extensions of that person is the definition of batt… https://t.co/ioPazknHxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the answer is not how to make these products cheaper so they CAN buy them but to drive up the cost of or ban ev… https://t.co/Zpn6NIsEml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddieahlgren_ for threeeee! Gladstone pulls away from Iron Mountain, 50-35, tonight in Gladstone. Braves improve… https://t.co/G3JzZeJmzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLD!! Received multiple offers, closed in 10 days, “as-is”, sold over asking price. Yep, all went according to pla… https://t.co/vNKAAiP0rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pistons have been playing well lately,Drummond in 10 games late feb. avg 21pts,16 rebs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever hear a song that slaps so hard and you can’t wake to slap it in your car haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @NJAHPERD for another great conference!  #NJAHPERD100 was great.  See you next year! #physed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sumdood88 @MLB @TheAthleticMLB @TheAthletic @Bharper3407 “Ohtani-San, ILYSM, we getting that ring this year”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question on @Quora: Why is Blizzard allowing the original Diablo game, and Warcraft games, to be released on GOG wh… https://t.co/TmUB7yz5aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregHale1 @Postmates @milkbarstore LIES! and a good store @milkbarstore has an inferior product delivered. Sigh. I… https://t.co/Baqsqkb2xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaWallace steady hands walking away from the soda machine. Go get'em today. I know ya can do it. Go #TeamBacon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSchneider @allthingscomedy Me too Rob. I tell this story every year since I was a stage manager at SNL from 95-… https://t.co/gyksxDtHtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Michael, lately you have gone up in my book... keep it real!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up from a nap terrified i missed my class... i graduated a year ago...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this look of concentration as he tests his code🤗 I am so thankful to be both a parent and an educator at EWA.… https://t.co/2dYyzLTD6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon practicing the "treat yo self" philosophy on fat Tuesday.... @ Harvest Buffet &amp; Grill https://t.co/C1HQGgCy9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett you deserve grace just as I did when I hit my knees and asked for forgiveness. I was wayyyy worse o… https://t.co/0kP07ylcS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[... we need them (media) to not only be inclusive in their hiring but we need them to be more balanced in their rep… https://t.co/pqCCsiurlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 BILLION social media followers:  “We want Finn Balor as Intercontinental Champion!”   WWE:  “Let’s take the title… https://t.co/yDyipJyVe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @ShelbyCassesse https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/RsnoynNrXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Costco pizza making is fascinating. No wonder why it’s sauced well. #yummy https://t.co/n5uJTA1fJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest podcast: the future of commercial television, creating the “Dave” TV channel - and why “linear television… https://t.co/zPRRrJF6mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get @KamiKarras to 100 followers today? #FF https://t.co/90TdlXbJeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you never watched "the Whitest Kids You Know" growing up and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Saturday and a new round of musical delights. Fool On The Hill is the fourth studio album by Sérgio Mend… https://t.co/HG6Ky7kG4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coaches please visit #hogfbchat.net for information on the upcoming clinic!  Also DM me and info you would like on… https://t.co/cYp68yR7tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llego la hora del Best Bet en #Aqueduct #Hablanloscaballos https://t.co/yegnZ218SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a walk today, wasn't to bad out,but the wind killed it. Eating better and down like 5-6 inches. ☮️😎🐈😺😸 @ Brist… https://t.co/FTgb6too9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starrymarii This looks amazing! I love your style and the colors you used!]]></document></documents></author>