<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ok @espn your so called #AB story is full of, want to feel sorry for him. This #SCFeature is awful. Showing the slu… https://t.co/O5EojhKo4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike Lee’s BLACKKKLANSMAN is back in theaters today at @SeattleCinerama, and you can catch Jackie Chan in POLICE S… https://t.co/LOzOnl73jE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipo matar um Ben and Jerry's inteiro sozinho e depois sofrer com azia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luiselenu @laprea2 Es una mezcla de los dos componentes y unos granitos de la viveza Venezolana para sazonar la estupidez!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome talk by @modMasha about security behavior change and working with our users instead of complaining about th… https://t.co/F8z7VPSk1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved watching @SachiaVick last year can’t wait to see her excel this year  #BNPPO19  #TennisParadise #tennis… https://t.co/x3yPQfw7hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every athlete is always just one bad step away from never competing again.🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giselefetterman Happy belated Birthday #SLOP if your are in Harrisburg today I want a hug!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the7era Best point guard in the Lou!!! And can shoot but best spot up 3 point shooter is Jackson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeahCartel @McGeezer67 @LA_Karma1 @cpw_Numenor @spiritmoon7 @Sand628Sandy @AskLifeY @bassorita @josi_59 @sandra_gr… https://t.co/Nfc9HQwqw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Russellmania621 Machado will make more long term because he will be able to be a free agent 3 yrs earlier. Harper… https://t.co/xMmqzjPMh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Engineering Technician I" in #WestMonroe, LA. Go on informational interviews. The… https://t.co/0DocThdp0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Pennsylvania's 5th Congressional District https://t.co/OmpZxSuWzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginkers I found Fiorentina’s press release to be very cold, they added at end his journey at club is over (which w… https://t.co/dSjUcnoRcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shopped in the Ladies everyday! I've done what I can ladies push on me.  I'm on my shoes for the rest of this...I'm here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob performing tonight at Kitty Kiernan's Thursday Night Open Mic!  @kittykiernans #kittykiernans… https://t.co/cYNOjlS1v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really REALLY need to learn how to handle situations with something other than humor]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ottawapoet #ottawaartist #canadianartist #canadianpoet #misfitpoet #anthonygorman #handsinthegarden #mentalhealth… https://t.co/FolPDiswBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long wait till end,,  skipping, numbers also hate https://t.co/9ZRawH4SnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Senator says it is “perfectly ok with me” to have DOJ punish media Trump doesn’t like. Many ya hoos from his sta… https://t.co/ShZMsZHcqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[a database company trying to poach me today. nah yo. Love me some @microsoft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Florida will be a A combination of New York and California. It will ruin the state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool New Yorkers doing New Yorker things. 🏢- - ❤️ - #NewYorkForever #nyc #NewYorkCity #newyork #city #photooftheday… https://t.co/Qn2xyLDq09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilerq74 @LowryBaseball Doesn’t look too bad. Truckee’s field still has 6’ on it.🤦🏻‍♂️.  And I’m sure South Tahoe’… https://t.co/dY7sz6JW7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifesStyleBlog @KristinaNadia @riapanacea @MrsTyler78 @DandMe_MomOf5 @judyohtweets @RichP222 We used to do this th… https://t.co/sb1aiooah4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov. De wine needs to tax the medical pot manufactures! Make pot legal and do it like deer tags! There is your full… https://t.co/GqZPleiow6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SageCanaday @InsideTracker I do, yeah. I fully believe in the product and our mission, and am proud of what we’re doing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @UtahLacrosse on winning their second game in program history this past weekend. https://t.co/0fElT5UJ0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeymourSnott @JZ_Flair @imthathoop @tappedoutpod @officialturbo @SmittytheYankee @VisionDents @HallidayDoug… https://t.co/2gP3l61JId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisTFP Despite the shorty, I don't know what Doughty thought he was doing on that play. He took away the opport… https://t.co/a0qWvQ6tcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven I wish someone would say that stupid racist shit to someone in my presence. I’m ready to be on YouTube.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPEACH RASHIDA TLAIB - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/3CbnI6RS5D via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3:49 AM + I cant sleep, but I am ready to shout into the void my twenty favorite film performances of 2018!!! https://t.co/U4XKpzxvuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is very easy to know which systems work, let take a look at the countries are under a Socialist, Venezuela, Cuba… https://t.co/eaR8m8m3Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @Only_one_thomas to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s). Ea… https://t.co/cRW3EvEFbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @WhiteHouseCEA Yeah your policies did a great job widening the wealth gap, just like all the tax cuts s… https://t.co/YSediGHWvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OloriSWANK @JPowers25 @OloriSWANK You have to start Jackie Channing @JPowers25. He just talking to talk. He can’t… https://t.co/rPNeKWTqjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MildsAndDatYak See. Put me on to your connect. This that Facebook group jet shit 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Taste has been here. The quality is better!! You can't go wrong choosing JON'S GOURMET NUTRITION and GRAB-AND-G… https://t.co/RVSfpzrI7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Either (1) you’re really ignorant, or (2) you’re really stupid, or… https://t.co/LmwakqGBmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBlargg you know want you son of a bitch you’re not even an American citizen, shut your goddamn face up. Your op… https://t.co/iFPwqtwY31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Social_Citizen If you heard it today for the first time, would it still be a *great* song?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizmarkiedesade @bartellall @really_polly @IanSams @SER1897 @TexasPete No it isn't. It's a woman eating collards t… https://t.co/HhYxuNRitk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zizou knew something we didn’t last year and didn’t wait for this to happen to make a decision ... Ajax executed th… https://t.co/LqGXYvmI6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danagould Nobody is asking the most important question. What does this all mean for the Bubbles the Chimp movie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CunningSq16 @maryh92 @CIAnderson3 @Eathbound420 @everyhumanknows @FireGoddessB @RuleChicago @Cdubey_Texas… https://t.co/HrJDJeNHxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[be careful with number four; skulls are usually not dishwasher-safe  #Repost @deathwishcoffee ・・・ I'm partial to nu… https://t.co/UtXGx7VKsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Gayle has some real composure. I guess that's why I like watching her every morning. https://t.co/KuRxBIHDdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have the day off congratulations. If you're working today... Well traffic is lite. @ Cerritos, California https://t.co/vHiM8ZxgV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally home from an incredible fucking performance! 😤  @chrislake @followthefishtv https://t.co/gO7M3oTtHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final workout of the week. Gravity seems to be increasing upon me wherever I do pull-ups. #backday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, we need the law put back that does not allow Muslims to hold political office!!!  Assimilate to our culture o… https://t.co/wvtvDrHnUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soaking up some sunshine on the beach after a trip to the Sunday Market. ☀️ 🏔 #seattle #wa #ballard… https://t.co/hXhTa5s9J7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Gotta be a bot. There seriously can’t be people so stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 months before the Temple's mass murder-suicide, Jussie Smollett's mom's BFF Angela , spoke via amateur radio tel… https://t.co/tYCWJxKfqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We could be in for an interesting predicament. East Peoria’s WiFi connects to Twitter, but not my Mixlr broadcast,… https://t.co/urDSfeN7zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Hey idiot, TOKENISM is RACISM #RacistMarkMeadows #TrumpTreason #ImpeachTrump #ProsecuteTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtkantor The next time that Bobby Orr or any present Bruin walks onto the Fenway field during a pre-game festivity… https://t.co/c9O3PY25J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LevántateAEntrenarQueElQueTeQuiereGanarYaSeLevantó #FoamRollingStinkyBallCoreWheelsYRuntasticResultsWarmUp martes… https://t.co/X2NRMWLBME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POLITICOMag @A_Big_Hell_NO @greenfield64 Trump has convinced the GOP to jump off a cliff. I don’t care! Are you go… https://t.co/KBqA7q8906]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class 4A Area Championship Seminole 30 Levelland 35 Halftime https://t.co/APKMXZYEiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Network Engineer"? What did you like most about that job? #ProjectMgmt #Denver, CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are girls hella easy these days or what cause it never fails that a guy tries to have sex with my on/right after a… https://t.co/14570pKMBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StPaulResident Free agency hasn't even started so no way to gauge Teddy interest. Slow your roll!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Northwest Heights Neighborhood in Portland, OR https://t.co/Roo9rSSVVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to say the later seasons of the office aren’t as good as the first few ones but Jesus Christ this show is ju… https://t.co/mWbMrUIm3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorBlackwell @RealSaavedra The real tragedy is rampant Leftist dishonesty. Shameless and devoid of consequences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh if we draft Ed Oliver at 29, I will shotgun 29 beers out of happiness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougHeye Apples/oranges.   This is an enforcement issue.  You're proposing new law.  No comparison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Canoe_Ideas @Wilnerness590 Because he tattooed the Toronto skyline onto himself...??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuna fish sandwiches 🥪 are my jam!!  • Here’s what I put in mine: -1 packet of Tuna (Starkist Chunk Light Tuna in w… https://t.co/54nW32AGyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[$BABA can't help but notice that every high it's made this week has been a negatively divergent high on the 30 minu… https://t.co/qk6Qqm92Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since when do Boston Bruins fans chant Beat LA? The Bruins and Kings have no rivalry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yvesdiscount @rafajoannart Mmm i agree i overthink way too much when I’m stoned 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #AnthemIsAMust on @tyltsports. Honoring the military is important https://t.co/SJBT31JmTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing to hear from old white men... “I don’t hate gay people but they better not hit on me.” 🙄  Oh you… https://t.co/gRRKT71W2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Delusional, these Republicans twist themselves into a pretzel to justify Trump’s immirality]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @FakeKevinKugler. A little birdie totally not @nilly21 told me that you were concerned about my team's football… https://t.co/a0Yj47T48T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoezMcfLy I have to think they are trying hard to move him and basically told him not to come to camp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Bull &amp; The Bear in Monterey, Calif https://t.co/RSTOgN4gPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari- I have asked for years of effort? C- I would guess 10 years unless I stop my Twitter Sari- laughing don't do… https://t.co/6jKYpESkbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoachBDB @LindseyPelas This guy is uncircumcised, my son and grandson are. Stats are off, more traditional mexican… https://t.co/841SCpSF2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raincienfuegos @JamesSurowiecki There are many kinds of opinion among Catholics, from the Catholic Worker types to the friends of Franco.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beers (@ Alosta Brewing Co. in Covina, CA) https://t.co/vUxU9KcxVz https://t.co/oV0pke5i6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really is wild how the IFC can have constant hazing allegations but continue to remain on campuses but the secon… https://t.co/bq6xGMQtaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great lesson @lexiliebig  I’m humbled to have had you and Sarah a part of this much-needed discussion on… https://t.co/ZV3E9ZixAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at HAVEN Riverfront Restaurant and Bar - @havenedgewater in Edgewater, NJ https://t.co/nRgzaa7rpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streak day 313. Not the run I wanted to get in but I'll take it. #zensah #teamzensah #teamnuun #stingorbestung… https://t.co/UUctQRVHNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cooljosh1021 brought the 💪🏾 to the weight room today. Putting up big weight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come hang out it the chat! The Annie Frey Show 2-22-19 https://t.co/SStQ62C45r via @YouTube @anniefreyshow @kfitz971 @johnphilosopher]]></document><document><![CDATA[The LORD is my light and my salvation— whom shall I fear? The LORD is the stronghold of my life— of whom shall I be afraid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoneReads @Elliott_Duncan @greggabe @StubbHub @FourVerts You racist bro because your boy sucks at qb?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philliesmf @ryanhoward @PeteRose_14 @JimmyRollins11 @SlidersNSaves54  for Tugger]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the chances that Skinner signs with the Sabres?  I don’t think he will. But I’ll put it at 20%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 That invitation was sent in the form of His Son Jesus Christ! That invitation is open until Jesus returns - I p… https://t.co/Btdc7WAUc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salas__10 @Chestertweet @Kel_Chanell @ken_vero @Itsmxlli_ Name one policy trump has put in place to disadvantage m… https://t.co/DDzB4jnN5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are good to go... but there is still that patient or patients that still sticks around 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. The last days in the New testament were the last days of the Old Covenant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzJoseqt @TheAcademy I didn’t see first man but ready player one should’ve one that shit was crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My superhero power is eating too much for breakfast then napping a bit.]]></document></documents></author>