<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[no one look at me during lonely codependent at kayak, free throw and tiny moving parts because i will be ugly crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scardyginge Agreed. My alarm still says 2:15 am(PST) and I want it to be still be that.🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got prescribed codeine for severe pain and man lemme tell you that shit is fuckin STRONG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did some research and in the Year of our Lord 1860 in the United States, USA had over 4 million slaves owned by Dem… https://t.co/uUIIKrHe00]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just realized the cast party for our community theater production is ........... on st. patrick's day. 27 years o… https://t.co/wRrsJctQgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeeSunnySierra I just wanted to get as close as possible without dying! 😅 mission accomplished. I was actually at… https://t.co/T0dnbJWsW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliant to see @hattingleywines #EnglishSparklingWine 🇬🇧 front and center in the sparkling section at @WholeFoods… https://t.co/cPb7scr5wL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until I’m done paying off my student loans... because I don’t ever remember these fucking passwords 😤😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisyn_a_arm I’d love to see your short film, but can’t get to Green Bay.  Please tell me how I can watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings starters: G Bernier, D Green, D Kronwall, F Glendening, F Ehn, F Athanasiou; #Flyers starters: G Hart, D… https://t.co/EMpGOvDE53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson #pictureperfect #NationalMargaritaDay https://t.co/NlPARvAIcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: the captain marvel movie is better than black panther]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanWitte No! Frisco, TX, went down to 22! And that is not in Celsius ... I have never been to South Dakota, but i… https://t.co/UN3N0Vscz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's wild because sarcastic and arrogant are Tony Stark's defining traits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted a challenge from @andrewbouska to post the covers of 7 books I love - no explanations - just the cover.… https://t.co/8gYTAYFr4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei @Bayer Cup of black coffee with sugar or a coke ,caffeine does the trick .]]></document><document><![CDATA[[comes with Ergo, puts on couch and assumes the position]  “I’m ready for a piggy back ride, Mimi!” #matildamaeve… https://t.co/2AOZpHvwYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 @62WalterP Wolf bane and eye of newt comin' up........boom chicka boom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Momof3gngrs @abnerdominguez @SenKamalaHarris Excuse me but the parents would have already made the baby with "fata… https://t.co/TbciljjQIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bluecent65 @IngrahamAngle @Acosta Ask yourself, is what he says or does,  benefitting any of us?  He is supposed t… https://t.co/bvEtxUkOOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell you how many times I’ve frantically searched my house lookin for my kitty - lil escape artist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mowoodier @FlatMatzley @StillCrankyAF @PhillyTalk @AV_SardonicWaif @szysgt @danmsnyder @ihate_everyone2… https://t.co/FO7xj0u9ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin This is the state program the senator wants to cut. It doesn’t touch the #federalfood portion, only the… https://t.co/zgpoh6Lht0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well after 7 hours our power came back on at 7pm.....then went out again at 8pm.....might be a very long night in G… https://t.co/QplML3crQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from the audience: Linda RN: strategies for how to handle difficult people/situations/conversations should be… https://t.co/x4T5bDgb6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMerkley I felt she lied several times, esp. about not knowing the number of kids still separated. It was just… https://t.co/66zPyfGdIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phoxx_3D @KillrMillerTime @cmdrjesse @levelupseries @_Kevin_Ha @TheAlexValle @ViciousFGC @DoctorStantz_… https://t.co/y4ABX4jYt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump disrespects that office as often as he can... but that mfer did not mention Cohen. However he was… https://t.co/H2wwHunvNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5goC99aN93 arts education raises scores #artmatters #thewholechild]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know they gone be ran thru everything by Wednesday im not excited no more 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s irrational at this point how mad I get when people say “play” instead of “musical”. Like I won’t tell them tha… https://t.co/kRFXlI3NL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyyyleejordan ABH dip brow in ebony is what all of my dark haired friends use and it works!! just make sure you ti… https://t.co/UmsTMlFGo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[💃📸 thanks to @nono_mcsd for the 5th 📸 and @hitophotography for the 2 last one❤ #usa #newyorkcity #nyc #nyfw2019… https://t.co/rrStDo0DzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stormy Point Village looks good no matter how you look at it! #stormypointvillage #bransonresort #familygetaway… https://t.co/QMPC6pTmzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are you?? Get in here!!! @usmcsky and @dizdezSky are in the middle of #horrorfestFriday. It’s supperrrrrrr sc… https://t.co/RS5e9h0R2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, no matter how much you wanna be happy, the best you can do is fake it. Sometimes, no matter how hard you… https://t.co/Kj3EhYiMPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#petertork #davyjones #themonkees #daydreambeliever @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/8gcOg8HR7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuccarello36 Our hearts are broken! You were the heart of the team! We will be forever grateful for all you have d… https://t.co/1fLrVpEdrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minot State Baseball game tonight! @ Tucson, Arizona https://t.co/0qD7FGwS9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was looking at my timehop and I've had my one year anniversary of working for my uncle already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenPage your dramatic dogtalking our POTUS and VP being the reason for hate or whatever in America is just plain… https://t.co/2yj3XCRbnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaddyTam12ge @pam_brundige @Loujacbella @lakehermit2 @suejard @ProfKCW @KrugerJoette @8_Leo_0 @romey4 @dobbs_ron… https://t.co/Xms2ONLUan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCinHD THIS HAPPENED TO ME TOO it’s not just you (and, unfortunately, not just your coworker)]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of our neighbors peering over the fence at Huerhuero Vineyard. @ Paso Robles, California https://t.co/QSH2vYV8IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have questions about my position (VP of External Relations) meet up with me, so I can tell you all about my… https://t.co/1SZ4cetll8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break up in a small town by @SamHuntMusic still resonates with me years later]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga did so freaking good. 2. I definitely cried. 3. So happy for all the awards bohemia… https://t.co/3AOkCk0pzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ninth Circuit Judge Richard C. Tallman said the true purpose behind the appointment was to once again challenge the… https://t.co/5T6POITWw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph S. Barometer 30.079 in, Rising. Temperature 20.2 °F. Rain today 0.03 in. Humidity 70%]]></document><document><![CDATA[me after she told me i wasn't talented enough to make it (which only motivated me to try harder) VS me after she li… https://t.co/Y5rIHm3Amz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trenna_jo I tried explaining they had the wrong house and how there wasn’t a Brian who lived here and they just st… https://t.co/7MbkdoRoq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My normie friend is teaching my sex worker friend how to strip and THAT is how drunk we are]]></document><document><![CDATA[A packed house! #sfchronicle #sfchroniclewinecompetition #4rwinery @ Fort Mason Center for Arts &amp; Culture https://t.co/vzzpcTx6pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyEberle13 They’ve had reparations. Welfare, affirmative action, quotas, busing, diversity training, open enrollment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eli Lilly will decrease the price of one of its insulin drugs. https://t.co/zC5ZLFd4Td]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real conspiracy. @cnnbrk @maddow @HuffPost @AdamSchiff @nytimes @colbertlateshow @JoyVBehar @HamillHimself… https://t.co/tGZv5O5JHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow us on Pinterest by using our personal Pincode!   •Save this photo, open your Pinterest app, click the camera… https://t.co/1d2tFR4HVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldgoldengirl2 Thanks, I never did see it.  Like you, I wonder why such a sign would be permitted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nbs I wanna know what I did to deserve certain shit from certain people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis My daughter Reality Winner found a way to preserve the proof of Russian election hacking. She definit… https://t.co/qIQS0qUjpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like I’m winning with this very yellowed, used copy of Suchman’s Plans and Situated Actions. Previous owner… https://t.co/eqBTb0rGDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @BlairBraverman @QuinceMountain #bravermountain team!  Lucky #11!!! Here we go! #uglydogs #Iditarod2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[This post made me scream at my phone and now my bf and dogs are scared of me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @BernieSanders Bahaha. Be careful! I almost spewed my coffee across the room]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK @Amazon in the spirit of being a good corporate U.S. citizen, can you now please select a community that compara… https://t.co/PhCbOTqFvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWalkingDead @RamboDonkeyKong Is it just me? Or... https://t.co/S6abbyul28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its #flexfriday after all. And I finished up my week 6 workout called Powerful. I increased all three transformers… https://t.co/pV1CGZH7Ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at that a little over midnight prior to the beginning of a school week-  #ShownuBombardment TIME‼️‼️💢‼️… https://t.co/vIiKR3Qkgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday #sexysaturdays Repost from @fit_lolamontez Is This Photo Dynamite 🧨❓• • Get that bag ladies… https://t.co/6kG7W8zVsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[New mosaic piece in progress. Stay tuned, final dropping soon! Getting busy in the studio during this snow storm ❄️… https://t.co/j2Kcuu2GmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Coach Annie....see you in France and Spain (our @SELECTS_Hockey girls are lucky to have a role model like… https://t.co/ARay2rM8sZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a seat at the table doesn’t make a difference if you don’t open your mouth. -@KarenSpilka #wbalegislativebreakfast2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#billmurray made me start #writing. Now I sleep so I can start again tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to spontaneously try cooking today, and to illustrate the extent of my lack of culinary prowess, here are… https://t.co/642FZ3B6xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[And also all of the badass women scientists here on Twitter and in real life who make themselves heard and seen. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3widedraft @mitchellvii @AOC Ha!  That and too many twirls on building rooftops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL People keep commenting about her emptying her clip. In my class for concealed carry that’s what th… https://t.co/dnL2nRDXLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@francis_sielski @Gropher_Tump @TaylorRMarshall Remember Christianity itself is Mysterious and Miraculous. It is NO… https://t.co/8AG7mZ5hoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It cracks me up when people talk about "taking care of their kids" but they're always running around without the ki… https://t.co/9XKCUBQ8ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[For every Starbucks promo challenge I complete through the app, there’s another one I complete and have to complain… https://t.co/LB48QlZVEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomDominant I used to be big into collecting friend's legs photos. Here's a wild pair for ya. https://t.co/9g0ksaitmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibstatguy @nvwineandcigar @OrneryPiglett You WHAT? did someone not like your stunning beach shots? That's just sil… https://t.co/MAY5wnwYHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpartanRace Will do, thank you so much. We will see you on the island.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine You said Pres needed to lose some weight, HE AGREED so he is EXERCISING you DOLTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is wrong with the men on here? Are they that desperate that they have to ask women they have never met and cha… https://t.co/3t63OumlZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 I’m 44 y/o and I still believe there’s a chance you could be Batman. Go for it Graham! 😛🦹🏼‍♂️🦇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett I can not believe what a liar you are! Paying ppl to do what you manufactured-calling it a hate cri… https://t.co/2iSjchYktd]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re a piece of shit if someone tells you their pronouns and you still purposefully use the wrong ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s about to go down!! Missing you @LisaJBourne https://t.co/lBVT01xUrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re in the country when the school auction has guns and liquor sitting out unattended for bids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can preorder one of these for the next 36 hours ♡ https://t.co/cT2dgpXH3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I agree. Why I am so inspired by the #CIT officers program. @PeoriaPoliceAZ @ScottsdalePD @MesaPD @davidshopeaz… https://t.co/Hi9m8JfmlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jetemetet @bearski55 @dazzlecarol @cas_33 @allyemmerson @lucretialive @lusciousvixen @jaguarlogdrum @feromoon Buenos días 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NonMaternalMum As soon as I woke (its 3:40 a.m. here) I checked! You are doing a great job Mama ♡ hang in there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Narrator: "To maintain a delicate peace in the house, Colton made an emergency pumpkin spice latte run."… https://t.co/iDbO9dckf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now- a #classic lecture by Dr. Seymour Sprayregen on “Contrast Reactions- Diagnosis and Treatment”… https://t.co/nRd06Nsx1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have this weird irrational fear where somebody is always watching/judging what I'm listening to on spotify.... li… https://t.co/EyynpVekiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golf season starts today!🎉🎉 Good luck @bmccarty10 as you begin your junior season!@chadmccarty @ClipperGolf https://t.co/JwUHbHlcvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a recent visit to #AhmansonTheatre #DowntownLA #DTLA We sometimes forget that legends got start in theatre. He… https://t.co/SJEDY2wjnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said the FLIP is a reference to what may end up of the local furniture if black folks attempt to play this so… https://t.co/YNS5LvuoOV]]></document></documents></author>