<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The best is watching RJ Barrett flex on an 11-17(4-12) they're barely beating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kali_gail @BentleyMarieAz 👩🏼👩🏻👩🏼‍🦰 I’m thinking the world is gonna get more than they know... 🤔, more than they ca… https://t.co/SbbPJHwwgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLFlyers @herrfoods I Just Love Watching Hockey Now  https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jordynwoods #jadapinkettsmith #Kardashian #lol #Gameofthrones https://t.co/WjxJMJDIAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santiago4kd @Rayados Ni de broma Layún antes que Stefan, no nos hagamos como tú dices Santi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jupiter2012 @OJenEspanol I think she’s fine. It was more than enjoyable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Me Home * * * * * f/5.6 || 1/3s || ISO 100 || 70mm #sonya7ii #sonymirrorless #nycnightlife #thisisnewyorkcity… https://t.co/sg5Mt5JzSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Country Music Dials Down on Girl Power as Nashville’s Women Find Even Fewer Slots https://t.co/V9KkGjCA7A @CountryMusic @Variety #music]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r2romasanta @AdamLanceGarcia Why if you feel passionate about something telling other people about it shouldn't make you defensive]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you don’t know won’t hurt you, but what you remember can hold you back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Planeta1027  porque si ponen canciones de @yahirmusic @yuritaflowers @_CarlosRivera  y de @MyriamMonteCruz  no si… https://t.co/HdO43QinqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allievivona Just like Fleetwood Mac. A solid, above average band but not as great as everybody says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The decision was reversed after parents objected. Which shows it was never sincere in the first place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see this year later . He’s been #mafiadon for a lifetime. He may be getting that one room place at long la… https://t.co/NaIUWUZsBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dong_kkc @SupaReal @HubSpot @dantyre Love it, Kim! Anything in particular you find interesting or extra helpful? I… https://t.co/EJIQia05EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Na I’m good, my dental clean as hell and if I’m meeting a fire nurse we usually hit it off]]></document><document><![CDATA[We here @ Love Fellowship Tabernacle-NY with Bishop Hezekiah Walker https://t.co/E7y07XVPvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peikko763 @BradleyLems @tan123 Define “wrong”! Seems the people who actually know about the science, disagree with your uneducated opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: STILL. NO. ELIMINATIONS. ??????????  #WWEChamber https://t.co/1jS01LBUAj  https://t.co/WIXdx2dJTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you are traveling down a certain road just because its the road you are used to..sometimes you got to go where is no road!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dupree Congrats on an incredible 6 years my friend https://t.co/rwUvPNvCwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole thing about how if you're a creator you shouldn't criticize other people's work isn't really true. Steve… https://t.co/aJQXcGbSTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are remembering that Paul Rudd doesn't age  https://t.co/QqVPiPiYG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fsmikey @FSBigBob does Zerorez use their empowered water to get runner's diarrhea out of treadmills?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gary28573 @KAliceCompeau Almost Put In There. Greatness.  My Bias For Witchy Woman Won Out.  Thanks For Listing That one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMalikaSiker @erikk292mke @CarnevorMKE @Calderone_Club @TheFirm_LLC @MKEKitchenCab @MarkKassMBJ @drdavemke… https://t.co/0bC5C07CO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_Rizzuto @peterdaou @NRA So the founding fathers didn’t know the meaning of the word regulated, yet they were… https://t.co/5t8ohH12g2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in case you Misfits are wondering, check out Venezuela and see how that socialist society worked out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greg_mcgeady Totally agree. Reminder that Cory Seager was drafted after him, as well as Marcus Stroman, and Michael Wacha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a run.   #hockey #nashville #smashville #preds #nhl #photography #sony #sonyalpha #sonya7riii #gopro… https://t.co/FbxbkMiPCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySekulow “Live birth abortions” are impossible. After birth, or botched abortion, you can’t have an abortion? Yo… https://t.co/5GJC8FbnxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrawfish @micheleneggen @Horrorellablog @nolan_mcbride I can’t wait to listen!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeroCarbSarah When someone calls me a carnist I 😂 because I know they are reciting #ideology vs anything factual.… https://t.co/RAumcegUVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn Linux with the Raspberry Pi https://t.co/oeYOf8DxKS via @opensourceway]]></document><document><![CDATA[The resistance to moral relativism used to be a core conservative argument and a cornerstone of conservative talk r… https://t.co/tc8FVIw6KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying alone: the act of checking if you have your wallet 87 times.   ...wait let me check again. https://t.co/NOJRKRAW7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renchia_arendse Hahahaha nothing like that, if I did that here on the Rez they would have put me in the crazy house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Lincoln Park: heavy snow, 30°F 83% humidity, wind 8mph, pressure 1022mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quavo really believes he’s a basketball player this nigga show up to every all star weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomTillis I am deeply saddened by the back stabbing of Throm. The reason Democrats are a strong they stick togeth… https://t.co/azJk3Fxvwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueerMerboy @sblpodcast on Twitter and Instagram  https://t.co/HTphxXakzP  Spotify -https://t.co/TkH7RuoFTC  iHear… https://t.co/Rb9i1DCl77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roger_Roeper @FailedMusician @ShatTheMovies @ShatOnTV That was my Micheal Jackson phase.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome turnout to see some outstanding students. Our kids always amaze me. @carrollisd #ExpectExcellence… https://t.co/NWU6ubULMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Its practically no larger than Trinity County CA. Of course they can!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHaseman @chimojr5 @KateAronoff @AOC If the united states were to just vanish a what 2% of co2 be gone still would… https://t.co/6sO7uw8esO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EPrime35 @IsraelUSAforevr @ShawnLyn5 So if you get a DUI and you are born here is is a crime. But not if you are illegal. Pure insanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarah_1876 i watched it as a kid and ive rewatched it multiple times. Its fucking great 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is no respected politician or conservative calling for the expulsion of Omar from our US  Congress?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing the video with the #Samsung10e . Good morning @ #WordOfFaith #Toronto #Canada #Worshipper… https://t.co/XeaWnmhpuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel @nickkroll @JasonWGeorge @samfendermusic I just met Tim Apple Baba Booey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast testing your theory, let’s see if I get retweets. I’m mad! Go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayARob @WCVB I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOME Day1U… https://t.co/E07ecVnF7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marjori19821146 @AnnieDuBois69 @lunaml @ABC @IlhanMN Oliver North has done more to protect this country than most.… https://t.co/HPJyk6mO5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife got me the greatest Valentine’s Day gift ever!! 👶🏽 #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/R5frfimm1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson Wow, you just got your third voice champion in a row!  He was amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $2,723.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/tJTfXebzka]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are ALMOST to Boston but now anyone who was headed to Ruggles now...isn’t. They’re skipping the station. Also we… https://t.co/Pio0PrByF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabsorderpizza I know hahaha then I did this I had just like sent it to you on Instagram or some shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nyxi117 did you make enough for the whole class!? https://t.co/IwzYzjOIUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArashMarkazi Just write the truth. Like how Dodgers ownership values profits over winning, or how dumb Lakers have… https://t.co/T6rjC56pjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garypaljr @santaanitapark @ABRLive Wow. It's a golden ticket. Praying AH is ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Splash from last weeks Cap 8! #captainamerica #marvelcomics @frankmartinbox colors❣️ https://t.co/RSEjjphUCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendenHill Time will tell. They still have several holes to fill on both sides of the ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you just saw my tweets and didn’t see who posted them you’d assume I’m a grumpy old man lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[so u just gonna bring me a birthday gift on my birthday to my birthday party on my birthday with a birthday gift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PitOutsideBox @TheCathyBrown @rottzillasgirl @eddiecolvin7 @Pixxydoodle @GAstarwarsfan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me a minute to muster up the courage to share again but by god here it is #TBT to my short lived dancing caree… https://t.co/7oMACOqvx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would be the right person to offer testimony on Trump’s behalf? Or any other person accused of such an ugly thi… https://t.co/VAHvePmCPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitmanjoyce100 That’s why you are a true champion Johnny. Hard work does payoff. 🥊]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing I could ever do with my life is to be a good DAD!!!  Everyday I wonder if I’m doing it right because… https://t.co/9IUhnGU0Af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Atlanta, GA? https://t.co/PR9SlP5VZj #Engineering]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinayperez @MSignorile I was beaten / gay bashed.  I also had death / arson threats for daring to have LGBTQ… https://t.co/sOoaLmuVs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talented QB, but buddy how are you gonna play full court D and get cheesed at a guy setting a pick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for Rutgers Unviersity for hosting me during a Junior day recently. Had a great time. @alexgleitman… https://t.co/7jXMcVTdCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWard028 @Penguingonemad I’ll be playing Galactic Assault Saturday AM. Look for me on the field. ^_~ have you play… https://t.co/HEnDlbfLuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How my #bandmates and I #felt about a very small #amount of #new #music on the #radio going into the #studio. I… https://t.co/2bWCfEmqNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michiganians understand why this protection, If you want US Mail, make sure that any 🚗 can drive up to your mailbox… https://t.co/5F1BvwInYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Of course take healthcare away from women who can’t afford an exam.  U do understand all the servic… https://t.co/WkFF9CrtZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC Iconic  #newyork #nyctimessquare #citylife #citytravel #wanderlust #wanderer #wander #travel #traveler… https://t.co/7Zczqri4S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about trends in Greek Life at #NASPA19 ! https://t.co/3aYx8TyUHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aglaia_Berlutti @Dra_Guaripete @Super_Kaa La brujis nunca juega con algo tan serio como los libros, jejejeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seungminkim Wow. I think you may not be taking advantage of this income stream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out with the Fam @TrevonePerry @jacksladd #brothers @ Sea Thai Restaurant Brooklyn https://t.co/3rBVA0Me1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great evening last night. Hall of Famer (J Gordon), the young gun (William Bryon pole sitter) and my bride (the t… https://t.co/oVsQWvIfnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything belongs to God, so why keep trying to rob God. Instead GIVE God what's due... When the PRAISES go up, the BLESSINGS come down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was a tough game for all three teams out there @SanJoseSharks @NHLBruins @NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessesaintjohn This already sounds like the best type of sadbop, I am in https://t.co/uyrE3XYEFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweet if you noticed how all of these Republicans are so interested in Cohen’s potential book 📚 and movie 🎥 deals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever dwells in the shelter of the Most High will rest in the shadow of the Almighty. Psalm 91:1 NIV… https://t.co/vc6Pd1QDpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepting Clients For Election Cycle 2019-2020.   #PoliticalStrategy #Finance Management #Field #DirectMail… https://t.co/4N4Jvp2ca6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet the party continued to ask him to campaign for HRC... which he did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part one of #LeavingNeverland is fucking brutal to watch and hear. It's insane how fame can blind people so easily.… https://t.co/4vqr8ze6Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike - where can one get this sleeveless hoodie? https://t.co/JAZVzQpReB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new @ACEducation report is a wake up call to all of us in higher education. Thanks to @lorelleespinosa and the… https://t.co/1zzGjcdxTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ112sa @RichNice2k1 This is definitely some Chicagoness. NYC fam would've added some "Mac" or "street sweeper" talk... but same energy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article said it was disinformation Campaign and this was something other than what it is.  I didn’t put a Samb… https://t.co/KycXLmTIo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moodyredhead @AnkurAg23493625 @drzack87 @TRHLofficial How did I move the goal post? I’m asking you to prove one sy… https://t.co/2a8a7ciykC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruising down the road towards Nashville. Should have some free time if there is any gaming-topgolf-basketball-kara… https://t.co/hSOOCFx10f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Glenn L. Jackson Memorial Bridge in Portland, OR https://t.co/DaFWIoanXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KHOU11 The #Rockets have recalled forwards Gary Clark and Terrence Jones from their single-affiliation G League partner Rio Grande Valley.]]></document></documents></author>