<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Rockets lead 81-72 after the third quarter.  Luka has 17-13-6, Brunson 16-5-2, Maxi 10-9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smells Really Fishy @SpeakerPelosi is just an illumidonkey puppet! https://t.co/gecuqb0kAI #Q #QAnon #QAnons #WWG1GWA @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking and weathering should be illegal 🍻🌪❄️☀️☄️ https://t.co/YkRpR659fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealgynomite @becausewecare1 @Tigerlilyteddie Here we go. Deflect? I already answered this. https://t.co/SMrWrgc8Pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not saying we’re better but if A Star Is Born ever thought of cutting costs, @TheSchwiz5 as the man Brad and me wit… https://t.co/JNIvU3w8Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im gonna say this one last time...Ally’s SNL performance was some amateur fucking trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Dan Crenshaw. It's obvious Democrats don't give a shit about our Borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpinator_the @NBCNews @TheDemocrats @AOC AOC is not in the Senate, genius.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just about time for Class 5 Sectional basketball in Sedalia! @hoops_jacket https://t.co/f1VDt4olJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @BrunkerCyn #Trump and McConnell Tax and Scam us into the obis !]]></document><document><![CDATA[January and February are gone...its time to #March on through....... #springiscoming #cameinlikealamb #rebirth @ Ne… https://t.co/NoDJoBezV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my gurl nachos so many fun adventures together I never want them to end she is an adventure to https://t.co/2iEBhbGXVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m delighted to be supported by @extremitieswear and @TerraNovaEquip on all my travels.  Let me out someone..!!! https://t.co/FMHJdG6vwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[things i can’t do:  1. parallel park 2. a lot of other things i’m not gonna list them all just know it’s a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was on freaking tour I thought returning after being in NYC and traveling living somewhat a dream that people wou… https://t.co/XVi964wQT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber Obama used executive power to destroy United States Of America as founded, President Trump is usin… https://t.co/lFOkyXESpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my students ask “What happened to your hand?” It becomes the perfect moment to give into #curiosity… https://t.co/6rcgY4GdqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bienvenidos a Adventureland! #adventureland #magickingdom #waltdisneyworld @ Adventureland https://t.co/GGR9WrFNi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Kill a Mockingbird (@ Shubert Theatre - @shubertorg for To Kill a Mockingbird in New York, NY) https://t.co/4XhDLG4vne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkilpat512 Yes Mam.....the pleasure was mine and meeting Anita's oldest son. Priceless❤SAFE TRAVELS 😍❤😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imthathoop @TheRealSkySteel @JZ_Flair @MrKlondikeBill @Trukstop428 @adam_rotella @joecs1220 @sophvas @Badmoneyslim… https://t.co/vUNYxlJDg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalAbsintheDay #LaVeeVerte #TheGreenFairy #HenriMarieRaymonddeToulouseLautrecMonfa @JohnLeguizamo… https://t.co/bPB4iqRVQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarchMadness #ncaabasketball starts next week - still time to setup your League Contest with @FntsyPostseason.  Si… https://t.co/5sFsx70EDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_raddatz @MPRnews A wall is different than fencing. Democrats know this and support fencing in appropriate areas,… https://t.co/ePvbp0a54t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkohlrogge Also The administrating has made it much more difficult for immigrants to enter legally.  That’s probab… https://t.co/cIiCVkShGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Certain divisions in the audio visual industry,  some people choose ground and sides - it's so hard to understand a… https://t.co/CxsRjj6QtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfstarr1 @RedSox @Yankees Wade's mother, Roger's mother, Johnny's mother, Jacoby's mother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseymcmillanmd @joshuaesc @F3Columbia @F3Gear @F3Augusta @F3Nation @F3Aiken @F3Alpha @F3Cherokee1 @F3Savannah https://t.co/9KY1y96p4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@no2libs007 @cq2101 @hirschA8720 @POTUS @gatewaypundit No..: @TheDemocrats  would never do anything cruel or evil.… https://t.co/7UTSsK0k9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teammates that don’t even try to recover you and respawn you need to stick to playing solo Fortnite and not @PlayApex #ThatsNotHowThisWorks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend selfies 😘📸 bnpparibasopen  #FullBloom @ BNP Paribas Open https://t.co/4DHOfc0bHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stealing content is just that. Stealing. Don’t do it, and if you’d like to use someone else’s content, ask for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLucido You know what is kind of shitty?  @GregKirk17 and I have been begging to meet with you re:auto no faul… https://t.co/dGbLswYJJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing away  #blessings @BrianLoging https://t.co/gYkduDmtDH @ Columbia, Tennessee https://t.co/yaD726qBRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HanumanthaNate3 @whatsdf @fumigalli @MelodyMarksxxx I'm happy that you do so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People literally don’t know how to make a right turn on a 2 lane righ turn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SizzleSimmons @BRrebellion Well you both missed what I said. There’s a way to ask a question. I make sure my guys… https://t.co/Ck19lm2QBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @PhillyInquirer @JonathanTamari Maybe the Democrats shouldn't play political games with the presidents out… https://t.co/jaBEQm1pyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It becomes about cultivating and building an identity. One key component, no matter the resounding positivity, or t… https://t.co/i1tOlbJkiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scalpanika @_leannereneexo Fuck I wish I could of went to breakfast this morning!! Tm for sure haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpuopolo @LindseyGrahamSC @USAmbIsrael Never heard of seismic sensors dumbass?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox @KFCBarstool President Trump cheated on his current wife while she was pregnant and shortly after she… https://t.co/GWjLJxxR0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you my lil boo, im going to test your limits, im gonna wanna fight, allat 🤣 niggas be fine mad &amp; “fighting”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTelevisa_com @CarlosLoret @yeidckol Y si los ve, mejor se queda callada. Obvio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VMS had such good documentation, and the commands are like a text adventure game. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our invite must have been lost in the mail @brentcarcher @seeburnett @arebake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting sick right before hosting an 11-game tournament is definitely #SIDProbs but the show must go on. Time to ge… https://t.co/GNci5eiy1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner… https://t.co/kpb1jzv0Hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cezarykrysztopa @AndrzejDuda @AndZyberto Czyli zalozenie zaklada pan warunek ze postepowanie A spowoduje reakcje B… https://t.co/J1lx5rLLpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ajbend @franklinleonard @justitia77 It’s true i can’t remember a movie running that long at the Vista since I’ve lived in the nabe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never really did a girl wrong cause ima faithful guy but I could've treated one a little better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter I suspect #Coulter of a hidden agenda, otherwise her constant carping about the Presid… https://t.co/RrmpHu7E8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murphy The #Boxer 🐕🦴 Says 50° 👀🌬 And no I didn’t fart either 😆Windout #Lazysunday 🤷‍♂️Nascar 🏁 good morning all ☕️… https://t.co/ABumoSepFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HennyGod_ Right people are weird lmao I also think it’s cause a black man is dating a white woman, they’ve been up… https://t.co/CVqWucwVKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[APAGON cumplió mas de 50 horas matando bebés por falta de oxígeno. La mayoría de los hospitales no cuentan con plan… https://t.co/JIqpxkwFE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisHilton @christiancowan @powerpuffgirls @shesthefirst @kevinostaj That can’t possibly be any cooler! Who’s you… https://t.co/h5uESKJeeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinwb10 @dannyhackett97 Trying to get you to give my buddy a shoutout (@theillest313 )for getting into one of t… https://t.co/zXl349eaS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyeEddyBruce @CoachWilly1875 @SoccerParenting It makes me happy when two people’s work I enjoy are able to connect. 👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting a shooting on location in WPB on the film Ask Aldo with Guy Richards #standupcomedy #askaldo… https://t.co/9tqdzG4rcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[PORCUPINE HARANGUING!  I swear I’m getting closer to figuring out how this game is played]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanSohn It has been this way for years. Progressive ideology has become dogmatic. This is why you find liberals rebelling against it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching this grown woman in the front row sleep while I can’t in the 3rd... https://t.co/xBk3Mk7WXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude cancel the fucking season. Who in the damn hell said it’s ok to give him $13M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is also big news today. #ProChoice #antiabortion   "Trump administration bars clinics that provide abortions o… https://t.co/C2wO0LASDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitivamente la mejor presentación de In my blood  https://t.co/8zrBPKg8q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoeschutte7 Omg girl I’m having some of the same feels during my midterms rn hahaha! You got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Bert! Check out today's #sockoftheday! #sockgame #ilovecrazysocks #sockgameonpoint @ BackSpin Golf Shop https://t.co/c64WalLuKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lightning win 50th of season, tie for fastest in NHL history https://t.co/gsnQDS6bEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toriamos Hey can you meet me in pensacola i have dropped the drink and what you to get me that chance sorry if i came on to strong before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenCarman Correct me if I’m wrong but didn’t Trevor Bauer tweet about “playing with a drone”this past season?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames I read you made 86 million last year. After fed. taxes that is about 55 million (if you paid full 36%.)… https://t.co/vjqW3dJTcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_A_Blevins Ever wonder what kind of workout gives a man massive forearms but no biceps?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @RadioFreeTom I think a buffoon like Trump who acts like a spoiled diaper baby and pathological lyin… https://t.co/nTfzhGigBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domluszczyszyn Opened the flood gates for Leafs' fans (sponsored by Kleenex) to come pouring through.  But I agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be out on the boat while your all in school! @brookestarkk @spartankate #betrueblue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niegate @lunalucia23 @Viernes_Sabb @Reforma @NicolasMaduro @dcabellor ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chad_bowen @kevinwatson @RitterChris Does someone have the blue graphic that summed up each plan? Something like “… https://t.co/gLOEoxcKbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️ is was in the air for @Braves that stayed behind today’s https://t.co/JZ5f8OLauN 2 watch them @ casual practice.… https://t.co/WZVfUb63mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nutmeggles @ChrisEvans Can you literally shut up? Omg dan is a republican Chris please get away!! This is exactly… https://t.co/Sb5jyGSG2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreelyRangers and Old Town/Orono hit the ice for warmups for the boys Maine Class B State Championship #mesports… https://t.co/EB2kwlOTda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom told me to bring a tuber ware to dinner, I said I’m bringing an aluminum tray 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storms southeast of Birmingham are capable of producing strong gusty winds https://t.co/qgBQHD9U4M https://t.co/uMVvWEFjho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Why don’t you go back to whatever shithole you crawled out of !! 💩💩💩🤮🤮🤮😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsherDeMontreal @3Rev_ITSDavis @ITF_Forum The most relevant analog seems to be utilities. Either you have a highly… https://t.co/UGeWAuzrEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never not have a  https://t.co/BmDSwIG8zx tab open when doing writing of any kind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was part of this amazing show wearing originals by @HausOfBetch for the raw art event last night in Los Angeles https://t.co/158i7iDZO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[V excited about 2019 Indy concerts so far  @Houndmouth Apr 26 @zacbrownband May 25 @JohnMayer Aug 12  Now just need @arizona 🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vonnielopez You were amazing and should be the winner of @WorldsBestCBS May God continue to bless and anoint you! #Anointed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karaoke Tonight! 6-9! And Excuse me.... Taco Bell gets me every time! @ AJ's On The Bayou https://t.co/eS7TVxaTyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRabbit55 @MarkFusetti I don’t see the tweet anymore. Did Roc go to twitter jail again already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see more niggas at afters than  At regular house music functions  Cause niggas got no other choice  For afters… https://t.co/qT5W8mUock]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Yankees Spring Training! Had a blast. #Yankees #NewProfilePic https://t.co/DAWO6rOXmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contemplating the next move...#surf #girl #beautiful #day #surfinggirl #white #surfsup #surfphotography #surfgirl… https://t.co/i0mLhSseq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA as you have presented it, @realDonaldTrump, was already insulting and steeped in racism. Your policies and ac… https://t.co/qD5uwarp9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the #AdvanceCamp team for putting together this awesome event. One of the best educational opportunitie… https://t.co/DdOXop7z12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArrowheadTom if the Chiefs move up for Devin White then Brett Veach should lose his job. That's not a knock on the… https://t.co/qnnTfGauvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PhiladelphiaEagles Def is gonna light it up!  Gonna be first to say it, #eaglessuperbowlchampsLIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm reading "Called to Lead: 26 Leadership Lessons from the Life of the Apostle Paul" by @johnmacarthur which is ju… https://t.co/y2kHmPkl3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MarALardAss #TrumpIsTheNationalEmergency #FakeTrumpEmergency #FakeTrumpEmergency  #FAKENationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[No temptation has overtaken you except what is common to mankind. And God is faithful; he will no… https://t.co/zNzuvLsNU0]]></document></documents></author>