<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Stephan64042310 @toejackson34 @UPS It’s okay it’s a joke with me and @toejackson34 now 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 20, I was throwing mega house parties with my roommates and breaking back into the house with just a spo… https://t.co/Ga8q8yLGCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kara_vdM @PoklukarJ @s_msonia He sure is blushing something fierce... LOL.. Too adorable https://t.co/0uzHp9qUwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irockphilly Totally cartoonish! It’s so silly how many people on social media try and get away with this]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has to stop could you live with it call your congressman call your senators this is going to kill our little a… https://t.co/5cTpWLXHxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest game of the year coming up Thursday and the @NYIslanders play like a hot mess tonight? I think that sound i… https://t.co/MBku1lsiW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so beyond done with this back pain, man.  If someone knows anyone that will give me a new back I'll take their… https://t.co/IgX8OMZinn]]></document><document><![CDATA[After @keloland investigation landlord gets house back: https://t.co/PLZ1PjApKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked up KP at Disney World and apparently this past July they had Kim and Ron there (I guess for the live actio… https://t.co/kN2bXZMTaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlatuBaradaNiko Okay Gretchen, I don’t even want to know how you are so organized and developed on here.🤣 I have d… https://t.co/6NL43MSrIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTooCanBeGuru Yes!  @ScaryMommy’s is private and it makes no sense to me at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrBobbyBones talks so fast sometimes I think I’ve got my podcast on fast forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Glütiny Pale Ale by @newbelgium @ 30th ave south jacksonville beach fl 32250 — https://t.co/6lbyrWYQzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grandoftwo She’s young and trying to prove herself because everyone rather comment on her looks. She know’s the co… https://t.co/53czyZOb3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holmes Mentorship Program in full effect. Teamwork makes the dream work!!! @NISDEsparza @YMartinez36 @GGarcia198… https://t.co/7CAwmHnJCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The few loving amazing people in my life make it all worth it. Thank you to the people who have never left my side♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdinaryCDN They should be sorry, anyone with Trudeau should be sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JNoyesMaker I truly just wanted to know what he had slated because FIRST MAN shouldn’t gotten more hype. and I was… https://t.co/6yeX7rV2VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSchaefer53 @NMRLaBorde @CHNOLA @CHPedsHaylock @CHNOLAgroninger @amajaxn @LouFragoso @CHNOLAPedRNLead… https://t.co/NWH5QsAm1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyCannavale @howardhafkin @mespo2013 @Robert_NYMetro @sheehang632 Awesome job Denise]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NotesFromNationalEmergency Day 3. Just waking up, peeking out from the covers. Everything’s quiet, but it’s taking… https://t.co/LrLPUbn0cB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work bring results - been trying to get 1-2 workouts in every day. This stuff works.  - - - #winter2019… https://t.co/Tx4Uykoj94]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I mean, it is fine. He looks cute.” - me “He is wearing all black.” - H “I want to wear a handsome shirt” -4yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What to do on a rainy day in Fort Lauderdale? Watch a movie at @IMAXSOFL and check out the exhibits at @IMAXSOFL 😊☔ https://t.co/aMFFtxWqso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NasirDickerson3 @Carlynnx02 I would have walked out. No human being deserves to be spoken too like that #USA. #wearebetterthenthat]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all do respect, Representative Lee, Kamala Harris won’t help you there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to someone you like for even a minute can make the day so good ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #Insurance job in Indiana? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Collisio… https://t.co/rQWwF01Qaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beckawrites Adriana's mood on a semi-regular basis lol https://t.co/K8fogPnwYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSharits It was a directive.  No time for pleasantries...the twittersphere responded accordingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton I have never been been a supporter or a fan of D Trump. I believe him to be a pathological liar, a… https://t.co/SaVbvRcFEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioTrist10 @derekensign @OrlandoCitySC @AustinFC Number 2!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the bday tonight at updown then Westport. See ya there, or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caliicoder3 @dlmerrill @KamalaHarris @SenWarren @CoryBooker @SenGillibrand Faces of evil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion Dictator Donald Trump will declare National Emergency to build a wall. Will also declare Martial Law and take away your guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Devil is working with the Democrats and spreading evil while doin Satan’s work. https://t.co/vlaRNOKFaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How common are #links with traffic across the top 10 #SearchResults? - @timsoulo [@Ahrefs Study]… https://t.co/efroX1uQuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading down to Miami for @500Startups #UnityandInclusion Summit! Stoked for the event and to learn more about the… https://t.co/48QGlvmai4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems want background checks on Americans but if illegals try to buy guns ICE CANNOT BE CALLED. Democrats Always for… https://t.co/97kfn4EG81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone get the feeling like the makeup is being done on them when watching a makeup tutorial, almost like porn… https://t.co/Jlaxa8QU5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @TheMikeClayton8 Lol new face for false flags.  Have to laugh because it is so tragically sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weluvlibertyUSA @WSJ Send your kids to coal mines.  Thank God the majority of Americans want to protect our planet for future generations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, i just wanna break up all your shit call your mama phone and let her know she raised a bitch 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Pasadena Museum of California Art (PMCA) https://t.co/TH5X7BvnAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a husband that hates The Bachelor so much that he wears noise-canceling headphones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze All you can do is Shake your head anymore! Everything is out rages!🤢😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting Aiden on a schedule made everything better. Once something “fell out of place” that’s when the outburst beg… https://t.co/pcDCkIb2st]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh u guYs i made colcannon for myself here (yes my homesickness peaked) but i made it with kale and purple cabbage… https://t.co/lyBiKSyAR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakesLatte99 @CNN Please another troll, who believes everything he reads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from all day errands, and changed into my PJ’s at 3:30pm. It’s about to get turnt up in here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like the days leading up to fyre festival are a lot like sorority recruitment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fltsteve I'm getting to that point myself... I have so many books and movies. I have roommates and I keep everythi… https://t.co/tIaSvA8rTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed speaking yesterday to @UVALaw Professor Crystal Shin’s Public Interest Law and Advocacy Skills class about… https://t.co/NDRrENjbyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Guys I swear we’re not cops. We’re just a non-descript food truck. We sell food.” #SXSW2019 #sxsw https://t.co/2PPhDkDZLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I done called like three different weed 🔌’s and I guess they all in a meeting 😂😂😂🤷🏽‍♀️🤣 #nohustleatall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucess at Hanoi Sumit for trumps Bucket List :a; went a round with Fu-man-chu  (aka)Kim Long Un. (b) Went to Vietna… https://t.co/SMObkTx6Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glassed study rooms in the center of the library. Teens busy with school projects and crafting. https://t.co/G7g45Gjcur]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to cap-off #ReadAcrossAmericaDay here at @syracuselatin - Thank you @lhandsyr for bringing in Moose to r… https://t.co/3mFxe1ar0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise Reagan only ended the Cold War without firing a shot if you don’t include the proxy war he waged in N… https://t.co/Dbjqayb61a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmlarese Why can’t you have both? It’s not 1995 anymore...these platforms play nice with each other. Be open to se… https://t.co/prcMXdHrK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making a little bit of progress tonight on #intellectualdishonesty @ Commerce, Georgia https://t.co/UT3ZrAZnhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kleversh90 @ClaireR585 @CNN I think we will be in a depression by the end of the year unfortunately]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maldito sea el gurú🎤 Que levantó entre tú Y yo un silencio oscuro🎧 Del que ya sólo sales Para decirme:vale Ahora es demasiado tarde Bla bla]]></document><document><![CDATA[This house swears fealty to House Blum. @jason_blum @blumhouse https://t.co/ljSYnNl6xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed! This is an amazing article that gave me some new thoughts on things I’ve been working through at my site ri… https://t.co/CRktmNfTyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[TBTuesday to last weekend...grey beach day full of adventure. Now back to work for the week. @ North Myrtle Beach,… https://t.co/cMXSPSNXIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't believe that my Senator @SenBobCasey voted against his party!! @SenateDems]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much estrogen in the air! It is great, to be a woman. #happyinternationalwomensday @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/iIJO4XkBiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHIMPSINSOCKS happy birthday Beautiful! Hope you have a wonderful day today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussKlettke @maggieNYT Oh, pshaw. The site posted the whole version on it's site. Do your own damn research, stop spreading your own lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanKLieb @thebakingnanna1 @Rob_C_Allen You're making me so curious! Online I found "a small fruit cake with a… https://t.co/ceU1OyJiXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The vanity chair inspired by Vako Design. #ids2019 #artdeco #furnituredesign #design #toronto #lighting… https://t.co/54hKz8dUuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT OKAY IM NOT… https://t.co/Ns5l2eI2zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoltTracknField @ATCAnna @northliberty @gazettedotcom @SwimICWest @BoltGirlsSoccer - you ladies/coaches want to jo… https://t.co/b73JLpf9uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to my side hustle hoping someday there will be pay equity #HappyInternationalWomensDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I snort lines of lavender it’ll make me hyper-relaxed...right? https://t.co/DTyFrFvzJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that episode when Snooki’s put her ass in the fridge because she burnt it in the tanning beds? Sorry Hampt… https://t.co/xnF1ApIR7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this was literally HELLA crazyy... and the next day when he ran the 5k he SPRINTED the entire last lap. Like… https://t.co/E6UmUbJBkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellevueDotCom @BVUEjared @ParellaLewis @BellevueRadar @innab @sweetnesscater @BellevueLfstyle @Chrisbell85 Fun do we have an eta for open?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC They're trying to intimidate with their ignorance. Don't let them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ainda são 20 horas e acabei de acordar de um cochilo e custando a ficar com o olho aberto  Certeza que só vou acost… https://t.co/y7zZ5Cimdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Trump was aware of longtime adviser Roger Stone's efforts to reach out to WikiLeaks” https://t.co/juqIQZC6BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey if anyone knows a medical examiner in their life can you ask them if a pulmonary embolism death is painful? Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patbuckley10 @conormac122 Congratulations Connor! Truly a great player and even better person!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discussing the value of engaging our APPs to their maximum potential in our healthcare systems. Tune in, @RI_ACC… https://t.co/OjkcD588R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m patiently waiting for @MorganCWallen to rock a mullet like this next https://t.co/QhqdajxKFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok finished the series and I’m wrecked. First, the overall story line was great and the character development was p… https://t.co/ZoNwqDeDym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephan_Tyson @Vegunz @AMAAnimalRescue @_PJParker_ @Canine_Rights @DogRescue2014 @Burtonportrescu @cassandra17lina… https://t.co/EnPttPxY8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am honored to chair the Seaport Economic Council, and we were pleased to award a grant to Eastham last summer to… https://t.co/vkGBF73iPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[***TRAFFIC ALERT***  Two lanes closed on University Drive between Ramblewood Drive and Atlantic Boulevard. Turning… https://t.co/pVt2VhH0yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh Bersin nails it again! We have all got to make time for learning and this article provides practical ways to i… https://t.co/lEDddKHzLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engaging discussion at multidisciplinary stone conference on hyperPTH, nephrolithiasis, and ureteral strictures led… https://t.co/w7ymEGsaSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son gave me these today for Valentine’s Day. 😳😳 I said “awww son, I thought you was gonna leave me hanging this… https://t.co/hnNrp4xKwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@theverizonarena has been transformed for @PBR! Join us on @KATVNews #Daybreak for a look behind the scenes. https://t.co/k1DrVWv0mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop the rain from falling I can’t stop my heart from calling you it’s calling you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too often we spend all of our time seeking God for answers to our problems when what we should be doing is just seeking God.👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hang in there spring lovers. Good news is we got 13 days left until Spring 🌷⚘ woop woop 🙌🙌 https://t.co/YApfU9BOeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My First Cosmetic Procedure | Dr Tracy Mountford  https://t.co/E19WTYYTQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett @FoxNews @w_terrence A Personal Check?!? You left a paper trail on top of it?!? Are you that DUMB??… https://t.co/WtQdpwy7F5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep.  Thank you @voguemagazine  #domesticviolence #domesticabuse #Misogyny Guys who can show their feelings are san… https://t.co/Sh5PHHTnMc]]></document></documents></author>