<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @Rosie Yes!!! In that case, I can wait til July!!! Otherwise, hurry up Mueller!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our energy introduces us long before we ever speak.  BE the person who’s energy radiates positive vibes and a real,… https://t.co/RAZJhBPHUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lydiiio Lmao it’s a real feeling! 😂 &amp; yeah I keep telling myself that, it sucks ass 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s an even better look at this missing fence on Grandview Ave. near Shaler Street. You can see the drop-off fro… https://t.co/XSQYdaYoIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would love to share the interview that aired this morning about our beautiful show but can’t locate it on the… https://t.co/1KM0IKc7fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PITA444 @ChapulinColoRed @goodmedicine4us @ncar999 @SURGDissection @USATrump45 @SweetKat111 @FaleroJr @TheSteveKon… https://t.co/T783qlVzUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWorldof_AJ @JawsCEOQB @Eagles I've been asking for these for YEARS. Please, Eagles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A remarkable day to relive key moments in our history with leaders (political and public service) who made it so.… https://t.co/FoWVxxH4jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LasVegas #ILEA Vendor Showcase is not something you want to miss!  A night with industry professionals enjoying fo… https://t.co/mVV69DJTKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[lately I’ve been feeling very unappreciated and sad, I do so much for certain people, for work,for school,for art,f… https://t.co/W9iilEOYVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a meeting tonight for Student ministry, during my talking portion I told the leaders not to give praise out l… https://t.co/V4HDwBnpZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RStarbridge @SBFNC @MSNBC @CNN @ABC @CBS @NBCNews @PBS My biggest complaint is that they cover the same story ever… https://t.co/o0DTDPJM4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[9% employee engagement. No one is surprised, though since we switched to a different survey company, maybe that's the difference...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHollywoodland Totally forgot to tell y'all about this one. It's inconsistent but very solid @CybelNfotd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m preparing notes for a seminar on being black in the workplace. Any thoughts or suggestions?? I would love to hear your feedback!!! ⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream journal:was trying to go out, my ex kept following me. Jeff Probst takes to me about a game where we could bo… https://t.co/mPMGx5xpLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, does this mean you believe criminal behavior is forgiven if the perpetrator simply sends a halfhearted apology… https://t.co/njN6UohFIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There needs to be a national dumb bitches day so we can feel appreciated and accepted]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY TURNED OFF THE MIC THIS IS WHY I WATCH THE OSCARS THIS TEA RIGHT HERE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though it's cold and ugly out here, and Im low key stressing off my midterm tomorrow, I'm still feeling good a… https://t.co/r70AXC8W4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile, there’s coffee. @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/Uvdydab3Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protect our wildlife and wild places, our natural heritage, and our clean energy future. Speak out here against oil… https://t.co/bprwNLWvEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooo I’m so annoyed! The DJ at prime bar is ok the radio LIT AF! Can even go the club, no dang bag!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essential oil diffusers can be toxic for cats: https://t.co/NcV1C4nHHH #CatsOfTwitter #cats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether or not #TS7 happens this week it’s a good PSA for swifties everywhere to start saving for tour and new merc… https://t.co/BmN446tFRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hahahaha. You gave up American citizens in favor of your dictator friend who tortures and starves… https://t.co/IFctV4pTVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBreslowWKRN @WKRN So again we have kids killing kids is unacceptable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blacklilmermaid You can't get surgery until 18 https://t.co/mcUJ1tINyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #Paris #drawstring #bags in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa https://t.co/Z0q7OmEhzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nivosupremo @mattrorabeck @itsbooyeah Thanks! It was a fabulous experience and I didn’t embarrass myself, so I’m happy :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @POTUS we actually needed you to do this. It may be the only good thing that comes of this fake national… https://t.co/eU6L8RslEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoMoreBS2017 Honestly, a fair portion. But also, a lot of that costs is in claims, litigation, advertising/marketi… https://t.co/44AmR2uNwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[All propaganda the swamp monster is running out of water what the hell NYC HE IS RUNNING THE STATE BANKRUP YOU NEED… https://t.co/zDEDxeJ0e9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not her religion wake up Remember 9/11 She’s part of another terrorist group!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is having a personal “bra lady” that comes to your home!    #essentialbodywear #braladyamanda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinDuplantis Anyone who is negative is either 1. A complete asshole and you know plenty 2. Jealous because they… https://t.co/eLJmTC0PkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never asked anyone to heal or cure me, nor do I expect anyone to. This is no one’s responsibility but my own,… https://t.co/XR7HeVgAFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mostsmartest @racatiwood @daveweigel She can win all the votes she wants, but if it doesn't get her to 270 it ain't a win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so funny seeing all the men frantically rushing through the Valentine’s isle last minute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaStJohnBoxer @kristoffstjohn1 @TheArtofJulian Praying for you Mia...🙌😇😥...you got this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt AENGDU saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea (Mini #DogMeat #Farm) Now AENGDU is… https://t.co/qBmnAZ8Tv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeTwidda Grandmaster Flash was ahead of his time. I love old school rap. I grew up on metal and rap. My friends a… https://t.co/1KjMMS39JG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzelibrarian @Jenny_Trout It's also in 'Being Erica', a Canadian TV show that surprised me when it revealed itself to be Canadian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TmahoneyA @garrettelliott I went to the lunchtime protest... not many people are able to attend at that time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC Thank you @JesseKellyDC.  A bunch of horrible scare tactics.  All four of my grandparents lived throu… https://t.co/fSQEYXthJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t believe everything you hear. There are always three sides to a story: yours, theirs and the truth.  A new add… https://t.co/wZDK9gaiz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRINITY_NG Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight.  https://t.co/dV1bRqmseN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got this!! #transform20 #day40 #cut #shaunathon #fitat49 #almostdone #6weeks #20mins #fitmom #momstrong… https://t.co/nBGQ8KXF9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone fell off my bed and the screen came off and I fixed it (thankfully) ... then I dropped it in the toilet...  so this is my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adulting es que ayer me consiguieron 2 disfraces para salir en la batalla de flores y el tiquete estaba regalado pa… https://t.co/VRDjtfGghK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chelsea in the Uber last night “ I have a feeling we gonna for today Kiarah it’s gonna be one of those nights “   😢😢😢😢😢😢😢😢😢😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[To indo no shopping fazer compras com a minha chefe, mano o banco do carro dela faz massagem, eu to vivendo num mun… https://t.co/JVfuCnZPDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re hoping I fall down, I am praying you get on your feet ... we are NOT the same !]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful sunset in the Arizona desert #nofilter @ Anthem, Arizona https://t.co/CM5nxa2EWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristy_QS Pues piensale, también puedes leer los comentarios de la ropa]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all who are or have been a care giver, I’ve been there too. Here’s to you! Happy Care Giver Day! https://t.co/rvU6h3ZSsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do states in the NE know about the situation on the southern border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guyaustin9 @TexasMonthly @arielle_avila Lol says the guy who apparently doesn’t even live in Austin...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I woke up to my alarm (that never happens) and I got not 8 - but 9 hours of consistent sleep (also never happens) #SpringFoward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders We can't afford Medicare for all. You shouldn't give people false hope. How will we pay for it? We a… https://t.co/xDjxoUzI4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine tasting before final stop in Sedona!  Sunday Funday!  @bebermeyer @artofwinesedona  thanks for the wine! 🍷🍷🍷… https://t.co/iDFRddmP9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endian Airforce is environmental hazard.  Killed 3 trees and damaged branches of one😒😒 #IndiaAgainstTreePlantation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperBuker @yo_mama_bot Yo daddy’s so fat he were a red shirt and he says hey hey hey it’s fat Albert]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t watched The Giver in 7 months, so I thought it was time to watch it again since I watch it like 3 times a… https://t.co/OtbEP5BTjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDaveGames @RealMikeKay YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAASSSSS https://t.co/44Hn4lYig2]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜 #mygirl #loveher #puglife #sassypotato #bosspug #puglove #blackpug #speakpug #mops #scarlet #guruscarletji… https://t.co/7JtbO92xra]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday  My youngest daughter &amp; grandson 6 yrs ago. They gave me a pop up visit. @ LaPlace, Louisiana https://t.co/JRr89vGErD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Schiff, what are you going to do when Mueller proves that Pres., Trump is not guilty of collusion, after you h… https://t.co/DbHwS3Ps7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering what @GOP stands for. It's sure not fiscal responsibility. #grifterparty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @mattgaetz But didn't daddy hire @MichaelCohen212  as his personal lawyer? And curious about… https://t.co/kSMv4cDxLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryonnyM @HLAurora63 @RandPaul Who else is tired of these back stabbing republicans? Get them out of office, Start with Mitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This work is hard” - our trainer shares. Thank you to those that do the heavy, important work of dismantling racis… https://t.co/VhpbG0tMB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DR_defutebol @FilipeKunrath @anandamuller Nem conheço esses dois "jornalistas" hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi The problem is you are NOT for the people. This bill takes away VOTING rights. Besides, you gave awa… https://t.co/mepuaZwSD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy will call me cute and then call me ugly right after with kissy faces... maybe I should fuck around and say… https://t.co/Bl32RjGxfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Yesterday, "They can't take it, they are the guilty parties at the National Security Agency" who conducted… https://t.co/L9Zo2D6QTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing out our #solarpowered ovens as part of our #ebdteems fourth grade unit!  Can the melt a S’more?  Collect da… https://t.co/miW2XeLmy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicole1124 @grannyanon1969 @Great_Again2018 @LadyNY4Ever @DaveSchreiber3 @Trump_Girl_USA @BigErnie2020… https://t.co/IJeFvTQ4bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkronRubberDuck @Birdie_DuMonde 🤞classic rubber duck https://t.co/OkeEfwx8ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wahahaha kaya nga sbi ki bka makalimot nnman mahirap na! Bash natin mamya! Lam mo na! Hahaha  #POPSSSSMusikero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virginiahair1 @psychdr100 He is not intrested in what is above the waistline it is below he is intrested in.  Just… https://t.co/cl4u5TU5Qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picked up my traveling buddy in Phoenix. Next stop New Orleans, LA!  ✈️🌻🍀👏😍👍🏻🍸🍷🥃🍾🥂🥮🍤🎪🧹🎉 #thebigeasy #worklife… https://t.co/qvif6D30e1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Softball weekend kinda night!  So happy I can see my baby in person!! @ Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Central https://t.co/MPA3cuicnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xan_desanctis @JohnJHarwood CPAC attendees.. can't handle the truth.. so sad they live in their bubble and when tr… https://t.co/qIw7qGRsEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boryne @ROMEbeensaved @4ryss4 I was misinformed, and "clout" was not the reason why I spoke up against your rude, unauthorized video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[planning birthday trip, would also love suggestions on where to stay/things to do ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When God created me she said “mmm let’s take all the morning person out”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Underwater Dogs by Little Friends Photos. Love this photog! https://t.co/UOO8GyThO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry has died following a massive #stroke last week. #RIP Please take a minute to review stroke’s symptoms. M… https://t.co/6lnxNlIj1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabes un poco de todo, me proteges, me haces sonreír. Somos tan iguales, tan distintos pero tú me amas así. Sé que… https://t.co/Vqbi2TidWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is one of those nights where I am especially grateful for my dexcom. For those of you that don't know, it's… https://t.co/5V5MXDhyJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are likened to our priests, religious and all the pious and holy men and women in our church. They sought to l… https://t.co/bXqL6a5WXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7covers7days 7 covers over 7 days of books I love. No explanation or reviews. 1/7. Today I challenge… https://t.co/VTEl6COUGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SexCounseling @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Hey hey you aren't in Kansas anymore. Just click those fake  ruby slipp… https://t.co/zEYbMHEau4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chai and shortbread.  Perfect combination.  #chai #latte #matchalatte #matcha #tea #greantea #masalachai mw.brought… https://t.co/r2AondCMfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[And THIS account added me and said it was him..... keep in mind it’s a completely different name https://t.co/ZTK2r8MRR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ChrisVanHollen Passing paid family leave would give working women the time they deserve—and it would also benefit… https://t.co/E4dkZLeYvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖🧘🏻‍♀️💪🏼🥰 #sparkjoy #movingon #newjob #twoweeksnotice #newadventures #alwaysforward #newopportunites #growth… https://t.co/RG5L4qFRks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TG_isthe_Best Like I am use to the wait cause I get those extra credits for having a kid, but my friend gets the s… https://t.co/tQ3ioWO14w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarquisDMann @AlyMartin5 @adoreeamaya Ok remember my simple ass though.]]></document></documents></author>