<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Capi690 El único que hacía polémica buena era tu papá pero a ti no te sale, mejor así déjalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Really !  so ,she is a Female Democrat ,so , let us  let her  walk on this]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Make Room for Me by @jbutlerguitar, from #SoundHound https://t.co/XgDEEr0zm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we know why you have to take it a second mortgage on your house just to go to one fucking NFL game!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCMcrush “I was merely taking some horticultural notes!” https://t.co/RquDdepgZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @gtconway3d Right.  Not all Republicans.  There are about 5 or 6 of them.  Country over party.  Country over criminality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fine Dr. Using brachytherapy for #prostacancer #treattocure #oneyourdone #standardofcare #prostatehealth… https://t.co/2Prn9wToQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi really said “ain't got no time for no subliminals After awhile, bitch bein' petty just means you miserable Uh… https://t.co/wkWBa6pmdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrimmage 5pm today vs @chtigersbsb at Jordan. Field still needs to dry a bit and we will send out an update/final decision at 12-1pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orchid opening, day 3. #orchidee #orchid #orchidée #orchidées #orchids #phalaenopsisorchid #phalaenopsis… https://t.co/XWxsJ4cPup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OK_Dumbass @CNN He wanted a criminal lawyer to cover up his criminal actions. Covering up his sexual affairs was a… https://t.co/baMNFz4Ivd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lethalnicole Sometimes things just work out the way they should you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usarmyretired96 @Bamafanaticfan1 @realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @BetsyDeVosED Because if your asking that question you m… https://t.co/2CPMIyOWxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebstiles The problem with the 40/25 play clock is that it’s like a shot clock in HS basketball....very, very few… https://t.co/CVfCl3Ba5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! NBA unveils a futuristic jersey that allows you to change the text  https://t.co/FepaVIGjIP @SatCenterIM @satcenterDM @Drtamssen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@segalink I agree with you. I am so ashamed. Anyone who can think and who is not compromised, will easily arrive at… https://t.co/Qqvxaf8Y7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKelsoColt He lives here in #MiamiBeach #CEO #VirginCruises #VirginMobile etc etc etc...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyNolandFOX29 @MoshuluPhilly @TitosVodka @UnleashedPetco @ACCTPhilly @FundMac @Zoeann_NOA We can’t wait! 😻 https://t.co/DNgqFYWgud]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the REAL story. And how we’ve gotten to the place where this isn’t the story we are interested in is absolu… https://t.co/cLa3kxLHEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NascarChuck336  The reason that the lyrics to "O God, Beyond All Praising" should mean  a  lot to us is because ou… https://t.co/HtUHESVwrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboutArchie @CaseyNewton Yea I just wanted a nice dedicated app instead of chrome tab 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to share @SewaneeAdmiss with Orange County students. #OCPSGoes2College #SewaneeNearYou https://t.co/KaH9p7LMnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhdabbs @groves_chase @Delta That's why you growing a mullet, to keep your head warm when your hat gets lost?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonChron To better understand the Italian Psyche a 1976 movie "A Special Day" Italian housewife meets a Gay Go… https://t.co/vKB4W9J3cS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being with a guy from Brooklyn, NY has slowly changed my vocabulary. I’m saying stuff like “you talkin ta me?” and “let me tell ya somethin”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drugproblem @artaodza_ Really? Yeah, I think maybe she was leasing a piece of the map from the many, many performers before her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- why do you want to talk about this? C- I feel like other than the mind scape i am sane.  With the mind scape I a… https://t.co/YAKeS7O8cY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning from two of faves, @WAChamber &amp; @TheLimaChamber  at @CCEOhio re: their outstanding advocacy programs. https://t.co/p8fDZZm7hL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @MKBHD @Tesla @koenigsegg if I had to choose. https://t.co/Bj2AdeYPQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurts SOO good! If you have low back pain it could be due to your tight hips.  If the hips are tight it could be pu… https://t.co/mOrK7T47Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Since the 1930’s the progressive/democrat/left has tried to DESTROY the middle class. They’ve done so thro… https://t.co/ewu6TXHQ0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KingJames. If you fail on this Space Jam 2 I’m putting you in the “Smush Parker” category of Lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/CALrJ86jI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but ya gotta win the game. #isles otherwise we all look stupid. 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Crying with you and your daughter right now. Glad she is safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyElliot Every dunk contest last decade been trash. It’s just like the HR Derby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Costco dethrones Amazon as internet retail leader, report says  https://t.co/AQ3vppyYAJ #FoxBusiness. Shows the imp… https://t.co/pqsBRwuSzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Sera lo ultimo que hagan !!! El reino tenebroso de maduro está en pedazos y solo los mercenarios cubanos l… https://t.co/ZxV9lNwRfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riley Ridley is an explosive, flexible mover at the wide receiver position, who projects as a Day 2 selection in th… https://t.co/ZpI39MdUSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielllle3 @FQswp @zeldacanuck @HonAhmedHussen @MattDeCourcey La majorité des musulmans qui arrivent ici s'intègr… https://t.co/ERpCLdgrXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvePetThatDog @Twitter It’s about time! Now...get out there and pet. that. dog!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol don’t claim to be a gang banger if you gonna try to justify your snitchin “they stole from me” “kidnapped me” “… https://t.co/BOtY4ibjHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the work of @DPSNewsNow teachers like @allyorwig and colleagues @dizzvh and from @nextgenstoryli1… https://t.co/aZM5IYgAn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[PJ Morton &amp; JoJo did this!! I absolutely love this track. Thank y’all so much for the musical magic. #SaySo… https://t.co/kXGevJYjjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKevinConroy @willfriedle @HamillHimself @Paul_Dini You ain’t old! You just play old on tv!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weekley Morgan Freeman in Deep Impact is my favorite. A truly remarkable talent as an actor. https://t.co/YKtINlo5HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiked #southmountain here in #Phoenix with my bro @mattsheets from alaskanyi yesterday to @dobbinslookout Also got… https://t.co/13tXgEnkOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonmstirone @elakdawalla I’d do the whole thing but I’ve got to get to LAX 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Native Film Festival. (@ NETV in Lincoln, NE) https://t.co/bNcHstVFrG https://t.co/DH5BtlEuWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DAVIDANDTAMELA It’s really Sad that my foundation posted on Facebook asking for people to donate to a Single Mothe… https://t.co/OYJVme2F4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all the #Oscars winners tonight. Hopefully one day I’ll have the Honor to walk that same Carpet and cel… https://t.co/oGOyn1L6h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbcquestiontime When will the Brexit morons realize that it will ruin the country. The UK isnt a super power, no m… https://t.co/7wR32bpvTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VDHanson @wbmosler @StephanieKelton @SRuhle @DavidCayJ @RepDavidEPrice I am equal to you as a citizen peer of the… https://t.co/V9tix8Yl5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @GregSopko Oh, no. I've been treated for anxiety/depression on and off for years. It's just been particul… https://t.co/wT4SLKyAIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenseiBryant Anytime Brodie you already know! Same here man enjoy your day champ! 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[A destroyer of?  #socalstorage #storage #badsign #notthebest #deathcomestousall  #selfstorage #losangeles… https://t.co/Xchv1Ql0TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have y’all ever seen Queen Mother Vera Hill on FB?  When I first saw her a year ago, I just knew she was playin.  T… https://t.co/aPqLDP6e9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤗🤗🤗 Watch live: Michael Cohen testifies at House Oversight Committee hearing https://t.co/aQQUeR6Jrn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeTrahan Dude is an idiot. The nfl literally tells you when their is a random drug test and you get tested once a… https://t.co/nLzbpBgCKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Power Up: Cracks show in wall of Republican support for Trump: (At least one anyway.)… https://t.co/YjDDLUJqNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAntWright The divisional structure makes the competition uneven, we see mediocre teams making the Championship… https://t.co/6b34ETn0oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran to them, grabbed Harrison and held him soooo tightly and for a VERY LOONG TIME. He cried and cried and cried… https://t.co/g5GQitIGLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Dutch #Teach https://t.co/S8kP8mIHTz #NationalBikeSummit #NBS19 #bikesummit19 @TheCLC2019 #BikeSummit 🚲… https://t.co/q1FJWEsqi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big thank you to Hannah and Emma and former LCBER Bella Boutiette for helping out on the tables tonight in our an… https://t.co/qKhuuc4t3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some trains and the #BostonGolfShow. Great way to spend a Sunday.... https://t.co/bBdq3OHm0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a way to mute tweets about soccer. Just couldn't care less about that stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drayzze @KenDawgzz Jasper gets a charge out of standing outside in his undies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After court, Young's attorney said he deleted messages before the court order to make more room on his phone. Says… https://t.co/meciMixQRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Mick has waved the white towel with 4 min left and saving Cumberland the extra minutes for tourney time.… https://t.co/CEWtiIBnte]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the @Phillies lineup. Is it the best in the NL? I think it depends on Harper. At 26, he is heading into his… https://t.co/KxTUjg8VLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiserdidier @betofloresRG690 @SoyJairRamos @10APG Antes se sabia que no podia jugar dos partidos por semana pero s… https://t.co/azWxzS7KBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleHaase That WCHA scenario they posted is really well done, though! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@893CP @theLegitCEO Question: is it more impressive to be successful with players that don’t really star at the nex… https://t.co/cer2CoDvK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo shows the cut CB got while in a fight. The guy slashed his leg with his knife but CB said the guy came o… https://t.co/Ncd7ZwhOCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying out new logos for the “going out of business” phase of MMH https://t.co/LxK2vDag2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regina King...  that’s what I call a SPEECH!!!!!  congrats on the win! #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I look tonight @jasoncollings ? @ San Luis Obispo, California https://t.co/I575k6OZ3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN LA COMICS..Might be time to move to Colorado you sexually repulsive 2 faced slobs. https://t.co/GazEd2gssj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: Iroquois defeats Lew Port 52-46 to advance to the A2 semis next Tuesday at Ken West.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was Trump not in Munich?  Was it the emergency on the border; all those hordes of terrorists coming across?  No… https://t.co/qWdPBoLfz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[...The key point is what you will do. 'Ruling out' involves using future-tense verbs. Period.  Elizabeth Warren pla… https://t.co/fqk4o3pUes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-reading and revisiting prior annotations of @biblioracle's WHY THEY CAN'T WRITE: "In reality, every piece of wri… https://t.co/Y3nnxRUjg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something Big Is About To Happen, [DS] Trapped And Desperate - Episode 1... https://t.co/PUX5H2qFN5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bunnyspatial I loved this. I hope they bring Most Stuf to the vanilla cookie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan @Timcast No thanks. Jack is full of shit.  His platform protects pedophiles.  Fuck that guy.  Who is on tomorrow?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The organization formerly known as the International Humanist and Ethical Union has rebranded in a very cool way. B… https://t.co/VbpLJ4cGSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelFinkelman Does Ethan Happ realize that you are actually allowed to just shoot a layup from the side of the bas… https://t.co/eW9OL160wS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went as far as pausing my watch today and saying that I had run enough before remotivating and doing another mile… https://t.co/NHgQD78c9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FtSumterNPS looking forward to visiting this weekend! Question: is there a separate passport stamp available at Fort Sumter itself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[To find your best self, you must lose your weak self. @glrosario_ . . . ● .  #glrosario .  George L. Rosario NYC's… https://t.co/IxtwqSPm6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Innocent man???  You are as corrupt a person as there has ever been in the White House!!  A criminal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelMannella1 I love tequeños more than...Mozzarella sticks. But nothing like #HawaiianPizza https://t.co/DBUcfHmFFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinncy @SaraJBenincasa And there are millions of “Aunts and Uncles” who will accept you for you. Don’t be fooled,… https://t.co/E5jl5YZeoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dixie_picker1 @ScoutSteveR I was born in La, lived 15 mins from Baton Rouge, so yeah, I know how to get there. As… https://t.co/aTQNPk8f70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarciaLJessica @citymuseum Also I haven’t seen you in forever so you definitely wouldn’t drive me crazy. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineMCook1 @Dr1ven_Ind @AnneMossRogers @TheGenuineU @BipolarBattle @Alycelauren2 @laura_corbeth… https://t.co/szrDefSV0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDrury559 @boettger_eli Yes, Fresno State should win but Air Force won't make it easy given their style of play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ariana still won’t reply to my DMs. Doesn’t she know that I have to get my prom guest pass by March 8th?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joyryde  Dubloadz b2b dack janiels  Subtronics  Saymyname Diplo (cuz mans can partyyyy)  Yung pinch  Lil uzi vert h… https://t.co/gUeWyAVGNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiembouvier @CollinsMandy Right after reading yours...bad day all round?]]></document></documents></author>