<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[my mom says I look like a 12 y.o. k-pop star in this photo ? #NewProfilePic https://t.co/aV0K3eXba0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewVeasey Yes they will which is why I don’t think Harper will opt out and if he does then I’m ok with it, mor… https://t.co/GQUVqBoZ2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captainothehunt @HaileyPiperSays @GeneforTexas My child has a medical exemption. Now what do you have to say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[📈🚨The most Tweeted about people at #SXSW so far🚨📈 1. @AOC  2. @BillNye  3. @JordanPeele  4. @Lupita_Nyongo  5. @leinilyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1035KISSfmBoise Have you seen this @NKOTB gem yet? #BoysInTheBand https://t.co/wcIaRmUvEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have THE SWEETEST husband. I have always loved looking at these flowers...... and they last an ENTIRE year! We do… https://t.co/kgd7S43s75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyiDee I gotta check them out. I never knew they sold that type of Jewelry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaymondBeeze Obviate derives from Late Latin obviare (meaning "to meet or withstand") and Latin obviam, which mean… https://t.co/dfZkbPR0Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special shoutout to the friends that understand your decompression needs and ask if you’re truly up for a back to b… https://t.co/vKl1H4w0z5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Etiquette Lessons:  so Jackie how do you eat the bread?  Me:  is it gluten free?  #TheBachelor #Celiac]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been completely dairy free for a month and haven’t ate meat in 9 days and I feel like I’m a feather floating through life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a little State Championship wrestling. Go Indians! @ Propst Arena - Von Braun Center https://t.co/hZQDDhLKzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: It’s not a new trend, but I would love to integrate some digital resources into my library! We’re not a 1:1 sch… https://t.co/nzuzohbuC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you are starting a small business or just considering your options, it is vital to understand business laws… https://t.co/BCWN4IuAJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaaneel_ Dc stepped on his toes and that’s a big dude I know it hurt 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell my family that I have a ton of stuff in my car and can only fit like 3 people, all they seem to hear is… https://t.co/Bxsso437Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know when I hit the age that I have to down a handful of Advil to sleep 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @NWMOSTATE! Facility Services up at 0400 hours clearing roadways and walkways. https://t.co/2VpTGECJmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom who lives on a mountain in Sweden "It almost feels like April!.......it's about 4C!"    😂     Which is like maybe 35F, burr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do i keep thinking that eating before kickboxing class is a gr8 idea 🙄🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/9ZhRyciElG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayPenison @MSNBC @NBCNews A stereotype of black people is that they are inherently lazy. But, you knew that already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nataanii_Means Demons good vibes your way homie. Glad to hear you’re stepping back to take care of yourself. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who actually want you around will make effort for you. So people who just want you around when it’s convenie… https://t.co/lCAJBt8Qap]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t listen, you won’t learn.  #ItIsAnOptionToListen @ True North Mediation https://t.co/MI7AuPL0cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UNCENSORED @TasiasWord ♥️♥️♥️ My baby!! I love you tasia!! 😘😘 https://t.co/qzF3WJJbjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @roddy202620 @mitra9816 @BFISA @gator4kb18 @KevinMFerrara @Libphobic @trumpAngel45 @Stephen57036680… https://t.co/a4LXhmsOLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uuuuummmm all these men giving women advice on how to spot a whore. Where is there advice for the men? Game recogni… https://t.co/o53hRK1FL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[so could ya just stop thanks. I’m doing great. You are just annoying at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mas_critical @undead8bit @whenbatmenfly As far as we know. Flerkens are sentient creatures with a fully functionin… https://t.co/W9LFaFlzC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noahs mom saved the petals from the first bouquet of flowers Noah bought me for our flower girl to throw down the a… https://t.co/7YXV7Ho1aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC You too!  I hope I wake up in time to watch you tomorrow. Look forward to your comments on 45’s speech on Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drop everything and read for Dr. Seuss week! We celebrated with our 2nd and 3rd grade buddies! @LanderSchools… https://t.co/kqaJeMnlw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaDKline @LSUBasketball Man you petty. I woulda texted you congrats if y’all won]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat just woke me up by licking the VapoRub off my throat &amp; chest &amp; now I’m disgusted. 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCiccarello Of course I hope I’m not a nuisance with my posts and remarks😬😍🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siudan2 @JewishLabour @JolyonMaugham US elected Trump. I support Israel not its gov.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ Plesse HELP SWEET SENIOR DUTCH by SHARING his story, so he can get OUTTA this… https://t.co/ZgSCd65BPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Detox Your Stress Glands to Shed 15 Pounds in 20 Days  https://t.co/UeY9hKHoXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️💗 Nada mejor que descubrir nuevos destinos junto al amor de tu vida! #tbt #mexico Con mi gordovallejo  Aprovecha… https://t.co/tOnV5M6jv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rest in Paradise my beautiful Voice sister @janice_freeman !  Gone too soon but wow...heaven's choir gained the BES… https://t.co/nlgcBeUWDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingggJohngg @pwillisjr @yagirltoomuch @_shantwan Where where you when their grades were slipping? Weren’t you pay… https://t.co/O42lTvJypI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panda does not make her pedicures easy for me. 😆 @ Albany Park, Chicago https://t.co/OPs2FZJuy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldBankWater @SOILHaiti Great to see @SOILHaiti. Always good to donate to them. Also good to consider how much s… https://t.co/0NxCkpofon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlrd What a twisted, vile human...now REAL victims will be assumed to be liars...shame on you, @JussieSmollett  fo… https://t.co/Rk7rtDFkyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOUISIANA BOARDWALK GETTING A DOLLA TREE??? now it won’t be $500 million in debt!!!!! https://t.co/FPNC3cPizM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinAllen_14 @netflix THANK GOODNESS. That just made my whole day 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not a good judge of weight because marshmallow fluff is very light but the stated blood pressure is definitely… https://t.co/VpGVUrTKRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMcKoon @thecjpearson You better tell God all about man don’t control the weather!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prranch We weren’t fans of it, either. Which felt like an extra bummer because Force Awakens mad eusbfeel like the… https://t.co/NTwuziJsSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolChief Drowning my sorrows from last nights loss with some retail therapy https://t.co/9HJK5ozD6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realblancaster and @collin_davison : I have found #ATK on YouTube! Been binge watching the last few days! So happy… https://t.co/tduZJmACTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day #RhettRun  #dogsofinstagram #dogs  #Barnstable #CapeCod #Beach #Capecodliving #capecodlife… https://t.co/cUEwWKpfBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re one of those people who use dating apps to find friends please DM me and explain why]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday to the best tire changer around!!🎉🎉@mmegery20  hope your day rocks🤩💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booty and leg day. Trying to make this thing grow! 😂 🍑 ____________________________________________________________… https://t.co/e7KOXQdBLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuzzy Wuzzy #auntiemsprofessionalpetcare #petnanny #petsitting #petsitter #loudouncountyva #itsacatslife… https://t.co/dTL5PolmeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[what would be a first step if one wanted to adopt a child from Venezuela @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melanin Beauties-Sherina Mikasa https://t.co/LMo7nnKaBT via @YouTube: women who envy my daughter.  Oprah Winfrey is… https://t.co/kYmJLFX26a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahcasciano @ImKileyDavis @PatrickQuarter Yea, because we have inbound marketing and multiple emails lists. But y… https://t.co/f8GKeR79Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New comedian working the circuit must be code for "can't get my career off the ground, so I'll virtue signal by c… https://t.co/24bnwnJ8EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonkurtz @redsteeze And what about the milk they produce and the cheese? Stop enjoying that too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seabiscuit7 Just started about half hour ago. Storms not here yet but it's raining]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus said that I am not a 🇯🇲 Witch. He said I am a Child 🧒 👶 of God. I have the ability to Write for the Nation🌍.… https://t.co/nM3RiVLyT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled this fund has launched in DC! @capitalimpact and The Clark Foundation can’t wait to see this #placebased… https://t.co/YZBjUPwRrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerLetsRoll @kcinor @Hulk4Trump @FemFoxx @garway95 @janasea21 @jhudson176 @SealeyGerald @Lmchristi1 @TeedIsMe… https://t.co/KNq0IHuODQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out after finishing up install for tonight’s event @uclarec #ucla #uclabruins #rainyafternoon☔️… https://t.co/HxP1D2bICd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_benfanti ain’t nothin too soon about that, he’s already tryna add his students back on facebook acting like we wanna be friends w him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylieWhitman3 @LukasGraham See honey I told you.. This is a most uniqe and wonderful group!! Keep listening... I p… https://t.co/imR9xzOjFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What's that smell in this room? Didn't you notice it, Brick? Didn't you notice a powerful and obnoxious odor of me… https://t.co/CGUGeMhLwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[To follow my previous post, here is a quick and simple baby bok choy recipe. 🌿 . I know not all of you have condime… https://t.co/7fqOf6XI8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antitrumpresist @OjPats4 Her resume is fake.  Why pretend to be a book publisher if you're not?🤔🤥]]></document><document><![CDATA[whyyyy are virgo boys so attractive to me?????? they just love messing with my feelings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am late to the party that is @leonbridges newest album but hi I have arrived and lemme tell ya, it’s a good time 🎉✨🕺🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taxes are finally filed! Here’s to getting some money to pay a couple of bills 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to know all the bones in the body for my exam tomorrow and I’m STRESSED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kathlee72011373 @jennycohn1 Oh PLEASE.   If they were "more concise" they would not say WHAT IS NECESSARY TO SAY n… https://t.co/CUOtfbUxaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakfastislife @peterjhasson Then there is Linda Sarsour whose exact words are "you shouldn't humanize jews" Mayb… https://t.co/CvMG5GnAU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[RORAIMA 2X 48FT, 2X 72FT Adjustable Straps, 2X Carabineer Hooks $9.96  Copy Link:  https://t.co/DnB6wC46M6  Thanks… https://t.co/3NPyqfKjvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name: Pepper  Qualities: cuddles and energy  What I actually call her: peppins, salt n peppa, mini Dalmatian, spice… https://t.co/Jk4wHB6Sw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[although Matt can really get on my nerves sometimes, I sure am one lucky girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeless @casamarinakw  in Key West , #firstkiss , #brideandgroom , #weddingdress , #keywestwedding , #luxury ,… https://t.co/pKbnKdD3n2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheap and don’t care about picking up a disease. Police stated “minimal hygiene.” Rape and filthy conditions. Serio… https://t.co/6NjPMZoixg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our own Joey Drews present Microsoft Teams (a new communication tool). ESLnteacher will have their own team and can… https://t.co/JhmdpEpYR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxipam Jajaja exacto!! Pero para morirse de frío mejor el calor de largooo. Wisconsin estimado 🥶🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Mexico, neighbors in Colonia Roma celebrate @alfonsocuaron. Shout out to the #interpreters bringing th… https://t.co/MGEo2wsPab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I’m very upset @METROHouston and I have all day to tell the upstanding ppl of @HoustonTX all of my train horror… https://t.co/HgirjhiP11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC The President lies continuously about everything-try to get your journalistic priorities straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don't poop without Putin's permission. You are the traitor. We believe McCabe. We believe Come… https://t.co/B4vC9BhYte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Lied @ affair w/Ms. Clifford, told over 8,000 LIES Rigged Our 2016 Election w/Putin he LIED Helsinki Summit M… https://t.co/OF5MVH3ckc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ieizlem When it came  to MI or Bir litre gözyaşi - many more I won’t name -ratings is relevant indicator of qualit… https://t.co/98r6sDuqUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @KamalaHarris The only different between Kamala and a snake is she has hips!!!  What a piece of work… https://t.co/uFEhseLP1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[it makes me sad when i can’t find the music my boyfriend puts me on to ):]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing so now. It's a process but you have to be able to look inside, acknowledge your actions, and grow from them.… https://t.co/9uMwRYy39W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrowingEastMoCo @MCPS @justupthepike “On this map, you can see how there are a number of cases where over-utilized… https://t.co/fV8qwoMPx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_JamieLloyd_x @BillyHi01173863 Good nobody’s picking on you or anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear thunder? Believe it or not, we went from seeing snow to thunderstorms in less than 24 hours! https://t.co/aOPIbcUecr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, think about how you might strengthen your soul. Search for ways to be kinder, more inclusive,  more open-min… https://t.co/qzpymDSXUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys my best friend FaceTimed me last night from AUSTRALIA just to see what sweatshirt I wanted. I don’t deserve her 😭 @NicoleNiebs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Callejón Cultural Barrio Antiguo in Monterrey, Nuevo León https://t.co/nIIMHvUmwA]]></document></documents></author>