<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Getting homework done before my Florida vacation. #2MoreDays #GetMeOutOfThisCold https://t.co/ElVnk4G7Mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast #entertaining at Miss Gay Supernova USofA Newcomer last night. Congrats to Anahi Norell for being crown… https://t.co/nRhP4mEFUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drdougboston They just think they are sane, but that’s the tell of a truly twisted mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly don't understand or use LinkedIn, but I do have a profile over there and every once in awhile I get a notif… https://t.co/lIOHwMKHl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My proudest moment when taking off make up is knowing i still have eyebrows 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your library hold comes in just in time for snow day AND vacation #librarianAF https://t.co/8AlrOfGEQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javachik yes, which is a little pathetic...the best bosses know not to ask people to do things they won't/haven't.… https://t.co/Pktx5X9We0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess she wants attention. Cal de Kitty in the In Box https://t.co/Jzkkra4jzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @JoyAnnReid Meanwhile the clown who called for the national emergency is busy playing golf and tweeting more lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t go out often, but when I do I usually wear leggings 😂 #thicccc#jeansdontfitthis #figurepro#fitnessmodel#nur… https://t.co/6Eu7u3waGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here to cheer on @SMSRaiderHoops boys at State! 🏀 💛💚 #oursouthstory #smsboysbasketball https://t.co/UO9rg2bIlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watch friends at least once a day and my life is significantly worse when I don't https://t.co/drrvsSz42y]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to acknowledge @danielle_skedz of @DelValAggies. Dan was a member of our inaugural Magic team and remains p… https://t.co/1VfSZYKROp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #WeGotThis just arrived. Only had time for the intro before heading to school this morning, but already saying "… https://t.co/Q7re0PuA77]]></document><document><![CDATA[just thinking about how annoyed i got when i saw target’s summer section when it’s 50 degrees outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my dog alone for one night and she’s still mad at me. If you look up spoiled in the dictionary there would be a picture of her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 139 more followers to go. #PushIt #wicked @LivePDNation @LivePdFans @OfficialLivePD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending #GenderRole stereotypes and inspiring more dads/men in advancing #equality! Check out @johnlegend, and… https://t.co/QnsOiCyQo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love our coaches!!! We aren’t the only gym whose coaches get excited!! #crazyarms #purplefamily @CheerEclipse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlatMatzley @mowoodier It's too late baby, yeah, it's too late.  There's that time thing again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgentSpectre It’s just very odd since they already MADE the toys, so it wouldn’t be any more effort to release them in both places. 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#getGAreading set us up for deep thinking around the social emotional connection! Let's get children hook on people… https://t.co/lGRGjVawGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princessbraandi @jacobthornhill4 He needs attention while his mother is in Oklahoma and well dad is at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TONG_mEDown No, continue to do right be others. You have to walk away so the right one can appreciate your faithfulness ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world running off high strung emotions and it's really irritating my soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skipperdee2015 @GabbieKDrice @rcarr57 I’m not using an argument I’m simply asking for information to support an ac… https://t.co/TXOGPqrDsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You took a shepherd boy And made him a King.” So I’m gonna trust you and give you everything I’ll be a conquerer 'C… https://t.co/xwJu0nTOG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorge Ramos and his team are free, but the interview footage has been confiscated. Say No to Socialism! #Venezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews She got that wrong Hillary Clinton has already been proved to have colluded not trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear these sleeves are getting shorter and smaller every year. 😩 https://t.co/Y9vn79dhVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met someone who spells her name the same way!!! https://t.co/fDMDb9PJnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are in your room, getting ready for bed, SWAYING back n forth, falling over......   realizing, you are... in fact.. fucked up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hashtagged(Bird) Tagged by hashtaggedapp #bird #birds #earlybird #BirdsOfInstagram #birdwatching #birdstagram… https://t.co/NxIy0teZPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're a douchebag Steve Calandrillo. Stop sleeping in and maybe you'll get it. Figures you're a law professor. Pro… https://t.co/6QbXkJaz8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Please see my tweet re: DNC blocking Fox coverage of 2020 debates. This tweet gives you my twitte… https://t.co/PYPl14BRs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish The Get Down &amp; Dear White People we’re still rolling. Rewatching the first 2 seasons ain’t enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was setup so nobody would believe me but all I have been saying is His truth.   Please repent for Jesus Christ an… https://t.co/RghZjWH30h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man can you imagine if they had, say, created a coordinated operation to find you at restaurants and scream at y… https://t.co/ZmMR82y3RY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm v over people bailing and cancelling last minute. Doesn't take that much to keep your word🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@genedavis47 @thenurse75 Someone who isn't part of tRump's inner circle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first night i’ve spent without austin in like 2 weeks and i’m feeling lonely as hell 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars all around! From last week at work, celebrating Universal Pictures’ Green Book and Focus Features’ BlacKkKla… https://t.co/Z2ketmaYoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin @SaraCarterDC I think there was a SVU episode on tv. But they got them from their parents cabinets. So… https://t.co/UTDRzuVzT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere @cw_mills I’ve never sent you poolside trash before.  This one I have in mind, I’m sure you’ll rea… https://t.co/goyXPBAxNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy sitting behind me is like a Toy Story toy. He appears to have learned three hockey phrases (“get out of the… https://t.co/B7EI9Rxv4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Santa Rosa: broken clouds, 51°F 76% humidity, wind 6mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin Kathy, your flowers are beautiful! I hope you had a good Valentine Day!? Did you see my pup, Zeus wea… https://t.co/hKnxfMRuU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💙💕❣️💛🧡🖤❤️💞💓💗💖💘💙💖💚💓💛💜🧡💞❤️💗💚💘💙💖💕❣️💙💘💙💓💛💞💚❤️💙💜💚💛💚💖💗💓💚💚💚 https://t.co/qb7wEtKpTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tractor trailers should not be driving in any lane but the right lane especially in a snow storm like thank u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are delusional. But go ahead and live in that delusion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated: UCF President Dale Whittaker says his offer to resign is "the most significant step" he could offer to rep… https://t.co/kyl5wBGEKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @iamzvelle for this beautiful feature on my story in honour of  #InternationalWomansDay2019 You have a be… https://t.co/XnNPIxmarZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again.  POTUS believes Kim over US Intel. No deal made.  #TrumpKimSummit  #TrumpFail  #TrumpKimVietnam]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... frozen 2 is coming out in November now... hmmmmm I wonder... does this have anything to do with @shanedawson… https://t.co/KFPyOoGbrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four specific phrases students can use to self-advocate, early on. #HISD #DYSLEXIA #Advocate https://t.co/D21fFGeZue]]></document><document><![CDATA[His moustache was actually in my mouth. #LivePD https://t.co/ZBN8w0T1F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[An @AugustAlsina and @Kehlani  colab 😍😩 my arms already have goosebumps just imanging the vocals on that track .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to go to sleep wtf. I need to be up early to look for Girl Scouts before work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD Good night?, it's only 2208 here, have a little less than 2 hours left]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halfthepicture @mindykaling @NishaGanatra Excited to see this! Heard nothing but great things at #Sundance2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouKnodis I'm so sorry for your loss, my thoughts are with you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to toot my own horn or anything but I think I made a pretty stinkin’ cute baby #CooperLaceky https://t.co/w8VY9peng6]]></document><document><![CDATA[recently got an influx of white followers. Weird flex, but ok. Welcome. This will likely be one of the only times I… https://t.co/H7hUbyvQjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Give up creepy Adam Schiff ! You are a total sorry ass loser...nothing you try will work. Practice acceptance]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW.  can’t imagine speaking to children who are so passionate about something in that way.  Thank u, next, Feinste… https://t.co/gqWnKrsuQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Inmates go to prison AS punishment, not FOR punishment.” What a thought-provoking comment on today’s @1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soderberg_chris @awix22 @KMeKyllo @jentsch_amber I love that you assembled them into a book. Excellent idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami Dade Commissioner Joe Martinez believes he’s being pulled over by a police impersonator - now Franklin Dixon-… https://t.co/fJFEMzqmmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Venezuela isn’t a wake up call for voters in 2020 we truly have a Nation of blind sheep. But I don’t think that’… https://t.co/hVptORImcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLBrandt What's different between the ones in the junk heap and the ones that ended up going on eBay for thousands of dollars?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago prosecutors charge R. Kelly with 10 counts of aggravated sexual abuse. https://t.co/5ybnLsCUV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 years later and still dragons #kindergrads @ Rockenbaugh Elementary School https://t.co/tyJWi899LD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazy4OReilly90 @rtadter @MsAFromBK @lno09281978 @DragonMom98 @BuffBills53 @Burke_William1 @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/UEWDCoHUFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me omw to my computer to start a graphic that I didn't conceptualized ahead of time: https://t.co/AQYUBGde1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And you sir, are the biggest liar!  So it’s okay for you to lie, but when someone else lies, it’s treason ‘. WOW!  So fake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrerucker51 @CHHolte @sunrainsunrain @Solange_Sonnier @midwestnorth @mamastronomy @GJamesMasterton @ladyred1956… https://t.co/fUOUgEkETU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Cuando tengan dificultades, ayúdense unos a otros. Esa es la manera de obedecer la ley de Cristo.” Gálatas 6:2 TLA… https://t.co/0SAhuwPuxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yangszechoo I thank goodness for Marie Kondo because I came upon a stash of forgotten accessories, including a red… https://t.co/j9uvlfJ8ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DionnaSanchez Glad to hear that! Enjoy the rest of the weekend! Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @WileyWonka59 @snyder777 @JG_SOCCER18 @eddiedial @robyn_lance @Fish_171 @phillyeaglesfa1 @BenJackd1… https://t.co/r2WWn4WurW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Csamaniego_1623 @BoilingCrabLV Me too!!! Want to treat me ? Lol I can eat enough for the both of us 🤤🤤😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Asmus @AOC For real. I'd like for her to come talk to us out in the Midwest. Although she'd probably think we are backwater hillbilly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adeyanjudeji ABSOLUTELY CORRECT AND WHY IS EVERYONE ALLOWING THIS TO HAPPEN??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markzbarabak Another case in point: April, 2017, Feinstein is booed at a town hall. "You can yell and scream and g… https://t.co/afdawuOhr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashton5sos you are the sweetest most caring person i have ever met and you truly deserves the world. 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere @TMobile Yes I like free stuff. But usually even free stuff come a price so 80% of the tome it still comes with a price🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent 15 minutes watching  #cheesechallenge videos and I have narrowed the babies reactions to two options. 1. Th… https://t.co/iO7xEqeYsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff SHIFF..Why don't YOU attend one of President Trumps rallies and see for yourself if people NEED him… https://t.co/h8R86Pyngc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc13houston Keep summer school for the kids who are struggling.  Extending school days is not the answer and will… https://t.co/T5meI1sygW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordan_Sather_ @AndreVanDelft Research Japan. They no longer do combo shots due to side effects. They know they aren’t safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to attend my first Speech Language Hearing Association Conference tomorrow 😭 https://t.co/vPU0qip1nH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only who truly rolls my rat's when @iamcardib says " your 🐱 basura, my 🐱 horchata"??   Like I cant say "or… https://t.co/TADIysejo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USNationalGuard @OHNationalGuard God Bless You Both for your service 💜 Come Home Safe ! Thank you ! HOOAH!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope that anyone that doesn’t like me follows Hilary Duff on Instagram so that in a way they constantly see my face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champgnecoasts Thank you ♥️ it is from Zara but I had to cut it bc I didn’t like the original length]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live until God calls you❤️ @ Stony Brook University Hospital https://t.co/dLP65Bn2kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby’s first OSCARS!!! Thank you @abcnetwork for the most surreal opportunity ever. And thank you @karla_welch for… https://t.co/5EOdjqzNkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support a Clothing-Optional Beach for Tampa Bay! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/HbCueWZ4uS via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whats  their character ? And these are the men and women you voted for? Where would they be if this law was affecti… https://t.co/676u4y6QNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited that @NBCGoodGirls is back on tomorrow #GoodGirls #nbcgoodgirls https://t.co/gu0Lg1rg8i]]></document></documents></author>