<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @jetrotter Ha!  Nobody listens to him or cares what he has to say!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken Starr: Sitting presidents should be indictable https://t.co/dfDe2goUks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angela Bassett should always wear bright pink, bc she looks amaaaaazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Girl Scouts pounce as you try to leave the grocery store https://t.co/HgY57VRt9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Canageek Nope. And we'll scold the woman who's trying to change the ratio of footballers to scientists period to b… https://t.co/ZAwTaIrhW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Val Napoleon talking about how we see gender work in #IndigenousLaws #IdeaFest19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sete meses de gravidez e essa semana descobri os milagres da acupuntura. Gente, quem ainda não conhece, vá descobri… https://t.co/CfHhApSt4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember all trading decisions are your own!  Whether all happens as companies hope, there are always situations th… https://t.co/ElS48RingA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein should become tried again since all this happened, anything less is not Justice and is still the go… https://t.co/ebMsVSqWFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i said i was getting kbbq before we started the challenge again and i didn’t. i goofed 😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialchevel i am extremely proud of the person you are and always have been! thank you for being so true to us… https://t.co/XbOp2DfeD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know girl 🤦🏾‍♀️I think it’s too late for me to even get it, I missed out on the hype 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[They be doing that in LA had me google if it was one here just to set me up for disappointment 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[my uber ride was going perfectly well until the old man tried to hit on me 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really think I’m just giving them a rude look, like no that’s my face. Sorry :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CKJustice_AP42 @willownorkiki They go by how THEY "feel" and are in constant denial.  You can't talk with them bec… https://t.co/JW4M44mIpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLove27 @jzulgad I have no idea whether it’s *most or not, but I went to Creighton and basketball is all we had f… https://t.co/VvXNkZnV37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ljmatt22 True. You are right. I was being cheeky but it's not funny in hindsight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve used @audible_com for years. Anyone have experience with @librofm ?  Pros? Cons?  Suggestions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitting one #goal &amp; #planning for the next is my #MondayMotivation.📚👩‍💻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k31149575 Thanks Tara! Yes we have a few nasty flu bug going around. I hope your mom gets better too! ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roberta_lanzoni @Viviane6677 @gabryluce @GizellaGerics1 @mich_onelove @Jose93571656 @consuiglesias… https://t.co/33dXxUuDPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witeywitee On busy nights and everyone wants lemon drops I see red and wanna kill them all 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your man code? Mine is 1,3,4,2 Toronto’s Exclusive Gay Orgy Find out more at https://t.co/wKEiSjYBXK https://t.co/O4cXqumfVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t go a week without a bus cancellation :)! But in all seriousness, it’s slippery out there from freezing rai… https://t.co/vaqQT7z3bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paulaqua764gma1 Hey! Sorry I announced it on air and forgot to tweet it! It was actually Atlantic Blvd!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimHall60 @Ljfly47 @krassenstein Seriously though, how are you going to feel about democracy when you are told by… https://t.co/lEAXuDJvfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayhurst3 Thank you for writing such an inspiring blog post. Your reflection about the #G2Great chat with… https://t.co/ZFvVPmxXGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Copper IPA by @InBrewing @ Somewhere In Particular Brewing — https://t.co/4qUdcJaeJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @carson_burtron ! Makes me proud!  @IHSAA1 #faceofsportsmanship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 57 of Stay in Touch is up https://t.co/WhDrsaMi0O Suspects The image is… https://t.co/2NhB3ODEAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, help me through the power of your Holy Spirit to live a holy life and to develop the characteristics of humil… https://t.co/7wF7QLqhUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the best feeling in the world to feel your baby kick 😭🤩 I can’t get enough of her!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the few platforms that reported income for all workers, 95% fell under the threshold (earning 54% of all income… https://t.co/AKRvjngUs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SenateGOP_ @GOPChairwoman the country is still waiting for an explaination to this. https://t.co/0IJndJAdzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidTaormia @cathairs @memizon @OWingsgirl @DABradioshow @najat @OccultFan @jimroy @PyramidRealm I'll share what I can when I can 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot think of why anyone would oppose voter id unless they want a corrupt system.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needy for my mom and dad if that’s a thing... I miss them every day and I’m PROUD! https://t.co/DciDasxXBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just throw this whole semester away. Seriously that’s how bad it’s going for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not trying to be mean or start any shit at all i just wanted to throw my opinion out there as someone who was in th… https://t.co/9XHn0CbrVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Since you're referring to fishing expeditions, one word for you, sir: BENGHAZI!  Two and half years, no indictments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning.. Diddy - Dirty Money - Hello Good Morning ft. T.I., Nicki Minaj, and Rick... https://t.co/5G1IaqLfv9 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The key to realizing a dream is to focus not on success but significance, and then even the small steps and little… https://t.co/wzLUeZz1gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥳🌈🥳🌈🥳  #birthdaygirl #happybirthday #thebig8 #istheresomethingonmyface #whippedcreamfun #partyhatonfleek… https://t.co/zJJmKid3Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @ArthurAtkinson0 @gtlem @Westview_Al @Pepperfire @suepeac @TheJasonPugh @StradlingDianne @CleanPeteCan… https://t.co/CAbUvyF8xZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Charlotte: light rain, 42°F 93% humidity, wind 8mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave06031956 Even Pinterest added an edit button. That was the best thing ever happened because it’s annoying to d… https://t.co/cxBPza1S5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherguy781 Hi Rob! Okay, so it's the winter population issue. Although, I had a pair of cardinals outside my do… https://t.co/mv1f1hWIn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue  @Braves pitchers are reporting  And catchers are too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye New York! It’s been incredible 🗽🍏✈️🏙🌇❤️🚇 #oneworldobservatory #nyc #newyorkcity #memories @ New York, New Y… https://t.co/ErerWCzALh]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we came up short this evening, I could not be more proud and more grateful for the support I did receive, and… https://t.co/XTtUbN82HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC As a customer service person and food service industry high five to you young lady!! Our Country is made up of… https://t.co/MQkFyYkKft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPS your package reschedule fee of $5 is ridiculous. I have paid it twice and nothing gets delivered correctly eve… https://t.co/CCLLhTIotS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add a nuance to the service, if you go with out a week without response the design service is terminated and non re… https://t.co/3l7bK7eWLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writewish | Write your wishes, dreams and inspirations anonymously #comedy #lol #smirk #humorous https://t.co/kQZeTxUBsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[also it’s gonna fuck me up if there’s like a really sad song about tyler doubting himself and stuff because we’ll k… https://t.co/zQxRjNeUNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bernice7087 @AidenWolfe Thank you 😊 we will! 🇺🇸 ISA is coming back better and stronger after we get our House back… https://t.co/E7jLARdRGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjRowdy5 @DonaldJTrumpJr I respect your opinion about Junior, which I assume to be a positive one.  I don’t share… https://t.co/f0TH5daqpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceWorlddd thank you for figuring out all of my emotions for me, i love you #DeathRaceForLove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RustyRay1980 @MollyCuculich If I tell you to stop doing that one more time, I’m going to give you away on Craigslist]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even mind that tomorrow is Tuesday and I have the 2am shift because it’s my last 2am shift forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallassmith @deanbrody @ChadBrownlee @MacKenziePMusic @JimmieAllen Well, you’ll see me at 1 or 2 of these.... or 6 or 7... 🤷‍♀️😎🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds Omg, just watched DeadPool 2!  You are fucking hilarious!  Proud Canuck to another.  The scenes afterwards, hilarious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never forget when I was in 5th grade and one or more of my classmates got projectile vomited on in the middl… https://t.co/jeDVvmxfme]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just hear/see someone’s name and you automatically get annoyed? Or does that just happen to me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting a tattoo after I have this baby. If someone wants to pay for it, that's cool 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankelJeremy @dbongino Just use duct tape to make them stay in bed it worked for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snevets_Yaj @brooklynmarie I think in one of the eyewitness reports someone said they were about to. I wasn't ther… https://t.co/1s0wNYLyG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i always had nightmares about life without you but this is a whole other feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crying in my kitchen and texting my high school BFF like we knew Luke but 90210 was freaking everything back then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some mornings your dog 🐶 just has to say it like it is... words of wisdom for Wednesday! (or not🥶) Be safe today! .… https://t.co/5h9RkVcANd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_ebooks it's absurd at this point, and I still cannot believe the number of people that take cpd's word off the bat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gah, 3 hour flight delays on @cathaypacific for a tire that was losing air... this is terrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i LOVE seeing friends in the wild appearing on their friend’s tinder photos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBrewsterCO @conroy_e @RideRTD @DenverChannel I don’t trust people being smart these days 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib Congratulation on your new song Love the lyrics much ❤️ there's  more to come]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feministgayry I’m Gabrielle :). I’m 17, I live in Michigan. I like to dance, and paint, and I love music. I like t… https://t.co/bS3NwPSEew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrogSpeaks @JesseKellyDC Um....Media Matters is trying to get dirt on Tucker.  And failing.  Is that really a picture of you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd to Arie dumping @thebkoof, this has to be the rawest moment on #TheBachelor ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeycoulter I hope your answer was yes. That’s the only appropriate answer when asked if you want pizza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you live in a condo, you improvise. Used my festival flag pole in place of the table umbrella. #enter… https://t.co/SuVLIAAWQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re walking down a middle school hallway and three kids yell, “Mrs.Boire your Girl Scout cookies are in”...… https://t.co/WOq2TR7FBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[***FREE EVENT***Saturday April 13th...SAVE THE DATE... @ Biltmore Hills Park https://t.co/TKJWR2U2qY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Learn to live with ambiguity” 🤔 #TrueDetective https://t.co/XqUx0vbQpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2k19 and niggas in Sudan still perming and slicking their hair back like if they’re Elvis Presley. CUT IT OUT YAKHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[YEP! Thermal energy quiz today, but it is Friday before a long weekend! #tgif @ Macopin Middle School https://t.co/gZjtIcguF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a month off between classes, so I’m going to try to make a dent in my TBR pile - starting with… https://t.co/mOYHWoCyKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how but the Lord has been blessing my business so much! I give all the Glory to him!!! I can’t believe it! 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do school projects include glitter? It has the half life of radium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityNews @ericaracheltv Guilty of manslaughter cuz he used PTSD as a defence. He knew what he was doing, and we sh… https://t.co/EW3QVaS8ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unpersuaded112 @CNN Omg seriously, who the hell thought hiring #evilkeeblerelf is a good idea? They are destroying themselves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope #westcoast… https://t.co/YR9IoS8ER4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gearing up for Rachel and Robert's wedding and so excited! ⁣⠀ @ Old Alton Bridge https://t.co/XvCJJ94xty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okokMadison بس بما انو اني عايشة هنا اكدر أكول و شبيهم العراقيات اللي عايشين باميركا لو احنا ما نعجب 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[me talking in class when i get called on and don’t know what i’m talking about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lincolnmaster @cantgoback69 @SawyerFrdrx @bobbi_Reno In my opinion it’s more about exposure than winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may recall we ran the CAFAS outcome initiative for 15 yrs 2000-2015 until policy changed to phase it out. We ha… https://t.co/t1L05qNBIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[my girlfriend is a sexy ass nerd, check out her sailor moon collection on depop #SailorMoon #anime #vintage #90skid https://t.co/ilGzy3Ck5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love and Support like this for the other young women like me is so warming and it’s just really feels like someone… https://t.co/y5EdUDWOrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to golden hour feels like having a big sister telling me about her life and comforting me when i’m sad. t… https://t.co/aMY0rdyECC]]></document></documents></author>