<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Telling y’all Russ gone be a different nigga this second half of the season. He not bouta be off how he was]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is an amazing person, works around the clock all of free. This no Obama that spent $86 million in vacation. Y… https://t.co/QLVGi9lcy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Vegan expands it's horizons to the trendy Northwood section of West Palm Beach, Fla. Soft opening now and g… https://t.co/cH4uyyuBJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davebelton112  this is still going on, are you still representing me?           Alleged victims say powerful Georg… https://t.co/4NkpvcgAlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guadian15__ @Backroombarbershop on instagram  817-372-5247 my personal #]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @CoachClawsonNMS to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews-jus… https://t.co/MNA7LYoIwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryMarbach That’s. I mean. No. Just. I know he’s a wonderful man.  But no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home made tacos !! Echos por mami 💋💋💋💋 @ Inverness Crossing, Magnolia, Texas https://t.co/rHNzsuTRcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going into deep work mode for the next week or two. I'll be back with my finished book, cya✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhsundermeier This is excellent @lhsundermeier . So many ways to apply this. #PTBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThursdayThoughts Did I spend my #ValentinesDay virtually with @SkylarStecker by streaming all her new songs on a l… https://t.co/SUvpdETJp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bottechia1998 @pipelnrwife @kemppam @GovMikeHuckabee Nah, someone compared a 4 year old who hadn’t learned to hate… https://t.co/LPE5beAax4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DOriginalNation @MannyDouglas419 My mom saved EVERYTHING I’ve got a dope starter for the boy when he’s bigger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hjtorrespr sintonizado ya para oír el Marronazo de hoy espero que hables lo del junte de Rosellón con los seudos d… https://t.co/of5vcO5xw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittRecruiting_ @joeybagovdonuts I to this day wished they stuck with Wreggett in that series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway what other options do people have? every fucking love from Brooklyn is delayed bc you can't fucking do your job]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-7, 249-pound QB Tyree Jackson turns heads with fast 40-yard dash at NFL combine #Topbuzz https://t.co/I5c4Tfrlkd… https://t.co/RG1loPi45t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pau Gasol and Nick Young were on that team and they won 27 games. Nobody on this lakers team is a s good as Pau Gas… https://t.co/mdfDJKXdyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrozenSicleGirl @KevinHarvick I can not... Ive had about a half a can... And i just cant drink it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I SURPRISED HER WITH WHAT?! https://t.co/upkJUKMe64 https://t.co/YlfH4NVAS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I meet a guy that listens to Streetlight, I’m marrying him on the spot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Game_with_Evan @labyrinthdc I am in Florida, preparing to get on a cruise ship so not this time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what you're saying is @WWE is putting 12 Women in essentially wrestlings version of sex cages and making them ta… https://t.co/CQ4OJR8XSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[He cares for you few words, if any, are more important in the fight against anxiety...  David Mathis]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In an effort to keep your account more secure, two-factor authentication will be required to sign in to your Apple… https://t.co/hyawHpAEAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEMS CAN'T STAND TO SEE POTUS &amp; AMERICA WIN AGAIN SO THEY KEEP COMING AFTER HIM. SICKENINH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz dia Amor Mio ... mi pavlovac @ Doraville, Georgia https://t.co/uznUSUGjRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’mon, Connor beat Tulsa in football and has started two games on the mound. You really think he needs a statue alr… https://t.co/WTBo7wFDuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crackedmirror Fried pickles. Yum.   Also, Tabasco is a +1 on most anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BakersLand6 @Jjksu22 @mattgargs @RandallTime Been Around More That Do Than Don’t  🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful night at @ChallengeCSUC! John Strappazon gave such an inspiring message and the band killed it as always a… https://t.co/IaMMJuyuP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicole where are you now? Are you home...? Percilla ordering chinese for you.. is wayne drinking one of those bottles of wine ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaniiGS @lieesuhh 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 literally no one says that. We usually refer to our hometown as “hell” or “a giant shithole”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IdealSeat @TheAthletic @jonahkeri @TheAthleticMLB Congrats @jonahkeri let’s go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Winter Botanical by Ebb &amp; Flow Fermentations @ Ebb and Flow Fermentations — https://t.co/oX6eaKMPqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mormon Row at sunrise, Grand Teton National Park, Wyoming. 🇺🇸  ———————————————————— #mormonrow… https://t.co/lfV0CyBZKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_verynicegirl As long as the ceiling is unobstructed.  That’s my favorite selfie of yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you aim for the best quality. We are getting ready @colfruits @valle_agro https://t.co/NG2hEdfPrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@H_Ta_The Nothing but love from here. Can’t lose my birthday boo, no how nowhere, too important and too good. Much love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southside is not that far of a walk from anywhere on camp, y’all just lazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Al_antunez25 @jbaduel @malvapica Me refiero a que tenga derecho a Juicio....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atlblog I AM THE VICTIM. OF A FEMALE, SEXUAL PREDATOR. A NARCISSIST. LIKE HILLARY. WHO IS ABOVE. VIRGINIA, LAW. OR… https://t.co/cPOsyBbmHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeedsofJake Pretty bad.  Ted had way too many misses in the top rounds, reason the team is in its current condition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching people cook is some type of therapy. I just wish I could taste it when it’s done]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been in an on and off depression for a while, and I just realized I haven’t watched Road House in a long ti… https://t.co/fQVLmqwogn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patmick2626 Didn’t your brother Don get into pre-gamer at Mariucci?  Something got him going during warmups?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendaFlournoy1 @MikePoynton @kfoxhouse @SafetyGirl100 @Jr7Jimi @kleigh062 @BeacheyGirl @79uptowngirl… https://t.co/TKMtQhJWSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle with me for a bit. Image Detail for - Friday Funnies Return! « HealthSkills Weblog #funniness #lol #smile… https://t.co/7eTnvTAhnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[excelente lunes :) saludos a todas las parejas sw y chicas con permiso de salir con single discreto limpio y sobre… https://t.co/BkLkPuLR1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JimmyMcCormick He continued his streak of 31 games with 10+ 3PA though]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Attention** calling all Point Guards.  Skyline Varsity boys basketball team has an opening for next year. Taking Applications now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stargate4444 I was just following my intuition. I think the timeline may be a bit off I was just waking up. But th… https://t.co/U9To5dCmKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bella_Astro Looks like it's going to be a great spring day for you Claire, can't wait spring time here sooo really for it !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally starting Letterkenny is the best decision I've made in a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Nero.. Devious, Sexual predator &amp; destroyer of Rome ☠️👹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tmsn2000 @abibascencio The main problem is rational Democrats like you are no longer the voice of the left. Used t… https://t.co/YmtgMns9KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go #Gators!!! Chance for a huge road win tonight in Baton Rouge. #BeatLSU #GoGators #GatorsHoop #UFvsLSU 🐊🐊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with my Oldest Daughter (@ Chick-fil-A in Buford, GA) https://t.co/f10bq2YZRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our View: Rep. Paul Gosar is a disgrace to Arizona. Somebody please unseat him https://t.co/cwhwslos0T via @azcentral]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Vh1 should start a new show kinda like their old show ‘The Pick Up Artist’. Except the new show features experts on sliding into DMs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotHereForThat 😇😇😇😇 Lmaoooo you told us you just cuddled with him. What a whore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build that wall is all about the money. A lot of people will make a lot of money. Matter of fact planet earth is al… https://t.co/0NyFyj1RwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to start my day at Alderman @mattoshea19's Get Behind The Vest Pancake Breakfast at @sjfschool! Had the pl… https://t.co/v1CQ0BNbtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not a woman, but are totally on board with the fierce women of #TheResistance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagnusRanstorp Jag gissa att det finns stor oro för "placeringar" inom många bostadsområden i Sverige.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve got to love State Basketball fans.  They come up with the best excuses why their team loses https://t.co/f2dWS9HHQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition to make Mad Max mandatory viewing in public schools to prepare the youth for when the planet dies and civi… https://t.co/N9w2xzqa4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeRomanNose @Speedee19 @hessbrass @mattrob74779817 @RepAdamSchiff @AOC Yeah, Mexico has a real problem with cri… https://t.co/nZwTMlDc5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody thought Mikolas would be an ace but it turns out that it was a bad decision.  And they’ve had too many bad d… https://t.co/hd7vLfMpBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOTtrades I thought sure you placed your life savings in that one?🤣 Plenty of shorts fuel here...could be another ROKU??]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody   vegans : IF IT HAS EYES I WONT EAT IT   me , a culinary artist: well then what r we gonna do here https://t.co/zeqVsJo9dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of South America today 02/26 Real-Time #GOESEast #ABI TrueColor/IR and #GLM Lightning Group Density with… https://t.co/U5qjYRMtNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdsEyeSports Yikes, that’s not a good sign!! We have a home on Starr Dr. Great shot!!👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EscoBlades This happened for The Force Awakens. Shows for the first 48 hours straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @LeanderISD learning continues for our leaders with @LISDCareers and @JennyWellsATX speaking to our team.… https://t.co/dwh3vsOHbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally photographed Woody!  Photographed March 7, 2019 #nature #birdsofcolor #woodpecker #gastateparks @ Cloudla… https://t.co/7biWEOl4ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejtheuerkauf Hi Ethan. Mark Torregrossa here at MLive. I am going to post about summer lake levels forecasts. Can… https://t.co/KGCs2TG4sO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I think back to what I loved about studying communication and what got me though four years of essays and graded… https://t.co/bOKnrubqAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downstate Illinois has the same instinct—in both cases, calls for rural areas to secede expose an ignorance of the… https://t.co/M3ZXW672p4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NM_Barbarian I'm well aware how lucky I am to be an American citizen, I'm just also well aware how much the succes… https://t.co/ERH9IO91Cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleveland bans high rise dev on most valuable land in our second downtown @inthecircle via expansive institutional… https://t.co/Ano2COditV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimthecritic @Lightfoot365 @IronMaiden Where are you? My mom and I are in 103.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#angelaverbrugge #canada #singer #jazz #radio #plug #kansascity #neonjazz @ Belton, Missouri https://t.co/waWW6Dsdos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @biddergalore they are not racist,they just want their country back and letting all these people flo… https://t.co/b3HsiYtEm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrentonHockey good luck tonight!!! #GoTrojans #RoadTo15 #BeatWoodhaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr the only #hoax is that your dad is president and you are still talking ! Please shut up and go away… https://t.co/KRjZk7eqq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@padschicago @TonyaFrancisco @WGNNews @WGNMorningNews Don’t reset my workweek.  Please!  It’s almost my weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs. SOLUTIONS: ++ DR. WALTER WILLIAMS : LIBERTY IS MORAL ++ BIG GOVERNMENT IS THE PROBLEM 22TRIL IN DEBT....… https://t.co/aV9PN0eZPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just announced: Along with “Hamilton,” the 2019-20 @FoxCitiesPAC season also will include “Dear Evan Hansen” and “T… https://t.co/h04BITjZ07]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt like it was excessive to bring up even in my gay men’s psychotherapy group - despite it being something I th… https://t.co/T7XFpJh6be]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will someday have more than $80 left of my check after paying all my bills. Someday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elchelis @Club_Queretaro @ClubPueblaMX @LaCasacaBlog que bonito sponsor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smeneses19 @AlanPonce_29 @lopezobrador_ En #Mexico el pueblo está atontado, no visualiza los alcances que implican… https://t.co/UqI6pPbogM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drunkacid haven’t had t*co b*ll in forever...rn it’s got me like https://t.co/M0NwCW2As3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s been interesting to me at least—is lawmakers/state health officials have really leaned on the e-cigarette/Ju… https://t.co/mduRNx3XEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big congrats to #Marvel’s #BlackPanther and #SpiderMan #intothespiderverse on their big #Oscars wins!!! @igndotcom https://t.co/5OZhlypnvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving 5 hours and waiting through the rain was worth it to see @Vol_Baseball win big! https://t.co/EdbFvKNaAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/KPsEPh3IV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazonico1974 Yo diciendo q acá saco mi inglés y están a la q cae jajajajaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all an innocent misunderstanding.  Mr. Kraft loves Jazz, but because of the LOVELY BAHSTAN ACCENT, his request… https://t.co/Bxsafy4XI4]]></document></documents></author>