<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bull.   Lyin Donnie.  Again and again and again to the power of 1000.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna travel w my bestfriend. but that envolves me having a bestfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone seen this?  Anyone have this? ~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Phish Chrome Auto Emblem - 5" x 3.75" https://t.co/lM5eWr7wU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBIndyNews This is a devastating reality to this community. The next time someone says that this is the price you… https://t.co/dPM2eEIqUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The duo got to party at the @UClubPDX tonight - it was a great way to spend Valentine’s Day! #valentinesday2019… https://t.co/oWsJArMeFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy all day, since I’m not feeling well our cat has stayed by my side. He slept outside my bedroom, would foll… https://t.co/qKbuWh6SXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 lbs down since chemo began. If only I could take credit for my calorie control rather than my stomach lining being inflamed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For this Agar is mount Sinai in Arabia, and answereth to Jerusalem which now is, and is in bondage with her childre… https://t.co/gSYwpHwosA]]></document><document><![CDATA[warrior cat pictures of jayfeather - Google Search #humor #chuckle #grin #comic https://t.co/21n7lNMt27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockMomSPN @demon_heart_spn @lovedogspn @mariepop60 @DonnaY1legwondr Happy Wednesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClandestineRos1 Instead of "run out of town on a rail", she needs to be "ran out of the country on a rail" Another… https://t.co/PXPqUQsb14]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the past twenty four hours I have written an angry five page review of my instructor, decided last night was the… https://t.co/k9YnV76GyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!! Today starts Multiple Sclerosis Awareness Month 🧡🧡🧡 #youneverknowuntilyouknow @ Winter Haven, Florida https://t.co/rSb3UmlqIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[set a goal for yourself, small attainable goals. whether it start with getting rid of sugars or soda or carbs in yo… https://t.co/YUilH2L8KM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF to last Friday @wtrmrk 2019! What an #amazing day of #women #finances and #representation! Everyone moment/tal… https://t.co/UDP6DTGYed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the insured annual Out of Pocket Maximum - in this balance billing discussion? The insurance company and t… https://t.co/OlMtAmmWeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahmarasmithart oh my god. was she wearing brick shoes?? no wonder she was stressed out omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly OK with us I wasn’t expecting anything big and I’m actually quite happy with this thank God it ain’t l… https://t.co/ztUOBHCCuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@engyn243 @MichaelJGrant5 @POTUS Absolutely correct. The leading core Demon-crats hate their followers and party to… https://t.co/oTSkIGBDig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animals are still being poisoned and killed in tests for cosmetic ingredients in the EU. Please take action: https://t.co/4zPxP4Egzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed to have such talent to help me bring this song to life! ♥️ GO DOWN FIGHTING is an ode to my muse, my scr… https://t.co/s5X9MWmgHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoverDrive12 @Nixons_Head_ @Keubiko Duct tape. Lime. It’s the first thing you learn in Newtonian physics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@max_the_ripper If you like them and Gretta Van Fleet you should definitely check out Palaye Royale as well, they a… https://t.co/NZR8FtFvCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoWomanIsRight 1. your @ got me weak. 😂 2. for particular situations maybe, but not every women out here never sat… https://t.co/iYR9tmtEeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope yes you did mean to blurt it out you were going to blurt it out all along anyways so don't say you weren't!! 😠 #BoldandBeautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[flight home canceled too 🙃 plus still no resolution from my last flight being delayed so long that I missed an enti… https://t.co/GOeebXUMdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ma Perna Sen summing up the #Australia #Canada session on Sexual Harassment in the Workplace.  “Gender Equality is… https://t.co/Xk1lDD3ISw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@questlove I feel badly for the poor horses-lord we humans are a consistently hot mess]]></document><document><![CDATA[This psychedelic graffiti wall has had me trippin for awhile. I finally caved and took a picture of it to share wit… https://t.co/aAW5Spfoa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunudronov @thmissff Simm, ta no calendario academico que as faltas de fev vao ser lancadas so em março 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting set to judge the #3MT competition @mylakehead @ Thunder Bay, Ontario https://t.co/Qm4miYzQdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJESSsayin87 That laugh disappear quick when shit start getting real lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zelle I transferred money to a relative using their cell number and they never received the text with further inst… https://t.co/WKoGlUycOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there’s anything I’ve learned in all my travels that applies to my life as a nurse, it’s to “put your oxygen mas… https://t.co/EoXBYcrHZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaFirn @FacultyHarcum I agree! I can’t wait to implement some ideas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am disappointed that Stone wasn’t jailed. I can’t say for sure what the judge was thinking, but I do have some th… https://t.co/cByt6Z1EqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really feeling this one today 🤣👏🏻🙄🧘🏻‍♀️ #proflife #bartleby #iprefernotto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I celebrated with people I hold dear to my heart and soul!! All these people have come at different walks t… https://t.co/p6WHvXRpqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my students are saying they saw Captain Marvel and hated it so I need some real input y’all. Is it worth going to see?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HIREME #comedy #comedian #comedienne #faceforcomedy #actorlife #broughttoyouby makala_the_ukulele and refindsc… https://t.co/jVuTOOZAQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot @AngeleStar11 @RepAdamSchiff @PostOpinions You can't be this willfully stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Borrowed this one from another TRS Coach! I loved it! We all have ups and downs! One day we are flying high and ano… https://t.co/CjMbD8GzuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss @HowardSchultz The rest of the democrats such! So does Howard. There is no real candidate running that… https://t.co/XMPub2cHNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kara_krewer Perfect for a two parties in one night kind of Halloween! You've already got me planning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some amazing friends we met @dejavoom are really convincing us to give @HolyShipFam a shot. I’m considering it. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orvie83608158 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump I really wish he was the target....... this country would be a safer pl… https://t.co/uUKIYWBglG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up still mad that nigga called my mama ugly. I’m still ready to hook 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I lived in southern Iowa not north Alaska another 10 inches tomorrow someone come rescue me from this madness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But now I realize love comes in many forms. In order for me to maintain a consistent happiness, I need different re… https://t.co/h1NsBg5n92]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone else has big sister advice that’s more responsible than that, please help me. Lmao thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[And hearing from Jessie Rasmussen and Edgar Villanueva, as well as @JohnBKing. #TEGAC5th]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the Supreme Court: Can federal courts appoint a special prosecutor to argue against the pardon when both he and… https://t.co/hB8kG3cB4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about tRumps performance at CPAC. I do believe he was recording a comedy album. Maybe he’s trying for a Grammy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @erinblackirish with get_repost ・・・ You don’t want to miss this. @erinblackirish presents a back to back se… https://t.co/V5CpdoHLiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed @RealJamesWoods -  man I hate to use those words but she just is!  #Idiocracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc what ppl say. A guy/ girl will change their wrong ways for the right person]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catwoman1957 Jst saw post from vets office..Z is amazing in his unfettered gait....so happy he is well on his way… https://t.co/5FdRTd1iQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep in mind ... a belief runs much deeper than a thought ... This is the lesson of #Digestzen… https://t.co/03tVTNrdm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OTD in #NYCHistory the 1st #adhesive #PostageStamp in the #USA was introduced by a private carrier service called… https://t.co/oNIjteuYxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracebible757 &amp; @esprin041 ❤️’s @BrookwoodElemen ! So thankful for Mr. Daughtry!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ow that kinda sounds right.. To get a check..or screen time.. Wow! Shiid i would.. But it did seem like Yandy Sugge… https://t.co/7pYKqMbYx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFreels Happy Birthday Darling #iloveyouforever💙 https://t.co/snOXvhCyAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost all of my family on my dad's side will not speak to me because I'm a liberal. They used to love me because I… https://t.co/TZfPwGmByQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRicardoG @steph93065 @KamalaHarris The people that would suffer the most if black criminals were set free are th… https://t.co/DSHjMEmFa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week residents in the Bay Area were warned of “Atmospheric River Conditions” from all the flooding and rain, A… https://t.co/LqUWseSKGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithellison Minnesota needs implied consent to have cellphones searched in vehicle crashes when they are potentia… https://t.co/5MCHfTdiuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be kicking off our 8th annual Shot@Life Champion Summit this morning! Looking forward to the next few da… https://t.co/Tau45ypKMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissa_dee @MikeLupia701 He got a gravy boat full of hot fudge with his sundae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greer_xxx @LiamAngellXXX @willangellxxx @therealtytycub @RonanDelaneyXXX @JohnThomasXXX1 @MattMuck1… https://t.co/yhsyONX9ET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeezynv @speaktoheall @LaBeautyologist That hyaluronic acid be drying tf outta most people’s face, some people hav… https://t.co/StP09GDhvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @matthewamiller Think about the people Cohen has dealt with in the past.  Mostly low life conmen,… https://t.co/tDSw8nWREs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 What a scum-bag: Question is maybe she does ...IDIOT.. https://t.co/7UmBFMluPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrissAnn Like my dumb neighbors who woke me up at 2 am beating and screaming on things outside after a drunken… https://t.co/su3LXjZ7Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamAmbrogi @aztammyp Yes, it is an obvious way to improve operational efficiency while improving the customers’ experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Gaston County, North Carolina https://t.co/544mVnAiSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to thank daylight savings for restoring at least some of my sanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carrie_Bland @bernardfbunye @thinkingpoker I so own you (poker term). xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of a toxic thought process, just bc someone didn’t want to remain in a relationship doesn’t mean they cared an… https://t.co/9TJqThayd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why International Women’s Day Isn’t Going Away https://t.co/eo6OjHYzxt #BalancedForBetter #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe Morgan really deals with me complaining while I’m hungry. Which had been happening a LOT lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NellieLucas07 @TrailblazerLady @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump I guess I look at how he died and why and that’s unacceptable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter family and friends and get well soon Joe Roman Reign https://t.co/kUxkhHnWwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travel agenda.....NYC, NJ, CA, MA, FLA, LA, GA, MD, etc..... BRING ON SINGAPORE.....🙌❤️🤪 https://t.co/1uIc4vjaVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[People love to hate on me but at the end of the day my tits still big, my ass still cute and I have more confidence… https://t.co/q4FDrC4Kzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kid made me a name tag. @ Skeleton Key Brewery https://t.co/SGnxudOO9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain:  “Did you give me my debit card back?” as I zip it back into its compartment.     Also my brain:  (sits o… https://t.co/RJgzAvYFNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking out my next car!! Thanks @BernieMorenoCo for bringing all my favorites! #autoshow https://t.co/NzP67IKRD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes Nice...💕 What Are you doing up so late...it's 1:23 am n California 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poetry This just came in from my Collards Greens Garden. I Call this patch #MollyVille 🇺🇸won’t listen👂to you. That’… https://t.co/zdiujqPb5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a democracy, our voice is our vote. House Democrats will take action this week to ensure voters are no longer si… https://t.co/lN43HdZJeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlancReine Totally her choice, as well as the wee crystal beads that I'll weave into the netting...tomorrow... Hopefully!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cozy and comfy in my twinpalmsco lounge wear on this rainy day in Cali... . . Bow headband from aloayeclothing  . .… https://t.co/FXSTaEVakb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chloe was so happy to eat dinner at my house because we buy the same tortillas and salsa as she does and if that is… https://t.co/uXh1cSSPdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at Evolution Wrestling @ Carver Park https://t.co/EheppEbV2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quédate para que nos sobren las razones y nos falten años... 💖🎶  Hermosa canción para iniciar Marzo!   Quédate by… https://t.co/sKZnFKH7t8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta @franksesno Is that where Mr. Sesno landed? CBS News Wyatt Andrews is now at the University of Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBKOWeather thanks but Channel 5 issued a FLASH FLOOD WARNING for Robertson-Montgomery County over an hour ago during UK game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gideonator15 I’m so happy for you Gideon, love you so much husband&lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I constantly talk with my friends about how I need to be an actual adult and here I am going to get a finger tatt t… https://t.co/x9aeARW4y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmhslmc Join our #Mashpee Middle/High School Students for #ReadAcrossAmerica Make a local, National or global connection]]></document></documents></author>