<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Laundry room in the works...So we purchased our first home in early December and it has a laundry area.... in our d… https://t.co/X5PGTBRIli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David42716938 Hi David! Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8switho… https://t.co/EMNCD6hrCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 4th graders rocked their  Valentine’ escape! @breakoutEDU @Mr_Summers2 #teamwork #BHWarriorpride https://t.co/cAOsJvfwqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t know how stressful it was to get concert tickets until this morning 😒😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna have to say, I just started watching RHWBH this season.  You ROCK my dear. 🍾💕🙌 we moved to LA last May a… https://t.co/BF8OC4A56P]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 year old girl leaving pizza place in NYC: "Dad, what do you call two squirrels that aren't married but have a con… https://t.co/knIHWHJmp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I play mind games with niggas &amp; it don’t even be intentional 🙃 karmas coming for my ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a picture perfect day at the Mac! Come join us!  First pitch at 4 p.m. https://t.co/di7OGE6q0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏#RUN👏TO👏WORK!  What’s great about this run is that I pass two parks, where I will eventually add mileage.  Also?… https://t.co/RFVTUyxH8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estafeta Pues mi paquete estaba programado para llegar el 15 y no llegó 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexa, Siri, and Google Don’t Understand a Word You Say https://t.co/WNioDi4LoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I haven’t mentioned it yet, please watch @RussianDoll on @netflix. I can’t stop thinking about it. It was so bri… https://t.co/im5BQ4sGnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealMcCready too late for mailbag but maybe a(n) @OxfordExxon podcast question. I’m watching Pelicans at Lakers. L… https://t.co/WW6Qm5Nwxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatUnleashed #Don'tBeAJudy.  Judy squashed all my thoughts about being a 1st time caller. I don't want to #BeA□#PutThatInYourPipe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleciaalexander So now Arrogant J Nadler w/a personal opinion can investigate 80+people w/his own opinion is that… https://t.co/XUHjamte84]]></document><document><![CDATA[☹️ via @ARTFIXdaily Another year passes without National Medal of Arts Awards https://t.co/0mICf3UwjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSPANJNKY @TariffMYtaxCUT @cspanwj @alaynatreene @axios @JonathanTamari @PhillyInquirer The democrat party hates that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigguface @JordanUhl No thank you. I’m not here for rewards. I’m here to foster progressive dialogue. That woman b… https://t.co/hWeaxys8iP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah, the by-Elections are over and we are back on our regular election schedule.  Register to vote if you haven’t al… https://t.co/4z2Qhy81jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alectheapple @AlexisWriter1 that’s why my essays done and urs isnt :D JK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom asking me how social media works...  Random stranger’s Instagram post of his leftover nasty ass french fries… https://t.co/8IFF6Ncc1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chorlton1973 @EllieMellie1 @NeilSeasman @PhilipPullman Emma, the guiding document *should* be 2016/2017’s “Citizen… https://t.co/NRLObej8bH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@empresseskeys @jazzleberrypate It's nearly 3:30 in the morning and I just about peed myself laughing at the combin… https://t.co/16nXgIOOPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming in March, Grace School Musical Theatre presents Willy Wonka Jr. https://t.co/uGMjbFWXjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryEMcGlynn @SpaceX @NASA @NASAKennedy I loved you from afar. https://t.co/78JGFa6I3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the days where I could go “home” but my mommie passed away &amp; my dad doesn’t live in the same state as me. 🥺😥 uggggghhh🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enserio amo las sesiones de fotos en la playa, los fotógrafos se inspiran de una manera impresionante]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really don’t think we don’t know about wear and tear and “stocks” most of them never had. We know the game ju… https://t.co/pQXHwk5uDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule I love that woman. Bravo! As for Ivanka... She has that lost in the headlights look. Just another… https://t.co/ux4YF48HyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time has come for yet another #SundayBunday lottery. Tickets are ten dollars apiece, and the grand prize is the… https://t.co/gY3frmkDMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you support education, and would like to be a safer rider, PLEASE go to https://t.co/nTLSwMZLue and like our pag… https://t.co/Pzo7erQMCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terry Crews is the perfect example of why Black women and Black LGBTQ folks generally should not extend our solidar… https://t.co/CjxDF0dITA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been a firm believer in the girl code. Idgaf if it wasn’t “were talking” or “were dating” if one of my… https://t.co/lbadcnvZ6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madsatan6969 @beers300 @Smokeyholler @HippieVol @DollyVol @Shawn172510 @gwoman9810 @CMcNair87 Easy there pawpaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyfallon That is the truest tweet you have ever tweeted.....or will ever tweet!!!😁😉  For you to have realized t… https://t.co/QsQMe1t8dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greek week is in a few weeks... I’m competing against the other sororities to win money for my philanthropy,… https://t.co/BZs9UhLe0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missellie_ @hopelessdials Oh freaking K!!!!!! Brb while I wipe the drool of my face, LORD HAVE MERCY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newhome #homeforsale #listings #realestate #realtors #luxuryhomes #bluffsideatcountryclubcreek #homebuilder… https://t.co/CldRexEHpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @Jim_Jordan @realDonaldTrump @USSenate Stand on the side of the American people! #ProtectOurBorders… https://t.co/dCULX5XaNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was fun now let me go to sleep I gotta be up in a couple hrs 🙄🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@draco2023a I like my life too. But what are we suppose to do? Allow more drugs to come in not to mention illegals… https://t.co/0IRDyFDSgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctydweller08 @MillAlwaysReady @Freeyourmindkid I think he hid his own money somewhere for problems like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bibliogato EDUCATED by Tara Westover is fantastic on audio. Listened in my car driving back and forth to bookselling job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my fav weird human. Thanks for doing life with me kiddo. I don’t have to say a lot bc we already… https://t.co/hMUT8boHt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonNadeau @loveGoldenHeart @beckworthandco @aftertheflash @JulesHalvy @FolderRed @monstervoyage @RoadtripC… https://t.co/zNEG1aKySP]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT #consumerproducts INFORMATION  Inside of white plastic milk jug has green slime inside. Please watch both… https://t.co/gGVIfB4ji1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You HAVE to pick the green and blue pill. You have 3 days to take advantage of and get as far ahead as you can usin… https://t.co/BB0cMH0rmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magssca @CompaTiger Exactly. Idk how people eat those extra stuffed Oreos 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loverboy12390 @AllieSinn15 @AGT I would be sooooooooooo excited if Darci wins again she Angelica and kechi are my main favs!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new mug!  I love it and I love being this to an amazing man and #bestie for life!  @MarkCimarosti ❤️ @ The Cimar… https://t.co/9u4r4qLW0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a special opportunity to become an LCI in Northern Virginia and teach bike and pedestrian safety.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner We all know why he was appointed, @realDonaldTrump is trying to keep him quiet,  we all know Donnie is a… https://t.co/CiWIPhvl8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimhofmann @JoyceWhiteVance Sessions recused himself from investigations. Whittaker wasn’t .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en San Nicolás de los Garza https://t.co/ehFa9cNBEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesFrye @SueBee0619 @jorleigh1 @Kobuk440 I believe you manifested Wickson on the team through psychic energy and… https://t.co/FBnlWejGry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mo_minraj Society still looks down on anyone who has PTSD or Stress Disorder from jobs like Police Officers, Fire… https://t.co/KSKJahb7j6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddhoadley @HilliardSchools It was well attended! What I enjoyed were the #continuedconversations happening after… https://t.co/CCSZBstqy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJMcKean The straws issue is ridiculous. The guilty are the ones disposing trash into our oceans. Why aren’t we st… https://t.co/L39DGdg0oD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudekaty @fransco My cats love the possums. They think they’re all family 😐😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh So we can use the 25th for psychiatric reasons? Great. Thanks for the info Alan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capricorns are the kind of people you want in your court. They're responsible, disciplined (and over-achievers, to… https://t.co/llfGRLTPLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withamorxfaith Well, if you drink alcohol, theres a good amount of stuff to do. if not, then, not much. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super fabulous die-cut sticker that matches my backpack (and attitude) perfectly. Thanks feministcollectivemcc!… https://t.co/5G2rDqYxOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏻💚🏋🏻‍♂️ #EquinoxMadeMeDoIt ItsNotFitnessItsLife FitWoman #HealthCoach @ Equinox Newport Beach https://t.co/93CaBONnNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, it was in the 30’s two days ago... and now I’m over here sweating like a hooker in church.  Make up your mind New Orleans, geeezus]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscars is reminding me of so many people I forgot I love and want more of... Queen Latifa, Javier Bardem, Bette Midler....yes. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Inskigator @llkaline @Angelangels17 @GoldenKnights Yay!! Thrilled to meet another dedicated hockey fan!! Hockey is… https://t.co/O7mG9hisaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 8 Funniest Unknown Girl Memes #hilarity #lol #smirk #laughable https://t.co/KhX0l6ml66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliBruer My bf does that and maintains that it’s an oil field safer measure. Note: he works in a corner office in downtown Tulsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesdoughnuts We're all dog lovers so this hits all of us hard. Much love to you and your family and may Kailani… https://t.co/hTdVwnduqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7-Day Book Cover Challenge from @Mrs_Harbaugh to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations o… https://t.co/MGQxA8LlOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when I read super passionate tweets, my brain reads, "blah blah blah, blah blah blah, blah."  #blahblahblah]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Finance job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Sr. Financial Analyst… https://t.co/iJprefsbWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They day a leper never changes its spots. Well, I’m not a leper.” - @LuvAfterLockup #LoveAfterLockup https://t.co/47usCCSoM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I have come to truly HATE you. You are so opposite of President Barack Obama. He’s class you’re an… https://t.co/4LltLHh2yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@01wise @djpsom @Nysteveo2AOLcom @siano2020 Bernie could never raise the money necessary to run as an independent.… https://t.co/Gd78KBCjyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jason_blum To say I loved it is an understatement! https://t.co/oqhSvUE9a3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Eminem for keeping my life sane with your music for the past 12 years. 👏🏻 it’s a jam session tonight on this drive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby fever is at an all time high rn after seeing babies all over the Internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bollemdb @fioreze2004 ESTE POVINHO NANIQUINHO VIRALATINHA TUPINIQUIN QUE DEIXA TUDO ROLAR MERECE COISA MELHOR?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked up on the trailer and had a little snow adventure with Lilly and papa today 🐶☃️❄ (📷: rch71) @ Elmgrove Trai… https://t.co/Slno2Gw5Pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I just found my spring look 👀 2pac forever 💙👕🧢🕶 or was already wearing it? @ Bedford–Stuyvesant, Brooklyn https://t.co/fhAvYDM5uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLIENT: "Do you sell houses outside of the Triangle?" ME: "If they build it I will sell it!".  #KimSellzNewHomes in… https://t.co/RHbAlpL0im]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is arguing about the continued existence of the caucuses, but what's worse: the parties' insistence that t… https://t.co/nXUOAdyefo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp I’m so sorry for your loss, it must be horrible having to live with that about your mom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysteriousdays @bernardfowler His voice makes me weep. What an incredible artist. His stage presence is perfection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[T.G.I.F I’m giving up wine 🍷 for lent so come have a glass with your girl 🤔😉😘 @ The New Dating Game https://t.co/iHpM8ryYCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano As a teacher, PLEASE don't take tricking children away from us!!!!! How else do you expect us to threat… https://t.co/rQwNm7bA4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hepburnetteswp Can’t believe it’s been 7 years since you told me where you’re from. Love ya, girly! 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLee418 @jonesbrent570 @chevychevelle48 @ToddTPrice24 @Chrisracefan1 @laura24fan @43324FAN @georgia242011… https://t.co/RfL3mRV96y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority Brandon saw you on Mark’s show last night. Awesome I hope you reach millions to get the word out. “They are already free”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pothole Patrol: Where are the worst potholes in our area? https://t.co/v5XdCZ6U2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssa_drasco @_allylain_ Y’all you know she is a good photographer if pics of me turn out like that.....😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@payinmydues2u @VisitVirginia @mySWVA @AppalachianPro1 @SuprtAppalachia @appalachiahome So so very beautiful Raymon… https://t.co/yHl3qpGCKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I brought the basketball and volleyball out of my car ceremonially tonight though all those years my only work out was waking to food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your assistant manager tells you to do something stupid and you tell him it’s stupid, and then your store mana… https://t.co/LER6dmDL79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @chiditarod, Thank you for the follow. You give me great joy. Love you and I’ll see you the 2nd! (Everyone, pl… https://t.co/mV68Tq0QjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shellyihall They built a new library (I think technically just moved locations- but it’s newly built) on brookvill… https://t.co/5WJDNa8k8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s #PwC Power 100 is out ! Congrats 💥 to @PwC_Canada for #whatmattersmost #culture #values @ByronBergren… https://t.co/J4YhnLufDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is Maryland wine month as well as women history month, the perfect time to celebrate women in wine! 😊🍷Thank y… https://t.co/AH9rihAies]]></document></documents></author>