<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There’s so many sports news that are so exciting to talk about but none of my friends have any clue of what I’m talking about 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaina @fentybeauty Damn it, I'd convinced myself that I didn't need it and then]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone surprised by this? A racist is a racist is a racist. Anyone want to make book on when he’s going to viola… https://t.co/HHMGDlTmy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no excuse good enough to kill a human life in its most vulnerable state. None! If you don’t want the child… https://t.co/Kv1vTGc0hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Authoritarianism/fascism requires that Dear Leader be the only source of real authority in a society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @AyannaPressley He is a liar he is trying to save himself he is a liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a getting in @JustinFaulk27 pants joke ready but decided against it..lol https://t.co/IiUpUc7zsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be careful what you pray and ask God for, because you just might get it #HOWIWENTTOTHEOSCARSWITHOUTATICKETTRUESTORY https://t.co/ollgISn9HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkrelldavis @DrPattiJones My daughter has a massive set. I might use them sometimes....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why he’s always telling me that I’m the one that can’t be trusted. You said it to me so much that I am numb to… https://t.co/9aRZ9axXsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HectoRodriguez Asesino cada muerto for falta d e insumos lo llevas en tu conciencia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackieKahane @BlueBoxDave Not all men...just the ones who hate &amp;/or objectify women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like would I like to see ambitious ecosocialist policy happen? Fuck yes I would, believe me. But pretending really… https://t.co/K7feL8CpYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epigmenioibarra @saos50 @Veneguerrera @zibilspring @bazarmonedas @gerente_nap @Mboe55 @francoleal215 @Drago237… https://t.co/8mYgrn2eks]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my little girl dreams came true @ Flamingo Las Vegas Hotel &amp; Casino https://t.co/85wXgQD1PI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only Nat knows how i feel about a specific situation that i rarely ever talk about :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of us was ready for that pic 😂😂 , idk how Nic always looks good in her off guards but she needs to teach me]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7iNQJ91okC ***link to shop in bio*** #cierasendlessxpressions #cieranicole #boutique #boutiqueshopping… https://t.co/HH5JiYJlVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many of y’all remember these books? These use to be my joints 😂 https://t.co/kzHkxRyA6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was very fun, stepping outta my comfort zone feels S OO amazing!!✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you go to school and you don’t have to have a job, you are a very lucky individual 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[The class with the most spirit this week will win the spirit stick! 🎉 @Potowmack_ES @PotowmackPTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreasonMaybe @thehill @HillTVLive We already have barriers at the border. Are you suggesting we should dismantle those?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimHall60 @Ljfly47 @krassenstein Hahahaha!  At least you didn't mention HRC or Obama. I give you credit for that.… https://t.co/YMU0W9dxMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I’ve been nominated by @MrsDiPede to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanation or reviews, just covers.… https://t.co/qpH2b3zP7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew there was a reason why I don’t watch Clint Eastwood movies. I would hope in 2019 he regrets mocking Sachsen… https://t.co/Dw2pkI7yeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re like me you’ve compared yourself to others. You’ve felt down on yourself because so and so achieved this… https://t.co/jrmur46Zeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoBenavidesEsq @MeghinDelaney @CSNCoyote I use my phone to scan! App called TurboScan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawks4evah @Bravewriting How many times am I allowed to retweet this?😁😆😂🤣 #NeverWithBernie⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ghenneberry47 @WindomChris @MRDerekClaxton I love that Derek is smiling and y’all two look like some thugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake Parenting is the most difficult job but it is also the most rewarding. I don’t think I could get any ou… https://t.co/RXrLOEpNkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing out the seismograph at #GriffithObservatory—it works @GriffithObserv https://t.co/Go6CV4aNcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[pipeline for Myanmar go to the government and ultimately fund those who this past summer Saudi Arabia condemned. On… https://t.co/a8POi5Y2FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzi_2904 @austinnreeed We did but they’re we’re two different guards telling us two different things. One was ye… https://t.co/34W9jKPVs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of yall nvr had your grandma tell you to "beast ya head still" and it shows. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had real friends one of you would have texted me to make sure I a) knew about this in a timely fashion and b)… https://t.co/zQhahdEZZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorKimberley , I'm wondering if you could relate to these tweets. https://t.co/AA0bEOhvJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeenTippman @DavidCornDC hey, I just respond to what I read on the twitter.  you OTOH may be in possession of "f… https://t.co/nL6s5vab2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure, it’s 12 degrees. But it’s a perfect day to acknowledge your mortality and need for repentance which is why As… https://t.co/UMuhFnzGAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st Birthday Wolfe!!! I love you soooo much sweet boy!  🎊💙🐺❤🎂🎉 hawkattack @ Redlands, California https://t.co/uyjjRdYTQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Neek knows she’s definitely not getting out of making her famous Mac and cheese for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE have spoils in our party that smells.of disloyaty to the party..... they need to change to the Democrat-Socialis… https://t.co/7AurSNSkuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl Or is Trump a stand in for republicans and we’re kicking their ass out of the country? Because I gotta s… https://t.co/tKECtVruiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHStokyo @thistallawkgirl @ManInTheHoody How did i leave Mash off my list?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minute by minute #humanrights abuses #Yemen #FlintWaterCrisis #Venezuela all controlled by the oligarchs #WakeUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay update I grew a pair and asked this guy on a date, he said yes. Now I have to figure out when I’ll have time 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Did you also mock CNBC for calling them “war games” in 2017? https://t.co/wmMt9FtHY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_ms_hdms sharing great information on Specialty Tuesday! https://t.co/C6vHgKswVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jr_chillin550 @DanRather I thought their stick was fiscal conservatism, instead the deficit keeps growing without… https://t.co/cRwYw0R4SN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessssss!  Indeed he will. Gods favor is in and on our journey with us. ✝️ 🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spurs @Patty_Mills @manuginobili Thank you for your dedication, passion and continued love for the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really gotta stop telling people “you know the vibes” cause not everybody familiar with the vibes if we being honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my babies. If it wasn’t for them idek how many times by now I wouldn’t have been strong enough for life. God knew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theycallmebob Rock n Roll! Literally! Love it &amp; thanks for introducing me to a group I haven't heard of yet. 😁 https://t.co/3OyU6JhhAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New book arrived just in time for Valentine’s Day 🥰 @theslumflower https://t.co/aYLPSwHzE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brennan Elliott Movies #NannyExpress @VanessaMarcilM #LoveYouLikeChristmas  @BonSomerville  #ChristmasEncore… https://t.co/D8YehXPOO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my dear friend @zangtoi for an amazing evening and a spectacular collection. He truly is the epitome of… https://t.co/3bhnc386NQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to win tickets to @stagcoach! @MalibuRumUS #MalibuRum https://t.co/2augT9gNS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackieHillPerry So she’s only apologizing cause she was called out? Sue the weird privilege out of her please!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking forward to a special screening and discussion of Ian Mauro’s latest film, Beyond Climate, tonight. Bey… https://t.co/SIfd6xHEYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfilerPatB I’m throwing the #bullshit flag on that. Is there also “White fragility”? Nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i applied for a barista position at r*lph l*uren and i ended up getting an interview and then i looked at their ins… https://t.co/4B8UFkbWoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toxicoffroad Thank you!!! I’m soooooo happy with them and sooooo excited to be a part of @toxicoffroad!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Babble I know, especially with those "official" records you keep getting.  You must have missed Ruth Ginsberg a… https://t.co/TmWVZF84sN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K102Muss VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥 LIKE A… https://t.co/4Dt3l0hi8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This trip, we were on the Disney Dining Plan so we took a note from @disneyfoodblog and had the Pineapple Upside Do… https://t.co/BUOvuaH9PT]]></document><document><![CDATA[it ain't gon land in the room, it's gon look better on cam LMMMFAAAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilianaSnchez9 @Fernand80760480 @mainzina @szalacain1 @jobragag @Cantero9Vega @angsala67 @JSaintPastour Feliz mart… https://t.co/lcauUslSqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kurt Elling... graciously allowed a photo. After all, he knows my brothers. Next time, I’m setting up an interview… https://t.co/peUkAhig8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande Girl, @paigegenevievee had a 7 Rings b-day party yesterday. Shit turned out A M A Z I N G. Go check out her pics✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could you imagine your Friday nights without basketball/football games followed by Steak ‘n Shake and long car rides]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Not to mention that Congress is a separate and co-equal branch of government that appropriates funds… https://t.co/gCFYzGZKOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Truckee #snow #northstar #Tahoe @ Northstar-At-Tahoe Resort https://t.co/Yo4JwYdZu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanylj22 I’ll be hey @MisterPreda and @JoeyGraceffa catch me outside how bout that🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how my best friend since 7th grade and I are complete strangers now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zollinger4Idaho Except that there is ZERO evidence that work requirements help break that cycle...The evidence sho… https://t.co/027dXglTfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son dos loser ,Natacha ya no está para defenderse y aprovechan las cobardes ,no tienen ethica moral así les va a ir… https://t.co/bhF23DYC4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[We cannot wait to support our Miss Pioneer Valley's Outstanding Teen this weekend at Miss Utah’s Outstanding Teen.… https://t.co/994zp9sqIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCarroll17 @woodbridge_ms A7- I’m bringing back to passion- I know when passion lacks in my room that’s when beha… https://t.co/03av67d1FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sallieheart @ECMcLaughlin Oscillo contains “Anas barbariae hepatis et cordis extractum 200CK.” Don't be fooled by… https://t.co/uQW9mXYASL]]></document><document><![CDATA[riz was two years ago today and what happened that night affects me a lot more recently than it has in a while, i r… https://t.co/YOsY7OBehQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one can tell if I’m tuning in for @johnlegend over @ChicagosMayor... right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend will be so odd not being spent watching NCA Nationals live streamed...for the past like 6+ years I’ve… https://t.co/6OnbbLQowE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t deserve to be in pain all the time definitely not by the people I love]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi! dj’ing the after party for the hot chocolate run this morning...yes you read that right, i started dj’ing at 7a… https://t.co/P1XlaIl6QJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robportman @MarkMeadows Hey Mark, any more black people you want to parade around to say you’re not a racist???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib needs to be deported Stripped her citizenship she is a traitor to America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKruhaj you are SO amazing and going to be the best nurse 💛 I’m so happy for u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre hablan de Sergio Ramos pero este es un marrano tramposo y nadie dice nada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson says it best! “Carol and Maria Forever!” captainmarvelofficial @lashanalynch these women stun the whole… https://t.co/kUu1R6LbjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FoodForThought: Should the term 'racist' be redefined? https://t.co/rFDPIt08FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCQueensPark @CBCToronto @OntarioPCParty Sorry to hear there are still that many fools out there who are duped by… https://t.co/sOl48yoWun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACShilton Not the most but certainly one of the most annoying is when I run across this bridge in my town and truc… https://t.co/oyVNpM7Pmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkilahObviously Goodbye Yellow Brick Road; Harmony; I Guess That’s Why They Call It The Blues; Where to Now, St Pe… https://t.co/E63VSf0kHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Supervisor Logistics - https://t.co/mCM7YwI4Zj #logistics #Destin, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they work and they are not harming her :great , but for many people they don’t work well and physicians do not o… https://t.co/mVJZlvogu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_almdztori Lmaooooo wooowwww try having 5% tint in the back and no camera lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoniLove I see your beau is hosting SNL this week! https://t.co/D4ngYziEcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much delusional winning, that would possibly explain their ingrained racism, sexism/homophobia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready to spoil you, PayPal or cashapp  #sugarbabywanted #sugarbaby #standards #sugarmomma #losangeles… https://t.co/esujKxAsAO]]></document></documents></author>