<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ERICKROWAN blatantly attacked @FightOwensFight in front of the referee and no disqualification?  C'mon bruh!… https://t.co/xdhdGqZ4gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryHepola Love it but my wife won't let me play it when she's in the car!! No appreciation for unique vocals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even It Up playing Even It Up. Ha. Fun show @hobdallas @ House of Blues Dallas https://t.co/i9VOgtNTL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ditto Kevin! King Rice is a good guy. If it was me I would have brought my son in anyway and told the MAAC to do yo… https://t.co/MvTp7hLFf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Macadmian nut onion rings as the app. Crunchy skin, subtle macadmian taste. Very good. Comes with BBQ sauce and ran… https://t.co/0XrfPEn6Cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morehouse better stop playing and cancel classes for the rest of the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not as clean as the Citra version, but still wildly enjoyable. Thank you, Sarah!! - Drinking a Love Buzz (2018) Bat… https://t.co/riDS4uFlwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[More fun from the aquarium @ The Maritime Aquarium at Norwalk https://t.co/F1st82y7eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on the edge rn bro all I had to eat was a chocolate muffin when I woke  up fruck]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of my children are sick. Ben has a bad cold, Allie and Grace have the Flu and Carl the Chameleon isn’t eating .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daltonsaber31 yeah, seeing that this AM. obviously changes things a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adignan @benedictevans LOL, I was just on a 6am flight I almost missed yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XDogeGamingX @doman8ter @EASPORTSNBA They have his shoes, his courts, his jerseys for teams. 2k doesnt own Jordan… https://t.co/72UkYvzaDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauriecrosswell What’s that old saying about “Birds of a Feather”? . . . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another esteemed group. Coach Parcells is getting it done on the course and in the classroom. Developing Champions… https://t.co/QDDnMhxGEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha, this is the phone is need for conferences ;-) 50 day battery life they say !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope we continue to see Yalitza Aparicio Martínez in other movies after this Oscar season and that she doe… https://t.co/Hq7M8Ge9Bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to a television near you (if you’re in #Phoenix): ME! Later this month I continue my TV journey as a weekend… https://t.co/9iu6K6zC2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnimpressedTX @Regan0002112 @TexHellCat @waconia3 @FactCheckU @DaddyJim52 @steamtug7 @D_R_Gringa @kellyz713… https://t.co/damxYFItvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell me the school in Tulsa she was going to visit today used a snow day. 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could have never believed that Marvel movies would have reached into the depth of my soul as they have - one may… https://t.co/kHgrVnzNSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is a absolutely not true. @tapjets We implemented everything we polled. However private jets average booking p… https://t.co/3iJsjM9yi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorbilt @LinkeDrive It's some crazy cool software with a gimmick deal you attach to your data port on the truck… https://t.co/iwybvcVy41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronLemingNFL AR12 seemed to step up in big moments last year. Do you think he deserves more targets even though… https://t.co/LoB1BQZzxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[For this day inspired by Saint Valentine: Spread the Love. https://t.co/Atd0tIYlJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayferrarotsn Dude, you were a true leader as an Isle. Best display of leadership was in the 1992-93 #Isles season… https://t.co/ZcuRGleATp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del. Lisanti’s constitutents should hold her accountable for her unacceptable comment. It does not reflect the valu… https://t.co/c0cXud5bb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick visit to see my sister, bnl, Ashley and step-dad...and Chester, the sweet dog. @ Monroe, Louisiana https://t.co/WiWPSPf6mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robyn. Hollywood Palladium. 2.22.19.  #robyn #losangeles #hollywoodpalladium @ The Hollywood Palladium https://t.co/eMZ96FEIpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How disgraceful and horrible. This guy needs our prayers, because he definitely has problems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petereliopoulos @WTEN @NYSThruway Some of these truck drivers are such https://t.co/zRomnOcJLg’s like how far do t… https://t.co/nbEyvMWyRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wasn't he your lawyer? I thought you hired the best people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump. The king had you in mind no doubt. more Elvis Presley - The Impossible Dream (1971) https://t.co/q2VBkvLWuX via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rupaulsdragraceseason11 #carvedcandle #inspo #carlgstark #hifriend #highfriend @ Milwaukie, Oregon https://t.co/XKTscZ7hoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeLemieux @UNLVRebelGrl @UNLVRebelFan_1 @UNLVRunWithUs @LVSportsCentric @JTRoss34 @Masked_Rebel @msw_sports… https://t.co/Qz6dGrdQYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could the newsroom use this @ReedGazette and @MarkCMahoney99? @GrittyNHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putemupcdukes I'm late to the party but i remember thry had a S'mores edition of Golden Grahams!  OMG. I could eat… https://t.co/9sCQpdgT17]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@richeisen and his #RunRichRun is a wonderful thing - and it makes me smile every time he does it. 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcarmody 1. Christina Ricci. Really discovered her when I was finishing up high school. Haven’t been aware I’d bee… https://t.co/7GgO0ld7PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks official @dallasmavs for having the difinitive video of this act of pure class from @DocRivers the… https://t.co/EbjD30Bwvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect start to the third for Foxboro. Matt Tully finds Ronnie MacLellan and he blasts a slap shot over the glove… https://t.co/jF3Imj9YSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapchat “1 year ago today” is coming for me and I’m not here for it. How rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pomdr How I know I am getting older..."End of Daylight Savings Time" might be my favorite holiday! Sleepy today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_megginson @Independent They’re all struggling for revenue. It’s  desperation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanessa_wxgirl Yes, absolutely! We used to say that the NEK has 9 months of winter and 3 months of summer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordonez's AL Pennant-clinching homer https://t.co/OsWh4VZtRT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Exactly or they sit back in silence and lay in wait for someone to say something a little bold so they ca… https://t.co/jVdQr1QL6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macawcaw123 i mean average boob job is 4K possibly more for a good one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes Y'know there's a @shakeshack just down the street from the @WhiteHouse . Just sayin'...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccawissler @jeffjmanning I don't think this debate is going to get resolved. But we can all agree that one's c… https://t.co/J1zd2UIIi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivyfikes I’m sorry this was just too dumb to not acknowledge. I’m going back into the world of having him muted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afasterhorse07 @ErikPtfc @AlYourPalster @UrbanHealthPDX @BikePortland @trimet what do you do Mason other than trol… https://t.co/vCcnzJyqnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[ADAG tonight, gonna be working a long shift tonight. No time for the gym😞 #army#armythings @ Fort Carson, Colorado https://t.co/L9sGhIMDgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every city does it, your infatuation with the city of Philadelphia only weird thing 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @Pattern @MarsRovers OPPY has always visually reminded me of the robot from the movie “Short Circuit” with Fi… https://t.co/xP8U8TRwXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKubby First time I heard that was playing horse on the court as a kid.  Still applies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeltwayBernie @PirateSpitter @lordthx1139 @OrdyPackard @SahilcdesaiC Yes, just like the Nazis were socialists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The judge did not rule on collusion, you desperate dumbass clown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If LeBron averages 18PPG for the next 4 years (including this year). He will pass Kareem on the all time list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a loop of feeling physically great and mentally shitty then physically shitty and mentally great through out my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shemayah5 @kishoreragi @GeraldKutney Spoken like a true paleoclimatologist. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael_mcintos @HarveyStaub1 @cs00582scs @LadyRedWave See, no head cover! Just started !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanningAndrea Well...I watched it “Devils Bathtub” Very disheartening hard to believe hard to understand. Murder i… https://t.co/qfP2oVVL1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kishawn_11 I’m dead .. I ain’t use to winning ? 😭🤣 my high school team I played for went to state . My college tea… https://t.co/s5RZDqXoOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winxthexwar @JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr At least I have friends your such a wus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattygilli As a native Chicagoan, so glad to hear of the Judge's decision.  Pres Library has no business being bui… https://t.co/DAx92jReK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE The HOF will not be complete until we see @TheJimCornette and The Midnight Express inducted! Tag team innovati… https://t.co/dw7XTHDza3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishrygirl There are tens of thousands of bridges in the U.S. that are failing. We are teetering on a disaster. Y… https://t.co/xBUZkUHTea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBrown_80 Nice. I went to Male and lived right down the street from FCHS all thru high school. Small world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond PROUD seeing former students representing PG!  Congrats to Brandon, Brody, Noah, Brooke, Adam, and Colin! 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yes. @Cubs Wrigley field somewhere between the stomach and esophagus. I went to med school just south of the s… https://t.co/bGEKF0ndKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpomerleau I’m going to get a time machine, tell 2009 Democrats that they are way too worried about the medium-ter… https://t.co/PC0teYaGeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsaycoder 10 bucks! I know sometimes he does 2 for 15 tho so if you have a friend that wants it too it's only 7.50 a person :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi must know a vague “feel good” resolution will fail to stem the tide of anti-Semitism launched by Left-wing M… https://t.co/lNVkIRGfGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear in 50 years people are still gonna say this to me like it’s news like they do now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJimArd @charliekirk11 @AOC I wrote the same thing and then i saw your tweet ...great minds think alike]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @CNBCMakeIt I feel so bad for these women, many of whom had to get a second job cleaning toilets just to get by.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms texts about being so far away break my heart😫 https://t.co/IfQKcE2lmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymysterio305 @Nohillary2 Disgusting behavior by Democrats so poisoned by “BUT TRUNP” their districts suffer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#makeovermonday • Had the privilege of bringing this young buck back to the land of the living.   🤘🏼🐺 • Haircut by… https://t.co/REc5OQ5qkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Alita Battle Angel in 4DX with my bro @kevinjq925. Instead of paying $30.90 we're seeing it 4 $4.00 thanks 2… https://t.co/CZcCyJCPPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetterOfficial I hate to make a comparison but this situation reminds me of Porter's transition between spitfire a… https://t.co/HsB0dQDUhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job doing this interview and doxxing yourself, Shane. Now everyone can see how much of a racist piece of shit… https://t.co/50thHN8hOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up at 5:30 this morning and it wasn’t that shitty honestly I have hella energy rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#offworkhype #2daysoffhype LET'S ROCK BABY! TOMORROW, #Devilmaycry5 #xbox. @OctolingJen plays tonight on… https://t.co/cpD5bKVdhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter community you're amazing. Thanks to everyone for the supportive and congratulatory remarks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to have the gang back together!  This time just a crazy adventure in our backyard.  To paraphrase P “this… https://t.co/0d5iOU7boF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smash Bros at a bar 😁😁😁😁 #supersmashbros #n64 @ 16-Bit Bar+Arcade https://t.co/ghl578jA3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTFIII I feel like The CW isn’t overly concerned with ratings or shows like The 100 or IZombie would of been cance… https://t.co/CaHYWu6StY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kev_egan My own very similar experiences are validated by this tweet. A loving parent will adapt to any crazy situation for their kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcburgess SOLUTION TO BORDER WALL PROBLEM During WWII the Treasury Dept sold War Bonds. SELL Treasury Dept W… https://t.co/23KZUM7MOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwilson75 @realDonaldTrump Babies are born with grotesque non-survivable deformities all the time. It doesn't make the evening news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But not as the offence, so also is the free gift. For if through the offence of one many be dead, much more the gr… https://t.co/O9VgtbhEkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an A Passing Haze by @BallastPoint @ Munson’s House Of Booze — https://t.co/VVfsTUaKQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjoker2328 El hizo un mierdero! Todavia es la hora q no sabe q rotacion usar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama MBB plays tonight at South Carolina at 6:00 on ESPN 2. How y’all feeling??]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 Is that not AMAZING to you?!?!? The Creator of the universe - the Author of life dwells within those who have a… https://t.co/oKKkgjq7PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump knocking it out of the park at CPAC. So great to finally see a man a real commander-in-chief. Not t… https://t.co/xR98ZzBo3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bokchoifresh @Conway26686 @DezBryant I dont think he realizes that being a white male and continuing to dig at whi… https://t.co/Ty3AJ0PCp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaelynTaelyn1 That’s an Oscar performance he giving. Especially with them crocodile tears 😂]]></document></documents></author>