<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Caught a few #yellowtailsnapper and #reefdonkeys yesterday #wreckfishing #bottomfishing #fishingchartermiami… https://t.co/UDrZXvUoCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Boys &amp; the Snow Lantern @ Burlington, Ontario https://t.co/wiMEXJjeMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awful. Public parades should really have quality control and decline participants with racist and offensive… https://t.co/e4aurRmR4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single person I know who used to work at cracked is a giant douche who thinks the president stole their jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Online grocery sales could double in next 5 years. $60bn by 2023 #SXSW2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabesalkin @BriannaWu @Tesla @jandrade Only thing I can figure is she's referring to the ewaste.  I really can't s… https://t.co/2yNnqRDscE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankieSarabia @Benaskren Way to keep your consciousness, and that muscle memory going.  Gongrats on the win Mr. Askren]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Perfect Porr by @CombustionBT @ Casa Grinstead — https://t.co/nyWg3BBHD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again @JessG_XO_ cant wait to add the dagger next time👌🙌Txt/call 760.668.8320 for booking. Deposit required.… https://t.co/TmHc3jo2v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwbackthursday Can’t believe it’s been 3 years since the launch of the Pacific Lights Collection.… https://t.co/tvNTOkPUQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dem9345 @JimCarrey Jim Carrey's not here illegally. You just hate him because he hates Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BerniePleskoff Agree. Look at TV deals and $50+m from tech sale per team]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫If This Is It by Huey Lewis &amp; the News, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/HYQW1u8rxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kimmel been waiting on this R Kelly jokes all day. He done got me out the bed cracking up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... i am proud to say @TDBank_US is still best sercuity bank ever.... 😭 even thought it worst customer service… https://t.co/e7aWRDomEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nate_Denny Would be fun to meet you and talk Vikings! Tight ends anyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunsOFplaydough @msdeejay28 @counterchekist Remember when tRump gave that awful speech at “See 👁 A”?  And they alr… https://t.co/sxxC1pQF5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clean out and cable managed everything.  Only thing i changed after this picture was i moved the elgato under the g… https://t.co/utGfO0Kczh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaguMonero @El_Universal_Mx En efecto, los Secretarios Administrativos corresponden a c/u de los Fondos Sectoriale… https://t.co/wJX5Bqz4rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can't I ever be someone who goes and does anything with you Lisa??.. I love you so much Lisa I miss you all the… https://t.co/MEg7cFZQpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a single reason Amazon backed out of NYC. And we all should have seen it coming @justinjbariso https://t.co/vTJMgxSLME via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@number33allstar Hey, Solo, #cyclONEnation is behind you 💯.  Take care of yourself, listen to your trainers and you… https://t.co/iXLlxjFH4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews =🐍🐍 #AlternativeFacts #FoxNews 🤷‍♂️🤷‍♀️ https://t.co/tjgRiSaPQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight from NCA All Star Nationals to the gym!  #moorestuntseason https://t.co/Z7XI3BMhrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_dunlap But...what if they ARE BEING KIDNAPPED and they’re too traumatized by the play on the field to say an… https://t.co/YfQX624aCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @Jim_Jordan Congres is the problem if they act @realDonaldTrump wouldnt of acted with national emerge… https://t.co/VqycijyJpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing Londoners. They sat and kept to themselves.   In NYC we call this a Tuesday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buckeyecardnut @B_Litch88 It’s spring training everyone is in the mix. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toxic masculinity can also come in the form of what books you recommend.   Are the authors the same as you? Do they… https://t.co/9gx7ZeK4zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaFarrow @realDonaldTrump @MattGertz He knows KJU will see his interviews and hear POTUS comments about him. That… https://t.co/iPDtPm4M4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[J’ai eu la chance d’écrire un petit quelque chose sur l’Oracle pour le dernier numero de @basketlemag. Check it out… https://t.co/2O1q6axpo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please use this in a question in the 2020 debates... “Is FEMA aid contingent on voting?”  https://t.co/64gs7wEUQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazy4OReilly90 Literally didn’t even check his twitter feed. Just wanted to be first. So lame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenMichael31 It has been difficult to keep up with on Twitter. This is not the UMC I know and love. 🙏🏳️‍🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter All cultures are the same is accurate to a point. Because all Myths culture is based on were written by… https://t.co/ZwRe5cTFWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️FLASH HOODIE SALE‼️ Grab any style of @JeffTTF hoodie for just $35 was originally $50. Hurry cause some sizes are… https://t.co/cQF14G7O8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scav61 @ChuckCallesto She doesn’t have to worry. She won’t be around to see it anyway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deejayy_c I’ve got zero issues with a coach holding his guys to a standard of respect for your opponent, especiall… https://t.co/o5uqOHJbpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hashtagger_007 Wish her a Happy B'day, and the hope she has many more.. hope she enjoys her day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inter is Inter and Milan is Milan. Let's not confuse the two. Ever. Don't be that person. https://t.co/J01YhstjNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow well Pelosi, as you continue to spin stories to protect these three, it is clear you are NO LONGER  speaker!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmabrey1 @ndwbb You’ll be happy about that decision for the rest of your life. Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HassanAKhaire @MusseSaara You once sat me down and told me I was “born to do what I do”.  It was a great courtesy… https://t.co/H1UMikH4yg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the percentage of people who wear cargo pants that vote Trump?  I’m thinking 97.2%. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ronaldo’s words today encouraging Juve is much needed. They need to push atleti right from the start. Clinical fini… https://t.co/RzhWZtoC73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Fits for Kyler Murray After Heisman Winner Fully Commits to NFL https://t.co/p90HoMK529]]></document><document><![CDATA[@primitivadavila @Pr1meroJusticia Can you help me out by signing this petition? https://t.co/qWMiY1JRJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yooo_Dcro @Brian_DeWolf @joeysredhots1 @jake_schramm @sbivona28 @Azehm8 @nyck_latus11 74 points, 28 Boards, 18 ass… https://t.co/9Xi4BR0bdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way too many but a few that immediately come to mind include @lprocope, @reetamac, @kishizuka, @scheidel,… https://t.co/8HkuaIgKHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: i wanna have a relaxing week, where i don’t have to stress all week.   my pchem lab report: https://t.co/JRQDfJkIsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, has Bernie Sanders figured out how to print out those tax returns yet or... ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I filmed a wedding yesterday and all the white men had the same haircut. Shit, even I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holmesy_83 @yIlovemovies He was good in the House Bunny. Hell I love the House Bunny]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/B71vUSjtsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mercedes AMG GT is not a daily, but someone seems to use it that way @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/uVWtKqRD3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_jaffe This makes me sad and I’m a Padre fan!!! Heal fast Salvy!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing phone call about a job I never thought I could be considered for.  What an amazing blessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRoss My hooks crazy .. I sang my ass off and got crazy hooks ... give me a chance I guarantee we make a hit 😎👑🎙]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman Omar, she has to be deported and not be part of the USA Congress! The FBI, the Attorney General Office,… https://t.co/bgXk5CjSFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHuddlestonKY @nytimes All I can say is what about the Palisentians bad spelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes.  McCain a true hero.  Reagan a true gentleman and leader.  This coming from a Democrat.  Neither party today h… https://t.co/JBvYcdfmft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZIGWATERS How can the same be said for cardi? Nicki’s entire verse consisted of her  adding iana to the end of every bar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[60-80 million dollars in a secret settlement for Kap?!? THAT BOY IS EATIN NOW! Big ups to Colin, Eric Reid, and his… https://t.co/9BQdfLawvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to these #CalSPRA2019 individual honorees, three amazing and amazingly deserving #schoolpr leaders and fri… https://t.co/l6Wb7zM2oV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is not about what you are capable of,  it's about what you are willing to endure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fateless44 @PattyMattson @OnlyOneSylvanas @_Jesse_Carson_ @Alistrine @ChristieGolden Have toons that do. I play th… https://t.co/jxLDLSyKp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Songs Spotlight February 13, 2019 TMP's Featured Songs For February 13, 2019  Styx - Blue C… https://t.co/6cWKjHIICD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez warns of 'list' for moderate Dems who vote with Republicans: report https://t.co/3gGW0APrL7 #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo If anyone should be investigated and it jail it is Bob mueller and the enablers and participants of him]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KevinLyman: *breathes*  Every scene press outlet: WARPED TOUR FOUNDER KEVIN LYMAN IS TEASING THE RETURN OF WARPED… https://t.co/CavYyYo71k]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Dale City: light rain, 37°F 74% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1027mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is first day where the full roster of players in camp for the White Sox, meaning it's time for manager Rick R… https://t.co/SXPv8nRWAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandrasimmons @hngmskincare @MYXBlendBar Love lip balm @dandrasimmons would love to consult with @hngmskincare on lip care]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice malt forward IPA. - Drinking a Freestyle Series: Ontario IPA by @CollingwoodBeer @ City of Kingston  — https://t.co/RaeOFRiNYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyxxSense @CountDankulaTV YOU ARE TO BLAME HERE MIKE. VENTI, EXTRA CREAM, NO SUGAR. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeThePeople Got your back! @realDonaldTrump @TomFitton @JudicialWatch #WWG1WGA This is America!Mess with one of U.… https://t.co/HjOgWwfa36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for the night! (@ Lucas' House in Omaha, NE) https://t.co/SmPsDDqKQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Afelanto @clubleonfc @RodolfoCota_ @5FerNavarro @Chapomontes10 @JJMacias9 @miseleccionmx Que te valga verga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this thread!  A pitch made of the 12 slides you’re “supposed to have” often lands flat 📚  Instead, script a “m… https://t.co/zw2pyQVGc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyOCN Greetings OCN! I am a follower of yours and I am a Byzantine iconographer. Would it be alright for me to pla… https://t.co/mbb5MEL65E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnarkyPlatypus We may well disagree with what "best" means. We may extremely disagree with their methods. But they… https://t.co/TeN8EbFc84]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConwayShow u guys scared me for a second, but im taking the 18 up there from the back way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethLynch2020 WTF is this, BTW? Look at her company’s slogan. https://t.co/rC7sbjPJxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetsHaider @errollouis It remains in the economic development pot. As much as Republicans liked to compare gov't s… https://t.co/Wvq5XZ6Ixq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ascend practice canceled this evening. We will resume Sunday 2/24 11a - 1p.   Good luck to everyone up in Albany!… https://t.co/n1GfAWyrvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendofBamba @PapageorgiouMBO Bamba will be a long term project for the J Brothers. Will be at least 3 years before we see the potential]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders didn't support his gay kid, but supports other gays. WTF?  Levi Sanders, the son of Sen. Bernie Sanders… https://t.co/p4pCi5u8b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depende de la nevera, porque hay algunas aquí en USA que se conectan a Internet y esas si se pueden hackear,]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait till I’m back on the clock man. This no working shit is really getting to me. But I have to continue t… https://t.co/vZh50U4XHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quand je vais trouver la femme il yaura plus ça en vente. Perds toujours le temps]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to see a real site through a pork chop in the yard and let the ducks get at it , they will beat to cats  t… https://t.co/25I1x21FkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alli_hessel Where at? I might be able to hook you up with one if you provide the details 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames What is going on with RDR2 online? No animals spawning. Booted after 2 minutes of play. This is not a good look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onemillioncubs I think the 2007 Topps update is the Justin Verlander RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[how bout instead of cancelling classes when it snows, cancel class when the wind chill makes it below 20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help others before being helped. Do your most important task of the day first. And remember your performance is due… https://t.co/infibvMxL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pau_Mttl Bueno el detalle de la cerveza es q te relaja y sin dudar lo q lo hace es x  el alcohol,  claro q lo pued… https://t.co/E7gfanKaXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The possible Ala Fuel Tax 01 cent per gallon Increase or Decrease will be decided by the Annual report of the National Fuel Tax Index.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcestey @FlyingWithSara @AOC @afa_cwa I must have really bothered you lil buddy!  I do, and if you want to have a… https://t.co/SLOGAlXwwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annbaroco @jambie61 @People4Bernie I filed with turbo tax.  I couldn’t tell u where my paperwork is now but I did file]]></document></documents></author>