<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Brennan_and_Riz @allknowing67 Good job, friend! 👋😃👍#keepgoing! A little bit everyday. You’ll get there. I tell mys… https://t.co/gcB5TZfKDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is very scary if these crazies think a red hat can cause people to act insane🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Garbage everything here. Garbage prez, garbage followers, garbage ideology and politics. Straight… https://t.co/H6cra51S1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALISON!!! linda loves you very much!!! thank you for the mems!!!🌷🌸💗👅💖👅💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamHoshiAkari @dimash_official Yes, it does! #TWBDimash #TWBDimash #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TichinaArnold Hey Gurl drink one for me as well....I hope too see U in Virginia sometime soon.. hint..hint  Hampto… https://t.co/mlpQ5A6Gl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to @JohnBerman and Alisyn Camerota @NewDay for this fascinating conversation!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 @Raiders Don’t let the door hit ya on the way out. @steelers were too good for you. In @TeamJuJu we trust. https://t.co/wA1PbYZLNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpCrimeFamily At 72 yrs old still blame everyone else except yourself. This is why u suck! blames Cohen testimo… https://t.co/tjjZZqavvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to take this time to let everyone know, we don’t give GAP the credit it deserves and it needs to change! #ilovegap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gotten in the habit of taking three hour naps after work on Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the way ya work it  If you lay me down I can show you that I'm worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophia is so close to walking but I pray she doesn’t do it before Austin comes home 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Winter blues got your skin down🤷🏼‍♀️We are stocked with scrubs, soaks, serums, lip balms, beard oil and more from… https://t.co/zOJjZUaEae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to give props to th incredible artist who designed this cup from Starbucks Creative Studio! Her name is Nina P… https://t.co/eOTBlGGu5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Ralph_ I appreciate the support. I had to get it off my chest. I'm so worried that my dream reflected a subcons… https://t.co/AGtzj6LxXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenPenaloza @Elpanita82 Yo, siendo él,  no me comprometería tanto, a fin de cuentas, muerto no podría disfrutar de… https://t.co/Zd8QPwZk0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay not to sound obsessive but you’re bomb af Tesla. You’re HELLA nice and CUTE AS FUCK. Sis you’re glowing with p… https://t.co/pM9TAcQFTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ Why are you still tweeting? Take a trazadone and go to bed donald, the golf cour… https://t.co/2g5DCzaiAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was amazing, students that never met before were able to communicate, collaborate and be so creative!  #teamfry… https://t.co/CEEqmlE7Eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalTellAFairyTaleDay from the #Chiefs 🤗 This is so adorable you HAVE to read it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You probably should know sir, your Muslim brothers and Sisters are commanded by the Quoran and Hadith  to behead yo… https://t.co/mexoFSQDx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where else can you create the untraditional-  more than just your normal high school @ptsa_ahs @FirstAvePTSA… https://t.co/ARKQbP2Eem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chain breaker, miracle worker, light in the darkness that is who you are! You are here moving every heart! I worshi… https://t.co/iIxEWhBopX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my friend @CMSStefani - aka: Catherine Stefani, our District 2 Supervisor! I ALSO love her for investing in… https://t.co/pCiFYXLi4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCBachelorThe @chrisbharrison Can you please do a shout out to your number 1 fan my dad Donald Chant. He just pas… https://t.co/yjMFnkf9S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham I was playing a game on my phone. And ad came up asking me to go against our pres. God put him in… https://t.co/7Uu0GXA45Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxwelltani Incredible? I wouldn’t be caught standing anywhere near that hideous garbage. Is Russia/ Putin in there too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrerucker51 @NOW1SOLAR @SarahGould_SA @poppij @DudekLinda @Itridpm @delgeo1 @hey_butter @Msgargoyle13 @agavecorn… https://t.co/ubuk2kCgCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turned the sound off so you could imagine this is a @BookCameo for you, a friend, a family member or a loved one.… https://t.co/vKegw4Gg36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We supported you before and we will support you now and we will continue to support you we believe… https://t.co/KSdyzHF30C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Albert_PrinceC @GalgosRGreat @fras99 I’m a big fan your Royal Highness!  Now following!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the other night our favorite Kansas State Wildcat and former dallasmavs rolandoblackman22 💚💙💜 #MFFL @ American… https://t.co/z9L8m2qfgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when my alarm goes off at 7:30am for my class that has the notes online.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be shooting a feature for the New York Mets this morning. Work has been dead as a 500-year-old door nail,… https://t.co/g3F5sEybXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberPlaster Sleeping in the theater so it doesn't sound like the house is under attack https://t.co/TSOIgOvqQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This rhino is not taking your shit.  #wrapparty @ Avenue Los Angeles https://t.co/jkOMRdazBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you say your technically single but low key in a relationship then your not single]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you make this crap up yourself or does @FoxNews write it and pay you to say such stupid things. Dems are totally… https://t.co/qrs689dSFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peppertrumper @TempusSpiritus @QueenBee1917 @KristinKellyUSA @1PunchSena @gnfytr556 @DanielGoane @Aussie_Pride… https://t.co/hqsScqfzK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigCo62 Before and after pics life in jail house 🏠 indeed is inevitable, congrats Manafort]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow what a blast! Disneyland with my babies and of course @alllybooo_  was awesome!🐭🎆🏰🎢 thank you for inviting us t… https://t.co/NfdFG57f3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[do u know how does it best feel when someone who used to doubt you is now encouraging you to do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know what will go viral on the internet... this morning it’s VAN SNEAKERS! Have you tried this challenge… https://t.co/EfRpVuxL1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone is doing base visits today, it’s perfectly acceptable to show up in leggings and an oversized T-shirt ri… https://t.co/Y3n9lnsQe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullPup2A that is why I #StandwithPOTUS and why I love my fellow #Patriotbrothersandsisters #MAGA #WWG1WGA… https://t.co/jAZvop362a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BondageLand Looks heavy.  (Noticeable bondage by its wearers is a plus imho)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolishPatriotTM Lucky for her there are no white, black, brown or any MEN of any color in Hollywood let alone “dud… https://t.co/NCyeDcpz7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want ice cream so bad but I already have my bonnet on and I don’ have time  for the looks from  my melanin deficient neighbors 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[stay close to people who feel like sunshine. ☀️ what a weekend! quality time with this beautiful soul, great conver… https://t.co/zR0QzmI4r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @SeaveyDaniel remembers me freezing in Texas because #ColdinLA reminds me of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The a-ha moment cannot happen without the crashes!  Growth doesn’t happen in comfort zones!  Happy to learn with… https://t.co/C7ADhw8cHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 400 tickets have been pre-sold for the 5pm screening of “Eva” at @artcrafttheatre tonight! This is one theat… https://t.co/H7ZFeuCouy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Of course, Soros has been busy, hiring buses, planning televised blurbs of these poor people suppos… https://t.co/AnArabrqHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyHowdyESPN catching up on the Bachelor. Anytime the music stops for a long time on the date, I get nervous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay ! My name’s Rebecca and I’m a software engineer working on making my industry more in… https://t.co/tRBVIHvNOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG thank you @itsevieclaire Every item is fabulous. I can't wait ro use my new purse. #HollywoidMess #romancebooks… https://t.co/Fovw0eaDEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court documents show DNA processed in Maine led police to Steven Downs, the man accused of killing a college studen… https://t.co/S4uQ0sEsGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJ_Braithwaite I watched about that time too. What especially hit home for me was the song Let It Go. Lassiter’s s… https://t.co/F9isgaqfF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zip lining through Fremont Street! @ Fremont Street Experience https://t.co/QzPOr07lBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews Innocent people don’t worry you seem worried]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldymcbthndahouz @Eiggam5955 @UROCKlive1 @funder I'm sorry that your first experience was one of violence.  If you… https://t.co/ACBHMLARkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcprintz I’m so exhausted that I had to read this like 4 times to understand it. I was like “what does this have to do about kangaroos?” 😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a strong feeling that @jordynwoods just demolished the Kardashian empire. @KrisJenner is about to adopt Jord… https://t.co/k6eXW5z3bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great hike at Forest Park today! #hikingwithfriends #hikingwithdogs #bassethoundsofinstagram #petsarefamily… https://t.co/IiWfHkwI9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh you Wynne Peeps who have been asking for more TL candles.... they’re back!! With some fun new scents for spring… https://t.co/atdF7N9nyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agonyexe Me before i send the 3rd text in a row after getting left on read from my double https://t.co/Wrb7w453bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love introducing people to @nbcthegoodplace and watching episode 13 with them. The moment of pure amazement and c… https://t.co/hjmNfVm24U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never enough time with this one. Atlas ❤ #atlas #mybaby #mylove #amstaffcorso #dogcuddles #cuddlebuddy… https://t.co/pFPvxhjEw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santi Torres for Valiente Polo World Polo League at Grand Championns Polo Club #Polo #worldpololeague #wpl… https://t.co/842u5WtREh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJohnsonless Well u said u were gonna be an asshole today, nice work!! A positive asshole!! 😂😂😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pillar Communications, which has been tasked by the summit for a second year in a row to interpret speeches.  Co-fo… https://t.co/DoxqEHw9FM]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's laughter all around us. Google Image Result for https://t.co/I75HSTiKxP... https://t.co/rfKByunDxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather in NYC today got me in my spring feels 🤸🏻‍♀️☀️🧶 @ Outdoor Voices https://t.co/LOJtN6wrmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliansRum @outlawjw Im pretty tech stupid.  But if you can do all of that why not make another twitter type app a… https://t.co/Sp9BSdBJeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These days I feel like the Constitution is a beautiful death trap of a house that lots of people have lived in over… https://t.co/eJRtFNduVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[KU Fans: “Why are you so happy about a shared title, you couldn’t even win it outright smh”  Right. A shared title… https://t.co/qJm0dEKWdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyRiottWWE @RondaRousey @MsCharlotteWWE You should've left the tweet after disregarded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some kind of hybrid cake/chocolate chip cookie.. the moisture of a cake but the taste of an excellent chocolate chi… https://t.co/9mM592mi4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workout Complete 🙌🏻 Cardio Kickboxing and  Lower Body Strength Workout  @fitnessblender #fitnessblender #fitforme… https://t.co/dxqpsNdjq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is scared of thunder storms so he woke Lorenzo and me up 3 times in 15 mins by busting down the bedroom door… https://t.co/hRPdYHUVE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikethegratest @philkid3 Also I like Space Mountain because I'm not a fan of roller coasters cause of heights and… https://t.co/WbgMTZR1k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifeisgreatsut @SXMCollege @PerfectGameUSA @AmandaFreed7 @SoftbalAmerica @profastpitch @SueEnquist @NCAAsoftball… https://t.co/xpAEM5gyxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dancefestopia @RuthDawg17 I literally got lost in camping for a good 30 min on my way to ATliens set bc it was dark and super late 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[As with many things, less is more on your envelope. Keep it simple. — @RKDGroup #DCNP2019 https://t.co/aOxgXkhyjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[when the Lord says to us: ‘So if you are offering your gift at the altar, and there remember that your brother has… https://t.co/A59cWOZWQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Maverick and I talked about our favorite food.  We’re now besties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @keialadevon said you were apart of the “dripping out ministry” lol listen it be time to go!!! 😂😂😂 https://t.co/sy97sAJLvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S98Billy @IlhanMN BS you liar The kkk omar said Jews were not loyal and antisemitics like you give her a pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BernieLoveForChicago  "Those years enabled me to understand a little bit how wars got started.  And racism."  Educ… https://t.co/Yw8u7J76hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg all the chocolate is legit $2/5 at Walgreens https://t.co/HxlwpbM7IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKaylaKnapp “And think I’d be a good boss” is the real selling point here. Anyone who applies would be lucky to work with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 10:45 To Denver by Eppig Brewing at @eppigbrewing — https://t.co/rLeTGMmwoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Purisima Mission, is one of two of the man missions that is actually a state park. Beautiful and expansive groun… https://t.co/9whfbYvxL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an incredible day meeting with Arkansas legislators and organizers who want to bring the #firststepact to their… https://t.co/gjIQnbsejM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran into someone in the hall way and they said “wow freshman” not gonna lie, imma little hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashSevereWx Rural and urban. Belmont ave. near Lipscomb is out of power, could Barely see, almost pitch black, lo… https://t.co/ZUNZaV8llm]]></document><document><![CDATA[He gives his full attention ..always felt he listened and gave feedback..In my some 63yrs in the workforce...I have… https://t.co/xJMAkuHJQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelBearsDiva This is what I do for fun in my spare time...sit in classrooms and pretend to sub 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We haven’t seen snow in a long time. Grandbaby #8 is on its way today. Girl or boy? @ Port Chester, New York https://t.co/eIZ8gSld2j]]></document></documents></author>