<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @USAID Liar! Your dad did give Jared his clearance! Why lie? Oh oh never mind 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Microsoft and #Facebook’s record-setting #undersea #cable sets another record   https://t.co/UZYA5euZHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seriesofdreams4 @UncleAL_2012 @RagingBabe I can see him being can now for sure. Funny thing is I believe somebody may pull his string.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I ask for a dj @BeyondWland is to mix in All Star by Smash Mouth into their set pls 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 2018 study from @pearson found that #GenZ students eschewed physical books, preferring video as a source of infor… https://t.co/cBNsHwbfCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[In recognition of your last home game, thanks for an unforgettable first season at TBA. Now get us that natty… https://t.co/MdDHtAec6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie is annoying to me... she ain’t wife material either in my opinion #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @yourmumspants @ellen5e @dadbaddy @zapher134 @PolyRhuagh @1CubbieKat1 @NickSoutter @Cern_lXXl… https://t.co/9jlx2UTIGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Feinstein didnt act like an ass. She was completely respectful, the people who visited her were being disre… https://t.co/oGvhus4inJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Investors Should Run From Stock ETFs Into Individual Municipal Bonds https://t.co/FVH1KpFIQ4 https://t.co/qHX0Be6eTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search marketing company Botify raises $20M https://t.co/hFaXg6Zl8U #startup]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not secretly important; it's no secret that I'm probably not important. If I was, it must be in a context of a… https://t.co/nKSJTUrPfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Word #Amen @realDonaldTrump  why so quiet? Trumpy Bear ? 😜😂 #DomesticTerrorism  a true emergency #ScaredWhiteMen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notdochawkTU The research is going well. This weather though makes me wish it was summer, so I could complain about the heat. #dhtu19]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to work, I’ll wake up any minute now this is just a bad dream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I gain in experience, I do not think more of myself but less of others.  —Gen. George S. Patton Jr. https://t.co/fViMGXFUTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cle_ItIsGone Sky line chili @Reds Great American Ballpark in Cincinnati Ohio    The best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tellesmith @IPrevailBand @Bri_Prevail @eric_prevail Workaholics 🔥🔥🔥 oh and also your thing is pretty cool too]]></document><document><![CDATA[#unionsquare #greenmarket @ Union Square Greenmarket https://t.co/5JGY1VhBGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[this actually goes to show when a man has a lot of money, it’s easier for him to spoil her]]></document><document><![CDATA[let this 3 day weekend begin probably going to involve shoveling snow though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @CR6Trojans Lady Trojans for representing the CAC conference in the Class 1 Final 4. Good luck next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @Cernovich I agree. No student loans without swearing allegiance to the flag and vows of free speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding space for professionals to do their craft is incredibly rewarding. When I found a spot for Byrd Williams IV… https://t.co/jeCdpmytI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I don’t have alerts on for the ol Alt country mailing list. #pcfh https://t.co/xQbiJvBEpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have to say @NeNeLeakes attitude with the new girl is #disappointing #RHOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@engadget You mean they found a better way of doing it without getting caught...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tolkienesque ideas on a Hobbit-sized budget: Meet emerging Memphis fantasy filmmaker Rachel M. Taylor:… https://t.co/JBO9ZCLTja]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the ingredients are there for some strong tornados in northern Mississippi and southwest Tennessee today. If yo… https://t.co/qIXO5l7pgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[what really throws me on The Bachelor is girls complain about not getting enough time w Colton, but when they do ge… https://t.co/fRFJCRdWnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaime singing The National Anthem at Fight The Freeze Martial Arts Tournament. https://t.co/ZJFMjVvPJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[CROSSMARK is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #EventsMarketing job openings, including "ENGAGEMENT SP… https://t.co/4rmVSR2lsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my big sister samanthawinner72 🥳🎂xx @ Houston Zoo https://t.co/f1VX4OzwSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE NOT JUST A GYM!! https://t.co/ASrf9o5gb9 #strongtogetherchelsea #countryspiritcrossfit #crossfit #fitness… https://t.co/tZY7YC1JE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @dlfriedlander This bible signing is the height of insanity. How can any person who claims to be a god… https://t.co/bwBqPxr8y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jan_doig Policing should never be privatized.  Making a profit incentive on prisoners leads to more prisoners.  We… https://t.co/PnvJPh2rXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women use being “strong willed” as an excuse for never taking accountability for being selfish, inconsiderate, and… https://t.co/YNDWafzgYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristianHarloff @moviesandmurder @BeckyLynchWWE @SashaBanksWWE @RondaRousey @MsCharlotteWWE Don’t sleep on… https://t.co/XXfD41PwhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe wants me to join in hell for a beer later much later @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/J1wIYiuLoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachcolwell1 @Coach_Timmerman @CoachShiffman OLine performance has tons of stuff on you tube and a subscription b… https://t.co/zY3xzmvbYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball season is coming! @IronPigs @BRC13Sports #BRC13Sports https://t.co/auNG942rk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulSaxMD @doc_in_a_box If you don’t mention the pay, glamour, and beautiful people, I don’t know what you’ll mention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You start dating a man he has no car but he works long hours and he’s saving that’s working toward getting better.… https://t.co/x0JCGDwJSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine hearing “the president’s profane language” in any administration before this one]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing brings me quite as much joy as drinking (at least one bottle of) wine and cleaning my apartment while the i… https://t.co/RhHaxJwsRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty. … https://t.co/7d1tMwjzu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traecrowder Many Americans especially youngins' are just not gonna hold their nose and vote for a pro-war industry… https://t.co/ASaIzdN1ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrHarrison Pope Francis preached on that today. https://t.co/Dg8ncAtjoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @ATT Fuck you! So I follow you, and got to hear your stupid ass rant! I'll fucking quit your service, scamming ass phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve NEVER seen THIS many #seagulls at one time in #ColumbiaSouthCarolina !!! Is this some kind of sign??? 😮😮😮 It w… https://t.co/Isjuc4FJDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Girls Basketball Team on an amazing Season. Tough loss tonight in the OHSAA Division IV Regi… https://t.co/6IPZRFtBXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classroom full of learning by building Rube Goldberg Machines!#stem students learning to collaborate in building a… https://t.co/Ltrz9HtRRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[my reaction to half y’all mothaaafuckas out there https://t.co/UQZWHLnE8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @rockyhillschool girls varsity #basketball #SENEISAA All-League selections! . 2019 GVBB SENE ALL-LEAGUE… https://t.co/uxMikxVts2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biephiephus @balcom_holly @J_M_Roth @dillonliam @nathanfletcher What issue? You’re strawman? I don’t drive hybrids… https://t.co/Pgx6HQwU5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magic Johnson and Rob Pelinka making personnel decisions https://t.co/JwMgowWmIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prefiero callar y sonreír, xk si hablo, acabare llorando. Y a pasear 🚶 se a dicho, besitos de marrano 🐖 ups sin pal… https://t.co/F8LGV6HWFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were a gravedigger I would know when to stop because the top of my head would be even with the sod.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trcfwtt @RealMuckmaker She has no originality, just like phony Melania...ugghhh...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVG will y’all be at the center of the racing world with live on site coverage next Saturday, instead of dedicatin… https://t.co/DGZL1lCpqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the face I make when I’m not cleaning at 1/6! Lol https://t.co/CPlee7WRpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lambda school’s coverage of the backend so far is by far the best compared to anything I see online. Didn’t think I… https://t.co/1H6eWRFq6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!  Coming up on @FoxBusinessAM with @cherylcasone to talk about $AMZN not moving to NYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell I'm sorry but how dumb are you? Congress is a separate branch of government from the executive branch… https://t.co/sBC7OLDzl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBApple @Bravewriting @coleyworld You don’t think Clinton was strengthened by the failed impeachment attempt?  You… https://t.co/4NtPDmPbAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[*belting*  🎶This career is not a competition🎶   Thank you. Caleb Michael number 178.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheCockLove @lithium66 @NaponapVideos @M6969Xx @masinofan1 @ilovetransbabes @pradiphsbc @CXMDRUNK @Shemalesbr… https://t.co/zFHM4tPIDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people tend to make things ab themselves A LOT. When in reality it has nothin to do with them 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBMCPA I can’t even wrap my mind around this one. I’ve watched it a couple dozen times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad a wall was built across the southern border and caught this.  Oh, wait....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump What 25 billion, for the wall? Nope. What 10 billion for a wall? Nope. What about 1.8 bil… https://t.co/pBmQm4sBT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A casual picture of one of the most powerful names in diversity and inclusion. @Atlassian is lucky to have… https://t.co/vDHTysMDpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsemezing Ah, tenho que tomar antiácido e deitar com a cabeça meio elevada quando dá essas crises]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeMensbball_ @BlueDevilNation Despite all of the Obama is a UNC fan hot takes, seems a good time to remind the w… https://t.co/xPeKVqBqle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to be clear. On tonight’s big brother finale, control of the house came down to the question.. how many hours… https://t.co/52ejcwWjP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just so funny to me because I remember when @_ClutchCarter was getting rim stuffed at downtown Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, open our hearts to the treasures of nature, and lead us to contemplate and reverence the earth and all that… https://t.co/gzo5vn9a5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Saturday February 23 , 2019 , items to keep an eye for today include : Opposition pushes to deliver humanitaria… https://t.co/h7CpxGV2fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unofficial top 10: Self, Gibbs, Eckes, Smith, Heim, Holmes, Okrzesik, Lessard, Honeycutt &amp; Braden #ARCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulliedinHS I didn't until earlier  I had a script in tempermonkey that got rid of them but apparently it broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one point, Block Buster was apparently opening a new store every 17 hours. So, they didn’t see any reason to buy… https://t.co/HLSMXYO5gX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones I hope you're still up for producing his album. #whitedonte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popdust Going full Carnivor will cure your Soda addiction also and your sugar and Carb also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei And 1 more thing... Ever notice how conservative philosophy (for the most part) doesn’t impinge on any… https://t.co/T1wZ2BNr7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSDesMoines -14 and freezing fog with visibility less than 100 yards at Ledyard, IA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 No. We need to count non-citizens to get handle on size and demographics. Just need them to NOT hide… https://t.co/cekXTnnD03]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was as blond as Brie Larson. Her hair looks especially great tonight. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg   Rare 'mega-storm' could flood dozens of cities in California, reports say  https://t.co/mEsbN4HLCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aiVYhfmBle Johns Hopkins teacher  made numerous trips 4 research African sleeping sickness  BY JACQUES… https://t.co/2r5cCV08BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gustafson_coach @jpbt1_ @bambam12rivera @BeGreatAntt @reecegus @smithelize1 @Bstreet908 Congrats to you Reece and the whole team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHart4real lmao right it would be like if someone turned down a job like hosting the Oscars because they were… https://t.co/pqylmK6RVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeM_Feldman @Gail_G_Scott @DBHIDS I’ve not seen requirements to have both an agonist and antagonist (or all 3… https://t.co/pfpN5Vxv2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maduro_en Meanwhile, during the #carnivals in #venezuela https://t.co/FEIoPPUCxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wendys I’m tired and sick at work. Please bless me with your food and give me strength to finish my shift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedWeZag @CondorianFM @Simmotre1Trent @NGDavenport4 Is slot em in between Pepperdine and Santa Clara this year.… https://t.co/gla2ARBd8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joseph4Meg @sjianna @BarusArus @FBI I was surprised about Netenyahu. Couldn’t believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JUPITER2010 @melrodriguez680 @husi076 Perdón, llevo años viviendo en Norteamérica y acá no es asi! Acá los derecho… https://t.co/7VPTuZZSBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spence1013 @ProFootballTalk Yet somehow the Braves attendance exceeded the Phillies. That has to be embarrassing]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with this approach is that it does not differentiate between consensual sex work and human trafficking/… https://t.co/BSan0zTTaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Go get the orange bastard, Ted!  #presidentMF]]></document></documents></author>