<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@colton @hornets Colton I’ll be the one outside the arena with a sign that says “#Fence” and “We want answers” on the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trom771 @pleasure74 I am terrified I am never waking up from this nightmare]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever felt sick and then when you wake up you feel 1000x better?  Well this is the opposite of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lomadia Take it easy and here’s to hoping the sniffles only stay for a day 🤞 https://t.co/iitOcAAEoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay  #Austinstrong  #Tugglenation  #BankOnIt https://t.co/6XsJaIcYu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if I will ever stop crying while watching American idol auditions]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Whoah looks like we made it, we’re Kids Incorporated!” I legit just sang this entire song from memory thank you fo… https://t.co/hRBDjEWPfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Westword's 'Artopia 2019' celebrates decades of hip hop culture!  #denverlifestyle #thingstodoindenver #hiphop… https://t.co/IthnNJPvKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJHeadtoHead @nytimes @mehdirhasan However I hope I never have reason to be on your show; I doubt I--or anyone els… https://t.co/CemDOfbGj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just recorded episode 3 and I think we’re actually getting the hang of this?? People are fucking listening to us WHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: when shambles be the next song in my music. @themodelyouth @AdamLusk11 @hiddenbynature @ThomerConnerson https://t.co/qWkGiRguYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Like to see someone doing their own research.  Sickening isn't it??]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really hard to articulate the rage I feel on behalf of @IlhanMN. She is a fierce leader and they have been com… https://t.co/6LD4W2PbZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do love good beanie weather, but can it be warm now? 🌸☀️ @ Oklahoma City, Oklahoma https://t.co/wJAFwMGhj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 40 straight of my #rigside #mealselections here on my drilling rig, which I'm happy to say will be the last for… https://t.co/aaJFyahxG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a friend that will do nothing while watching parks &amp; rec with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[After knocking on doors in #ScarboroughAgincourt tonight, I attended the #TeamTrudeau Climate Action rally:… https://t.co/kTzTn6vIaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsAlsheimer @mr_Alsheimer Love seeing other educators being the gifts they are to our Ss🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deolebear I embrace the life I’ve been given and do my best with what I’ve got. And when I take the time to count… https://t.co/QK8zSL6Svp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Northeast Washington, Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/Hkd3eMFqeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Openwave offers first-class services for #ECommerce Website Development in New York! Connect with us to design, cus… https://t.co/vDet9tDrJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@AssnDeptsFamMed⁩ #ADFM19 Winter Conference Day 1 highlights #SocialJustice #RacismInMedicine… https://t.co/pmTpwKvTfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Augmania_ @ArlanWasHere @Backstage_Cap @emilychangtv @StartupGrind Everyone has a story, and everyone’s story matters. #truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Maxine Waters you need to talk to the Border patrol agents. Also you need to be in contact with al… https://t.co/bAnP9TiFhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[my cousin paired me up with her friend for carpool ... this bish driving high https://t.co/Qs2pozuw0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#damnright #sowhatsitgonnabe #italldependsonyou #rocknrollgoddess #angelaleeburnett #angelalee @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/E297oAU7zA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbieTHarris Absolutely and I am a die hard steeler fan and was a AB Fan the cover cursed him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouldDaFkOut @Fourens_ @lexuchiha That's what I've been saying this whole time lol. The plant itself isn't bad. Bu… https://t.co/ggW1iaVQEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I went to the kimball side all you can hear Guss saying “quien quiere a mi prima” LMAOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLogan2020 @TBBprivate @GiselleMarks1 @vicky_whedbee @drwilliams7777 @BernadetteHill0 @jaywils25315547 Same Da… https://t.co/sI358dKclB]]></document><document><![CDATA[How might we build an equitable culture where more students are empowered to access STEM opportunities? #T3IC  @TICalculators]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been having dreams about solange and I haven’t even listened to the new album.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGT Is every act supposed to make me sob? It's difficult to drink my coffee while soaking up all this joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast seeing the  #DWTSTour at  @wagnernoel_pac tonight.  I just love me some @JennaJohnson @EmmaSlaterDance… https://t.co/xzHtHkVAl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando tu hombre lleva ignorándote toda la noche pero luego te sorprende 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudeYork @1077TheEnd Could’ve sworn that was the one too. You guys have a super distinctive sound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer I mean the next thing you know they’ll be working with the Russians to steal an election.  So very ins… https://t.co/VZMA6xiOuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_manne Just the fact that the personalities of candidates are only a widely discussed issue when the candidate… https://t.co/Ti5vxQVAlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAnnWagner That, of course, does not include the current WH occupant. #corrupt #mendacious #unfit #amoral #lazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here comes the sun dodododoo here comes the sun...… https://t.co/SRcTGBXvU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn't care less what Tucker Carlson said over a decade ago &amp; neither should you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzkhalil Thank you,never heard of it and spent many years in cardiac everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quasibee Somewhat related: I was just reading Cressida J. Heyes's "Feminist Solidarity after Queer Theory: The Cas… https://t.co/a7a5vBtNSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minnlion Check out Trump's signature on the $35,000 check made out to Cohen. It looks like it reads dummy. Check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at old pictures has got me in my feels rn 🥺 like, can I just go back to my first day of college when I didn… https://t.co/thS2qgvJb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my big brother 💔 Free my mf niggga out them cells , Amor de cAsKKo y toda la vida ✡️💙✡️💙✡️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past is gone .. it went by like dusk to dawn  Isn’t that the way  Everybody’s got their dues in life to pay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland What's the difference between this Phallic Shaped Object and... https://t.co/HfxgWBxl5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the #BookCoverChallenge from @educating4tmrw  to post 1 cover per day for 1 week. No explanation, no rev… https://t.co/TWvlaplfQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Nature is using all of her colors today. #bitch #wintersucks #enoughalready https://t.co/9OOwdWDTI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next person to cut me off and almost make me wreck is getting their tires slashed IN TRAFFIC... not my fault y’all… https://t.co/NUqfivEBXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would have been DC's #BirdsOfPrey but it sounds like they're already doing a great job with it!… https://t.co/qxWMOSeOod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #IT job in #Mooresville, NC? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Senior… https://t.co/6ogW5LtIiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashrog14 Mine will be at @LambeauField ! My hubs @dtpayton and I want to be tag team tour guides! #GoPackGo @packers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HikindDov @AndrewPollackFL @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN About Time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her pink lipstick in this movie is really pretty and I WANT IT. #ElyssaWatchesFSOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re laughing now but you won’t be laughing when your wife gets stuck on the other side of your bitchass wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoJor18 Good Evening Alberto Hugs follow me again unless you always have followed me Alberto Hugs https://t.co/fLNjPbrkjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[pen to paper man...that shit is a lost art   put your phone away &amp; write that shit down ✍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kt_flexing Ur mom is basically 20 years older than me. Actually dy yee lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had this earlier this week and can’t wait to go back. #eatatbento #asianfood #yummy @ BENTO asian kitchen + sushi https://t.co/MvJyvbzY1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[München und Hamburg in Texas  ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/qtDJW6myQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep a pair of scissors with me at all times Incase I need to cut mfs off]]></document><document><![CDATA[These boots are made for hiking #GrandCanyon #USA #outdoors @ Grand Canyon National Park https://t.co/d6wLLCeZuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve known @Newsies was coming off of @netflix for awhile now but didn’t believe it until I woke up this morning an… https://t.co/g74Sp8BCBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your SuRpRiSe visits always make my day @thedruejackson 🤗.  #proudofthisone https://t.co/JKEJABCFJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The server at Taco Bell gave me his number on the back of a receipt, his home phone number! after zero interaction!… https://t.co/e9MrHmtLpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks heatherhairetic for your haircut magic today! #sideeye #bettiebangs #waves #hairdid @ Hairetics Salon https://t.co/xzAFc1PEC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really so upset about my doctor who DVD. Money down the drain and I cant even cheer myself up with a  new season of doctor who]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t plastic straws and other small plastic items be recycled? Also what can and can’t be recycled in San Anto… https://t.co/9EScBg1pVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a pretty good morning now let’s just hope i don’t fail my test 🙂🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[The preschool students in the classroom of Julie Powers @NorthParkKids explore many opportunities daily to practice… https://t.co/eVEyTmRGDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes, Sir the American people are very smart! They can see through the Democrats true agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakaway71 and I have made it! #LetsGoPens #StadiumSeries https://t.co/TmvTxhpWuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned how to pen flip when I did speech and debate in high school. Some people always seem impressed by that. O… https://t.co/eWpv2GtumW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to put banda on my work playlist But I know these ungrateful ass, musty ass, no-common-sense-having little s… https://t.co/6uczBO8bQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @PeterMoylan on your enviable career.  Have a great retirement but know that there are many true… https://t.co/SQsme4vRWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethan is such an angel. Over here poppin my pimples and not even being grossed out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaiGurira @TheAcademy @BROCKCOLLECTION @LeightonJewels @Winston_Duke @michaelb4jordan @letitiawright… https://t.co/4ZDzoCZOdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walt’s all, “Let’s do dinner tonight,” and honestly, all I want to do is order Thai food and go to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apgb126 Luckily I’ll get my money back in time for our Disney trip so it just forces me to save 🤣 gotta find the s… https://t.co/s4Z9xTxkhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JharoshRoshan @johnddias @vRealizeOps You need to ask Cisco R&amp;D or @bluemedora for that 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllyLynn12 @karleeseevers @rylie_unzicker  Good Luck in ft Collins  this W/E Thu vs @IdahoStateSB  Fri vs… https://t.co/5TgEWqhHbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hadn’t been on fb in a while and the first thing I saw when I reactivated my account was the fact that an old fri… https://t.co/7kB1q7dAxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m genuinely curious to know if one direction fans at the time knew this wasn’t their song or not]]></document><document><![CDATA[best compliment in the world is telling me that my handwriting looks like a teachers handwriting. i’m really trying to get that skill down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @hurlburt_alex All I can think about are those pinky toes are too close! 😩 but fr he is a special type of human. 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely do not understand how so many millennials are bad at @instagram, but it keeps me employed, so thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York Post : Trump rages against 'SNL' after latest Alec Baldwin skit. https://t.co/eUDAk8roGj  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChartingHockey I will.. i am an old person trying to learn new tricks.. ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He's always "playing a role".  Today he is the mighty liberator of Venezuela -  while he threatens… https://t.co/9myc1w8B0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[My upstairs neighbors are having relationship problems and only choose to fight VERY LOUDLY at night when I’m tryin… https://t.co/EL3z0yoLTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your cuz is really more like a sis. Thanks for always being there for me. @SMSanders06 https://t.co/Ga4Z8mjdV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are y’all gonna stop only pointing the finger at the other woman when what you need to do is check your own man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are Brad Pitt and Jennifer Aniston working on getting back together? #BradPitt stop dating celebrities. Jennifer? C… https://t.co/uivyuhyLjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mel_Edwards80 I’m so sorry. My heart breaks for that little girl (you) that had so much ugliness at such a young age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok can we just talk about this?! Cannot wait to see @nealbrennan in Minneapolis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveb2030 Beautiful! Your run looks a little different than mine.. 81 and sunny down here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balance for a Better future. To all my sisters, Happy International Womens Day #InternationalWomensday… https://t.co/KBWLXQSMlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Audrey’s sent me videos from a year ago of me crying over my breakup.... they are honestly hilarious 😂 not funny at the time tho of course 🤣]]></document></documents></author>